[THEME SONG PLAYING]
-[GAME CONTROLLER CLICKING]
-[TV CHATTER]
-[THUDDING]
-[GROANING]
-["HELPLESS" PLAYING]
-[WHEEZING]
PERRY: Get up.
[GRUNTS]
Celeste, you're fine.
Oh…
Hey.
Uh…
[GASPS]
Hey.
-You just got the wind knocked out of you.
-MAX: Mom, we gotta go.
[CRYING]
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Mom isn't feeling well today, so
I'm gonna take you guys to school.
What's wrong with her?
Her tummy's a little upset. She's okay.
But that means that the monster
will take you to school instead!
I'll be right down, guys.
["HELPLESS" CONTINUES]
[GROANING]
[WHIMPERS]
[GASPS]
I'm sorry, Sparkles.
-[CELESTE SOBBING]
-[SEAGULLS SCREECHING]
The only mystery to me is,
why all the damn questions?
I mean, you know who
did it, for God's sake.
Chloe! There's a zero tolerance
policy on tardiness, young lady! Let's go!
-CHLOE: Coming, woman!
-Get your butt over here.
ED: Well, she has still yet to
launch it, that's a good sign.
Abigail? There's no sign of a
launch on her Facebook page.
So, you're Facebook-stalking her after
you got up on your Clydesdale about it?
What exactly did you say to her, anyway?
Common sense, I said, "Live
right or go straight to hell."
-Are you having your period?
-Get in the car.
ED: Are you?
-Are you trying to be funny?
-I'm trying to be serious.
-What is going on with you?
-I have to get her to school.
[DOOR SLAMS]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
JOSEPH: Are you sure it was Tori?
Does she drive a gray Saturn?
She was just driving slowly by your house?
Clearly, she knows about us, Joseph.
First of all, she flat-out accuses me.
-And now she's going all Glenn Close.
-She suspects. She doesn't know.
I did a good job of denying it.
Not that my capacity for denial
would be a fraction of yours.
You know, I'm busy.
[SCOFFS]
-The thing about you, Madeline, is that…
-"The thing about…"
Let me finish!
Central to your core,
is your grossly, if not
artificially inflated,
sense of moral integrity.
For you to be fucking me for three
months like a mad hyena in heat…
-How dare you speak to me like that!
-…could only mean that, yes,
not only were you in love with
me, you had the best sex of your life!
You've gone so far in
the direction of wrong.
Oh, yeah? Then why are you here?
You could've called me.
Are you going to fuck me again?
Let's do it. There's no one in the
building. On the couch.
Come on. Me and you.
You think you own this town because you
have money? You self-entitled rich bitch.
Just get the fuck out of my office!
See you at the party tonight!
[CELESTE SIGHS]
[CELESTE GROANS]
Tsk. Oh, God.
Don't touch me, please, just…
[SIGHS, SNIFFLES]
I got the apartment.
Are you in it?
[EXHALES]
Is the refrigerator stocked?
Are you gonna leave him?
[SIGHS]
-He's going away in the morning, so…
-Okay.
We just have to go to this
school gala tonight, and then…
Oh, Jesus.
[SIGHS]
It's one thing should he kill you,
but God forbid you miss a party.
You know, your husband
is ill, Celeste, but so are you.
There are children in the house.
I told you, he will not hurt the children!
He will never hurt the children!
God!
It's all right. I'm fine.
[SIGHS]
JANE: Yeah, I sent
the invoice 12 days ago.
Great, I appreciate it.
Thank you so much. Bye.
[CLEARS THROAT]
[THERMOMETER BEEPING]
How's it looking?
Ninety-eight point six.
It doesn't get more normal than that.
All right, buddy. Tell me what's going on.
[TV TURNS OFF]
You've had two bowls of cereal.
You're watching cartoons.
You don't have a fever.
Do you actually feel sick or do
you just not want to go to school?
-I feel sick.
-You don't sound congested.
I have aches.
Is it possible your
heart aches, because the
other kids were told not to play with you?
Because I would certainly understand that.
ZIGGY: Friends play with me.
Josh. Chloe. Skye. Amabella.
Amabella Klein plays with you?
Yeah. We're friends.
She likes Star Wars, too.
-It's not me who hurts her.
-I know, baby.
Do you know who is hurting her?
Who is it?
I don't like to talk about it.
Well, you don't have a choice.
You have to talk about it.
Tell me who it is.
I promised.
Look, sometimes it is important to
keep promises, but other times, it's…
-No, I promised!
-Who did you promise?
I promised Amabella.
You've known all of this time and
you've just been taking the blame?
-I only just found out.
-Who is it?
She said if I told, she
might get killed dead.
She…
[SCOFFS]
Okay. You promised her you
wouldn't say anything, right?
But you can still point. Right?
You point and show me who it is
and I promise you Amabella
will not get killed dead.
Who is it?
Ziggy, look at me.
Amabella's been a really
good friend to you, right?
Yeah.
It's our turn to be a good friend to her.
It's not fair that she keeps getting hurt.
We have to protect her. Right?
Ziggy! Point to who it is.
MADELINE: Really?
-I don't know what to do.
-Well, you have to tell Celeste.
She's going to want to
hear it directly from you.
Honesty is always the best policy.
That's what I…
I mean, I knew the boys roughhouse a lot,
-but I didn't know they were bullies.
-JANE: It was only Max.
-Hey.
-JANE: Ziggy was very clear about that.
MADELINE: Are you so relieved about Ziggy?
JANE: Yeah.
Hi, sorry, to interrupt.
-Hi, Madeline. Jane, Gordon Klein.
-Yeah.
Renata's husband.
We met at the school the other day…
-Yeah, of course.
-Listen. I'm wondering
if we might have a private
conversation, just for a second.
-Sure.
-Yeah?
Well, I'm feeling a little excluded.
-We're in the middle of a conversation.
-Okay. Actually…
No, that's good. You need to hear this,
since the two of you seem to
be making quite the little team.
[GRUNTS]
Look, Jane, whether or not Ziggy is
the one who's been hurting Amabella…
-JANE: Actually, there's…
-…you're the one who attacked my wife.
Now please understand
that if you ever go near Renata again,
I'll be taking a restraining order out.
TOM: All right. All right, Gordon.
That's enough.
Understand that?
I'm going to have to ask you to leave now.
Tom, Tom, we're just talking here.
-No. No.
-It's fine.
Everything's not fine. I can't have
you in here harassing my customers.
-[LAUGHS]
-Now I'm asking you politely, please.
-I don't think you have the right…
-Please go.
I don't think you have the right
to remove me from the premises.
I'm not interested in your legal advice.
Just go, Gordon.
[LAUGHS]
Just remember what I said, okay?
Mm-hmm.
-Okay?
-Yes.
Madeline.
Look, I'm sure I'll see you some
other time. Just not today. Okay?
You just lost yourself a
lot of customers, my friend.
[SEAGULL SCREECHING]
[EXHALES]
-Unbelievable.
-I'm so sorry.
-That was really impressive.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
-You're a real prince, Tom.
I would've told him to go fuck himself.
-[JANE LAUGHS]
-But I don't talk like that.
All right, I'm off to transform myself
into My Fair Lady. Call Celeste, okay?
-I will.
-Bye, Tom.
-Thank you.
-TOM: Bye.
You know, I've actually
been trying to figure
out a way to impress you for a while now.
I just haven't had my chance.
You're straight?
What?
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
How was your day, baby-cakes?
Well, TGIF.
[WHISTLE TRILLS]
Ugh, you're telling me. I was either
starting fights today or joining in.
NATHAN: Hey, Maddie.
Hey!
Are you ready for Trivia Night tonight?
You're coming, I presume.
Yeah, I'll be the one
dressed as Audrey Hepburn.
[CHUCKLES] That's funny.
Listen, um, Bonnie and I
went to see a counselor today,
one that specializes in teenagers.
-So, I just wanted to share some of it…
-Wait a second.
-You went to see a counselor?
-Yeah.
He thinks that this is a kind
of, um, scream for attention.
Divorce, yeah. Messes kids up pretty good.
Oh, so, splitting up can
negatively affect the kids?
I wish I'd known that before I walked out.
Wait, did I?
Why do you gotta turn
everything into a fucking fight?
[SIGHS]
You know what, Nathan, I'm glad you're
taking this parenting thing seriously.
I really am.
You know, despite all
of our shit, I root for you.
I appreciate that.
Oh, uh…
Just so you know, Bonnie's going to
be singing tonight at the talent thingy.
Maddie, she's good.
She's like, really good.
CHLOE: Good to know.
Knowing what I know now,
I'm surprised there wasn't
more carnage on Trivia Night.
One dead, we definitely got off light.
[SEAGULLS SCREECHING]
[SIGHS]
[INAUDIBLE]
[SOBBING]
[PHONE CHIMING]
Oh.
Hello?
-JANE: Hey.
-Hi.
Thank you for meeting me.
What is it?
Ziggy…
Ziggy told me this morning…
…that apparently it was Max who
choked Amabella at orientation,
and apparently it's been him
who's been bullying her all along.
-What?
-Yeah.
Amabella told Ziggy, but
made him promise not to tell
because Max threatened
to hurt her more if it got out,
so, he's just been keeping this secret.
You're sure about this?
I mean, I definitely considered that
he could be lying just to protect himself.
And I have to face the fact that violence
could be in his DNA, given who his dad is.
I think he's telling the truth.
He said also that Max
pushed Skye down the stairs,
um,
and that he's been a little
aggressive towards her as well.
[SIGHS]
I'm so sorry, Celeste, to tell you this.
They're kids, though, you know.
They bully. It's human nature.
They grow out of it.
Sometimes they don't.
[WHIMPER ECHOES]
[CELESTE GRUNTS]
[FAINT SINGING]
-Kelly, can I just have a moment, please?
-Yeah, of course.
Max.
Come here.
What?
[JOSH HUMMING]
You need to tell me what
you've been doing at school.
You're not going to get in trouble,
but you got to tell me the truth.
Do you understand?
[EXHALES]
[WHISPERS] We all do bad things sometimes.
All right?
I can help you with that, but
you need to tell me. [SNIFFLES]
It's all right, baby. It's all right.
[CRYING]
And then he said, "I'll see you
tonight," which sounded like a threat.
I seriously doubt he's
going to blow up his life.
Why do you want to blow up yours?
I wish I knew the answer to that.
I can't really make sense of it.
I think maybe…
…sometimes I'm just holding
onto this idea of perfection so tight…
…that something has to give.
And I can't explain it.
And I won't excuse it.
I've been wanting to tell Ed for so long.
I just haven't found the courage…
…yet.
I decided not to go through with it.
My project.
Oh, thank God.
[SIGHS]
It was pointed out to me, not by Bonnie,
that whatever attention
I bring to the cause
will be buried under the
controversy of my methodology,
so I'm going to find another way.
Maybe I never really wanted to do it.
Maybe it was more of a publicity
stunt, you know, to raise awareness.
And to piss off your mom.
Don't start.
I really wish you hadn't
confronted them like that.
I'm not just going to just
stand around and do nothing.
Oh, great.
I'm the one that's getting vilified.
Why would you be the one to get vilified?
Because I'm a working mom. I've told you.
Worse, a CEO, which deems me a bitch.
You have no idea.
If I get shot in the head tonight,
half these moms are going to say,
"She couldn't bother herself to duck?
What?
"What, she couldn't get the
nanny to stop the bullet?" Trust me.
These women, especially
Madeline, they're vicious.
Let's blow this off tonight.
I'm serious. Let's…
Let's just… Let's not go.
Then we're demonized for
blowing off a fundraiser? No.
What, the rich people?
They spend their money,
but they don't have the wherewithal
to even show up and invest their time?
That's not going to work.
Sorry. Sorry. No.
I hate everybody right now.
Except Jane, believe it or not.
How funny is that?
Go get ready, Elvis.
This feels very dangerous.
[CHUCKLES]
We're already late for
the party, and you have
the temerity to stand
in the shower like this.
Do we really have to be on time?
I'm sorry to say we do.
Well, I'm not going to budge.
Not until you at least give me a kiss.
[GASPS]
You look really pretty.
Thank you.
You really do!
Thanks.
I don't know how I'm gonna
survive in these heels all night.
Well, you look exactly
like Audrey Hepburn.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
-ZIGGY: Ooh, your date!
-Shh!
-Hey.
-Wow! You look incredible.
Thank you. You look great, too.
Uh, I don't really do costumes.
I don't normally either, but
Madeline roped me into it.
Mm-hmm. I rode my bike here
and got us an Uber. Can I leave this?
Of course.
-Hi.
-TOM: Hi, Ziggy.
JANE: I'll be seeing
you in a few hours, okay?
ZIGGY: Okay.
-Thanks again!
-LYDIA: No problem. Good night.
-[CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING]
-[CHATTER]
["IT'S NOW OR NEVER" PLAYING]
ED: Wow!
Thank you.
♪ It's now or never… ♪
-Ready?
-Yeah.
There they are, the Mackenzies,
looking great as always.
-Ed, good to see you.
-Good to see you.
Hey, don't forget to get
in on that raffle this year.
-Yes.
-Please…
Audrey Hepburn meets Eartha Kitt.
I love it.
Doesn't she look great?
You better keep a close
eye on her tonight, Ed.
That dress was inappropriate
and desperate, if you ask me.
I intend to. I intend to.
[LAUGHING] He always does. Oh, excuse me.
-Hey.
-Hi, Joseph. Hi, Tori.
-Hi.
-You look great.
Thank you.
Should we head up?
My heart was captured
My soul surrendered…
NIPPAL: Oh, look at this guy.
A little Jailhouse Rock.
Give me a break.
Yeah. It's going to be wonderful.
-Oh, there she is. Hey.
-Hi…
Stop staring!
NIPPAL: Enjoy the party. Buy
some raffle tickets, please. Thank you.
It's now or never
Come hold me tight
Kiss me, my darling
Be mine tonight
Tomorrow
Will be too late
It's now or never
My love won't wait…
Wow.
You look so beautiful.
Thank you.
[CHUCKLES]
I got a tooth loose.
You do?
It's your turn to have one now?
Max, look at me. It's all right.
The tooth fairy's going
to come for you, okay?
You don't have to worry about that.
You're a good boy.
Wow.
[IMITATES GUNSHOT]
Did I hear something about a loose tooth?
-Really? Show me.
-Yeah.
I have a message for you.
Tracy.
-Look at that guy.
-I don't know anyone called Tracy.
Your property manager.
Oh, yeah, this guy's really loose.
They're putting in smoke
alarms in the apartment
and want to know if they can
get access Monday morning.
Does that suit you, honey?
Kelly!
Wow! [CHUCKLES]
PERRY: What do you think?
KELLY: It's perfect.
PERRY: Thank you very much, Kelly.
Thank you very much.
All right, let's hit the road.
We don't want to be late, do we?
[KEYS JINGLE]
-Bye, kids. Love you!
-KELLY: Bye, bye!
-MAX: Bye!
-Be good tonight.
-JOSH: Bye, Dad!
-All right. Bye, Kelly!
Bye, bye! Have fun!
♪ Make me feel at home ♪
♪ If you really care ♪
♪ Scratch my back and
run your pretty fingers ♪
♪ Through my hair… ♪
♪ You know I'll be your slave ♪
♪ If you ask me to… ♪
Thank you.
Do you want one, honey?
No, I'm going to wait
until after my number.
Okay.
♪ If you want my love,
then take my advice… ♪
Something on your mind?
♪ Treat me nice ♪
[CHEERING, APPLAUSE]
Okay, everybody, Elvis who?
Let's give it up for Stu!
Whoo!
Now, folks, don't forget
to visit our mixologist.
They made a signature cocktail for
this evening called "The Otter Bay."
Thank you.
The drinks were strong.
That didn't help matters, you know.
People getting half in the bag.
You "otter" try one! [CHUCKLES]
We're currently reviewing our alcohol
procedures in relation to school events.
PERRY: So, when did
you plan on telling me?
Or was I just to discover you
gone when I got back from Hawaii?
The latter.
-I told you I would get help.
-Did you make an appointment?
No, but I will. I promise you.
It's too late. It's all too late.
[CHATTER]
-[TIRES SCREECH]
-[ENGINE REVS]
Where are you going?
[BEEPS]
[PERRY SIGHS]
We have a family, Celeste.
We have to think about the boys.
Max is the one that was
hurting Amabella Klein.
It wasn't Ziggy Chapman. It was Max.
How do you know?
Because I asked him and he
admitted it, and Josh said it was true.
Okay, well, we'll…
Well, we'll talk to the teachers.
No. I will talk to the teachers.
Oh, Jesus. Open the fucking door, Perry.
-Open the fucking door!
-We will talk to the teachers together.
-Open the door!
-Mother and father. Husband and wife.
And I will talk to Max tomorrow
morning before I leave for the airport.
And what are you going to say to him?
It's not the way a man should treat a
woman? That men should never hit women?
Come on. Is it any wonder that it was him?
The boys have never seen anything…
You don't know that. And if they
haven't seen it, they've heard it.
They know what their
father does to their mother.
[SCOFFS]
You can't leave. You… We… I…
Can we… Can we talk about it?
You're never going to change.
You know that.
I am going to change.
I am.
I know I have this madness,
these fucking demons in here.
But I am… I'm fighting them.
I'm fighting them…
[CHEERING IN DISTANCE]
♪ Don't ♪
CHORUS: ♪ Don't ♪
♪ That's what you say ♪
♪ Each time that I hold you ♪
♪ This way… ♪
She's really good.
Yeah, I'm sure the
room is full of erections.
Yeah.
♪ Baby, don't say don't ♪
♪ Don't ♪
♪ Leave my… ♪
Jane?
Tom and Jane?
Really?
-Wow!
-ED: Jane, is that you?
New and improved. [CHUCKLING]
Is that a smile I see? Hi!
-You look great.
-JANE: You do, too. It's…
TOM: I'm going to get a drink. JANE: Okay.
-Can I get you something?
-Uh, yeah, a beer would be great.
-All right.
-Oh, can you get me one as well, Tom?
-Yeah.
-Thank you.
-Hi.
Hey, Ed. You're next, buddy.
-It's my turn.
-Go get 'em, honey.
♪ Every word I'm saying… ♪
♪ Don't ♪
♪ Don't feel that way… ♪
Can I get a, uh, double…
-Eh, triple vodka-rocks, please?
-Sure.
Can you just help me help myself?
Because I'm sick.
I'll do whatever it takes.
I promise you.
In sickness and in health. We took a vow.
Yeah. To have and to hold. To respect.
To cherish. They were our vows.
Not smashing my head into a wall.
-Not fucking hurting me.
-Well, you've been violent, too.
Yes, I've been violent
but only in reaction to you!
Only because you initiated it!
-It's enough now.
-And I agree!
It's enough!
And we can make it stop, together.
But for you to all of a sudden…
It's not all of a sudden!
I should've left you a long time ago!
We wouldn't be in this situation!
This wouldn't have happened.
I kept saying, "Come on, Celeste.
You can do it.
"He's going to change. You've got to stay.
It's going to be good for the kids.
"You stay for them."
And now I have to leave. I have to
leave for them, and you know I do.
Hey! Ready for the big night?
You guys look…
Babe, babe, babe, babe,
babe, babe, babe, babe…
Sorry…
Oh.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Fuck.
♪ Baby, don't say don't… ♪
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
-Cheers.
♪ Baby, don't say ♪
♪ Don't ♪
[CHEERING, APPLAUSE]
[WHOOPING]
Bonnie, thank you for that,
uh, concupiscent interpretation.
Our next singer not only gives
of his money, he gives of his time.
He actually animated the little
otter on our school's homepage.
Let's bring up my friend
and yours, Ed Mackenzie.
-Where are you, Ed? There he is.
-JANE: Whoo!
MADELINE: Go, Ed!
Whoo!
You know what, can you give me a second?
-He forgot the lyrics?
-Shh.
[EXHALES]
[GUITAR PLAYING]
[VOCALIZING]
♪ When no one else can understand me ♪
Yeah!
♪ When everything I do is wrong ♪
♪ You give me hope and consolation ♪
♪ You give me strength to carry on ♪
♪ And you're always there to lend a hand ♪
♪ In everything I do ♪
♪ That's the wonder ♪
♪ The wonder of you ♪
♪ And when you smile, the world is brighter ♪
♪ You touch my hand, and I'm a king ♪
♪ Your kiss to me is worth a fortune ♪
♪ Your love for me is everything ♪
♪ I guess I'll never know the reason why ♪
♪ You love me as you do ♪
I'll be right back.
♪ That's the wonder ♪
♪ The wonder of you ♪
He's so good.
[GASPS]
-I'm going to the restroom.
-Okay.
[PANTING]
Madeline?
[SOBBING]
[SOBS]
Fuck!
Honey, what's wrong? Look at me.
Breathe. You have to breathe.
What's happening?
-I cheated on Ed.
-What?
I cheated on Ed.
[SOBS] It was a long time ago, but I…
I feel like a horrible person.
I'm a liar. I'm a fucking fake.
No, you're not.
He's the greatest man I've ever known.
And I feel like a selfish fuck.
No, you're an amazing person, and
you're not perfect. Welcome to the club.
[CHUCKLES] We're all fucked up.
Madeline was out-of-her-mind hammered.
-Hi.
-Hey, I'm up next.
Okay. Maddie just ran away.
It was so weird.
I just wanted to tell her how good he is.
-Ed?
-You're better, baby. Stop.
I'm going to get a drink. Do you want one?
Yeah.
Okay.
-WOMAN: Celeste.
-Hi.
♪ I guess I'll never know the reason why ♪
♪ You love me as you do ♪
Are you all right, sweetie?
♪ That's the wonder ♪
♪ The wonder of you ♪
[CHEERING]
[MAN WHISTLING]
It might be those
Otter Bay drinks talking,
but, Ed Mackenzie, I think
you're the wonder of me, sir.
Let's hear it for Ed, everybody.
That was a special, Ed. Just special. Um…
I think we're going to take a
break away from our singing Elvises
and back off the raffle,
and our trivia portion of the
evening will be starting in one hour,
and I'm going to give
you the first question.
Which celebrity kept a
pet deer, Elvis or Audrey?
Think about it, and we'll be right back.
Thanks, everybody!
-Hey.
-Hi.
So, how are you doing?
PERRY: Um, I'm doing great. HARPER: Good.
I just found out today that…
-Amabella pointed right at Ziggy…
-No, no.
Because she was frightened of him. Of Max.
…leather.
-Fits like a glove.
-HARPER: Is this custom-made?
Yeah. Exactly. Will you excuse me for one…
Sure, sure. Yes, please.
-We'll talk later, though. Okay?
-All right, yeah. Okay.
-You look great.
-You do too.
Gordon, how are you?
Hey.
We will talk…
-What did you guys talk about?
-Nothing.
-Can we go back to the car?
-Stop it.
[CHATTER]
[BAND PLAYING]
Hey, have you seen Madeline?
Uh, yeah, according to
Bonnie, she just stepped away.
-Oh.
-You might wanna go tend to her.
What do you mean?
Well, I think she just, you
know, mixed drinks, again.
I didn't mean to offend. Sorry.
No, I think you did, Nathan.
I think you did mean to offend.
I don't think you're sorry, actually.
What's wrong, Ed?
You're not happy with
your performance up there?
Yeah? You're gonna get your
ass kicked tonight. You know that?
Sweetie…
Ed, that was great.
Okay. What's going on, here?
Nothing, nothing. Just the usual.
Ed's being a dick…
-Hey.
-Let's do it.
For God's sake!
What is wrong with you two?
What?
Ed's been trying to pick
a fight with me for weeks.
-I'm standing up for Madeline, you dick.
-Relax. Stop it!
-Would you relax?
-What do you think…
Oh, God!
I personally saw Ed Mackenzie
throw his drink at Bonnie Carlson.
I'm afraid to tell him.
I mean, I wanna tell
him, but I'm afraid it'll hurt him so bad.
-I'm so sorry.
-But I can't do that to him.
NIPPAL: Nathan Carlson!
Oh, God! [SOBS]
[CHEERING, APPLAUSE]
-Are you all right?
-Thank you. It's okay.
-Here, let me…
-Ed, it's fine.
Go on. It's your turn, baby.
Go sing. Baby, go.
Baby, I'm all right. Go knock 'em dead.
Truly wonderful.
Okay.
One more time, Nathan Carlson!
Hey, here he comes.
Here he comes. Go get 'em, guy!
I'm sorry.
["HOW'S THE WORLD TREATING YOU" PLAYING]
[VOCALIZING]
♪ I've had nothing but sorrow ♪
♪ Since you said we were through ♪
♪ There's no hope for tomorrow… ♪
No…
♪ How's the world treating you? ♪
♪ Every sweet thing that matters ♪
♪ Has been broken in two ♪
♪ All my dreams have been shattered ♪
♪ How's the world treating you? ♪
I need you to take the boys, now, to
this address that I'm gonna give you.
Um, I'm…
Yes. Right now.
I don't know what to do. [SOBS]
I don't know what to… [SNIFFLES]
Oh, God.
Hi.
Sorry, I don't want to interrupt anything.
-I just…
-That's okay.
I was talking to Celeste, and she
told me that it wasn't Ziggy, and I'm, uh…
I'm so sorry. I've treated you
and your little boy so badly.
-It's okay. It's… No apology necessary.
-Thank you.
And my husband was so
inappropriate and out of line.
I did try to poke your
eye out, in his defense.
-[CHUCKLES]
-I clearly deserved it.
It takes a really big person
to apologize like that.
You're a very big person.
♪ …said we were through ♪
♪ There's no hope for tomorrow ♪
What's your name?
-Sorry, just one minute, please.
-Oh, come on. Really? You serious?
[LAUGHS]
We paid for it. Help yourself.
♪ Every sweet thing that matters… ♪
-Cheers.
-Hey, cheers.
♪ Has been broken in two… ♪
-I'll catch you later.
-Yep. Sounds fine.
♪ All my dreams have been shattered ♪
♪ How's the world treating you? ♪
MADELINE: I really underestimated
what a compassionate soul you are.
But I was just protecting my friend.
-She's just a little bit drunk.
-And I'm sorry I was so horrible.
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
Celeste…
Can I talk to you for a minute?
CELESTE: No.
Please.
Celeste, can I talk to you?
No.
-Can we go back to the car and talk?
-I'm not coming back with you.
-Celeste…
-No.
I think she just needs a minute.
I appreciate your concern, but
I'm talking to my wife, not you.
Celeste, let's just go now.
We have to talk about it.
CELESTE: No! I'm not coming home with you.
So, just don't do this in front of
everyone, do you understand?
[AUDIO FADING] I'm not going…
[SINGING ECHOES]
[FAINT SCREAMING]
[MUFFLED CHEERING, APPLAUSE]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
[HEAVY BREATHING CONTINUES]
FIREMAN: Ma'am. Stop moving please.
GIBSON: Victim's on the back terrace.
QUINLAN: How compromised is the scene?
GIBSON: They did a pretty good job of it.
[LIGHTER CLICKING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
-[LIGHTER CLICKS]
-[POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
Already dead when we arrived.
[LIGHTER CLICKS]
[CAMERA SHUTTERS CLICKING]
Oh, my God.
-[DOOR SLAMS]
-[ELECTRICITY BUZZING]
[INAUDIBLE]
[QUINLAN EXHALES]
[QUINLAN SIGHS]
[INAUDIBLE]
-[INAUDIBLE]
-[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
-[SWITCH CLICKS]
-…to, uh…
To kick me again. And…
And I think that's when he must've
taken a step back, and he fell.
QUINLAN: Turn it off.
I'm so sick of these fucking lies.
CELESTE: I got up, and I…
It wasn't an accident.
Because?
Their language.
It's all the same.
The husband, when he got violent
with the wife, he didn't trip and fall.
He was pushed.
GIBSON: All right.
So, self-defense case then.
She fought back. He tripped.
Involuntary manslaughter.
-[LIGHTER CLICKS]
-Twelve months community service.
Good behavior, she's
out in six, maybe three.
Why bother to lie?
QUINLAN: That's what's bugging me.
Why lie?
They're not.
Let it go.
-[PIANO PLAYING]
-[LIGHTER CLICKS]
[SEAGULLS SCREECHING]
[PLAYING CONTINUES]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[INAUDIBLE]
[QUIET CHATTER]
[LIGHTER CLICKS]
[ENGINE STARTS]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SEAGULLS SCREECHING]
[INAUDIBLE]
[SCREAMS]
[PANTING ECHOES]
Oh, God!
Perry!
Oh, my God!
[GASPS]
[SEAGULL SCREECHING]
[INAUDIBLE]
[CHILDREN CHATTERING, LAUGHING]
[LIGHTER CLICKS]