[THEME SONG PLAYING]
[ECHOING MOANS]
[GASPS]
-CHLOE: What's out there?
-You scared me.
Gonna have to tie a bell around your
neck so you don't keep sneaking up on me.
What do you look at in the ocean?
Oh, nothing.
You spend a lot of
time staring at "nothing."
Okay, I take it back.
It's something, it's the big "out there."
The ocean is powerful,
but mostly it's vast.
It's full of life, mystery.
Who knows what lies out
there beneath the surface?
-CHLOE: Monsters?
-Monsters? Maybe.
Dreams, sunken treasure.
It's the great unknown.
That's what the ocean is.
ZIGGY: I don't want to go, Mom.
I know you don't, but you have to.
It's gonna be fine.
They all think I choked that girl.
Yeah, but you know that you
didn't and I know that you didn't.
And it's good enough for me.
It should be good enough for you.
It's gonna be good enough
for everyone else, too.
What's our mantra?
Every day, we're gonna be…
-Brave.
-So brave.
Good job. Let's go.
ZIGGY: Mom. Why did we move here?
Ziggy.
Okay.
I don't have time for this this morning.
Please put your shirt on.
Why did we move here?
-Why?
-That's enough.
You can finish that in the car. Let's go.
I don't mean to do your
job but it begs the question,
"Is she running from something?"
You cannot be serious, Joseph.
[SOUL MUSIC PLAYING]
What?
No.
No, this makes us look like cowards.
If you roll over on this,
it sets a precedent…
-JOSEPH: He basically laughed.
-Do not yell at me!
-They don't know.
-You're the one… Honey, can you…
If I go talk to the mayor,
he might consider legal…
Do you understand the
precedent that you'd be setting?
-I'd have to solicit the city council…
-Don't yell at me.
…to even get funding to retain a lawyer.
You know what?
I'm a lady and I've never said this
to anybody ever in my entire life,
but I'm going to say it to you.
You can go fuck yourself on the head.
Right on the head?
I'm sorry, but he's trying
to shut down Avenue Q.
He says it's too controversial.
What does he want to replace it with?
Don't tell me Cats.
[MUSIC PLAYING OVER STEREO]
Do you remember your first day at school?
I do, actually.
I got asked out on a date
by a second-grader, no less.
PERRY: Did we accept?
He wore white Docksiders.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm sorry about last night.
The idea of a bully in the class…
CELESTE: I don't think he's a
bully, but you're probably right.
We should err on the side of safety.
Hmm.
Wish I didn't have to fly out tonight.
I was thinking, when
you get back from Vienna,
maybe we could see another counselor.
Yeah. I think it's a good idea.
This is gonna be a really
good year for us, Sparkles.
COSMO: We'll just go away forever.
TIMMY: Why?
-WANDA: That's what the rulebook says.
-[CHUCKLES]
Oops.
Oh, wow. Bit of a line here.
Oh, it'll move quickly.
We just drop-and-go.
They've got it down to a science.
JOSH: Water, water, water.
We don't go in?
No, we just drop them off. They
can't be bothered with the parents now.
What, so we don't get
to meet the teachers?
We did all that yesterday at orientation.
No. They go right into class
today, don't you? Hmm?
Big boys.
JOSH: Max, look what the witch gives me.
MAX: Whoa!
And that's not something
you could have mentioned?
We discussed it.
MAX: Hey!
School time.
You could've told me
the Orientation Day was…
Don't.
CHLOE: We may have assigned seats.
If not, you can plop
down right next to me.
Hi, Skye.
-This is my friend, Ziggy.
-Hi. We're half-sisters.
Sort of.
-My mom was married to her dad.
-Hi, Chloe.
-Hey, Mama Bear.
-Hi.
I'm going to yoga class.
You wanna join me?
I would love to, but I
have a job interview.
Oh, wow.
Don't worry about him, honey.
-He's gonna be fine. I promise.
-[HORN HONKS LOUDLY]
Get laid, bitch.
God! See you later.
Maybe it was inappropriate
handing out invites on the first day,
but Renata's a planner.
Renata was sending a message.
[MADELINE WHISPERS] I
was thinking you could do it.
I don't practice anymore. I can't.
I know, but you could come out
of retirement just this one time,
so you could safeguard
all the arts for Monterey.
Plus, hear me out.
I would be your only client,
and how fun would that be
to have drinks with the client?
-Yoga is a time for quiet reflection.
-Yeah, I know.
-I don't like to be touched.
-Okay. Breathe into it.
-Okay.
-There you go.
Back corner.
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
-[INSTRUCTOR SHUSHING]
-Don't "shush" me.
She has her own yoga studio.
What's she even doing here?
-[INSTRUCTOR SHUSHING]
-Okay.
We do have a session where the
rules are more relaxed, you know?
Our perimenopausal class.
That won't be necessary.
I won't be coming back.
MADELINE: You will never
believe what she just said to me.
-What?
-Here. No. Here.
-You look so pretty…
-Please don't post that on Facebook.
-Ed will kill me…
-Hey, Maddie. Hey, Celeste.
How amazing was that class?
Hi, guys. Nathan, yoga, wow.
Yeah. Bonnie got me into it.
Yeah, well, you know.
Gotta sweat out all those toxins.
We drank like a bottle of wine last night,
and today I was like,
"You're going to yoga."
You know, I got Abby to sign
up for one of my piloxing classes.
That's fantastic.
Oh, I'm gonna call again
about that petition thing.
-I mean, it's ridiculous.
-You don't need to worry about it.
But they should be able to
just take my name off it, I mean.
Nothing's gonna stop us, honey.
Ticking bomb, I'll leave it at that.
Tick, tick, tick.
-Could she put a shirt on?
-[LAUGHING]
Boom.
Our very first project
will be for each of you
to do a family tree.
Where you get to talk
about your wonderful family.
Isn't that great?
But, before that
I am going to introduce you to a
very, very special friend to our class.
This is Harry the Hippo.
Now Harry here has been a
beloved member of the first grade,
for almost…
Ten years!
Now I know you're not
in kindergarten anymore,
and you're about to find out
that the transition to first
grade is not always easy.
But with Harry here, you
won't even notice it. I promise.
And the best part.
You will all have your turn
to take Harry home for sleepovers.
ALL: Yes!
Well, I'm going to start off our
day by passing Harry around,
so you can all greet him with a hug. Okay?
Here you go, Billy.
Yes.
Does Harry want to be hugged?
Why, yes. Harry loves hugs.
GABRIELLE: I mean, look, let's face it.
Amabella picked that Ziggy out of
a line-up and she was unwavering.
The kid was off, I'll leave it at that.
I thought your flight was at 5:00.
Traffic might be bad.
-It's 11:30.
-Thank you. Good to know.
Are you serious?
I changed my flight so I could
be here on their first day of school.
And then I don't even
get to go in the building.
I understand, but I just…
And for you to just dismiss
my being upset about it?
I didn't dismiss anything.
-I just don't want to get blamed…
-Yeah, you know what I think?
I think you didn't want me
to be there for Orientation.
What?
You decided to have
that moment all to yourself.
Mommy and her boys.
You are such a child.
[YELLS]
[GASPING]
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I'm…
Don't.
I'm so sorry.
Fuck.
Hey, hey. Hey, hey.
Sorry. It's just…
Fuck. I'm sorry.
It's just, all this traveling, I feel
like I'm missing out on so much.
They'll be grown one day and I…
Sorry. Sorry, sorry.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
No, no, no, no, no.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
There you go.
Mmm…
[YELLS]
-[GRUNTS]
-Yeah!
-[MOANING]
-[GRUNTING]
No!
Oh, God!
-[GRUNTING]
-[MOANING]
-Oh.
-God.
[GASPING]
[GROANS]
[PANTING]
BERNARD: Perry and Celeste?
Honestly? I'd sleep with either.
Call the Wall Street Journal and tell
them we make a deal now with these guys
or they're never gonna
have anybody buy them.
No, this is ridiculous.
Juliette?
Because my daughter's gotta get picked up.
Sorry, I'm distracted…
Yes.
You need to get in the car right now and…
Hold on one second.
I thought you were picking her up.
No, I'm doing an interview here!
MADELINE: Turns
out, it's actually harder to
have a part-time job
versus a full-time job
because, in addition
to doing all that work,
you're out there scouring for another job.
JANE: Are you looking for another job?
MADELINE: I only do 20 hours a week, max.
Between you and I, I try and
maintain my full-time mommy status,
so I can lord over women like
Renata and the other career mommies.
[LAUGHS]
Oh, there they are.
Our future world leaders.
JANE: Do you see mine? MADELINE: Yep.
-Chloe!
-Ma'am, please.
What, I can't call for my own daughter?
Please re-board the vehicle, ma'am.
-CHLOE: You causing trouble, woman?
-Get in the car.
And don't ever blow
your whistle at me again.
You're new here, I'm not.
ZIGGY: Mommy! JANE: Hi, baby!
-So, how was your first day?
-Fine. We got to meet Harry the Hippo.
JANE: And, Zig? ZIGGY: Good.
-JANE: Yeah?
-Teacher's nice.
She is? Oh, that's amazing!
-That's so great.
-What's that?
Oh, Amabella's having a party.
That's sweet.
I didn't get invited.
Honey, you don't know her very well.
You don't know her at all.
MADELINE: This is about
that stupid accusation.
It's fine.
[INAUDIBLE]
Okay, what are we listening to?
Feces is never terribly
far from Madeline's fan.
And the whole party
thing created a vortex.
Outrageous is what it is.
For the whole class to be
invited with the exception of Ziggy?
-I mean, come on.
-Is he the kid who…
-Will you please…
-What?
Chloe.
-Abby, come on.
-MADELINE: This is so Renata.
On the very first day of school?
Well, if she's convinced that this Ziggy
poses a threat to her daughter's safety,
of course he's not going to get invited.
I'm just saying
that distributing the
invitations in the classroom,
to the exception of one person,
I mean, it's just unacceptable.
Thank you, honey. This looks delicious.
Abby, are you dating the fridge?
Mm. Chloe. I set up a standing
playdate with you and Ziggy on Thursdays.
Cool.
-Are we sure that's a good idea?
-Why would it not be?
We don't know for a
fact that he's innocent.
Maybe the benefit of the doubt should
run to Chloe's favor instead of Ziggy.
Are you suggesting I might be
putting my daughter in harm's way?
Oh, you mean our daughter?
Chloe, I don't know why you didn't text
me or call me when the snub happened.
I might have been able to intervene.
How would she call you?
She has a phone in her doll.
Don't start with me right now.
It's just for emergencies.
ABIGAIL: You really shouldn't
encourage her to play with dolls.
And why is that exactly?
It's a little 1960s.
Not to mention sexist.
Is it a Barbie doll?
You can't fit a phone in a Barbie, dummy.
MADELINE: Chloe.
Barbies aren't allowed anyways.
Sylvie Baker's gave
Joey Proccacini a boner.
Okay. You know, Abigail,
I am super impressed with your
emerging social conscience, I really am.
Shall we leave it at that or is
now the time to pile on Bonnie?
I just have a very low
tolerance for injustice,
which is exactly what's going
on with Ziggy and his mom.
You fled the table when
Abby brought up Bonnie.
I'd ask you what's the deal with Bonnie,
but I think we both know
it's really about Nathan.
-That is not true.
-That is true.
Ed, I shouldn't have to
constantly run into the guy.
Monterey has 30,000 people
and I can't go to a goddamn yoga
class without seeing him and her?
And yoga? Give me a break.
When I was married to him, he
wouldn't so much as go for a walk,
and when he finally
did, he never came back.
Remember that big fight I promised?
-Yeah.
-I think now would be a good time.
Why?
Is Nathan the one?
What?
-What do you mean…
-The one.
For every person, there's "the one."
Case in point, you're my one.
-Well, you are my…
-Shut up!
But for you, he's the one
you fell irreparably in love with,
who irreparably broke your heart.
Who you apparently can't
get over, 15 years later.
[SCOFFS]
-Have you lost your mind?
-No.
I'm never out of my mind.
I don't get to be crazy, Madeline.
I'm stable, I'm grounded.
Good old steady Eddie, that's me.
Wow.
Where is this coming from?
It's coming from the fact that
you don't really seem to adore me,
that you're rarely
interested in having sex.
But, specifically today, it's coming
from your constant carrying on
about Nathan and his
seemingly perfect life.
Which tells me that you're
far from satisfied with your own.
And I'm fucking sick of it.
Look, I may not be the
good-looking adventure ride, okay?
But there is something to be said
for being there, for being truthful,
for being somebody you
can steadfastly count on.
I will not be anybody's runner-up.
You need to hear that.
Scratch the surface of any Jimmy Stewart…
Charlie Manson.
JOSH: No.
-You okay?
-He's scared.
Scared?
What are you scared of?
No, I'm not.
-He is.
-Oh, he is.
[SIGHS]
How's Ziggy doing?
Good.
Do you think he was the one
who hurt Amabella the other day?
-BOTH: No.
-He's really nice.
Could he come over?
-Yeah. Maybe.
-Okay.
Just have to ask your dad.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
Hey, wanna meet me at Side Door?
I need to swap out my
family for some vodka.
[CELESTE LAUGHS]
-Is your nanny there?
-Yeah, she is, actually.
Great. I'll see you then.
I think they both had drinking problems.
I do.
Well, I'm happy to let you post it,
but nobody really reads these flyers.
And if you want to get work
these days, you need a website.
-I know, it's just so expensive.
-It's not as much as you think.
Madeline's husband, Ed, is in web design.
He could help you put something together.
Maybe.
I already have an accountant,
but otherwise, I would…
-It's all good.
-No, I would.
Do you have any clients?
Yeah, a few portables
still from Santa Cruz.
Can I ask what brought you here?
The schools are great, to
build a better life for her son.
That's all you'll get.
Whoa. Yes, Ziggy.
I did come here with dreams
of a certain life. You are right.
Hopefully a better one.
Mom.
JANE: The chocolate one?
Okay, but I'm eating some.
We're looking at the
victim's relationships
with every parent who
attended Trivia Night.
[FEEDBACK SCREECHES]
"Is Nathan the one?"
[SCOFFS] Of course not!
MADELINE: That he doubts my love for him?
And Ed's not a neurotic guy.
So, maybe it is me, maybe I'm
just lousy at conveying how much I…
I don't know.
You once said that you two
don't have sex very often.
That's because I'm exhausted all the time
from school, or the kids, or the play.
What was Nathan like in bed?
I don't want to talk about Nathan.
-Really?
-Yeah.
But we are talking about Nathan.
-No, we were talking about Ed.
-Okay.
Okay, what?
Is it possible that you had a little more
passion for Nathan than you have for Ed?
And maybe he senses that?
Men can be a little more intuitive
than we give them credit for, you know.
Have you thought about seeing a counselor?
My God, we don't need a counselor.
Couples fight.
You telling me you and
Perry don't ever fight?
Yeah, we do.
Sometimes.
And then do you run
off to therapy afterwards?
[LAUGHS]
More often than not, we end up having sex.
Really?
Yes.
Starts with anger and… It's complicated.
Sometimes I think that he likes
to fight because it leads to sex.
[CHUCKLES]
Sometimes I think I like it, too.
How often does this happen?
Happens enough.
I have to say, Celeste, that
sounds a little bit twisted.
But kind of great, too.
[LAUGHS]
So the sex that you have, is it like…
Hello!
[LAUGHING] Hi, Celeste.
Madeline. How are you?
I was over there with my
girlfriends getting our drink on,
and I saw you two.
-Do you have a second?
-Sure.
RENATA: Did you know that they're thinking
about closing down the local VA hospital?
It means that vets are having to drive all
the way to Sacramento for their services,
which is so upsetting.
I've really dedicated
a lot of my life to vets,
and specifically PTSD,
so I'm gonna hold a little
fundraising dinner party
and help defray costs
and keep the facility open.
It would be so great if
you and Perry could come.
Yeah, sure.
And you and Ed, of
course, would be so nice.
-You're such a kind person, Renata.
-Thank you.
And, you know, it was very sweet of you to
invite Chloe to Amabella's birthday party.
Of course. Of course.
However, it wasn't very sweet to
single out and exclude little Ziggy.
Really?
Do you think it would be okay
for little Amabella to be
strangled at her birthday party?
I don't think so.
If Ziggy doesn't go,
then Chloe's not going.
Okay, I don't think this is
the right time to be… Let's just…
Thank you.
And if Chloe's out, then
the entire brigade will follow.
-She's basically the pied piper.
-What?
I like you, Madeline.
And I actually admire you for
sticking up for your unapologetic friend.
But if I can offer something
as objectively as I possibly can…
Do not fuck with my daughter's birthday.
GABRIELLE: I was in that bar,
and I distinctly saw Madeline
glance at a steak knife.
MADELINE: What a cunt!
-Excuse me?
-Why don't you get fucked!
RENATA: Wow.
The war is on.
ED: This really isn't fair to Chloe.
Excuse me?
Last year Amabella had a
jumping castle and a magician.
This year only figures to be better.
Oh, please.
And for you to summarily say she can't go,
and use her as a tool to
get other kids not to go?
MADELINE: I am not doing that.
One minute it's Nathan
or Bonnie, now Renata,
not to mention the parking
monitor, the girls in the car…
I can't even keep track
of all the fights you start.
Somebody needs to invent an app.
Well, maybe you could have
my back on some of them.
What is it about this Jane?
What is she, long lost
sister or something?
-Just a cause in lieu of…
-In lieu of what?
In lieu of a life?
Is that what you were gonna say?
And Jane's a single mom. Do you
need an app to put two and two together?
When Abigail was a little
baby, Nathan was not around.
And I was a single mom, Ed.
And I'm still angry about it.
It's not my love for Nathan
that lingers after 15 years,
it's my resentment.
There's a big difference!
[SPITS]
Did you hear me?
Oh.
They arrived just after you left.
Double the price, I think,
for nighttime deliveries.
Wow.
On a less positive note I
believe I've failed you miserably.
[SHRIEKING AND GIGGLING]
I thought Harry was just a
stupid stuffed animal for babies.
He is.
-Mom?
-[LAUGHING]
-Can we sleep with you tonight?
-Again?
Mm.
Well, as long as Harry doesn't snore.
I've heard it's a problem,
a real problem with hippos.
-Daddy snores.
-Yes, Daddy does snore.
[MOCK SNORES LOUDLY]
-[LAUGHING]
-No, like this.
Like this. [MOCK SNORES LOUDLY]
[ALL MOCK SNORE LOUDLY]
[LAUGHING]
I wish Daddy were here.
Oh, yeah. Me, too.
But the four of us all
together, we're gonna be fine.
-Mm.
-Hmm?
Oh! What happened?
Harry is missing a leg!
JOSH: It was Max. MAX: It was Josh.
JANE: You know, that's really…
That's super sweet of you, Madeline,
and as much as I appreciate
that, I feel like, you know, if…
If this birthday party is
ruined because of him,
then it's only going to
make things worse for him.
Sweetheart, everyone just assumes around
here I'm the root cause of everything.
Don't worry.
JANE: I'd prefer it if you just let
Chloe go to the birthday party…
Let me call you right back.
Chloe, get in the car.
-Chloe, get in the car right now.
-What?
I need to talk to you.
Now.
[SIGHS]
-I'm not having sex, I promise you.
-What are those pills?
They're just for in case,
you know, the day comes.
Not that it's coming any
time soon, but I just have 'em…
You are 16 years old.
Where did you get them?
-From a doctor.
-Dr. Ennis?
She wrote you a prescription
without calling me?
Not her. I went to Planned Parenthood.
Please don't make a big deal about this.
I'm not sexually active, okay?
Who took you there?
-What?
-Planned Parenthood.
Did you take a car, an Uber?
Did somebody give you a ride?
It's in Seaside. How did you get there?
Here you are.
-Love you, Mama. Bye.
-Love you. Bye.
Have a good day.
-Stay in the car.
-[BLOWS WHISTLE] Ma'am!
I'm just gonna be a minute.
Bonnie?
Bonnie, can I talk to
you for just a second?
-Of course.
-Couple of things.
First of all, I'm happy that Abigail
has bonded with your mother.
Thrilled about the communal
potato-peeling thing.
But when it comes to my
daughter's social recreational life,
particularly as it concerns to medications
that will permanently affect
her reproductive organs,
will you just kick that little
can of worms over to me?
-Do you understand?
-I do.
And should Skye come to
me ten years down the road
and ask for a little lift
to Planned Parenthood,
I would give you that courtesy call first.
Thanks.
-Ma'am!
-MADELINE: I'm dropping off my kid!
Come on, Chloe.
My daughter. It's my daughter.
Next time you wanna
do something like that,
why don't I take your daughter?
Your daughter.
Do whatever you want to her. [SCOFFS]
Are you fucking kidding me?
MADELINE: And what I don't understand is
why my own daughter
wouldn't come to me first.
JANE: I couldn't talk to
my mom about birth control.
MADELINE: Really?
If I were you, I would just let it go.
I would. With Bonnie, Abigail.
I'd ride it out.
I love my grudges.
I tend to them like little pets.
-All right, I'm just saying.
-I do the same thing.
I'm not into forgiveness either.
Really? Who do you not forgive?
No one. Just in general, you know?
"Never forgive. Never forget."
That sure sounds like a motto to live by.
-Good morning, Maddie. How are you?
-Hi, Tom.
-Everyone's making me angry.
-I'm sorry to hear that.
-Except for you. And you guys.
-And me.
Oh.
Marv Hermano, he runs
the muffler shop on Kentner,
and I hear that he's in need of
some bookkeeping assistance.
Great. Thank you!
And actually maybe some legal assistance,
too, if the zoning board stays on him.
I'm retired.
Unless you're defending
the First Amendment.
You never give up.
Oh, I heard about this.
-Ridiculous.
-I mean, I can't.
-Where are we living, girls?
-It is ridiculous.
It's obscene. What can I get you, Maddie?
I'll have a cappuccino. And a shot.
I'm sure you have one back there.
-I'll see what I can do. [LAUGHS]
-Thank you.
Yeah, I guess Shakespeare got it wrong.
"The play's the thing,
unless it has puppets."
Exactly! See? He understands me.
Unfortunately, gay.
-Really?
-Hmm.
-Come on.
-Yes!
-You're sure about that?
-All the best ones are.
-ED: Hey.
-Hey, Ed.
-What's up?
-Hey, man.
Love the look.
Especially the mirror, it's…
You gotta respect a man
who has his own back.
Well. Standard stuff.
-Yeah. How's the computer business going?
-Oh, great.
Kinda like landscaping, I guess.
-Growth business.
-[LAUGHS] That's clever.
-Um… Hey, Thanks for meeting me.
-Yeah, yeah.
Yeah. I just wanted to discuss
this whole thing with, like…
That happened with Bonnie and Abby.
Sure.
You know, as far as I can tell, there
was no undue influence or interference.
Like, Abby asked Bonnie some
questions about Planned Parenthood,
Bonnie answered them,
Abby then asked Bonnie to drive her there.
There was no parental usurping
of any kind, I promise you that.
But I can discuss that
whole thing with Maddie,
but what I wanted to take up with you is,
I think you can probably
appreciate that it's
a bit of a delicate
balancing act with my ex.
So, you know, I kind of
expect her to be rough on me,
but I think it's…
Like, you can't punish Bonnie.
Well, I believe she's
being nice to Bonnie,
or at least trying, under
the circumstances.
What circumstances would those be?
Nathan, come on.
It was pretty tough when you left.
What? That was like 15 years ago.
It's difficult for Madeline to see you
at every school function, so involved,
when you weren't there for Abigail.
It's difficult to run into you
at yoga when you never…
You know what?
Maybe I'm talking out of turn here.
No. I was young. You know?
And maybe a bit of a shit.
And I made some real mistakes
with both Maddie and Abby.
But should I be required to make the
same mistakes with Bonnie and Skye?
No. But, you know, it doesn't hurt to be
mindful of other people's
feelings sometimes.
Oh, yeah, yeah. Mr. Sensitive.
Excuse me?
No, actually, I meant
that as a compliment.
You're kind of like today's
standard bearer for the evolved man.
Like you work at home, and you…
And you do almost 50-50 of the child care.
You even cook.
So you're the guy who likes
to fish and hunt, and I'm…
-Mr. Girly-man?
-That's not what I meant at all, man.
Listen, I thought it'd be indelicate
to bring it up with Maddie.
That's why I'm bringing it up with you.
Well, that sounded like a threat, Nathan.
Are you threatening me?
No, but actually, I feel like
you're starting to threaten me,
which I don't think you want to go there.
You know, this thing with that
Ziggy kid, all the talk of bullying?
I was bullied.
Sixth grade.
And I always turned the other cheek,
thinking that was the
more mature thing to do.
Some 30 years later, it still haunts me
that I didn't beat the
shit out of that kid.
So much so, I find myself fantasizing
that somebody will come along one
day and say or do something to me,
that'll offer me the
chance to redeem myself.
You've always treated
me quite well, Nathan.
It's too bad.
Too bad.
[SCOFFS]
The first thing I said,
the very first thing I said,
it wasn't just the mothers.
I'm gonna kick your fuckin' ass,
you fuckin' talk to me like that again,
you fuckin' little shit.
Ed and Nathan hated each other's guts.
Are we all afraid to say that?
There's clearly a lot of
bad blood in this community.
MADELINE: What did he say?
JOSEPH: The mayor refuses to
authorize funding for the production.
MADELINE: Well, it should be a legal
matter and we could
make it a legal matter.
The funding is discretionary.
He could deny it on whatever grounds…
Is he denying it?
He's suggesting we pick
something more community-centric.
Joseph, we have worked so hard for this.
And we are being victimized
by the small-mindedness
led by the likes of Renata Klein.
Understood, but we need to
pick our battles. And this is just…
And, sometimes, our battles pick us.
We can't quit. We just can't.
Is this about the play, or winning?
[SCOFFS]
I don't know.
Maybe it's a little bit about both.
But I get sick and tired
of the morally superior in this town
stepping all over everybody else.
And you said you wanted to be
brave with your artistic direction.
That's all I'm asking.
Just…
Just be brave.
You told me to go fuck myself on the head.
[LAUGHS]
I just get… You know how I get.
[CHUCKLES]
Please, this is important to me.
-I'll talk to the Mayor.
-[SIGHS] Thank you.
You're not gonna regret it. You're not.
What's this?
JOSEPH: Frozen.
I'm taking my wife and my little niece.
Amabella passed out her
invitations on Wednesday morning.
Madeline was on the phone inviting the
kids to Disney on Ice, by Thursday noon.
HARPER: The two events were
scheduled for the same day, same time.
A vicious shot over the bow.
[WHINES]
HARPER: Yeah. It's ridiculous.
-Okay. Thank you.
-Yeah. Of course.
I mean, I don't know what's
wrong with this woman.
It's like she's power hungry,
she can't just let us all get along…
[SCREAMING] I said, "Thank you!"
[SCREAMING]
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE VIBRATING]
Hello?
[PANTING]
JANE: Sexual assault?
PRINCIPAL NIPPAL: It
appears Ziggy kissed Amabella.
Ziggy's advance was
unwelcome and a little aggressive.
[ECHOING] Ziggy kissed Amabella.
[PHONE RINGS]
In addition to the murder investigation,
we are investigating others on
assault and conspiracy to incite violence.
The intent, by all accounts, was to
simply make peace with Amabella.
Which is an admission
that he did try to choke her.
No, just hold on.
Zigfield still maintains his
innocence on the whole choking front.
The idea of brandishing affection upon
Amabella was first proffered by Chloe
in an attempt to ameliorate
the birthday party brouhaha.
I'm sorry, excuse me. Are you saying
Chloe had something to do with this?
-Yes.
-RENATA: Yes.
Mrs Klein.
She played a song. She invited
Zigfield and Amabella to dance.
And it seems your
daughter has inherited the
"Let's solve everyone
else's problems" gene.
[SCOFFS]
The motion was then seconded by Skye.
I don't believe that my daughter would
ever sanction a non-consensual touching.
She's a very peaceful child.
Isn't this just a lot of
brouhaha about nothing?
Well, look, we have a policy,
sir, and we'll get to the bottom of it.
-RENATA: Really? You have a policy?
-Yes.
RENATA: Well, isn't that great news?
Why don't you follow your
policy, or I'm getting an attorney.
-Okay, we're not there yet, Mrs Klein.
-I'm there.
God. Attorneys? Really? Is that necessary?
Actually, in my graduate thesis, I
coined the term "helicopter parent."
But these gems, they're fucking kamikazes.
And I'm not kidding.
No one takes responsibility for
anything, and Chloe's involved.
MADELINE: …not to mention
her health and well-being.
I mean, if I had a dime for every boy that
I tried to kiss when I was six years old,
I mean, I can't even tell
you, there were so many.
They're children, for Christ's sakes.
They're supposed to be doing
things like kissing each other.
Jane?
What's wrong, honey?
[SOBBING]
You okay?
I'm sorry, I just…
MADELINE: Honey. It's okay.
They're just kids. By this time
tomorrow it will all have blown over.
Come on.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
How can you not wanna
make up on this song?
Come on!
Make up, yes, not make out, silly.
It's what you guys do when you get
mad at each other, big hug, kiss, bang!
And everything's better again.
-But it's different with married people.
-Why?
I don't know. It just is.
Don't start with me.
This is a beautiful song, honey.
[SKYPE TONE CHIMING]
Hey, baby.
-PERRY: Hey, Sparkles.
-I thought it was like midnight there.
Yeah, well, I can't sleep.
Jet lag.
Right.
Is that the bathrobe I bought you?
Mm-hmm.
-It is.
-Ah…
Thank you for the flowers.
They're beautiful.
I miss you.
Yeah. Miss you, too.
And the boys miss you.
So how was their second day?
It was fine.
[CHUCKLES]
Will you do me a favor?
What?
Would you take that
beautiful robe off for a second?
[CHUCKLES]
The boys are waiting for me downstairs.
Yeah, well, I have to
help myself go to sleep.
I need you to help me help myself.
Do I now?
Let me just a look at my
gorgeous wife for a second.
Ten seconds.
I'll give you five.
Well, make it a nice five.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Okay. That's enough, naughty boy.
You'll have to come home
sooner if you want more.
Come closer.
I love you.
Take her out of school
if you're that concerned.
She's the one that has to leave?
She didn't do anything…
I just don't think legal
action is the answer. All right?
Let's see how it goes.
I'm guessing it'll all sort itself out.
-I do not feel supported here.
-[SIGHS]
Well.
I don't suppose I could
argue with your feelings.
[CHUCKLES]
JANE: Ziggy, why are you awake?
You're supposed to be asleep.
-What's going on?
-I saw you crying at school today.
I was just stressed out.
I'm sorry you had to see that.
[WHISPERING] At pick-up, I heard one
of the mothers say I was a little monster.
What?
Baby, you're not a monster.
You're not a monster.
Ziggy, there's nothing wrong with you.
Okay?
I love you so much.
[KISSES]
[SIGHS]
Pickles and mustard.
I'm not pregnant.
You know, if that day ever comes,
the one you alluded to earlier…
Hmm.
The day I decide to have sex? That day?
Yes, that one.
Can we talk about it first?
Sure.
'Cause I actually
think I could be helpful.
Okay.
I have a lot of girlfriends, as you know.
Never has any one of them ever said to me,
"Gee, if only I'd had sex sooner in life."
Mm-hmm. This is awkward now.
Bye.
So Nathan said that you
threatened to beat him up.
Oh…
Of course not.
He wanted me to get you
to back off Bonnie a little bit,
it led to a discussion, and…
I never threatened to beat him up.
I did let him know I wouldn't
be intimidated by him,
which, I think, was his intent.
So how did you two leave it?
We left it…
He's got Bonnie's back and I've got yours.
My He-Man.
Oh, come on.
[LAUGHING]
Can I just say one thing?
You never leave it at one thing.
You're the one, okay?
You're my only one.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[MOANING]