[THEME SONG PLAYING]
"[PAPA WAS A ROLLING STONE" PLAYING]
MADELINE: Oh, my goodness. Oh! [CHUCKLES]
ED: Ah, good one, Ziggy.
MADELINE: That was…
-Yeah. Work it out.
-ED: Oh, my. Go, go, go!
MADELINE: Work it out, sister. ED: Yes.
Oh, my gosh. Karate star.
Oh.
[THUDS]
[INAUDIBLE]
[DOORBELL RINGS]
-What?
-[GUNSHOT ECHOES]
MADELINE: I should have never
googled him, or stirred you up like that.
This is my problem in life, I
can never let dead dogs lie.
Well, but that's the
problem, he's not dead.
For all we know, he's out there
right now assaulting women.
Can I ask you, when you
went on this little road trip,
did you take your gun?
No.
-You don't sound sure.
-I didn't take my gun.
And had this Saxon Baker been
the guy, what would you have done?
Were there others?
Other Saxons in your Internet search?
Listen, you moved to Monterey
to start over. To build a future.
I suggest you focus on that. Not the past.
[SCOFFS]
[WIND BLOWING]
PERRY: [WHISPERING] You're gonna kill me.
I have to go to Phoenix tomorrow morning.
I'll be back Thursday night.
But it's the play and it's opening night.
Oh…
Well, well. I'll see it when I get back.
It's opening night.
Madeline's gonna be so disappointed.
It's a whole big thing.
I don't want you going
to the premiere either.
What?
Come to Phoenix with me.
Baby, I can't…
Look I know "Come to
Phoenix with me" isn't
the most romantic thing you've ever heard,
-but we can…
-[LAUGHING]
We can sneak off to Sedona, for a night…
-No, I can't do that.
-Why?
Because she will never speak to me again.
It's a big thing for her.
-Madeline's beginning to piss me off.
-Oh…
How often do we get a chance
to sneak away, just the two of us?
-Look what you're doing! Look at it…
-What, what?
You're the one who suddenly has to leave,
and I am the one who disappoints… [SCOFFS]
-I'm just trying to be romantic.
-[SIGHS]
Huh?
Just a little romantic here.
-JOSH: Mom!
-Mm.
NATHAN: I don't want to…
Divorced people are not
supposed to be friends.
Supposed to be civil or
have dinner together, and…
You know, it's okay for
things to be ugly sometimes.
That's like life.
Got it, life can be ugly.
I'll make a note of that. Thank you.
-[CHUCKLES]
-What are you doing?
Oh, just puttering around
in the garden, honey.
Trying to help things grow and evolve.
[SCOFFS]
Hey, what have you been doing all day
behind your closed
door there, locked away?
Working on your secret project?
Yeah, well, it won't be
a secret for much longer.
-My official unveiling is on Wednesday.
-Wow.
You've been working really hard on this.
Well, colleges look for
passion projects now, you know.
It's not just about, like, your GPA,
and being captain of volleyball.
Finally. [CHUCKLING]
Yeah.
[WIND CHIMES TINKLING]
I wanted to say, thank you for
having the dinner on Tuesday.
I know you and Mom really don't
get along, or necessarily want to,
but the idea that we could all be
together sometimes like we used to,
it's kind of cool.
-Good night.
-BONNIE: Good night, sweetie.
Don't. Just cut.
MADELINE: I feel like I just opened
up a giant can of violent worms.
So how did you leave it with her?
Well, I tried to diffuse her.
Imagine me, playing the role of diffuser.
I should just stay out
of other people's lives.
I'll talk to her.
What could you possibly say?
Excuse me?
Well, I mean, she can
hardly relate to my life.
What on Earth is she gonna
do to identify with yours?
Which is just a tick north of perfect.
[SIGHS] My life isn't perfect, Madeline.
Bad things have happened to me.
I do understand the concept. [SIGHS]
I'm sorry, I've offended you.
I can hear it in your voice.
Just tell me to go fuck myself.
No, I'm not gonna do that.
I just don't think she's
a dangerous person.
Really?
I'm starting to get a little bit worried.
I'm gonna have to call you back.
Is Perry there?
Hello? Hello?
I'm just gonna have to
call you back, all right?
Okay. Good night, honey.
Okay.
Tell me, baby.
What bad things have happened to you?
["PAPA WAS A ROLLING
STONE" PLAYING VIA SPEAKER]
All right, put it away, babe.
We're pulling up.
Wait, my favorite part.
Ziggy, you can watch it when
you get home from school.
-Put it away.
-Here it is.
[KNOCKING ON WINDOW]
-Hey.
-Hi.
Can you come see me?
Yeah.
There is evidently a petition circulating,
calling for Ziggy's suspension.
His suspension?
I am furious about it, as is
Mr. Nippal, and we will get it stopped.
-But in the meantime…
-Are people actually signing this?
Yeah, it seems so.
He's six!
We don't even know that he's the bully!
I know. I just found out about it myself.
And we will absolutely handle it,
Ziggy will, of course, not be suspended.
HARPER: I'm not ashamed
to say I started the petition.
The school was doing nothing.
That Harper was so far up Renata's ass,
she could have chewed her food for her.
I signed the petition.
-I signed it.
-I accidentally signed it.
The school was not doing nothing.
MS. BARNES: The
petition, we will get squashed.
I am more concerned…
Some of the children have been
instructed not to play with Ziggy…
[ELECTRICITY HUMMING]
[KIDS CHATTERING]
-You behind this petition?
-Excuse me?
-I asked you a fucking question.
-Hey, whoa, whoa, calm down.
-Calm down.
-Was it you?
What're you gonna do, huh?
Choke me? [SNICKERS]
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey!
-'Scuse me, don't you…
-Stop, stop.
-Oh, my God, my eye!
-What the hell is wrong with you?
If they had any sense they would have
canceled Trivia Night
right then and there.
I'd actually planned on skipping
Trivia Night until the eye gouging.
I should have taken that job in Reykjavík.
I'm gonna sue you!
-[GROANS]
-Is her eye okay?
Apparently. [SCOFFS]
She'll be fine.
I need to get out of this
town as soon as possible.
Hold on a second.
Ziggy is very well liked.
Chloe says he's popular.
Even Amabella plays with him.
This is about the parents,
and I'm not gonna have you
bulldozed out of Monterey.
Neither will I, for what it's worth.
Exactly, thank you.
[CHUCKLES] Thank you. Thanks.
A lot of parents are probably
applauding you right now.
There's more than one person in this
town who wants to deck Renata Klein,
yours truly included.
I actually think this is a good thing.
It's high time that people know they
shouldn't fuck with Jane Chapman,
and they're not gonna
mess with your kid, either.
I had my gun.
What?
I had my gun, in my purse
when I went to San Luis Obispo.
I don't think I would
have shot him, but I had it.
Okay.
Well I'm not gonna lie,
that gives me pause.
Yeah, it gives me pause, too.
Like I think I'm going insane.
Like I still hope, that
whoever he is, is a nice guy.
That like, maybe that night
was just a bad misunderstanding,
or a night gone wrong,
or he had a bad day, or his
parents got in a car crash.
And like, I make up these crazy excuses
because I'm so desperate to believe that
Ziggy's father is actually a good person.
Well he's been very, um…
[CLICKS TONGUE] Affectionate.
Very clingy.
Which usually means
he's feeling insecure, or…
Or what?
Or it means I have the power.
Sometimes he has it.
Sometimes I have it. It's like a seesaw.
When do you get the power?
After he hits you?
Yeah, when he hurts
me I get the upper hand.
The more he hurts me, the
higher I go, the longer I stay. Until…
He's been, um, ahem,
very loving the last few days.
-But at some point he gets the power back.
-Mm.
Usually when my bruises fade…
…and he doesn't feel as guilty.
He feels insecure, and
then it all happens again.
Where is he now?
He is in Phoenix. He left this morning.
When are you going to leave him, Celeste?
-[SCOFFS]
-When he hurts you badly enough?
When he hurts the children?
He will never hurt the children…
You need to rent an apartment.
Locally, if you don't wanna
disrupt the boys' school.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
We're getting way ahead of ourselves here.
No, I don't think so.
Stock the refrigerator,
make sure the utilities are paid
for, have the beds set up for the kids.
Get it all ready,
so we can at least remove, "Where on God's
Earth would I go?" from the equation.
You'll have a place,
a mind-set, another life
standing by should you need it,
which we both know you will.
I don't think a therapist
should be this, um…
I don't think you should
be behaving like this.
I'll get you the number of the Better
Business Bureau, you can report me.
In the meantime, start
documenting the abuse.
Write everything down,
photograph your injuries,
keep doctor reports.
That could be important
in a custody battle
and men like your husband
typically do go for custody.
He has the resources,
the money, the contacts,
most importantly,
he has the ego to see this through.
I don't understand why you're
being such an alarmist right now.
-Nothing's…
-Because I'm alarmed.
Have you told anybody
else about the abuse?
No.
-Why not?
-I don't know.
If you were to guess…
[SCOFFS]
Perhaps my self-worth is made
up of how other people see me.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm sorry.
I'm just amazed by patients who can
harbor such profound self-awareness
underneath the hard shell of denial.
Find a friend to confide in. Do it today.
[SIGHS] Because…
Because if there is a custody battle, you
know what Perry's lawyer will be asking.
"Did you ever tell anybody, Mrs. Wright?"
Hmm?
"Really, you told nobody at all?
"Is that because it never really happened,
"and you're just making
all this up to win custody?
"In fact, you've
repeatedly maintained what
a wonderful husband and father Perry is.
"Haven't you, Mrs. Wright?
"Nobody's ever witnessed
this alleged abuse, ever.
"Isn't that true, Mrs. Wright?
"We only have your word.
"You said he was wonderful,
now you say he's a monster.
"Were you lying then,
or are you lying now?"
You're a lawyer.
You know how important
it is to have a witness.
-Hey.
-Hello.
-Juliette? Right?
-RENATA: What do you want?
Uh…
I just wanted to say that I'm so sorry.
I completely lost control,
and I stepped out of line,
and I should've never shoved
you like that, there are no excuses.
And I'm so sorry.
Yeah. [SCOFFS]
The truth is, is I
finally realized that I've
been feeling exactly
what you must be feeling.
There's nothing worse than
your child being victimized, right?
So, I understand and completely
empathize with what you're going through.
I am as sure as any parent
can be that Ziggy is innocent.
I took him to a child psychologist.
And she examined him and tested him,
and said that he was a gentle young boy
who's completely incapable of
doing what he's been accused of.
Renata, I am at my wit's end.
I don't know what to do anymore.
Does Amabella still
say that he's hurting her?
No. She says he's a sweet boy.
And orientation?
Well, she hasn't taken
back the accusation.
But she refuses to talk to
us about anything further.
You think you're at your wits' end,
my daughter's the one
getting hurt, and I can't stop it.
[SOFTLY] I'm so sorry.
Me, too.
Thank you.
Yeah. My baby lost another baby tooth.
-I put it under my pillow.
-Good.
There is no Tooth Fairy, idiot.
It's Mom and Dad.
Would you please get me a tissue?
-Is it bleeding?
-No, not a lot.
[GROWLING]
-Are there any bad teenagers in here?
-Dad!
What are you doing here?
Hey, boys.
Don't we have a
premiere to attend tonight?
You made it back for the play?
I wouldn't miss it for the world.
They're gonna kiss.
You did that for me?
Yeah, of course.
Thank you.
Wow! Kazowie.
Did you say, "Kazowie"?
I did. You look fantastic.
Thank you, honey.
What, you got a big date or something?
As a matter of fact I do. A very big date.
Oh. Congrats on your opening night!
Thank you, honey.
I don't really have anything
to do with it anymore.
You have a huge amount to do with it.
It wouldn't even be happening,
but for you. Are you kidding?
-Let's go.
-Okay.
[GUITAR STRUMMING]
How do I look?
-You look nice.
-Thank you.
Remember you're not
allowed to sing that one.
-Okay.
-You can play it, but you can't sing it.
Why can't I go to the play?
It's not really for kids.
I like puppets.
I know you do.
Is it because the puppets have sex?
-Who told you that?
-Chloe.
She said the boy puppet
puts his penis in the girl puppet.
[STAMMERS]
Chloe said that?
Yeah. It's icky.
Sometimes magic comes from icky, Ziggy.
-WOMAN: Hey!
-That's a longer conversation though.
-Hi!
-How's my little champion?
-Awesome.
-Yeah?
You learned some more chords this week?
-Yeah.
-Yeah, you always do. [LAUGHS]
-Hi.
-Thank you so much.
No problem.
-I won't be gone too long. Give me a kiss.
-[STRUMS GUITAR]
[SIGHS]
-You look amazing.
-Mm.
Thank you.
Beautiful dress.
We're gonna be late. Stop.
Don't do that.
-What, this?
-Yeah.
I thought you liked when I do that?
Just… Come on.
-Come on.
-Get ready.
-We can be a little late.
-No, we can't.
I'm just very excited to see you.
To be home with my beautiful wife.
[UNZIPPING]
Oh. Yeah, I can feel that.
Yeah, you can feel that?
[BOTH GASP]
-[EXHALES]
-God, that's quite a trick.
-Yeah, that's quite a trick, huh?
-Mm-hmm.
Come on baby, please
get ready, we gotta go.
Come, come, I just want you…
Please, this is important.
We've got to go.
-What is this?
-Really, stop it.
-What's wrong?
-What did you do,
-take a pill or something?
-No, of course I didn't take a pill.
You're actually capable of
arousing me without medication.
-Celeste.
-You're being ridiculous.
Am I? Huh?
-[YELPS]
-Is this being ridiculous?
Ah! [GROANING]
-♪ Only for now ♪
-♪ For now there's life ♪
-♪ For now there's love ♪
-♪ Only for now ♪
-♪ For now there's work ♪
♪ For now there's happiness ♪
-♪ But only for now ♪
-♪ For now there's life ♪
-♪ Only for now ♪
-♪ For now there's love ♪
-♪ For now there's work ♪
Still no text or anything?
She must've lost her sitter.
-♪ Only for now ♪
-♪ For now there's friendship ♪
♪ Only for now ♪
-♪ Only for now ♪
-♪ Sex! ♪
-♪ Is only for now ♪
-♪ Your hair ♪
-♪ This show ♪
♪ Is only for now ♪
♪ Only for now ♪
♪ But it's only temporary ♪
[WHISPERS] So good.
♪ Everything in life is only for now ♪
[PIANO PLAYING]
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]
-Okay. I'll see you at school.
-Yes.
Congratulations.
Oh, Stu. Thanks for coming.
-Hey, guys…
-Hey, congrats.
-Maddy, congratulations.
-Thank you.
-Amazing.
-That is a good idea.
-I'm gonna get us some drinks.
-Okay.
That's really great.
You know I'm not really a
huge fan of Muppets, but…
Right.
Um, where'd Abby go?
She rushed out.
She told me to tell you she loved it.
Oh, what's she rushing out to do?
-No, it's the whole… Her whole…
-Project.
Secret project. Seems to be all consuming.
Well, I'm gonna join Ed.
-Yeah, of course.
-Thank you for coming.
-Oh, yeah. It was amazing.
-Yeah.
-I'm gonna call Celeste.
-Yeah, just let me know.
TORI: Madeline.
Hi, Tori. Hello.
Congratulations.
Thank you. And to you, too.
Joseph was great.
And I feel like it went really well.
Was it you?
I'm sorry?
Are you the woman Joseph is in love with?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I know he had an affair a year ago.
I can tell when he lies.
-Okay.
-He also told me he was over her.
Which… I can tell when he lies.
Was it you?
I'm happily married,
just friends with Joseph.
I would never do that.
What were you doing in his car?
[TURN SIGNAL TICKING]
ED: Kind of quiet.
I'm just reflecting on all of it.
Big night. I would think you'd
be bubbling over a bit with pride.
You should be.
Thanks, honey.
I don't know, for some
reason, I'm just thinking about
this dinner with Bonnie and Nathan.
Just kind of dreading it.
It'll be fine.
-Yeah.
-[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
Finally. She better have a good reason.
Where were you?
What?
A broken urethra?
I know. Can you even imagine?
Chloe, it's time to go to bed, honey.
Gimme ten.
No, time for bed, right now.
[VOCALIZING]
Chloe, now.
7:00, final offer.
I said now.
-Night, sweetie.
-Night.
-Love you.
-Love you, too.
Good night, honeycake.
-Love you.
-Love you, too.
So it happened during…
I mean, talk about wild sex.
Can you imagine being in the hospital?
I mean, how embarrassing.
I just can't imagine the
passion it would take
to shatter a urethra in two places.
You sound a little envious.
You want me to smash yours?
[ED LAUGHING]
Well, not smash, but you know.
[MADELINE CHUCKLES]
We never have wild sex.
We have nice sex, I like it,
but, you know, usually times
out between four and six minutes,
and neither of us are in any
remote danger of physical injury.
Well, that's just kind of mean, Ed.
Sorry, maybe I am envious.
What, Perry walks through the door and…
Whoosh.
Wish we had that kind of desire.
[SCOFFS] Well, by "we" you mean me.
Okay, you're a fiery person.
Which makes your tepidness
for me more conspicuous.
I don't mean to punish you.
Well, I mean, it feels like you are.
I tell myself all the time,
like married people, you know,
after a while, they reach this
sexual plateau and that's the norm.
I hear about other couples,
you know, breaking urethras and…
Well, it's hardly like you're
some sort of raging bull, Ed.
The only time you touch me is when you're
reaching across me to get the Visine for…
That's because you
don't want it, Madeline.
And we never talk about that because
that would make it harder to pretend.
And sometimes that's the
essence of a happy marriage, isn't it?
The ability to pretend.
In the days leading up to Trivia Night,
it just seemed more and more
people wanted to kill each other.
It was hard to keep track.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SINGING ALONG]
-[MUSIC STOPS]
-What are you doing?
Abby told me that Chloe
said that Ed was rehearsing.
They say he's pretty good,
so, I'm gonna kick his ass.
I was just… What, I'm inspired
by the whole play thing.
And besides I'm sick and
tired of his little fucking digs,
like he's the cultural shit or something.
I'm gonna show him who's evolved.
Kick his cultural ass.
What about this one?
[VOCALIZING]
If you're looking for trouble…
Baby, the whole point of this
dinner is to try and reduce the friction
that contributes to an
unhealthy environment.
…came to the right place.
Yeah, between Madeline and I.
But friction between Ed and I is fine.
First of all, I'm very
disappointed in your attitude.
And second, and more importantly,
we have a bigger problem.
Abigail's secret project.
Yeah, what about it?
[CLICKS TONGUE]
She is auctioning off her
virginity on the Internet.
For Amnesty International.
So it is for a very good cause.
[CLEARS THROAT] She's
selling her virginity on the Internet?
Good cause.
NATHAN: Abigail!
MADELINE: You smoking?
ED: Just for tonight.
It's been 15 years. Why not?
So you think our marriage is pretend?
No. I said that in every
marriage there is pretending.
Even the best ones.
You said it was the essence,
if I heard you correctly.
I mean, I don't pretend to love you.
I know you don't pretend to love me.
But what I do like to pretend, as do you,
is that I'm all that.
So is this back to the "Steady Eddie"
theme? Is that what we're talking about?
No, Madeline. I'm the lucky one.
I get to wake up every day
next to the girl of my dreams.
That makes me the winner.
I just feel like the loser sometimes.
I know I haven't always
been the best wife.
I'm really sorry.
I get angry sometimes,
and I made a mistake…
Uh-uh. [SHUSHING]
[SOFTLY] I made a terrible mistake.
Don't say that.
NATHAN: What the fuck?
You're selling your virginity?
I thought you'd be proud of me.
Proud of you?
Yeah, a lot of girls lose
their virginity for a lot less…
So you're selling yourself?
-At a worthy price! For a worthy cause!
-Okay, gentle tones, please.
-Don't try and tell me…
-You know that is prostitution!
-Women are exploited all the time!
-Hey let's just make sure
everyone feels heard here.
Let's have a conversation.
Wait, is this thing set up live?
Is it already up?
[STAMMERS] No. Not…
-Where are you going? Dad!
-Guys!
-Dad.
-Come on!
-Where is it?
-You're being crazy!
-No, you're not taking that.
-Are you serious?
You're not taking that!
No, until you tell me or you shut it down.
You two are…
Stop!
-Stop it! Abby… Get off me.
-I'm not shutting it down!
Get off. Get off.
-Give my computer back!
-No! Forget it.
[SHRIEKING]
-Honey, it's okay.
-SKYE: Stop it.
[SKYE CRYING]
Hi.
How are the boys?
They're fine. Sound asleep.
PERRY: Thank you for staying late.
You can go now.
You can go now, Kelly.
CELESTE: We're fine.
-I hope you feel better.
-PERRY: Thank you.
Good night.
I'm going to get you some ice.
You're lucky I didn't kill you.
What did you say?
You could've done permanent damage.
So the spermatozoa fertilizes the egg.
Women lay eggs?
[CHUCKLES] No, women have
eggs inside of them, in their bellies.
So the sperm fertilize the egg in
there, then out of that comes the baby.
So you want a baby,
and my dad ferlitized you?
-"Fertilize."
-Fertilized you?
Something like that, yeah.
What do you mean, "something like that"?
Exactly like that.
You're too smart for me.
Where is he?
I don't know, baby.
[KEYS CLACKING]
Have you spoken to her?
No.
Are you going to?
-Hey, honey?
-I'm running late.
Um, it'll just take a second. Please.
Listen, I think the idea
behind what you're doing,
it's extremely noble.
What other 16-year-old even
has a social conscience, you know?
So I'm proud of you. I'm very proud.
But I think that there are other
ways to accomplish your goals.
Dad, come on.
A 16-year-old white girl from
Monterey selling her virginity online?
Wolf Blitzer would
saddle that up for weeks.
That's the way.
BONNIE: Abby.
Thanks.
-I blame you for that.
-Me?
Yeah, you taught her
to care about everything.
-It's just rubbed off on her.
-Oh, come on.
"Wolf Blitzer's going to saddle that up?"
[SCOFFS]
You know, Madeline's so
going to blame me for this.
-No, she's not.
-Oh. Yeah, yeah, yeah. She will.
I can't believe you're eating that shit.
-Got you!
-No, you didn't!
[CHATTERING]
♪ Well, baby, when times are bad ♪
♪ Call on me, darling
and I'll come to you ♪
♪ When you're in trouble ♪
Ziggy!
♪ And feel so sad ♪
♪ Well, call on me, darling
I said call on me and I'll help you ♪
[DOORBELL RINGS]
ED: Sitter's here, honey!
JANE: A playdate? Really?
Well, we could keep a
watchful eye on them,
which the teacher and an
assistant can't do, really, with 22 kids.
Are you still convinced
that Ziggy's the culprit?
I don't know,
with everything you said,
which is why if I schedule playdates
with each and every child in the class,
I can eliminate suspects one by one.
You're going to schedule a playdate
between Chloe Mackenzie and Amabella?
If that psycho will allow it.
Sorry, poor form.
I know you're friends with Madeline.
It's all good.
-Hey!
-Hey! Everything okay here?
RENATA: Everything's great.
JANE: So nice of you to ask, Harper.
You know, schools should set up special
commendations for gestures like that.
Maybe I'll start a petition.
[CHUCKLES] "Petition"! Touché.
All right, I'm going to work, girls.
See you later.
Bye.
We just want our children
to be safe, that's all.
Of course we do. It takes a village.
Got to have each other's backs, right?
Who's got yours?
There was this rumor whipping around
that Jane and Renata
had settled their differences.
I never bought it.
I believe women are chemically
incapable of forgiveness.
It's pretty, huh?
So this is our two-bedroom, two-bath.
Mm-hmm.
You know, some of the units
come furnished, but personally,
-I think the décor is hideous.
-[CHUCKLES]
And they're on the ground
floor, so you don't get this view.
No, unfurnished is fine.
It's definitely on the
Monterey city limits?
Yeah.
We're Southwest Monterey.
And it's available now?
You can move in tomorrow.
-What a beautiful sunset.
-Mm.
Do you think I'd be able
to come back a little later
and spend some time here by myself?
-Yeah.
-It probably sounds weird.
No, it doesn't sound weird.
I mean, it's possibly
where you'll be living, right?
I'm just going to leave you the
key, and I'll clear it with the office,
-and just take as much time as you need.
-That's amazing. Thank you.
Just call me tomorrow. Let me know.
[SIGHS]
ED: If you feel yourself getting angry,
just remember it's all about
getting along for Abigail's sake.
I'm going to be fine.
I took a little something.
Just a half.
This is a good thing that we're doing.
MADELINE: Such a long drive…
ED: Good. Everything looks good.
And the chef, not too bad.
The cook's even better.
Uh, Madeline, do you want some more bread?
-Mm, yes, please. So yummy.
-Honey, will you pass that? Thank you.
Bonnie, I love this music. Is this Adele?
Uh, no, it's Sade, actually.
We should get this, honey.
Oh, we have it.
BONNIE: Red wine, anyone?
I know white goes
with fish, but I like red.
MADELINE: Yes, please.
[LAUGHS]
Down the hatch.
I love this place setting,
like when there's extra
forks and extra spoons,
especially the little tiny forks.
-[CHUCKLES]
-It feels so special, doesn't it?
I just want to use all of them.
The little ones are for the oysters.
And I love these really
creative little cups.
They're clay. I think they're from Mexico.
Yeah.
MADELINE: That's so nice.
Ed prefers more traditional
glass cups for wine, but these are…
I'm actually more kind of a beer guy, but…
Oh, do you want some beer?
-Oh, no, no, no.
-We have some.
-Are you sure?
-Sit down.
You've done enough.
And since we're talking about wineglasses,
-let's have a toast!
-A toast.
-Yes, toast.
-Toast.
The, uh…
To, um… For…
-I should make a toast.
-BONNIE: Please.
To Nathan and Bonnie.
-Because I heard…
-And none of us killing each other.
[LAUGHS] Yeah, right.
-[LAUGHTER]
-I'm just kidding.
This is yummy wine.
-BONNIE: Mm, is it?
-It's really good.
Uh, is Abigail going
to join us for dinner?
She'll be down for dessert.
She says she can only be stuck
with the grown-ups for so long.
Yeah.
I think she's just wanting us
to have some bonding time.
Teenagers. Oh, she's probably
working on her secret project.
Mm.
MADELINE: I'm so curious.
-Do you guys know what that is?
-Mm-hmm.
Yeah, we just found out, what it is. Yeah.
-No way.
-Do tell.
Baby? [CLEARS THROAT]
It's unconventional.
It's even a little radical.
Good.
Listen, when I first heard
about it, I overreacted,
and I just got to caution you
guys to take a breath, process it,
before jumping to a judgment.
MADELINE: Okay, can
you just tell us what it is?
[CLEARS THROAT]
It's… [LAUGHS]
Well, she's attempting to raise
money for Amnesty International.
-All right.
-So she showed me her website.
-It's like very professionally done.
-Website…
I…
Abigail is auctioning off her virginity
in order to raise money
to protest sex slavery.
-What?
-Yes.
[SCOFFS]
-Very funny.
-No, I'm being serious.
She said if a seven-year-old
can be sold into sex slavery,
then no one would bat an eye
if a white, rich American
girl would sell hers online.
This is for real?
Look, it's not gone live yet,
and we have no intention of
letting that happen, obviously.
You know, Nathan, if
this is some sort of joke…
This is not funny, Nathan.
Okay, it's shocking, and a bit disturbing,
but I think it is important that we
separate the nobility of the cause
from the misguided means
of pursuing it, you know?
We champion the former and
dissuade her from the latter, right?
-[RETCHES]
-ED: Oh, honey!
-Are you okay?
-That's okay. That's okay. That's okay.
I got it. I got it.
That's a human reaction.
That's completely… Baby, get a…
You okay, honey?
No, I'm not.
-Oh, my God.
-ED: Oh, honey.
Okay. Thank you. Thank you.
That's all right. Here.
That's all right.
This is how you parent, Nathan?
She's been under your roof for two minutes
and now she's some sort of prostitute?
Did I tell you?
Great parenting!
All right, let's all just
settle for a minute.
Okay? Please. Let's just settle.
Let's remember that we are living
in the time of Facebook, and reality…
Ugh… God damn it!
-Oh, my…
-Shit.
It's the shrimp.
I'd heard that Abigail
was a little slutty.
Knowing the mother, I
wouldn't be surprised.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER ON TV]
-Bye, guys.
-Bye.
Where are you going?
Out for dinner with Jane.
[SIGHS]
That's enough.
Abigail!
You're done with dinner already?
Look, I don't even know
where to begin about this,
so I'm just going to
go straight to the end.
This is wrong, Abigail. Completely wrong.
And I salute your cause. I really do.
But what?
Saluting a cause?
Recognizing a problem isn't enough.
A person has to do something.
Well, this something is not that, honey.
What about your play?
What about my play?
You said it spoke to you because it
was about finding a purpose in life,
which I get.
Making your mark. I get that.
You're the one who always said
a person's life needs to matter.
-Okay.
-Was it all just bullshit?
No, it's not.
And I'm not going to give
you some long song-and-dance
about how precious and
sacred your beautiful body is.
Mm-hmm.
But it is not for sale, Abigail. Not ever.
No matter what cause, no matter what cost.
And one day, you're
going to look back at this,
probably pretty soon, and think,
"What the fuck was I thinking?
"Why was I going to
fuck up my life like that?"
[SCOFFS] Must be nice to be so right.
-I'm not right!
-And so perfect.
I'm not fucking perfect!
You think you know me so well?
I fuck up, too!
I make mistakes.
I've made mistakes bigger than this.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Last year I cheated on Ed.
I ended it very quickly.
And the two things I value most in
this life are my kids and my marriage,
and I risked destroying both of them.
Just because I was selfish, or…
So tell me…
Don't tell me I'm perfect, okay?
I know about fucking up.
And fucking up doesn't make
your dad and I get back together.
Fucking up doesn't fix your life, okay?
At least what you were going
to do was for a good cause, and…
I was just being selfish.
Do you still love Ed?
[TV PLAYING]
Mom, watch this.
["PAPA WAS A ROLLING STONE" PLAYING]
♪ September ♪
♪ The day I will always
remember, yes I will ♪
♪ Because that was the
day that my daddy died ♪
♪ I never got a chance to see ♪
♪ Never heard nothin'
but bad things about him ♪
♪ Momma I'm depending
on you to tell me the truth ♪
[MUSIC CONTINUES]