All triple area sightings
is to go on a list,
any fella on that list
can expect a visit.
Well, let's hope their wives
aren't in.
Let's hope they are.
Hey! If their wives are in,
we tread carefully.
The last thing we want to do
is embarrass these men.
In our determination
to catch this man
we're driving him
out of his comfort zone.
He is now making repeated mistakes.
Is it fair to say
that every woman is at risk?
Inadvertently.
So, Chief Constable, what would your
advice be to the women of Yorkshire?
Stay home. Stay safe.
I want you to go into that office
and type up what's on here.
Who's it from?
So, we're all agreed. Whoever wrote
those letters, sent that tape.
And if it's not him?
It's him.
We call a press conference,
have it on television tonight.
Someone is going to know the voice.
The voice you're about to hear
is the man we believe to be
the so-called Yorkshire Ripper.
TELEPHONE RINGS
ANSWERPHONE: 'Thank you
for calling this freephone number.
'After the tone,
you will hear the voice of the man
'believed to be
the Yorkshire Ripper.
'If you recognise it, please contact
West Yorkshire Police.'
BEEP
'I'm Jack.
'I see you are still having no luck
catching me.
'I have the greatest respect
for you, George,
'but, Lord,
you are no nearer catching me now...
'..than four years ago
when I started.
'I reckon your boys
are letting you down, George.
'They can't be much good, can they?'
TELEPHONE RINGS
MEG: Millgarth incident room?
Are you still in touch with him?
HUBBUB OF CONVERSATIONS
OK, can you describe him
for me, please?
From Roker but moved to Ryhope...
Works in Kirkgate Market.
Thank you.
No, that's very useful.
Will you just hold the line for me?
Good morning,
Millgarth incident room?
Short hair.
Short temper, did you say?
Can you speak up for me?
POLICEWOMAN:
Were there any peculiarities?
COUGHING
All right?
Says I can take two spoonfuls
every four hours.
Right...
Let's get this done, and then we'll
get down to Wakefield, see Gregory.
TELEPHONE RINGS
Oldfield.
WOMAN: 'I've got Mike Dugdale.'
Yeah. Send him through.
Mike?
'Look, I can put this on the front
page again, but I need a quote.'
Something from you, give the
readers a sense of how it's going.
Well, tell them it's going fine.
'Fucking hell,
is that the best you can do?'
It's hardly Oscar Wilde, is it?
Oh, aye? Tell 'em 50,000 calls
so far to the hotline,
2,000 calls
coming into the station every day
and we're closer to catching
this bastard than ever.
Yeah, not before time an' all.
Right, in light of the letters
and the tape,
there are five points
of elimination.
One - the Ripper must be born
between 1924 and 1959.
He must not be coloured.
TELEPHONE RINGS
Can you take that off the hook,
please?
What if it's important?
They'll call back, won't they?
Just do as you're told,
take it off the hook.
DIAL TONE
He must not have a shoe size
bigger than a 9.
He must be blood group B, same
as whoever killed Joan Harrison...
TELEPHONE RINGS
Take them off the hook
for two bastard minutes!
Right, finally.
He must speak with a Geordie accent.
Anybody not meeting
these five points, they're gone.
Is that clear?
ALL MUTTERING: Sir.
SHOUTS: Is it clear?
ALL, FIRMLY: Yes, boss.
Good. Now, just put the phones back
on, get back to work. Let's go.
Jim...
you're coming too, apparently.
TELEPHONES RING
HUBBUB OF CONVERSATIONS
I've been questioned once already.
End of '77.
Like I said,
these are just routine inquiries.
Have you been to Huddersfield,
Leeds and Bradford
in the last 12 months, Mr Watkins?
This is about your blue Ford Escort.
Well, yeah, I travel for work.
Have you ever visited a prostitute,
Mr Neale?
We can do this here or we can
take you down to the station.
Once. Maybe twice.
But never in Huddersfield.
Sugar?
BOTH: Two, please.
What about Bradford or Leeds?
I'm not sure.
So, you don't know where your
husband goes at night, Mrs Ashworth?
At-At night?
Only he's been spotted out,
driving late in the evenings.
Well, if he goes anywhere,
it'll be to see his parishioners.
Alan always makes sure to make time.
Why?
Does he look like someone
who goes off with prossies?
He's got no need, he's got me!
It's all right,
they're only doing t'job.
Would you be willing to provide us
with a handwriting sample?
Maybe a letter
or a page from a diary.
It's not him!
Right, so let's prove it,
and then that way,
we won't have to come back
a third time.
Sir.
There's an advertising agency
overseeing it.
Budget's a million pounds.
Unprecedented.
If ever there was a moment
to capitalise on the interest
of the tape, this is it.
We push on every front,
television, radio.
We're talking 5,500 billboards
across the country.
Well, it's a mistake.
No more talk of prostitutes,
this is all about the voice.
It's a mistake.
Explain.
Well, we can't cope.
Who can't?
Nobody.
The bloody building can't even cope.
Had to reinforce the floor
cos of all the index cards.
We're taking thousands
of calls a day as it is.
We carry on with this Project R
then the numbers
are just gonna go... What?
What are they going to do, George?
Double? Treble?
What the hell does it matter,
if it gets us the one call we need?
What the hell does it matter?
Well, I say we don't do it.
Well, you don't get to decide.
You don't get to decide
because you have failed.
The most wanted man of the century,
more resources than anyone, ever...
..and you... and you...
and you have failed.
BUZZER
Yes? 'A Detective Nevill,
calling from Scotland Yard, Sir.'
One moment.
My current meeting's just finishing.
A fucking advertising agency?
'Chief Constable,
this is Jim Nevill.
'I'm calling on behalf of Sir David.
'He has asked me to call
and arrange a visit.' To London?
'Well, he thought it might be more
effective if he came to see you.
'Says he feels like it's a trip
'he should have made
a long time ago.'
What a tremendous idea.
Make an arrangement with Pam, and...
I look forward to seeing you.
DIAL TONE
There has never been an inquiry
of this scale
in the annals of police history.
The reward being offered
for information leading to an arrest
currently stands at £30,000.
Are you sure this is the voice
of the Ripper himself?
Oh, most certainly.
We shall be publishing copies
of the letters
in 300 newspapers across Britain.
And repeating that information
on television, on radio,
and various publicity points
across the north.
The message from George and his team
is clear -
even if you have only
the slightest inkling,
about a man at work, an uncle,
a chap who lives down the street...
call us. Contact us.
Help bring the worst killer in
British criminal history to justice.
Any questions?
Chief Constable,
how can you be so sure
that that is the voice of the Ripper
himself?
CLAMOUR OF QUESTIONS
DOORBELL RINGS
MAN INSIDE: It's OK, I've got it.
Mr Peter Sutcliffe?
Yes.
I'm Detective Constable Laptew,
this is Sergeant Robert Blake.
We're making house visits
in relation to t'Ripper inquiry.
Am I right in saying you're
the owner of a black Sunbeam Rapier?
Not for about a year.
Right, but you did own one?
I did, aye.
Mind if we come in?
No problem.
What do you do for a living,
Mr Sutcliffe?
I'm a lorry driver.
Have you had a visit before at all?
Have any of our colleagues...
The lads are doing house visits
for the Yorkshire Ripper inquiry.
Now's the chance to get rid
of your husband if you want to,
Mrs Sutcliffe.
Would either of you like a cup
of tea? I'd love a glass of water.
Your Sunbeam Rapier has been spotted
in three red-light areas
relevant to our inquiries.
Manningham, over 30 times.
Leeds. Manchester.
Why might that've been, Peter?
Well, I go through
Manningham red-light district
on my way into work.
I'd be hard pushed to avoid it.
Er, Leeds,
I went to not so long ago.
I dropped Sonia off to meet some
friends. Chapeltown, that were.
And what about Manchester?
When?
February.
February...
Why would my car have been
in Manchester in February?
It's not just the car.
These are sightings of males
alone in cars. Thank you.
Well, when in February?
The 16th. A Tuesday.
That wouldn't have been our Peter.
We barely ever go out.
Certainly not on a Tuesday.
Well, the thing is, Mrs Sutcliffe...
You'll have made a mistake.
Peter would have been working.
And if not,
he would've been here... with me.
Would you be willing to provide us
with a handwriting sample?
Aye. Yeah, no problem.
What shoe size are you, Peter?
Why?
Never mind why.
An 8. 8-and-a-half.
You never owned a shoe or a boot
smaller than 8-and-a-half?
Why would I want to do that?
I'm sorry to ask...
..what about prostitutes?
In all of your visits
to these red-light areas,
have you ever used prostitutes?
I wouldn't want to do that either.
We need you to help us find the man
they call the Yorkshire Ripper.
Gather round, everyone,
and listen to the tape.
Nice and quiet now, please, so
that everybody can hear it properly.
I have come here tonight
to play you a tape of the man
who we believe to be
the so-called Yorkshire Ripper.
If you recognise the voice,
don't hesitate in coming forward.
'I'm Jack...'
Listen, then look at the writing.
Who do you know who
might have handwriting like that?
'I have the greatest respect
for you, George...'
This is not a man with devil horns.
'You are no nearer catching me now
than four years ago...'
He's a dad.
A brother.
A son.
'I reckon your boys
are letting you down, George.'
And he lives in one of these houses.
You can help us now.
You can tell us exactly who he is.
Right, well,
sorry to bother you again.
I know you've already spoken
to our colleague DCS Domaille,
but you've also spoken to the man
that we're looking for.
You've spoken to the Ripper.
You heard his voice.
That's right, love.
I don't know if you're aware,
but he's sent a tape,
so we've heard it too now. So...
It would be very helpful for us
if you can confirm that this voice
is the man we're looking for.
There are those in our organisation
don't believe it's him, you see.
It's not him.
Well, let's take a listen first,
shall we?
I don't need to have a listen.
I've heard it on t'news.
It's not him.
Well, let's just listen, shall we?
Carefully,
and then we'll discuss it.
'I'm Jack.
'I see you are still having no luck
catching me.
'I have the greatest respect
for you, George,
'but, Lord,
you are no nearer catching me now
'than four years ago when I started.
'I reckon your boys
are letting you down, George.'
That's not the man who attacked me.
'They can't be much good, can they?
'The only time they came near...'
Well, I think you'll find it is.
No, love. He were a Yorkshireman.
You said it were a gentle voice.
Aye, cos it were. It were soft.
What size feet did he have?
How would I know?
Roughly.
I've got... I've got no idea.
I don't want any messing about here,
Olive.
If the man who attacked you
were not the Ripper,
well, then it's time to come clean
and tell us.
I trust the evidence over some woman
who's been banged about the head.
Sir David.
Ronald.
Jim.
Chief Constable.
Follow me.
"Never an inquiry of this scale
in the annals of police history."
Those were your words
when you announced the launch
of this Project R.
I saw that the other day,
and I thought to myself,
"Aye, I suppose that must be true."
In this country, undoubtedly.
You know, Ron, there comes a point
when your inability
to catch this man
becomes a matter
of national concern.
Well, it's certainly a concern
for all of us
on the West Yorkshire Force.
Our greatest priority.
But I don't know of anyone who
believes this series of crimes
will extend beyond
the north of England.
That's not what he's saying.
Four years, 11 murders.
A succession of Senior Investigating
Officers... No arrests.
No arrests. Barely any suspects,
or have I got that wrong?
That's not entirely...
This is starting to affect
the public's confidence
in the police as a whole,
nationally.
That is what he is saying.
This Project R,
to see it another way,
this is just you highlighting
your own shortcomings.
"We need your help
to catch the Ripper..." ie,
"..because we can't do it
ourselves."
Josephine Whitaker.
She was not a prostitute.
No... Jayne MacDonald.
And yet you maintain that this man
is hunting prostitutes. You insist.
And insist that he's a Geordie.
Those are the findings
of George Oldfield and his team...
But, Ronald...
A very experienced team.
But, Ronald!
The buck stops with you.
This is on you.
Downing Street called me.
Asked whether this wasn't the time
for the Met to get involved.
An internal review from Jim here,
perhaps.
To which I said no.
Such an imposition
could never be possible.
Not unless Ronald Gregory
could be persuaded to meet with us
and, er, sanction such a thing
personally.
His shoe size were an 8.
He said 8, 8-and-a-half.
And put that he's a lorry driver,
so he'll have access to tools.
Gap in his teeth.
This is Marilyn Moore's file.
Photofit done December '77.
What do you wanna do?
Only about half of the people
whose voices we like
have given a writing sample.
This one's not far off.
The G's and the P's.
But then again, "You say seven,
but remember Preston '75."
The Y's are completely different.
Right, so we should eliminate that
and move on, yeah? David?
David?
What date was this sent?
This first letter to Oldfield?
It was, erm... last year. Erm...
March 8th, '78.
Yeah.
And when was Donna DeAngelo found?
DeAngelo was, er,
found after the letter came...
April 10th, '78.
Yeah, April 10th, '78.
So, the letter is 8th of March.
DeAngelo is found 10th of April.
So we have McCann, one.
Jackson, two. Richardson, three.
Atkinson, four. MacDonald, five.
Jordan, six. Rytka, seven.
And then March 8th, '78...
The letter.
And then the letter. It says,
"You say seven
but remember Preston '75."
Meaning, er, Harrison's linked.
Meaning eight.
And then... on the 10th of April,
Donna DeAngelo is found
underneath the mattress.
David, where are you going
with this?
DeAngelo becomes number nine.
She was found April 10th,
a month after the letter arrived.
But here's the question -
how long had poor Donna DeAngelo
been lying dead
underneath that mattress?
Two months.
Meaning she was killed...
Before the letter was sent.
Now, here's a man who is keen
on making sure Oldfield
gets the total number of victims
right.
So why no mention of DeAngelo?
Why does our man
with the Geordie accent
fail to mention so recent a victim?
Because he doesn't know about her.
And why doesn't our man with the
Geordie accent know about her...?
Because he's not the Ripper.
HUBBUB OF CONVERSATIONS,
TELEPHONES RINGING
Meg, I need to get...
That's OK.
So he lives where, sorry?
Newtown Farm Estate?
And what's his name, please?
Is Nunn in?
No, I don't think so.
Sir.
I think we might have something.
Lorry driver. From Bradford.
I visited him last week.
Geordie accent?
He's a dead ringer
for t'Marilyn Moore Photofit.
Shoe size is close,
but here's the bit that gets me.
This is from t'Jackson scene.
Now, we only noticed this
the other day.
The right boot, 8, faded. Look.
Like he's been using that
bit of his foot more than t'rest.
Well, he's a lorry driver, in't he?
So he'll have been pressing
on t'pedal.
How many times?
Sir?
Has he got a Geordie fucking accent?
No.
Thank you. That's all I wanted.
TV: 'The body of Barbara Leach,
'a 20-year-old university student
from Kettering
'was found on Monday afternoon.
'She left the Mannville Arms
around one o'clock
'and was walking home alone in the
dark, when somewhere along the way
'she met the man
they call the Yorkshire Ripper.
'Miss Leach becomes the 12th victim
and the third in the Bradford area.
'Like Josephine Whitaker,
'Miss Leach
had no links to prostitution
'and was murdered nowhere near
a red-light district.'
What's this?
She was a student. Like Jackie.
In Leeds?
Bradford. She was just walking home.
'The truth is,
they couldn't do much to stop him.
'For, even with his voice on tape,
his handwriting
'and the evidence of 12 murders,
they still don't know who he is,
'leaving many women afraid to walk
the streets at night.'
I don't go out to pubs and clubs.
'It's not just pubs and clubs,
it's anywhere.'
And if you do go out,
go out in a group or a pair.
But never alone. D'you understand?
'Mam, I get it.'
I don't want anything
to happen to me either.
'I love you.'
I love you, too.
'Yeah. Bye.'
OK, bye.
I'll be one minute.
GIRLS CHATTING
Have you seen this?
Look at her. She's just a child.
No, you daft 'apeth.
No, the article on t'other page.
Oh, right.
All the papers are saying the same.
They're all saying
they've not got a clue.
It proves nothing.
It's a vital detail.
If we spent our time worrying
about what criminals didn't tell us,
we'd drive ourselves fucking daft!
He's also stopped
going for prostitutes
in case you hadn't noticed.
He's stopped cos we've driven him
out of t'red-light districts.
Maybe we should stop patrolling
them, hm?
Say that again?
Well, he might come back,
stop going after innocent lasses.
I can't believe I'm hearing this!
I do not think the man on the tape
is the Ripper.
You've made that clear.
I want that on record.
But you're wrong.
There are things in those letters
and on that tape
that only the Ripper would know.
You not heard about
the similarities between our letters
and the ones sent to the inquiry
in London?
Yes, I have, thank you.
Or has that passed you by and all?
Remember who you're
fucking talking to!
Commander Nevill's here.
TELEPHONES RINGING,
ANIMATED CONVERSATIONS
Sir. Mr Oldfield's asked me
to find you a desk somewhere quiet
so the noise in the incident room
doesn't put you off your work.
If you'd like to follow me?
TAXI DRIVER: Come on, ladies.
GIRLS LAUGHING
All right, ladies,
that's us full now.
You'll have to wait.
Oh, come on.
I'm only round the corner.
Sorry, love.
I'll be back in 30 minutes.
Get the door, love.
Will he be waiting up?
Oh, no. Thank goodness.
He's not been in the house
for a while.
Oh, Meg.
TELEPHONE RINGS
Don't you dare.
Night, love.
Thank you.
Millgarth incident room,
how can I help?
RADIO: 'Hi, Jenny, you're on KBC.
What's your question?'
'Well, what I'd like to know is,
'what if he just put on
a Geordie accent for the tape?
'That's what nobody
seems to be saying.'
'That's a really good question,
Jenny.
'We've been ask...'
POLICEMEN CHATTING
GIRLS LAUGHING
MEN DRUNKENLY SHOUTING
DISTANTLY
GLASS SHATTERS
SHOUTING AND SHRIEKING
DISTANTLY
DOG BARKS AGGRESSIVELY
RUSTLING,
BIRD CRIES
Hey...
Excuse me. Hey, wait a minute.
You dropped your keys, love.
There. See?
You're a lucky lady.
Thank you.
D'you wanna go for a drink?
No.
Oh, go on.
No. Thank you.
SHE BREATHES SHAKILY
YELLING IN DISTANCE
TELEPHONE RINGS
Grange Moor.
'George? It's Mike Dugdale.'
We're running a piece tomorrow
saying that...
..we've lost faith.
'The nationals are saying the same.'
George. It's out of control.
All the things I've done for you.
It's nothing personal.
'He's killing the wives
and daughters of our readers.
'They're fucking terrified.'
Who was that?
TELEPHONE RINGS
GRUFFLY: What?
'Hello? Mr Oldfield?'
Speaking.
Oh, erm, this is Mrs MacDonald.
Irene MacDonald.
'Jayne's mother.'
Mrs MacDonald.
How can I help you, love?
Well, you know you came
to see us that time,
and you gave us your number and you
said we were to call you anytime.
Aye, I meant it.
'Only... we heard the tape,
you see.'
The voice.
And it got us thinking...
Now, this were five,
six years ago now,
but we went on holiday to Scotland.
'And there were this man
staying at the hotel...
'..and he were a Geordie.
'James, he were called. Or Jim.
'Do you need a minute
to find a pen?'
Thank you.
'Jim. Average height. Fair hair.'
FAINTLY: Thank you.
'Thank you, Mrs MacDonald.'
Only... They want us to think now,
don't they?
'It said in t'paper...
he could be anybody.'
Nobody knows.
'Thank you, Mrs MacDonald.'
And I meant what I said, you know,
if...
..you think of anything,
then you just call me, all right?
GRUNTS
No woman is safe,
with bank workers, students,
baby sitters all being killed?
Well, what women need to do,
and George has said this,
is make sure they do not
go out alone, late at night.
Is that the official advice?
Well, that's just common sense.
How would you best characterise the
system that you have in place here?
The system's the same system
as is put in place for any murder.
But this being several murders,
that system has become overburdened.
"Overburdened." "At a maximum."
Depends what word you wanna use.
I want to use the word overburdened.
We haven't spent all this money
and done nothing.
We've tried to catch the man
who's committing all these murders.
So if I were to ask you
to bring me all the evidence
pertaining to a Joe Bloggs,
how would you do that?
That depends.
Does Joe Bloggs drive a car?
No idea. Sorry?
That's what I mean.
You tell me.
Well, you'd look under B,
for Bloggs. Then J, for Joe.
Then it'll come down to
which Joe Bloggs you're on about,
cos there'll be more than one,
name like that.
It's 12-hour days, six days a week.
But we don't mind that,
cos we want him caught.
And nobody does more hours
than Mr Oldfield.
Where is Mr Oldfield?
Well, I've been told
he's got a chest infection.
Meaning he's unfit to lead?
I can't think of anyone fitter.
What would George say
if, in my report,
I were to recommend
a different approach here?
A new way of doing things?
Honestly?
Please.
I think he'd say
you should get back to London,
concentrate on catching
your own Ripper first,
then once that's done,
you'd be more than welcome
to come back up here
and tell us all how it's done.
Is there anything else about
this case that you want to tell me?
Anything you feel
we could learn from?
Only that...
SHE SIGHS
Go on.
Only that they say
there's been 12 victims.
But you think there are more?
There will be.
People's lives
will carry on being destroyed.
Until they catch this man.
No.
Long after that.
TV: 'Tonight, we bring you a special
report on the Yorkshire Ripper,
'asking if the police
are looking for the wrong man.
'Some senior police officers
and other observers
'fear that the investigators could
be so entrenched in their beliefs
'about the kind of man
they're hunting,
'that the killer
has been overlooked.'
JACK: 'I reckon your boys
are letting you down, George.
'They can't be much good, can they?'
'It has been four years
since the first killing,
'nearly two months
since the murder of Barbara Leach
'and the Yorkshire Ripper
investigation needs a fresh mind.
'Many are feeling
that George Oldfield,
'who recently stepped back from the
investigation due to health issues,
'has become too close and too
personally involved in the case
'to view the matter objectively.
'Tonight, we take a look
at what has been going wrong
'for the UK's biggest manhunt.'
What Jasper means
is that nobody in this room
works for the Probation Service
itself, we're volunteers.
I'm Ruth. This is Tina, Tony
and, of course, Jasper,
who is our chair.
We visit prisoners.
Prisoners who don't have
anyone else to visit them...
and prisoners' partners,
for support.
Everyone does what they can
but we can always do more.
Tonight is just an opportunity
for us all to meet
and for anyone to ask any questions.
Yes?
Do we get to choose who we visit?
Well, I don't want to go see a...
some kind of pervert.
It's a very good question. Erm...
you don't have to meet anyone
you don't want to.
But what I would say is...
depending on how long
they've served,
the man that you meet in prison
is not necessarily
the man who committed the crime.
But if you're unsure,
it's better to know.
If you sign up and don't turn up,
you're not letting us down...
..it's the prisoners.
But a good question, thank you.
Anybody else?
OK, well, I'll pass it back to you,
Jasper.
I've been reading up.
I think it's important
people do this.
Why are you so certain?
Because punishment's not enough.
My dad says it's too good for some.
There's no point
just locking people away,
whatever terrible thing
they might have done.
They need to get better.
So we can all get better.
Or... does it not work like that?
It doesn't work like that, Jackie,
but I rather think it should.
SOBS
MUFFLED SOB
SOBBING
GEORGE: What were her name?
Thanks for letting me know, Dick.
TELEPHONE RINGS
Can you tell me
what sort of accent he's got?
They could have saved her.
What?
Two students found her handbag on
the road at ten o'clock last night.
The bag had blood on it.
They've given it to the police
and they've told 'em
to look for Jackie,
look for her straight away,
and they've done nothing!
They've not looked for her.
SOBS
No, no! She might've been alive.
She might've been alive...
So sorry...
RONALD: Good afternoon,
ladies and gentlemen.
We have already made a statement,
and as the investigation is ongoing,
we will only be taking
a limited number of questions.
ALL SHOUT AT ONCE
Had you looked for her
at the point you found the handbag,
there's a chance
she might have survived.
Is this true?
It's easy to say they should have
found the body sooner.
Maybe they should.
But what should've been done
and, with hindsight,
what might have been done,
is, of course, pure conjecture.
Should Scotland Yard
be taking over the inquiry now?
Scotland Yard sent one of their very
best men to see us not long ago,
and I don't think
it would be an understatement
to say that he was rather impressed
by what he saw.
Chief Constable!
CLAMOURING VOICES
Oh, hell, what are they doing here?
REPORTERS CLAMOURING
What makes them think that
we would ever want to talk to them?
What if we can say something
that makes her be more careful?
Who be more careful?
The next lass.
I want to ask everyone,
not just in Leeds or around Leeds,
but the whole of the country,
to please help us find the person
who killed my daughter.
He could live in a mansion,
or a block of flats
or down the street.
Perhaps he lives in your house.
He lives somewhere.
He works for someone.
But please... please think.
Shall I put the kettle on?
Doreen?
Doreen.
What are you doing?
Doreen, what...
Doreen...?
MUSIC: 'Bridge Over Troubled Water'
by Peggy Lee
♪ When you're weary
♪ Feeling small
♪ When tears
♪ Are in your eyes
♪ I will dry them all... ♪
SOBS SOFTLY
♪ I'm on your side... ♪
OK, if everyone's ready,
let's go and meet
on the front lawns,
and we'll walk into town from there.
All right, let's do it. Come on!
♪ And friends just can't be found
♪ Like a bridge
♪ Over troubled water
♪ I will lay me down... ♪
CHANTING: Reclaim the nights!
Reclaim the nights!
♪ Over troubled water
♪ I will lay me down... ♪
CHANTING: Women unite,
reclaim the nights!
♪ Sail on silver girl... ♪
CHANTING CONTINUES
♪ Sail on by
♪ Your time has come to shine
♪ All your dreams are on their way
♪ See how they shine... ♪
CHANTING: Wherever we go!
♪ If you need a friend
♪ I'm sailing right behind
♪ Like a bridge
♪ Over troubled water
♪ I will ease your mind
♪ Like a bridge
♪ Over troubled water
♪ I will ease your mind... ♪
CHANTING: Women unite!
Reclaim the night!
Women unite! Reclaim the night!
CHANTING ECHOES
AND FADES
CHANTING ON TELEVISION
'Five years is too long.
No, it's been going on too long.
'If they can't...
If they haven't caught him yet,
'I don't think they ever will.'
He won't be back in a hurry.
No.
But he'll turn up somewhere.
Business?
How much?
Ten pound.
With a rubber.
Go on, then.
Subtitles by accessibility@itv.com