RADIO TUNING
'Well, The Beatles are getting back
together again, then...'
WOMEN CHANTING,
RADIO TUNING
'We're just 90 seconds away
from our breakfast sequence.
'Radio Leeds AM.'
'The British people,
in clear and unmistakeable terms,
'have made their historic decision
'that Britain shall remain
a member of the European Community.'
'You see, since 1972, world prices
of commodities and raw materials
'have more than doubled.'
'We are suffering
as we haven't in 25 years
'from a rise in the cost of living.'
REPORTER:
How are you managing for money?
Well, we're desperate now.
We're on... I'm on me last £5 now,
and then that's it.
I've spent all our savings now,
so it's these next few weeks
that we'll really feel.
Ever since the end of the disastrous
seven-week strike here
earlier this year...
Have called for strike action
from Monday.
The standard of living
of the humblest and the poorest
being attacked and eaten away.
I think this is the closest
we've ever been
to a revolution in this country
for years.
CHILDREN GIGGLING
WHISPERS: Go back to sleep.
WHISPERS: Richard.
Richard!
She's not come home.
VEHICLE RUMBLES
DRIVER: There you go.
Thank you, love.
Ta, love.
She'll be on the next one.
Stop saying that.
Sonia and Richard, yeah?
So, Mummy said
she weren't going out,
but you think she might've done?
Had she done that before, love?
Left you on your own?
And did Mummy ever say
where she were going?
Or who she were seeing?
What about Daddy?
Are Mummy and Daddy still friends?
She'd been slipping out at night,
apparently.
But not through front door,
through here.
So neighbours wouldn't see her
leaving kids.
Who told you that?
Neighbours.
Four kids between seven and three.
We're calling the children's home,
see if they can't take 'em.
Least till we can work out
where the Dad is.
Explain to them what's gone on.
What you thinking?
I'm thinking... them little ones
went to bus stop to wait,
they only just missed her.
Cheers, mate.
Sir.
♪ Only when I fly alone
♪ Was all I could reply ♪
And all... ♪
MUSIC FADES,
BRAKES SQUEAK
MUFFLED MUSIC
CONTINUES
Oh, that reminds me,
we're off out tomorrow night,
me and your mam.
You'll need to look
after your brother and sister.
No, we're not. Painting town red.
Eh?
No, we are not.
It's Eric Owen's 40th.
How long has that been on t'cards?
40 years, presumably.
Oh.
HE CHUCKLES
SHE INHALES,
CLEARS THROAT
I don't do reading.
I know,
but you can see what colour it is,
and that's third
we've had this week.
You'll have to tell Eric we can't go
cos we can't bloody afford it.
He's my oldest mate.
I've said that we're going...
and we are.
CAR DOOR SLAMS
At 7:41 this morning,
the body of a 28-year-old woman,
Wilma McCann,
was found
in the Prince Philip playing fields
behind Scott Hall Avenue
in Chapeltown.
Wilma had been stabbed 15 times.
Two further lacerations were found
on t'back of her head.
Impact wounds from some kind of
tool. Hammer, spanner, maybe.
I'm telling you this
not to shock you...
..because
I want you all to appreciate
what one person did to another
person in our city last night.
And it's our job, it's your job...
to find out who they are
and why this happened.
SOFTLY:
I think cos she was an whore.
Little louder, John,
so all t'class can hear.
I said she died, sir,
because she was a prostitute.
Vice have never heard of her.
Don't mean she wasn't one.
She'd already been done
for drunk and disorderly.
She might've been a prostitute...
..she might not.
Might've liked a drink, might not.
But nobody, whoever they are,
deserves to die
like Wilma died last night.
It starts now. 4pm October 30th,
and it don't end
till one of us catches the bastard.
MUTTERING
Right, priorities now...
Get Dugdale from t'post.
..Wilma's movements on the night.
Door-to-door,
and a fingertip search of
the home and the surrounding area.
Any questions?
No? Good. On you get.
CHATTER
Problem.
Go on.
Perception.
You saw for yourself
how it was out there.
PHONE RINGS
Aye.
'I've got Mike Duffield.' Go on.
'Hello, mate.'
Mike. 'Yes.'
I might have something
for one of your photographers
on this Chapeltown job.
Have you got a pen?
Dennis, we're a newspaper,
we've got stationary.
Afternoon.
LADY: Hello there.
Oh.
What's that?
TOY BELL RINGS
This your favourite?
What about you lot?
What's your favourite toys?
Is Mummy coming soon?
Mummy's not coming, love.
Mummy's had an accident.
Was she hurt?
She was. That's right.
So where is she now?
Well...
She's up in heaven.
She says, "You're not to worry."
She's in heaven...
and she's waiting for you.
All right?
Now...
Why don't we take a photograph...
of you...
with your absolute
number one favourite toys?
How about it?
SHUTTER CLICKS
OK, everyone, looking here.
Perfect. OK. And...
SHUTTER CLICKS
That's it.
If we're to get
any help from the public...
Just a couple more.
..that's the message.
Look here, that's right.
She were a mother of four kids.
Prostitute don't come into it.
Straight at the camera.
SHUTTER CLICKS
Thank you.
MAN: Right, off you go!
INAUDIBLE
Well?
Right.
Last sighting of her... is right
the way back down Meanwood Road
just after last orders and
then nothing between there and here.
A bloody field next to a car park.
There you go.
That's your first clue.
That's why no-one sees her on t'bus
or walking all the way up t'hill.
And that's why he brings her here.
Not to some field...
next to a car park...
to a car park next to a field.
The killer was driving.
He could've been on foot.
He could have followed her home
after seeing her in t'club.
Who goes to a club
wi' a spanner and knife?
Aye, fair point.
QUIET TALKING
MUSIC: 'I Love To Love'
by Tina Charles
Here we go.
HE WHISTLES TO SONG
MAN: Eh!
Hey-hey-hey!
Where's Linda and t'rest of t'wives?
Eh?
Am I just your lift home,
is that it?
Yeah.
Look.
Neil found that.
Hm? He said "Give that to Mam.
"Tell her to put a song
on t'jukebox. Cheer her sen up."
Right! He-heyy!
Now we begin. Here we go!
Fucking hell!
MUSIC: Sold My Rock 'n' Roll
(Gave It For Funky Soul)
CHATTERING
Excuse me, love.
INDISTINCT
SONG CONTINUES
NEW SONG PLAYS
Hm?
I've seen you before.
Hm. All right.
How does it, er, work, then? Er...
You got a place where we can go?
How much?
MUSIC AND CHATTERING
CONTINUES
The last confirmed sighting
of the dead woman, Wilma McCann,
was on the corner of Meanwood Road,
at 1am.
What we want now
is for anyone who was either in
or driving through
the Chapeltown area at that time
to make themselves known to us
immediately. Wilma was a mother.
Her kids were waiting for her,
but she never made it home.
Please, if you have
any information... come forward...
for their sake.
Er, Chief Constable Gregory's here.
I can see.
I saw
the Mercedes parked up outside.
Here to check up on me?
I'm here to do nothing of the kind.
The lovely Jenny
has provided a cup of tea,
and I'm... familiarising myself
with this map of yours.
This arrow here,
I was wondering, represents...
Last known sighting of Wilma McCann.
And this is where she was killed?
Sir.
And all you've got to do is
figure out what happened in between.
So... you are here
to check up on me.
I'm dropping in to make sure
you've got everything you need.
Sir...
we have a list of 29 suspects...
we found in her notebook.
We're working our way through them
as we speak.
What's interesting about this case,
it's... not been motivated by sex.
He's killed her first. But it's not
purely violence, either...
Dennis. You are confident,
and I have every confidence in you.
No, the reason I dropped by
was to make sure you don't try
and duck the Christmas drinks
for the third year running. Drinks?
This new merger -
chaps I'd like you to meet.
Well, sir, I... I shall certainly
see if I'm free that night.
You are free. According
to the lovely Jenny, that is.
You can give me
the proper update then.
TV ON
Mum!
CAROL SINGERS SING
SILENT NIGHT
♪ All is calm
♪ All is bright
♪ Round yon virgin
Mother and child... ♪
Shall I get money?
Yeah. No.
Yeah, in my bag.
You don't have to!
♪ Holy infant
So tender and mild
♪ Sleep in heavenly... ♪
You've not got any change.
There we are, then.
You've only got a note.
♪ Sleep in heavenly peace. ♪
Thank you. Thank you so much!
Very kind.
♪ At the sight... ♪
What were that? Eh?
What the fuck were that?!
What the fuck do you think it were?
You're giving me a hard time,
for what?
So you can start chucking money
about?!
I am not...
We're in over our heads!
I am not having those people -
her across t'road -
I am not having her thinking
we don't have money. But we don't!
And I am not... SHE WHISPERS:
..having them kids suffer any more
than they already have done.
I want our life just to be normal.
We're in over our heads.
You're the one saying it.
So go on, then, eh?
What we gonna do?
DOOR SLAMS
SHE SIGHS,
PHONE RINGS
29 suspects interviewed,
29 suspects eliminated.
Ex-husband took a bit of finding,
but, nah, he's in the clear an' all.
We've handed out 10,000 leaflets,
and we've gone door to-door
on every house
in a half-mile radius.
Pubs?
And the pubs, aye. We've gone
round them twice. And every shop.
The only new witness is a bloke
who sold her chips and curry sauce.
When?
Just after one. She were pissed.
That's all he remembers.
Right. So we keep going.
Door to door.
Go back to the pubs. Print
more leaflets, print more posters,
set up even more roadblocks.
You see,
I think if we end up doing that...
Has to happen now, Jim...
else it'll fade from people's minds.
No, you're right. You're right.
I need to tell you something.
What?
SHE SIGHS
There were this man
at Eric's birthday,
when you were at t'bar...
this good-looking man.
And when I went for a dance,
he went for a dance.
And when I went to t'toilets...
so did he.
If this is what I think it is,
I'll kill you.
You do know that, don't you?
Just let me finish.
I'll kill him an' all.
Sydney. I swear to God!
Well, I could've done.
I could've done something,
and... well, why shouldn't I?
It's not like we ever do,
ever since Derek died.
I'd've been within my rights...
No, you wouldn't. I didn't.
No? I didn't, no.
Because he offered money.
He thought he'd seen me before
at, um... Spencer Place,
with the working girls.
He thought what...?
He even took out a £5 note.
£5, Sydney.
£5 for how long would it have been?
Five minutes?
No.
No, you're my wife.
They've sent a summons.
The mother of my children.
And someone has to provide for them.
It's Christmas, Syd.
No.
We've got your family coming.
How're we even gonna start to pay
for all that?
MAN: Just routine, sir,
regarding a murder that took place
here some five or so weeks ago now.
INAUDIBLE SPEECH
Call the incident room. Good to go.
Evening, sir.
You all right?
Just routine,
regarding a murder that took place
here some five weeks or so ago now.
Do you recognise this lass at all?
Sorry, when did you say?
October 30th, early hours.
TV ON
PHONE RINGS
TV: 'You've cheered up, any road.'
0406?
Oh, hello, love. Let me try him.
Hang on a minute.
Who is it? It's Jim.
Shall I tell him to ring back?
Why? Because it's Emmerdale Farm.
No, no.
Jim? 'Now, then, Dennis,
we've got a witness. Lorry driver.
'We're bringing him in now.'
On me way.
Ready?
You look nice.
You never say that normally.
Don't you dare say it now.
I'll wait in t'bar.
Syd?
Did you take t'tools out of t'back?
WOMAN: All right, love?
CAR DOOR CLOSES
MAN: 'I thought
she were soliciting.'
You can tell by the way they stand.
Especially that time of night.
I see 'em along there all the time,
you see -
it's on my way out to the M62.
But this one here...
she's not on t'pavement,
she's right in front of me,
right in t'middle of t'road.
Her hair weren't like that,
though. It were darker.
So, go on, you drove past her?
No. No. I was...
You picked her up.
No. Now is this something
that you do all the time, or...
Let him speak, Jim.
I were thinking about it.
About picking her up.
No crime in thinking about it.
I even parked up.
But when she came over to t'window,
I could tell
she were too pissed for it.
Could hardly stand still.
I'm not having her chucking up in
my cab, you see, it's only on lease.
So you just leave her there?
Drunk, in t'middle of t'road? No.
That's how it sounds,
t'way you're describing it.
This is why I wanted to talk to you.
So, I've decided better of it,
so I'm expecting a bit of stick as
I pull away, but I don't get any...
..cos she's already got
another punter.
He's pulled in right behind me.
Another lorry?
A car. And she goes with him.
Did you see t'driver?
No.
But it were a Corsair. A Corsair
or a Fastback. Summat like that.
So, why has it taken you a month
to come forward with all this?
Well, I live in Rochdale.
This is t'first I've heard of it.
You're talking
like this is a well-known thing.
HE SIGHS
How much, pet?
Five.
All right.
Where?
Down 'ere.
♪ Bye, bye, baby, baby, goodbye
♪ Bye, baby, baby, bye, bye
♪ Bye, bye, baby, don't make me cry
Bye, baby, baby... ♪
LAUGHTER FROM PUB
Knickers off.
Money first.
I've only got four.
I said five.
I were only joking.
Now... turn round.
UNZIPS TROUSERS
UNDOES BELT
HE MOANS
MUSIC PLAYS IN PUB
CAR DOOR SLAMS
QUIET CHATTERING
Gents, refresh the drinks?
Dennis.
Sir. Good turnout.
Well, that's the merger.
Not just the city boys this year,
you've got the country lads as well.
Not enough cheese and pineapple
in West Yorkshire.
There's someone
I'd like to introduce you to.
Dennis, I'd like to introduce you
to George Oldfield.
No introduction required.
Hello, Dennis, how are you?
All right.
You still on this prostitute thing?
Well, we don't know
if she was a prostitute, but, er...
Oh, he is.
He's got half our DCs over with him
at Millgarth, helping him.
Not quite...
but I know what you mean.
Here's hoping you get your man.
He will. He'll have the bugger
banged up by New Year's Eve.
Isn't that right, Dennis?
That's the idea.
Well, I find if you don't solve a
murder in the first couple of days,
it's an uphill struggle after that,
in't it?
Oh, maybe that's just me.
You're more involved in rural crime.
That's right, in't it?
George covers half of Yorkshire.
Farmland. That sort of thing.
Now, now, chaps.
'Tis the season and all that.
Merry Christmas.
I've got a list
of all Corsairs and Fastbacks.
Only slight problem is
there's 700 Corsairs
and 900 Fastbacks.
And that's just in Leeds...
Dennis...
T'killer might not live in Leeds.
Might live further afield...
Dennis! It's the Christmas do.
How many men do you know
don't own a hammer?
Look, I'm being serious.
Enjoy your drink.
Take five minutes off.
You'll catch him. You always do.
MUSIC: 'Lonely This Christmas'
by Mud
CHATTERING
Thank you.
You like it?
Yeah, it's nice, thank you!
It's a talking doll!
Oh, thank you!
It talks! Maybe as much as you!
It's a jumper. Thank you, Mum.
What did you get?
INAUDIBLE
Oh, it's nice. Right size?
Yeah, it should fit. Thank you.
Thank you!
♪ ..Without you to hold
♪ It'll be lonely this Christmas
Lonely and cold. ♪
Pat's got some news.
Oh, aye?
Well, shall you tell them
or shall I?
Well, she and Ken have been
courting now for, how long is it,
five months?
Eight months.
Last Sunday, Ken came round
whilst Warren was washing the car.
At first, we thought
there'd been an accident
cos Ken never comes round
on his own,
but he wanted to ask
Warren's permission, you see.
He wanted to ask for Pat's hand.
Oh... Pat!
And Warren liked that.
Oh, I bet he did.
Yeah, that is lovely.
Congratulations, Pat.
Thank you.
Both of you. Aww.
Congratulations, Pat. Thank you.
Give my best to Ken.
Will do.
Cheers.
Cheers, yes.
Well, go on. Ask her.
I wanted to know
if Bubs'd be a bridesmaid.
It'd be her and Carol.
Please!
I think she'd quite like that.
LAUGHING
I mean, it will mean
a bridesmaid's dress,
but t'wedding in't till March,
so there's plenty of time to save,
and you don't have to buy new.
No. Is Carol getting new?
Yeah, Carol will be, but...
She will be.
Yeah. Well, then Bubs will too.
You mustn't feel pressurised.
I don't.
They do 'em second hand.
Yeah, well, there's no need.
Well, how much are they?
It doesn't matter how much they are.
It's Pat's day, so we're getting it,
and we'll get it new.
DOORBELL RINGS
I'll get that.
Oh!
MAN: Hello!
She'll look lovely.
CHATTERING IN HALLWAY
Morecambe And Wise are on tonight.
They didn't do one last year, so...
PHONE RINGING
Leave it.
0406?
Oh, right.
SHE SIGHS
Right. Thanks.
Am I keeping it warm, then?
Anything else you need?
No.
Deal was you'd call at three,
and that's what you've done.
Merry Christmas, then.
Aye. Merry Christmas, love.
Hey, it's Morecambe And Wise
tonight.
That's what they say.
SHE CHUCKLES
PHONE RINGS
Incident room.
The Wilma McCann case, that's right.
You did...? Erm, hang on.
Just let me get this down.
Sorry, so what time was it?
1:00AM?
Right, Meanwood Road,
the big turning...
And what sort of colour was it?
Make and model.
Green, maybe.
Yes, she was wearing flares.
White flares. That's right.
No, that's very helpful.
Thank you, take care.
No! Make and model!
Didn't have to, sir. She told me.
He's a Chapeltown regular,
and he drives a green Land Rover.
There aren't 965 of those,
are there?
That's good.
That's very good.
How much is the dress?
Eight fifty.
Then there's the shoes, jewellery.
All adds up.
Right, listen to me. Sell t'telly.
The telly's not worth owt.
Washing machine.
Oh! We need t'washing machine!
Or the van! Listen to
what I'm saying to you, right?
I-I can't take it anymore!
Ah! You can't take it?
You can't take it?!
HE SOBS
It's three times, that's 15 quid.
I'll get it done tonight,
and then it's over with, yeah?
It's finished for good.
Hm.
Thought you'd given up.
I have.
WOMAN: Ta, love.
CHATTERING
PHONE RINGS
Sir?
RADIO: 'All units, be on the lookout
for any men driving a Corsair
'or a dark-coloured Land Rover
in the Chapeltown area.'
May or may not be green, remember.
Yeah.
Hang on.
He's gotta be out here.
It's your turn.
You're all right. He's a regular.
Not so keen on him.
All right?
How much?
It's a fiver.
You hear anything, anything at all,
call me.
What's the latest we can ring?
No such thing.
Here we go. John!
Go, go, go! All units, go, go, go!
SIREN BLARES
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Out the car! Out the car!
Get out the car.
On your knees! Knees!
Stay there, fella, stay there!
We've got him, Les,
we've bloody got him!
MAN: How much?
It's five.
Subtitles by accessibility@itv.com