'Previously on "Hannibal"...'
How do you know Hannibal
is in Florence?
Botticelli.
You're drawing them to you, aren't you?
I'm not searching for Hannibal.
I know exactly where he is.
I will pay three million dollars
for the doctor alive.
I'm Inspector Rinaldo Pazzi.
Dr Lecter is careful. He will strike.
You are going to be caught.
It has already been set into motion.
Jack.
He's wounded. And he's worried.
No, Hannibal doesn't worry.
Knowing he's in danger won't rattle him
any more than killing does.
If Rinaldo Pazzi had decided to do
his job as an officer of the law,
he would've determined very quickly
that he was Hannibal Lecter.
It would've taken thirty minutes
to get a warrant.
All those resources
were denied to Pazzi.
As soon as he decided to sell Hannibal,
he became a bounty hunter.
Outside the law and alone.
Well, here we are:
outside the law and alone.
Have you told la polizia
they're looking for Hannibal Lecter?
They're motivated to find Dr Fell
inside the law.
Knowing who he is, what he's worth,
it'll just coax them out of bounds.
- It'd be a free-for-all.
- And Hannibal will slip away.
Will you slip away with him?
A part of me will always want to.
You have to cut that part out.
Of course you found him here.
Not because of the exhibit,
but because of the crowd it attracts.
You had him, Jack. He was beaten.
Why didn't you kill him?
Maybe I need you to.
I want to be able to draw these streets
from memory.
I want to be able to draw
the Palazzo Vecchio and the Duomo.
You won't be coming back here
for a very long time.
Memories of Florence will be
all I have.
Florence is where I became a man.
I see my end in my beginning.
All of our endings can be found
in our beginnings.
History repeats itself.
And there is no escape.
You've packed lightly.
I've packed for you.
This is where I leave you.
Or more accurately,
where you leave me.
This isn't how I intended
to say goodbye.
I imagined it differently.
I didn't.
I knew that you intended to eat me.
And I knew that you had
no intention of eating me hastily.
It would be a shame
not to savour you.
I have not marinated long enough
for your tastes.
When they come for you...
And they will come.
What will you say of me?
I will help you tell the version
of events you want to be told.
I will help you
because you asked me to.
You may make a meal of me yet,
Hannibal.
But not today.
Pig tails, cut into sections to give
the aesthetic of fingers cut at the joint.
Finger food. Huh!
Hands are how we touch the world.
They're tactile, sensual.
Remove an arm and your patient
will still feel phantom digits.
Imagine how Dr Lecter will feel
when he's watching you
nibble on his fingers.
Oh, poetry, Cordell, poetry.
In a ginger-black vinegar sauce.
Mm... It's mostly skin and bone.
The actual fingers will have more meat.
Then there's the marrow.
Here it is in a fermented bean sauce.
Ugh! I prefer the ginger.
No, no... Spit.
A Buddhist singing bowl. The gong
represents the start of a new day.
Buddhists don't eat meat.
This isn't meat.
This is man.
Papa always used to say
meat was a people business.
He was a pioneer in livestock production,
I'm sure he's eaten someone.
I must admit,
I tremble at the notion myself.
I find there's something reassuring
about you eating Dr Lecter.
It makes you the apex predator.
I like that, "apex predator".
- We could Peking duck him.
- Oh?
You have to torture a duck to prepare it.
Pump its skin up with air,
then glaze it with a hot honey
and hang it by its neck until it dries.
And then roast until crispy.
Transubstantiation.
I'm here. Tell me.
I feel like I just paid a lot of money
for a dead dago.
The faeces will fly about Pazzi.
Better to get it out that Pazzi was dirty.
They'll take it better if he was dirty.
- Was he dirty?
- Except for this, I don't know.
What if they trace Pazzi back to you?
Oh, I can take care of that.
You took care of Pazzi.
I have little interest
in the expensive piece of meat
twitching at the end
of that electrical cord, Dr Bloom.
Might want to get interested.
Hannibal could disappear too well
and you'd be left with nothing.
Better buy another cop.
Better buy the whole department.
You must be looking for Hannibal Lecter.
One of his patients?
No, not a patient. Where is he?
Seeing how you let yourself in,
forgive me if it's forward for me to ask...
- Who the hell are you?
- Family.
And you've come all the way from home.
Who are you?
I'm his psychiatrist.
Medicinal purposes.
You're like his bird.
I'm his bird, too.
He puts us in cages
to see what we'll do.
Fly away or dash ourselves
dead against the bars.
You haven't flown away.
You are flying right towards him.
How does he inspire such devotion?
You're his psychiatrist.
You could add to what I've learned
from my experience with him,
and from the mute postures
of the dead.
Were you there?
Did you watch
as the wild beast within him
turned from the teat
and entered the world?
I met the beast.
And I saw him grow.
Someone wants to kill him.
More than one someone, I'd say.
What do you want?
I want to cage him.
I thought Will Graham was
Hannibal's biggest mistake.
I wonder if it isn't you.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have to take my medicine.
Mrs Fell, I presume?
My husband is a doctor.
He's been treating my condition.
And what condition is that,
Mrs Fell?
I get confused.
Oh, please!
You need to get over yourself,
whatever self that is, Bedelia.
My name is Lydia Fell.
You expect us to believe
that you somehow lost yourself
in the hot darkness
of Hannibal Lecter's mind?
That Lydia Fell is some construct?
- It's you, isn't it?
- Well, now, I'm really confused.
I don't believe you.
You are not confused, Bedelia.
That is not my name.
You know who you are
and what you've done.
You know exactly how you're going
to wiggle out of it. What is this?
Sedatives? Hypnotics? Ethanol?
Scopolamine? Midazolam?
Same cocktail
Dr Lecter served Miriam Lass?
You've been freebasing your alibi.
And I'm not even mad at you.
To tell the truth,
I'm fairly impressed.
Mostly because
you're still alive.
When this fog of yours clears...
...I'd love to hear
how you managed that.
You say my husband murdered
a Chief Investigator.
Where is the polizia?
Shouldn't they be questioning me?
Don't worry, they will.
They sure are taking their time.
What could possibly be the delay?
No... I have an idea.
- Do you?
- They're being bought.
By the same people
that bought Rinaldo Pazzi.
Interest in my husband
is certainly getting competitive.
Will?
- Will?
- I wonder who will catch him first.
I've made new friends in Italy.
They're cleaning up and starting over.
So, all you need
to concern yourself with now is
what'll happen once Dr Lecter
is in your hands.
You've worked so hard
to give me what I want.
It's only fair to talk about
what Margot wants.
Come sit on Santa's lap.
You know what I want.
The biggest regret of my life is
taking away your ability to create it.
Adoption is a nice thing to do.
No pedigree in buying a Chinese baby.
They're cheaper than shoats.
I wish I could give you a Verger baby.
Our own baby, yours and mine.
We could raise it together.
The last time you said
you wanted to have a baby,
you removed my uterus.
In my defence,
you weaponised your uterus.
You shouldn't have been waving it
around like a loaded pistol.
- I brought it on myself.
- As you so often do, Margot.
But there's a possibility that
I'm still packing loads of viable sperm.
Stumbled across
any viable uteruses lately, hm?
What are you up to, Mason?
I want us to have a baby, Margot.
I could be really good to a child.
I could take parenting classes.
Let's find a way, Margot.
Let's find a way to be a family again.
If I saw you every day forever, Will,
I would remember this time.
Strange seeing you here
in front of me.
Been staring at afterimages of you
in places you haven't been in years.
"To market, to market,
to buy a fat pig.
"Home again, home again,
jiggity-jig."
I wanted to understand you,
before I laid eyes on you again.
I needed it to be clear
what I was seeing.
Where does the difference between
the past and the future come from?
Mine?
Before you and after you.
Yours?
It's all starting to blur.
Mischa?
Abigail?
Chiyoh?
How is Chiyoh?
She pushed me off a train.
Atta girl.
You and I have begun to blur.
Isn't that how you found me?
Every crime of yours...
...feels like one I am guilty of.
Not just Abigail's murder,
every murder stretching
backward and forward in time.
Freeing yourself from me
and me freeing myself from you,
they're the same.
We're conjoined.
I'm curious whether either of us
can survive separation.
Now is the hardest test,
not letting rage and frustration...
...nor forgiveness,
keep you from thinking.
Shall we?
After you.
Mason's ahead of the FBI
in the pursuit of Hannibal Lecter.
Mason has no intention
of ever sharing his lead with the FBI.
I do.
Once he has Hannibal.
There's something I need to get
from Mason before he goes to prison.
Any experience harvesting sperm?
We cannot locate Dr Fell.
Close attention has been brought
to bear on him.
We have eyewitness accounts
of a bloody figure,
matching his description,
running from the scene.
The Italian public have already decided
Il Mostro has killed Rinaldo Pazzi.
A twenty-year-old debt finally paid.
The Italian public is right.
Il Mostro died in prison.
Il Commendator Pazzi had been
assigned to investigate
the disappearance of two men
from the Palazzo Capponi.
My husband knew Professor Sogliato.
We were at his home many times.
We believe your husband was
responsible for the disappearances,
and murdered Pazzi when he came
to the same conclusion.
If you haven't already,
access the ViCAP database at Quantico.
You'll find Dr Fell
on the "Most Wanted" page,
under the name of Hannibal Lecter.
The fingerprints you'll pull
from Pazzi's noose will be his.
If you knew Dr Fell
to be Hannibal Lecter,
why didn't you bring it
to the attention of the Questura?
He had a price on his head.
Pazzi knew about it, tried to sell him.
That kind of money,
I can't blame him. Can you?
You've already been questioned
regarding Rinaldo Pazzi's murder,
Signor Crawford.
Since you're not in Florence on
official FBI business, that will be all.
Not you, Signora Fell.
You stay right where you are.
This is going to hurt.
That bullet is still inside you.
Chiyoh has always been
very protective of me.
Did she kill her tenant?
Or did you?
She did.
Excellent.
You dropped your forgiveness, Will.
You forgive how God forgives.
Would you have done it quickly,
or would you have stopped to gloat?
Does God gloat?
Often.
No. No, no, no, no, no...
Give that a moment.
I can almost taste the butter.
Taste and smell are the oldest senses,
and the closest
to the centre of the mind.
Parts that precede
pity and morality.
They play in the dome of our skulls,
like miracles
illuminated on a church ceiling.
The ceremonies and sights
and exchanges of dinner
can be far more engaging
than theatre.
What's for dinner?
Never ask.
It spoils the surprise.
I don't indulge much in regret,
but... I am sorry to be leaving Italy.
There were things in the Palazzo
Capponi I would've liked to read.
I would have liked to play the clavier
or perhaps compose.
I would've liked
to show you Florence, Will.
The soup isn't very good.
It's a parsley and thyme infusion,
and more for my sake than yours.
Have another sip.
Let that circulate.
Are we expecting company?
Wrong floor.
Will?
He's under the table, Jack.
Your husband left you behind.
I had no reason to run.
I've done nothing wrong.
I hold in my hands the photographs
taken for Dr Fell's state work permit.
Oh, I also have
his French work papers.
Looks different with a beard, no?
- That is not my husband.
- This is Roman Fell.
And this is Lydia Fell.
I am Lydia Fell.
Did you murder her
with your husband?
Or did you just watch?
I am Lydia Fell.
I don't care who you are.
I don't care if you're in your right mind
or your wrong mind, understand?
Those things are inconsequential.
I understand, in this moment,
you do not work for the Questura.
That's a good thing to understand.
I don't want to be seen
as uncooperative.
How you are seen is entirely up to you.
Rescued by the brave Questura, or...
...apprehended.
I have never considered myself
in need of being... rescued.
Until now.
Is your husband still in the city?
My husband was hoping to meet
a friend before he left Florence.
Where?
The nature of the meeting
required privacy.
They will be somewhere
no one is supposed to be.
I've taken the liberty of giving you
something to help you relax.
You won't be able to do
much more than chew,
but that's all you'll need to do.
I didn't have an opportunity to ask you
during our last encounter,
but did you enjoy the exhibition?
A different kind of evil minds museum.
Not that different.
We were supposed to sit down
together at your house in Baltimore.
Just the three of us.
You were to be the guest of honour.
But the menu was all wrong.
Yes, it was.
Jack was the first to suggest
getting inside your head.
Now we both have the opportunity
to chew quite literally...
...what we've only chewed figuratively.
Hannibal...
Stop!
Gentlemen.
Welcome to Muskrat Farm.