'Previously on "Hannibal"...'
You're full of surprises, D.
I find you very mysterious.
I am delighted that
you have taken an interest in me.
- I want to be recognised by you.
- See how magnificent you are.
The man who killed
the Jacobis and the Leedses chose them.
I have to believe
there is a common factor.
Are you familiar with William Blake's
"The Great Red Dragon"?
You're the second person
who's asked to see the Blake today.
As the dragon grows
in strength and glory,
there are families to come.
So whatever he says he wants to do,
you'll take him anyway.
I promise I'll try to make it
as easy on him as I can.
- He ate a painting.
- He ate it?
He ate it up.
The Art Squad in New York snapped to it
when they found out what he ate.
They pulled two partial prints
from the plastic pass he used.
No ID, but it's still the same thumb
that was on Mrs Leeds' eye.
What about the docent at the museum?
He had a sweet touch with her.
She had to have four stitches.
- Mild concussion, but he didn't kill her.
- Why?
He'd have been better off killing her.
And you.
Maybe he's trying to stop.
You think there's a way to push him
to being self-destructive?
- You mean push him toward suicide?
- Suicide suits me just fine.
If he's really trying to stop,
he's not going to kill himself.
How could he be sure his death
would affect whatever's inside him?
You must know something about him
otherwise you wouldn't have found him.
Jack Crawford...
...fisher of men, watching my cork
move against the current.
You got me again.
Hannibal told me where to find him.
He knows.
He knows who the Dragon is.
He probably treated him.
It stunned me the first time I saw it.
Like Blake peeked in your ear
and saw the Red Dragon there.
Coiled inside you. Coiled around you.
This new two-ness with the Dragon,
it's disorienting for you.
Our wills were one.
But not now.
Not since her.
The Dragon has never
spoken to me before.
It was frightening.
What did it say?
It called my name.
It wants her.
If it weren't for the power
of your Becoming,
if it weren't for the Dragon,
you could never have had her.
I put my hand...
...on her beating heart.
Heard the sound of her living voice.
A...living...woman.
How bizarre.
I don't want to give her to the Dragon.
The Dragon is in your belly now.
'You can choose to have her alive.'
You don't have to worry
about feeling love for her.
You can always toss the Dragon
to someone else.
Will Graham...
...interests me.
Odd-looking for an investigator.
Not very handsome, but purposeful.
He has a family.
Save yourself.
Kill them all.
I have a little homework.
Sure.
If I'm keeping you from working,
I can go.
No.
I want you to be here.
I do.
I have some film
that I need to check.
It won't take long.
Hmm. Does it have a soundtrack?
No.
May I keep the music?
Uh-huh.
I think I'll just stretch out here
for a few minutes, if you don't mind.
No, don't move.
I have plenty of room.
Wake me up if I drop off.
Are these your nocturnal animals?
Uh-huh.
Think they know they're being filmed?
No.
- Mum! Mum!
- What?
Something's wrong with the dogs.
They may have got into something
they shouldn't have.
Has there been any changes in their diet?
My husband usually
makes their food from scratch.
But he's out of town
and it's a lot of work,
so I've been feeding them
canned food.
- Was that canned food made in China?
- Is it bad to be made in China?
If you're pet food. Dogs get poisoned
by Chinese pet food all the time.
- Are the dogs going to die?
- No, they're not gonna...
- Are the dogs gonna die?
- No, you got them here really fast.
The activated charcoal should
soak up whatever's in their system.
Bring a sample of what they've been
eating, so we can run some tests.
I'll bring it by tomorrow.
In the meantime, we'll keep the dogs here
overnight and monitor their recovery.
- They should be fine.
- Thank you.
Are you going to tell Dad?
Erm, you know how I always said
that secrets were bad
and you shouldn't keep secrets?
I have an amendment to that,
and we're going to keep
this secret for now.
Just you and me.
You want me to lie?
It's not a lie,
if you keep your mouth shut.
Your dad has enough to worry about
without worrying if I'm going
to poison the dogs again.
I'm not fortune's fool.
I'm yours.
"Behold the Great Red Dragon."
And did you?
The Brooklyn Museum is closed
to the public on Tuesdays,
and researchers are admitted.
You knew that's when
we'd both be going.
A sophisticated intelligence
can forecast many things.
I suppose mine is
sophisticated enough.
He's contacted you.
How do you imagine
he's contacted me?
Personal ads?
Writing notes of admiration
on toilet paper?
There is a family out there
who don't know he's coming.
We can save them.
Tell me who he is.
I don't know who he is.
When you close your eyes, Will,
is it your family you see?
No...
How's he choosing them?
Social media, I imagine.
Can't be too careful
with privacy settings.
Do you know who they are?
Yes.
And you're willing to let them die.
They're not my family, Will.
And I'm not letting them die.
You are.
Wait for me by the car.
Count to a hundred.
If you see anyone else but me,
run for the road.
Forty-four...
Wait here. Stop!
Mum!
Come on, quick!
- I almost killed you! What are you doing?
- Stay down! Get back in the car.
Your mum's in surgery now.
Is there anything else I need
to know to see about Mum?
You're both safe here.
This crazy guy wants to kill you?
No...
Well, we don't know what he wants.
Are you gonna kill him?
No.
I'm gonna catch him.
They'll put him in a mental hospital,
so they can treat him and keep him
from hurting anybody else.
Tommy's mum had this little newspaper.
It said you killed a guy and
you were put in a mental hospital.
Is it true?
Yes, yes.
It bothers you, finding that out?
Because I married your mum?
Then you shouldn't put this guy
in a mental hospital, you should kill him.
I want to watch baseball.
His team playing?
He read about me
in a Freddie Lounds article.
I had to justify myself
to an eleven-year-old.
Resentment's raising
a blister in you, Will.
You think you might lose me
after this, Jack?
You think I might go back
to my family?
- For a minute, I did.
- Right...
Then you realised what I realised,
which is I can't go home.
And neither can Molly and Walter,
not until the Red Dragon is
out of the way.
Sorry to interrupt.
You have a telephone call.
It's your lawyer.
Would you like to take it?
Did he say why he was calling?
I called him.
To confirm that he hasn't called you.
Not since you've been declared insane.
I could have told you that.
- If only I'd known to ask.
- If only.
Would you have told me the truth?
In my own way, I always have.
Mr Metcalf, that'll be all for now.
Thank you for your time.
You've been talking
to the Tooth Fairy.
I think he's earned the right to be
known by the name he's chosen.
He's the Great Red Dragon.
You have hubbed hell, Dr Lecter.
I often do.
You got what you wanted.
Suddenly, you're very relevant.
There is one way
for you to stay relevant...
...and comfortable.
You want me to speak with the Dragon.
Given his recent failure,
you believe he will seek counsel.
We need to make
your contact work for us.
Standing trace order
for any time you're on the phone.
When he calls,
you keep him on the line.
I can't refuse him a sympathetic ear.
He no doubt needs it.
Don't do that.
D?
You in here?
Yes.
What are you doing
sitting here in the dark?
- How do you know it's dark?
- The lights aren't on.
Do you remember it?
The light?
Is it worse to have seen it
and lost it?
I know I can never have the light,
but there are things I can have.
There are things to enjoy.
You sound strange.
Reba...
I don't know what to say to you.
I don't know what's happening to me...
with you.
You threaten me and
yet you do not threaten me.
It's confusing.
It's OK to be confused.
We spend most of our lives confused.
It's rare to really figure anything out.
I can't be with you.
Most men are terrified
of entailing a burden.
That fear is amplified in my case.
That's not why I'm afraid.
I'm afraid I'll hurt you.
It was nice to spend time
with someone
who has the courage to get his hat
or stay as he damn pleased,
and gives me credit for the same.
Get your hat, Francis.
Get it and go.
Hello?
'You are the Dragon,
you don't have to be afraid.
'You know who speaks.
'From the beginning,
you and the Dragon had been one.
'You are becoming.'
And the Dragon is your higher self.
If I'm not as strong as the Dragon,
she will die.
Don't let fear leach your strength.
I need to think.
I told her I can't be with her.
You are almost blind
to your own true feelings,
no more able to express them
than a scar can blush.
Do you know how you feel about her?
Yes.
I...
I'm afraid she will come
to the house to talk.
I don't know what will happen
in the house.
The Dragon may come down.
I know how easily she would tear.
I think about what the...
She called me a man.
A sweet man.
I didn't hear Reba's heart.
They are listening.
The Tooth Fairy used
call-spoofing software,
piggybacking on Lecter's old line,
but the caller ID showed
his lawyer's number.
Hannibal's having his fun.
You're not the only one
who keeps their promises, Hannibal.
The toilet, too.
Wally's safe.
The dogs are safe.
We're picking them up
and bringing them in.
You look different.
You said you wouldn't be the same
when you came home.
- And you said you would.
- Hmm.
Boy, was I wrong about that.
I wanted you to go.
I told you to go.
Nobody to blame but myself.
And Jack Crawford.
I do blame Jack Crawford.
Jack knew what he was doing.
And so did I.
Is he after you now?
Is that why he came after us?
He came after you
because Hannibal suggested it.
He urged him to do it.
That's a clammy, sick feeling.
Yeah, I know it is.
Wally almost died.
My son almost died, I almost died.
I knew it was him. I knew it was him.
I saw your picture in that paper
and I knew it was him.
Hell, I got mad there for a second.
I hate this, Molly.
I'm sorry.
Erm...
This could take a while.
It might.
We'll be back home...
...won't we?
Yep.
It's tough to hold onto anything good.
It's all so slippery.
Yeah, slick as hell.
I'm just about worn out
with you crazy sons of bitches.
The essence of the worst
in the human spirit
is not found
in the crazy sons of bitches.
Ugliness is found
in the faces of the crowd.
What did you say to him?
"Save yourself. Kill them all."
Then I gave him your home address.
How's the wife?
How's my wife?
She's lucky.
She survived the Great Red Dragon.
That takes a pinch more than luck.
When you look at her now,
what do you see?
You know what I see.
Before he became the Red Dragon,
this shy boy would never
have dared any of this.
Well, now he thinks
he can do anything. Anything.
Anything.
The Dragon likely thinks you are
as much a monster as you think he is.
Is this a competition?
"Two souls, alas,
are dwelling in my breast,
"and one is striving
to forsake its brother."
The Great Red Dragon
is freedom to him,
shedding his skin,
the sound of his voice,
his own reflection.
The building of a new body
and the othering of himself,
the splitting of his personality,
all seem active and deliberate.
He craves change.
He didn't murder those families?
He changed them?
Don't you crave change, Will?