["Gotta Be Movin'"
by The Record Company playing]
♪ 'Cause I gotta be movin' ♪
♪ I'm running like a rabbit
On a dog track now ♪
♪ Won't stop till I made it
Or they put me in the ground ♪
♪ You can run if you like
But don't run in place ♪
♪ You can hide if you want
But don't hide your face ♪
♪ I'm not gonna sleep tonight ♪
♪ Got ten miles till I see a light ♪
♪ My wheels spinning round
Like an old cassette ♪
♪ 'Cause I ain't where I wanna be yet ♪
♪ Lord, I gotta be movin' ♪
♪ 'Cause I gotta be movin' ♪
♪ We're not gonna sleep tonight ♪
Another run this afternoon.
You said two runs a week.
Any more than that is too risky.
It's gonna rain.
["Gotta Be Movin'" continues playing]
[music ends]
[unsettling music creeping in]
[ghostly echo ringing]
After she passed,
I couldn't stop thinking about it.
I… I finally had a name.
I knew who my father was.
I've apologized to your folks
for how I showed up.
I've just been nervous
to talk to you guys.
I can't imagine
what you must think of me right now.
I am sorry I lied about who I was.
I just wanted to know you all,
and I wanted y'all to know me…
which is why I'm still here.
Can I…? Um…
Let me get this straight.
His mother worked here, right? Um…
You were friends with her, and then Dad…
Uh…
And I should know who Bebe is?
I was six or seven or something.
I don't think that's important right now.
And, Dad, um,
so you've just been cheating on Mom,
like, our whole lives? Is that it?
Should we be expecting, like,
other siblings to show up?
-Come out of the woodwork?
-I'll keep you posted.
-Don't be an ass, Cane.
-[Cane chuckling] Okay.
You're okay with this?
It's not about me right now, is it?
Well, uh…
And you pretended to be a bartender?
I mean, who does that?
He just explained it.
-No, he didn't.
-It was a mistake. I'm sorry.
I can't believe you are buying this.
I'm sorry, dude, but, like,
how do you know he's telling the truth?
-That's enough, Cane. That's enough.
-No, I--
You expect me to go along with this shit.
I mean, that's like…
I got too much stuff to do
to be dealing with this.
Um, welcome to the family.
What?
[chuckling] You're loving this.
Cane's a mess,
I'm fucked up, but no worries.
You get a second chance.
You have a do-over.
-Please, not everything's about you, Bree.
-Clearly.
Uh… My deepest sympathies, Shawn.
I would not wish us on anyone.
Best of luck.
Way to go, Dad.
Oh, shit. Did I hit on you?
Uh, yeah, a little.
Jesus Christ, Bree.
That was intense.
Yeah, well, I'm not buying it.
I think he's lying.
[Bree] Why would he lie?
Who'd choose to be a part of this family?
We have money and standing.
-That should be in the past tense.
-He doesn't know our finances.
My point is, he could be a con man
after God knows what.
Does your brain
always go to the worst place?
What the hell is he doing here?
[tense music playing]
Mr. Buckley, Agent Sanchez.
Can I talk to you for a second?
-Excuse me, Tommy.
-Yeah.
[tense music rising]
-I thought you said you called him off.
-I tried.
-You really knocked that out of the park.
-I told him I was wrong about you.
About-- About all of it.
But he's still trying to make his case.
-Against Dad now?
-No, he thinks Dad was covering for you.
He's just getting desperate.
He doesn't have anything concrete.
-It's all conjecture and circumstantial.
-Are you a lawyer now?
-No, that would be our new baby brother.
-[Cane sighs]
How can I help you?
You've been in business for a while.
Father built this place
from the ground up, didn't he?
Sounds like you already
know the answer, Agent.
Yeah, well, I read what I could.
[chuckling] I do know
how he built the place back in the day.
-Probably also read it caught up to him.
-Yeah.
It's why I know better than to do anything
that would have the DEA sniffing around.
You're wasting your time.
Yeah, I was starting to think that I was.
I went to Sheriff Porter's this morning
just to have another look around.
Found a trail camera near his garage.
Yeah.
I have footage of you arriving
at the sheriff's house the night he died.
[suspenseful music playing]
Followed by your wife's arrival.
She leaves an hour later
holding what looks to be…
I don't know, dirty rags?
Blood, maybe?
Anyway… [chuckling]
She tosses them all in her trunk.
Want to get to the point?
I think Sheriff Porter was onto you,
so you and your wife killed him.
[chuckles]
Wait. I killed him? Or my wife did?
You're a funny man.
Here's the thing. I don't give two shits
about a murder charge.
What's this about, then?
Point me in the direction
of your supplier.
-If I get a bust, this footage disappears.
-I'm not talking to you without a lawyer.
You do that,
this camera goes into real evidence.
Sheriff Porter was a lawman.
They won't let that go.
Once they start investigating,
what else are they gonna find?
Why not just save us all a shitstorm?
I only want your supplier.
[suspenseful music continues]
I'm taking this to the DA tomorrow.
I don't know you.
-I don't trust you for shit.
-I realize that, but you should.
I have a personal interest in this case.
I'm throwing you a lifeline because of it.
Take it, Mr. Buckley.
What's this about?
Ask your dad.
Maybe you can talk some sense into him.
Tomorrow.
What's going on?
[uneasy music playing]
Hey, what's up, man?
You wouldn't happen to know
where Harlan Buckley is, would you?
He's my granddad.
Probably at the fish house.
Oh my God. Another Buckley.
What? [chuckles] Hey, I'm Grady.
-This is my friend, Nate.
-I'm Diller. Is that your yacht?
[Grady] Uh, more or less.
I mean, I think it is.
Or it will be. It's complicated.
-Which way to the fish house?
-I'm heading in. I'll show you.
[Grady] Lead on, Buck Junior.
[Grady giggles]
[uneasy music continues]
[Bree] You didn't think to tell me?
-I found the camera this morning.
-You're wrong about it.
-Wrong? Your father insinuated I'm not.
-You promised you'd leave them out of it.
And I will if they give me
the supplier's name.
I can't promise what my unit captain's
gonna do, but I meant every word.
What happened to the sheriff
was an accident. Even the police said so.
They think it was, but they don't have
the information I have.
-This was about Cane, no one else!
-It was. Now it's about this!
-You said you loved me! This is not love.
-I said I love you.
-It was met with deafening silence.
-Your feelings hurt?
-It's why you're doing this?
-My feelings aren't hurt!
I'm doing this
because it's my fucking job!
All right?
I could have gone straight to the DA.
Had your whole fucking family called in
for questioning. I didn't because of you.
For you.
Now, if you can't tell them to cooperate,
the best you can do is get out of my way,
'cause I'm not fucking stopping.
[grave music playing]
-[car door opens and closes]
-[engine turns over]
You actually saw the video?
[Harlan] Grainy, but definitely us.
-Coming and going.
-Okay, the sheriff's body was cremated.
There's no weapon.
All Sanchez can do is put us at the scene.
If he keeps pushing, we lawyer up.
And say what?
Okay, listen to this.
You arrived,
found your old friend crushed to death.
Horrible shock.
You started having heart palpitations,
and in your confused state, you called me.
I came and helped you recover,
and then I left.
It's questionable, but then we hire
some fancy lawyers to answer questions.
Or we give them Grady.
No. We give him Grady,
he talks, and that leads back to us.
There's no way we can trust him or Grady.
Okay, okay. Don't let this get to you.
None of this matters
if your heart gives out, you hear me?
I'm fine, I swear.
I have a damn machine sewn into my chest.
It better be good for something.
We will figure this out.
[indistinct chatter]
Hey.
-You said he didn't have anything.
-I didn't think he did.
Wrong again, Bree.
He doesn't want to charge them.
He needs the supplier.
You think they could pass over
that information without consequence?
Were they really there, at the sheriff's?
According to the security footage,
yes, they were, Bree.
I was never trying to hurt them.
No, of course not. Just me, right?
Did you tell Dad about me and Marcus?
-No.
-Okay.
He's gonna find out soon enough
once we all do life in prison.
-Congrats, you burned it all down again.
-No. No, I can fix this. I'm--
No, you can't fix it!
You want to know why?
Because you always break shit.
-What's gonna happen when Dad finds out?
-He doesn't need--
He still believes in your bullshit.
I'm done with it.
I mean, Dad, this is going to kill him.
This is on you.
[dramatic music playing]
[sobbing]
Fish get unloaded and processed here,
packed with ice,
then sent off on the trucks.
Whoa. So cool, Diller.
And how many trucks do you have?
[Diller] I don't know, I've never counted.
-Smell never bothers you?
-Nah, you get used to it.
And how many boats does your family have?
Like ten, maybe?
Other boats come through as well.
All the fishermen wanna unload here.
It's the biggest fish house around.
They all come to us.
[Grady] Whoa, that's so impressive.
And how many employees?
Diller? What's going on?
Oh, these men want to meet Granddad.
This is my uncle, Cane.
Oh, no way. What's up, man? I'm Grady.
Grady.
Oh, no, come on, man. I'm a hugger.
All right.
-This is Nate.
-Hey, Nate.
Hey, uh, Diller, get out of here.
You're done for the day.
No, I'm not.
You are. You're done for the day. Get out.
Go on, now.
Nice to see you, dude.
You too. Thanks for the tour, Big D.
So you're Cane.
Whoo! Those Buckley genes.
Guy could be a model, right?
I'm not kidding, you got those blue eyes,
got that square jaw.
Bet you got a six-pack hiding
under there, right? [chuckles]
You doing your own deliveries now?
You got the truck parked in the back?
Nope, floated in on a boat.
That shipment should be here soon.
Where's your dad?
-Next door. You want me to call him over?
-At the restaurant?
Oh, we haven't seen that yet.
Is it this way?
Come on, keep up, sexy.
[sobbing]
-What's wrong with you?
-I'm fine, sweetie.
-[sniffles]
-Right.
You out of here?
[Diller] Yeah, I guess so.
I shouldn't be here with you.
Why are you crying?
-Don't mind me.
-What? Did something happen?
Okay.
The truth is that your mom
ruins everything she touches,
she always has, and this time
she managed to do it sober.
So, I don't even know why I try.
Mom.
["Don't Owe You a Thang"
by Gary Clark Jr. playing]
♪ Ain't got no money, no fancy car ♪
♪ Ain't got no excuses, baby
Hanging at the bar ♪
♪ I don't owe you a thang, baby ♪
♪ I don't owe you a thang ♪
♪ Oh, we ain't gettin' married ♪
♪ I ain't buyin' you no diamond ring ♪
♪ That's all right ♪
♪ Well, we ain't gettin' married ♪
♪ Ain't buyin' you no diamond ring ♪
♪ That's all right ♪
♪ Well, we ain't gettin' married ♪
[police siren blares]
♪ Ain't buyin' you no diamond ring ♪
[siren continues blaring]
[music ends]
Y'all can take a seat here.
I'll go find my dad.
You gentlemen want a drink?
-Yeah, let's get a--
-Two bourbons, neat. Anything top shelf.
Two bourbons, neat, please.
Sure.
[Grady speaking indistinctly]
-You should be seen…
-Well, I…
[Grady continues speaking indistinctly]
-I'm sorry for how everything went down.
-Not now, Shawn.
Look.
There's something you should know.
I'm very protective over my family.
I know and I respect that.
[Grady] The guy had two options, right?
Fuck around and find out. [laughs]
-Hey.
-[Harlan exhales]
What is he doing here?
I have no clue, but we need
to get him the hell out of here
'cause that DEA can be back at any time.
Which one is he?
The talky one.
[Grady] HB.
Hydrogen bomb.
-You remember Nate, right?
-I believe so. Good to see you both again.
-Now, what are you doing here?
-I know.
I know, I'm sorry.
We should have called first.
It's a pet peeve of mine too
when people show up unannounced.
I just had to see
the famous Buckleys in action.
Speaking of which,
I bet this is Mrs. Buckley, isn't it?
It is an honor to meet you.
-I'm sorry, I'm a hugger.
-I'm not.
Okay, hey, I'm Grady.
And if you'll permit me to say so,
you are even lovelier
than this establishment.
I can't believe
it's taken me so long to discover it.
Your first time in Havenport?
I think I came here once when I was a kid.
I'm not sure.
-Grandparents lived in Morgan County.
-Mom, Shawn needs you at the bar.
Okay, I'm starting to see where
this stud muffin gets his good looks.
-This guy--
-Take care, Grady.
All right.
Hey, cheekbones.
Join us at the table, huh?
No, really, why are you here?
Well, I show you mine, you show me yours.
-And now that you've seen ours…
-Trying to get rid of me, gorgeous?
Discretion is a key ingredient
to what we do.
We shouldn't openly fraternize.
Oh, come on. I know you Buckleys
are more hospitable than that.
Your grandson was gracious enough
to give us the full tour.
It was very impressive.
We could be doing
so much more business together.
I had no idea.
It's a fully operating fishery.
We're doing exactly
what we should be doing.
Right. Uh, speaking of which,
how long can I park a yacht in the harbor?
That's your yacht out there?
Uh…
It's a long story, but, yeah,
I think it's safe to say it's my yacht.
-Want to check it out?
-Maybe some other time.
Okay. Promise?
I'm a little hungry.
Can we see some menus?
Look, we've got a lot to do,
and you can't be here.
[chuckles]
I can't?
You want to discuss the schedule,
the amount of runs,
how smooth everything's going?
We can do that in the office.
This is the restaurant.
-We don't do business in here.
-[phone buzzing]
Hey.
[phone continues buzzing]
Yeah, uh, give me a sec.
Uh-huh.
Oh, shit. Um…
Okay, yeah, send me your location.
Well, you'll get your wish, cutie pie.
I gotta bounce.
You're coming with me, though.
Where to?
Not you, cupcake. Your dad.
[Harlan sighs]
[tense music playing]
Table four, please. Thank you.
[Belle] Hi, how'd it go?
-Badly.
-What happened?
What happened is you killed the land deal,
now we're stuck with him.
That's what happened.
[sighs]
["All the Trouble"
by Lee Ann Womack playing]
♪ The deck is stacked against you ♪
♪ Life's a losing hand ♪
♪ Even when you think you're up ♪
♪ You're right back down again ♪
♪ Either way you play it ♪
♪ The house is gonna win ♪
♪ I got all the trouble
I'm ever gonna need ♪
♪ And I just don't want no more ♪
[Diller] Hey, Dad.
How was swim practice?
You know, whatever.
You sure it wasn't canceled
due to the storm?
-That's the call I got.
-Don't ask if you already know the answer.
Get in.
Here's another question for you.
How long have you been working
at the fish house?
[scoffs]
I ran into old man Devin today.
He asked how you like mopping fish guts.
I had no idea what he's talking about.
Why would I? I'm only your father.
How long?
Not long. It was just a couple of shifts.
But it ends today.
It's a job for my granddad.
I'm a Buckley too, you know?
You'll never be a Buckley, ever.
There is something
seriously damaged about that family.
They look bright and shiny on the outside,
but there's something wrong on the inside.
-How do you know that?
-'Cause I lived it.
Jesus, look at your mother.
-You're not legally supposed to be there.
-I don't see her. She's in the restaurant.
You're missing the point, bud.
I don't want you there.
You can't stop me.
Diller, she is going to disappoint you.
Again.
That's all she knows how to do,
is disappoint.
It's who she is.
She's an addict. It's what they do.
You're not to go back there.
Do you understand me?
[seat belt clicks]
[thunder rumbling]
[Harlan] Is he dead?
They didn't say.
I told you
these day deliveries were tricky.
We really need to do this my way.
[Grady] Okay.
-Harlan, what the fuck is going on?
-Quiet.
Quiet. You're fine.
This is a misunderstanding.
So this is your guy?
-What's he doing pulling over my truck?
-He didn't know about you.
Now he does, so it won't happen again.
Right, Drew?
[breathing heavily]
Yeah, see, that wasn't very convincing.
Let me talk to him. Alone.
That all right?
[chuckles]
[snaps fingers]
[Harlan] Come on.
Now, what the hell were you thinking?
How was I supposed to know
that you were a part of this?
They were speeding.
Jesus, Harlan.
In a truck with enough drugs
for the Eastern Seaboard.
I cannot let that go. I am the sheriff.
Because of me.
I'm the only reason
you have that badge, so listen up.
I'm gonna try to clean up this mess,
but from now on, you see these guys,
you just give them a wave and keep moving.
No heroics, no busts, nothing.
-I don't know if I can do that.
-You have to or I can't save you.
[uneasy music playing]
When did I get the chance to say
I wanted to be a part of this?
You didn't even give me a choice.
You didn't ask me.
I'm not this guy.
I didn't get a choice.
You have one now.
[uneasy music builds]
[woman] All right, I'll see you soon.
Hey there, Annie.
Hi, Cane. What can I do for you?
I have some, uh,
family business to discuss.
Oh, you want to talk to Mr. Freeman.
He'll be back soon.
You know, it's simple stuff, really.
I'm sure you can help me out.
Do you mind if we sit down for a minute?
[Annie] I can't tell you about that, Cane.
The Buckley accounts
are in your parents' names,
and the land deal is confidential
per your mother's request.
-But you know about it.
-Well, yes. I do all the revisions.
I'm a senior account specialist now.
I was promoted last month.
It's about time.
Right? Been here 14 years.
Look, like I said before,
I really just wanna know about Wes Benson.
Mr. Benson has been here several times
to talk to Mr. Freeman.
He's trying to broker a deal to package
some of the loans that have been…
T-- Troublesome?
We're not a big institution.
The economy has affected banks too.
So you're selling our debt off?
[sighs] I really don't know, Cane.
I just heard them talking about it.
Mr. Benson is working
with a bigger bank up in Raleigh.
And nobody thought to tell
any of us this is happening?
Well, it hasn't gone through.
If it does, they have to notify you.
-Well, your parents, I guess.
-[tuts]
My family's been banking here
my whole life. Longer.
Loans move around all the time.
What do we do to stop it from happening?
Pay them off.
That really is the only way.
[Harlan] He's family.
He understands loyalty.
He knows how to keep his mouth shut.
You're not gonna have any more problems
on these runs. Isn't that right?
I'm here to protect and serve.
It was my mistake not knowing
you're all friends of the family.
I don't know, man.
It'd be easier if I just kill him.
Uh, easier than having
the sheriff in your pocket? Be smart.
Well, it'd be cleaner.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Okay, come on.
I'll do it, I'll do it, all right?
I got you. I'm your guy.
I can protect you.
[shakily] Please.
Ask Harlan, I…
I did everything he wanted me to
with the sheriff. Cleaned up the reports.
I did everything I could with the DEA guy,
like he asked.
DEA?
What DEA guy?
What's he talking about, DEA guy?
One agent stayed behind.
He's been trying to make a case,
grabbing at straws.
He's got nothing.
You're being watched?
This why you tried to push me out earlier?
Not watched, just playing it safe.
-But you're gonna handle it.
-It's under control.
You have my word.
But for now,
we gotta get Drew back in his patrol car
before people start wondering
what happened to their sheriff.
-Oh, do we?
-[tense music sting]
No…
[whimpers]
Please, I got a family.
I'm just trying to scare you.
Sorry. [chuckling]
Sorry. [imitates whizzing shot and laughs]
No, I'm kidding.
-Are we good?
-[Drew breathing heavily]
Absolutely.
Okay, let's get you back to work.
Wait, what am I talking about?
Look at you. Y-- You're a mess. Come here.
Help you out here.
Boop-boop-boop-boop-boop.
Yep, there we go.
You don't look so bad.
Let's tuck you in a little bit.
There we go.
Get some water on that face, okay?
Maybe a… little bit of ice.
All right, now listen.
It's pretty simple, all right?
You're good to me,
I'm good to you.
Okay?
Okay, get out of here, you little punk.
Drew.
Figure out how to explain your face
before you get back. Got it?
-For you.
-[grim music playing]
Take it.
[firmly] Take it.
[grim music continues]
Fantastic.
[thunder rumbles in distance]
Did you know
what Wes is up to with the bank?
Sounds like a conversation
we should not be having here.
Too bad. Hey.
He's gonna take the land
right out from under us.
I didn't sign the contracts.
The deal is not going through.
Yeah, okay, you didn't sign them,
but you did show him our finances.
-I had to. It's standard.
-Oh my God.
Okay, well, now he knows we're vulnerable,
and I'm guessing he didn't like
being used and discarded.
-Hey, whatever you think, it--
-Yeah, I don't care.
I don't care that you and Dad
have a toxic marriage.
You're cheating on each other,
got secret kids, whatever.
-I don't care. I don't have time.
-You're a child.
I'm trying to figure out what the hell
we'll do when our debt gets called up
and we don't have the money.
Can they really do that?
Can they take the land?
-Why don't you ask your boyfriend?
-Watch it.
I liked it better
when you and Dad hated each other.
Hey.
I was hoping we could talk.
Sure, bro.
We can do that.
What's up?
I wanted to maybe answer
any questions you might have.
[chuckles softly]
Okay, sure.
You said you came here 'cause
you wanted to get to know us, right?
Um, forgive me if that sounds
a little like… like bullshit.
Look, I don't know how to prove to you
that I'm not after anything.
Nothing concrete, anyway--
I guess I just don't understand
what you're looking for.
-'Cause you already have it.
-What's that?
You have a family.
Support, a place you belong.
Look, man, all that stuff
is just one big fucking trap.
Okay? As you can tell
by my suppressed anger.
-I mean, I speak from experience here.
-Yeah, it's not so suppressed.
Okay.
What is it that you want, Shawn?
When my mom died, I lost everything.
I thought that maybe
there was something here for me.
Whatever's here,
you don't want it.
Okay?
You came, you saw what you wanted to see,
and you should probably leave
while you still can.
Because trust me, you don't…
You don't want to end up here.
[somber music playing]
[thunder rumbles]
[Bree] Hey.
What's going on?
Oh, come on. We both knew this was coming.
Rehab dries you out for a bit,
but this is my true form.
What am I looking at?
A fucking train wreck. [chuckles]
Hey, come on.
It's true.
[sniffles]
You know it's true.
I mean, look at the family I come from.
You want to send them all to prison.
They're bad.
You think I'm bad too.
You can get out.
You're not involved in any of it.
-You can get away from it all.
-How?
With you?
I know it's your job.
You deserve a win,
and I want that for you.
I do.
We can leave together.
I won't let any of the fallout touch you,
I promise you that.
Where'd you get it?
[Bree] My favorite dealer. [sighs]
I got scared when you said you loved me.
Why?
Because…
Because if this were real,
you know I'd have to choose.
You or them.
-Bree, come on now.
-It's too late now.
[gentle music aches softly]
I'm sorry I couldn't say it.
I'm a coward.
That's the last thing you are.
[Marcus grunts]
You taste like whiskey.
You said it was your favorite.
[gentle music continues]
[Harlan] We need
to slow down these deliveries.
I don't wanna store this shit
on my boats between runs.
Why?
You worried about that DEA sitch?
I told you that wasn't a problem.
I like this relationship.
Honestly, I look up to you, man.
Let's not change that.
Okay?
So it's business as usual, then?
Absolutely, but usual means cautious.
Good, because let me be
perfectly clear on my end.
There can be no DEA.
You've seen how I do things, right?
You need to solve this problem.
Period.
Like I said, there's no problem.
Fantastic.
[ominous music playing]
[Cane] Dad.
Dad, listen to me.
We can't--
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey, hey, hey.
Drew says Sanchez
is at the Crystal Cove Motel.
What do you plan on doing with that?
Dad, no.
We are not those people.
That's not how we deal with our problems.
We are those people,
and it's exactly how we deal with them.
You're either all in or dead.
That's the way it works.
-You know this is the solution.
-I do not. Listen to me. Hey.
Hey, just-- just let me deal with this.
Let me talk to Sanchez. I'll deal with it.
-Dad, hey, let me talk to Sanchez.
-Cane! We are done talking!
[intense music playing]
[thunder rumbling]
Fuck!
[suspenseful music playing]
[Cane] Dad, what did you do?
Found him this way.
We can't be here.
We gotta go.
We have to find the camera.
Look for his iPhone, laptop, anything.
Oh, Jesus.
[somber music playing]
Dad.
Dad, we gotta go.
Hey, hey, hey, seriously.
We need to go now!
Come on. Come on.
For all we know,
his dealer stole his camera.
If it surfaces, we deal with it then.
This shit really doesn't affect you, huh?
No, it affects me, but it doesn't stop me.
Come on, Bree.
[somber music continues]
-[line calling]
-Oh, come on, Bree.
God, Bree, pick up the phone.
Pick up the--
[voicemail] Hi, you've reached Bree.
Leave me a message.
Jesus Christ.
Jesus Christ!
Bree!
-Jesus. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
-[Bree moans]
You're awake?
Hey, hey, hey.
I got you, I got you.
Jesus Christ, Bree. What'd you do?
What is this? What did you do?
[Bree whimpers]
-What did you do? We're going home.
-Hey. I did it.
-You're okay. You're coming home with me.
-I did it.
We're getting you out of here, okay?
Come on, let's go. Come on.
There. You're okay?
I killed him.
♪ I got all the trouble… ♪
Okay, we're going.
♪ I got all the trouble
I'm ever gonna need ♪
♪ And I just don't want no more ♪
♪ Hey, I need a happy ending ♪
♪ Somebody write me one ♪
♪ If there's a prince awaiting ♪
♪ Somebody send him on ♪
♪ Even Cinderella ♪
♪ Had to find her own way home ♪
♪ Well, it started with a dirt pile
And a couple drops of rain ♪
♪ Then the storm and the wind
And the thunder and the lightning came ♪
♪ Somebody give me shelter ♪
♪ I've had all I can take ♪
♪ 'Cause I got all the trouble
I'm ever gonna need ♪
♪ I got all the trouble
♪ And I just don't want no more ♪
[music ends]