[sharp whoosh of flame]
[Peyton whimpering]
-[flame whooshes]
-[Peyton screams]
[shrieking]
[chilling music builds]
[screaming]
[breathing shakily]
[brooding music playing]
[panting]
[sobbing]
[dispatch chatter over police radio]
Call me when you find out.
[Cane] I can't believe this.
I cannot fucking believe this!
Tim and Reggie are going to ask around
to see if they find the guys who did this.
-How did this happen?
-This was a warning from our friend Owen.
The sheriff? Sheriff--
Of course it was the fucking sheriff!
Keep it down. I'll take care of it.
How are you gonna take care of it?
[Belle] Hey, we're here. Is she okay?
-[Cane] Freaked out.
-Where's Savannah?
She's upstairs. I sent the sitter home.
-Hey.
[Belle] Hey, how you doin'?
Okay, stay with her.
I'll check on Savannah.
I-- I smell.
It's okay. It's okay.
-Hey, Drew.
-Yes, sir.
Has the sheriff been notified?
I called him. He's aware of the situation.
You called him?
Is he at home with his thumb up his ass?
-You're not helping.
-Don't worry, Cane.
-We're gonna find who did this.
-Can we finish this up, please?
Yes, ma'am. Just a couple more questions.
-Are you okay?
-No.
[brooding music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[music continues]
[ghostly echo ringing]
[music fades]
[tense music playing]
You've got to work on your handwriting.
[music softens]
How can I help you, Harlan?
Speak to you in private?
[tense music resumes]
[Clyde] Hey, go on. Take a seat.
You want to tell me
what the hell that was?
Some meth heads out to score drug money.
My guys are on it.
But I'd say
your daughter-in-law got lucky.
My family is off-limits.
It's a shame what happened.
The world gets more dangerous every day.
It helps to have friends.
I told you.
No more runs.
Not until I meet Grady.
Well…
[somber music playing]
Think that through, Harlan,
and my guess is you'll change your mind.
[inhales sharply]
[exhales]
[gritty music playing]
[Savannah] Daddy, if we don't go now,
I'm gonna be late.
Okay, go get your stuff.
I need to, uh, say goodbye to your mom.
-Come on, we leave in one minute.
-[Cane] Yeah.
Baby?
Hey, it's okay. I'll take her.
No, I got it.
Jesus, my hair still smells like an Exxon.
Don't you want to stay home? Take it easy?
[Peyton] No, I'm good.
Are you sure? I think it might be
a good idea if you just stayed home.
-I said I'm good.
-Jesus Christ, Peyton.
Cool gun!
No, that's not cool, okay?
That is not cool.
You do not touch that, ever.
You understand me?
Not those shoes, the blue ones.
What are you doing?
At least I'm not trying
to hide everything from her.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means that whatever
those men wanted last night
had nothing to do with me,
which leaves you.
-You can start talking any time.
-[sighs in exasperation]
Baby, I honestly don't know who did this.
Okay? You gotta believe me.
[Savannah] Okay, I'm ready.
[Cane sighs]
I will drive us, okay?
We can all go together as a family.
-You ready?
-I don't think so.
Let's go, hon!
Before I hurt your daddy.
[tense music plays]
[door opens]
-[line ringing]
-[door closes]
[tense music continues]
Hey, can you, uh, follow her, please?
It's okay if she sees you.
Just-- just keep an eye on her for me.
[Tim] Yes, sir.
Okay, thank you.
[knocking on door]
-[Marcus] Sorry, I was in the shower.
-Uh, no, this… This works for me.
[chuckling]
[sighs] I got your message.
What happened last night?
Cane's wife was attacked.
-Really?
-Yeah, she's okay, but it's suspicious.
-Is it drug-related?
-Maybe. It's unclear. I'll let you know.
-Did anything I give you help?
-Um, yeah.
I went through the manifest
for the trawler.
And the Morning Breeze
recorded four trips…
in the past month.
You cross-reference these
with the fishery's log?
No catch of any kind was unloaded.
The boat was gone
ten to 14 hours each time,
returning to port with
two instances of engine trouble,
and two trips were written off
to inclement weather.
That's completely consistent
with the Miss Glory manifest.
So Cane had two boats actively smuggling.
[scoffs]
[Marcus] Interesting.
What do you know about these guys that
run the boat? Tim Donnelly, Reggie Miller?
Both ex-cons.
Cane hired them six months ago.
-Do we know if the AIS was turned off?
-How would I know that?
[tense music playing]
-Can you get me on the Morning Breeze?
-[chuckles]
If the AIS was manually disconnected,
that's illegal.
Is it enough?
Enough for my captain
to issue a shadow surveillance
to follow the next run.
Best way to make a case stick,
I gotta catch them in the act
with drugs in their hands.
I can get you on the boat.
This could work.
Wanna have sex?
[laughs heartily]
-I love your nuance.
-Come here.
-[chuckling] You are such an addict.
-Mm-hmm.
I'm starting to like sober sex.
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
Maybe it's just sex with you.
[atmospheric music playing]
-[Shawn] Ms. Buckley?
-Hey.
You got a second?
Of course.
Why don't you take a seat?
Uh, I'm sorry I ran out on you last night.
There was an emergency.
-Is--
-Everything's fine.
And about what we talked about…
It's just a lot to process.
I know.
I'm sorry for the way that I handled it.
-If you want me to take a DNA test, I can.
-No, no, Shawn. I believe you.
I also believe in memories,
and I keep lots of them.
Surprise.
[pensive music playing]
Your mama.
Bebe.
She worked here years ago
when we were just a tiny place.
She was sweet
and so funny.
My God, we laughed.
I'm sorry to hear she passed.
She was amazing.
The absolute best.
She never talked about my dad.
I never pushed.
I figured it was a bad subject for her.
But then she got sick and…
You said it was cancer?
[Shawn] Leukemia.
Diagnosed right as
I was finishing law school.
I was with her through treatment.
Then, toward the end…
she told me one day, out of the blue,
"Your father's name is Harlan Buckley."
"He's a fisherman
from Havenport, North Carolina."
-You must've been curious.
-She told me he was "complicated."
-That's the word she used.
-[laughs]
That's putting it mildly.
Yeah, I tried to let it go.
I figured I don't know who this man is,
how he's gonna react.
He has a wife, a family.
Figured I need to decide if I want to get
to know him before I blow up his world.
And do you have any other family?
Just me and my boyfriend.
Been together for two years.
He knows I'm here.
So?
Now that you met your father,
what do you want to do?
I feel like if I don't tell him who I am,
I'm gonna regret it.
-Did you know he and my mom were together?
-No, I didn't.
-I'm sorry if I've upset you.
-I'll be fine.
Hey.
You've done nothing wrong, Shawn.
Thank you for being so kind to me.
[exhales, then breathes in]
-Can I ask you a favor?
-Yes, ma'am.
Can we wait a little longer
to tell Harlan?
Today's probably not the best day.
Well, only if I still have a job.
-Of course you do. I need you.
-[Shawn chuckles]
Why don't you keep those?
Thank you, ma'am.
[exhales]
[suspenseful music playing]
Radar's over the helm.
[Marcus] All right, I'll be quick.
The AIS is disconnected.
-That's good, right?
-Yeah.
The radar's a 410 too,
so it has GPS that records.
-I'm gonna copy it real quick.
-How long will it take?
I'm going as fast as I can.
[suspenseful music continues]
Compressor's out in the small ice room.
What? How much?
Reynolds quoted 3,200.
Jesus.
-This goddamn place is falling apart.
-Yeah.
[tense music playing]
[Harlan] Cane.
Come with me.
Where are we going?
Um… just take care of it.
-Talk to you later.
-All right. Will do.
[suspenseful music playing]
What's this about?
Go on, say it.
I'm sorry. We both are.
We was never gonna hurt anybody.
-We just wanted to scare her.
-Porter made us.
[Harlan] You attacked his wife.
Sir, I'm sorry. [breathing shakily]
We were just supposed to scare her good.
[grunts and groans]
[Hollis coughing and groaning]
[Harlan breathing deeply]
Go on.
No.
Look at them.
Look at this one,
like fresh out of high school.
I never graduated.
You shut the fuck up.
Do it. You'll feel better.
What good does this do? Huh?
It sends a message to everyone else.
"Do not fuck with our family."
I ain't never gonna
fuck with you again, sir.
Shut the fuck up!
These two hurt your wife.
Think about her
lying on the ground, screaming.
["Soul Drifts Away"
by Siege of Rhodes playing]
[sharp, rapid breaths]
[music rising]
This…
-This is-- No, no.
-[tire iron clangs against concrete]
♪ Ashes return to ashes ♪
[tire iron clangs]
♪ Dirt returns to dirt ♪
-[thwack]
-[grunts]
♪ And it left us all still stuck ♪
[grunts]
♪ To carry all the hurt ♪
[Hollis] No, no, no, no!
[Levi] No, no!
[music continues]
[loud, despairing exhale]
[sighs deeply]
[music fades]
[indistinct chatter]
[Belle] Hey there.
How is everything? Good?
-[man] Yes.
-[Belle] Thank you. Top you off?
-Sheriff?
-Hey, take a seat, Belle.
-Harlan's down at the fish house, so…
-Well, I came to talk to you, so sit down.
[exhales] What can I do for you?
Let's not even pretend
that you don't know what's going on.
In fact, something tells me
I should be dealing with you anyway.
I need you to do something for me.
I don't control Harlan.
You two need to work this out.
Eh, don't… screw with me
the way Harlan does.
It's really simple.
Get your husband in line,
or we're gonna have problems.
Do not come into my restaurant
and threaten me.
No, that wasn't a threat.
This is a threat.
You get your husband to fall in line,
or your family will begin to disappear.
Do you understand?
[breathes heavily]
[ominous music playing]
[exhales]
-[Bree] How much longer?
-[Marcus] I'm almost done.
What'll it take?
Any traces of heroin or fentanyl,
and the DEA will reopen the investigation.
Okay, I'm done.
I'll test these back in my room.
All right.
-Jesus!
-Sorry, ma'am.
[Bree] What do you want?
-I thought I saw someone on the boat.
-It's just me.
-Can I help you with something?
-I… I was looking for Cane, actually.
[tense music playing]
-You check back at the fish house?
-Um…
I thought I saw him come down here,
but I guess I was wrong.
Can you actually
help me over the railings?
I have these… boots. It's Reggie, right?
-[Reggie] Yes, ma'am.
-Where are you from?
-From Florida, originally.
-[Bree] Oh!
-How are you liking Havenport?
-It's nice. A lot more peaceful.
[Bree laughs]
[Bree] Maybe I missed Cane in the office.
I'll check.
[tense music continues]
["Summer Breeze"
by Seals & Crofts playing]
♪ Blowin' through the jasmine in my mind ♪
♪ See the paper layin'… ♪
[line ringing]
Hey, Tim. Is, uh… Is Peyton okay?
[Tim] Yeah. Dropped Savannah at school.
At the hair salon now.
I got eyes on her.
She's sitting there on her cell phone.
All right. Okay. Thanks, buddy.
Okay, bye.
♪ …makes me feel fine ♪
♪ Blowin' through the jasmine in my mind ♪
Okay. Yeah, so these are
ten and one and a half.
Try both of them.
If one doesn't work, just bring it back.
Okay. Have a good day.
[Jenna clears throat]
What can I help you with, sir?
[inhales] I was just roaming the earth,
and it led me here, so…
Right.
Well, since you're here, I'm worried.
How's Peyton? Does she hate me?
No, no. She totally supports me doing
recreational drugs with old girlfriends.
[groans]
I'm sorry. Should I call her,
or will that make it worse?
No, no, it's already a scandal.
We've named it Gummy-gate.
[laughs]
So just let it lie. We'll move on,
make better choices. Yada-yada…
Yeah, right. Like, uh,
stopping by to see me unchaperoned.
I needed a friend, okay?
-And a drink, so…
-But you're the one with a bar.
[Jenna sighs]
[Cane inhales deeply]
Uh…
Yep.
-[Jenna] Mm.
-Your dad was always reliable.
Yeah, well, I don't know
how old that is. [chuckles]
The older the better, right?
So why do you need a friend?
-I just had a really bad day.
-I'm sorry.
Oh…
Oh, yeah.
So how's, uh, Scott?
-Seems like a real guy's guy.
-[Jenna laughs]
Uh, he took off.
Not because of the dinner, right?
He's not really good around sick people,
and my dad's really sick, so…
Truth is,
he's much happier in our marriage
when I'm not taking up
too much of his bandwidth.
Huh.
I'm sorry, Jenna.
[inhales deeply]
How is your dad doing?
Mm.
I brought in a nurse to help,
but he's not gonna get better.
That's a really hard thing to think about.
[Jenna sighs]
So, you're not the only one
who needs a friend.
[gentle music playing]
It'd be nice
if we could learn how to do that.
Yeah.
[indistinct chatter]
-[Harlan] Did something happen?
-The sheriff came by today.
[Harlan sighs]
What did he want?
Same old, same old.
Get in line or be burned alive.
I'll deal with him.
How?
-I could rip his throat out.
-I actually think you mean that.
But you can't. He's the police.
He can do whatever the fuck he wants.
Not if I rip his throat out.
You need to do whatever he says.
That's the deal,
and he's the devil we made it with.
This isn't the old days when your dad
was the big man everybody was afraid of.
We're in someone else's story.
We need to play the part they want us to.
-Peyton could have been killed.
-Yeah? Well, it could get a lot worse.
You need to talk to him and work it out.
[Harlan] I tried!
Then try harder!
Find some common ground!
Make him your friend.
Take him fishing, play some checkers.
Whatever it takes!
Play checkers?
Seriously, Harlan…
you need to win him over
and not do anything stupid,
you understand?
[atmospheric music playing]
He can make real trouble for us.
Okay?
[loudly] Okay?
Okay!
I'm going home.
Tell Bree to close up.
[bell clanging]
You know what, can you finish this for me?
I've gotta check on something. Thanks.
[phone buzzes]
[tapping on phone screen]
[message whooshes]
-You need some help?
-Sure, if you want.
-I can take that from you.
-Great. Thank you.
Hey, I thought that was you.
Your dad should be mayor.
Everyone loves him.
Well, they love a free drink.
Yeah. He does like to give them away.
Uh… he's faking it.
-Hey there, sir.
-Hey, Harlan.
How you been? All right?
I can tell when it's real.
[Shawn] But he's a good dad?
Mm…
Not always.
He can be.
Sometimes he even
has moments of spectacular.
But he can also fall short
in spectacular fashion.
Thank you so much, ladies.
You have a good night.
-What about you?
-Mm?
-You're from Texas, right?
-Yep.
What's your dad like?
I guess you could say they're similar.
Is he as handsome as you?
FYI, I'm seeing someone.
So am I. Lighten up.
-Hey, Shawn.
-Yes, sir.
-You got a bottle of Michter's back there?
-Uh…
It's locked in the back. I can go get it.
[Bree] I got this.
Your mama wants you to close tonight.
[sighs]
["Tennessee Whiskey"
by Chris Stapleton playing]
[phone chimes]
-[tapping on phone]
-[message whooshes]
♪ Used to spend my nights
Out in a barroom ♪
♪ Liquor was the only love I've known ♪
♪ But you rescued me
From reaching for the bottom ♪
[Jenna] Okay. I got snacks.
Ooh.
-You still writing for the Atlanta paper?
-I am. They don't know what to do with me.
They asked me to write this piece
on the preservation
of Outer Banks lighthouses,
and I'm dozing off
just telling you about it.
[chuckles softly]
So what happened today?
-The usual.
-Come on.
What's really going on with you?
The truth.
I guess I just…
made some pretty bad decisions, and…
I can't fix them.
And now they've affected
every area of my life.
Except for you.
You're the one sweet distraction
I have going right now.
[pensive music playing]
[exhales]
[music turns gritty]
["Moving" by John Fullbright
playing over speakers]
[knocking on door]
[Clyde] Yeah?
Come in.
I figured you'd show up again.
Then I didn't disappoint.
[Clyde]
I guess Belle told you I stopped by?
She did.
You come yelling at me at my work,
I figured I'd do the same.
You brought the good stuff.
What'd Belle tell you?
She thought it might be time
for you and me to share a drink.
Yeah, why not?
What's going on here?
Oh, I picked it up
at a car show last year.
A '70 Chevelle with a big-block V8
that ain't for shit, so I'm rebuilding it.
-[Harlan] Didn't you race some?
-[Clyde] A little stock car racing.
Amateur weekend shit.
Nothing serious, but that was long ago.
[chuckles] So what is it you want, Harlan?
Spit it out.
I want to make right
whatever's wrong between us.
I want us to move forward
in a less hostile fashion.
You think we can do that?
[breathing heavily]
[grunting and exhaling]
[panting]
[Belle] Ooh. Okay.
Oh.
-Oh, man.
-Oh, yeah.
[Wes] That was…
[softly] Fuck.
[exhales]
[Wes] …special.
Should we order some room service?
A steak?
A couple salads?
No, thank you. I'm not hungry. Thanks.
[softly] Fuck.
Uh, what about drinks?
Let's get more champagne.
I'm good.
You sure?
We could get a bottle of red.
Whatever you want.
-We could toast our new venture.
-Oh…
I should get back to work.
I need to close tonight.
Work? I thought you said
you were off tonight.
They said it's busy, so, uh, they need me.
[in singsong] Shoe, shoe,
shoe, shoe, shoe, shoe, shoe…
Thank you.
-Here you go.
-Thanks.
Okay.
-You feel guilty. You don't have to.
-No! No.
-God, that was just great, great sex.
-Yeah, yeah… Uh-huh.
[exhales]
[exhales] I want to thank you
for what's been a lovely time.
[softly] Yeah.
And, um… I want to be sure
this doesn't impact our business, okay?
Oh, no. No, I don't…
I don't work like that.
My lawyers just send yours
a few little contract stuff. That's all.
Small stuff.
-Okay, let's get it done. Okay.
-Okay. All right.
Oops.
Okay. Excuse me.
Thanks so much. Bye now.
[door closes]
[door opens]
Hey.
Where you been?
I had to close.
How are you?
What did your captain say?
Said it's not enough
to warrant a shadow operation.
Why not?
It costs money to tail a trawler.
Boats, drones, manpower.
It's a big number. Said no.
Did you show him everything?
Yes, I showed him everything.
The GPS info, the AIS, all of it.
-What about the hold?
-Inconclusive. The hold was clean.
Your brother and his boys are good.
[exhales in frustration]
Babe…
[Marcus] Mm.
-They want me to come home tomorrow.
-Wait, you're leaving?
I don't see how I can stay, Bree.
I just--
God, I just feel like such an idiot.
The captain didn't believe a thing I said.
He just kept asking about my sobriety.
It's gonna be okay. This too shall pass.
Please stop, stop. Just…
You don't want to be
anywhere near me right now, Bree.
I'm crawling out of my goddamn skin.
-You want to go to a meeting?
-I want to fucking shoot up, Bree.
You know the drill.
The highs are high, the lows are… too low.
[somber music playing]
What can I do?
Nothing.
Stop.
Would a little distraction help?
Stop, my--
[Marcus grunts]
I don't want to leave.
[music fades]
Where have you been?
I was scared to come home.
You threatened bodily harm.
You idiot.
Baby.
No, how hard is it for you to understand
that I want you to be here?
Okay.
I mean, I came home.
You should feel lucky
that you get to be here!
That you get to be with me,
that you get to have this family!
You're right.
I mean, you are absolutely right.
I… I messed up.
-[exhales]
-[Cane] I should have come home.
Things have been really crazy.
My head is all over the place.
Cane, you gotta start talking to me.
I'm not stupid. I know something's
going on with you and your dad.
No, you're not stupid.
Okay, I'm the stupid one.
But I'm here now, okay?
Why can't you be honest with me?
I'm trying. [breathes in]
I-- I want to do better.
I-- I want to be better.
Okay?
[low, hopeful music playing]
[sighs]
Come here.
[music rising]
[Cane exhales]
Well, for what it's worth, you did
a really good job with your shampoo
because your hair smells fantastic.
[chuckles emotionally]
[sobbing softly]
[Harlan] Oh, no. I've had enough.
Well, that's a first.
So, I've been thinking.
Oh, I knew it was coming.
Only took half a bottle.
It's real simple.
I know how to run drugs.
You know I know how.
My daddy taught me well.
So, here's the deal.
You put me in touch
with your supplier, Grady.
I organize the runs with him,
handle all the risk,
and still pay you your cut.
Anything happens, you're clean.
So you do want to cut me out.
You want to be cut out.
You're the law.
You need to stay clean
so you can protect my ass.
It's a smart play.
Efficient, mutually profitable.
You're still in charge.
Let me do what I do best,
and you do what you do,
and we keep the money the same.
Did you come here tonight
thinking I'd go for it?
Come on, Clyde. I need you.
It's the stupidest goddamn thing
I've heard.
You get to stay in control.
It's what you want.
Well, thank you
for letting me have control.
Jesus!
I know the game.
This is your first move, not your last.
You're making this more complicated
than it needs to be.
Because I can!
You don't have a choice.
You can come in here and talk nice,
come talk tough.
It don't matter. We do this my way.
Clyde,
listen to me.
I ain't playing
this grudge match bullshit.
Just know, this is on you.
I tried to make nice.
[cocks gun]
Sit.
[brooding music playing]
You won't use that.
Think it through.
This is not the move to make.
I think it's the only move.
'Cause we both know you ain't gonna stop.
I go away, so do my boats.
Well, I still have your son.
You know, we were doing fine without you.
He fell right in line.
And with you gone,
he'll be too scared to cross me.
You're being stupid, Clyde.
Hand me your gun.
I didn't bring a gun.
Well, now which one of us is stupid?
[grunting]
[chilling music playing]
-[grunts]
-[choking]
[groans]
[both grunting]
[Harlan yells]
[pants]
-[grunts]
-[wet crunch]
[groans]
[squelching thrust]
[gurgles]
[somber music playing]
[panting]
[groans]
Oh…
Oh, God.
Fuck.
[groans]
[heavy groaning]
["Can't You See"
by The Marshall Tucker Band playing]
♪ Can't you see? ♪
♪ Whoa, can't you see? ♪
♪ What that woman, Lord
She been doin' to me? ♪
♪ Can't you see? ♪
♪ Oh, can't you see? ♪
♪ What that woman ♪
♪ She been doin' to me? ♪
-♪ Can't you see? ♪
-♪ Oh, she's such a crazy lady ♪
-♪ What that woman ♪
-♪ What that woman she been doin' to me? ♪
-♪ Can't you see? Can't you see? ♪
-♪ Lord, I can't stand ♪
♪ What that woman, she been doin' to me? ♪
-♪ Can't you see? ♪
-♪ I'm gonna take a freight train ♪
-♪ I'm down at the station, Lord ♪
-♪ What that woman ♪
-♪ Ain't never comin' back, oh boy ♪
-♪ Can't you see? ♪
-♪ Gonna ride me a southbound, now ♪
-♪ All the way to Georgia, Lord ♪
-♪ What that woman ♪
-♪ 'Til the train run out of track ♪
[music ends]