[gritty music playing]
[seagulls crying]
[man over radio] Sector 29217,
we have spotted an object in the water,
and are investigating, 20 nautical miles
north-northeast of Havenport.
The object appears to be a net
with possible remains entangled.
[water sloshes as body is shifted]
[grunts softly]
Both victims appear to be deceased.
[gritty music continues and builds]
[ghostly echo ringing]
["Down in the Gulley"
by Brent Cobb playing]
♪ Well, my granddaddy was a good man ♪
♪ No matter what the papers say ♪
♪ All the weeds and pecan trees ♪
♪ Hid a secret we all swore to keep ♪
♪ Well, my granddaddy knew
What the law would do ♪
♪ If they ever come snoopin' 'round back ♪
♪ Lord, I'm down in the gulley ♪
♪ Where the creek is high ♪
♪ Lord, I'm down in the gulley
Where only the moon shines ♪
♪ It was down in the gulley ♪
♪ Where the creek is high ♪
♪ Lord, I'm down in the gulley
Where only the moon shines ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
What's going on?
Shawn. The… the new bartender.
Right.
Uh, the two fishermen, Troy and Curtis.
They found their bodies.
No shit.
-Do they know what happened?
-Got tangled in the nets and drowned.
Both of them?
I think one got tangled in the net
and went over,
and the other went in after or something.
Why? That's what life rafts are for.
I don't know. A freak accident.
-How did they both get tangled?
-That's why they call it a freak accident.
-How did it catch them--
-I don't know, Shane!
Shawn.
I'm not made of answers.
There's the Coast Guard. You can ask him.
[uneasy music lingering]
[Belle] The first ten plots
labeled 42B in your plans
are where you see those poles.
That's where the primary
resort structure will build.
The condos, Phase 2,
and the private residences, Phase 3,
are beyond that, so we'll drive out there.
No, no, no, not necessary.
Everybody is thrilled.
RNY can't wait
to break ground on this place.
Well, the preliminary paperwork
is signed and should be in your inbox.
-Let's get the formal docs to the lawyers.
-Absolutely.
You know, there's no reason
why we can't break ground this year.
I'm glad your company saw the opportunity.
-You designed all this yourself?
-I didn't exactly design it.
Well, you're the vision behind it.
-We'll need your involvement.
-I'm looking forward to that. Thank you.
So, where's your husband?
He's been absent through all this.
Oh, he's a busy man.
He entrusted it to me,
but I'm keeping him up to speed.
Don't worry about that.
He's excited to get started.
-How are the revisions, by the way?
-The revisions are superb.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Um… want to come back
to the hotel, and I'll show you?
-Grab a drink, celebrate.
-A little premature, isn't it?
No. Not at all. This is happening.
Do you ever eat
in any other restaurant besides your own?
[chuckles] Not really, no.
Well, let's change that.
I flew all the way here,
let me take you to dinner.
-Let me show you the other parcel.
-Okay.
[Clyde] I don't have a lot of time.
[Cane] What's going on?
The sheriff was telling me
about Troy and Curtis.
What's going on? Is the DEA investigating?
Two men drowned,
coroner ruled it an accident.
-Let's talk about your next run.
-Too soon for that.
The DEA is still in town.
I agree, but the original buyers
of the shipment need to be made whole.
-I need you to deliver it to them.
-That's a hard no.
We don't do the runs.
We have Reggie and Tim for that.
Well, I don't know Reggie or Tim.
After Hoyt's monumental disappointment,
I'm not chancing it.
No, it's you and Cane.
-Absolutely not.
-Dad… No.
-No.
-Okay, here we go again.
The Buckleys calling the shots.
I start to think this ain't gonna work.
What happened to "we're partners"?
Well, we are,
but there's always someone in charge.
It can't be you.
You look like shit lately.
-You sure you're up for this?
-We're old friends, Clyde.
You don't have to speak
through your asshole.
We can't do this.
We need to wait a little bit, okay?
I get a new burner every week.
Keep it on you at all times.
I call you, you don't call me.
Be vague, but specific.
-What the fuck is that supposed to mean?
-Plan for sunrise.
I'll text you the rest.
Don't make me regret this.
[huffs quietly]
You're okay with this?
Him just ordering you around like that?
I'm not okay with any of it,
but you got us into this.
-Not me. You!
-Yeah, look, I get it. I get it.
But we need to pump the brakes on this.
We-- we cannot trust him right now.
You saw what he did to Hoyt.
Blew his face off without batting an eye!
Trigger, blam! His face was gone.
[trembling] I can't stop seeing it.
You started this.
But I didn't actually do it.
I just gave them the boats to do it.
That and take the money.
We're in this, okay?
I'll figure something out.
But for right now, you gotta suck it up.
[uneasy music hangs in the air]
The menu out here
is more casual than inside.
So are the prices. Except the alcohol.
Is this open year-round?
Strictly seasonal.
This is for the swimsuit crowd.
We'll shut down in another month.
Yeah, just… help them set up.
I'll be right back.
Buddy, leave that here.
-Get some gloves and help in the ice room.
-[Diller] Yeah.
This is good. Okay?
Hey.
-What are you doing here?
-Granddad gave me a job.
Uh…
-Okay, well, he… He didn't ask me.
-Why would he?
Are you forgetting
there's a court order in place?
I can't be within 300 feet of you.
Then I'd go back in the restaurant
and count your steps as you go.
Diller, I could get in a lot of trouble.
Is that what you want?
Are you blaming me for your shit?
No.
No. No, I'm not, sweetheart.
Just… don't get comfortable.
Dad.
Why did you give Diller a job
without asking me?
Yeah, I'm out.
It's good for him to work.
You don't want to raise a couch spud.
If the court finds out,
I could lose visitation rights.
That's not gonna happen. I won't let it.
Nobody's gonna keep you
from seeing your son.
Not the courts,
your shit ex-husband… Nobody.
The boy's a Buckley. He should be here.
And you should get to see more of him.
Maybe you can fix some things.
I don't know, Dad.
Then go fire him. He's right over there.
[faint bittersweet music playing]
[Belle] I never liked Clyde.
Even in high school, he was a prick.
You gonna be able to handle him?
He's got an axe to grind, that's for sure.
He loves me kissing his ass.
-Okay, so what do we do?
-You kiss his ass.
-Unless you have another way.
-How bad are we sunk?
We're four months behind on both mortgages
and two months behind on the loan.
-How much?
-[exhales] Roughly $6.8 million.
How are we not in default?
Willis at National
gave us a three-month extension
due to our number of employees
and the impact it'd have on the town.
-So, layoffs are off the table.
-We're not laying anyone off.
Then we have to come up
with $2 million in less than three months
to bring us up to date.
Won't save us,
but we won't lose everything.
Yeah, and with consistent runs,
we should be good in a few months.
Here's the thing.
There's no way
Porter is the top dog in this.
He's answering to someone.
[Belle] Hmm.
Like a supplier.
If we can find his supplier
and establish our own supply line,
then we don't even need Porter.
-That's how we make this really work.
-Dad… I hear you.
It just sounds a bit intense.
[Belle] This is a temporary situation.
We're not gonna make a business out of it.
Those days are over.
Yes, but with no Porter,
we negotiate a higher fee
and get out faster.
Or…
we could, and hear me out here,
partner with a developer
and build out the beachfront.
It would solve everything.
Not right away, but eventually.
-Why would you bring that up?
-Because it's a real option.
Hell, we're gonna lose it anyway
if we can't pay the bank back.
We're not touching that land.
You know that.
-Not now, not ever.
-I know how much it means to you.
God damn it. No.
-It's not a conversation.
-Granddaddy!
Hey.
Hello, darling.
-How'd it go today?
-It's all but done.
-Waiting on the lawyers.
-You'll have to tell him at some point.
Did you not hear me? I tried.
Yeah, yeah.
He's gonna explode when he finds out.
[exhaling] Oh, shit.
It's all so fucked up, man.
[huffs] I mean, you see him, right?
-I mean, he's acting w-weird, right?
-[snorts]
Like he's enjoying it?
Yeah.
Crime always did agree with him.
-[Peyton] Hi, baby.
-Hi.
Hi, Peyton. How are you?
-I'm fine, Belle. How you doing?
-Great, thank you.
Good.
-Okay, let's get the table.
-[huffs]
[insincerely] Enjoy.
["I'm a King Bee"
by Peter Frampton Band playing]
♪ Buzzin' 'round your hive ♪
♪ Well, I'm a king bee ♪
♪ Well, I can make honey, baby ♪
♪ Let me come inside ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I'm young and able ♪
♪ To buzz all night long ♪
-[Bree panting]
-[dresser thumping against wall]
♪ I'm young and able ♪
[panting]
♪ To buzz all night long ♪
[moans and pants]
[light switch clicks off]
[music fades]
[Bree sighs]
Why are you so quiet?
I'm… discontent.
-We just killed that dresser, come on.
-[chuckles]
[Marcus sighs sharply]
God, I need a meeting. [exhales]
-Have you been going to meetings?
-I've been working.
There are meetings
in every church in this town.
-I go every day.
-I mean, wha-- You kind of have to.
You got the nudge
from the judge. [chuckles]
How many meetings
have you been to since rehab?
-I don't know. I forget.
-Zero?
Yeah. That's it.
Mm-hmm.
Isn't it mandatory for an agent?
I mean… everyone fudges it.
-Another reason I'm an addict anyway.
-[snorts]
[Bree sighs]
[Bree sucks teeth]
"Hi, my name is Bree."
"I'm an alcoholic and a pillhead."
Hi, Bree.
Thank you. Uh…
Today was a shit day.
I hate my job.
My son hates me.
Uh, the one highlight was an amazing,
but far too brief, sloppy fuck.
[chuckles]
Would anyone else care to share?
-[Marcus] Mm.
-How about the man with no clothes?
[Marcus sighs]
Hi, my name is Marcus.
I'm a heroin addict.
[recites] Hi, Marcus.
Let's see,
I spent another day in… bumfuck nowhere,
investigating a bumshit case
that's probably gonna get me fired
and ruin my career.
But I, uh, fucked a motel dresser
to death, and that was fun.
-Could you really lose your job?
-There's nothing here, Bree.
Boat was clean,
no trace of drugs, the men drowned.
I witnessed it with my own two eyes.
I saw Cane with Troy and Curtis and Hoyt,
and they were talking about a drug run.
-Did you talk to Hoyt?
-I can't find Hoyt. No one can.
Jesus Christ.
You might be right about your brother,
but to make a drug bust, I need drugs.
And there's nothing.
It's my first case out of rehab.
I'm on probation.
-They could fucking bench me.
-Follow Cane.
-He'll lead you to Hoyt.
-What about your mom and dad?
-No…
-Would they want to help me? Hear me out.
If they knew he used the fish house
for drugs, wouldn't they want to know?
-No. You told me, you promised me…
-Bree.
…you'd leave them out of this.
They have nothing to do with it.
This started when my brother
took over the business.
That's when Hoyt started showing up.
Cane is the one you want.
What's your deal with Cane?
Why do you want to expose him?
Why do you hate him so much?
I have my reasons.
[exhales]
Some of the agents are starting to leave.
I've got a few more days myself.
Well, I'm sorry I brought you here.
But I'm right about this.
Everything happens for a reason.
You know…
when I was undercover and shooting up,
phew, I knew I was in trouble.
-You know I OD'd, right?
-Mm-mm.
I was dead for over a minute.
I came back,
and that's what put me in rehab.
-I think that was to meet you.
-[softly] Yeah…
I'm sorry.
-Mm-hmm.
-[Marcus] I don't want to leave.
-Not when it's this good.
-[playfully] Mm-hmm!
That's the addiction talking.
You know that, right? Yes.
[coughs softly]
Trust me. I have been sober a few times.
It's transference. [giggles]
It's a distraction.
Anything to keep your mind off using.
-Oh, yeah? Is that what you think?
-That's what I know.
Now, don't get me wrong.
You're cute
and I'm into you and all, but… [inhales]
I'd shoot a fireball
up my ass right now if I had one.
[laughing]
-Yeah, I bet you would.
-Mm-hmm.
[chuckling]
Hey, did Cane tell you
Jenna's back in town?
-"Jenna" Jenna?
-Mm-hmm.
No, I didn't know.
I can imagine Peyton's
popped a few blood vessels over it.
[Harlan] What is it?
You got me paranoid
about the new bartender.
Why?
Could he be a DEA informant
that Porter told you about?
He's not a very good bartender.
I think it's time we give Bree
a little more responsibility.
-She wants back in the office.
-Stop. Do not go soft on her.
I want one full year of sobriety
before we ease the reins.
If we give in now,
she'll get right back to it.
Do not let her manipulate you.
It's for her own good, okay?
We're confirmed for dinner tomorrow
with Jenna and Scott.
Oh!
That's happening.
-Mm-hmm.
-Okay. Um…
Where are we going?
Well, Jenna misses
your mom's hush puppies.
-Here?
-Mm-hmm.
-Okay.
-[chuckles softly]
Okay.
We can cancel if you want to.
Um…
Cancel or reschedule?
-What do you want?
-[chuckles]
It's your call.
Mm.
How are the drinks?
Can I get you anything?
-I'm good.
-I'll have a Zombie, please.
A Zombie? Yep. Okay. Coming up.
[whispering] Watch.
He doesn't even know what a Zombie is.
[Harlan] A Zombie.
Good God, you're paranoid.
Well, you started it.
This is our life now,
always looking over our shoulder.
I'm sorry.
I've been waiting
for the right time to say it.
Not sure this is it.
Sorry for what?
Everything.
[scoffs]
You need to be more specific.
[inhales deeply]
For all the drinking…
the carousing, the women.
For disappointing you.
Honey, I stopped having expectations
a long time ago.
I'm sorry.
You're so good at sorry.
It's the staying sorry you struggle with.
[bell clangs]
[dolly rattling over wooden boards]
-Hey, uh, who are you?
-Stevie.
-Where's Porter?
-I think you mean Owen.
-Is Owen coming?
-[Stevie] He sent me.
We need to get this in the hold, fast.
Why does Owen get to have a Stevie,
but we can't have a Tim and Reggie?
There's two more behind this one.
Let's go, before the sun comes up.
Okay.
[ominous music playing]
[grunts]
[boat engine rumbling to a start]
[engine running]
[ominous music builds]
[boat motor winds down and stops]
Why are we stopping?
Aren't we meeting them here in the sound?
The ocean's choppy today.
Here, take the wheel.
This one's yours.
What? No.
-I don't want a gun. Why do I need a gun?
-Relax.
It's not loaded.
The other guys will have guns too.
Why give me a gun without any bullets?
So when they rip it out of your hands,
they can't shoot you with it.
Here. Take it.
-Seriously, why do we need guns?
-It's all a pissing contest.
-You have to know how to present yourself.
-Okay, I'll be fine. I'm not an idiot.
What do I do with it?
Put it here like you're doing?
-Is that good?
-Never show fear. No sudden movements.
It makes people nervous.
Did Granddad send you to mob school?
Your grandfather
could handle himself in any situation.
Well, except for that one time.
Listen, god damn it.
You want to always keep eye contact.
Roaming eyes tells people
you can't be trusted.
And here's the hardest part of all.
Don't speak.
The less you say, the better.
Words get you killed.
[uneasy music playing]
-You're from Texas, right?
-Yes, ma'am. Galveston originally.
What'd you do down there?
Bartend, mostly.
In an Outback in Port Aransas.
How'd you end up in Havenport?
I wanted a change,
and I like being by the water.
There's a lot of water in this world.
Why Havenport?
I don't know. I just did.
-Is there a problem, Ms. Buckley?
-Nope.
Nosy me. Excuse me.
[suspenseful music playing]
[typing]
[suspenseful music continues]
What are you doing in here?
We ran out of staples and pens
in the restaurant.
Are those radars?
New models.
The sonar range is double the old models.
We didn't have portable radars
when I was a kid.
-We had to find the fish on our own.
-You know how to fish?
Eh, it's been a minute, but yeah,
your granddad used to take me
when I was little.
He said he would take me.
-Does your dad know you're here?
-It's only like two shifts.
I'm gonna have to tell him.
I have to be transparent, Diller.
-I could get in a lot of trouble.
-Yeah, you deserve it.
I know.
[exhales]
All right, I'll make a deal with you.
Don't tell Dad, and I won't tell
Child Services what a whack job you are.
I think they know.
Why do you want to work here so badly?
You should be happy
I hate TikTok and Adderall.
-That's not an answer.
-It's cool.
And Granddad's a badass.
All right, I'll take your deal.
But you cannot miss school or swim team,
and your grades have to stay up.
Can you just drop the mom talk?
Please. You are not great at it.
I'm trying my best.
Well, it's a shame your "best"
gets you arrested,
thrown in jail and shit.
[door closes]
[sighs]
[atmospheric music playing]
[sniffles]
[sobs quietly]
[music sharpens into gritty pulse]
Hello, gentlemen.
Let's get you tied off.
[seagulls screeching above]
[tense music playing]
Keep a watch.
[grunting]
[grunts]
[tense music continues]
You're ten kilos short.
No. Count again.
I counted four times.
You're ten kilos short.
-[Harlan] It's what we were given.
-And you're ten kilos short.
What the hell you want me to do about it?
That's all of it.
-[grunts]
-Whoa! Hey, hey!
-We don't fuck around.
-[Cane] No, no, no.
Hey, hey, hey! Let him go!
Okay, okay, okay.
It's all good.
No sudden movements.
No roaming eyes.
I can be trusted. Boom. Take it.
I don't need it. Take it. You know why?
Because we're friendly. We're friends.
This is a friendly exchange.
Stop talking.
Thing is, this is my fault.
I don't know the rules.
Ask him. He's my dad. Ask him.
I must've weighed the drugs improperly,
or the scale was off or something.
I mean, goddamn metric system.
I mean, kilos? Come on. What happened
to just weighing in pounds and ounces?
Where the hell are we right now, right?
I'm stupid, but here's the thing,
I'm not so stupid as to think
I could steal from you guys.
Ten kilos. Is that worth dying over?
Fuck no!
It was a God's honest mistake,
and we will make it up to you.
Okay? We'll make it up to you.
In the end, everybody gets made here.
We can do that if we just--
If we just call Porter.
-Let's call Porter right now.
-Who?
Po-Porter-- Owen.
Owen! Owen! Let's call Owen right now.
I got my phone in my pocket here.
Or you can call him. [breathes shakily]
Just please call Owen, right now. Please.
Please call him.
Please.
These two assholes
just showed up ten kilos short.
-Okay. Yeah.
-Jesus.
Yeah, okay.
All right. Thanks, Grady.
What?
It's cool. Come on. Let's get out of here.
[sighs in relief]
[softly] Thank you.
[atmospheric music playing]
You okay?
[breathing heavily]
[exhales]
Oh, shit.
-Oh, shit.
-[boat engine starts]
-[man] Right.
-Makes sense.
So I've been meaning to ask,
why are you deciding to build now?
People have been chasing
your waterfront for years.
It's a very sentimental piece of property
my husband inherited.
His father bought it for his mother,
and it was her wish for it to remain
a little piece of Havenport. Untouched.
A lasting symbol
of community, family, legacy.
So why the change of heart?
I'm a realist.
-And I believe in change.
-Mm.
-We're struggling. Everybody's struggling.
-Yeah.
The fishing industry's near extinct.
Restaurant's seasonal.
We live and die on tourism.
It'd be irresponsible
if we didn't develop it.
-True.
-We provide jobs for a lot of people.
-Yeah.
-And there's a responsibility in that.
-You're very protective over it.
-Well, I grew up here.
Not on the water.
More inland, less money.
Me too.
I grew up dirt poor.
I know it well.
So you know
what a driving force it can be?
I hate being broke.
It's paralyzing. Soul-killing.
Can be.
Okay, you're very good with the oysters.
I'm in the seafood business.
-Well, it's very sexy.
-There it is.
-I thought you were flirting with me.
-I was trying not to. It's hard.
-I'm sorry. I was trying. I'm--
-Okay, okay.
I guess I'm just attracted
to talent and visionaries.
Uh-huh.
That's a really good line.
-It-- It sounds like a line.
-Sounds like a line.
-Fully.
-I'm okay with it 'cause it's the truth.
We're business partners.
It would be very bad if we…
-And I'm married.
-Yeah.
-Right.
-So am I.
-Doesn't seem to stop my wife.
-I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm dealing with it.
I love my wife, but…
I finally came to the realization that
you can't get everything from one person.
[indistinct chatter]
[clears throat]
Hello. Where's Peyton?
Uh, she's gonna meet us here.
I was just over at the fish house.
[sniffs]
-But you smell so clean.
-Yeah, where I showered and changed.
Mm.
[exhales] So what are you doing?
Just hanging out at the bar,
drinking by yourself?
Your bartender Shawn
has been keeping me company.
He's new in town.
I'm giving him the skinny.
-Evening, Mr. Buckley.
-Can I do a bourbon with ice, please?
Actually, you know what?
Make it a double in a tall glass.
Tall glass.
Yes, sir.
I've had an insane day, okay?
I think the bourbon's gonna help.
Mm-hmm.
So, where's your amazing
superman of a husband?
Running late.
Yeah?
He works too much. It's his flaw.
Yeah, 'cause making a lot of money
is always a detriment.
Mm.
-[inhales]
-[Cane] Mm.
[exhales uncomfortably]
-I'm a little nervous.
-Why's that?
My husband
and my high school boyfriend meeting?
-Aren't you nervous?
-[scoffs] No.
Okay, well, I'm nervous.
Yeah, okay.
-Yeah, I might be a little bit nervous.
-Mm.
[huffs]
Yeah.
I took a gummy.
You want one?
-Fuck, yeah.
-Okay. Oh, and let's do shots.
-[slams counter]
-Scratch the bourbon.
We're doing tequila shots, okay?
Line them up.
-A blanco.
-[gasps]
-Yeah.
-Always.
-[giggles]
Oh, man.
Okay.
-To…
-Yeah.
-[snorts]
-It's okay.
Mm.
-[Cane] That's good.
-[Jenna] Mm!
[Cane] Mm.
I'm so glad we're finally doing this.
Scott, it's lovely to meet you.
I'm happy to finally get this way.
-Mmm, wow.
-[chuckling] Somebody's hungry.
Oh, you have to try these.
I missed these hush puppies so much.
His mom has a secret recipe.
[chuckling]
-Mm.
-Uh-huh.
-[Jenna chuckles]
-Mm!
They're certainly fried.
[Jenna giggles]
Me and Cane used to come here
every day after school,
and we'd have chowder
and eat hush puppies,
and then we'd take the sailboat out.
Do you still have the little Sunfish?
-No. Gave it away years ago.
-No?
-Mm.
-Peyton, how do ya fit in this love story?
-No love story.
-It was a long time ago.
I meant growing up here,
when you were all in school together.
Well, I was a freshman
when they were both seniors,
so we didn't run in the same circles,
but they were the "it" couple.
-Pretty and popular.
-I…
No one is prettier than you.
Peyton was a looker in school,
and you still are, so…
-Yeah.
She is and will be forever.
You know, Peyton was, uh,
Miss Teen Carolina.
No, I was not. I was top ten.
Nine, to be exact,
and let's just leave it there.
Question. I'm driving up here,
and I see the name Buckley everywhere.
Does your family own the entire town?
-No.
-Just the harbor and the restaurant.
The Buckleys have always been
a prominent family here.
Jenna tells me
you were the high school football star?
You should try the grouper.
It's delicious.
[tapping on table]
-[hits silverware]
-Yes, I was, Scott.
I was a football star. I was very good.
And that you were, uh…
You were gonna go pro, and you never did.
-What happened?
-No, it was a dream.
-It was a kid's dream.
-[Scott] Mm.
And then I grew up.
Who needs a pro football career
when you can stay in this tiny little town
and shovel fish?
That's… That's not exactly what happened.
And he doesn't exactly shovel fish.
Close enough.
I need another drink.
You guys need another drink?
And I apologize in advance
if I offend you.
-Okay.
-But…
do you want to come back
to my hotel? [chuckles]
Why don't we just
keep this about the work?
Do you know
how to compartmentalize, Belle?
Yes. Story of my life.
Well, me too.
And I'm very good at it.
My career, my marriage…
You seem curious. You a little curious?
[giggling]
Nope, I'm afraid not.
No strings.
No stress. Like… just a beautiful memory.
I can't tell you how entertaining
this has been, but I'm gonna say no.
Let's keep us about the work.
Understood.
I won't bring it up again.
You're a delight, Belle,
and I will call you soon.
-Good night.
[blows raspberry]
[pulsing bass line music playing]
Hey.
[music builds]
[exhales]
You're right, I was curious.
Good night.
[music fades]
[exhales]
[Jenna] No, it's…
So, what was it that broke you two up?
-Oh.
-Uh…
Life happened, Scott.
Life happened, uh, and it ended.
The first love is never last love, is it?
-I like that song.
-I don't think it's a song.
I think it's the lyrics
to, like, every song.
-You think…
-[giggles]
Excuse me, I'm gonna be right back.
You know, we should think
about going. The sitter?
[Cane] Right.
Oh…
-[Scott] I'll get the bill.
-No, no, no, no, it's on the house.
It's, uh… There's no bill.
It's the perks of a broken dream,
you know?
Well, then, I guess I'll go take a piss
and let you two be you two.
[sputters]
-What was in that edible?
-Oh, Jesus.
God, I'm so stoned.
-I can't even keep my head straight.
-Did they know? Or did we do okay?
No, they know. Yeah.
-Peyton was shooting death rays at me.
-No.
-And now she-- she hates me. I'm awful.
-No, you're paranoid. She doesn't care.
She-- She… She's fine.
-No, the gummies were a bad idea.
-[laughs]
No, I-- I just thought it would help with…
[inhales]
Help at what?
I don't-- I don't think we should do
dinners anymore. [clears throat]
And why's that?
Cane, just don't.
Let-- let's just not talk right now.
Can we do that?
[smacks lips]
I will say,
I thought the gummies were a great idea.
[chuckles nervously]
[sighs]
[muffled rock music playing]
Nice Jet Skis.
For my boys and their kids.
I was hoping it'd get them down
to see me more, but nope.
Nice car.
I like my toys.
You shorted the shipment.
No, I didn't.
That turd Hoyt
dipped into it prior to his, um…
[laughs maliciously]
[chuckling] And then I just thought,
well… let's see how well
you and your son perform under duress.
We could've been killed.
Yeah, there's always that chance.
No, I figured, you know,
someone would call me first,
but, you know, when that didn't happen,
yeah, I was a little worried.
[tools crash onto floor]
-[Harlan] Come on, get up.
-[Clyde puffs]
[panting]
[sniffles] You remember
the night your daddy got shot up?
What were you? 29? 30?
I was just a deputy then.
[panting]
It was… It was a bad night.
All they did to him, the blood everywhere.
[huffs] Jesus, it was awful.
I felt so sorry for you,
finding your daddy dead like that.
Little Bree all covered in blood.
And then, like a week later,
I found you in-- in-- in Turner's,
sitting at the bar, drinking all alone.
Do you remember any of this?
I remember.
[Clyde grunts]
I was… downright sad for you.
And I ordered you a beer,
but-- but you wouldn't let me pay for it.
You refused.
I said, "No, I want to buy you a beer,"
but you wouldn't have it.
You had to pay.
You insisted.
You said, "A cop don't make much.
Save your money. I got it."
I was grateful to you.
I wanted to pay.
Yeah, that's the way it is
with you Buckleys.
You pay, you control…
You're always in charge.
When a friend wants to buy you a beer,
you let him.
Okay, Clyde.
You can buy the beer.
You can buy all the beer.
Oh God, I fucking hated you.
[tense music playing]
Everybody loved you,
so I had to love you too,
but I despised you.
Well, not anymore. [chuckles]
Now I enjoy you.
I mean,
watching you and your family struggle…
[exhales]
…hell, it makes me happy.
[chuckles]
You worked really hard for that badge.
And the power.
And now… I'm in charge.
I thought that was Grady.
Yeah, who's Grady?
Your supplier.
Who told you that?
-Tell him I want to meet him.
-Why?
So you can go around me? Cut me out?
I wouldn't advise it.
No more runs until I meet Grady.
[tense music continues]
[thunder rumbles]
[Cane] Sorry, I'm a little drunk.
A little?
And I may or may not
have had a tiny little gummy.
And where'd you get the gummy?
-From Jenna.
-[scoffs]
What?
I've had the worst day. You have no idea.
Can I… Can I please just get
a pass on this one? I feel queasy.
And I feel humiliated.
What was that tonight? Was that foreplay?
What?
I-- I thought we were being
completely respectful.
-[scoffs]
-I think. I don't remember everything.
But I'm really,
really sorry about the gummy.
This isn't funny, Cane.
It's a little funny. [titters]
Peyton, you put the dinner together.
You didn't think
it would be, like, a little weird?
You are so glib when you should be
begging for forgiveness.
Peyton, please,
can we just, like, laugh it off?
[beeping as car unlocks]
I'm sorry, okay, baby? I'm sorry.
You were so obvious!
I wish you'd step out of your bullshit
for five seconds, look at what you are.
All you do is bitch about your dad.
He's a drunk. He's a pig.
He doesn't understand you.
But the joke's on you, hon,
'cause you're already him.
That is not true.
You just don't see it 'cause
you still got your training wheels on.
There's a problem with this metamorphosis
you're going through.
It's me.
I'm not your mother. I don't see things
the way she sees them, and I never will.
So turn your ass around
and start heading in the other direction
because I will only take so much.
[engine turns over]
[tires screeching]
[distant thunder rumbling]
[rain pattering]
[door opens]
-[thunder rumbling]
-[puffs]
Hiding from Mom?
No.
[Cane] Are you, uh,
having a little moment?
Peering into your soul?
Porter's a problem.
We have to find Grady…
and end ties with Porter.
[exhales]
Why did Porter set us up today?
That was for me.
He was testing me.
Testing us.
I thought we were gonna die.
[Harlan] You're not
on the sidelines anymore.
You're in it.
But you're gonna have to toughen up.
Okay.
[Cane sucks teeth]
You know, I wouldn't be so bold
as to expect a compliment
or a pat on the back
or anything like that, but…
I think we could both acknowledge
I'm the reason we didn't get killed today.
You think what you did was smart?
Smart? No, I wouldn't say that, but…
it was the truth.
And I was scared shitless, man.
[chuckles softly]
Yeah, it got a little scary.
I'm sorry I broke your rules.
You got lucky. You try that shit again,
I guarantee you'll be killed.
Here we go. Condemnation.
I'm looking out for you, son.
I'm trying to protect you.
Protect me?
I think the word you mean is "control,"
but that's okay. We can go with "protect."
You don't know this world the way I do.
You need to listen to me.
No, you need to listen to me.
I will do this,
but I'm gonna do it my own way.
I'm not worried about Porter.
You wouldn't either if you could just
put aside your ego for two seconds, Pop.
You're a fool.
[distant thunder rumbling]
At least I'm not you.
[pensive music playing]
[rain pattering]
[Marcus] Yeah?
-I found it.
-What?
Something Cane
doesn't want anyone to know.
And it will crucify him.
[Marcus exhales]
[Shawn] No, it is going to take more time,
because I barely had time to talk to him.
No, you need to have more patience--
I have to go. I'll call you back.
Well, that was heated.
[Shawn exhales]
Personal.
No worries.
-Let me give you a hand.
-Oh, no, ma'am.
I'm-- I'm almost done.
I was just about to take off.
Who are you?
I'm sorry?
You're a shit bartender.
You know that, right?
-Are you firing me?
-I called your references.
Granted, Bree should've
done that already, but you met her.
Turns out the Outback in Port Aransas,
where you claimed to work,
has no record of you.
Well, did you--
Did you talk to the manager?
They have such turnover, it's--
It's a mistake is all.
The mistake, Shawn,
is that there is no Outback
in Port Aransas,
and there never has been.
[somber music playing]
Are you an informant?
A what?
Did the DEA send you?
-No, ma'am.
-You lying piece of shit.
-I'm not lying.
-One more time.
-My name is Shawn West.
-One more fucking time!
-Who are you?
-I told you. My name is Shawn West.
-I'm from Galveston.
-Don't fuck with me!
-[glass shatters]
-Okay!
-Do not!
-Bebe West!
Bebe?
My mom.
[breathing heavily]
She died last month in Galveston.
Before she passed,
she told me Harlan Buckley was my father.
[somber music rising]
[exhales]
[brooding musical sting]
[gasps]
[breathing shakily]
[panting]
-Come here! Shut up!
-No! No! No!
No! Help! Somebody, please! Help me!
Help, help!
-[Peyton grunts]
-[violent thud]
[groaning]
[screaming]
Stop!
[Peyton coughs]
[shrieking]
Stop, stop!
[chilling music rising]
[Peyton shrieking]
[screaming]
[closing theme music playing]
[music fades]