[unsettling music playing]
[soft rumbling]
[exhales]
[grunts]
[waves slap against moving boat]
[unsettling music continues]
[man 1] You wanna head back, or what?
-[man 2] Not until we're past the barrier.
-[man 1] Okay, good.
[sudden music sting]
[door closes]
[unsettling music rising]
[music fades]
[ghostly echo ringing]
Hey, Harlan.
Honey, wake up.
Bree didn't come home last night.
When was the last time you saw her?
At the fish house,
when we were cleaning up the office.
Think it could've been too much for her?
Maybe she needed a drink.
No, we talked it all through.
She was fine when she left.
Well, what are you implying?
Could Grady have done something with Bree?
[sighs]
-Where are you going?
-To get ready. I've got shit to do.
Excuse me, our daughter is missing,
and there are two bodies in our ice room.
I hear you. I will deal with it.
[sighs]
You and Shawn go to the restaurant.
Be around people.
[door closes]
[dull scraping]
[cuts off shower]
[thudding]
[explosive music starts]
[panting]
[brooding music playing]
[gasps] Jesus! Cane!
[sighs in relief] Jesus Christ.
-What the hell is wrong with you?
-I didn't know you were coming home.
Oh, clearly.
Jesus Christ.
-[Peyton exhales]
-Where's Savannah?
I left her with my parents.
[Cane] Oh, Jesus Christ.
Listen to me, baby.
You cannot be here right now.
It's not safe.
[scoffs] What are you talking about?
[panting]
What did you do, Cane?
Okay, we-- we've been smuggling heroin
with this guy who's got a poppy field
about an hour away from here.
Well, he-- he had a poppy field.
I kinda, um-- I kinda burned it down.
Jesus, Cane.
Bottom line, it is not safe
for you to be here right now.
-That's convenient.
-Listen, I'm not lying to you!
I can't have anything happen to you!
Where were you the other night?
[breathing heavily]
I was at work.
Oh, bullshit.
I have the Ring app on my phone.
I know every time
you've walked in and out that door.
You haven't slept here
the past two nights.
So let's try this again.
The truth this time.
I don't have enough time
to be dealing with this shit.
-To be working through this--
-Damn it, Cane.
I can't deal with this now.
You have to trust me on this.
Tell me the truth, Cane.
Okay.
Uh, yeah, I slept with Jenna.
Oh my God.
[Cane] I don't know what happened.
I just, uh…
It happened.
I don't know what to do now.
I don't know what to say to you.
I-- I don't know, um…
I don't know anything.
[voice breaking] Do you love her?
I love you, Peyton.
[tense music playing]
Okay?
Well, I hate you.
And I hate her.
I warned her.
Peyton, listen to me. This is not on her.
-This is on me. So if you have any anger--
-I've got enough to go around.
-Peyton, listen to me. This is not on her.
-Don't fucking touch me!
[tense music builds]
-You find your sister?
-No.
-I was too busy destroying my marriage.
-Something happen?
I should have left this town
a long time ago, but I didn't.
I just wish I was somewhere
other than here. Anywhere.
Are you done?
Yeah.
I left word with Rodney and Diller.
They're not picking up.
If Grady actually took Bree, then why?
I mean, why? Why?
If it was a ransom situation,
he would have called with demands
and a deal already, right?
He wouldn't actually kill Bree.
We burned up his entire operation.
[suspenseful music playing]
[phone buzzing]
HB! I was wondering
if I might hear from you.
Grady, you need to listen to me.
No, I don't listen to you.
You listen to me.
We're going to make an even swap, okay?
You, for your daughter.
Come alone, she lives.
Break that one simple rule,
and she dies.
-Where are ya?
-I'll text you the rest of the details.
[call disconnects]
What happened? Wha-- what did he say?
[phone buzzing]
Coordinates.
He wants to meet
in the middle of the goddamn ocean.
Okay.
-We need a plan now.
-I got a plan. Get our daughter back.
That's not a plan, Harlan.
-I'm coming with you.
-[Harlan scoffs]
-You go by yourself, he's gonna kill you.
-If you come, he'll kill us both.
Harlan, they're right.
You won't come back,
and Bree won't either.
You're all acting like
there's some other option. There isn't.
What if there is?
[suspenseful music playing]
[crying]
[gasping]
[exhales]
Peyton, what are you doing here?
-I told you I would come for you.
-I just came from the hospital.
My dad passed last night.
[somber music playing]
[sobbing]
You're gonna be okay.
[continues sobbing]
-[Emmett] Thank you for calling me, Belle.
-Thank you.
God, you Buckleys
are always in the thick of it, you know.
Right in the eye of the storm.
That's the wrong analogy.
The eye of the storm
is where it's the calmest.
That's not where we're at, is it?
Am I wrong to be in business
with the Buckleys again? I mean, does…
Does Harlan still carry a grudge?
What do you think? You killed his father.
Is that something you could ever forget?
[inhales] Well…
You sure made a… success of this here.
-Of course, you had my family's money.
-Yes, we did.
Gosh, we have--
we have so much history, Belle.
You know, I remember you
when you were in your teenage years.
-So, so beautiful.
-Mm.
And I must admit, I'm--
I mean, I'm a little surprised
you stayed married to Harlan.
You know, he's a-- he's a hard man.
-He sure is.
-Yeah.
How's that going?
What do you think?
We have our troubles just like everybody.
Yeah, I suspected as much.
Given the debt y'all are facing.
[lock engages forcefully]
[tense music creeping in]
See, I know all about
your financial situation.
That busted-up land deal.
Wes Benson, he's a piece of work.
Took you for a ride.
Although, for what it's worth,
you were right to develop the property.
See?
I'm on your side, Belle.
I'm on your side, and I… I hope you know
that Harlan's not what he used to be.
Maybe you should be in charge.
If you ever needed a favor,
I could be a friend to you.
[tense music rising]
[music turns gritty]
-[clack]
-[grunts in pain]
[gasps]
Mom?
Diller?
-What are you doing here?
-I saw them take you.
Oh God.
No, you-- you can't-- You can't be here.
-How are you here?
-I heard you yelling in the boatyard.
And I came to watch.
And I saw those guys grab you.
-Did anyone see you?
-No, I climbed the bow's tie.
-I hid in the line locker.
-How long have we been out here?
Maybe two hours.
How many men did you see?
There's four guys.
One's the captain, plus Grady.
We're gonna figure this out.
We're gonna figure it out.
[man] I dunno what he's doing with her.
[continues speaking indistinctly]
You need to get in here.
Do not make a sound.
-What?
-You have to hide.
-What about you?
-I'm right here. Right here.
Do not say anything. They cannot find you.
[suspenseful music playing]
Let's go.
Come on. Now.
["Brandy (You're A Fine Girl)"
by Looking Glass playing over speakers]
♪ Lonely sailors pass the time away ♪
♪ And talk about their homes ♪
[Grady] ♪ There's a girl
In this harbor town ♪
♪ And she works laying whiskey down ♪
♪ They say
"Brandy, fetch another round" ♪
♪ She serves them whiskey and wine ♪
Come on, sing with me.
♪ The sailors say
"Brandy, you're a fine girl" ♪
♪ What a good wife you would be ♪
[chuckles]
I'm Grady.
[scoffs] I cannot believe
it has taken us this long to meet.
I thought we could, uh,
get to know each other a little better.
What?
Look.
I just talked to your dad.
He's on his way out here right now.
I thought we could… share a meal?
-We gotta kill the time somehow, right?
-My dad's coming?
Yeah, literally as we speak.
Please, have a seat.
[Bree clears her throat]
You know,
I thought if we got to know each other,
you might see we got
more in common than you think.
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
-You want something to drink?
-I'll have a vodka, neat.
Okay, but, uh…
Aren't you a, you know, like a, like a--
Blugh, right?
Make it a double.
You know what, bring the whole bottle.
Whoa, okay.
Fuck it. Rock and roll, right?
A vodka for the lady, please.
Ah!
Oh, here we go.
Bon appetit.
By the way, I'm gonna…
cut your meat for you.
I hope you understand
I can't let you have a knife, so…
You'll have to eat this with a spoon.
Oh, no.
This is well done.
Derek.
It's well done.
I asked for it medium rare.
I don't want it chewy.
Thank you.
[exhales]
I'm so sorry.
Good help, right?
Right, we want Mr. Tate transferred to
the Mulberry Funeral Home, not Wendell's.
They're closer, but they're cheap.
Once he's there, let me know.
I'll bring Ms. Tate by
to make arrangements. Thank you.
Your aunt's on her way.
When you're ready, I'll drive you
to see Mr. Norris at the funeral home.
He'll want to know
what your father's wishes are.
And I talked to Delilah's.
They make the best funeral arrangements.
How do you know how to do all this?
Well, you figure out what needs doing,
and you get it done.
Thanks.
For being so kind to me after…
I didn't plan on any of it.
And it was the worst thing.
We're not talking about that right now.
Life's full of moments
we can't understand.
[suspenseful music playing]
That's it?
Yeah.
There's a false panel in the back.
It's smuggler's holes.
It's a tight fit,
but no one's gonna find us in there.
-Here.
-[Shawn] No.
-Take it.
-I'm not gonna take the fucking gun.
It's better to have one than to not, okay?
So just take it. Come on.
You ever use one of those before?
No, I've never…
never done any of this before.
Yeah, me neither.
I grew up with a hunting rifle.
I never pointed a gun
at another person before, until Grady's.
But you did.
Yeah, but I was scared shitless.
I-- I froze up. I didn't know what to do.
Okay, well,
let's hope it doesn't get to that.
What are you still doing here?
Why didn't you leave?
I mean, you can't want this.
Look, you and Harlan have your issues,
but you belong together.
Do you know what it's like to not belong?
Why is my dad so important to you?
Are you kidding me?
That guy's the ultimate badass.
It's like if John Wayne
had a baby with the Marlboro Man.
I love cowboys.
I always wanted to be a cowboy as a kid.
-Why weren't you?
-I mean, you can't just be a cowboy.
At least not in my world.
I mean, yes, I was born privileged,
but that can actually be a curse.
It makes you spoiled, makes you soft.
Ironically,
you have to work twice as hard.
Yep, totally. It's… It's awful.
Okay. [chuckles] Go ahead, make fun.
Few people understand
the hardships of wealth.
Mm.
-What?
-Wh…
-What is it?
-It's just, um… That's gross.
It's really undercooked.
See? Oh my--
That's exactly what I'm talking about.
Unacceptable. Derek?
Derek?
Now, this is undercooked.
I said medium-rare.
I don't want it, like, mooing.
Whoa, Jesus! Ah!
-[man] Hey! Stop her!
-Oh!
-Turn the fucking boat around.
-[Grady] Look at you.
-You're a little badass too.
-Give me that!
-[gunshot]
-[groans]
-Shit!
-Oh fuck! [grunts]
Next one goes in your fucking head!
Move.
-Don't make me say it again.
-I won't.
Come on. You heard her, boys.
Turn the boat around.
[man] Where are you going?
-We're gonna do what she says?
-You wanna be next?
[Earl] Yo, we got a stowaway.
[softly] Oh no.
-Mom.
-Oh no.
Where'd you come from?
-Let go of him now.
-Fuck you.
I said let go!
And then what?
What, is he gonna swim all the way home?
Don't be stupid, Bree.
Just drop the gun
or I'm gonna have to have him shot.
[Diller] Mom?
-Again.
-[Diller] No!
[tense music rising]
-[Diller] Mom.
-Okay, okay. No.
Okay.
[Grady] Okay.
That was hot. That was very hot.
How about you, buddy?
I was trying to be nice.
And then she goes
and picks a fight for no reason.
I mean, the apple
doesn't fall far, does it?
In fact, you know what?
The whole Buckley family tree is rotten.
We gotta prune a couple branches.
-Ah!
-[Diller] Mom!
[grunts]
[Grady screams]
Fuck! Fuck this.
I only need one of you.
-[gunshot]
-No, no, no! Mom!
Mom!
[Bree] No!
[screams]
No!
-Fuck.
-No, Mom!
Stop him!
No! Mom! Mom, no!
Don't worry about her, she'll bleed out.
Get him downstairs.
Shut him up.
[brooding music playing]
[groans]
[panting]
[grunting in pain]
Here we go.
[ominous music playing]
Check the boat.
HB, welcome aboard.
Look, Grady,
things have gotten out of hand.
The boat's clear.
I just wanna put it right.
Yeah, I know.
It's like, how did we even get here, man?
I'm an old man. I'm set in my ways.
And I fucked up. I admit it.
Yeah. You did.
That's, uh, quite an understatement.
You do something for so long one way,
it shuts you off to the smarter person
with the smarter idea.
[suspenseful music playing]
I think, at your core, you're a good man.
Oh… [chuckles]
Okay.
Oh, you almost had me.
I'm begging you, let my girl go.
You destroyed all my heroin.
So that's like millions and millions
and millions of dollars just up in smoke.
I think all that's worth
one alcoholic daughter.
Don't you?
Please, Grady, just let her go.
Unfortunately, we had to cut her loose.
-You what?
-I threw her overboard.
What?
[grunting]
Don't worry. We got someone else.
Recognize this handsome fella? Huh?
-Grandpa?
-Diller!
Goddamn it, Grady! Let him go now!
Shut up!
This could've been so easily avoided.
We could've been such a team.
We could've been rich!
You know what? I want you to die
knowing you're the one to blame.
You're the one
that led your family down this path.
This isn't me. This is you!
[grunts]
[Diller] No, Grady! Please stop!
You're killing him!
What?
I don't get it.
Where's Bree?
[groans]
No, don't!
Put the guns down!
Tell your men
to put the fucking guns down now.
Fucking do it now!
Do it.
Diller, get over here.
Get on the boat.
Lock yourself inside the cabin.
-What about Mom?
-Diller, go! Now!
[tense music playing]
Hey! Hey! Hey!
[gunshots]
[cocks gun]
[panting]
[intense music playing]
Come on.
Okay, Harlan. Look…
[trembling] Okay, okay. Okay.
-Let's talk.
-No more talking.
You can't do it, can you?
Okay, whoa, Harlan, Harlan.
Look, Harlan,
I want you to ask yourself…
This is the guy you want for your son?
You want this guy for a son?
Someone too much of a pussy to pull--
[gunshot]
[wet burst]
[gritty music playing]
Come on.
We gotta find Bree.
-[man] Hey, what are you doing?
-[gunshot]
No!
-[loud thud]
-[man groans]
[whimpers]
[thudding]
[Beau screaming]
-[groaning]
-[thudding]
[sobbing]
-[gunshot]
-[Beau screaming]
Hey.
Hey… Hey, listen to me.
You're just a little girl.
You didn't know.
You didn't know how. How could you know?
[bittersweet music playing]
[breathing heavily]
[whooshing]
I got you.
[echoing] I got you.
-I got you.
-[Harlan] I got you, Bree.
-[Bree] I got you.
-[Harlan] I got you.
["Burgundy"
by Laura Jean Anderson playing]
♪ Life falls punching a girl ♪
♪ White horse, whisper as you run ♪
♪ My choice already begun ♪
♪ Flying high so I can reach the sun ♪
[footsteps approaching]
[door opens]
Hey.
Where is she?
With the doctors now.
They said hypothermia, blood loss.
Oh my God. Jesus, look at you.
I'm fine.
Okay.
Hi, sweetheart. How you doing?
I'm so sorry, I heard what happened.
It's gonna be all right. Don't worry.
Hey.
Look at me.
Grady never would've stopped.
He would've kept coming and coming
until he got to someone you loved.
Maybe me, your sister,
your mother, your wife.
You were protecting your family.
That's one way of looking at it.
It's true.
Make peace with it.
[Cane] Hey.
You look fantastic.
So do you.
We owe you big time, son.
[subdued emotional music playing]
[Cane breathes deeply]
You okay?
Yeah.
The boat was all clean.
The guns, the bodies, the evidence,
everything was dumped and scrubbed.
Thank you, Drew.
I hope the best for Bree.
Night, Harlan.
[imperceptible]
[sighs in relief]
Surgery went well.
She lost a lot of blood,
but they were able to keep her leg,
so she's gonna be okay.
Listen, I-- I got something
I need to go do
but I'm gonna come back here, okay?
Okay.
Cane.
Buckley Seafood was a family business.
Me and my father.
Side by side.
That's how I've always known it.
That's why I wanted you to stay.
[bittersweet music playing]
I didn't want to be alone.
Are you okay?
[inhales] Um…
My-- my family's here. That helps.
Peyton left a while ago.
Peyton was here?
Yeah.
She, uh…
[sighs]
She was wonderful.
Kind.
She told me you told her.
Yeah.
I'm glad you did.
What do you mean?
Jenna.
No, Cane. Listen to me.
I can only speak for myself,
but I screwed up.
You were a nice thing during a hard time.
A distraction from my dad and my marriage.
But it's not real.
I mean, it's…
It is real.
No, I'm just a band-aid for you.
The only person who can fix you is you.
Jenna.
You need to go home.
Just please,
please don't come back here again.
Okay.
[cries softly]
[bittersweet music playing]
[muted whimper]
[nurse] Right in here.
Take your time, hon.
Hi.
I told you everything would be okay.
This qualifies?
Did you call your dad?
I'm not leaving.
I want to be here.
-[sniffling]
-Mom, are you okay?
-[Bree trembling] Yeah, I'm fine.
-I can get a doctor.
No, no, I'm fine.
It's just a little bit of pain.
I only get like two Tylenol
every six hours.
You just had surgery.
-Can't they get you something stronger?
-Yeah, they can. I just don't want it.
Thank you.
For throwing that life box.
That was quick thinking.
You saved me.
You saved yourself.
[emotional music playing]
[winces in pain]
[emotional music rising]
Is it over?
Everything with my dad?
Yeah, it's over.
Me and Jenna…
that's over too.
And what about us?
What about us?
What do you want, Cane?
I want us to be good.
I want to be good.
Peyton, I'm sorry.
You're the stronger one here,
so you just tell me what we need to do
and we'll do it.
Okay?
First thing, sit down.
I'm gonna heat up some food.
Everything's fine.
You and me, we're fine. Understand?
I'm gonna see to it.
[coughing]
-Can I have that, please?
-Yeah.
Here you go, baby.
That's a girl.
[groans]
Thanks, Mama.
[phone buzzing]
-Oh, thank you.
-Yeah, of course.
-You okay?
-Yeah, I'll just be a minute.
-Uh, Emmett?
-[Emmett] I spoke to my father.
We will help you with the land deal,
but only if you take over.
So after you let Harlan know,
come by the fish house
and we'll make it official.
Got it.
[softly] Phew…
Hi.
Hey.
I wondered where you went.
Just needed a minute to think.
[blows raspberry]
We can't stay like this.
You and me, we're better than this.
Yeah, we are.
But not always.
We can't love each other
every minute of the day.
You know that, right?
Oh, I know. Believe me,
sometimes I flat out hate you.
But not all the time.
-No, not all the time.
-Do you hate me right now?
No. Not this very minute.
Good.
I don't hate you either.
[gentle music playing]
I'll see you.
-[thud]
-[man grunts]
Belle… I do appreciate you coming.
Do we have to do this here?
Oh, this is exactly
where this needs to be done.
[man grunts]
[grunts in pain]
[uneasy music playing]
[Wes groaning]
[whimpers]
You gonna kill him?
Oh, no. No, no, he's no good to us dead.
But we will need his complete loyalty,
to both of us.
[grunts loudly]
[Emmett] Well, what do you have
to say to your new boss?
[Wes] I'll do anything.
I'll do anything.
["Deep Stays Down" by Larkin Poe playing]
♪ I thought I told you ♪
♪ I thought I told you
That the deep stays ♪
♪ I thought I told you ♪
♪ I thought I told you
That the deep stays ♪
♪ I thought I told you ♪
♪ I thought I told you
That the deep stays ♪
♪ I thought I told you ♪
♪ I thought I told you
That the deep stays ♪
♪ The deep stays down ♪
♪ The river runs deep
And the deep stays down ♪
♪ The deep stays down ♪
♪ The river runs deep
And the deep stays ♪
♪ Pray for rain, it's a bone-dry summer ♪
♪ Been sweating like a mother
And the sun just beats ♪
♪ Who they gonna blame? ♪
♪ Who's a-gonna pay
For every single secret ♪
♪ That the river don't keep? ♪
♪ The cat's in the bag
The bag's in the river ♪
♪ And the river runs deep
And the deep stays down ♪
♪ Better dot your "I's"
The lies getting bigger ♪
♪ Don't lead 'em
To the needle in the haystack ♪
♪ The deep stays down
The deep stays down ♪
♪ The river runs deep
And the deep stays down ♪
♪ The deep stays down
The deep stays down ♪
♪ The river runs deep
And the deep stays down ♪