[waves lap gently]
["Dead Man Walking"
by Channing Wilson playing]
♪ Dead man walking down the hall ♪
♪ Lord, if you won't save me
The devil will ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm a dead man walking ♪
[phone buzzing]
♪ I'm a dead man walking ♪
Hey.
What?
Wait, hold on. What?
Slow down. Slow down. I can't hear you.
What happened?
Jesus Christ.
♪ I'm a dead man walking ♪
[Harlan grunts]
[doctor] Man o' wars are very painful.
Lucky you didn't have
an allergic reaction.
That's when your heart will get you.
-You still drinking?
-No. I've been real good.
♪ Dead man walking… ♪
Mom?
-What are you doing here?
-I stayed over. Your mom is outside.
[Cane] Mom.
-Hey.
-Hey, are you okay?
Oh, I'm so glad you're here.
-Where's Dad?
-Grady hurt him really bad.
Hold on. You need to back up.
Just tell me exactly what happened.
-[knocking on door]
-Go away.
[knocking]
I said go away.
[door opens]
[Cane] It's me.
Where's your mom?
-You need to cut her a bit of slack.
-Did you know about the land deal?
Jesus Christ.
-The betrayal.
-Yeah, well, glass houses, Dad.
She went beyond anything I've ever done.
She knows what that land means.
-We got bigger problems.
-Bigger than losing everything?
-Yeah, what are we gonna do about Grady?
-Kill the son of a bitch.
Time to put a bullet in his head
and take him to the swamp.
That is plan A.
Let's start thinking about plan B.
That's the only plan.
We can't work with him.
No matter what we agree to,
he'll keep changing the terms.
-Dad, just…
-[phone buzzing]
It's him.
Okay, just-- just be cool
and don't make anything worse.
Don't aggravate him. Okay? Let's just…
Hey, pal. How we feeling?
-You stupid motherfucker.
-[whispers] I said don't aggravate him.
Question.
When can I schedule a run?
See? I called.
-Just like you asked.
-Fuck you.
Oh, please. Don't be such a crybaby.
It was just a couple jellyfish.
And you're already up
and walking around, right?
He's watching us.
What do you mean? Who's watching us?
[tense music playing]
Jesus Christ. Yeah, that's his guy.
Are you keeping tabs on me?
Tabs? You mean like surveillance?
Why would I have to do that, Harlan?
What are you doing?
Hey, wait. No, no, no. No, no, no. Dad.
[tense music rising]
[grunts]
[yelps]
Run, you little shit-brain!
That's right! Keep running!
What are you doing? Are you crazy?
Please.
If I wanted him dead, he'd be dead.
[Grady] What's going on there?
Next time you send a flunky to my house,
he'll come back in a bag. You understand?
Oh.
Oh. [chuckles] Okay.
You stay away from me and my family.
We are done.
That solved nothing!
It felt good.
[ghostly echo ringing]
Harlan, Grady's men keep calling.
They're trying to schedule a run.
-Ignore those calls for now. Thanks.
-Yo, what's going on, Mr. B?
Not now, guys.
[uneasy music playing]
What's this shit?
"Hey, buddy, get well soon. XOXO, Grady."
[exhales]
This is a goddamn game to him.
We need to focus here, okay?
We are in a financial hole.
We have 45 days to pay off this debt. 43.
[sighs]
Tell me about Emmett Parker.
[scoffs]
-[exhales]
-Who is he?
Why do you want to know?
Can he help us?
No. The Parkers are big-time drug dealers.
They have a whole operation,
probably one of the biggest in the South.
At the memorial, Emmett said that he--
he knew me when I was younger.
-He went to my football games.
-We weren't exactly friends.
Your grandfather worked for them.
It was strictly business.
Until it wasn't.
So the Parkers killed Granddad.
Emmett's father ordered the hit.
[uneasy music continues]
Is their operation bigger than Grady's?
Grady's nothing compared to their setup.
They've been doing this a long time.
Emmett gave me… his number.
He wants to work with us.
Don't mess with the Parkers.
They're not good people.
I called him. Emmett. He wants to meet.
-You called him? Why'd you do that?
-Someone's gotta do something, Dad!
You finally decide
to put on your big-boy britches,
and this is how you do it?
It's just a meeting, Dad.
Let's just see what he's got to say.
It's never just a meeting with them.
I'm trying to save
everything you've built.
We are out of options here.
[knocking on door]
Hey, wha-- what's with all the messages?
Is Diller okay? What happened?
This way.
Where's Diller?
You said he was hurt. Where is he?
What is she doing here?
-I called Daphne, asked her to come.
-I told you, it was an accident.
-He was with my dad--
-Maybe we should all sit.
I wasn't even there.
I didn't break any rules.
Rodney has requested a screening.
You used our son to-- to ambush me?
[Bree gasps]
Rodney, that is…
That is vile, even for you.
We can do this in peace
or we can do this slinging mud.
-Which will it be?
-I'm not doing shit.
-You'll lose your visitation privileges.
-Rodney thinks that you may be using.
I am clean and sober. I…
I have been for months, and you know that!
You didn't look
clean and sober at the hospital.
Please be a decent guy!
-A drug test shouldn't be a problem.
-We are doing what's best for our child.
My child, Georgina.
My child. He's not your child. He is mine!
-Pee in the cup, Bree!
-Hey!
Everyone, knock it off.
Can he make me do this?
Legally, he can request
a screening at any time.
And if I don't want to?
Bree, I highly recommend that you do it.
Call my lawyers.
[exhales]
[poignant music playing]
[poignant music continues]
[abrupt loud shaking]
Nice juggling act.
Yeah, well, when I fail the bar,
I have a backup career.
Have you been studying at all?
That's a hard no.
Everything okay
with Harlan and that Grady guy?
I told you
it was just a business deal gone sour.
You know I know there's more to it.
I figured you knew more than you let on.
Excuse me.
[Belle] Bree? [clears throat] Hey.
-You're over two hours late.
-Yeah, I know. Sorry.
Are you sober?
Yes, Mom. I was just at an AA meeting.
Oh, okay.
I'm sober.
Since when?
Okay, fine.
-I slipped, but it was short-lived.
-Right.
One day. Now I'm back
and rededicated to my sobriety.
It must be nice to start over
every five minutes. I wish I could.
Jesus Christ.
[ominous music playing]
[Harlan] They just pulled up.
Reggie, Tim, will you show them in?
Might be a good idea
if I do the talking here.
This is serious shit, son.
I'll do the talking.
You have no idea
what we've gotten ourselves into.
[exhales] Okay.
[ominous music rising]
We're alone.
It's just us.
Cane? I'm glad you called.
Harlan. Nice to see you.
[ominous music continues]
Harlan, remember my father, Jeb?
Last time I was here,
I walked around on my own two feet
instead of being pushed around
like a baby in a goddamn stroller.
[Emmett] Well, we're here.
We'd like to make a deal.
We're willing to offer you
our boats and runners for a year
and push the product at your pace,
uh, in a way in which
we wouldn't be raising any red flags.
If we do, by some chance,
come across the law,
we would take the heat.
In exchange, we're looking for 12 million.
Seven up front,
and, uh, the rest at deal's end,
at which point
we could renegotiate the terms.
Sounds like you need fast money.
Does this sound like something
you'd be interested in, or no?
Don't overplay your hand, son.
Now, last I heard,
you were smuggling with a third party.
You aren't double-dipping now, are you?
It's a good deal.
It's a rich deal.
A yes or no is all that'd be necessary.
[chuckles]
You raised a tough kid, Harlan.
But I can't trust it. It's desperate.
You must know all about that, Harlan.
All that nastiness
from the last time we tried to do this?
That's the past.
We're talking about right now.
And we both know you're interested
or you wouldn't be here.
[clears throat]
Well, we'd have to be exclusive.
Nobody else has access to those boats.
Meaning you cut ties
with your current supplier.
[Jeb] Yeah, what-- what's his name again?
-Oh, it's Grady.
-Right.
[inhales]
I'd like to commit to that.
I'm not sure Grady will be amenable,
but I'm sure you could handle that issue.
[Jeb chuckles]
So, we're gonna kill this guy for you,
and then throw in
seven million on top of that?
Do I-- Do I have this right?
I gotta ask.
Why does this guy have to die?
Why quit him and come with us?
The man has no code.
No sense of honor.
Ah. That's what you're missing? Honor?
With you, for better or worse,
I always knew where I stood.
But how do I know you've got honor?
How do I trust the son of Beau Buckley?
I know as well as anyone
what happens if we cross you.
All right.
We'll take care of Grady tonight.
The rest we can work out during the week.
It's always good
to work with people you respect.
[ominous music continues]
[Harlan breathing heavily]
Changing of the guard, eh?
Nice work, son.
So that old man tortured
and killed Grandpa.
[sighs heavily]
Why?
Your grandfather betrayed him.
Jeb is old school.
Whatever else you want to say,
he has an honor code.
Why'd he cross him?
Selling drugs is a drug.
You get that money in your pocket,
greed in your eyes,
ego in your head.
It's hard to find your way back.
[foreboding music playing]
Here. I'll do it.
Oh.
Does it hurt?
No.
Not anymore.
Good.
Can we talk?
I don't wanna talk.
Fine. Then you can listen.
We've been married for 36 years.
Some good, some bad.
Things get better, things get worse.
Then you go and have two heart attacks.
Business goes to shit.
You drown yourself
in women and booze more and more.
Someone had to take control.
It doesn't excuse what you did.
I made a decision,
and it was the right one.
You couldn't do it.
But that land isn't yours, is it?
You had no right to touch an acre of it.
Oh, don't give me that crap.
This family is as much mine
as it is yours.
I've earned the Buckley name, which is
more than I can say for you lately.
I was gonna tell you
the minute it was all in place, okay?
You're not getting it!
You lied to me.
Like you never lied to me.
You want the truth? I fucked him.
The man I brought the deal to?
You what?
I slept with another man.
You think just because I'm a woman,
I don't need something extra?
Something to take my mind
off this bullshit for five minutes?
So telling me this
is gonna make everything okay?
You want to hurt me?
Well done.
I'm hurt.
I didn't do it to hurt you.
[sighs]
I have always tried to have your back.
I have always
put you and this family first.
Fuck you for not seeing that.
[knocking desperately]
[knocking continues]
Jesus Christ.
What is wrong with you?!
Wait. Hey, Rodney, we're not--
-Where is he?
-What are you talking about?
I'm not playing games with you, Bree.
Where is he?!
Who, Diller?
I'm serious, Bree!
Why don't you know where he is, Rodney?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Diller didn't come home last night.
What?
Jesus!
Rodney…
Okay, okay, uh,
where was the last time you saw him?
We got into an argument.
I sent him to his room.
I went to check on him, and he was gone.
And now is the first time
you're telling me?
We were hoping he'd come back on his own.
Oh my God.
Okay, all right.
Damn it.
He heard what happened with the drug test.
He should be mad at me, not you.
He heard me ask Daphne
for a petition to relocate.
You want to…
You want to move?
I got a job offer in Virginia Beach, so…
Wow.
Georgina and I think a little separation
would be good for all of us.
-Let us know if you find him.
-[door opens]
[door closes]
[line ringing]
[Diller] Text me.
I don't talk on the phone.
[voicemail] The mailbox is full and cannot
accept any messages at this time. Goodbye.
-Come on.
-[line ringing]
[Diller] Text me.
I don't talk on the phone.
-Morning, Shawn.
-Morning. How are you feeling?
Much better, thanks.
You decided to stay?
Yeah, well, most of my things
are still at the Airbnb, it's not a lot.
I'll help you with that.
You headed to work?
-Yeah.
-You can ride with me.
Just give me five minutes.
Hey, are you…
Are you ever going to tell me the truth
about this family? What's really going on?
This weekend, you take a day off.
We'll go out on the boat.
Do a little fishing.
And talking.
Okay?
Okay.
I don't know how to fish, though.
I never learned it.
I'll show you.
It's not law school. It's pretty easy.
[Savannah] Grandma took me to the mall,
and we saw a movie,
and she bought me a new dress.
Oh, that's amazing, sweetie.
-[Savannah] When will I see you?
-Uh, soon, I hope.
-Are you at work?
-Yep, just got to work. Where's your mama?
She's still sleeping.
Oh, she is, is she?
You gonna do anything fun with Nana today?
Daddy, what's wrong?
Oh, nothing, baby. I…
I'm gonna call you back, okay?
I'll call you back.
[unsettling music playing]
[breathing shakily]
So you don't fish. We got that covered.
Do you sail?
Like a sailboat?
That's a no.
[chuckles]
Any kind of boating experience?
-I can jet ski.
-That doesn't count.
[chuckles]
If you're gonna be a Buckley,
you gotta grow some sea legs.
Do you think that's even possible?
For me to be a Buckley?
I hope so.
This family could use
some more good added.
[tires screeching]
-Jesus.
-Hang on.
[intense music playing]
-[crash]
-[Raf] Out of the car!
-Let's go! Get out!
-What the hell?
[Raf] Now, move! Car!
[Raf] Get out now!
Alright, out of the car!
All right, goddamn it!
Hey, you want me. Just me.
Harlan, what the fuck is going on?
-Both of you!
-He's got nothing to do with this.
-Now.
-[gunshot]
-Let's go!
-You don't need him!
-Shut the fuck up!
-Leave him here!
In the car!
[man 2] In there!
Move, pretty boy!
Go! Go!
[intense music continues]
[gasps]
Jesus Christ.
Who are they?
Emmett Parker's men.
What the hell are you doing
tangled up with the Parkers?
We met with them last night, okay?
We made a deal to-- to do runs
in exchange for cash for the land.
Oh, and your dad agreed to this?
It was my idea.
We're out of options here, Mom.
Honey, do you even know
who the Parkers are?
I know what happened to Grandpa.
And I also know
that Grandpa had it coming.
Oh my God. Fuck!
Fuck…
Fuck me.
Fuck.
Why are these men dead?
They offered to take out Grady
as a part of the deal.
I-- I'm guessing it didn't work.
-Where's your father now?
-I tried calling him. He's not picking up.
-I sent Tim and Reggie out to find him.
-Goddamn it, Harlan!
Grady's not going to kill Dad.
He's too smart for that.
He knows he needs him.
This is all just theatrics.
This is him. This is--
This is what he does. It's all for show.
These two men are just for show?
-Is that all their lives are?
-That's not what I meant, Mom.
I'm closing down the fish house.
Everybody, listen up!
We need to pack everything up.
We have a gas leak, and we need
to clear the building out ASAP, all right?
Let's go!
[phone buzzing]
-Y'all find him?
-We found his truck just off Creek Road.
Right outside of town.
The door's open, engine's running.
Crashed into a tree.
What-- What do you mean?
What the hell happened?
I found this.
-Guys, what the fuck is going on?
-[Reggie] Someone forced him off the road.
Took a shot at him, Cane.
Bring his truck back here.
As soon as you can, okay?
I'm gonna come meet you outside.
Diller?
[line ringing]
[hip-hop music playing]
[exhales]
[knocking]
Come on out. Jig is up.
All right, fine. We'll do it your way,
but just so you know,
I got nowhere to be, so…
[clears throat]
Well, hi.
How'd you find me?
I'm your mother.
So you're going to call Dad now, or…
Ugh. Oh, please, let your father squirm.
He deserves it.
He told me about the move.
I'm not leaving.
[pats on wood]
Come here.
[exhales]
I'm not going to force you to go home,
but I think you should.
Truth is, neither of us can really do much
about what happens next.
It's so unfair.
I mean… he won't let me say anything.
-And it's my life.
-Yeah, he can be a stubborn asshole.
-Yeah.
-So can you.
-[exhales]
-So can I.
[chuckling]
Do you know what
he's the most stubborn about, though?
You.
Because he loves you.
All he's ever trying to do is protect you,
and that is a gift, not a curse.
Trust me, I know all about curses.
So why didn't you take the test?
[inhales]
[exhales]
Because I knew what it'd say.
And I…
I know it would be better
if I could explain, but I can't.
And I-- I don't expect you to forgive me,
but I do need you to know
that I love you too.
I want to protect you too.
And you…
You are the only reason that
I will never stop trying to be better.
Whether you're 5 or 500 miles away.
[emotional music playing]
I wish things were different.
Me too.
[sniffles]
[chuckles]
-Dad's gonna be so pissed.
-Oh, yeah.
[both chuckle]
-Do you need a ride?
-No.
-He'll just find a way to blame it on you.
-[chuckles dryly]
-Good luck.
-See you later.
[tense music playing]
[soft thud]
[door opens]
[Belle] Oh!
[whispers] Oh. Hi. Hi.
-Oh my God.
-It's okay.
-Oh my God! Oh my God! Mom!
-It's okay. Hey. Stay clam.
-Bree…
-Those guys are dead. They're dead.
-I need you to stay calm.
-I can't breathe… [wheezing]
-This is…
-Okay.
[Bree breathing shakily]
[suspenseful music playing]
Come on.
[grunts]
You are bumming me out, HB.
[chuckling] I thought
you'd at least have the balls
to try and kill me yourself.
Whatever this is,
it has nothing to do with the kid.
Huh.
Would you look at that? It's you again.
Fun. We'll unpack that in a sec.
What am I doing here?
Let's not do this dance.
We both know what you did.
I don't like playing games.
[chuckles]
Well, for someone
who doesn't like playing games,
you got a hell of a poker face.
That shit is just… granite.
Okay.
Why don't I take a shot at it?
You let me know if I'm getting warm.
I think you got home the other night
from our little tête-à-tête.
And your wife wasn't too happy.
Who can blame her? You look like shit.
You put your worried little heads together
and decided it's not so fun
working for a raging,
narcissistic sociopath.
Yes, I have been formally diagnosed.
I mean, I'm not sure
I get the whole narcissist part, but…
[chuckling] I mean, I guess that's
just the definition of irony, right?
Anyway, here's the part I don't get.
Instead of plotting your revenge
like I expected,
you decide to grovel?
You go crawling back
to your former employer
and sic the Parker clan on my ass.
How am I doing so far?
You're wrong. I cut those ties years ago.
Ah, see, that's genius,
'cause it's not quite a lie,
but I keep a very close eye
on all my assets,
and I know for a fact that the Parkers
visited your fish house last night.
They know I'm running again.
They wanna do business.
I told them to go to hell.
Okay.
How about this?
Lie to me again,
and I put a bullet in your friend's head.
-No, no!
-Get that thing out of his face!
Ooh! There's that gravitas again.
Who is this little troublemaker, anyway?
You keep popping up everywhere.
He's a bartender.
He has nothing to do with this.
Is that true, Five O'clock Shadow?
You're just a bartender?
I, uh…
[panting]
I'm a bartender.
-Okay.
-[cocks gun]
No, no, no! I'm his son!
-What?
-I'm his son.
Whoa!
Holy adultery!
I did not see that coming. Is that true?
Aww.
That's not fair.
Everyone gets to be your son.
Let him go.
I'll do whatever you want.
[Grady] See?
Was that so hard?
I knew we could find some common ground.
Fantastic. You guys sit tight. [chuckles]
I'll be right back.
[giggles]
[gasps in panic]
Bree, stop. Stop, honey. Stop.
We need to call the police.
We're not calling anybody.
Oh my God.
Did Dad do this? Did you do this?
Of course not. No!
[exhaling] Oh my God. I don't know.
This is, like--
This is really bad. This is really bad.
-You don't know what you think you know.
-I know Dad killed Sheriff Porter.
And don't bother lying
'cause Cane as much said it to my face.
It was in self-defense.
He had no choice, Bree.
There's always a choice, Mom.
You never let me forget that.
You all chose to go back to this life.
You and Cane and Daddy.
Please. You say you wanna be
a part of this family?
Now's your chance.
We need to get these out of sight.
[groans]
-I could really use your help.
-Okay, fine. Okay.
What are we gonna…?
-Okay.
-Okay, I'll take his feet.
On the count of three.
One, two, three. Go.
Ah!
[suspenseful music playing]
It's up through there, right?
A farm a couple hundred yards
in the woods.
Well, that's the place.
Okay.
All right, fellas.
I don't know what we're getting into.
I don't even have a plan.
Last chance
for you to bail if y'all want to.
[softly] Okay.
["Dig a Hole"
by Stephen Wilson Jr. playing]
♪ There's a fire ♪
♪ There's a fire, there's a fire
There's a fire burning in me ♪
[whispers] Let's go.
Come on.
♪ All my trouble buried in the rubble ♪
♪ Running from the devil
Is hell on earth ♪
♪ Dig a hole ♪
♪ Dig a hole, dig a hole, dig a hole ♪
♪ I better save my strength ♪
♪ It's harder than you think
To dig a hole ♪
I think they got him
in the house over there.
Cane, you go left. Reg, you go right.
I'll cover, then follow.
Jesus Christ. Oh shit. Okay.
All right.
[exhales] Okay.
♪ Can't save my soul now ♪
♪ Give me a shovel ♪
♪ Put it in the dirt ♪
♪ All my trouble buried in the rubble ♪
♪ Running from the devil
Is hell on earth ♪
♪ Dig a hole ♪
♪ Dig a hole, dig a hole, dig a hole ♪
[song ends]
[creaking]
[intense music playing]
[grunts]
[Cane groans]
[screams]
[grunting]
[gasps for air]
[Cane panting]
Thank you.
[Reggie] Jesus.
You guys good?
[panting]
Guess what?
You're gonna help me
set a trap for Emmett Parker.
Call him.
Tell him to meet you at your fish house.
Then I'm gonna kill him.
You're gonna start a turf war
that won't end well.
You're right. It won't end well.
For Emmett.
Do it.
-[man] They're over there! Get them!
-Go, go, go.
Holy shit. Go!
Go, go, go, go! Oh! Jesus Christ!
[suspenseful music playing]
What are you doing? Go.
-This shit is worth more than your life!
-There ain't no saving it, Grady.
Fine. Give me your gun.
Unbelievable.
Get ready to run.
[Grady] Oh, Christ.
Oh shit.
[Grady grunts]
[intense music continues]
[straining]
[gun clicking]
Ah, fuck.
Tim!
Stay with me, buddy.
[grunts]
[Shawn] Harlan!
Harlan, we gotta go. Harlan.
He's gone.
Oh my God. We have to go.
We have to go now. We gotta go.
Cane, come on! Now!
[frantic music playing]
Where's Tim?
-[Cane] Let's go! Come on!
-[rapid gunfire]
Get down!
[grunts]
[groans]
[grunting]
[screams]
[shouts in frustration]
Goddamn it! Goddamn it!
Fuck you! Fuck you! Fuck you!
[Bree] Jesus Christ.
[both panting]
[panting]
We need to lock it up now
until we figure out what to do with them.
[door opens]
[scrubbing]
Ugh…
-Honey, you need to take a break.
-No. It'll leave a stain if we leave it.
Can't have anyone asking questions.
-Bree, stop.
-No, it's--
You need to breathe.
Let's be honest.
I haven't been able to breathe
since I was seven years old.
I'm sure this has brought up
some really difficult memories for you.
Fuck you, Mom. Are you serious right now?
Yes, I am freaking out.
I'm allowed to freak out.
Just let me freak out.
-I know what happened to you wasn't easy.
-No, you don't.
You have no idea what it was like for me
because I lied for you.
I lied to the police,
and then you and Cane and Daddy
got to just live your lives
and pretend it never happened
the way it did.
The only person
that was left with the truth was me.
You think I lied to make our lives easier?
Huh?
You were a witness.
You could identify the men
that killed your grandfather.
If I hadn't made you lie,
they would've killed you too.
Well, maybe you should've let them.
I killed him.
Honey,
you were a child.
-There was nothing you could've done.
-No.
No… Marcus.
Agent Sanchez.
-I killed him.
-What?
He was gonna go after you and Daddy,
so I-- I got him some drugs.
I knew he'd take them…
and he died.
Oh my God. Why didn't you tell me?
Why would I tell you?
You sniffed out I'd used in two seconds
and wrote me off even faster.
And I guess it was obvious,
'cause Rodney did too,
and now he's gonna take Diller away,
and I'm not gonna see my son
for God knows how long,
and a part of me thinks I deserve this.
I deserve to be punished.
No. No, you don't, angel.
You've been punished enough.
From the moment we found you that day,
I failed you.
I tried to protect you, but I failed you,
and that's on me.
Not you, you understand?
Okay.
Hey. Come here. Come here.
-It's all gonna be all right.
-[Bree sobbing]
[grunting]
[Shawn] All right, slowly.
-Slow, slow.
-[Reggie groans]
-He needs a hospital.
-We'll get him to a doctor, okay?
Hey. Thank you for coming for us.
What was I gonna do, let you die?
You could've.
Well, next time I know.
We gotta call your mother,
your sister, and your wife.
We need everybody safe.
Grady's not going quietly.
[intense music playing]
[Bree] No, he went home hours ago.
I haven't seen him, Rodney. I'm not ly--
Diller?
[line ringing]
[Diller] Text me.
I don't talk on the phone.
Diller?
[ominous music playing]
[screaming]
[music intensifies and stops]
[closing theme music playing]
[music ends]