# Do you want me on your mind
# Or do you want me to go on
# I might be yours
as sure as I can say
# Be gone, be faraway
# Ooh
# Mm. #
Did you not hear me?
You've got no authority over me.
Now, I've said that I'm heading
home. Open the...
We need to discuss the search you
just did.
Oh, I see. I cannae do it now. I've
got to head home. I'm cat-sitting.
You need to debrief us.
Am I free to go or not?
It will be easier for everyone if
we can find a way to co-operate.
So, you're not detaining me. OK.
Gate, now.
I need to get him out. The tunnel's
filling with nitrogen!
He'll suffocate.
Come on, Come on!
Ready. OK, three, two, one, lift.
Quicker, quicker!
Move it!
Right, get him on to the bed.
Come on, quickly.
That's it. Get him laid down.
He was caught in the nitrogen burst.
He'll be all right, won't he, doc?
We'll have to wait and see.
You'll be all right, mate.
Emergency battery engaged.
Power restored.
Sir?
Report. What the hell just happened?
The reactor was running perfectly.
There was no signs of any problems
and then it scrammed.
An emergency shutdown but without
the emergency,
at least not one that we can find.
I've lost one coolant pump before,
but this...
Can you give us a likely cause?
We're checking the coolant pump
breakers now, but they seem OK.
I've got all hands on deck but I'm a
man down.
Walsh was injured in the nitrogen
burst.
Sir, how are things looking on the
roof, if we need to run the diesels?
Surface weather? Wind blowing 40
knots, wave height 20 feet,
low southerly swell.
Surface contacts?
It's very noisy up there, sir. Maybe
four or five merchantmen on.
No, not maybe. It's four or five.
Determine the facts, then report.
Aye, aye, sir. All drills cancelled.
Cox and brief the crew to secure
everything
for surface running in rough
weather. Aye, aye, sir.
Sir.
And get rid of her.
If the batteries run out,
how long have we got on the diesels?
I mean, we'll be getting towed home.
We can't make it back to port.
Prentice, prepare a plan
for possible at sea diesel
replenishment. Aye, aye, sir.
How long have our batteries got?
We're checking them now.
Maybe three hours. Three h...?
Capacity's well down on what it
should be. They need replacing.
Yes, well, everything needs
replacing.
The reactor supplies the power.
We can run off batteries for a few
hours,
but then, we'd have to use the
backup diesels,
which means going to the surface and
sticking up a periscope.
Sir, is this a drill? No, it's no
drill, stow for sea.
Shake everyone in your bunk space.
Aye, sir.
It's a nightmare staying below the
surface at periscope depth.
The exhaust leaves smoke trails
and the noise lights you up like a
Christmas tree. Watch it!
Lads, get this stowed!
So, what happens if the reactor
doesn't re-start?
Then, what, we're in some kind of
danger?
No, only if the motor gives out. But
we've been running on batteries.
What happens if the batteries
give out?
Then, we sink, so fingers-crossed,
ey?
I don't want us anywhere near the
surface -
not if there's a chance we're being
shadowed.
Three hours on batteries means you
have 2.5 hours to diagnose,
fix and restart the reactor.
Carry on. Aye, Captain.
Cronin, signals log.
I know Burke was dismissed the day
the trawler went down.
Why?
You're in charge of discipline,
aren't you?
I've got less than two days,
there's never going to be a better
time to ask questions, is there?
OK. Yeah, if an officer puts someone
on charge, then, yes, I deal with
it.
So, what happened with Burke when
the trawler sank?
He picked an argument with his
superiors,
it was a stupid thing to do.
Now, Amy, I've got to crack on.
Look. Hey, there's a no-touching
rule -
it applies to everyone without
exception. Sorry.
Were you told to punish Burke?
No, no. He died before I had a
chance to log it.
What do you mean, "log it"?
It's all in the duty logbook.
I'm going to leave you here
because I can't do my work with you
asking these questions, OK?
So, just tell me what "logged it"
means.
It's where officers report
disciplinary matters.
I keep it in my office.
Great. Can I see it?
Yeah, it's in the grey file on top
of the cabinet.
Keep breathing.
How long was he in there?
Aw, I don't know, a minute.
I think he's smacked his head.
No ESB mask on.
I'm not dead. You can ask me.
Lie still.
I need to take your clothes off.
It's a tenner for watching.
And then I need to wash your hair.
You what, ma'am? Right, scissors?
Right, saline.
Thank you.
Start dripping that into your eyes.
I feel fine.
Yeah, you might do for now,
but, in a few hours' time,
we'll start to see whether your
lungs hold up.
Good. Good. How is he?
It's too early to tell.
You all right, Adams?
Still not right, ma'am, my vision
keeps blurring. Right, you better
get to your bunk...
No, no, no, no, no. I need every man
that I can get.
The EPM's already tripped once.
Our party has been clear.
We do not want these
weapons in Scotland.
Westminster is about to vote on
whether we should commission
new missiles,
a vote we had to force
through, by the way,
after this government tried to slip
this once-in-a-generation decision
under the carpet...
..without consulting parliament.
Longacre speaking.
Evening, Longacre. It's Porter.
You calling from the office?
Sounding a bit judgmental there.
Got a name for one of guys who beat
up Burke.
I might need your help getting his
file off the Navy. Have you eaten?
Nope. Do you fancy pizza?
So you've got a name?
Yes, Gary Walsh.
He's Burke's crew mate on Vigil.
Apparently, him and one other guy
beat the crap out of Burke at the
local pub.
Oh. Who was the other guy?
Don't know.
Spoke to the bar staff. They all
knew Gary, but not the other
assailant.
They're pretty sure he was Navy
though. Right, OK.
So, "Walsh...
"Gary." Let's see what we've got.
Right, so no disci...
Ah, amazing, thank you.
No disciplinaries or anything...
And... OK, he has two brothers -
one of them Navy as well.
Dishonourably discharged.
There's a flag here for
a younger brother, Sam.
A record for shoplifting.
And possession of heroin.
Wait a minute.
Hello? Lieutenant
Commander Branning.
This is DS Longacre. I'd like to
send a message to DCI Silva, please,
as soon as possible. OK.
Enter.
Yes?
Any news on the reactor?
What, were you sent to investigate
our mechanical issues as well?
I've been through
the Cox'n's logbook.
You put Craig Burke on charge
the day before he died.
Probably.
Can you remember what that was for?
This annotation references
the type of offence.
"Reckless endangerment of
equipment."
He put a full mug of coffee on top
of a narrowband sonar set.
You also put Burke on charge on
days two and four of the patrol.
You disciplined him more in a week
than the rest of the crew
put together.
We have standards for a reason.
We have a duty to safeguard lives.
So what did Gary Walsh
do on day six?
There's no annotation there.
Can't remember. I just want to know
if there's a reason why...
What do you think I am doing here?!
If we run on diesels
we will need to refuel at sea,
or abandon the patrol,
which cannot happen.
Do you have any idea how challenging
it is to get a boat this size
to rendezvous with a refuelling
tanker whilst also trying to
remain undetected?
Can you even begin to imagine
the tactical challenges?
No, no, I didn't think so.
Follow me.
Sir, may I have a word?
Go ahead. Detective Silva is
interfering with operations.
I explicitly told her to go through
the Cox'n, which she has
chosen to ignore.
I therefore think we need to confine
her to quarters. There's just one
thing to consider there -
interfering with a police
investigation is an offence.
We are on patrol!
You can't just wade in here
and start taping off the bloody
control room! All right.
DCI Silva, we're on backup power.
Several areas of the boat are unlit.
As much as anything, it's hazardous
for you to be without an escort.
Now I won't confine you to quarters,
but you will have to have Glover
with you if you're going to work.
Will you put him at my disposal?
Negotiate that with him. Carry on.
That means get out of his sight.
XO, enough.
Cronin, escort DCI Silva to the
Cox'n's office. Aye, sir.
Oh, shit, Cat!
Hello?
Emergency services.
Which service...? Police. I'm a
police officer. Connecting you now.
This is Detective Kirsten Longacre,
calling from Flat B,
2 McMillan Street, West End.
I think I've been burgled
and they might still be here.
Police. I'm a police detective
There are more officers...
Get off!
Let's go, let's go!
You have 20 minutes.
30 if I ask nicely?
It'll do you no harm.
Message for you, ma'am. Thank you.
"Found witness
to Burke assault." Oh, eyes up.
"Burke badly hurt.
Gary Walsh is perp.
"Burke not pressed charges.
"Gary Walsh's brother, Sam Walsh,
criminal record for possession."
I need to search Gary Walsh's bunk.
What you doing, stealing his sweets?
Testing for heroin.
It was Gary Walsh who beat
Burke up in that pub.
Did you know that?
I knew they didn't like each other.
And there's a blank entry under
Gary Walsh in the logbook -
that anything to do with him
and Burke? I don't know,
you'd have to ask Prentice. Yeah...
Tried that.
You've checked Burke's bunk
already, haven't you?
Could you?
I'm looking for Burke's fleece.
Hadlow said Burke was wearing
a green fleece,
that's how he knew he was off duty,
but Burke wasn't wearing a fleece
when we examined him, so...
No, it's not there.
Why is that important?
You only get rid of it
if you knew it incriminated you,
like it had your blood on it,
or something.
You can't throw things
away down here, can you?
Uh, no, not really.
So, if someone's hidden it,
it means I'll be able to find it.
Well, theoretically.
I need to speak to Gary Walsh.
Do you have any idea what
they were after?
I found this USB stick hidden in
Burke's room at the base.
Now...
They tried to stop me from leaving,
so I reckon they know
I have something.
Admiral Shaw has requested
a meeting.
Have you had a chance to
look at it yet? I have.
It's videos of Burke, boss.
I mean, he seems to be some
sort of whistle-blower...
..but I think that's
just the tip of the iceberg
because all the main folders are
password protected.
I'll get Porter to have a
look at it.
Aha, well done! Hey...
Thanks.
What's her name?
Um, Cat.
It's short for Catherine.
You'll get yourself checked
out before you come in, aye?
I will.
Can you give us five minutes,
please? Sir. How are you, mate?
Bored out of my mind, but she won't
have me moving.
Cox'n, before I forget, will you
check in on Chief Adams for me
later? He doesn't look well.
Yes, ma'am.
Do you mind if I ask you a
few questions?
Well, "I'm a very busy man."
A few days ago, Executive Officer
Prentice put you on charge.
Why was that?
I don't remember.
Do you remember what your movements
were a few hours before
Craig Burke's death?
Well, I was on watch
back aft from seven till one.
I had Adams, Ansell and Khan with me
the whole time.
You didn't leave engineering?
No, I didn't.
At one, I went to my bunk for a kip
and I slept till EO Hadlow woke us.
Yeah, why did Hadlow come to
wake Burke up?
Keep the questions to ones I can do,
eh? I'm no' psychic.
Did you ever argue with Burke?
He was a prick, end of.
You had a fight with him in a pub.
So you know I argued with him.
Don't piss about.
It was a drunk scrap.
Ask me if I killed him.
Did you kill Craig Burke?
No.
Did anyone know you were in the
reactor area when it shut down?
We go and in an' out all the time.
It's not anyone try'na kill me.
OK. I've got everything I need for
now.
I'm going to need you to do
a drugs test.
How's that? I found traces of heroin
in your belongings.
If I've been home before a patrol,
then everything's coated in skag.
My wee brother's a junkie, not me.
Are you happy to do a urine test?
Are you going to hold the cup for
me?
Have you got a container for him?
Enjoy the show. It's all right,
we'll head out.
Don't spring something like that on
one of my patients.
Did you know about this? No, ma'am.
If his alibi holds, we'll know he
can't have met Burke on the missile
deck.
But do we need to go through with
this? Finished.
Here you go! My best stuff.
Oh, clean it up!
Maybe keep her out of my stuff, eh?
Clean that up and do it now.
You need to drink more water.
Negative for opiates. He didn't
bring them on for his own use.
Why would he bring drugs onboard
if he wasn't going to use them?
You know, you're not doing yourself
any favours treating Walsh this way,
especially when his alibi's rock
solid.
There's history of assault.
He brought heroin on board.
Maybe somebody else killed him,
but Walsh was definitely involved.
Well, your 20 minutes are up.
Oh, come on!
I'm here for less than two days.
I need your help. I need a drink.
Do you want one? You look tired.
Maybe, when you've finished this,
you should go and get a shower, get
your head down for a few hours.
Thanks.
I don't know why everyone's so
scared of me finding out the truth.
This boat's two billion
pounds' worth of kit,
but it's run by people who
are making split second decisions
that could kill the whole crew
if they fuck up,
so there has to be trust.
You can't introduce fear
and paranoia into that.
I appreciate that.
Ah, no, you don't.
You've only been here less
than a day.
Control, I can see
debris on the surface.
Sending co-ordinates for rescue
vessel Victor Two Charlie. Over.
I'm sorry we've not been allowed to
share it with you before now.
If one of my officers reports
a suspected murder,
I don't expect that to be
sat on for 24 hours!
Well, you'll have to take that
up with the MOD.
I don't care what the MOD thinks,
or the Ministry for Agriculture
for that matter.
It's not their remit.
It's above my pay grade
and yours, too, I imagine.
Look, in confidence, we are getting
a boat ready to replace Vigil,
but it takes time.
Perhaps DCI Silva could
remain on board
and continue her investigations
until Vigil returns -
I'd support that.
How long would that be?
Three weeks.
And we'd cooperate, of course.
I know we got off to a bad start,
but perhaps we can all do
a little better.
We'd appreciate being debriefed when
you've been working on this base.
I'll do what I can.
And can we ask you not to call it a
"murder investigation"
when you talk to the
crew's families? Aye, no problem.
Are we done?
Can you tell us what you know about
a trawler sinking off Barra Head?
Certainly. We're assisting the
coastguard.
One of our helicopters has spotted
debris in the water
and we may send in a boat to
scan the seabed.
And the cause?
To be confirmed.
Will you keep us appraised?
Certainly, but I do think that this
one will end up with
Agriculture and Fisheries.
Trawlers do go down from time to
time, I'm afraid.
If Amy thinks it's murder,
I back her.
I think you're right on that.
It's what the girl at the Peace Camp
said.
I mean, I wrote her off, boss,
but she just seemed like the type
who saw conspiracy theories
everywhere, you know?
Well, maybe she's not.
I just need to speak to
Branning again.
Go easy. Hmm.
Lieutenant Commander Branning?
Sorry, there was something I forgot
to ask.
Do you know anything about a fight
that Burke had in a pub?
If you put a request in an email.
This is a murder enquiry now -
we need to work faster than that.
That cuts both ways, doesn't it? If
you're not prepared to debrief us,
we'll do things by the book.
We will try to do...
I'll try to do things better.
Burke and Gary Walsh, they had
a fight in a pub down the road.
I wasn't there, obviously.
And it happened on their own time,
so it was never a formal matter.
I heard Burke went to the
pub to apologise.
For what? Walsh's younger brother
was a trainee here. Douglas?
That's right.
He got involved in some bullying
and Craig Burke gave
evidence against him.
After that, Dougie was discharged.
Did something happen to him?
He killed himself.
I was told Burke showed
up at Dougie's wake at the pub
to apologise to Gary -
that's what started it.
Shit...
I heard it was two men who
attacked him.
Do you know who the second guy was?
What?
I was just...thinking how weird
it is that you two look so alike.
I know. Everybody says it.
I think it's the eyes.
But she says it, too.
Mind you, I think it's more wishful
thinking on her part.
She asked me to marry you.
What, she...? Yeah.
You were proposed
to by an eight-year-old girl?
Yeah. Yeah.
Listen...
..you know how I feel.
I know.
I think I might be coming
round to it.
So we've ground you down with
our team effort, have we?
Good going, kiddo!
Attention, all crew.
The submarine has reached
periscope depth. High sea state.
All compartments
maintain stowage for sea.
What's going on?! We're up near the
surface and it's a bit rough.
High sea state...
We've come off batteries
and had to go onto diesels.
Belt up in here, please.
Best stay out the way.
People a lot more experienced
than you are getting hurt.
Oh, you've got post.
A message from the shore.
Gary Walsh's
brother Dougie was a trainee at
Dunloch.
"Burke reported him for bullying.
"Dougie was dishonourably
discharged,
"later killed himself.
"Second crewman who was close to
Dougie also involved in fight
"at brother's wake -
Engineering Officer Simon Hadlow."
Shit!
Full SOP's on the way, sir. Yep.
Coolant flow,
temperature and pressure were all
within limits,
then suddenly they spiked.
This has never happened before.
We need to figure out what caused
this. Sir. Where's the Cox'n?
I don't know. I'm recording this.
I can't get you a solicitor,
but a judge may determine
that this can be used as evidence
against you in court.
Do you understand?
There's no way I have time.
Lieutenant Hadlow has consistently
tried to avoid my questioning.
Look, I'm needed back.
Just tell me about your relationship
with Craig Burke.
I didn't especially have a problem
with Burke. Never argued with him?
Not so much as a cross word?
No.
But I know you're lying.
You and Gary Walsh beat up
Burke at his brother's wake.
You were close friends with
Gary's brother
and I think you held Burke
responsible for Dougie's suicide,
so let me tell you how a jury is
going to see this.
You and Gary have assaulted
Burke once before
and I can prove that Gary
brought heroin on board.
You were with Burke on the missile
deck where I found his blood and
it was you who found him
allegedly "already dead" in
his bunk, so...
This wasn't me or Walsh,
but I can tell you...
..nobody meant to kill him.
How do you know that?
If it wasn't you, how do you know
what his attacker intended?
I can't talk to you
about this right now. Why not?
It's not up to me.
There's a chain of command.
Oi! What? What does that mean?
Where's Glover? He wasn't available.
Your orders were no talking
without Glover present.
And, Hadlow, just gossiping
during a once-in-a-lifetime crisis
that happened on your watch.
I'm interviewing a suspect.
I don't have anything else to say.
Right, you, follow me.
Sir.
Stay here.
I will send Glover when he's free.
I don't take orders from you.
Do you have any id...?
Do you have any idea how much
trouble this patrol is in?!
You can't have it both ways!
Glover shows up or he doesn't -
either way I have a job to do.
Your job is irrelevant to this
mission. I disagree. Sit down.
Craig Burke would disagree...
Oh, fuck Craig Burke!
Burke was a treacherous little shit
who got exactly what was
coming to him!
He was a drug addict.
He's done enough damage.
No.
Let me out.
Let me out!
Can anyone hear me?!
So, what do you do here?
At the camp? Mm-hm.
From what I can see,
you make a lot of sacrifices.
What keeps you going?
Er, we make a difference.
If we hadn't been observing them,
the Navy would have never
admitted they had reactor
problems in the submarines.
There's a whole lot we've
figured out. Mm-hm.
So, you're kind of like an informal
Health & Safety team?
They want everyone to
think it's safe and it's not.
Is that what Craig Burke thought?
You told me that you thought
that the Navy had killed him.
I didn't say that.
You said something like it.
Come in.
We think he might have been
murdered.
With it covered up? Maybe.
I found the USB stick
he wanted you to have.
He left you a message as well
as a folder of files.
If it's mine,
you should give it back to me.
What did the message say?
What's the password
for the main folder?
See that? Someone did that to me,
trying to steal it,
and that's with them
knowing that I'm police.
They did a very professional job.
Now, will you look at where you're
living?
You don't even have a lock on
that and, if you did,
one good kick would batter it down.
There's 40 people here who would
help me out. That's not enough,
Jade!
I'm a police officer
and that wasn't enough.
Chances are it was MI5 that did that
to you. Do you know what?
I seriously doubt that. I know for a
fact they watch activist groups.
There's this one guy I've
seen a few times.
He likes wearing this really bad
Glasgow hockey jacket,
trying so hard to fit in.
Another time, when I was coming back
early from a protest
and I saw him at the train station,
he met someone for, like, 30 seconds
and then just walked away.
Tell me that's not dodgy.
If you're worried about that,
you should think about who knew
you and Burke were together.
Hardly anyone knew.
But it was out there.
Not really!
Even if you told one person,
then it is out there.
What was he doing?
Was he helping you?
Was he spying for you?
We were a problem for them,
and now you've gone and made
yourself a problem as well.
Trust me, they won't give a
fuck that you're police.
Jade?
We need to talk about Sunday's
perimeter action. So, can we...?
Is she police?
I'm dealing with it.
Right...
I'm happy to stay.
Nah.
Thanks.
You need to go, now.
I want you to call me
if you see or hear anything at all
that worries you, OK?
Don't look into it. Just call me.
They'll probably tell you
he was a bad guy.
He really wasn't...
..I promise.
OK.
All right? All right?
Tanker dead ahead! Go deep,
go deep, go deep!
Aye, sir. Dive, dive, dive.
Drop all masts.
Shut bulkhead doors.
Standby collision.
Brace, brace, brace!
Full down with the forward planes,
full down with the after planes,
full ahead.
New contact. Tanker.
Marking on sonar.
Zero Three Zero. Zero Three Five.
Zero Four Five.
Now bearing
Zero Eight Five, One Three Five.
We're not deep enough, sir!
Let me out!
Fuck.
One Eight Zero.
One Nine Zero.
Two Zero Five.
Two One Zero.
Contact clear and opening.
We've missed it. How can you not
hear a tanker?! Sorry, sir.
Bow breaker and it was very noisy
with the high sea state...
We nearly bored a hole in
its side! Wake up!
Ship control, report.
Two up achieved, sir. Very good.
Prepare to return to periscope
depth. Aye, sir, prepare to return
to periscope depth.
Let's catch a trim. Aye, sir.
There you are!
What's...?
I'm fine.
Fine.
The boat's coming up, you know?
It's... We're going to be all right.
Amy? What's going on?
Prentice locked me in.
He shouldn't have done that.
Oh, I've got you... Shit.
I've got you, I've got you.
It's all right, go on, relax.
Take a deep breath..
Take a deep breath. Here you go.
It's OK, you're out now. You're out
now. It's all right.
It's OK.
Just being in there triggered...
There was an accident...
Iain! Oh, my God.
I need to get you out.
Iain. Mummy, I can't...
It's OK, darling.
Mummy! OK.
All right, sweetheart, it's OK.
We're going to get you out, OK?
OK. All right, we need to take a
deep breath and then,
then we're going to open the door
and swim.
I'm going to come back for
Daddy, OK? Three, two, one...
I had to make a choice.
Swim, baby.
OK, baby, wait here. Mummy!
Please, Mummy!
Wait here. Please! Mummy!
I couldn't get him out.
You know there's a no touching rule.
Sometimes you've got to know
when to break the rules.
Oh, erm...
Briefing in 20 minutes, sir.
Right, thank you.
Right, so...
What next?
I need your help.
Hey, when's dinner?
Oh, shit, sorry.
It's my turn to cook, isn't it?
Tomorrow night? Mm-hm.
I'm going to meet someone.
I've found someone...
..who knows what happened to Craig.
Can I come with you? No.
I'm not going on my own.
They want to help us.
They know everything.
Sir, this is all highly irregular.
I'm concerned about the EPM
giving out again.
We can't run deep without
going to the bottom.
We need to run on diesels
at periscope depth...
..until we know what caused the
scram. No, sorry.
Sitting on the surface to
double-check things is not an option
if we're being trailed by an enemy
submarine. Restart the reactor.
There must be a reason for it
shutting down.
Restarting the reactor without
knowing why
could damage the core and cause a
complete meltdown and sink the boat.
Yes, I understand that.
Get it ready.
Aye, aye, sir. We'll warm it up.
Sir, if I may, I would suggest that
we should...
Mark Prentice, I'm arresting you for
obstructing a police investigation,
holding an officer against her will
and on suspicion of the murder
of Craig Burke.
You're not obliged to say anything,
but anything you do say will be
noted and may be given in evidence.
What in Christ's name are you
talking about? Sir, she clearly
ignored your orders...
I'm not here to debate.
I'm arresting you.
Navigator, you have the submarine.
Roger, sir. I have the submarine.
Have Hadlow inform me when the
reactor's about to go online.
Aye, sir. DCI Silva, XO, with me.
Where were you
an hour before Craig Burke died?
All over the boat, nature of the
job.
And the last time
you saw Burke alive?
I dismissed him from the control
room - plenty of witnesses.
What about Gary Walsh?
Why did you leave his charge sheet
without any annotations?
Why were there no repercussions for
Walsh? I've already told you this -
I don't remember.
No, I think you do remember.
I think Gary Walsh came to see you
a few days before Burke died.
I think he told you that he'd found
heroin in Burke's possessions
as an attempt to frame him
to get him kicked out -
revenge for his younger brother.
You saw through that,
but yet there were no annotations
on Walsh's charge sheet,
no repercussions for Walsh,
is that usual for possession of
heroin?
I don't know what you're talking
about.
I've swabbed your cabin.
What will you say when those swabs
come back positive for heroin?
That it was me who picked up
the drugs from Burke's body.
Of course I'm contaminated!
For good...!
With respect, sir, I really think
there's a better...
You called Burke "treacherous" -
it's a very particular word to use.
Why did you call him that?
I didn't call him that.
"Fuck Craig Burke!
Burke was a treacherous little shit
"who got exactly what was
coming to him!"
You hadn't served with him
on a boat before this patrol.
Why would you call him
"treacherous"?
He'd been sleeping with
a girl at the Dunloch Peace Camp.
How do you know this? With respect,
sir, the Admiralty put me on Vigil
to solve problems and improve
standards.
So you picked on Burke all patrol.
Yes, I disliked him, but I always
played by the rule book.
I picked him
up on his poor standards.
Commander Newsome, could you ask
Hadlow to come and join us?
I believe that he witnessed
the assault on Burke on the missile
deck.
Hadlow's currently overseeing the
reactor - I think you'll agree...
There're plenty who can do that.
It's two minutes of his time.
Officer of the Watch, send
Engineering Officer Hadlow
to the wardroom as soon
as he's ordered the restart.
At least that thing's still working.
Sir, surely Hadlow is
needed back aft? I...
I want to hear it from him. OK,
look, this is what I think happened.
I think you hit Burke, he fell,
he hit his head and there was blood.
You went back later to his cabin to
apologise, or maybe to threaten him,
but instead you find him dead.
You panic - you'd already
confiscated Gary Walsh's heroin
and it was those drugs that you
used to plant on Burke's body -
and I think we're going to be
able to prove that. Right...
Is this really how you operate?
Is tell tall tales and hope
the jury are fucking idiots?
Enter.
Did you see someone hit
Burke on the missile deck?
Uh, I think...
Uh...
M-maybe, sir.
But who?
I didn't see his face, sir.
And you didn't think to report this
to me, after Burke was found dead?
No. No, sir.
I hardly-hardly saw anything.
If you're lying about that, you know
you'll be court-martialled
and the police will prosecute you.
Last chance.
No, I didn't see anything, sir.
Look, when we spoke, you said it
"wasn't up to you".
You said there was a chain of
command.
Were you thinking of any
senior officer in particular?
Was it Prentice you saw?
Couldn't say, sir.
Did Executive Officer Prentice
speak to you?
Did he threaten you or Walsh?
That is a ridiculous slur.
On your way.
What the hell was that about?
Just helping the DCI out,
Mark, as per our orders.
The crew need to know they can be
honest with us.
You just asked a junior officer
if they saw me beat up a rating!
Yes, because I think that is the
question DCI Silva wanted answering.
You were fucked last year,
but they let you hang on -
I was the condition for that.
You are only here because I'm here.
Being married to
an admiral's daughter
doesn't make you
an admiral quite yet
and I do think you have
questions left to answer.
Lock her away
until we can get her off the boat,
or I will write the book
on your many, many failings.
And, yes, maybe I will get my
father-in-law to write the
dedication.
That's very florid, Mark.
That's quite the...
Christ's sake, sir! This is
insanity! Look at our situation!
We have a dead crewman, a reactor
scram and a trawler pulled down
right behind us! Those things
require your fullest...
Enter. ..and immediate...
Is it the reactor? No, sir. They're
still carrying out pre-critical
checks.
It's this. It's Burke's fleece.
We think it was taken from his body
and hidden. Where did you find it?
The DCI asked me to search the
most direct route from Burke's cabin
to Lieutenant Commander Prentice's
cabin.
I found it hidden behind a
ventilation duct on that route.
Thank you. What about Gary Walsh?
Yeah, I spoke to him.
He admits trying to frame Burke
with the drugs
and claims that Prentice took them.
Thank you, Cox'n. Is that all?
Yes, sir.
As you were.
You hid this because it has your
blood on it.
This isn't something
that you're going to get out of.
Yes, I understand that.
Sir, engine room's ready
to pull rods.
Very good.
Tell them one minute
and I'll be there. Aye, sir.
You're stood down -
the same will apply to Walsh.
I think it's better that the
crew know the truth.
I'll brief the officers.
You're confined to your cabin.
I don't need to lock you in,
do I, Mark?
When you're done, come and see me.
Ma'am.
Kirsten Longacre.
Can you come and meet me?
I'm freaking out a wee bit.
Can you come? Jade? What's going on?
I want to talk to you.
I think I've messed up.
OK. Where are you?
Um, by the camp. Don't come there.
I'll drop you a pin. Are you far?
Call 999.
It's probably nothing.
No, erm, I was just...
I was meant to meet someone,
but...I want to talk to you first.
OK, well, I'm at Kirkmouth
Police Station. I'm leaving now.
Go somewhere safe, OK? Stay around
people until I can get to you.
Call Porter.
Are you still at work?
Embarrassing you'd assume that,
but, yeah, I am.
Do me a favour - try the word
"Purity" on the USB stick.
Bear with.
We're in.
Oy, there's a tonne of stuff.
Good, great.
Where are you?
I'm heading to Dunloch.
Jade Antoniak called and I think
she's in trouble.
I need you to send backup,
OK? I'll send you a pin now.
On it. Stay in contact,
back up's on its way.
Don't go after Hadlow.
He's just being loyal to his men,
it's...everything we ask them to be.
Tell me about Gary Walsh.
He, er...
He came to see me.
Said he suspected Burke was...
..using drugs. Uh, of course,
I saw that for what it was,
a clumsy attempt to frame Burke,
so I put him on report and
had him bring me the drugs.
And I told him that's not how we do
things. Of course,
I had no intention of holding on
to the drugs, I just, I...
I hadn't got round to disposing of
them.
You didn't think to inform
Captain Newsome?
No. God, no. No, it was a judgment
call. Walsh would've been
court-martialled.
I'd have lost a decent sailor for
the sake of a bad one.
Why was Burke waiting for you on the
missile deck?
He asked me to meet him there.
And you agreed to that?
Yeah, I thought I'd hear him out.
All he wanted to do was
break my nose.
He...
..got a couple of good ones in.
And then I hit him back, and...
..he hit his head.
I went back...
..later, to apologise in his
bunk room.
Did anyone see you? Uh, no.
No. It was before change of watch.
And you found him dead?
He died in front of me. Um...
I mean, I must have
seen his last few seconds.
I did that.
One punch and...
I've worked so bloody hard for this
job.
I know what I did was wrong.
After Burke was dead, what then?
I took the heroin and I tried to
make it look... Well, you know that.
I... You can understand, can't you?
Losing my whole career for the sake
of one punch in self-defence.
You cost me days.
I know.
I know and...
Oh, Chri...
My...
My wh...
..whole life is the Navy.
You stripped this off him?
Yes.
I knew it would be covered in blood,
so I hid it.
Tell me exactly what he looked like
when you found him.
Exactly.
Uh...
He was comatose, but still...
..twitching. Obviously,
he couldn't breathe.
He was sweating.
His nose was streaming,
buckets of the stuff,
and then he died before I could
even think what to do.
I didn't hit him that hard!
He didn't lose consciousness.
I'm sorry.
There's someone else
I need to speak to.
You know what to do with the stuff
I've put together.
I'm trusting you there
and I do trust you, Jade.
I love you as well.
It's not easy for me to say that.
I should say it to your
face more, I know that.
I have nothing else to say to you,
DCI Silva.
I need to speak to Adams -
it's urgent.
I'll be quick.
You have 30 seconds. Go on.
Are you still feeling unwell?
Yeah, I feel ruined.
What are your symptoms?
Aching, fever.
My eyes keep swimming. Like the flu,
but it never goes anywhere.
You gave Burke mouth-to-mouth? Yeah.
What, have I got a virus off him?
No.
Then what? What's going on with me?
I can't discuss it with you. Can you
see the medic and wait with her?
Officer Adams, I need you here.
Sorry, no chance.
Jesus! He needs to see
the medic as soon as possible.
Captain speaking.
Hear this, all crew.
We are all aware what will happen
if we fail to restart the reactor.
Our entire mission is at stake.
Despite the risks involved,
we have no choice.
Ready to restart the reactor, sir.
Prepare to pull rods.
Did you hear that?
If the reactor scrams again,
note...
..this is a Command call.
On my head.
Go ahead, EO.
Start pulling rods.
Aye, sir.
Pumps are stable.
Pulling rods now.
Pull group one.
Group one...
..50% withdrawn.
Group one, fully withdrawn.
Group one, fully withdrawn, sir.
Group two, 50% withdrawn.
Group two, fully withdrawn.
Pull group three.
Group three...
..50% withdrawn.
Group three, fully withdrawn.
Group three, fully withdrawn, sir.
Reactor, critical.
Full power is available.
Thank Christ for that.
Reactor level 28% and rising, sir.
Officer of the Watch,
secure from periscope depth.
Return to safe depth.
Roger, sir. Cronin.
Returning to safe depth.
Sir, the recon vessel has located
the wreck of the missing
trawler, the Mhairi Finnea.
Have them dive at first light.
Aye, aye, sir.
I got it wrong about Prentice.
But he's admitted to it.
No. He did what he did because
he thought he'd killed Burke.
I don't think Burke
died of a head injury.
I think he was poisoned.
Jade?!
J...?!
Jade...
One, two, three, four, five...
C'mon! Jade!
One, two,
three, four...
J...!