.
- Previously on "Good Girls":
- He said there's someone else.
[knocking]
- They were out of cinnamon,
so...
- I'm the dick
who slept with your dad.
I'm a complete idiot.
I'm lonely.
- Nancy's lonely, too.
- You were awesome this week.
I mean, you moved more cars
than our top guy.
- I've been working
on your calendar.
- Where are you going to be?
- Here, at work.
We can't both steer the ship.
[moaning]
- You didn't tell him yet?
- Tell me what?
- We're partners now.
- You can go to hell!
- You can have whatever
you want, just stop!
- He said you were
former Mossad?
- That's the rumor, right?
[laughs]
- Did you ever,
like, kill a dude?
- You are hilarious.
- But have you?
- You got a good one in there.
It'll be worse for him.
- Whatever you need to know,
but he has to stay out of it.
What do you want?
- Her.
- How can I help you?
- Yeah, I got some cars
coming in today.
- What did you put in the cars?
- Yeah, you don't gotta worry
about all that stuff.
I am going to need you to
deliver me one more, yeah?
Why don't you just tell me
what you're looking for.
- 50-50.
- You look good
behind that desk.
- Do we have a deal or not?
- Mm-hmm.
- Great.
[alarm blaring]
[Polo and Pan's
"Dorothy" plays]
♪
- ♪ Scarecrow, Tin-Man,
Dorothy ♪
♪ Lion is afraid of me,
Lion is afraid of me ♪
la-la-la-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la-la
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la-la,
la-la-la-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ Escape from reality,
Where I go you follow me ♪
♪ Where I go, you follow me,
Where I go, you follow me ♪
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la-la,
La-la-la-la-la-la-la ♪
[alarm blaring]
["Dorothy" continues]
♪
♪ Tornado swallowing
my house ♪
♪ Get higher
♪ It looks like it's spinning
around ♪
♪ I'm lost, I'm lost,
in a shiny new world ♪
♪ Follow, follow, follow
the yellow brick road ♪
♪ Walking ahead
in a brand new style ♪
♪ Flower shower flowers
raining on me ♪
♪
[alarm blaring]
[clock clatters,
alarm stops]
♪
♪ It looks like...
- ♪ You wanna be a fly girl,
bust a move ♪
♪ You wanna be a fly girl,
show me proof ♪
say it loud ♪
♪ All the fly girls
break it down ♪
♪ You wanna be a fly girl,
bust a move ♪
show me proof ♪
♪ You wanna be a fly girl,
say it loud ♪
♪ All the fly girls
break it down ♪
♪ Break it down,
Break it down ♪
♪ Break it down
- [clears throat]
- ♪ Break it down
- What did I miss?
- That kid puked during tap.
- Was that
"Singin' In the Rain"?
- Singin' somethin'.
[phone buzzing]
♪ No cheap fakes
and don't be late ♪
♪ Fly girls love to
keep it classy ♪
♪ Never trashy,
always sassy ♪
♪ One, two, three,
I got a fly girl degree ♪
[whistles and applause]
♪ You wanna be a fly girl
♪ Bust a move,
you wanna be a fly girl,
♪ Show me proof,
you wanna be a fly girl ♪
♪ Say it loud
- I'll be right back.
- ♪ You wanna be a fly girl,
bust a move ♪
- [whispering] Excuse me.
I'm so sorry.
- ♪ You wanna be a fly girl,
say it loud ♪
♪ All the fly girls
break it down ♪
♪ Break it down,
♪ Break it down, break it
down ♪
♪ Break it down,
break it down ♪
[muffled music continues]
♪
- What's 50-50 mean to you?
- If this is about
the drop-off,
I'm doing it in the morning.
- 50-50 means I'm paying you
so damn much
I don't have to come
and track you down anymore.
At your recitals and swim
and the orthodontist and--
- Why do I feel like we keep
having this conversation?
- You tell me.
- Well, then let's stop.
[audience cheering]
- See, problem is,
our customers,
they want their drop
tonight.
See, me and you,
we're like FedEx now, right?
They sleep, we deliver,
'cause if we don't,
we're gonna hear about it.
- Well, I'm with my family.
Why don't you do it?
[footsteps approach]
- Sure.
- Thank you.
- I'll take the 100%.
- What?
- I'll do your job for you,
you take all
the personal days you want.
- I'll drop
the car off tonight.
- Cool.
[muffled cheers and applause]
Thanks, Partner.
[applause winding down]
- Yay!
Come here you little pumpkin.
You were amazing!
Ah!
What was your favorite part?
- The spinning.
- What was your favorite part?
- When she did the big leap.
- The big--what was your
favorite part?
- Uh...when she stood!
- [chuckles]
- Mommy, you missed it.
- I bet you were great.
- Oh, hey,
you're gonna take a picture
with everyone up on stage.
Go get 'em.
- Queen Thunder Clam.
- Ew!
[laughter]
Hey, I'm just following
the rules.
- What's mine?
- Okay, you are
Magnificent Glitter Beaver.
[laughter]
- I'll take it!
What are you?
- I'm Madame Whisker Waffles.
[laughter]
Who makes this stuff up?
- Wait, there's one for guys.
- Oh, my God, do Deansie.
- Okay, Deansie is
the Dainty Ham Tickler.
[laughter]
- What is this?
- Amy found this name generator
for your, um, for a woman's--
It takes all the letters
of your name--
- No, I got it.
- Did you want to hear about
the lice problem in fifth grade
or the geranium sale
at the nursery?
'Cause it's all on there.
- Nope, I'm good.
- I recorded her
for three days.
- I get it.
- It's not like we sit around
talking about crime.
- Of course not.
- I got what I could.
- Hey, thanks for trying.
- Well, Stan will be home
with the kids soon, so...
- Just one last question.
Do Sara and Harry
have grandparents?
- Stan's side.
- Relatively healthy?
- I guess so.
- Names?
[pen clicks]
- George and Charisse?
- You spell that with two S's?
- Why?
- Well, you're solid folk.
I wanna make sure your kids
are taken care of.
- What do you mean?
- When you
and your husband go away.
[sad music plays]
- I did every single thing
you asked.
- And still got nothing.
- I don't know what you want!
- Pictures,
people, names, dates.
Something I can use.
- All right you guys,
it's bedtime.
PJs, brush your teeth.
Jane, you need a bath.
- I'm clean!
- You are the opposite.
Will you make sure
that she wipes the makeup
off her face? 'Cause
that's gonna get on the sheets.
- Where are you going?
- I have a thing.
- Are you kidding me right now?
- It's for work.
- No.
- No?
- I got a thing.
- What?
- Book club.
- Okay, very funny.
- You take off her makeup.
- Dean, I can't leave them
here alone.
- You tuck 'em in.
- Dean?
- Book. Club.
[door slams]
[dog barks distantly]
- Where are we?
- We are on a secret mission.
- Can we get ice cream now?
- Yeah, we just have to wait
for Auntie Annie
to come pick us up.
- I want to go home.
- Why does Auntie Annie
have to pick us up?
[distant siren wailing]
- Because we have to leave
this car here.
- Why?
- Because it's...
a grown-up reason.
- Why?
- Who wants to listen
to the kid's station?
[The Kinnardlys
"Until You Smile" plays]
♪
- ♪ Out of the pan
and into the fire ♪
♪ Nothing stops me,
over the moon ♪
♪ And under the radar,
there I'll be ♪
♪ Into the blue and out
of my dare to steal ♪
♪ I don't care,
up on the clouds... ♪
- Well. This takes family night
to a whole new level.
- Okay, you guys.
Let's go.
- Hurry up, guys.
Auntie's running on fumes.
[song continues]
- Are you serious?
[engine stops running]
- Anything, hey hey ♪
[engine starts]
- Huh. No. Ha-ha.
- ♪ Hey hey, I'll walk
through the fire ♪
♪ Whatever it takes,
hey hey ♪
- All right, pack it up.
- Mommy!
Mommy!
- Okay, we're gonna find it.
- [crying] I need my dubby!
- Well, it's gotta be here.
- I can't ever sleep again.
- God, please don't say that.
Have you looked under the bed?
Did you check
in these covers?
- It's not anywhere!
- Okay, did you have it
this morning?
- Yes.
- Okay, and did you have it
when I tucked you in tonight?
- No...
- When was the last time
you remember having it?
- In the creepy car.
.
- [laughs] Tuck your chin.
Put your shoulders on my chest.
- [grunting]
- Find your point.
Come on, Princess. Come on.
Stop worrying
about your manicure.
- Ah!
[heavy breathing]
Okay, what if it was a knife?
- Straight shot to the berries.
- Okay, and a gun?
- Run as fast as you can.
[laughing]
- I'm serious.
- This guy is real bad news,
huh?
- I need him to go away.
- That's not a good road
for you.
- Yeah, he shot me.
- That's not all he did,
right?
Let's say I have a friend.
He takes care of your problem.
So you go back
to your good life
with a wife
who shtups bad people.
And one day
my friend gets picked up
for selling e-cigarettes
imported from Ukraine.
But they don't want my friend.
They want his boss.
He's not gonna roll over
on him because
then my friend's dead and so
are his children, his pets.
So my friend mentions you.
And the rest ends with you
in jail for murder.
- So what am I supposed to do?
Just let this dick
ruin my life?
- Go home.
Take a long shower.
- Yeah.
- Wash all that noise
down the drain.
- Be fresh as a daisy.
- And call the divorce lawyer.
- Stupid thing is...
I can't live without her.
What's that?
- My friend.
- Hey, morning.
Excuse me,
what about breakfast?
- I'm not hungry.
- Well, don't you need
a ride to school?
- Sarah's mom's picking me up.
- Sarah L or Sarah W?
- Sarah with an H.
- Does that mean she spells
her first name with an H
or the first letter
of her last name--
- Does it matter?
- Yeah, actually, it does.
I would like to know who's
driving you to school.
- Oh, right.
Because you're Parent Mom.
It's just hard
to keep track these days.
There's Parent Mom, Cool Mom,
Sketchy Mom, Cheating Mom.
- Okay, just plain old Mom
will suffice.
- I'm not gonna
be home tonight.
- Why's that?
- I'm going to the movies
with Jordan.
- Girl Jordan or boy Jordan?
Okay, well, I hope you have
a really great time
at the movies!
[sighs]
[phone ringing]
Oy, yoy, yoy.
What happened?
- I need your help.
- Yay.
Wait, why is everybody
on the floor?
- I just found her that way.
- I'll be right there.
Of all the places
to leave a dubby.
- Well, maybe they're parents
too and they'll get it.
- Are you sure you don't want
to make her go cold turkey?
I mean, I don't either.
[camera shutter snapping]
- What are you doing?
- Well, you know,
we're thinking about
updating our place...
- With a half a washing machine
on the front lawn?
- Or an oil-stained mattress?
- It's--it's got a cute porch.
- That is not oil,
but you must know that, right?
- Let's just do this.
Hi, I made a delivery here
last night.
- Uh-huh.
- And it's the funniest thing,
but I think I left
my daughter's
baby blanket in the car.
She calls it her dubby.
- Uh-huh?
- Probably right
in the backseat.
- Uh-huh.
- You know,
it was really dark.
- Yeah, you sure
this is the right house?
- Do you mind if I just sorta--
[clicks tongue]
Like, take a peek in the car?
- Mm.
[electro-hip-hop plays]
♪
So tell us about this,
uh...dubby.
.
- It's just a blanket,
hand-knit.
- You come across any, uh,
hand-knit dubbys?
Maybe if you were
a little more specific.
- Sure it's, um,
worsted merino wool
with a drop-stitch pattern.
- Uh-huh.
Color?
- Pink.
- Uh-huh.
- You know, it's really
not that big of a deal.
- Yeah, we got people waiting
who are going to be worried.
- Oh, no, no, no, no.
I got your dubby.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
It's just, uh,
[ahem]
it's in the basement.
- [whispers]
Oh, sweet Jesus.
- Well, go get it, man.
Go get the dubby.
Oh, and, uh, you.
Go help him.
- But he can get it himself,
right?
- Well, yeah, he could,
but that's no fun.
- I'll go with you.
- No.
You go next.
- No one's going anywhere.
Just keep the dubby, okay?
- Why don't you sit down?
Sit down!
- Oh.
You think 'cause you all have
guns that you're in charge.
That's adorable.
This guy's hilarious, huh?
[laughing]
[lightly edgy music]
Do you know who I am?
- Hm. Prettiest little mommy
I've ever seen.
- Well, thank you very much.
But, no.
I'm the reason you exist.
I bring you the pills.
Without me,
none of you would be here.
None of this would be there.
This...lovely home.
With its old world charm
and--
what was it that you liked?
- Uh, uh, just the porch.
- Yeah, the porch.
See, all this goes away
the second you disrespect me.
And you know
what I really don't like?
The idea that any one of us
would want to go
to your basement.
Nowadays,
that is really not cool.
- I mean...was it ever?
- No, it wasn't.
So what do you want to do here?
You wanna...make it personal
or you wanna keep it
professional?
- Wallets, phones.
- Seems fair.
- I didn't think it would--
- Mm-mm.
- At first he didn't seem so--
- No.
- Hey,
where have you been?
- I got held up.
- The Feds, our buddy,
he opened up a thing.
- What's a thing, Stan?
- An IA deal, or whatever.
- I literally have no idea
what you're saying.
- Internal Affairs, okay?
They investigate dirty cops.
- For what?
- The pen cap, Ruby.
What is wrong with you?
I'm sorry.
I tried to call you.
I was trying to text you.
- I lost my phone.
- This is bad, right?
- How many guys
are they looking at?
- I don't know, I guess
everybody who worked inside
the evidence room.
- Right.
- I mean, you think
it's protocol or you think
he knows something now?
- I don't know.
- I-I just don't know how
tweaked I need to be.
I mean, this could mean
serious jail time, Ruby,
if they know it's me.
But how could they, you know?
There was no one else
in the evidence room.
I made sure of that.
And I wore gloves.
[sound of voice fading]
- Stan.
It's gonna be okay.
[phone buzzing]
- It's Dean.
[Muzak plays]
♪
- Oh, hey,
is that the Princess Pink?
- Oh, yeah,
it's the last one.
Sorry.
- No, it's okay.
You know what?
Can I just have it?
I--I'm having an emergency.
- You have a yarn emergency?
- I lost my daughter's favorite
blankie that she sleeps with
every single night,
and I can't get it back,
so I need to knit
a whole new one
that looks just like the
old one in that exact color.
- Well,
I would love to help you.
- Thank you so much.
- But, I promised Kevin
I would knit him a new scarf.
- Is Kevin your son?
- My cat.
- Ah.
Didn't know cats wore scarves.
- Kevin does.
- Huh. Do you think...
Kevin would consider wearing
a scarf in a different color?
- This is his favorite.
- Ah.
I don't mean to be
disrespectful, it's just...
it's my child, you know?
- Oh, I get it.
I mean, Kevin is like my child.
- No, no, no, no.
That is not--no.
He is not a child,
he is not a person,
he is a cat,
Who would probably
eat your face off
if he didn't have food
for, like, five minutes.
[club music plays]
- Hey! What are you doing here?
- My taxes.
What does it look like?
- No, I--you just never come
for B-day drinks.
- It's someone's birthday?
- Megan's 40th.
- Who?
- Frozen foods? Megan?
We got her this hilarious
card, it says, um,
"You're not getting older.
You're just increasing
your value!"
- That's incredible.
- You want to sign it?
- Uh, excuse me,
excuse me.
Hi, yeah, um,
can I get a margarita?
Um, hold the lime juice and,
uh, the triple sec.
And the sour mix.
- So just tequila?
- Yeah, and could you, uh,
put it in a shot glass
and throw it
on the birthday girl's tab?
Thanks.
[slow tempo music plays]
♪
What?
- Nothing.
- I'm not going
to have sex with you.
- Huh.
- Yeah, I know for some reason
all this seems to scream
that I'm real down to party,
but I'm actually
just a regular person
who's trying to get real drunk.
I've had a week.
- I'm Noah.
- Hey, Noah. I'm Ariana Grande.
- I just started at
Fine and Frugal.
- [snorts]
Why would you do that?
- Well, I needed a job.
- What, and the coal mine
wasn't hiring?
- [laughs]
- Because I'm telling you,
there is literally
nothing worse.
Like, minimum wage,
minimum benefits.
Won't even let you
drop a deuce on company time.
- I can't go in public anyway.
- Well,
it's good news for you
because they make you
clock out.
[scoffs]
Place is run by fascists.
Excuse me.
- What about the managers?
- [bitter laugh]
Pfff. [belches]
Noah, sweet Noah.
Noah!
- It's that bad, huh?
- Mm.
Just imagine, if you will,
rounding up the saddest
little losers
on the entire planet--
perverts, knuckle-draggers,
and rapists.
That is who they hire,
every time, without fail.
- Well, I'm really looking
forward to it.
I think it's gonna be fun.
- That's sad.
So what are you?
No, no, don't tell me.
Let me guess.
Mm. Produce?
You've really got a whole,
"I've thrown away everything
in my life," vibe.
- I'm the new manager.
- [mutters]
We do use real crab
in the crab salad.
- I love crab.
- Me too.
- Are you Annie?
- Mm-mm.
- Is there an Annie Marks here?
- Oh, she's right here!
Hey, Annie.
- You have a call.
- Thanks.
Excuse me.
- Yeah.
- Hello.
[police radio chatter]
[somber music]
♪
- Dean!
- I tried to call you.
- What happened?
- You didn't answer your phone.
- What's going on?
- We can't find Jane.
.
- Okay, where were you?
- Okay, I was, uh,
I was making dinner.
- And you didn't see anything--
- No, the kids were all--
- Or hear anything?
- They were running around.
Well, the news was on.
- And you were watching them?
- Yes!
- Or were you watching TV?
- I really hate the way you're
speaking to me right now.
- Did you look everywhere?
- Kids get lost, Beth.
- No, parents lose them!
- You're putting this on me?
- No--
- You weren't even here,
as always.
- I know.
- Why don't you ask
Mr. Neck Tats? Huh?
- What are you talking about?
- Maybe he has an idea
where your daughter is.
- Are you suggesting
that he took our child?
- Oh, I'm so stupid! He shot me
in my own living room.
You gotta draw the line
somewhere, right?
How has it never occurred
to you that what you're doing
is going to come back
and bite us in the ass.
[door opens, slams]
- Where're you going?
- I'm coming with you.
- They took our wallets, right?
- Uh-uh, don't.
- So they know everything.
They know who we are,
they know where we live.
- Don't go there.
- She could be anywhere.
- It hasn't been that long.
- I have so many pictures
of those kids on my phone.
- Beth,
we're gonna find her.
- Son of a bitch,
where are my keys?
- Honey, they're in your hand.
- Okay, you guys stay here
just in case she comes back.
- Janey!
Janey!
- I just cannot believe
this is happening.
- Jane!
- We're gonna find her, man.
- Like, I am freaking out
right now, man.
- Janey!
- Jane!
- We gotta stop this guy.
[synth-pop plays]
Do you know what
I'm talking about?
- Yeah.
[dramatic vocalizing]
♪
- Got to go over there, okay?
Right now. They've got Jane.
- What are you talking about?
- They took my kid!
- Who took your kid?
- The guys with the drugs
in the house.
Your colleagues.
- Our colleagues.
- Okay, whatever.
- Why would they do that?
- I don't know!
I pissed them off!
- You went in the house.
- So?
- So what, Dean?
I can't just arrest the guy.
- That's not what I'm saying.
- Okay, what are you saying?
- What do you think
this is, huh?
Some kind of hobby?
You make a little extra cash
selling Herbalife
while you still drive
carpool and play dance mom?
- My daughter needed something
in the car.
- Who cares?
- I do!
I'm a mother!
- You're a drug dealer!
You move pills
and you wash cash.
That's what you do.
That's who you are,
and if you mess up at that
you go to jail or you die.
Get your head straight.
♪
They didn't take your daughter.
- How do you know?
- There no money in that.
- Me and a couple
of your cop buddies.
We end this guy.
- Hey, she couldn't
have gone too far, okay?
Let's look over
by the swings.
Janey!
[vocalizing]
- Sadie's not answering
her phone.
- You tried her friend?
- She said
they never had plans.
- Why don't you go?
- What about Beth?
- I'll stay.
Go. You should go.
- Okay.
- Go!
- Okay, okay. Just--
just call me later, okay?
[Alice Phoebe Lou's
"She" plays]
♪
- ♪ She
♪ She
♪ She didn't want to lose
her desire ♪
♪
♪ She
♪ She looked out
to the horizon ♪
♪
♪ She said
I wanna go to Mars ♪
[clattering]
♪ And this
♪ This planet ain't ours
♪ She said I want to go
to Mars ♪
♪ And this,
this planet ain't ours ♪
- Hi.
.
- Look at that suitcase.
Your traveling game
is on point.
I mean, You got your friends,
gummy bears.
What more do you need?
So where you headed?
Big Apple?
Vegas?
Hogwarts?
- I'm not allowed
to cross the street.
- Well, then the closet
is a smart choice.
Your mom's busy with work,
huh?
Well, we have been friends
for a long ass time.
Before you even got here.
Before your brothers,
your sister.
- Before iPads?
- Before iPads.
Way back.
The thing about your mom
that you should know--
whenever you need her,
no matter what's going on,
She's just...
you know...
she's just there.
[door opens, closes]
- Jane!
- Jane?
- In here.
[running footsteps]
- Thank you.
- Come to Dad. Come here.
Come here, baby.
[door opening]
- Oh, my God.
- Here we go.
- Where have you been?
- Told you I went
to the movies.
- That's funny,
because I tweeted at Roxie
who Facebooked Mia
who DM'd Paul who said
that he was having mango boba
with both Girl Jordan
and Boy Jordan at Noodle World,
so I know that's total bull!
- Oh, so now I'm the liar?
- Yes, correct!
- I went with Nancy.
Thought you'd say no.
- I don't care,
but I have to know
that you're safe.
- Okay.
- Guess I'm that mom.
- Don't ever do that again.
Hey, Sadie?
Do you have, like,
maybe an ETA?
- On what?
- When you'll be my kid again?
I'm really trying to give you
your space but, um,
gotta be honest,
it's kinda killing me.
- I don't know.
- Okay.
Good night.
[Clooney's "Everybody
Loves a Dream" plays]
♪
- ♪ There is one
for you I know ♪
♪ Everybody loves a dream,
crazy as that dream may seem ♪
- I like snacks,
so I feel like
that's how people
look at this.
- I like fruit
with my treats,
so like I'm totally down
with this blueberry.
I do like that there's
a large assortment
of bite-size...
Good morning.
- Hi.
- Hi. Did you pre-deuce?
Because, you know,
company time.
- Look, um, I think I should
save you some trouble
and just quit right now.
- No I was tot--I'm kidding.
I mean, you can deuce whenever
you want on company time.
- Will you stop saying that?
- Yeah,
you started that, though.
- Okay, um, here's the thing.
I had, like,
a really terrible relationship
with the last manager here.
- Okay. Was he a pervert,
rapist, or knuckle-dragger?
- Depended on the day.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Um, so if you're gonna
just torture me for the next
six months, I really think
it's better for both of us if I
just cut my losses and move on.
- I don't think
you should leave.
- Why not?
- Well, for one you've got
a great attitude, and I feel
like we could really use
that kind of school spirit
around here.
- Funny.
- Yeah.
Okay, you know what?
Um, you seem super smart,
you're funny as hell,
and I just feel like
I would have a lot
less fun if you weren't here.
♪
- I don't want
to clock in anymore.
- So don't.
I trust you.
- I don't want to pay
for my daily donut.
- I'm not counting 'em.
- I don't want to bag.
I'm a cashier.
- Right,
that's why we have baggers.
- Why are you being so cool?
- Because you deserve better
than this place.
♪
Am I wrong?
I--I do have, um,
I have one question, though.
What do you want?
[both grunting, moaning]
Oh, my God.
This violates so many codes.
- Shut up!
- HR, health, morality.
- And just common decency.
- Shut up!
[both laughing]
[children laughing]
- All right, Emma.
Here it comes.
Is someone moving
this one?
♪ Here's one
- Annie's shoes!
Annie's school!
- [laughing]
All right, Jane,
it's your turn.
[Timber Timbre's
"Run From Me" plays]
- ♪ Run from me, Darling
♪
- Oh!
- ♪ Run, my good wife
- Anything good?
- ♪ Run from me, Darling
- For you, Elizabeth.
- ♪ You better run
for your life ♪
♪
♪ Run from me, Baby
♪ Run, my good wife
♪
♪ Run from me, Darling
- Bye, Daddy.
- Bye.
- Hey, Baby.
Have a good day.
- ♪ For your life
♪
♪ Run, run
- [whispering] They're
giving us lie detectors.
- ♪ Run
♪ Run
[vocalizing]
♪
♪ Run
- Can you meet me right now?
[slow country music plays]
- ♪ Each time I see you
♪ I contemplate
♪
♪ What I love most of all
♪ Your swinging gait
♪