.
- Previously on
"Good Girls"...
- We got a mutual friend
turns out.
He's talking to the feds now.
So, I'm gonna need you
to handle that.
- You are ratting out a gang,
you think they're gonna
let you talk?
You gotta disappear for good.
How much?
- 20,000.
- I took a payday loan.
I used your check
as collateral
and forged your name.
- We'll figure it out.
- He said there's
someone else.
- They're out of cinnamon,
so...
- Hey, stupid bitch.
Open the damn door.
- Ooh.
[shouting]
- It was an accident.
- Where did you, um, put it?
- We have a--a meat freezer.
- Who keeps calling this dude?
- It's Marion.
- If you would just give me
a quick ring when you get in.
I just can't get to sleep.
- I'm worried about Leslie.
I didn't know who else I could
talk to, so...
- What's going on?
- I think something bad
happened.
all: Three!
- Okay, let's just go.
[dramatic music]
[ominous orchestral music]
♪
- [mouths words]
[truck whirring and humming]
♪
[bag crunches]
- [sighs]
♪
[dog barks in distance]
- What is on tap for you today?
- Just the usual:
Groceries, carpool,
dry cleaning.
- What, no book club?
- No.
- Oh.
What, a bad pick this month?
- You know, just some
crime thriller.
- [laughs]
- Got way too dark.
- That's pretty funny.
- There she is.
How does it feel?
We gotta celebrate.
You did it, you're a boss now.
Hey, can we get a couple, uh...
What's your poison, huh?
Like a--like a summer rosé
or something?
- It's 10:00 in the morning.
- The lady will take
a crisp chardonnay.
- Thank you, I'm not staying.
- You're sure?
I'm giving you the keys
to the kingdom here.
- Why?
- I'm out.
I'm done, man,
time for something new.
- No, why me?
- I think you
could be something.
- I don't wanna be something.
- No?
What you wanna be then, huh?
A fireman?
Astronaut?
- I don't know.
A good person.
- No, you're way more
interesting than that.
- You don't know me.
- I think I do.
- I don't drink rosé.
- Can we get a bourbon
on the rocks?
[indistinct music playing
over stereo]
♪
If you change your mind...
- I won't.
- Kingdom's in your name.
- And don't throw
the bacon grease out, dear.
I cook with that.
- Got it.
Hey, what's this stuff?
- Oh, that's for Leslie.
He does my finances.
- This one says "final notice."
- Well, he'll iron it out.
- Marion, this says
you're being evicted.
- Oh, he'll fix all that.
Gesture of congratulations.
Twelve letters.
- Well...
What if he can't fix it?
Just 'cause, you know,
he's not around right now.
- Well, he's gonna come back.
He has to.
He does everything for me.
- Pat on the back.
- I'm sorry?
- Gesture of congratulations.
Twelve letters.
- Well, look at you,
Ms. Smarty-Pants!
[chuckles]
- That's what they call me.
- [chuckles]
- What's going on?
- Um, homeless shelter,
youth home, church pantry.
Spread the Joy Detroit
only wants PB&J.
Now, I'm all for a theme,
but really?
The homeless get
to be picky now?
- [sighs]
[sighs]
- You okay?
- I'm a smart man.
- Okay.
- You know, I'm talking
common sense,
"I know some bull
when I see it" smart.
- Uh-huh.
- But there I stood
in the Qwik Ca$h line,
uniform and everything.
Ready to tell these fools
that even though we might look
like every person that walks
through that door,
that's not who we are, right?
- That's right.
And they can save their crap
for the next Joe
with "sucker" written
on his forehead,
'cause I'm not the one.
Not today.
- What happened?
- I walked out.
- Stanley.
- With a second loan
to cover the first one.
- Stanley Lamont Hill,
we just got another EOB.
- I think I might have even
said "thank you."
- Oh, my--what are we gonna do?
- You might wanna keep
that corn.
- You have to spend money
to make money.
You know, these bank people,
they just don't understand.
- How does this happen again?
- It's called an investment,
you know?
- Oh, my God.
- It's gonna take a minute.
I took my eye off the ball,
I was learning to walk again,
shoot me.
Oh, wait...
- Oh, my God.
- It looks a lot worse
than what it is.
- They are taking everything.
- Yeah, but we still have
the 'Vette.
- That is one car.
- Yes, but I'm gonna sell
that 'Vette,
and I'm gonna take the money
and get some fresh blood.
Right? And then it's Halloween,
and we have all those fall
promos and the Spooktacular.
[voice fading] The people
love the Spooktacular.
We're gonna move...
[forlorn rock music]
♪
- I have to show you guys
something.
♪
.
- I know.
- [exhales deeply]
- Fake?
- Yeah.
- And he doesn't want a cut?
- Nope.
- How much?
- A lot.
- [chuckling]
- So, I'm thinking we just
wash a little, right?
Just to dig us out--
- How long?
- What?
- How long have you had this?
- Not that long.
- This right here...
- So, you just--you weren't
gonna tell us, or?
- This is 20 grand.
- Well, I'm telling you now.
- Yeah, now that
you're in trouble.
- Are you serious right now?
[imitating Beth]
- "Are you serious right now?"
- 60 G's right here.
- There's no point,
I tried counting it for weeks.
- Hold up.
Did you just say "weeks"?
- I was trying to protect you.
- From what?
From being rich and happy?
- We got this by killing a man.
- We didn't kill anyone.
- No.
We just threw him away.
In a trash bin,
like an old, dirty futon.
- So, we wash what we need,
and--and then we burn the rest.
- Do you wanna know
what I think?
You're not the boss of me.
Yeah.
Okay.
[exciting music]
- Hi.
I have some returns.
- I have some returns.
- All of it?
- Yeah.
The bride got cold feet
last minute.
You wouldn't believe the drama.
All I can tell you
is the next time
someone asks me to be
in their wedding,
the answer is no.
- Just need to see your ID.
- Why?
I-I have the receipt.
- Our return policy's changed.
- Since when?
- About a month ago.
- Oh.
- Mrs. Hill?
♪
- Is there a problem?
- We know
what you've been doing.
- Southfield, Sterling Heights,
Livonia, Pontiac,
Allen Park.
- You've engaged
in a coordinated pattern
of buying and returning
all over Southeastern Michigan.
- You wanna charge me
with something,
you go right ahead, little man.
'Cause my lawyer's
gonna be so far up
that tight little ass
of yours.
♪
- Beth.
Hi, I meant to ask
after soccer,
where did we land on the...
- I put you on desserts
with Sandy.
- We--we can talk
about this later.
- Root beer floats,
diet for the teachers
and three dozen cupcakes...
no plastic toppers.
And everything's gotta be
nut-free.
- I bet you feel like
some big, strong, manly man.
Like a real cool dude
harassing his loyal customers.
Like some kind of pathetic,
little dick-ass--
- You're not being arrested.
- Oh.
- You just can't shop here
anymore.
♪
- Oh...
Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
- [sighs]
- What the hell, Annie?
- What do you want from me?
- I want you to return a text.
- Well, I have a lot
going on right now.
- Yeah, me too.
- Hey, you know your wife?
Your pregnant wife?
Yeah, she knows.
- Yeah, I'm aware, thank you.
- So, I think it's pretty much
game over, okay?
Can't sink any lower.
- Well, how's this for low?
- Don't.
- I wanna be with you.
- No.
- Yes.
I wanna leave
my pregnant wife--
- Shh, shh, shh, shh.
- And I wanna just be with you
and just--
I wanna drink
peppermint schnapps
and just look at you
for a while.
- You don't get to do that.
- You know what I've always
loved about you?
- Please don't.
- Your eyebrows.
- You do not.
- I do.
I can't get enough of them.
Wait, what are you doing
with all this stuff?
- Selling it.
Hey, wanna buy a Vitamix?
- I'm living in a motel.
- Yeah but it spins so fast,
it can make soup.
- Oh.
- Huh?
[laughs]
- Let me know
what you wanna do.
[soft music]
♪
- What you doing?
- Just crying
at my screensaver.
- As you do.
- Right?
[indistinct music playing]
I mean, look at that.
- Tiny humans.
- So cute.
I'm so sorry.
- I know.
- I really blew it... again.
- Come here.
- No.
- It all has to be anonymous.
- There's no way in hell.
- You'll use a fake name.
- Do you remember
when I had a penis?
'Cause I don't.
- Dean.
- What was it like?
Was it nice?
I seem to recall it had
something to do with
making children.
- Okay.
- What?
The guy shot me, Beth.
- I know that.
- And now you wanna use
his money to pay our bills.
- This is our way out.
- With his dirty-ass money.
- It's my money.
- Oh, yeah?
What'd you do for it?
- A job.
- Is that what we're
calling it now?
- Believe me, I earned it.
- Look, if you could just
give me a little more time.
- For what, Dean?
To sell the 'Vette?
- I could come up with plan B.
- We passed plan B, years ago.
This is it, honey.
This is what's left.
- I hate that guy.
I hate his money.
- Dean.
[dramatic jazz music]
This isn't money yet.
You have to make it money.
♪
- How?
- You do what you're good at.
You sell cars.
.
- I got 10 G's of espresso
machines up on eBay.
- Wanna sit?
- I'm about to roll up
to the freeway
and sell this shizz
outta my trunk.
- I did something.
- I literally get hives
every time you say that.
- That's why I asked you
to sit.
- You know what would help?
If you just led
with what you did
instead of letting my mind
run wild.
- I gave Dean the money.
He'll buy with fake
and sell for real,
and we'll take a cut.
- Cars for cash?
- What do you think?
- How much did you give him?
- More than a little.
- She's gonna lose her mind.
- Well, it's just paper
if we can't wash it.
- All right.
- Okay, maybe don't tell her.
- Hey, she's your sister.
- I know, but I hate
asking you to lie.
- Again, we threw a man away.
- We're still gonna burn
the rest.
- You think he can handle it?
- It's what he does.
- No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
This is a 3.6 liter V6.
- What's the difference?
- Oh, well, about
60 horsepower.
- Okay.
- I can always sell you
a bigger car,
but my job is to get you
what you need.
- How much do I need for it
just to drive regular?
- Excuse me, Mr. B,
I got a bite on that 'Vette.
- Ooh, if you'll excuse me,
I'll be right back.
Okay?
- Okay.
It's gonna be okay.
Mommy's gonna get you.
- I have the same car, here.
- Thank you.
- [chuckles]
- Do you like it?
- I mean, for me, it's perfect.
- How many horses or whatever
did you get?
- I think somewhere between
zero and I really don't care.
- [laughs]
- But this is what I love
about it.
This comes right down...
And you can put
your stroller there.
- Oh, cool.
- And see that latch?
It's a new system
for baby seats,
which makes it super easy when
your hands are full, which is--
together: Always.
- Oh, and the cup holders,
they're right where you need
'em for sippies and stuff.
And there's even one
on the dash that pops out.
- You think I could take it
for a test drive?
- I actually don't
work here, but...
- I can't--I can't let you
do that.
I just talked to my guy
in financing,
and the best bang for your buck
is that bad boy
right over there,
not the minivan.
Same sticker price, but it's
twice the car under the hood.
- You know, I gotta get
this one home.
- I understand.
Here, um, think about it.
There's my card.
You know, talk to your husband.
[dramatic music]
Thanks for coming by
Boland Motors.
♪
- Oh.
That was--that was nice
of Gloria to visit.
- They brought coleslaw
and stayed for five minutes.
[old-timey music playing
over stereo]
♪
- Still, I'm really glad
you got to meet
your great grandchild.
- Well, that's one of us.
[knocking at door]
Oh, get that, would you?
I've got something in the oven.
♪
- Why are you doing this?
- She's got two days left,
okay?
- What is wrong with you?
- It's the building, not me.
- Look, I will get you
the money for her, okay?
I just need a little more time.
- We've already given her
six months.
- No but her--her grandson
pays her rent.
- Not for the better part
of a year.
- Son of a bitch.
[door clicks open]
- Hey.
- How'd we do?
- Uh, great.
Yeah, really, really great.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, so many test drives,
you know?
- How many?
- You know, everyone wanted,
uh, they wanted a selfie.
[chuckles]
- No, how many did he sell?
- I wouldn't be surprised
if Boland Motors
was trending right now.
You know, we got so many bites.
Yeah, and it's all about
social media, you know?
Getting our name out there,
you know, and building a buzz.
And balloons--
you know, thing is,
people totally underestimate
the power of balloons.
- So, that's some gorilla, huh?
- Yeah, you can see it
from the highway,
really draws 'em in.
- How much did it cost?
[electronic music]
- You can't really judge
these things by the numbers.
- Right.
- Trust me, I got it.
It's going great.
♪
.
[lock clicks]
- Please don't be mad at me.
- Okay.
- I really messed up.
- [sighs]
Okay.
- I mean, the man is made
of excuses.
I mean, the first time
we almost went under,
he blamed the housing crisis.
- Wait, I thought it was 9/11.
- You know what?
You're right, he used that too.
- [laughs]
Yeah.
And then, of course, there were
the California wildfires.
You know,
"Nobody's buying cars."
- In Detroit.
- Mm-mm.
- Like, it literally made
no sense,
and I fully bought it.
- And Brexit? I mean...
- [laughs]
He never used Brexit.
[laughter]
Why do I still want him
to have the answer?
- Hmm...
Because he's a man.
- We really have to stop
doing that.
- To be fair,
it's not entirely his fault.
- That's, like,
the nicest thing
you've ever said about him.
- I mean, he's Dean.
He's Deansie.
He's never gonna not be Dean.
- He is what he is.
- He's Dean.
♪
- I don't know
anything about cars.
- I mean, I didn't know
anything about
robbing a grocery store either.
[upbeat music]
♪
[woman singing in French]
[singing continues]
♪
- ♪ Oui
♪ Oh, oui, oh
♪
♪ Oui
- What?
- I'm just surprised.
- What, I can't take you
to dinner?
- Are you kidding me?
Yes, of course you can
take me out to dinner.
This is--it's amazing.
- Dean.
- [clears throat]
Beth...
- I think the dealership
could be great again.
- Yeah, me too.
- No, I mean, really great.
- Yeah, sure, me too.
- I have a few ideas.
- Can I get you something
to drink?
- Uh, we will take a look
at a wine list.
- Perfect.
- So, I was thinking today--
- Hold on a second.
Excuse me, real quick.
What's your special tonight?
- Fresh mussels cooked
in a white wine broth,
served alongside grilled bread.
- Ooh.
- Mmm.
- Be right back with that list.
- Thank you.
- So, I know you love
the sports car stuff...
- Mm-hmm.
- And that is fun and great,
but I think that we're ignoring
51% of the population.
- Special sounds good, right?
Yeah?
- If we start catering
more towards women,
I think we could really
increase our sales.
We wouldn't have to reinvent
the wheel or anything,
I mean, we could have
child care
for when women are shopping.
- Huh.
- Could have a car seat guy
come and do installs
on the lot.
- Oh, look, they have
the barbecued short ribs.
I don't think they had that
the last time we were--
- Dean.
- I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Okay. Cater to women.
- What do you think?
- I think that you
were awesome this week.
You killed it.
- Yeah?
- I mean, you moved more cars
than our top guy, so...
- Really?
- Yes, it was incredible.
It was amazing.
And the thing is,
I would never tell you
how to raise the kids, right?
Like, you--so, you make those
sandwiches,
those cute, little sandwiches
with the face
and the little olives, right?
For eyes, and I think
that you use a cookie cutter.
[echoing] And I would never,
like, in a million years
think about using a cookie
cutter for a sandwich.
I think "cookie cutter"
and I just think "cookies."
We are a great team.
- Why's that?
- Because we both have our own,
you know, superpower.
Why would you wanna wreck that?
Oh, hey, you wanna do, like,
a bottle of chard?
- Bourbon on the rocks.
- Next.
- Ruby Hill, account number
four-six-eight-two-nine.
- All right.
It looks like you got
a partial payment due of...
What's that?
- My principal, my interest,
my service fees,
my dignity, my happiness,
and my soul.
You, sir, have a nice day.
- I'll see you next month.
- Oh, I won't be coming back.
- Everyone comes back.
- Everyone except me.
- Whatever.
- Get a good look, homie,
'cause you will
never see this face again.
- Okay. But I will.
- But you won't.
- I think I will.
- I know you won't.
- Excuse me, are you finished?
[upbeat music]
- How much?
- I'm sorry?
- How much do you need?
- Um, 200
for my son's prescription.
- Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
- Hey, no, you can't do that.
- Watch me.
Welcome to the bank of Ruby.
Let me see what you got.
I feel like this
should cover it.
Happy Chanukah.
- Hey, stop it.
- How 'bout you?
- No hablo Inglés.
- Feliz Navidad.
- [gasps]
Gracias.
- De nada.
I could do this all day!
- No, you not gonna do it
all day.
You better get up out of here!
- Oh--did you want me to leave?
- I don't ever wanna see you
back in here.
- Deal.
♪
- Okay, so,
you're on auto-pay now.
So they will just deduct
all your monthly expenses,
you know, your cable
and your rent--
- What about my permanents?
- Well, I will make sure
that there's padding
for a monthly salon visit--
- I go weekly with Gladis
and the girls.
- Weekly it is.
Okay, here you go.
And I will pick you up
bright and early.
- What for now?
- For the eye doc.
- Do I have to?
- Gotta get those cataracts
checked.
- I really don't want
that surgery.
- Girl, it's happening.
- He was stealing from me,
wasn't he?
- I'll see you tomorrow, Mer.
- [smacking]
[moaning]
So good.
So you wanna--
you wanna go home?
- No.
[upbeat music playing
over stereo]
♪
[woman singing]
[alternative rock music
blasting over stereo]
- How'd you find this place?
♪
- A friend.
- It is, like, super dope.
♪
I'm gonna get one more.
Hi, can I just grab
a--another...
Hi, excuse me.
Hi, can I get, um...
♪
Excuse me, miss?
Just need a...
Service lacks
a little professionalism.
Hi, can I grab another...
- I'll be right back.
- Oh, okay.
♪
[bass reverberating]
- You can't see a thing
in here.
[suspenseful music]
♪
[woman singing]
- Mind if I stop
at the drugstore?
- Not at all.
♪
- I'll just run in.
- Sure.
♪
[moans]
- Need anything?
- Just detergent
and toothpaste.
.
- You know, it's no fun
drinking alone.
Nah, I'm lying, it kinda is.
- Babe, I thought
we were saving that.
- Oh, you want
a special occasion?
All right, well, how 'bout...
your boy here
is getting his job back
as mall security.
- You hate that gig.
- Mm-hmm.
And I'm gonna be hating it
part-time nights and weekends.
- There's no way in hell.
- No, no, no, don't kill
the vibe, woman.
Drink.
- You're never gonna be
a mall cop again.
- What is this?
Wait, you paid
the whole thing off?
- Sure did.
- With what money?
- I'll tell you later.
- You rob a store?
- I'll tell you tomorrow.
- What did you do for it?
- Don't kill the vibe. Drink.
- [sighs]
- Look, you think
you love my eyebrows,
but that's just because
your wife
plucked hers to death and now
she doesn't have any left.
So, to you, they're, like,
this hot, exotic fantasy.
But Greg, one day,
you're gonna wake up
and you're gonna look at me,
and they're not gonna be
this hot, exotic fantasy.
They're just gonna be eyebrows.
Like, you won't even see 'em
on my face anymore.
- Um...you still wanna go
get tacos?
[melancholy music]
- We've been here before.
You know, we know
how this ends.
- How does it end?
- Total carnage.
- Probably.
- Like "Scarface" level
carnage.
- Which is still
the best movie ever.
♪
- ♪ I want you more
than I need you ♪
♪ I need you so bad
- I can't.
- ♪ Are you coming back?
♪ I'm waiting
- Okay.
- I'm sorry.
- Me too.
♪
[shouting]
- Guys, I swear to God,
you have to change
your underwear before school,
okay?
[doorbell dings]
It's super gross.
Hi.
- Bad time?
- [crying]
- Yeah--I mean, always,
but come on in.
- [wailing]
- Do you want some coffee
or something?
- So, I've been thinking
about what you said...
- You know what?
Never mind.
I think I don't have any, so...
- I'm fine.
- Okay.
- W--what--what did I say?
- About Leslie seeming nervous
right before he went missing.
- Oh, yeah, I said that.
Yeah--yep.
Um...
- You got a lot going on.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I'm hungry.
- Okay, can--can you give me
just a second, okay?
Thank you.
- So, Leslie...
- Right, yeah.
Yeah, he seemed really, like,
um, you know, freaked out.
Like he--like, thought someone
was out to get him
or something.
- Was it this guy?
- Um...
- Can we have popsicles?
- I don't know.
- Mom.
- Honey, I can't, I'm busy.
Can you go look yourself,
please?
- So, have you seen this guy
with Leslie?
- Uh, who--who is he?
- Well, he's someone
we've had our eye on.
- Oh, you think maybe
he has something to--
- I don't know where they are.
- Honey, they're probably
in the freezer.
- No, they're not.
- I'm sorry, I need to go.
- You took 'em out when
you put Daddy in there.
So where are they?
[upbeat music]
♪
[woman singing
in foreign language]
♪
- The money's gone.
He took it back.
- Why?
- He flipped his game.
[horn blares]
- Yo, so, I'm sitting here,
right?
I'm trying to figure out
who would buy a neon 'Vette
with ostrich interior,
and I think I finally
figured it out.
Nobody.
- What are you doing?
- You didn't tell him yet?
- Tell me what?
- ♪ Easy
- You didn't tell him, huh?
- No.
- Oh, come on, Ma,
it's too good.
- Tell me what, Beth?
♪
- Don't.
- ♪ Easy
♪
- We're partners now.
- What is he talking about?
♪
- I'm gonna provide
the capital,
and you're gonna wash it
with these cheesy-ass buckets.
- That wasn't the deal.
- Oh, what you need, a memo?
All right, here you go,
new deal.
Now I take 30%, cool?
- [scoffs]
You can go to hell.
- All right.
Okay.
♪
- No, no, no, no, no.
- No, no, no, don't!
- Don't!
Jesus.
- 40%.
- I'm calling the cops.
- You can't, Dean, you can't.
- Son of a bitch!
- [screams]
- 50?
- Stop it!
♪
- Take it up with HR, yeah?
- Who is HR?
- Me.
[laughs]
- No, no, no, no, no, no!
- [screams]
- No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no!
- You can have whatever
you want, just stop!
♪
- Sixty percent?
- Fine.
♪
- Now, let's go make
some money.
[dramatic music]
♪
- ♪ Easy
♪ Easy
♪