.
- Previously on
"Good Girls"...
- So what do think?
You got what it takes?
- Do it, Beth.
Just shoot him.
- I just want it to be over.
[screams]
- When's Dean-sy coming home?
- Made all your favorites.
- What happened
to the stop sign?
- The things you did...
Hand me those.
- Really?
- Wanna act
like nothing's wrong?
- I'm gonna leave Nancy.
- I have a secret.
Nancy's pregs.
- I'm going to take
these women down.
- Yes.
I'm his key witness.
- I can't go away for this.
What are you doing?
- Well, a husband can't testify
against his wife.
- Turns out
we got a mutual friend.
He's talking to the Feds now.
I'm going to need you
to take care of him.
- That's insane.
What is it?
- What is it, Beth?
[Spanish music]
♪
- You had to bring it?
- I wasn't going
to leave it at home.
- All right.
Let me see it. Come on.
- Careful.
- [whistles]
- Really?
- Put it down.
- All right.
How's Tuesday?
- Sara has
a doctor's appointment.
Well, Wednesday I have Sadie.
Thursday?
- I guess Thursday works.
- Wanna whip out your iCal or--
- No!
- You know, I'm just trying
to be proactive here, okay?
Good news is,
we have the means.
Now we just have
to find someone to do it.
- I say we look
on the dark web.
One "The First 48"
they always hire,
like, a gym trainer
or something.
- How do we get on that?
- I don't know.
That's why it's called
the dark web.
It's not meant for us.
- Am I the only one
who doesn't want to do this?
- No.
- He's a rapist.
- He's a person.
- Who rapes.
- God, I can't have
this conversation.
I'm gonna be sick.
[bell jingles]
Welcome to Dandy Donuts,
I'll be right with you.
- It's 2 A.M.
Who needs a frickin' donut?
- Why did he ask us to do it,
anyway?
- To torture me.
- Maybe if we wait
he'll get ants in his pants
and he'll do it himself.
- Yeah. Yeah, and then
he'll do the hokey pokey
and he'll turn himself around
and then you know
what he's gonna do?
Us.
- You know what this is?
A gang initiation.
- Son of a bitch.
- Blood in, blood out.
- It's a thing.
Trust me.
- Excuse me?
Can I order?
♪
- So then the doctor writes
the gender on a little slip
of paper and you bring that
slip of paper to a bakery
and they make a cake
that has either blue or pink--
- Wow, hey.
Sadie! Chop chop.
- I mean, obviously, who cares.
You just want a healthy baby,
blah, blah, blah.
Did you do it naturally?
- Uh, well, I pooped her out
in the bathroom at prom, so...
Is she coming down or...
- [stutters]
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Oh, uh,
did you get my message?
- About what?
- Uh, Sadie wants
to quit piano.
- Mm.
Well, I actually
think that's a good idea.
- Well, I actually think
that she should stick it out.
- Well, not if it's not
the right thing to do anymore.
- You don't quit something just
because it starts to get hard.
- Yeah, you can.
Because sometimes it's just
the end of the road, Greg.
Yeah,
and you got to deal with it.
- How about if she finds
another instrument?
- Yes, Nance gets it.
- Can you please tell her
that she has to come?
- Oh, no, no, no.
Uh, if...
- Um, yeah.
You should... Come.
- Good sell.
You really should.
You're the only other person
on the planet who has been
here, you know?
- Where's that?
- Pregs with Gregs.
[uncomfortable laughter]
- Sadie, please!
- So, how is Sara doing?
- Oh, she is way, way, better.
- Oh, goodness, so much better.
- And what about you guys?
- Is that a new Jesus?
- Oh, yeah, yeah. You like him?
- Yeah, word,
he's got the whole...
- So, how are you doing?
- God has put you two
through quite a bit.
- Um...
Well, you know the truth is
we've been having
a rough go of it lately.
- It's my fault.
I broke a vow.
- More than one.
- You were unfaithful?
- I wouldn't say that.
- Why not? I mean,
you lied, you snuck around,
you climbed in the bed with
a whole bunch of shady people.
- Okay.
- Did things I would never do.
- All right.
- This was betrayal, for sure.
- And infidelity is one
of the biggest tests
a marriage will face.
- It's like I can feel
the distance and it's on me
but...
I don't know how to fix it.
- What do you think about
what Ruby just said?
- I mean, listen, you know...
I love her, she's the
mother of my children,
she's my best friend--
- Ah, say it to her.
- [sighs]
- - You're my best friend.
You're my road dog,
and honestly when I look at you
right now,
I don't know who I married.
- Is it over?
- Is what over?
- The affair.
- Yeah, it's over.
- God is good and he forgives,
and in time Stan will, too.
[indistinct chatter]
- Friend's giving his
deposition in the morning.
- What the hell?
He's not my friend.
- So, how are you
going to do it?
- I don't know.
- Well maybe you should
figure that out, huh?
- I can't just murder someone.
I'm not a psychopath.
- Not easy being the boss, huh?
- I need to pick
up my kids now.
- Oh, yeah. You gotta hustle
if you wanna make it
to Scouts, huh?
- Do it tonight.
[dramatic music]
♪
- Did you see that shot?
That guy is incredible.
- Can we watch "Minions" now?
- It's the playoffs, my man.
Mm-mm.
Oh, come on! Oh, my God.
Right there.
- I want "Minions."
- Now if I'm going to be
your Daddy, Son,
you gotta learn to listen.
- Listen to your Daddy, okay?
- All right,
it's your lucky day.
- Yay!
- I gotta run for a bit, okay?
- Okay.
- [whispers] Turner.
Turner?
- Jimmy?
Jimbo?
- Get on your knees.
- [chuckles]
Oh, what is this?
"The Craft?"
What are you going
to cast a spell on me?
- Just get on your knees,
Boomer.
- So you can shoot me
with a squirt gun?
[gun cocks]
- Whoa.
Okay, hey.
- Just do it.
- What's going on?
- Don't let him talk.
Just do it.
- No, please.
No, no, no, no, no. Hang on.
- Beth, pull the trigger.
- Hang on.
- Shoot him now.
- No, please.
- Beth, trust me.
Don't let him talk to you.
Just shoot him.
- Come on. No, come on, please.
- Oh, God. Oh, God.
[sobbing]
Please.
Oh, God.
- You are not going to give
that deposition.
- What are you doing? Because
she's going to kill you! Beth!
- You are ratting out a gang.
You think they're going
to let you talk?
- Wait,
who is going to kill me?
You guys or the gang?
- We are!
Beth, do it! Come on!
What are you doing?
Give me the gun,
give me the gun.
- Annie.
- Ruby.
- Make her give me
the gun right now.
- I can't, I don't know what--I
can't help you.
- Jesus, Ruby, come on.
- Beth, pull the trigger.
- So I'm gonna go now.
- How much?
Come on,
everyone's got a number.
But you got to disappear
for good.
- $20,000.
- Oh, my God. Beth, come on.
- Deal.
- Sweet Jesus.
Well that's twice now.
.
- No, it's a stop sign.
It's not damaged, it's missing,
and we live on a street with,
like, a million kids,
so you know somebody, somebody
is going to get killed.
Where's the refrigerator?
- The medical bills
alone are...
Not to mention the mortgage.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- Because you just
got out of surgery.
- I can do something.
- What are you going to do?
What are you
going to mow lawns?
You can hardly even walk.
And that's on me.
So just let me figure it out,
okay?
- Is that it?
- I put the dishwasher
on Craigslist
and I've got a lead
on the patio furniture.
- That's not
what I'm talking about.
It's about him, isn't it?
- No.
- Have you talked to him?
- Have you seen him?
- No!
I'm just trying
to keep us above water.
♪
- ♪ It's gonna take
a bit of work ♪
♪ Oh-ho, work
♪
♪ Now that you're here
♪ Whoa-ho, work
♪
[vocalizing]
- [sighs]
I feel dirtier
than a truck stop ho.
- And those late fees,
they're worse than an STD.
- That's it?
- Are you for real?
- Literally the only thing left
of value
that I have are my eggs.
- Okay, lets sell those.
- Takes a full menstrual cycle,
but thanks.
- Well, we're short.
- How much exactly?
- $16,927.
- Well, gotta go.
- Seriously?
- Yeah, I got a party.
- Hey. I would have shot him.
- I'm not sure I have the right
address here.
I'm looking for
Leslie Peterson.
- He's my fiancé.
- Is he home?
- No.
- Will you tell him
Jimmy stopped by?
With the FBI.
- He's right here.
- Yeah, I've been a little
under the weather.
- Dude.
- You ever hear of IBS?
It's a chronic thing.
It flares up.
- We had a deal.
We're building a case, Leslie.
Look, I just need
a couple of days.
I swear. And then
I'll be back to regular.
- Did they get to you?
- Who?
- Come on, man.
- Oh, no, come on.
No one got to me.
- If somebody's trying to shake
you down I need to know.
- It's just a condition.
- So I'll get with the DA then?
- Yeah.
Let's do this.
- Thank you everyone
for coming out tonight.
I am so excited.
Okay, so, how many people
think blue?
- Okay.
How many people think pink?
- How many don't give
a rat's ass?
- Let's find out, okay?
- Yeah.
- Let's go. [exhales]
Take a deep breath, okay.
Three, two, one.
Oh, my gosh
I'm so nervous. I can't wait.
Is it ready?
- Ah-huh.
- It's a...
wait, what is it?
- I think it's kind of pink.
- No, it's nothing.
It's nothing, it's marble.
- Okay, uh...
- Great. Well, party ruined.
- No, no, no, it's not. What
do you want me to do?
I'll do anything.
- I wanna know the sex
of the baby, Greg.
- No, I--right.
- Yowza.
- What'd you get her?
- Oh, a bottle of wine.
You?
- The Moo Mama,
you know that pram?
- Damn, aren't those like a G?
- Oh, no,
I got her the good one.
- ♪ Head up, eyes woke,
Nothing you could do ♪
♪ To correct my flow,
My feet don't get broke ♪
♪ I'mma keep it moving till
the day I go ♪
♪ Hey, nobody said
it would be easy ♪
♪ And I don't need it
like that ♪
♪ Hey, nobody said
it would be easy ♪
♪ And I don't even want it
like that ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, bounce back ♪
- What are you doing?
- Looking for my phone.
- In someone else's purse?
- If you must know.
- Sorry.
- Just trying to keep
the mystery alive.
- [chuckles]
That ship has sailed.
- Really?
Like when?
- Oh, I could tell you
exactly when.
- When?
- It was when you Dutch Oven'd
me in high school.
- [chuckles]
You loved it.
[laughing together]
- Did you call?
- Yeah, um, it's a boy.
- Wow!
- Yeah.
- You excited?
But look,
this doesn't change anything
about how I feel about us.
- It changes everything.
So, I'm gonna, um...I'm gonna
put this inside me now.
- Yeah, just in there.
- Okay, got your 17 grand
and then some.
- The hell is that?
- It's a frick'n Tesla, dawg.
[car beeps]
Took it.
- You stole a car?
- Oh, I didn't steal anything.
- I'm not stealing
someone else's car.
- Yeah, you're not shooting
anybody either, are you?
- I made a decision
in the moment.
- Well you made it for all
of us and guess what?
It was the wrong one.
- Take the keys.
- [scoffs] Okay. I'm sorry,
if you have another way
of getting, like, 20 grand
by tomorrow then please,
go with god.
- Take the keys, Beth.
- Next time, I hold the gun.
.
- Hey, where--where
is the beer?
- In the cooler
in the basement.
- Well, that'll only take
me an hour.
- Where can I sell a car
for parts?
- We're not selling our car.
- It's not our car.
- Whose is it?
- It doesn't matter.
- Well, I'd like to know.
- I don't know.
- What is this, "Fast and the
Furious?" It is, isn't it?
- I don't have a lot of time.
- What does he think he's
Vin Diesel all of a sudden?
I'm not an idiot.
- You're just going to have
to trust me, okay?
- Trust you? I have a bullet
lodged a half inch
from my spine because you
can't stop seeing this guy.
Oh,
but I'm supposed to trust you.
I'm supposed to trust that you
have a great idea what to do
with everyone--
- Let me help you.
- I got it, thank you!
I said I've got it!
You should talk to Dominic
in Service.
He's been around.
- Okay.
- What kind of car is it?
- A Tesla.
- You can't sell
a Tesla for parts.
- Why not?
It's like a giant iPad.
Next time, go for the Honda.
♪
- ♪ Soon as I woke up I knew
something was different ♪
♪ My intuition says
I'm on my way to winning ♪
♪ Guess I've been playing all
my cards right, yeah ♪
♪ Oh, baby, baby
Oh, baby, baby ♪
- What do you want?
- Oh.
Tequila?
- Top shelf on the left.
- Did you not...
want a boy or...?
- It's a boy?
- Whoops.
- Oh, my God,
this is so messed up.
[sobbing]
- Hey, do you want me to go
grab one of your friends, or...
- They're not my friends.
They're just bitches
I follow on Instagram.
- Well I'll--
I'll get Greg then, okay?
- I don't think
he wants a baby.
- What?
- He's been really weird.
Like he's not there.
You know, like, he's like,
there but he's not, like,
there, there, you know?
- What was he like
when you were pregnant?
- I mean--freaked out.
- Yeah.
- For sure.
But you know, we also had
finals and teenage onset acne.
- [laughs]
- So.
- What if there
is something really wrong?
- You know,
I think you should just...
Just talk to him.
- Yeah, because maybe,
you know, it's just nerves.
- Yeah.
It's probably that.
- Okay.
Can you...
Can you stay for just a minute?
- Sure.
- [deep breathing]
You guys buy a lot of quinoa.
- It's a really good
source of protein.
[sobbing]
- I gotta ask you something.
- Okay.
- Is Stan good with you, now?
- I mean, in what--
- With the cheating and lying,
all of it.
Are you ever going to look at
him the same way you used to?
- It's different.
- That's not an answer.
- When Dean cheated and lied,
he did it for Dean.
You did it for your family.
And besides, I don't know that
I've ever looked at Dean
the way you look at Stan.
- Damn.
- Yeah.
- Sorry 'bout the wait, ladies.
- Whoa.
- Is there a problem?
- I mean, we'll take it.
- Hell yeah, we'll take it.
- So this isn't your car.
- It is now.
- Wait, what--
what car do you drive?
- A Tesla, baby.
- We're about to hit the club.
[laughing together]
- Come on,
I'm really slammed here.
- Fine, the Honda.
- Civic or Accord?
- Accord.
- Black or silver?
- Black.
- It's only half.
- You'll get the other half
when we know
you've left the country.
- Whoa, no.
That was not the deal.
- The deal was we kill you.
Want to go back to that?
- How will I get it?
- We'll mail it.
- You'll need my address.
- Yeah, it's kind of
how mail works.
- I'm not going to compromise
my location.
- We'll Venmo you.
- Oh, and have the IRS
up my ass?
- Fine. PayPal.
- It's the same problem.
- P.O. box.
- Yeah, that works.
- Done.
- Great.
- I'll leave first thing
in the morning.
- Hey.
I meant what I said.
If it's not us it will be them.
- I'll drop you a postcard.
- I got an early shift,
so you're on car pool.
- Couches are for cheaters,
Stanley.
Did you cheat?
- Nope.
- Neither did I.
- What do you want here?
- I want you to
come back to bed.
- Well I can't ask like this
didn't happen.
- So maybe we can just
give it back then.
- [sighs] What are you
talking about?
- The kidney.
Maybe we can return it.
- Yeah, okay.
That's just crazy talk now.
- What's crazy is that you
can't even look at me.
- You know what?
You lied to my face.
- I saved her life.
It wasn't God or the church
or any of those
thoughts and prayers.
It was me.
You say you don't know
who I am.
Well let me introduce myself.
I'm the crazy ass bitch
that robbed a grocery store
to save her child
and protect her family.
Your child and your family.
I'm that bitch.
Nice to meet you.
And you're welcome.
.
- Nana! [knocking]
Nana, it's me.
Open up.
[knocking]
- Leslie, what time is it?
- Oh, it's late, Nana.
I'm sorry.
- I fell asleep during "Wheel."
Why don't you come back
tomorrow?
- Uh, no, we gotta do this now,
okay?
- What's that?
- Oh. It's a phone, Nana.
- I already have a phone.
- Well, but,
you can't call long distance.
- I don't call anyone
out of town.
- Well you might need to,
and this way you can.
It's unlimited. Oh, and,
uh, here, check this out.
- Huh? See, now we can see
each other any time we want.
- But you're right around
the corner.
- Yeah, but what if I wasn't.
- But you are.
- But what if I wasn't!
- Is everything all right,
Leslie?
- Yeah.
- Are you in any
sort of trouble?
- No.
- Mildred's grandkids
got her one of these.
- I think it was so
they didn't have to visit.
- Oh, yeah?
Did she use it?
- For about a week.
Then she died.
I can't waste my time
learning a whole new gadget.
How about milk
and cookie, huh?
That be good?
- Yeah, sure.
[percussion rhythm]
♪
- Hello?
How about a little customer
service here, huh, guys?
[all exclaiming]
- What's going on, Janet?
Ron, Gary?
- Hey, welcome back, man.
What are you doing here, Mr. B?
- Last time I checked we had
some cars to sell, am I right?
Look guys, I just want to say,
um, it's real nice to be back.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, oh yeah, I'm great.
What is it the kids do?
- Oh!
- Hey, what is that Vette
still doing here.
- Oh, that?
Deal fell through.
Somebody's wife.
- Well.
By the end of the day
that bad boy is mine.
You mark my words.
It is on, gentlemen.
- All right guys, let's--let's
get out there and just have a--
let's have an awesome day, huh?
- Let's do it.
- Right.
- Good to see you, man.
- Okay.
- Hey, mom, watch.
- You're doing great.
- Kid's got a lot going on.
- We like to keep him busy.
- Oh yeah?
That's what he like?
- He's 11.
- Yeah, but if he doesn't
want to do something
he ain't going
to be any good at it.
- You're parenting my kid now?
- Nah.
No, I'm just saying
not everybody
could be good at everything.
- So that's it?
So how'd you do it?
- You want details?
- Oh, please.
- I googled the cleanest way
to kill somebody.
There's a part of the brain
called the light switch
in the back of your head.
I had tarps and coveralls
from painting Emma's nursery.
- Hey, mom, watch me!
- Hey, I'm watching!
We made him turn around
and put him on his knees.
He cried like a baby.
Then we turned out his lights.
- And what did you do
with the body?
- Put it in
a duffel with bricks.
We rented a boat and took it
out as far as we could.
- And you cleaned the boat?
- Of course.
- Wow, so you must have not had
much sleep then, huh?
- Well, I'm a mother of four
so I'm used to it.
- Right.
That's a hell of a story.
- Thank you.
- Yeah,
I just wish it was true.
You see,
you can't shoot someone
if you don't use any bullets.
[chuckles]
- Hey mom!
I'm gonna dive.
- Oh, you should watch.
This will be good.
- It's 455 horse power.
0 to 60 in four flat.
- Damn, that's lit.
- Oh, man.
It is lit.
- Hey, you okay?
You look a little hot there.
- Yeah, standing next to this
baby, anybody looks hot.
And look at that,
rolling on twenty-twos.
- Yeah, uh, you got a little--
- Only car in the world that
compares to this one,
in my opinion, is the Ferrari.
And it's what--it's five times
as expe--as expensive,
and it's not made in America,
so...
- Yeah, you know, you've got
some blood right there.
- You know what?
We sh--we should just go in...
- Yeah, I'm gonna--you know,
I'm gonna come back.
- I can't...
I can't--I can't promise that
this is still gonna be here.
- I really think you need
to see a doctor.
Can we get a little help?
We need a little help here!
- Hey,
what's with the pity party?
- Oh, she's picking out
her wedding cake.
- Hold up,
she's getting married?
- Yeah, people say that
Mr. Peterson knocked her up,
but, uh,
I think it's true love.
- Have a Fine and Frugal day.
- Um. I--I can get that.
- Wow. Big news.
Congrats.
- Can I try the lemon next?
- So, how did he propose?
Poem? Song? Rape?
- I don't have a choice, okay?
He's talking to the FBI.
- Look,
he's not talking to anybody.
He is long gone by now.
- What?
- He's probably in Canada
because it's, like,
the only other country
he's ever heard of.
- He's not in Canada.
- Okay, maybe Mexico but--
- He just booked our reception
hall an hour ago.
- And he paid in cash, right?
- He's invited
my entire church.
.
♪
[tires squealing]
[both gasping]
- I've been calling and calling
about that sign.
- I know.
- No one's ever
going to fix it.
- Hey, Carl?
Remember when you needed
time off for your kid's play?
And I made you work overtime.
And then I didn't pay overtime.
Instead, I docked you.
Because someone left
the meat locker open?
Well...
That someone was me.
But I couldn't tell you because
I knew you would be pissed.
How pissed are you, Carl?
[knife clatters]
There were like,
three or four of them.
I mean, they just--
they came out of nowhere, man.
- This won't happen again.
If I got to deliver you to
the court house myself I will.
- Appreciate it.
- You have my word.
All right?
- Let's get somebody in here
to clean you up?
- Give me the gun.
- I don't have it.
- What do you mean
you don't have it?
- I gave it back.
- Why would you do that?
- I have children.
I don't want a gun
in the house.
- Then I'll just use Stan's.
- He's a cop, Annie.
[tense music]
- Let's just go to a Walmart
and I will literally
just buy one, like,
over the counter or whatever.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah, really.
- You gonna wait the seven days
for the permit?
- Dammit. I'm gonna kill him!
Stupid, whiny, little...face.
Little...
Ah! I'm gonna kill him,
I'm gonna kill him
in his entire face.
[tires squeal]
You okay?
- ♪ The dark horse rides
♪
- Beth?
[Beth shouting]
- I don't even understand
what's happening.
[knocking]
- Hey.
- I talked to him.
- And?
- He said there's someone else.
- Okay, just start pulling
the anchor up.
- Copy. Hauling anchor.
- Actually, Conrad,
just take over the anchor,
and Joao you can come
into the bridge.
- Copy that.
- Something I need to know.
- Okay.
Is Captain Sandy still
giving Conrad a hard time?
- She's jamming him up good.
- Now see, that woman needs
to calm her ass down.
- She let Joao
dock the yacht.
- What? That's Conrad's job.
- I know. I know.
- That's just plain mean.
[sighs]
You turn it up a little bit,
please?
- You need your hearing
checked.
- What's that now?
[sighs]
[indistinct chatter on TV]
- You know, I bet it was one
of those Pharma sluts
that he works with.
Their short skirts.
You know, they're always
trying to land doctors.
- Greg's not a doctor.
- Yeah, he sells boner pills.
Something bad
was bound to happen.
- It's really not your fault.
- I just feel so stupid.
- Do you want
the honest to god truth?
The second you see
that little kid's face
nothing else matters.
- I heard you split so wide
you could park
a food truck in there?
- Oh, it looks like a sleeping
bag with the zipper torn off.
- [feigns dry heave]
- 100%.
- Ugh. [laughing]
- And do not get me started
on your nipples, my friend.
[knocking]
- Mine look like
sausages already.
Is that normal?
- Now just picture that you put
them in a food dehydrator for,
like, seven weeks and then you
feed them to your dog and--
- They were out of cinnamon,
so...
[guitar music]
♪
[drill running]
♪ If only
♪ My body
♪ Could allow
♪ The whiskey
♪ If only
♪ My body could allow
♪ The misery
- I can't do this anymore.
- What's that?
- The lying.
I lie to my family.
To my friends.
To the FBI.
To you.
I can't even
keep it straight...
And I can't hide.
Not from you.
And I can't kill somebody
either, so.
I'm just so tired.
I don't think I've gotten
a full night's sleep
in over two months. Knowing
you is like having a newborn.
Are you going to kill me?
- I'm gonna teach you.
♪ Oh, shake baby, shake,
shake off the leaves ♪
♪ Shake baby shake,
Shake off the leaves ♪
♪ Shake baby, shake
♪ Mm-mm-mm-mm, ah
♪ Shake baby, shake,
Shake off the leaves ♪