You like Rice Krispies treats?
Suit yourselves.
Sorry about the dog.
Believe it or not,
it used to be a lot worse.
What's his name?
Nothing's really stuck yet.
You have a dog?
I used to. His name was Bubba.
- Bubba?
- Bubba.
Oh.
So, Miss Durst--
Nora.
Nora, you do the questionnaire thing
for the government, right?
Uh-huh.
So you, like, ask stuff
to find out what they had in common,
everybody who poofed?
That's the idea.
So do people, like, freak out?
What do you mean?
Well, I just mean,
if I lost somebody
and had to answer personal questions
to get a benefit check,
I'd probably go mental.
No offense.
I've never seen anybody go mental.
They're sad, but they're safe.
Then why do you carry a gun?
- What?
- She has a gun in her purse.
Right?
What makes you think she has--?
Actually, Jill, I used to have a gun,
but I don't need it anymore.
- Why'd you need it before?
- Jill.
It made me feel better.
- Then why'd you get rid of it?
- Jill.
- What?
- Enough.
- Sorry.
- It's okay.
I just want to know
how she got better.
Hey! Nora's a guest in our house.
- I'm asking our guest a question.
- Then cut the shit, Jill.
Go ahead. Take a look.
- Nora, you don't have--
- It's okay, really.
Go ahead.
- Apologize.
- She doesn't have to.
She does have to.
- Sorry.
- No worries.
I think she really likes me.
She said, she was
looking forward to it. I swear.
Now that I've been inspected
for fire arms, the worst is over.
Don't go back in and fight with her.
That's what she wants.
I mean, sorry.
She started it, and--
That's very mature of you.
It'll get better.
How?
I don't know, but it will.
Jesus! You are taking a nap?
Come on.
She's still out.
THE LEFTOVERS
Morning.
Is my dad downstairs?
Nope.
I guess you must have scared him off
to her place.
Bang, bang.
You don't fucking know me!
You motherfucker!
- Fuck you!
- Megan.
Fuck you, you fuck!
You fucking fuck!
You! How fucking dare you?
You don't know me!
You're everywhere! Leave us alone!
- Megan.
- Fuck you!
Megan. Come home.
- Megan!
- Shut your fucking mouth, you fuck!
- Come home, Megan.
- Fuck you!
Come home. Megan!
Fuck. Do you know what he's doing?
Do you know?
This is about me!
This is my fucking mother!
My mother!
He's been talking to her friends!
He has one of everyone on all of us!
He can't do that!
He can't just fucking come here
and do that!
You can't let him!
Fine. Fine.
Let's see what Patti says.
I think she's playing possum.
You are playing possum, gorgeous?
Well, maybe you hit her
a little too hard, huh?
What the hell's wrong with you?
- What happened last night?
- What?
I need you to tell me everything
that happened last night.
Why?
I don't think I remember.
You don't think you remember?
This was all your idea, asshole.
What do you remember?
I remember getting into bed.
Oh, come on.
What, are you saying....?
What,
that you're fucking sleepwalking?
Just tell me.
Well, Kevin....
Apparently you got out of bed
and showed up at the bar.
And we had a couple,
and you insisted
on giving me a lift home.
At which point,
we passed our lady friend in there.
When she looked up,
she gave you that
"go fuck yourself" smile.
Next thing I know,
you were out, grabbing her.
Nothing like a spontaneous abduction
to get the heart fucking pumping,
and, boom,
we are off to Cairo, New York.
We're in Cairo?
Well, you gave me directions!
You said that you--
You used to come to camp up here
when you were little.
You snuck off to the cabin
to smoke cigarettes.
Why? Why would you do this with me?
Because we're friends.
Before last night,
when was the last time
we saw each other?
I don't know.
Couple weeks back, you know.
When we made the bet.
Oh, Jesus.
We caught a dog and
you bet that you could civilize him.
You win,
I stop shooting the fuckers.
I win, you give me a dollar.
Yeah, I will collect that dollar,
so don't try using
this amnesia bullshit to back out.
No, I don't have fucking amnesia.
Well, then what the fuck
have you got?
Shit.
Oh, fuck. Jesus.
You're okay?
I think things got
a little out of control last night.
- Jesus, Chief. What the hell--?
- Shut the fuck up.
I shouldn't have done this to you.
But you kept
fucking pushing me, Patti,
and I reacted.
So I'm gonna let you go,
and we're gonna get in the truck
and I'm gonna drive you home.
And all the bullshit up until now,
we're gonna call it even.
- We're gonna forget that it--
- Shut up!
I don't forget.
Well, well.
It speaks.
Gosh, you're so friendly now.
Tell me...
Am I still a fat,
heartless cunt?
That's what he said, right?
That is my recollection, yes.
Well, Kevin, that is a kind offer.
Take me home, give a polite
little beep as you drive off.
But you should know
that I have every intention
of reporting you
to the actual authorities.
I will tell them that I was abducted
off the street,
and I will identify my attackers.
And they will take your job,
and then they will take your child.
You want to undo this,
but I simply cannot allow that.
So, you're just gonna
have to batten down the hatches
and finish what you started here,
my friend.
Now get me a fucking cigarette!
However, when allied tanks
arrived on the outskirts of Daafeed,
the mass grave was empty.
The officers described a....
How long do I have to wait here?
Why are you so mad?
What was I supposed to do?
I mean, if we don't stand up to him,
then he's just gonna keep on
coming at us.
Why not?
They fucking hit us,
they spit in our faces,
they spray us with hoses.
Of course.
Please.
This is my sister, Nora,
my wife, Mary.
This is Laurie and Megan.
- She's the one who attacked you?
- It's okay.
Megan's mother passed away
on October 13th,
one day before the Departure.
She has a right to be angry.
Her grief was hijacked.
I accept your apology.
She's not sorry.
She's here. It's a start.
I'm not giving up on you.
Thank you for coming by.
Hey, Laurie.
If you're giving out apologies,
I have a suggestion
for your next stop.
I had dinner
with your daughter last night.
You might wanna drop by
and write her a note, too.
So, Garvey's totally
just staring her down,
and she's all like, "You're there
sitting in my mom's chair,
eating my dad's delicious chicken?
Uh-uh"
It wasn't my mom's chair.
Okay, and Nora,
who I know on a first-name basis,
by the way,
she's all like, "Go ahead.
I don't give a shit.
Look in my purse."
And I'm like, damn, is she bluffing?
Because obviously
Garvey's supposed to just be like,
"Oh, sorry, no, forget it."
But no, fuck that.
Garvey grabs her purse,
looks in that shit, and....
No gun!
- I don't get it.
- Why does it matter?
Because she's lying.
It wasn't in her purse,
but she still has it.
- How do you know?
- Because I know.
What's that got to do with the gun?
Absolutely nothing.
Garvey is cock-blocking her dad.
- She was pretending.
- Pretending what?
To be okay.
She lost her entire family.
Just so you know,
it is possible for some people
to be okay, Jill.
Are you okay, Aimee?
- Okay.
- I am fucking fantastic.
And I got to say,
I think your dad would be, too,
if you'd just fucking let him.
Guys, let's just calm down.
Come on.
Did you fuck him?
- Whoa, hey.
- What?
- Let's play ping-pong, okay?
- Yeah. Right?
Did you?
Did you fuck my dad?
Yeah, Jill.
I did.
I fucked your dad.
And I felt really bad about it.
So I was like,
"Hey, Mr. Garvey, this is so wrong."
But he was like, "Hey.
Let's stop pretending to be okay
because no one is okay."
And he was totally right.
And he was so hard, Jill.
So I fucked the shit out of him
on top of a pile of guns.
- Fuck you.
- Fuck you!
Other pocket.
If I cut you loose,
you gonna behave?
Jesus.
Chief, she just spit in your face.
You want her to bite
your goddamn nose off, too?
Certainly a risk.
- You want one? Help yourself.
- I don't smoke.
I seem to recall
Laurie telling me that you did.
I quit.
Who do you report to?
- Sorry?
- Your organization.
Your fucking cult.
- Where do you get your orders?
- We don't take orders.
Bullshit.
People have fucking chapters
all over the country.
Okay, I'm sorry,
but you brought me here
and strapped me up,
so you could ask me
about my organization?
Just answer the fucking question.
And who might you be, sir?
This ain't working out, Chief.
Reason I ask is because I've had
some experience in research.
And most people,
you can find out things about them
with no trouble at all.
But you, dog killer.
No driver's license, no records,
no anything.
So I don't know.
You may be able to shed some light
about your friend here?
But as far as I can tell,
he's a ghost.
I prefer to think of myself
as a guardian angel.
Well, shit.
I think I just heard a bell ring.
Word with you outside, Chief?
Something tells me you're about
to get some excellent advice.
- What the fuck are you doing?
- What?
I signed up
for this little adventure
under the countenance of strong
and decisive leadership.
But now, lo and behold,
that leader is now gone.
And the man currently residing
in his skin
clearly has no fucking idea
what is happening in there.
When we did this last night...
...what did I say I wanted?
You said it was time to end it.
I don't wanna hurt her.
Oh, yes, you do.
After what she took from your town?
From your family?
There have to be consequences.
Look. Chief, I get it.
You tried every way you could
to stop these fucks,
but you could only get so far
because you are a good man.
So how about you go back
to the truck
and get comfortable,
close your eyes?
Because I need to talk
to the other guy.
There's only fucking me!
- Dude, this is a bad idea.
- Up.
- Right.
- I mean it, you guys.
- I don't think we should do this.
- My right. Nope. Your right.
- Sorry.
- Got it.
All right, stop.
Click it, Garvey.
- I got it.
- Right.
- What the hell, man?
- We're looking for a gun.
Nobody keeps the gun
in the crisper, dude.
- That's where I would hide it.
- What if she comes home?
Then she'll go right for the gun.
Boom. Mystery solved.
That is the dumbest thing
I have ever heard in my life.
- Oh, my God.
- Shut up, Scott.
I still don't get it.
If the lady who lost her family
is, like, lying about the gun,
then, like, no one
can ever be okay again.
Do you think Aimee
was really fucking Garvey's dad?
Probably. Dude is ripped.
- Oh, shit.
- What?
Bulletproof vest, yo.
Jackpot.
- Hit me, bitch!
- No way.
Do it, chicken shit!
- Motherfucker!
- Let's get out of here.
- Why? What about the gun?
- Doesn't matter.
Dude, vest. Go.
Wait up!
Hello, you've reached Nora Durst.
Please leave a message.
Nora, it's me, Kevin.
Um, I only have one bar,
so I hope you can hear me.
I did something stupid.
Think I fucked up.
I don't know
what's happening to me.
So can you call me
when you get the message?
And that's just, I...
I need you.
No. No.
Fucking no!
Fuck!
Fuck! Fuck!
Fuck.
You're okay.
Did you take your nap?
Fuck this. We're leaving.
- Her word against ours.
- No.
Whoa there, Chief. Just hold on.
Just give it a minute, okay?
- What?
- Situation is taking care of itself.
- What did you do?
- What? Hey, hey! Goddamn it!
Jesus.
Don't fight it, Chief.
Just give it a minute.
Just let her go. It's what you want.
Just let her go, man.
Just let her go.
Fuck!
I fucking wanted to help you.
Now you are on your own, Chief.
Oh, shut the fuck up. I tried.
- You okay?
- Shh.
What, you want me to write it down?
I'm just asking if you're all right.
Can you believe Nora fucking Durst?
She just had to say something,
right?
You know what? Fuck her.
What does she know about
your daughter?
She doesn't know fucking shit.
I wish I could see her face
on Memorial Day.
Shh!
Patti sent you?
You got something for me?
We're good?
Okay. Unhitch it.
You people are some sick fucks.
Nora, it's me, Kevin.
Disarm system now.
System deactivated.
Where are you going?
Dorfman said I could crash there
for a while.
Cool.
I hope you feel better.
I'm fine.
Thanks for letting me stay.
Go.
Can I stay here?
Boy, are you fucked.
Tell me.
You're wondering
if I have a sense of debt to you
for saving my life?
Maybe I'll change my mind
about decimating yours.
- But you won't?
- No, I won't.
Oh, it's a pickle.
Can't let me go, won't let me die.
Oh, what to do, Kevin?
What to fucking do?
What do you want?
I want you to understand.
Understand what?
You ever think about the 14th,
14th of October?
The Great Vanishing?
The Sudden Departure?
The clusterfuck of the modern era?
When's the last time
you ever really thought about it?
- I don't.
- Me?
I think about it
every fucking waking moment.
I mean, come on.
What else is there to think about?
So you know where they went,
what happened?
It doesn't matter what happened.
But the difference
between you and me...
...is that I accept that it did.
And while you push it aside,
while you ignore it,
we strip ourselves of everything
that distracts us from it.
We strip away the colorful diversions
that keep us from remembering.
We strip away attachment,
fear, and love,
and hatred and anger...
...until we are...
...erased.
Until we are a blank slate.
We're living reminders
of what you try
so desperately to forget.
And we are ready,
and we are waiting
because it's not gonna be long now.
Now I know why
you don't fucking talk.
Got to hand it to you, Patti.
That is such an impressive line
of fucking bullshit.
Well, Laurie obviously
disagrees with you.
Laurie didn't join you
to become a living fucking reminder.
Then why did she?
Because I failed her.
Oh.
You think she came to us
because of you.
Because of what you did
with your dirty dick.
Yes, Kevin, there was a time
I told Laurie everything.
And then there was a time
she told me everything.
But she came to me because
I could offer her something...
...that you could not.
Purpose.
That's all any of us want now,
every single one of us.
Not answers, not love.
Just a reason to exist.
Something to live for.
Something to die for.
Did Gladys have a purpose?
Ah, you remember her name.
Of course I remember
her fucking name.
Well, Kevin, that was the point.
That woman was brutally murdered,
death by 100 stones.
And now, she can't be forgotten.
Did you murder her?
She was okay with it.
And when Laurie's time comes,
she will be okay with it, too.
And it's coming, so soon.
And you are all ready.
All you need is just a little push.
You want me to kill you.
Kevin, you can't kill me.
You don't have the fucking balls.
I want you to commit.
I want you to finish
what you started.
I want you to go all the way.
I want you to say you understand.
Understand what?
What happened, what's happening?
To me.
To you.
Oh, vanity of sleep,
hope, dream, endless desire,
the horses of disaster
plunge through the heavy clay.
Beloved, let your eyes half close
and your heart beat over my heart.
And your hair fall over my breast,
drowning love's lonely hour
in deep twilight of rest.
And hiding their tossing manes
and tumultuous feet.
Kevin.
Kevin Garvey.
You don't have to hide from me.
You're going home.
You're not gonna tell anybody
what I did to you.
Because I'll fucking tell them.
If I lose my fucking job...
...so fucking be it.
But I am not gonna lose my mind
listening to the words
coming out of your fucking mouth.
No, Patti.
No.
I don't understand you.
Kevin.
You do understand.
Oh, Jesus! Oh, God!
Oh, God!
What the fuck did you do?
You...
...understand.