This is the story of a little boy.
I'd say stop me
if you've heard this one before,
but you have,
and I don't really wanna be stopped.
This boy, he's a good kid,
not perfect, but good,
and when he's about ten years old,
his mom and dad tell him
he's gonna have a baby sister.
And the baby sister comes and,
of course, he loves her very much.
But... she's getting attention.
His attention.
So he wishes--
Actually,
he prays for that attention back.
A month later, he's diagnosed
with acute lymphatic leukemia.
And the cancer eats away at the boy
until there is almost nothing left.
But he fights it.
He survives,
and now he has a choice to make.
Does he decide that he was punished,
or that he was rewarded?
Will he be angry
for having been made to suffer
or will he be grateful
for that suffering
because it changed him?
This is the story of a little girl.
She's eight years old
and just over a week ago,
she's playing in the park.
She loves to go high on the swings,
up to the point where you hang there
for a moment, suspended,
before the chains clink
and gravity pulls you back down.
She's been asleep.
In a coma, for nine days now.
Her brain activity is negligible.
Her outcome is undetermined.
The girl's name is Emily.
And so, that little boy
is asking for attention again now.
For Emily, let us pray.
Heavenly Father,
You invite all who are burdened
to come to You.
Allow Your healing hand
to touch this girl.
Fill her heart with Your courage
and infinite love
for all that You create.
Please.
Stop. Please.
It's probably not a concussion.
Doctor will wanna take a look at you
before you can go.
- Thanks.
- Mm-hm.
"Mrs. Amber Johnson,
a local pharmacist trainee,
secretly stole
significant quantities of Percocet,
oxycodone and Vicodin
and sold it
to community college students."
I know what it says.
- Amber here, she poofed?
- She was a Departure, yes.
So you think our assailant
knew Amber?
Maybe didn't appreciate
your little newsletter.
I got this one, Lou.
Chief, I was taking a statement.
- There's no need for you--
- You wanna press charges, Matt?
- No.
- There you go.
Father.
Here we are again.
Occupational hazard.
What are you gonna do?
Stop pissing people off.
They need to hear the truth.
Your dad understood that.
Look where that got him.
You know, me and Jill
are living
in the old man's place now.
Come over tonight,
I'll grill up some steaks.
Do a Sunday dinner, like old times.
Nights are tough for me.
Sorry.
See you next time, Chief.
I guess you and me
are going to the same place.
You need help?
Emily.
The girl who was in here,
do you know what happened?
She woke up, asked for a Sprite.
- She's okay?
- I guess so.
You know her?
No, I visited with her,
but my congregation....
This morning, we prayed for her.
Well, she woke up last night.
Hello, you've reached the
administrative offices of Our Savior.
Please leave a message
at the sound of the tone.
Matt, hi.
It's Jim Lewis from FDR.
You're a hard man to reach.
I'd really love to talk to you
in person
preferably as soon as possible.
I'm here at the bank all day.
Talk soon. Bye.
Hey, hi, um, are you open?
Sure. Come in.
I don't know if you remember me.
I used to come all the time.
Craig, right? McNary?
Yeah.
Sorry, I haven't been in a while.
My wife, ever since the 14th,
she's not really into, you know....
Anyway,
she's over getting a manicure
and I told her
to get her feet done, too,
you know,
just to take some time for herself.
I'll take the baby, come back
to pick her up later, so....
How long does it take to do a,
you know, baptism?
We have that confidentiality thing,
right?
I'll try to keep my mouth shut.
I don't know what the appropriate
contribution is, but--
- Please. It's on the house.
- You sure?
How about you ask your wife
to join you and your son
for services this Sunday?
We'll call it even.
I don't think that's gonna happen.
Had to try.
If I don't, who will?
This guy I worked with...
...he used to get loaded
and drive out to the Indian Casino
in Connecticut.
He'd gamble away his paycheck
every other Thursday.
And when that was gone,
I heard he cleaned out
his kids' college account.
He went on the 14th.
What was his name?
Andrew Sasaki.
We don't discuss personal information
about our clientele.
Sure, of course not.
This man, Mr. Sasaki,
he was a Departure,
and the reason
I'm asking about him is....
I'm sorry, I know this is personal,
but did you lose anyone
close to you, sir?
My niece, she was nine.
May I show you something?
This...
...is Albert Wayne Studdard.
He abducted a young girl
walking home from school,
violated her sexually,
strangled her to death.
On October 14th, he disappeared
right out of his jail cell.
And this man, this monster,
is on the same list,
along with all the others
who left us,
along with the innocent and good.
Along with your niece.
Someone has to expose these people
for who they truly were
and what they truly did.
Because if we can no longer separate
the innocent from the guilty,
everything that happened to us,
all of our suffering, is meaningless.
I think I know what happened
to your face.
Can you help me?
We don't keep the security cam data
past six months.
But I'll see what I can do.
Jesus fucking Christ!
Come on!
What about the bet?
Get out of here. Get out of here!
I have to deal with this.
Get down to Pit Four.
There's fucking birds on the table.
I'm sorry, I don't have any in white.
I know you have a job to do,
but please tell Patti
she's wasting your time
sending you here.
I've made it this far.
I'm not gonna turn around now.
What the hell?
- What?
- Hello, Matt?
Hey, Jim, is that you?
I'm sorry.
My phone's been acting up.
- How are you?
- Good. I'm good.
Matt, I'm sure you're busy,
but can you come by the bank?
- Sure.
- It's important.
Yeah, I'll come right over.
Thank you.
There's been an offer on the church.
But I don't understand.
You said I could stay.
Matt, I said you could stay
as long as no buyers came forward.
I'm sorry, Matt.
I've been trying to tell you
for at least two weeks now.
And you always knew
this could happen
once you stopped making payments
and we had to foreclose.
Who's the buyer?
Corporate LLC,
probably a hedge fund.
They can't really remodel,
but the land is worth something.
They probably wanna knock it down
and throw up some apartments.
Knock it--
Well, it's not some restaurant.
This is a house of worsh--
I'm sorry, I have to take this.
Hey. Can I call you back?
I'm in the middle of a--
We're out of bleach.
What? Which kind?
Yeah. Okay.
I'll grab some on the way home.
- Bye.
How is Mary?
Tell me how I can keep my church.
With no other offers on the table,
we have to accept theirs.
But now if you can come in,
all cash,
even $1 above their price,
I can get your name
back on the deed.
What was their price?
One hundred and thirty five thousand.
How much time do I have?
Tomorrow. End of day.
- Hey, you.
- Hey.
- Bar fight?
- Am I interrupting anything?
No, I was just watching TV.
Come on in.
Doug won't mind. I promise.
Is Mary okay?
She's great.
And what?
I need to borrow $135,000.
- What?
- They're gonna sell the church.
I'm sorry.
I know it's a lot of money,
but it'd just be a loan.
Things are changing.
People are ready to come back.
I just performed a baptism
this morning.
I hate coming to you,
but this is our family church.
- Mom and Dad's.
- No, Matt, it's your church.
They left it to both of us.
They didn't leave it to anyone.
They died in a fire when I was seven
and then it was given--
Please, don't get upset.
- Why do you always have to do that?
- What?
Make me upset
and then tell me not to get upset.
You can't just knock on my door
and asked for $135,000--
Do you not have it?
I thought the benefit money.
That money was for my husband
and my children.
I'm sorry.
You're right.
I shouldn't have asked.
I just didn't know where to go.
- Will you stop making your paper?
- What?
You're asking me for something,
I'm asking you for something.
Stop making your paper
and I'll give you the money.
- I can't do that.
- Why not?
People need to hear the truth.
People need to punch you in the face.
I didn't say it was easy to hear.
Then deliver the "truth"
in your church.
That's what you're asking me for.
Right? Your church?
- That's not what this is about.
- No!
It's about the accident.
It's about the judge.
And it should have ended there!
But you kept going.
You dug up your dirt.
And people called you crazy
behind your back,
and I defended you
because I knew you were in pain.
But you decided it was your calling,
your purpose.
Like, you were personally
selected by God--
Don't say that word.
You don't get to talk
about something you don't believe.
I don't get to?
What do you believe in, Matt?
Do you know where my family went?
Do you know what it was?
It was a test.
Not for what came before,
but for what came after.
It was a test for what comes now.
Well, if it was a test,
then I think you may be failing it.
I love you, Matt.
But what you're doing:
your paper, the church,
it's not working anymore.
It's not making things better.
Maybe it's time to let it go.
Hm.
Doug was having an affair.
The kid's preschool teacher.
They usually did it
at her apartment.
But a couple of times...
...he brought her to The Plaza,
in the city.
He was smart enough
to use cash, but...
...I have the receipts from the ATM
in their lobby.
It's the one story
I will never publish.
Because I love you, too.
Get out.
They're gone,
but so much of them is still here.
You've tried to move on,
tried to live a normal life,
but you haven't let go
because you haven't known how.
Loved Ones bereavement figures
allow you to say that good-bye.
With as little
as a single photograph,
Loved Ones can create a tangible
likeness of your Departed.
A bereavement figure
for burial or cremation
allowing you and your family
to finally--
- Hey.
- ...begin to feel hope again.
Visit a Loved Ones associate today
- or visit us online to receive....
- Uh...
This is the only kind they have.
But bleach is bleach, right?
It's fine.
Is everything okay?
When are you gonna pay me again,
Mr. Matthew?
Oh...
Right. I'm sorry about that.
I'd write you a check,
but I've been moving money
between accounts and--
Three weeks I work here for nothing.
I know, I know. Here take this.
And I'll give you the rest
when I can.
Great, thanks.
If you can't pay me,
I can't do this anymore.
You understand, yes?
Yeah, I understand.
She needs her bath.
Hello, sweetheart.
Help me.
Thanks so much for doing this,
Roxana.
I never would've called
if it wasn't an emergency.
- Nights are overtime.
- Right, of course. Thank you.
Mary's asleep upstairs.
I just didn't want to leave her
here on her own.
How long will you be?
Three, maybe four hours,
morning at the latest.
And when I get back,
I'm gonna pay you
everything I owe you.
All of it, tonight included.
I'll come through this time.
I swear.
Uh, Kevin's dad,
your father-in-law,
he left something here.
For me.
He said I could get it
whenever I wanted.
I won't say anything, if you won't.
- Hello.
- How would you like it, sir?
- In chips.
What denomination?
Well, does it matter?
Twenty thousand. Good luck.
- Would you like to bet?
- Yes, on red.
Right there, sir.
High-limit tables are in the back.
If you'll allow me to escort you--
No, I wanna play on this table.
Please.
Twenty thousand on red.
No more bets?
Winner. Red.
Forty thousand.
- Oh, shit. We got a player here.
- Again, please.
Uh...
Forty thousand on red.
No more bets?
- Winner. Red.
- That was insane.
Congratulations.
Eighty thousand.
- Once more, please.
- Jesus, man.
Hey, you know something
that we don't know?
What the fuck are you doing, Tina?
You're gonna jinx the guy.
That's a fucking jinx.
- No, you bet with him.
- No, no, no, black is due. Sorry.
What do you mean?
Eighty thousand on red. Good luck.
No more bets?
One hundred and sixty thousand.
Congratulations, sir.
Ahh.
Hey, winner, winner,
chicken dinner, right?
Yeah.
- Congrats, man.
- Thanks.
You were on fire!
I've never seen balls like that.
I was trying to get my girl
not to bet against you,
but she fucking ignored me, right?
- I have to--
- Listen, here's the thing though.
We dropped our last hundred.
And we got to be in Niagara Falls
in the morning,
and that's at least
two tanks of gas.
I was just wondering
maybe you could help us out.
You know.
Unless you're short on cash.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
Here's two. Gas is expensive.
You know what, man?
Why don't you hang on to that
and I'll just take that envelope?
No.
Get in the fucking car!
My God.
Please, stop! My God!
Stop, please. Please stop!
My God. My God.
Are you okay, huh?
What did they throw?
Yes, there's been an attack.
A man was hit with a rock.
He's bleeding.
We're on Cedar Lane and...
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
- Am I too late?
- Of course not. All are welcome.
I'm sorry, Matthew,
but it's spreading.
- Are they burning in there?
- Yes, Nora, they are.
Why isn't anybody doing anything?
Sam. Sam, where are you?
Help me.
- We need some help.
- Sam!
Sam! Sam!
Honey? Can you hear me?
Help! Please, I need help!
Honey?
Help me! My wife is hurt!
Please help!
Why do you persist?
Why isn't anybody
doing anything?
- Hey, you shouldn't be up.
- What time is it?
You need to sit down.
- 16:30.
Please, I need you to call the bank.
FDR, the one on Beekman,
ask to speak to Jim Lewis,
tell him not to close.
Tell him Matt Jamison
is coming over right now.
- Wait a minute. I don't know.
- Just call him!
- No, no, someone called.
- Sorry, we're closed. We're closed.
I need to see Jim Lewis.
- We open tomorrow at 8:00.
- Wait. He's expecting me.
Hey, step back!
- Hey. Hey.
- Jim, Jim, it's Matt!
It's okay, Frank. Let him in.
Jesus, Matt! What happened?
I was.... I'm fine. I'm fine.
Here it is, all of it in cash.
What?
I'm sorry, Matt. It's too late.
No. No.
You said end of day.
It's only ten minutes.
I have the money, we made a deal.
That was three days ago.
What?
You came in on Monday.
This is Thursday.
Now, I tried calling you
on your cell phone, but--
I'm--
I'm sorry, Matt.
No one here wanted them to have it
but they paid all cash, no escrow.
They...
They took possession yesterday.
They?