Hi, I'm Chuck. Here are a few things
that you might need to know.
Let's dance.
- Hello, Chuck.
- Decker froze Bale's accounts.
Castle and the Buy More aren't frozen.
- All of our money? We have nothing?
- Payback's a bitch.
The Buy More.
We take Buy More's profits...
...put them into Carmichael Industries
until both companies can make money.
My name is Charles Carmichael,
and I have one final question for you:
Have you ever needed to subdue
a Basque terrorist on a Swiss train?
Or fight your way
through the jungles of Southeast Asia?
Or take out an arms dealer...
...with a penchant for murder
and ice cream?
Well, we have.
So while considering security needs,
when lives are on the line...
...I implore you to consider us.
It's not that one.
It's not that... Carmichael Industries.
Thank you.
- You did good.
Mm-hm.
That was good.
All right,
we have one more team presenting.
Uh, they should be here, uh, any minute.
What's happening?
Wait, this is not a real attack, is it?
No, this is our competition.
Three hundred agents
from all over the world.
CIA, KGB, Mossad and Interpol.
We work for the Pentagon,
we work for the Kremlin...
...and we'll work for you.
My name is Gertrude Verbanski,
and we are Verbanski Corp.
And if we can get to you,
we can get to anyone.
Verbanski.
Yeah, Verbanski.
Sorry, kind of got carried away there.
I thought... This is not a bit that?
Right. Uh... Go ahead.
Who is she?
One of the KGB's most ruthless spies
till the fall of the Soviet Union.
Then she went
into the private-security game.
And how do you know her?
Minsk, 1995.
I was being a patriot.
She was being
whatever she was paid to be.
Wow, 1995.
I was still in middle school.
Anyway, we had an altercation.
I ended up with a Rosewell blade
in my shoulder.
Made a nasty scar
right over one of my favorite scars.
Well, Verbanski is good. She took
all of our potential clients today.
Awesome ditched rock climbing
to help me.
He is gonna be so disappointed.
It didn't go well?
Did you give eye contact
to all four quadrants of the audience?
It was great,
all of your advice was great.
Of course it was. Same tactics I used
to woo your hot sister, heh.
Okay. Um...
Look, we were just a little outmatched
is all.
Well, at least
you still have the Buy More, bro.
Still cash flow coming in there.
Right?
- What? Is that an actual tumbleweed?
- Yeah.
We put in a home-and-garden section
to drum up business.
I'm glad someone
put out the tumbleweed.
- Oh, boy.
- Anyway, how was the presentation?
Not good. No, not good.
Verbanski Corp took all of our clients.
Put me out there, you don't worry
about what other companies are doing.
Look, I know I seem
like just an ordinary guy...
...but I am, in fact, the Intersect.
Multibillion-dollar CIA asset
turned super-weapon-for-hire.
Buddy, no one can know that we
have the walking CIA database...
...on our team, okay?
The Intersect is a secret weapon
for a reason.
That sucks, man.
I have all these powers and abilities.
And how am I to help people
if I can't tell anybody about it?
Because, Morgan, if you do,
it could get you killed.
- What?
- Oh, I just zoomed. I just zoomed.
- There's a bad guy in the Buy More.
- Are you sure?
Know what we gotta do?
We gotta take him down.
Take a breath.
We gotta be subtle about this.
He's going for a weapon.
He's coming.
- I'm in. I'm in.
- Morgan. Ah...!
Not good.
You just found out that the zoom
is mightier than the sword, my friend.
Hey, hey, hey. You okay?
Man, I feel incredible.
Did you see that?
You like that,
"the zoom is mightier than the sword?"
Oh. Casey,
we have a bit of a situation here.
Listen. I just got a call...
...and someone wants to hire
Carmichael Industries.
He's coming to the Buy More
to meet with us now.
We actually just met, heh.
Mr. Sneijder? Mister...
We are so sorry.
Please, take a muffin.
What's happening?
Welcome to Carmichael Industries.
Uh, I must apologize for your unnecessarily
rough welcome, Mr. Sneijder.
Or, uh, shall I call you Karl?
- You want a muffin or not?
- He made them fresh this morning.
Um, I just have one, uh, little question
for you.
Is there a reason why our, uh...
...partner...
...thought that you were, I don't know,
a criminal?
I do work in the diamond industry
in South Africa. We're not known...
...for keeping our hands clean.
- Hmm.
I don't eat bran. Nobody does.
I told you.
Listen, I've come to ask for your help
on something entirely legitimate.
We're listening.
My little brother, Wesley,
was kidnapped...
...by a buyer I may have wronged
in the past.
I don't know where he's being held,
but I do know he's being tortured.
My little brother, he never wanted
to have anything to do with my affairs.
He's a good man.
- And they will kill him unless...
- We save him.
Exactly.
Why should we believe
these people actually took your brother?
They sent me this.
We gonna draw straws
to see who opens that thing?
- Oh.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
That's not even on ice. I...
That's probably not gonna be able
to be reattached.
I know it's not a lot of money...
...but I'm willing
to offer you $200,000 upfront...
...and another 200,000
when you deliver my brother to me.
And I know you don't wanna help me,
but please consider helping my brother.
No one else will.
If you don't mind, we'll take some time
to consider your offer and check facts.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Oh, I...
Is your friend with the beard
going to be a problem?
- No. No.
No.
What Morgan did today in the Buy More
could've really blown our cover.
The first months with the Intersect
are a big adjustment.
It's scary and exciting.
Your hormones are totally out of whack.
You're really rediscovering your body.
- It's a lot to take in, all I'm saying.
- That's exactly why he needs a handler.
What? Who, me?
You had Casey and me, Chuck, okay?
Morgan needs you.
- Hey, buddy.
- Hey, Chuck. Good.
Listen, I wanted to, uh... say sorry
about what happened with Sneijder.
No, hey, buddy, you know,
look, I totally get it.
It took me a while to be out there
with the Intersect too, so...
It's like, uh, Peter Parker,
Amazing Spider-Man.
The thing is, it took him a while
to kind of really harness in his powers...
...to really get ahold
of his Spidey sense.
- Right.
- So...
Yeah, heh.
Uh, which, interestingly enough...
...brings me to something
I wanted to talk to you about.
Um, I was wondering what you thought
about me maybe being your handler?
I could show you the ropes
just like Sarah and Casey did for me.
- Yeah.
- Great. Yeah.
And on missions, you know,
you can still show off your...
...zooms.
But for now, we gotta keep the Intersect
under wraps and focus on the store.
Aloha, Chuck. Hello, stepchild.
- Hey.
- Like my new threads?
I just got back from four weeks
of sexual experimentation...
...and snorkeling
with my new wife in Hawaii.
So, what you boys been up to?
The Buy More seems empty.
Are we observing
International Pancake Day?
No, no, no. Um...
Business has just, you know,
been a little slow.
That's not gonna work for me.
I need this job.
Bolonia Grimes Tucker
is not a cheap tigress, boys.
I think we're on the same page,
Big Mike.
Not having to do
with your mother being a tigress.
I wouldn't know anything about that.
But we need something new, we need
something big to save the Buy More.
Hmm.
I may actually have just the thing.
Say, Miss Lady, you need any help?
Yeah, Pops, I do.
Do you have Betamax?
Sure enough. We even sell VCRs...
...depending, of course,
on what you're into.
- And it's on sale, only 2 grand.
- Oh!
That's a far-out deal, mister.
But come on now,
you only buying that?
Why don't you...
...Buy More?
Damn, I was skinny.
Boogie fever
So I figure we just re-air this spot.
Brought in a lot of business at the time,
if you know what I mean.
No offense, Big Mike,
but it feels a little dated.
Maybe we should come up...
...with something that showcases
some of our more current merchandise.
Maybe what we're looking for
is a fresh face...
...uh, to kind of tell people
that the Buy More, um...
...has something new to offer.
- Hmm, yeah.
- Right?
I hear you.
Everybody wants something new.
The finger is a positive match, Casey.
It definitely belongs to Wesley Sneijder.
Yeah, got it.
You were right on the location too.
Got eyeballs on Wesley.
He's being held
in a guarded compound.
Well, let's just see
how well protected you are.
What the hell
do you think you're doing?
Hey, hey, I'm just hunting waterfowl,
that's all. What are you doing?
- You're on private property, man.
- Oh, well, my bad, then.
Uh, sorry, I didn't realize.
No harm, no fowl.
Get it? Okay, have a nice day.
At least 12 guards
with weapons pointed at the entrance.
- We are not going in the front door.
- There has to be another way in.
If there is, I'll find it.
Oh, I get it, he meant waterfowl.
Hello?
Ah. Please forgive me.
It's our busy season.
- Hi.
Oh, yes, not many people
have disarmed Colonel Casey...
...but I like to remember all my victories,
even little ones.
Have a seat.
Uh, you mind telling me what I'm here for?
You said you had some information.
Verbanski Corp has a job opening.
- And?
- And put simply, I want you.
Private security isn't a game
you just try your hand at.
I have agents in 38 countries...
...under 15 separate Pentagon contracts
worth over 2 billion annually.
Well, that's very impressive.
And what does
Carmichael Industries have...
...other than a former colonel
and a CEO with skinny arms?
What am I really doing here?
We both know I'm not gonna
leave my husband's company.
Are you trying to recruit John Casey?
Is that his name
on that second folder?
Let me be frank.
I'm talking to you
because you're good...
...but your company isn't going to last,
Miss Walker.
You should switch while you can.
First of all, it's missus,
and second of all, I'm disappointed.
I thought this was gonna be...
...a friendly cooperation
between business associates.
But if it's competition that you want,
then I suggest you watch your back.
Oh, by the way,
when this whole thing ends...
...don't expect me to mount anything
of yours in my office. It's just tacky.
Casey said he wanted something light.
He said that, but he doesn't mean it.
Is this the best use of our time?
We could be doing so much more.
Zim-zam-zoom, chop-socky.
- Morgan.
- I... I know.
I'm talking a lot about the Intersect,
but, you know, I finally get it, though.
For the first time,
I sort of feel as cool as you.
I can't figure out
why I can't use what I have...
...to make this dusty little rock
that we all have to share...
...well, just a bit better for all of us.
- It's a pretty good speech...
- Give me all your money. Get it now.
- Morgan. Morgan, look.
- Hurry up.
- Please. I'm getting it.
- My God.
- I know.
- This is it, what I've been waiting for.
What? What? What do you mean
what you've been waiting for?
A chance for
the Bearded Bandit to come out and play.
What are you talking about?
This isn't a game.
I know, but I can do this,
I can save the day.
Do you even know
what "bandit" means?
It's like "robber" or "crook."
No, I Googled it. It's a fighter aircraft.
What? I don't...
What did you say?
I Googled it.
It's slang also for "fighter aircraft,"
so there's that.
This is not a good idea, Morgan.
Wish me luck.
Morgan, Morgan.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
Are you a cop?
Heh, not even close, sweetheart.
I'm the Bearded Bandit.
Oh, no. Uh...
Take whatever you want.
Just don't hurt me.
No, no.
It's a slang term for fighter... For... Uh...
- Morgan.
- Nice save, Chuck.
That's what I'm talking about.
We could do this. Be superheroes.
I'm the worst handler in the world.
Holy crap, Chuck.
Move, move, the fuzz, fuzz, fuzz.
Explain.
- I know, uh, I know, it's just...
- Chuck, we are a legitimate company...
...not a bunch of vigilantes
fighting crime at the Circle K.
I know that, I know.
But his heart is in the right place.
That should matter for something.
Morgan is your responsibility.
He could have gotten killed
and the clerk yesterday.
That is what matters.
Hmm.
We found the compound
where Wesley's kept.
We've already alerted Karl.
There's just one thing left
we need to handle.
Morgan.
You're sticking me in the van?
Chuck, come on, dude,
I am the Intersect, man.
Okay, all right, okay, look.
You don't wanna pitch me to potential
clients, that's up to you, okay?
But you gotta use me on the missions.
- Morgan, it's not that simple.
- But it is that simple.
How is it not? You're my friend.
Buddy, we got lucky at the Circle K.
Very, very lucky.
What you did was dangerous...
...and letting you do that was my fault,
I'm your handler, not just your friend.
I need to protect you.
Buy More commercial, take 28.
- Rolling, and quiet.
- It's one line.
Can't you even deliver one line?
Why not...
...Buy More?
Remind me of one of them troll dolls.
- And action.
- Why not Buy More?
Wow!
Man, I am so over
this whole Jeffster thing.
- Me too.
- Cut.
Just stop. My commercial was a hit
because I was a hot piece of meat...
...a thing women and men wanted...
...which, at the time,
was a lot less common.
The store's on the line here.
None of you have a face
that'll bring in customers.
Sookie, sookie.
Mike, you guys got any baby pads
around here?
Yeah, uh, Aisle 3.
Okay, heh.
That's a pretty man.
Casey did some recon and the
house is impregnable from the front road.
Yeah, and this cliff is impossible
to free-climb.
Told you, sounds like a job
for the old...
A job for real spies.
There, why don't you wait in the van?
Don't worry, buddy,
you'll be with us on the next one.
Right.
Unbelievable.
- Ready?
- Absolutely.
"Wait in the van, Morgan."
"Yeah, wait in the van."
"Oh, in the van, moron.
Hmm. Grunt, grunt, grunt."
We're on a private line.
I didn't wanna...
...worry Chuck, but I had a meeting
with Verbanski yesterday.
What did she want?
Ugh, apparently she wanted to recruit me,
but I think she was really after you.
What do you mean?
Well, she has your gun...
...on display in her office.
The gun from Minsk?
She kept my gun?
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Casey?
- Casey, I'm slipping.
- Casey.
Looking good, babe.
Doing good up there.
Doing good. There you go.
Jeez, what's up
with you and Verbanski anyway?
Don't worry, Walker. I got your back.
Still climbing. Holy cow.
- All clear.
- All clear. Yeah. About time.
Okay, Chuck, this is all you.
- Who are you people?
- We're here to save you.
- What are you talking about?
- Relax. Your brother hired us.
He did what?
What are you doing?
We're here to protect you.
The only thing
keeping my brother from killing me...
...are the men I hired
to guard this compound.
What?
- But your finger.
- Who do you think cut it off?
I'm trying to testify against him.
This is a giant misunderstanding.
We're not here to hurt you.
- Yeah, my men will be here any second.
- Morgan, get the van ready.
Morgan, do you copy?
Morgan?
Get back.
Kamikaze!
I'm gonna punch you in the face.
What's up, team?
You guys need some help?
- Yes and no.
- Okay. That's...
Just zoomed. Wesley's brother's
not trying to save him.
- He's trying to...
- We know.
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
If the Intersect wasn't stifled, we
would've known that ahead of time...
...and I wouldn't have had
to take out Wesley's guards.
- Really sorry about that, dude.
- It's, you know...
- Hey, Karl.
- Sat images show...
...that you took care of the guards
at the compound. Nice work.
I have a team coming up the access road
to pick up my brother.
Do you? That's great.
That's great news.
We'll be right here waiting for them.
Bye now.
Karl's men are gonna be here
any minute.
- Yes.
- Well, then I'm a dead man.
No. We came here to save you
and that's what we're gonna do.
What? No, no, no.
The Intersect runs from no man.
For now, he does. Let's go, Morgan.
- We had a deal.
- Exactly.
You hired us to save your brother.
No, I paid you to extract him
and bring him to me.
We didn't know you were planning
on killing him.
Nor did we know you were responsible
for the finger-cutting. That's crazy.
Listen, you have exactly four hours
to deliver Wesley to me.
Otherwise, I'm coming after you...
...and that is something
you will not enjoy.
And that comment card you sent
with the contract?
Well, you can consider...
- What are we gonna do?
- Got a fingerless guy in the game room...
...and his psychopath brother
threatening to come after us.
So we go to the source.
We take out Karl before he gets to us.
With what army?
We don't work for the government.
If we can get to Beckman,
she can help put Wesley into custody.
No, there's no time for that.
We have to act now.
We're not going into a firefight
unprepared. End of story.
I feel like a burrito.
Go on a food run, huh?
- A food run?
- Yeah.
- Again, I am the Intersect.
- Then act like it.
Okay, okay.
Why don't I just go with you, buddy?
And we can get a little breather while
we wait to hear back from Beckman.
Don't forget the utensils.
Thank you.
Must have had
one too many piña coladas...
...and my blood pressure
is generally outrageous.
I'm just glad I was here
for your dizzy spell.
Devon, ever given any thought to doing
something that involves less doctoring...
...and more making a commercial
for the Buy More?
- What?
- The Buy More needs a fresh face.
I'm about to go on paternity leave
to spend more time with my family.
Sure, I did some modeling for
Abercrombie & Fitch back in college...
...but, heh, I hung up those cargo pants
a long time ago.
Hold on. I'm not talking
about doing some teenage porno.
Look. This is your brother-in-law's
place of business, and it's empty.
But your creamy skin...
...and unusually high cheekbones
can change all that.
And if you are taking time off
to help your family...
...isn't Chuck your family too?
I can't believe Casey sent us out
for burritos.
Burritos, Chuck? I'm tired of running
errands for that man's stomach.
Look, Casey means well.
Yeah, but it's not just Casey, dude,
okay? It's Sarah too.
What is that supposed to mean?
Isn't she the one who told you
to be my handler in the first place?
- Yeah...
- Did it occur to you...
...that she made you my babysitter...
...to distract you from the fact
you're being sidelined?
I don't know if you noticed, chief.
You're on a food run with me.
Look, I'm not...
Look, I love Sarah, I do, okay?
It's just I wanna make sure
that she's not the one handling you.
She's not.
- You just passed the exit for Dos Locos.
- We're not going to Dos Locos.
We're going to Karl Sneijder's
corporate headquarters.
Oh, yeah. Zoomed on a file in Castle.
Oh, did you?
And why didn't you tell anyone?
Why would I, okay?
We're gonna take him down.
No. No, no, Bearded Bandit.
No, we are not. It is far too dangerous.
I'm gonna call Casey and Sarah.
They can help.
They can what?
Stick us both in the van?
No. Come on, Chuck.
We don't need them.
We're here.
Hey, they don't understand that you
and I are like Batman and Robin, okay?
Unless you don't wanna be Robin.
Who wants to be Robin?
We'll be Batman and Batman.
We should be saving the day,
not running errands...
...or waiting for Beckman
to get back to us.
Morgan, I know what it feels like to have
the Intersect surging through you.
- Like you can do...
- Anything.
Yes, yes, anything.
Save the day, be a hero, anything.
Put those away. What are you doing?
Here's the thing, though, Chuck.
You don't need the Intersect to feel that.
With or without it, you are a hero,
so don't call them.
All right, we can handle this together.
Just come with me.
I need you.
Morgan, no, no, no! God. Ugh.
Okay, okay, okay. Okay, okay.
- Chuck?
- Sarah.
We're at Sneijder's headquarters.
What? Don't go in there.
I know. Morgan ran inside,
he's in trouble.
We're in trouble, I'm going after him.
Chuck, no, you can't.
Please wait for us, okay?
I'm Morgan's handler.
It's my job to take care of him.
Which is why I called you, which is why
I have to go help him now.
You'd do the same for me.
Oh, God.
Chuck's doing a great job
handling Grimes.
The blind leading the blind out there.
We get to Sneijder's headquarters
before something happens.
Casey, what is this?
Your team...
They're at my brother's building,
right?
That place may look
like an ordinary office...
...but Karl realizes something's up,
he's gonna lock it down like a fortress.
No one's gonna be able
to get in or out of there alive.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- You came.
- Let's go.
No, no. Stop, stop, stop. Through
that door, that's Sneijder's office.
We find proof that he's smuggling
conflict diamonds and then grab him.
What are you talking about?
We have to go.
I'm not going anywhere, okay?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, trouble.
No, no, no.
Yes. Listen, you are the best spy
that I know...
...and I would rather have nobody else
watching my back.
Don't worry about it.
I'm gonna take it slow.
Please don't.
- See? Nothing to it.
- It's great. Very good. Now what?
In the old days, we'd just
call the commandos for backup.
Wanna work for Verbanski Corp,
have a DOD contract...
...go ahead.
- I don't wanna work for her.
I saw her website
on your computer, okay?
- How much is she offering you?
- Nothing.
The only thing Verbanski's interested in
is me.
Physically.
- Sexually.
- What?
Watch the road, Walker.
Sweep the leg. Nice.
It was a long time ago.
It only happened once.
Seeing her again
makes it, ugh, complicated.
Complicated how?
Well...
...you ever, uh, have sex with someone
who'd just tried to kill you?
Oh, God.
It was incredible.
Okay, I think we should focus
on the mission now.
Yeah.
Uh-huh?
- Wow, good job, Indy.
- Yeah.
Who?
Indiana Jones?
- You know?
- Cool. Let's go get Sneijder.
Wait, no. We have to get out of here
right now.
Good rule about bad guys: If there's five
to start with, then there's more.
- Chuck...
- Da-da-da-da. Intersect. Handler.
But look what we did here, man.
Just like I said, Batman and Batman.
Just because you have the Intersect doesn't
mean you don't have something to learn.
You have a lot to learn.
I'm not gonna let you kill yourself today.
- I called Casey and Sarah.
- What? You called them?
Mr. Carmichael?
I do wish you would have called
before dropping by.
Place is a mess.
So did you bring me my brother?
About that...
Wesley was right.
The building's already in lockdown.
We have to get in there.
Chuck's not answering his phone.
Can't. Suicide.
- We have to do something.
- We're not gonna get in now.
Place is a fortress.
The boys are on their own.
Well, that is not good enough. I'm gonna
do whatever it takes to get us in there.
Who are you gonna call?
I cannot believe that you called them.
I had Sneijder
right where I wanted him.
We're not superheroes, not vigilantes,
we're a team.
I thought this one was you and me.
Why are you
so against Casey and Sarah?
Because they don't believe in me,
they don't trust me.
And it's very clear to me now,
neither do you.
- Morgan...
- Shut up!
I can't listen to you schoolgirls
babble on anymore.
Come to think of it...
...I only need one hostage
to get my brother back.
What's happening?
Oh, I know what's happening.
Put your weapons down.
I'm sorry, one more time for clarity,
and then I shoot something that counts.
Put your weapons down.
I got a couple of buddies in Moscow
who would love to get you...
...in a tiny windowless room
for a couple hours.
- You came.
- Well, it wasn't cheap.
You know,
some might say it's tacky...
...hiring your competition to help you,
but I think it takes balls.
Oh, and I'll have someone
from our Burbank office...
...drop off your bill.
We don't have a payment plan.
Always a pleasure, John.
You guys all right?
Yeah. Thank you for coming.
We needed you today.
Yeah, of course. We're a team.
Hmm.
What's with all these people? My God,
do you think something's wrong?
Just tell me Jeff's not trying to bathe
in the washing machine again.
So this is more thanjust a store.
This is my second home.
It's the 1080p television
that I watch the big game on.
The waterproof radio
that I listen to in the shower.
It's the blender that I use
to make my protein shakes...
...that help me look like this all day.
- His eyes follow everyone in the store.
So, yeah,
I guess for someone like myself...
...who's a heart surgeon and a natural
athlete, why not buy from the best?
Why not Buy More?
Well, I guess we're in a better
financial situation than we thought.
Sneijder gave us 200 grand.
Yeah, well, we still owe Verbanski Corp
150,000 of that.
Plus, 30 grand for the repairs
on Wesley's safe house.
- The climbing gear.
- V-21 bolt gun.
Gas for the Lotus.
What? Okay, fine, I'll cover that.
Hey, it's a start,
and it's what we needed.
Well, it's something.
Hey. Ahem.
Chuck.
I feel like I should just say that, uh,
I'm sorry, you know, for what happened.
Buddy, me too. I'm sorry.
I called Casey and Sarah to protect you,
not hurt you.
I'm trying to be the best handler
I can be. I'm just new at this, you know?
Sure. I get it.
So I'm not gonna be a spy
for a while, right?
That's kind of what I'm picking up,
though. Yeah?
Look, you have all the potential
in the world. It just takes time, that's all.
And I promise you, I will be with you
every step of the way...
...until the day that you are ready.
- Hmm.
Yeah, I bet. I bet.
Someday, though.
Okay. I gotta get to Alex's place,
see her.
Uh, you're still in for movie-trilogy night
tomorrow, right?
Sure, man.
So Star Wars or Die Hard?
I don't know, dude. Uh...
You pick, man.
That's more your thing.
Intersect's going to his head, isn't it?
Yeah, uh, maybe. I don't... He certainly
doesn't seem like himself lately.
Today on the mission, it's like he
had never even heard of Indiana Jones.
And just now with trilogy night...
Ugh, I don't know,
maybe he's just distracted.
Grimes better get his head on straight.
And soon.
- Ah.
- No, don't stop.
It'll just get harder if you stop.
Thought you'd still be in bed.
It's so early.
No. No. Come on, I'm used to this.
Us spies without the Intersect
have to find time to exercise.
Hey, hey, hey. So, uh, quick question
since you're here, heh.
Did you ask me to be Morgan's handler
because you were trying to handle me?
If you don't think I should be in the field,
I just need to know that.
No, I asked you because the job entails
bringing out the best in somebody...
...and what better example for Morgan
than you?
So, no, I'm not handling you.
A, because you don't need a handler
anymore...
...and B,
because handlers can't do this.
Okay? Come on. Let's go.
That's not fair. That's not fair.
You can't just take off.
Oh, yes, I can.
Hello, Gertrude.
It's Colonel John Casey.
I'd like to have a meal with you.
My treat.
That was good.
That'll work.
Hello?
I'm sorry about that.
So I assume you're here
about the job opening.
Let me assure you
that I am more than ready.
See, uh...
...I have something I can offer you
no one else can.
The Intersect.
Really?
I've heard about that.
I wasn't sure it really existed.
Oh, ahem, believe me, it exists.
Well, I was wondering who the real
Luke Skywalker was on your team.
It's good to finally know.
I'll bet it is.
One question, though.
Who's Luke Skywalker?