Hi. Here are a few things
you might need to know.
The Intersect made me a jerk.
Not that it was the Intersect's fault.
It brought out my inner jerk.
Don't scuff it, Cabbage Patch.
I am really sorry
for what I did to Alex.
This whole thing has gotten me thinking
about our lives, our future.
Is the spy lifestyle really
where we wanna be raising our kids?
This is what I think our coworkers
are up to.
You think they're spies?
I knew it. Lester.
Okay.
I love this. This is the most fun you and I
have had together in quite some time.
- Yeah.
- We should make more time for us.
Anyway, I still don't get it.
I don't see how this is gonna make them
forget they found Castle.
X-13 gas. Short-term memory eraser.
They'll forget the last 24 hours.
Oh, right. Got you. They come to,
think they tied one on in Vegas...
...boom, back to normal.
- Yeah.
- Whatever normal was for these guys.
- Yeah. Right.
Pop this right here. Heh, heh. Watch this.
- Uh, that's not professional.
- Of course.
- That's good.
- Good?
Good morning.
I wanna quit spying.
Wow. Wow. Okay.
Okay. Let's talk about that.
Look, I've been up all night...
...and I've been thinking
about our futures...
...and, you know, maybe babies.
- Oof. Yeah.
- I want all of that.
The more I think about it...
...I don't know if that future
goes with the life we're living now.
Both of us have been captured
more than once.
Every day we make
a new dangerous enemy.
I just ran to the door with a gun because
I heard the newspaper being delivered.
Yeah.
Parents can't be shooting paperboy.
Look, I'm a spy,
and that's all I ever thought that I could be.
But I realized that we don't have to give up
what we've already built.
We can just shift
what Carmichael Industries does.
Okay, shift it to what?
Countering cyberterrorism.
It's your tech firm idea
but more spied up.
We keep your computer know-how...
...and mix it with my experience
in international bad guy-ery.
So we'd go after bad guys
who use keyboards instead of bullets.
Which means
we don't have to use bullets either.
I mean, the timing of it
does kind of feel right.
We've got nothing left hanging,
no new missions.
No wrongs to right.
Let's do it.
Now, how do we pitch the idea
to Casey?
Well, I love it, okay?
You know how I feel about bullets,
which is negatively. This is fantastic.
Where do I fit in? Am I chief Googler?
You'd be doing the same stuff
you already do.
Yeah. We're still gonna need field ops
to recover stolen systems...
...and breaching companies' security
to find weak spots.
Wouldn't it be lovely
not to get shot at?
- Aren't you sick of being shot at?
- Or getting shot?
I mean, you get shot a lot.
Not considering
how much I get shot at.
Hm.
Okay. Think about Alex.
Do you know how happy she will be...
...knowing that you're not out there
doing scary stuff?
All right, I'll think about it.
One thing's for sure, we go through
with this, no more Buy More.
We don't need a cover. Let's kick
the creepy cousin out of the family.
Wow. No more Buy More.
Son, this came for you.
- What is this?
- Boy, get your fingers out of there.
- Hey, how you doing, Big Mike?
- Always a beautiful day at the Buy More.
- You really love it here.
- Like a turkey loves Thanksgiving.
You might wanna rethink
that one, actually. You know?
- My old iPhone.
- Doesn't really seem to be your style.
No. This is from a few months ago.
I was kind of going through a thing.
- Ahh. The frosted tips phase.
- Yeah.
Made it real hard not to smack you.
Yeah. I can imagine.
Oh, Lord.
Chuck. Chuck.
If you're getting this,
something has gone terribly wrong.
I was getting my party on,
having a great time.
This dude comes up to me
with this pair of Intersect glasses...
...and he grabs me. I kicked his ass.
No prob, as per ushe.
I grabbed the glasses
and stashed them.
Dude, I stashed them in a vault.
But like I was saying...
...I have been partying my face off...
...so I'm a little discombobulated.
Which is an amazing word.
- Stop right there!
- If this guy catches me...
...I know that you know that you love me.
Tell the world of my glory.
But above all...
...you find those glasses.
You find the... Ahh!
Huh.
Morgan, what is this?
And where were you?
I don't know, Chuck. I don't know.
Between the Intersect mind melting
and copious amounts of booze...
...it's blank. Thank God I bought
that label maker you all made fun of...
...because at least I got the phone back.
So there's a stolen Intersect out there
somewhere.
Guess we're not retiring after all.
Well, it doesn't change the plan.
It just means we have one last mission.
- Why would she...?
- No.
- Come on, Walker.
- What?
Things never turn out well
when you say "one last mission."
Is this just because
of some stupid movie?
- Yes.
You never say "one last mission."
Never.
Wow, Morgan,
look at the air you got off this cliff.
Yeah, I was so cool back then.
Counterpoint: Are you wearing
a fake dreadlock ski hat?
Really? Is that...?
- Oh. Yeah, I was.
- Look at the dates on these phone calls.
It's when you were working
for Verbanski.
And look at these text messages.
There's a name. BD.
Does that jog your memory?
Negative. No. What does BD say?
"Where'd you go?"
Send BD a message. If they were with
you the night you found the glasses...
...then maybe we can get a clue.
- Okay.
Uh... Sorry, disappeared.
What's up?
No.
I was a little more douchey than that.
- "Wassup?" With a bunch of S's?
- Sure.
And in the meantime, let's try and find
a way to help you remember something.
What is it exactly you two think
I do for a living?
Brain science.
Didn't you learn how to hypnotize
people? To get at lost memories?
Yeah, in psychotherapy class.
But that was years ago.
Fine. Okay.
- Thank you.
Okay. I really hope this works.
I'm a little skeptical. I don't think
this brain can be hypnotized.
It's like a fortress.
So focus, look at the pen.
- Deep breaths.
- Mm-hm.
Breathe.
Ow.
Sweet mother of all that is holy. Ow.
Dude, what happened? Where are we?
I don't...
- I don't know.
- You're wearing a Vegas hat.
We must have gone to Vegas.
And stole a car.
We must have just partied too hard,
and now... Ow.
A woman gave us her underpants?
Breathe on me.
There's no alcohol on your breath.
Just gefilte fish curry, like always.
Really?
Lester, something really weird is up.
Yeah, last thing I remember...
...is there's something going on
underneath the Buy More.
Right, with Bartowski,
Grimes, Casey...
...and that whore-y blonde.
- We've gotta get to the bottom of this.
- Right.
We're gonna do that by sticking to
those fools like the stank on my breath.
Now, to the Buy More.
Careful.
Light traffic day.
Yeah.
Morgan might really be hypnotized
in there.
Great. Hey, look, I've been looking
at some new possible office spaces.
Aboveground.
We could have windows.
If we ever get there.
What do you mean?
It seems like no matter what,
the Intersect keeps finding me.
I keep trying to break free...
...and the very thing that started this
keeps hooking us back in.
We're gonna finish this,
and we're gonna move on, I promise.
Hey, Casey, you wanna see
your new office space?
No, because we ain't out yet.
Even if it belonged to a little someone
named Ronald Wilson Reagan?
Seriously?
The Gipper?
Hey, guys, I got something.
Morgan keeps repeating the phrases
"emerald and gold" and number 10.
- What does that mean?
- I don't know.
I tried to push him a little further,
but I think I got a little too aggressive.
You are so hot.
You're so hot.
If you went to prom with me,
I would be the stoked-est guy.
I think I took him back too far.
It's possible.
Okay, Morgan, let's undo this.
Look at the pen.
I don't know how to look at anything
but you.
You're so beautiful.
Wow. Hey, I didn't say anything stupid
while I was under, did I?
Heh, heh. No. No, no, no.
You get a return text yet?
No, nothing.
Are you the manager?
I wanna return this blender.
I'll take care of that for you.
You have a receipt?
Yeah, let me check.
Are you in a serious relationship?
- Excuse me?
- I just wanna know...
...if you're in a serious relationship
right now.
- I'll call you back.
- Uh...
I actually am.
- Back to the blender.
- Do you love her?
Personal question
for a blender return.
Dale, I told you to stop bothering me.
Morgan, I am so, so sorry.
Yeah. No, sure. Who's Dale?
He's just a guy I went out
with a few times when we broke up.
He's nobody, really.
What? Nobody?
Oh, so I guess it was nobody that...
Wait... How did you put it?
"Filled your body with rainbows"?
Oh. Tell me he's talking
about finger painting.
- I don't understand how that works.
- Morgan, there's nothing between us.
I was just hurt, and I was missing you,
and so I acted out a little.
Physically.
You acted out? Physically?
I think I'm gonna be sick.
There were rainbows.
I love him, Dale.
So just stop coming here.
We got a text.
Thank God.
Let's talk later, you and I, okay?
Just...
Any news?
- Dale.
- Hey, John.
What? You're the one that pulled
the text message breakup.
Alex, always great to see you.
Dale, store credit only.
Oh.
- We never hugged. Sorry.
- Are you kidding?
Where are they?
We lost them. We lost them.
She acted out physically?
Morgan, I know this is hard,
but you did dump her.
- Via text.
- I know, the whole text thing.
I know I shouldn't be mad, but I am.
You wanna know why?
Because I was true blue, baby.
While she was gallivanting all over
town spreading her filthy rainbows...
...to every Tom, Dick and Harry,
I stayed strong, dude. You know what?
I need to know every detail.
I gotta find out.
I know you're upset...
...but I don't think
knowing all the gory rainbowed details...
...is gonna make you feel better
about it.
Rainbows.
Guys, look. There's a Golden Peak
Resort in Vail, Colorado.
And look here. It's a Michael Carmichael
registered the night in question.
Hey. Looks like that's our ski town.
All right, kids, let's pack up.
Morgan, sadly, you're gonna need
to look the way you did that weekend...
...so do you still have any more
of that hair bleach...
...and your Affliction T-shirt?
Well, no. Why...? Yes.
Great, let's go.
Looks like all of Vail is here.
Hope BD is too.
Any of this triggering a memory,
Grimes?
Nope. Nothing yet.
You two better love each other.
Sickening, the amount of meaningless
physical encounters...
- ...that happens nowadays.
- Morgan?
Bo Derek?
BD.
BD is Bo Derek?
Wow.
- Thought I'd never see you again, lover.
- Mm.
- Hello, Bo Derek's tongue. Wow.
- Wow.
- You need to stay with it.
We need to find out
everything she knows.
I thought for sure
I'd hear from you sooner. Bad boy.
You're the guy who made out
with Bo Derek, so act like it.
Yeah, I know. That's just bad boy stuff.
That's just how I roll.
Hi, Bo Derek.
I'm Chuck. My name is Chuck.
Really big, big fan.
Just loved 10 so, so much.
- We do.
- I know what you did with that poster.
No, no, no. I wouldn't... No, no...
- Ew.
- Not that I didn't love the poster as a boy.
- How do you know my friend?
- I don't kiss and tell...
...but your friend rocked my world
one night...
- ...in November.
- Seriously?
No, I'll never forget that.
That evening.
But how did I go about that?
The rocking?
Words would ruin it.
But there were definitely rainbows
involved.
Is that...? Check that out.
There were rainbows.
I guess Alex wasn't the only one
with secrets.
What exactly happened that evening?
Because I'm a little fuzzy with all the:
Gluggity-gluggity-gluggity.
You were a bit out of hand.
- Come on, I'll show you.
- I'm always... I'm always out of hand.
Remember this?
Oh, seems like a lot of people
might know what you did that night.
He was telling everyone
who would listen.
How he'd saved the world that day.
- You're such a funny bunny.
- Heh, heh, heh. I am.
What else did I mention?
I lost something
and I'm trying to retrace my steps.
Yeah, what did Funny Bunny do
when he left the bar?
He came to my room.
Maybe the vault that the glasses are in
is a safe in Bo Derek's room.
You need to get up there now.
I have a girlfriend.
You should have remembered that
two months ago. Now, get to work.
Looking for a vault. Write that down.
We are not forgetting anything
this time.
Man, this brings back
some memories.
You're not still staying in that room,
are you?
Because if you are,
oh, boy, ding, ding, ding, round two.
- Come on.
- Yeah.
- Ohh. Have fun, tiger.
- Yeah, you know I will.
Remember this?
Yes. Yes, I do. Who could forget this?
Hey, now.
Okay. Incidentally, Bo Derek,
is this where the rainbows happened?
Because they've been coming up
a lot lately.
I'd love to know
what makes them happen.
- What is the trigger, you know?
- Oh, I'll show you.
Yeah, cool. Can't wait.
Taking off my pants now, Chuck.
Dude...
...Bo Derek is taking your pants off.
I mean, just go with it, okay.
Ask her to tell you more about that night.
Mm-hm. Mm-hm. Hey, so you know
what I would love, love...
...totally love, Bo Derek, is...?
Tell me the story
about our night together.
- Okay.
- Mm-hm.
But only if you tell me
exactly what you've done...
...since I was with you last.
Deal, lover.
So I first noticed you
when you were getting a lap dance...
...from that dirty whore Jaclyn Smith.
That was when he got the whole bar
singing...
..."Wake Me Up Before you Go-Go"
unironically.
Right. So he didn't tell you anything else
about his night?
He got me pretty wasted.
I woke up the next morning
in a puddle of Rumple Minze.
And then we played the funniest game
where you hid and I found you...
...and then I hid and you found me.
Oh, man, so fun.
Well, all I've been able to dig up
is what we already know.
- Grimes was an ass.
- Yeah. I'm getting the same thing.
Chuck, how's it going with Bo?
Have you had any sneak peeks
of your childhood crush's boobies?
What? No. Shut up.
Hey.
Ahem. We have a situation.
Oh, you are kidding me.
How did they track us here?
What you get
when you fly commercial.
- I'll take care of it.
- Copy.
Hey, were you just asking
about Morgan Grimes?
- Uh, yes.
- Ha, ha. That dude's hilarious.
I gave him the most wack tattoo ever.
You gave him a tattoo?
Tattoo.
Morgan, I need you out here ASAP.
Be careful.
Know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna get us a little fresh ice.
- What do you think about that?
- Hurry back.
No problem. Okay.
And bring back a couple extra cubes
for playtime.
You two.
We know what's going on here.
And we are not...
We're not gonna forget.
I disagree.
What is that? That smells nice.
Doesn't it?
That woman is into me. I'm scared that
whatever's gonna take place in there...
...is gonna be worse
than whatever Alex did.
- Plus, we're broken up, technically...
- You have a tattoo.
No, I do not. No.
What? What are you...?
"Don't trust Bo Derek."
That's what your tattoo says.
Come on, she must be involved
with the Intersect theft.
Not the strangest place
a man has tattooed my name.
Now, take me to the glasses.
I'm just gonna go out and say it.
You're no longer a perfect 10.
I know you remember something.
My backup is on the way...
...and you do not wanna know
what they will do...
Sorry I had to do that
to your girlfriend.
Oh. Uh. You didn't hit her in the face,
did you?
- Kidding. But it's Bo Derek.
- Did you see her?
Okay.
Ow.
Sweet mother of all that is holy.
Dude, what happened? Where are we?
I don't...
- I don't know.
- You're wearing a Vegas hat.
We must've gone to Vegas.
Yeah. And stole a car.
Must have just partied too hard,
and now... Ow.
A woman gave us her underpants?
Breathe on me.
There's no alcohol on your breath.
Just gefilte fish curry, like always.
Last thing I remember...
...there was something
going on underneath the Buy More.
Wait. We left ourselves a clue.
Bo Derek?
So...
...Bo.
Bo Derek.
Tell me about your night with Morgan.
- And this time for real.
- Yes, please.
And how Bo Derek got involved
with the Intersect.
Listen, acting isn't the only gig I got
because of my looks...
...and my capacity to make believe.
Are you trying to say
that Bo Derek is a spy?
My boss had gotten word...
...someone was running around
the intelligence community bragging...
...he was the Intersect.
We were already on the lookout for him
when he surfaced so publicly...
...one night in Vail.
Publicly? I doubt that.
Pretty sure
I was keeping a low profile.
Who wants to party
with the freaking Intersect?
I am the most powerful weapon
in the world!
Heh, heh. You maybe?
You, uh...
Ohh.
Hello.
Are you trying to take me down?
Hey. Ow.
Oh, boy.
Oh, yes.
That was real?
And a follow-up question:
If that was real...
...were the rainbows real?
Ha, ha. It meant nothing.
- It was only physical.
- What is it with women...
...and "it's only physica..."?
- Morgan!
Uh...
- What happened next?
- Then I drugged you and called my boss.
So this is what they put
the Intersect into these days?
What are you, an intern?
Hmm?
You take that back.
You take that back,
because this Intersect...
This Intersect can almost focus
on your stupid face.
- And when I do...
- Shut up.
Morgan Grimes...
...a.k.a. Michael Carmichael,
which is ridiculous.
You're not the only one
with the Intersect, Funny Bunny.
I spent a lot of time and money
getting these glasses.
I haven't used them yet
because I hear there are side effects.
Though you seem fine.
Oh, I'm fine.
I'm fine. It's you...
You made an enormous mistake
telling me this.
Your men here? Finished.
I'm gonna take them out.
And then I'm gonna hunt you down,
and I'm going to arrest you for treason.
I don't think so.
You're not gonna remember
any of this.
X-13.
As soon as you fall asleep...
...the last 24 hours of your little life
will just disappear.
And here's how confident I am of that.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Nicholas Quinn...
...and I'm about to become
the Intersect.
Give me the glasses.
Sorry, Bo Derek.
We're looking for Nicholas Quinn.
Bo Derek's been working for him.
Bo Derek's a spy?
I know, right?
And a talky one to boot.
Quinn's got an independent spy agency,
but not like ours.
Nothing like ours.
This guy's list of clients is gnarly.
You're talking Libyan Islamic
fighting group, Kim Jong-il.
And a couple of favorites as well...
...like Fulcrum, The Ring
and Volkoff Industries.
What? We've put
some of his biggest clients behind bars.
- Did we get Jong-il?
- He's been screwed by the Intersect.
- No wonder he wants it.
- The fat lip we can blame on the tattoo.
The ski jacket and the boxers
we can blame on Bo Derek.
- But where are the glasses?
- Where's this vault?
I don't know. Guys, I don't know.
Bo Derek said
that was the last she saw of me.
I wouldn't have just stashed
the Intersect anywhere.
I would have put it somewhere safe,
someplace I knew. That's my guess.
Alex.
Oh, boy. Okay, let me deal with this.
I'll be back. Uh...
I gotta come clean on a few things.
Buddy,
are you sure you wanna do that?
Because I think maybe we should just,
you know, let the past be the past.
It doesn't seem like telling her the
Bo Derek story is gonna do anything...
...except upset her.
- Yeah.
You slept with Bo Derek?
Yeah. Maybe more than once.
I acted out physically too.
And I rocked Bo Derek's world.
- Sorry. Morgan...
- Yeah?
Dale, he doesn't matter, okay?
You don't have to make up these stories.
No, I'm not lying.
Are you kidding me?
I made rainbows
shoot out of this woman.
There's Grimes. Let's just confront him.
I know he's part of this.
Wait. We are being sabotaged.
We've gotta fly under the radar,
quietly keep an eye on them...
...and record on our person
anything we learn.
Great idea.
I gotta pee.
It's 3: 14 p.m. Write that down.
I think, though, it's better
if neither of us knows the details...
...of each other's
rainbow-related activities.
Look, you were with Dale,
I was with Bo Derek...
...we're even. Let's move past it now.
- Okay.
Okay, baby.
We are even.
That's my girl. Okay.
Ahem. Son, you have the master key?
I checked the vault, it wasn't there.
What'd you just say?
The key. I checked the manager's vault.
Any ideas?
- He's getting away!
- Come on!
Sweet lady Buy More.
Emerald and gold.
Big Mike, is there a Buy More in Vail?
There's a Buy More in Vail.
They had a break-in that night.
Of course.
I knew I put it somewhere familiar.
It's in a manager's vault in Vail.
Looks like all roads lead
to the Buy More.
I'm never getting out of this place.
Oh, he's already down.
Watch out! Watch out!
Wow.
The Vail Buy More.
A lot of broken limbs
on these morons.
I think you only work here
if you've broken something skiing.
Grimes! Remember me, buddy?
Yeah.
Sweet.
I just tweeted you're back in town.
Beers tonight to celebrate, bro.
Oh, man. Sweet.
He tweeted you're back. If Quinn
has been waiting for us to come back...
We gotta hurry.
I hate Twitter.
Hello. Excuse me, mis... ter?
We're security specialists
with Carmichael Industries.
Corporate sent us to check
the recent break-in.
Bored of you. Talk to Big Michelle.
Right.
Our security is rock solid.
I don't understand why corporate felt
we needed to be checked up on.
This isn't any criticism on your store.
We just wanna do a proper check
for your safety.
Now, if you could first take us
to the manager's vault for a look-see.
How's a nice security check feel,
Casey?
This is as extreme as it will get
in our new job.
Nice, easy peasy last mission.
It ain't over. Keep your guard up.
I just don't understand
why no one told me you were coming.
I'm gonna have to call
and get the go-ahead...
...before I open the vault, obviously.
So much for her helping us open
the vault. We're gonna do safecracking.
Yeah? Well, hold on a second.
Maybe not.
Let me try something real quick here.
One, two, three, four, boom.
- Seriously?
- I was too lazy...
...to change the code in Burbank.
One thing you can count on:
Buy More laziness.
Oh, no.
Where else could they be?
Maybe somebody moved them.
Like, maybe the person
who is currently knocked out cold.
This place is hopping right now.
I guess it's the new expansion pack
for Gunz 'n Gold.
The vault.
Could it be?
Ha, ha!
Nice work, Morgan.
Let's go. Let's get out of here.
Let's go.
You people are spies!
And we are not gonna forget it.
It's right here on my arm.
Yeah. What he said.
Get down!
Everybody out.
Charles Carmichael.
First guy who got it instead of me.
What are you talking about?
I'm former CIA too.
The Intersect
was supposed to be mine...
...but then Larkin stole it for you.
So I went back out in the field,
and I got captured. Heh, heh.
Ohh. And tortured in a hole in the ground
for 378 days.
In a hole!
I was the best.
And then I was broken.
Dismissed.
And all because the Intersect
wasn't mine.
You don't want it, Quinn.
You do not want it. Trust me.
It doesn't work right.
I lost memories, important movies.
- A bunch of stuff.
- He's right.
Listen, you don't want it. Trust me.
Nothing good can come from it.
Take a good look at your wife.
You think you'd get that
without the Intersect?
I tried to win without it. I...
I tried.
Now, give it to me!
Jeffrey. Run!
Nice shot!
Thank you.
No, no, Casey. Casey, wait.
Quinn didn't get the Intersect. We did it.
We took down his team.
Let's call Beckman.
Call the authorities.
Tell them where he is.
But let's be done.
Can't we just be done?
We survived our last mission.
Let's leave behind the Intersect and
everyone involved with it, and be done.
Okay.
We're done.
- Okay. I'll call Beckman.
- Whoa!
I'm not done. No, I am not done.
I would like very much
to forget everything.
- Everything that I saw here today.
- Here we go again.
I'm scarred.
- I'm so scarred.
- Buddy.
Sorry, Casey.
Looks like we can't kick the creepy
cousin out of the family just yet.
There's no alcohol on your breath.
It's just gefilte fish curry, like always.
I believe we've been set up.
And what's all this?
Huh. We must have gotten
to the bottom of it.
I guess we were wrong.
That's kind of disappointing.
So now what do we do?
Hey, boys. Morgan told me
you might have gotten stranded.
Yeah, apparently we did.
Cheer up.
I brought turkey B.L.T. Subways.
- From the Fresh Fit menu?
- Yep.
- Watching my weight.
- How many you have?
Only two.
- Also, I had a thought.
Mm-hm.
- We're already halfway to Vegas.
And Bolonia's doing some
Native American feelings workshop...
...about her period all weekend.
- Ew.
But are you saying?
Vegas, baby!
Sarah?
Hey. Did I wake you?
No, it's... I mean, yeah, but it's okay.
Where are you so early?
I'm sorry. I couldn't sleep.
I'm just...
I'm so excited about starting everything.
I made an appointment to check out
some of these new office spaces...
...and I thought that we could get
Casey and Morgan together...
...and have a little ceremony.
You know, pop some champagne
and toast to our futures...
...and destroy the Intersect glasses.
I think that's the right end to this.
Yeah. That sounds perfect.
Turns out saying "last mission"
wasn't a jinx after all, huh?
I love you, Chuck.
I love you too, baby. Bye.
Bye.
Never let the bad guy get away.
- Hey.
- I have your husband.
Bring the Intersect
to the San Pedro docks, Pier 23...
...2100 hours...
...or he dies.
Casey, where is everyone?
You got anything?
Casey, hold your fire. They've got Chuck.
Sarah Walker, put the glasses down.
You show me Chuck first.
The situation has changed.
He'll be needed.
Now, put the glasses down
on the ground in front of you.
It was a trap! Where is he?
I don't know. We gotta get out of here!
Casey, you got an exit?
No!
No. Not from here.
Watch the exit!
Move, move, move!
What's our next move?
I've got one mag left.
Walker, no!
Don't do it!
Okay.
I got this.