I'm Chuck. Here are a few things
you need to know.
You really think
you've been fighting evil?
Doing good?
You think it was all a coincidence?
The Intersect, Fulcrum, The Ring,
Shaw, Agent X?
You're just a pawn. You always were.
No! No, no, no. Don't take the Intersect.
- You're fired, Chuck.
- No!
Operation Bartowski is done.
What if we went into business
for ourselves?
Hartley turned over
all of Volkoff's assets to us.
Our first purchase was the Buy More
and everything below it.
Freelance spies.
Under the radar, above the law.
Oh, man, this is gonna be so much fun.
Oh, nice.
Guys...
...I know kung fu.
So ocean view. Gulls flying by.
Think this is something
you could get used to?
I'm more of a toes-in-the-sand
kind of girl.
I like the idea of waking up in the
morning and rolling out onto the beach.
Okay. Well, then maybe we can find
a nice little place on the sand someday...
- ...if we, you know...
- Survive this?
Yeah.
Hi. How you doing today?
No shooting.
I don't want the blood
and the mess on the pool deck.
Make them jump.
- Think we can survive this?
- Uh, I don't think so, honey.
"Honey"?
You talk like an old married couple.
Well, actually...
I'm sorry, I don't care.
Throw them off the cliff.
Do it and die, Jean Claude.
We came for the vase.
It belongs to our client.
You let us have it,
and maybe we'll let you live.
You've fallen into our trap.
You see, we work with a master spy,
somebody who you can't see coming.
In fact, right now, he's probably...
I want it noted
that I took out six of their guys.
He was taking this.
You thieves have expensive tastes.
This vase is worth $6 million.
It's times like these
I wish I had the Intersect.
Well, you don't.
- What now, Moriarty?
- Kill them.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
We have another master spy.
Okay. Yes. Yes.
First mission as the Intersect.
You can do this.
They need you, Morgan, so get in there,
okay? And you be a man.
No, be more than a man.
Start with the man part.
Just be a man first.
Keep going, thief. This is fun.
The fun's about to end because,
while we've been chatting...
...our other spy has been effortlessly
breaching your compound's security.
I'm good, I'm good.
He's heartless, cruel.
Oh, I'm so sorry, fishies,
about your pond.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You think your security men
are the best? Top-notch?
I admit, I do.
Well, our spy is currently
slicing through them...
...like a hot knife through butter.
Go on, say something
about you-know-who.
Do I have to?
Yes.
He'll tear your limbs off
and beat you with them.
Okay, okay.
Points for trying,
but where is this master spy?
You looking for me?
Right here, tough guy.
Here we go.
Kill him too. Kill them all.
Come on.
- Now's the time, buddy.
- I'm working on it. Working on it.
And we're dead.
Let's dance.
Who the hell are you?
Charles Carmichael
of Carmichael Industries...
...private contractors, spies for hire.
Don't forget it.
Wow, I really thought
that the latch was latched, but, uh...
Buff that right out. I think we can still
make that... We'll make that work.
We're still working out the kinks.
Alrighty, folks.
It wasn't a total catastrophe.
The client was not interested
in the vase...
...but the microchip inside it,
and that is intact.
Boom.
- Bam, we're in the pink.
- The vase was gonna be our payment.
And still is, fully restored.
Who's not gonna pay 6 mil
for a slightly used Ming vase?
Chuck, we mowed through
the Volkoff fortune on start-up costs.
Look at these numbers.
Forty-two million dollars,
which is a lot of dough.
Rockets, bullets, the private jet,
servicing the private jet...
...the fresh shrimp that Morgan
likes to eat on the private jet.
They're just not the same frozen.
They're expensive,
and if we're going to stay solvent...
...we need to collect soon.
Or crawl back to Beckman,
get a government contract.
Never had a problem with Uncle Sam.
Beat the yahoos we got coming here.
Our problem is not Uncle Sam,
it's Clyde Decker.
- I don't see that changing any time soon.
- Beg, plead.
You know I get antsy taking cases
with moral ambiguity.
Guys, come...
Sarah, isn't this what we wanted?
Come on. Carmichael Industries.
The independence and freedom
to do what we want.
We're doing good. We're doing good.
We got a solid team.
We just need a little more time
to get our feet on solid ground.
And in the meantime,
we work for dirtbags.
Chuck, you're handling this really well.
All the bumps in the road...
...and Morgan with the Intersect,
and you without it.
Which is fine.
Morgan, yes, has the Intersect now,
but I'm happy for him.
Plus, I get to work with my
smoking-hot wife and my best friends.
Who could ask for anything more?
- What was that?
- What was what?
- Are you hiding something?
- Why would I need to hide anything?
- Okay.
Morgan, Operation VFTB is dead.
View From the Bluff is dead?
Ugh, Chuck, I found the perfect house
for you guys.
I was wrong.
Sarah doesn't want a house on the bluff.
- She wants her toes in the sand.
- Operation Toes in the Sand.
Actually, it makes a better acronym.
Toes in the... T-I-T...
Why don't we just call it
Operation Toes, okay?
Hmm, fine, fine. I'll start my research.
Oh, Chuck, I know you've been setting
aside funds for this house...
...and I hope my accident with the vase
didn't blow it for you.
No. Hey, hey, don't worry about it.
We got a very promising
potential client.
We're gonna wine and dine him,
and soon enough, we will be raking it in.
Good, and you know what?
If it all goes south, well, we still have...
The Buy More.
She's served us well over the years.
It all seems so normal.
A little too normal.
Yeah. Sleeping dogs, though.
Sleeping dogs.
Oh, it's Casey.
Wants us down in Castle.
Yeah, all right.
Hoist the flag.
Hey, Casey. What do you need?
New client's here. I don't like him.
What? The who? The what?
The client? The client is here?
I thought we were gonna
wine and dine the guy.
Waste of time. He's here.
Casey, this is supposed to be
a secret base.
I took precautions.
Oh, good.
Casey, what precautions?
What the hell kind
of operation is this?
We're still working out the kinks.
Twenty million dollars was stolen
from me by a high-level Ponzi schemer.
You heard the name Roger Bale?
Well, you will soon.
He's bilked investors to the tune
of about a half a billion dollars.
Why not go to the cops?
I did, but Bale has falsified records...
...saying he lost the money in trading
and he's broke.
But he keeps buying property
in St. Martin. He's a thief.
The heart of Bale's operation
is a computer vault...
...in his corporate headquarters.
Access the accounts, get my money.
Yes. We ride at midnight.
His security is deadly.
So maybe we ride
first thing in the morning.
- No need to rush.
- That's a better idea.
Twenty percent of what you recover
is yours.
Fifty. Done some digging
on you, Woodley.
You're just an ambulance chaser,
trial lawyer, scum of the earth.
Uh, he's kidding. He's kidding.
He's only kidding.
Casey,
Bale is worth infiltrating anyway.
Looks like he's stolen money
from teachers' unions and families.
He stole 2 million
from Rush Limbaugh.
Tell me everything you know
about this animal.
He's throwing himself a party
tomorrow night. His going-away.
But it's strictly invite, and everything
goes through his secure BlackBerry.
What a complete tool.
"Blah, blah, blah," on the Bluetooth
all day. How rude.
I'm getting a good feed from the satellite.
The party's being set up.
The place looks like a fortress.
See? Satellite was a good investment.
Just gotta figure out a way
to get into his PDA...
...and invite ourselves to this party.
Let's talk house, homeboy.
- What was that? Did you say "house"?
- Nothing. Just hopping off real quick.
The house is secret, remember?
The only real secret is gonna be
which room you're sleeping in.
Why? Seventeen of them.
Pool, screening room,
bowling alley, gourmet kitchen...
...second bowling alley,
and it's on the beach.
- I mean, it's crazy, but...
- Hey. Toes in the sand.
- Toes in the sand. Toes in the sand.
- Toes in the sand.
Could you imagine
how awesome this would be, buddy?
I mean, to give Sarah the dream life?
Owning our own company...
...living in the dream home,
a place that we can call our own.
We just need this gig to pay out.
I know.
One second.
Why don't we nab this guy's phone
while he's playing squash?
- What?
- I just zoomed on his gym bag.
Kensington Athletic.
A super-exclusive squash club.
- He's gotta have a regular game, right?
- Morgan, that's fantastic. Fantastic.
"Zoomed"? What did you say? You...?
What? Did you...?
You zoomed on his gym bag?
Yeah, because you had "flash,"
which was great...
...but, eh, wanna do my own thing, mix it
up a little bit, so I came up with "zoom."
- You don't like it. Ah, you don't like it.
- No, hey.
"Zoom" it is, buddy, you know.
Whatever you want.
Really?
You're amazing. You are so Zen now.
If I had a power like that and I thought it
was gone forever, oh, I'd be a wreck.
Whew. Not you, man. You are my hero.
You're great
even without the Intersect.
How certain are you that these glasses
only had one reload left in them?
Like, very certain.
I tried to access the program,
but there was no way to update it.
This version of the Intersect
is a one-time deal. I'm sorry.
That's okay. That's okay.
Morgan's got it now,
and he's doing surprisingly well, so...
Chuck, what's wrong?
The Intersect opened me up
to big dreams.
But in order for those dreams
to become a reality...
...I need this business to succeed,
and...
You think the company doesn't work
if you don't have the Intersect?
Yeah.
Chuck, I don't think that Dad wanted
you to have the Intersect forever.
And besides, you don't need it.
The computer
didn't make you a hero...
...it just gave you an opportunity
to become one.
Now it's up to you.
Training wheels are off, you'll fall down,
but I promise you...
...you can do this.
My 2 cents.
Thanks, sis.
I needed a good Ellie speech.
Well, what are sisters for?
The mission
is to access Roger Bale's PDA...
...and put ourselves on the guest list
for his party.
The phone is gonna be difficult to get to
and password-protected when we do.
If we do. Bale has bodyguards.
Could be trouble.
And that's why you're the one
going for the phone.
This plug-in will cut through
all the encryption...
...and install a virus
that will send me an invite.
Bale is playing in a squash tournament.
Morgan, delay his opponent...
...while I step in and match up with Bale.
He'll get to know my face and name.
When I show up at the party,
I won't be a stranger.
What? What's the problem?
What's up?
You're gonna play?
Do you actually play
any non-video game sports?
Yeah, I played some racquetball.
I think I can fake squash
for half an hour, heh.
- No, Chuck, I don't think so.
- Ahem.
Sarah.
Uh, well, sweetheart, um...
...you know, I think what, um...
Let's put Grimes on the court.
He can zoom on squash,
give the guy a game.
"Zoom," Casey?
It'll buy me some time.
You delay his opponent.
Take over the job I was gonna do. It'll be
great. What was the job I was gonna do?
Yeah. Oh.
Think I'm supposed to be playing now.
You sure it's only 2:00?
Oh, Mr. Burnham,
you just sit here and relax.
I will tell you when it's time.
And right now, it is not time.
Bale's coming.
Casey, he's headed your way.
- Get ready. He'll be there in a minute.
- Yep.
Chuck, you keep that bear on that table,
or this all falls apart.
Remember, I like it deep and hard.
That's great.
That just sounds great.
Hey, man, sorry for the delay.
I had a hot tub
full of nursing students.
- So chatty.
- Totally.
- So you must be Killer Burnham?
- He's a no-show.
I'm Michael Carmichael
of Michael Carmichael Industries.
That sounds like big money.
Hmm, you have no idea. You know,
if I was standing on my wallet...
...I'd be tall. Ha, ha.
- Yeah.
- Your skin is soft to the touch.
- There you go.
Is that a waxing situation?
My wife's talked to me about waxing,
but not a fan of physical contact.
Outside of my job, of course.
This is what I do every day, heh.
Hey, uh, your ball warm?
Here we go.
Amigo, my ball is red-hot.
- You're pretty quick.
- "Sneaky quick," they call that.
Bale. Sneaky quick.
- Put a little elbow grease into it.
- Oh, yeah? Should I do that?
- There you go.
- There it is.
Almost there.
Little deeper.
You know, you are a thick man.
- Yeah, right there.
- There it is.
Come on.
Turn and reach,
you old son of a bitch.
Hey, Chuck, we got a big problem.
Casey's caught up getting Bale's phone.
Maybe I can tranq my guy,
give Casey an assist.
So let me ask you a question. Uh, this guy
you're supposed to play, Jim Burnham...
...you called him something else.
"Killer." Heard he killed nine men
in the foreign legion.
The name stuck.
Hmm, only nine, huh?
- What the hell?
- Ah! No, no, somebody's not relaxing.
Relax, breathe, breathe.
I just dropped something.
Oil's slippery.
John Casey.
I knew you'd fall for that old line.
I haven't seen you since jump school.
Stark. Been a while.
- Breathe.
- Is that a gun?
I am gonna rip your head off.
What's a leatherneck like you doing
in the Kensington Club?
- Private security.
- Me too.
For a turd named Bale.
Real scuzzer, but at least it's a payday.
I don't have to sell you on selling out.
Guy with your skills, Casey...
...you've got to be raking it in.
- Uh-huh.
You think one little dart
is gonna drop 400 pounds of solid meat?
That's it.
Drop him and stretch it out.
You seem like
a moderately successful individual.
Let's say a fella had 40 mil
kind of lying around doing nothing.
- What would you do with it?
- You looking to invest?
I might be. I might be.
No. No. No!
Good game, Carmichael.
Oh, Bunny Doll. Bunny Doll, Bale.
Bale, Bunny Doll.
Hey, uh, why don't you guys come
to my party tomorrow night?
Tomorrow night? Bunny Doll,
do we have anything, uh, planned?
No. I don't think so.
- Well, how do you feel? You wanna go?
- Oh, I'm game.
- Hmm.
- Excellent.
Good, good, good.
It's a date, then, huh?
Tomorrow night. I'll e-mail you.
Quit goofing around. We gotta go.
- What about the mission?
- Don't worry. Morgan saved the day.
- Got an invite to the party.
- Huh?
Thank God for the Intersect, huh?
Hey, buddy.
- Nice work on the mish today.
- Yes.
We wired a couple million dollars into
Bale's account. You're set for the party.
Would you go Bogart
with the white tux...
...or would you go Bond
with the black tux?
Uh, black, definitely.
I knew it. I knew black tux.
Always bet on black. Right?
Okay, what's wrong?
Chuck, is this Intersect withdrawal?
I mean, are you missing it?
Sure. Yeah.
Of course. But it's more than that.
I'm just realizing
how hard it's gonna be without it.
I guess I got used to our spy missions
being a little easier.
But remember the big picture here.
Your beautiful wife, your perfect home.
It's all right here. "Toes in the sand."
- It's the big picture.
- Hey.
I gotta go. I'll get this to the lab.
- Good job, team.
- Yeah.
- Right. High-five here.
- Good, good, good. Good briefing.
Chuck, do you realize
that I'm a trained spy...
...who can tell when somebody
is keeping a secret? Especially...
...when that someone happens to be
my husband.
It's who I am.
Husband without a secret.
Casey and I are going
to scout Bale's headquarters...
...so we'll talk about this later.
Can't this be
that one-time conversation?
This isn't good.
We've finally lost control of this
store, haven't we?
All right, where's Jeff?
No. Where's Lester?
I can sense his evil little hand
all over this.
Hey, Jeff.
Heartbreaking, isn't it?
- What happened?
- What do you mean?
Is this about poor Jeffrey over there?
"Poor Jeffrey"?
He was trampled
by a stampede of secretaries...
...during the midnight release
of the talking Justin Bieber doll.
His legs were crushed.
He may never walk again.
But you would know that...
...if you ever bothered to come in
and actually manage the store, Grimes.
Or you, Bartowski...
...if you ever bothered to come by
and check up on your friends.
Shame.
Morgan, I can't believe it.
It's terrible. I feel so bad.
No, Morgan.
I mean, I literally can't believe it.
Really? This?
They wouldn't. They couldn't.
What am I talking about? It's Jeff
and Lester. It's a scam. Of course.
Please help.
Buy More insurance ran out.
Ugh. The audacity. As the secret owner
of this establishment...
...I know we have excellent insurance.
How are we gonna prove Jeff and Lester
are bilking from the store?
Maybe we construct some sort of ruse
and trick him up out of the chair.
Or we could... Hang on.
Or we could wait for him to stand up
like the moron that he is.
Yeah.
- This is some sort of insurance scam?
- Hey, guys.
Give back every penny,
or you're going to jail.
To see my mom?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, hey, guys, guys,
what are you doing?
This is a very sick man here.
Ah! Oh, my gosh.
Jeffrey, you can walk.
Guys, it's a miracle.
It's a miracle.
This is because of your donations.
Shame.
- Shame.
We may need to spend some more time
at the Buy More.
Yeah, we do. Oh.
Oh, I forgot.
Sarah wants to have a talk.
She knows I'm keeping a secret.
Oh, no. Not the house.
She's gonna try and break me.
Mm-hm. Mm-hm.
Okay, I'm gonna hold on to this,
right?
And, uh, you go in there,
and you be strong.
Good luck. Remember,
I'm not there to save you this time.
- Sarah?
- In a minute.
Um...
So, honey, here's the thing.
Uh, I'm not trying to keep anything
from you.
You are my wife,
and that's a part of the deal.
I'm well aware of that.
I would, however, like to keep
a few things in a "special category"...
...of "you don't need to know about"-ness.
Yeah.
No, no.
Not today. This has worked in the past.
Not today.
What is it?
This. This. All that.
What's your secret, Chuck?
My lips are sealed.
Well, let me help you unseal them.
- Hand it over.
- He cracked like an egg.
- It's an acronym. You see the little dots?
- Whatever.
If you were to break it up
and sound it out phonetically...
It's very sweet, Chuck,
that you tried to surprise me.
With a dream home?
Like that one right there,
right on the sand.
The perfect house for
the perfect woman. What do you think?
It's not right, is it?
You know,
I could just keep playing detective...
...and trying to read your mind and...
Well, I haven't, um...
Well, this isn't something
that I've ever told anybody.
Hello?
Husband.
It's my official title now.
I have a ring to prove it.
You can tell me things
that you don't tell other people.
Uh, well, when I was a little girl, my, uh,
dad's "work" kept us moving around a lot.
And I always imagined
what a real family would feel like...
...what the perfect home
for us all would be...
...and, you know, the dream house.
Is this stupid?
No, no, it's not. Babe, continue.
Well, I always imagined, uh,
a little white house with a red door...
And don't laugh,
but it had a picket fence...
...just like, you know, the houses
that you see on TV that people live in.
Hmm.
Mid-century. Very Leave It to Beaver.
Cozy, homey and simple.
And perfect.
- Really?
- I'm gonna find you your dream home...
...whatever it takes.
I'll do anything. I promise.
Testing, one, two.
One, two, three.
Looking good, team.
Especially you, Sarah.
Well, let's have a great mission,
huh, team?
While I sit by myself in the van.
God, I hope this works.
All right.
Let's go over the plan one more time.
Casey, locate Bale's computer vault.
Morgan, Sarah, create a distraction...
...giving Casey time to get into the vault
and tap into the system.
Got it.
- Bale, old man. Good to see you.
- Nice to see you.
- Right? Yeah, you remember Sarah?
- I do.
Right. This is Chalmers,
my mute manservant.
We have received your wire
and account information.
On behalf of our investors,
we're very excited to have you aboard.
Oh, I bet. I bet.
Follow me.
Will do.
I was to be your accountant.
What I did was I improvised.
- Okay.
- Hmm.
Morgan, buddy, you're doing great.
Doing great. Just stay on point.
Remember the mission.
Casey, you're up.
Excellent. Excellent, Casey. Excellent.
Cable leads down the hall.
- That's where the vault is.
- I'll need a key card.
- Sarah?
- I'm on it.
As you can see,
my fortune is based on shared wealth.
Finding others
who enjoy the better things in life.
Well, that's very bold, Mr. Bale.
Chuck, this jerk is starting to get handsy
with my girl.
Our girl. Your girl.
Calm. Calm, Morgan. Just calm down.
No, no, no.
I think I'm gonna zoom, okay?
I can feel it coming on. Kung fu.
I'll karate-chop this guy in the face.
No, no, no. Do not do that.
You're gonna zoom too soon.
Premature zoom? Really? Crap.
Okay, okay. What do I do?
Think about baseball.
Baseball.
Why baseball? I mean, come on.
It is so boring.
I mean, just pitch
the damn ball already.
And enough talk with the statistics. Do
you know what slugging percentage is?
I don't know what slugging percentage
is. And, honestly, who the hell cares?
All right, that worked.
Thank you, buddy. I'm good.
Perhaps I can show you around
the gardens outside.
They are modeled after
the pleasure gardens of Italy.
Well, the pleasure would be all mine.
You're a good girl.
- What a slime bag.
- Yeah.
Excellent work, everybody. Casey
is on his way to the computer vault.
- Morgan, Sarah, distraction time.
- Alrighty, Chuck. Am I up?
Oh, you are up, buddy. Zoom away.
Oh, yeah. I like that.
Sarah.
Let me show you how it's done.
Nice work, Morgan.
- We're in.
- Bingo.
Once all the accounts
are downloaded...
...we can reroute them
to the original investors.
No, no, no. What's happening?
Decker.
Hello, Chuck.
- What are you doing?
- I'm using your computer...
...to access Bale's accounts
and freeze them.
No, no, no.
You're gonna trigger the alarm.
My people are still inside.
Your people?
Cute.
I know you lied to me.
I know I'm not part of your plan...
...whatever the hell that is, okay?
You've won.
Now, let us go.
Payback's a bitch, Charlie.
No. Guys, guys, get out of there.
Mr. Carmichael?
Darling, I know what you did
with my key card.
Come with me now, or I will kill you
in front of all of my friends.
Uh-uh, I think, actually, what's gonna
happen is I'm gonna open up a big can of...
What?
Come with me, colonel.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You used to be a colonel.
Morgan, Sarah, Casey, please,
tell me what's happening.
I'm locked out of the accounts.
What have you done?
Do anything to us, and you'll never have
access to those accounts ever again.
You see, we work with somebody.
A master spy who always has a plan.
Okay. Okay, this isn't good.
No plan. No plan.
The master spy does not have a plan.
Uh, I don't wanna hear her voice anymore.
Take them all downstairs.
I'll decide what to do with them later.
I need you to get somebody from our
computer team on the phone right now!
Yes, sir.
I think I have a plan.
Computer emergency?
What's wrong with it?
An outside computer
is accessing your system.
You're under attack.
Don't worry. I cut into the attack.
Your accounts are here.
- Is it fixed?
- Yeppers.
Get rid of him.
Huh? Wait. What's happening?
I'm just the IT guy.
You saw things you weren't supposed
to see. And I don't like your face.
Kill him. Then the others.
I'd think twice about that, Bale.
I pull these wires,
your firewall goes down...
...and the CIA is inside of you
in seconds.
Inside of your computer in seconds.
Who are you?
Carmichael.
Charles Carmichael.
I have your brother, Michael.
I know, and you're gonna let him
and the others go.
I so much as sneeze,
and, well, you lose all your money.
Oh! Ha, ha. Oops.
That was about 10 million bucks
right there, Roge.
Let them go.
What the hell is going on?
You're free to go.
Hey, Chuck? Chuck, can you hear me?
Where are you?
- Sarah, you outside?
- Yeah.
They let us go. Are you still inside?
Don't worry about me. Just go.
No, I'm not going anywhere.
You, Casey and Morgan
get in the van and leave now.
Did I do great?
Shut up, moron.
Chuck, I am not leaving my husband
on a mission.
Sarah...
Sarah, I'm sorry.
I wanted to buy you the house.
I wanted to give you the future
you've always dreamed of.
- But more than that, I want you to live.
- Come on.
Don't make me die in vain.
Leave me behind.
Get in the van.
Leave. Leave me behind!
- We can't leave him behind like that.
- Please, leave!
Guys, please don't leave me behind.
I have a plan.
Your friends are safe,
but you're stuck here.
What were you thinking?
Actually, I was thinking fast.
There's a button on the control panel.
Hit that button.
I just hope they got my message.
Morgan, disconnect us
from the building's electrical line.
Casey, get the van moving.
Sarah, there's a rather large window
on the east side of the building.
It's the only way out.
So I'm gonna be jumping through it.
Casey, east side of the building.
Go, go, go.
And, Sarah...
...no matter what happens...
...I love you.
Also, ifat all possible,
if you could check...
...to make sure I'm still alive on the roof
of the van, that would be great.
- Good work, Chuck.
- Thanks, honey.
Hey, dude, that was awesome.
Listen, guys, team,
let's not get down, okay?
Yes, that was not
a classically successful mission...
...but, you know, we all made it out
alive, uh, so that's a plus.
And the news says
that Bale was arrested...
...so I think we should put that
in the "win" category.
Uh, win, uh... Win with an asterisk maybe.
- Ahem.
- It's not that, Chuck.
Well, okay, what is it, then?
Decker froze Bale's accounts, which
included the money we transferred in.
Castle and the Buy More
are the only things that aren't frozen.
Decker froze all of our money because
he tracked our deposit back to us.
Wait.
Wait. What? All of our money?
- We have nothing?
- Payback's a bitch.
Okay, think about it. We still have
the Buy More, and we still have me.
And, uh, Sarah and Casey, you.
This is still a team. We can still do this.
I think I, uh... I need a little air.
Chuck.
Listen, it's okay. We'll bounce back.
We always do.
Yeah.
I gotta...
Uh, I'll be back.
Chuck, you found it.
What's the matter?
I can't afford it.
If I bought it yesterday with our fortune,
we'd own it, but now...
I'm so sorry, Sarah.
Well, so what? I mean,
we knew this wasn't gonna be easy...
...and we didn't get married
because we thought life was easy.
We got married so that
we could be there for each other...
...when things got tough.
So we could work through things
together, rich or poor.
How are we gonna do this?
We gotta start over.
It's okay.
We'll get new clients and missions.
And we haven't lost everything.
We still have Castle and the store.
The Buy More?
The Buy More.
We use the store to support the
spy team. We take Buy More's profits...
...put them into Carmichael Industries
until both companies can make money.
For that to work,
the store has to turn a profit.
We can do that.
What about me, though?
You and Casey are super spies.
Morgan's the Intersect.
Who am I? What's my job?
Chuck, you're our leader.
That's the plan.
As you can see...
...our superiors' interference
in Chuck Bartowski's life...
...has only just begun.
Now you understand
how important he is.
And why he must fail.
You all have your orders.
This is the plan.
Its final chapter.
Nothing can stop it.