I'm Chuck. Here are a few
things you might need to know.
Ever hear of carbon monoxide?
Stop sleeping in your van, Jeff.
I'm seeing things clearly
for the first time in a long time.
Are you high?
The Intersect you uploaded,
something's wrong.
There was a Trojan Horse
hidden in the software.
That's why you're not acting
like yourself.
Text messaged a breakup
with my girl?
I can do better.
Morgan told anyone who wanted to hear
he had Intersect.
Decker wants Morgan dead.
Stop!
Chuck.
Chuck, what the hell, man?
You stay away
from that douche-cycle?
We gotta get you back
to Castle.
The CIA knows you're the Intersect.
You have a hit out on you.
Yeah. Oh, my God.
Yeah. Let's go, Let's go.
Don't freak out, though, okay?
I am still the Intersect.
Not to mention, I happen to stand by
my Monotracer's coolness factor.
- Please, okay? I'm gonna grab some...
- No, no!
- Yes, I agree that it is okay to freak out.
- Thank you.
The only reason there's a hit on you,
is you got the Intersect in your head.
We need to get it out
of your head...
...let the CIA know it's over,
and you'll be safe.
And a moron again.
Sorry. Moron still.
Okay, all right, how do we start that?
Is Ellie working on something?
No, we, uh, called in the big guns.
So shocked you people
are running out of money.
"Missile Command"
is a part of our process.
All right, let's clean up this mess.
Are you ready, Mr. Grimes?
Yes, ma'am. Let's do it.
Let's get this mind-melting...
...assassination-producing
thing out of my head.
Don't worry, buddy,
just sit back, relax, breathe.
So that's it? It's really over?
Superhero no more?
Okay, all right, if you're absolutely sure
this is the only way.
Morgan, look, trust me,
I know how you feel, I do.
The Intersect is a lot of fun.
But this is all for the best.
I know. I know, I do.
Can I just do one last thing first?
- You ready, buddy?
- Ready.
- Wow.
- Man, I miss the Intersect.
Okay, let's do this.
Bye, Captain Morgan.
Okay, okay, wow, yeah, yeah.
- You all right?
- Fine. Yeah, great.
- Relax, Casey.
- That was for dumping Alex.
I get it. I get it.
The first thing I'm gonna do
is apologize to her, okay?
But do I need to remind you
that my mind was melted?
How's your memory?
Remember Die Hard, Star Wars...
...Chewie, Yoda, "Yippie Ki-Yay"?
It all kind of sounds
like gibberish.
- It is.
- I feel fine otherwise, you know?
My brain got rid of unimportant stuff.
Which there seemed to be plenty of.
How long will it take to
call the hit off?
I'll contact you when he's clear.
Until then, Grimes, stay down here.
And the rest of you,
don't make a mistake like this again.
- Uh, thank you, General.
- Stop playing with government toys.
You have plenty of your own.
And we lower the babies
to our chests as we breathe in...
...and blow it out
as we raise them back up.
In, out.
Oh, hey, guys.
Grab a mat, join baby yoga.
- We can share Clara.
- We'd love to, but we're kind of in a rush.
Hey. Hey, baby Clara.
How's my favorite niece in the world?
Clara is a rad yogi.
I probably shouldn't say this...
...but she's a way more grounded
breather than these other jokers.
Wow, looks like you're really
enjoying paternity leave.
I have adjusted 110 percent.
I could do this forever.
Let's go ahead and put our babies
into a teeny downward puppy.
- Hi.
Hey, there's super dad's missus.
Uh, yes, Devon is really taking
to the stay-at-home daddy thing.
He's gotten into mommy groups
that wouldn't call me back.
- Hmm.
- Wow, you're lucky...
...he's willing to stay at home, heh.
Yeah, yeah, I'm a happy lady.
Happy lady,
have a great day at work.
- Thanks. Have a good one. Bye, Clara.
- Bye.
- Mommy loves you.
- Say, "Bye, Mommy."
Bye, ugh.
How great are
Ellie and Awesome, huh?
They're just a nice,
happy, normal couple.
Yeah, they are.
- We aren't all that normal, are we?
- No, no, not really...
...but we're happy and we're nice.
It's just, you know,
my best friend is being hunted.
His brain almost turned to mush.
I haven't slept in nearly a week...
...our family business
is on the brink of bankruptcy.
We're spies
who aren't allowed in the CIA.
I just think, you know,
maybe we're at a fork in the road.
Well, you know,
you wanna not be spying?
I just wonder what it'd be like to be
a normal married couple.
Regular nine-to-fives,
more taco nights, less evil cabals.
I know things have been a little crazy
right now. Morgan's gonna be fine...
...and we're gonna figure out
this whole free-agent spy thing.
- Now that we don't have the Intersect?
- Yes, even now.
Mm-hm, mm-hm, mm-hm.
Here we go. Here we go.
Oh, no.
Most of the assassins
have been called off.
Most of the assassins? Okay, good.
That's like getting
most of the brain tumor.
I don't understand what the problem is.
- The problem's name is Decker.
- That's right.
The order originally
came from his desk.
He ousted us from the Agency.
What's his problem?
- He's not done with us.
- Perhaps we should...
Good afternoon.
I hear we're having the most unfortunate
little kill order mix-up.
Don't you ever interrupt my feed again,
Decker. I am still your superior.
Morgan's Intersect-free.
Call off this hit.
Oh, I really do want to.
But unfortunately,
and probably not accidentally...
...I also sent the order out to
one outside contractor.
One who can't be recalled.
It's sort of his thing.
- It's, uh, codename Viper. Ahem.
- The Viper?
He goes completely dark
once he's cashed the check.
Which, sadly, he's done.
- What does he know?
- Just the name Morgan Grimes.
- That should do it.
- That's all he needs.
The Viper's never had
an uncompleted mission.
Why don't I leave you all with a little
look-see at some of his, uh, famous kills?
So many dead people.
I'm gonna be down here
for the rest of my life.
I have these broken relationships
I need to fix upstairs.
Don't worry.
Your name's not gonna be on that list.
No way. We're on it.
Yeah, leave it to the three friends
you recently stabbed in the back.
Marked for death. It's kind of sexy.
It's not terrifying.
Because my big bad spy friends
are gonna take care of it.
Right, nothing to worry about.
All we have to do is lure out this
Viper creature and neutralize him.
No reason we can't reason
with him. The man's just doing a job.
There's no vendetta involved.
Maybe we can talk to him,
contractor to contractor.
Like normal people.
Ooh!
Oh, man.
Jeffrey, you're not noticing
I'm doing something interesting here?
Oh, sorry. What's up?
Okay, so listen, as you know, the big
Salesman of the Year Convention...
...is this weekend in Riverside.
- But you never sell anything.
You eat Pirate's Booty
and watch large-lady pornography.
But I rigged it so that
every employee's sales this quarter...
...have been logged under my name.
My friend, I'm going to be up to my
eyebrows in popcorn shrimp...
...and some sweet
Inland Empire lady parts.
But what about the rest of us?
Like, what if I wanted to go?
No, no, you don't.
You like being number two.
- I made you number two, man.
- I don't think I do.
You do. Stop spewing nonsense.
Sometimes I think
you are a bad person.
Now, undo what you've done.
I know you'll feel better
if you earn this on your own.
Son, are you reading a book?
- Yes, I am.
- I'm gonna get my camera.
Let the reeducation
of Morgan Grimes begin.
Oh, yes, I am so excited.
What do I start with?
Easy. Star Wars.
I'm so jealous.
Enjoy, while we sort this out.
And don't worry,
the force is strong in this one.
Mm!
No idea what that means,
but I am pumped.
- Well, have fun.
- Okay, all right.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, Casey, Casey.
Want to watch Star Wars with me?
Uh, no. No, but hey,
don't start with A New Hope.
Old ones, nobody likes that.
Phantom Menace.
Everybody loves Phantom Menace.
Hey, you're all right. Thanks, man.
Yeah, sure. The Phantom Menace.
Heh, yeah, this is gonna be awesome.
- I'm sorry, who is this again?
- Jeffrey. Jeffrey Barnes.
- You know, from the Buy More.
- Oh, hey, Jeff. Wow!
You sound normal.
We need a decision on who will be
chosen to go...
...to the Salesman of the Year
weekend in Riverside.
Our manager cannot be located.
Huh.
You know, let me, uh... Let me
call corporate and I'll let you know.
- Great. Thanks, Chuck.
- Bye.
I know how to find the Viper.
So I've talked to corporate...
...and it turns out
that the Salesperson of the Year...
...and winner of the coveted weekend
in Riverside, California, is...
Morgan Grimes.
Are you pulling
my considerable chain?
Grimes has barely shown
his face in weeks.
- I love the boy, but it's true.
- No, no, no. Guys, guys, guys.
Do you not see what's happening?
This is a fix.
It's obviously fixed.
Now, you know what? I revolt.
- I revolt. Who's with me?
- Yeah!
Listen, I'm disappointed, too.
But aren't we all still lucky
to be here?
Working at a great place,
in a down economy?
Surrounded by our great-looking
Buy More co-workers?
Selling fine goods to the people
who haven't discovered Amazon.
So what if we just use this
as a wake-up call...
...and vow to work even harder
for the next year?
Yeah!
This is, heh...
I don't know what this is,
but I like the new work ethic, Jeff.
You keep that up. I gotta go.
So here's the plan:
We send Morgan to Riverside.
We make it as public as possible,
so that the Viper hunts him down.
But before he can strike, we do.
And after all this is over,
Morgan can be just a regular guy again.
Okay, yeah, put myself out there,
allow myself to be hunted. Yeah.
Hmm.
Now, not to sound like a baby...
...but without the Intersect,
it does seem a bit more terrifying.
It won't be as hard as you think.
Hi. I'm Morgan Grimes.
All these nice people.
Wonder which one is trying to kill me.
Hello, Buy Most-ers!
And welcome to all the
Salespeople of the Year.
Now, I say salespeople,
because some of you are even ladies.
So good for you.
Another crack in that ceiling.
We're gonna have to get that thing fixed.
I'm just joshing, just joshing.
Grab a yard of margaritas
and get your mingle on.
Well, Morgan,
you ready to get your mingle on?
So ready to get my mingle on.
Thank you.
- Casey, you good?
- We're up and running.
Remember, I need pulse bio-feedback.
Finger-pads don't give us lie detection
unless you're touching the subject.
Touch the subject, see if they're lying.
If they are,
perhaps they wanna kill Chuck.
If they aren't, I grab another crab puff,
heh.
Okay, stay alert. All we know is that
the Viper kills at close range.
That's why he's so accurate,
but that only means no sniping.
He could use poison, so just watch
your food and drink intake, okay?
Okay, he has strangled, knifed,
drowned, and there is a pool here.
- So, you know?
- Got it. Lots of ways to die today.
Okay. Once we identify the target,
I'll move in and neutralize him.
Yeah, not normal
husband-wife conversation.
Uh, Morgan Grimes, Burbank Buy More.
And where are you from?
Champaign-Urbana. Heh, prettiest
place on God's sweet earth. Ha, ha.
That's where I was born and, uh, where,
God willing, I will die.
Yep. He checks out.
As you know, we're all just visitors
in this sweet corn festival that, uh, is life.
Poor sucker thinks that's true.
Well, it's nice to meet someone
who loves where they're from.
And you?
You're looking a little flushed there.
- You running a fever?
- No.
Always get red
after my ninth or tenth.
Irish blood, you know?
Just a race to see if our noses
or our hearts will explode first.
Either way, though, we're dead by 50.
Oh!
Yep, true, too.
You guys are too much.
I'm gonna take off.
Hold up, you. Shots, shots, shots.
Aw! Man, Crazy Bob, you're killing me.
Literally, this is terrible
for my liver condition.
Hey, there you go.
You're the new guy.
Got you a special one.
Drink it. Drink it now.
- Drink it.
- Please drink it. They're so loud.
Oh, he took it down. He took it... Ha, ha.
Oh, you are welcome.
Crazy Bob's shots will kill you.
You're a lifesaver.
- Yep. He checks out.
- Oh.
Randy, come on.
- Leave the pretty lady alone.
- Heh, thank you.
I am sorry about how all these leeches
are gonna paw at you all weekend.
And also wildly jealous.
- Hi, I'm Linda, heh.
- Hi. Sarah.
It's, uh, very sweet of you.
So, um, seriously,
how do you look like this?
Ten years at Buy More, I can't keep
my face out of the cheese balls.
True.
The lady loves her cheese balls.
- Clear.
- Hi.
- She's good, too.
- Oh, I like your...
Clear.
True. It checks out. Clear.
All clear there, Jim.
Nothing in the old eyeballs.
Easy, buddy.
This gets you into the buffet.
Oh, sweetie,
Mama's gonna be home soon, I promise.
No, I promise
and I'm gonna bring you a treat. Yes.
- Uh, is everything okay?
- Oh, hi.
I'm just being stupid.
My son has a cold and...
- I feel bad I'm here.
- Oh, I understand.
- I'm Jane.
- Uh, Sarah.
Sarah. I'm here with my husband,
Morgan Grimes.
Walker, move your hand.
You just checked yourself.
Passed, too. You're getting pretty good
at this lying thing.
I promise I'm not one of those women
who can't be away from her family.
It's just been a while, you know.
I think I've been a mom
and a "wife" for so long, I...
I've sort of forgotten how to be
a regular person, you know?
- Oh, I do. I really do. Heh.
- Heh. I used to know how to have fun.
I came to one of these things
before I was married.
Crazy Bob and I led 18 people
in a midnight skinny dip.
- Clear.
- It sounds like you're the lady...
...I'm gonna stick with.
You know everybody here.
Oh, better.
I know what everyone looks like naked.
No.
Oh, my God.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Wait a minute. Oh, my gosh.
I have to ask you something
man-to-man here, okay?
Did I like Phantom Menace?
I would rather scratch out my eyeballs...
...than to listen to that
Jar Jar Binks anymore.
Ay, yi, yi, I don't know,
maybe my brain has changed.
Hmm. You know what hasn't changed?
My feelings for Alex.
Yeah, if there's one thing I remember
it's that I was an ass and that I love her.
The crazy thing is,
she changed her phone number.
Wondering,
maybe you can help me out?
Tell her you had a secret supercomputer
in your head, made you into a jackass?
No. Nothing left to say. It's over.
Hey, oh...
I lied. Start with the originals.
You love those.
- Really? Thanks, man.
- Hmm.
- Thanks.
- Oh, hey.
Just so you know, Darth Vader,
Luke's father. Leia is his sister.
Still mad.
So all of a sudden, right...
...after years and years of lunacy,
Jeff is smart...
...because it turns out he'd been
sleeping in his van for years...
...with the engine still running.
The guy wasn't a moron.
He was actually brain damaged.
Two of our Buy Morons
actually contracted scurvy.
- What? Scurvy?
- Yeah.
Turns out they'd been subsisting solely
on the candy from the snack aisle.
They didn't even know
anything was wrong...
...until they started seeing
their teeth in the jujubes.
Man, the, uh, Buy More never fails
to provide dinner table fodder.
My kids ask for funny customer stories
every night at bed.
Hey, hey, hey. Best job ever.
- Cheers.
- Who needs another round?
- I do.
- Me, me, me.
I'll come with you.
- I kind of love it here.
- I know.
They're, like,
the nicest people in the world.
We've checked everybody...
...and everyone is exactly
who they say they are. It's amazing.
And here we are, lying, all suspicious.
I think Jane wants to be my friend.
She asked me out for coffee, heh.
- She's the Viper.
- What? No, no, no.
She passed the test.
And I think that she just really likes me.
Honey, you're right. Of course.
Of course she does.
Duh. It's just my stupid
suspicious spy brain.
It doesn't matter anyway.
I'm not really sure what type
of friendship is founded on lies.
But we should focus anyway.
I'm sure the Viper is zeroed in on you
by now.
We need to lure him out
and get you alone and vulnerable.
Ladies and gentlemen,
ladies and gentlemen.
- What?
I've had too many,
I'm going to bed.
- Come on, Morgan.
- No, no, no.
Hey, there's poker later and probably
another less-clothed swim party.
I would love nothing more than to
see you do a naked cannonball, Irv.
Keep it on, keep it on, keep it on.
I need to lie down.
- I think the sciatica's acting up.
- Yeah. I think I'll call it too.
Bob. What?
- There we go.
- Good night.
- Come on. See you tomorrow.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I gotta call my family
before they hit the hay.
Yeah, one of my kids
had a big game today.
Oh.
That's a lie, Chuck.
Well, no, Omaha's no St. Louis,
but we have a good time.
Sally, in her day, ooh, what a looker.
Yeah, Corn Princess in 1987.
- Nope, still lying.
- Oh, heh, well, this is me.
Oh.
Guess I'm just gonna be in here.
All by my lonesome.
Sleep tight.
Don't let the bedbugs bite.
- Grimes.
- Hmm?
I shouldn't have joked about bedbugs.
They cost the hospitality industry
millions of dollars a year.
Wrong thing to say.
Yep. I'm alone and vulnerable.
Hello, Sarah. Come in.
I've been watching you.
You've got a cute little persona
going on.
But I can spot a girl in a costume.
You know, I'm not what I seem, either.
Yeah. I like costumes, too.
You're not going anywhere
until you hippity-hop over here.
It's party time.
It was the bartender.
Yeah, not everybody here is normal.
Huh.
Whoo! Yes. I'm not gonna die.
Hey, Viper. Suck it.
- Can I go home now?
- Yeah, buddy. You're good.
We're not letting this guy go till he
acknowledges the hit's off.
Which he's being very stubborn
about doing, I might add.
Go ahead, nod your head. Do it.
Yep, hit's off. No more killy-killy.
This is not how it's done, hmm?
First, we have to get Decker
to rescind the kill order...
...but we'll handle that, Morgan,
so, you know, I think you're free to go.
And if you go anywhere near Alex,
you're gonna be on another hit list. Hmm?
- I'm sorry, buddy. You doing okay?
- Yeah. You know.
I wish he'd give me the number
so I can explain to her.
Don't give up, you know? You gotta
keep trying. He's a tough one to crack.
You know, uh...
It's easier to ask forgiveness
than permission.
- Uh, truer words have never been spoken.
- A stitch in time saves nine.
Mm-hm, lead a horse to water.
Just...
Hmm.
Hey, I gotta make a call.
Jane asked me for a drink, and this is
gonna take a while, so I have to...
No, no, no. Go. Casey and I
can take care of the Viper handoff.
Really? You mean, like, I can go
and have an actual normal friend?
We saved a man's life
not having to use the Intersect...
...just awesome husband-wife spy
work.
Maybe we can have some
normal friends, too.
Okay. Well, I'm going to go have a drink
with a friend like a real live person.
- Have a great time.
- Thanks.
Jeff, you have shown incredible
improvement in motor skills...
...language ability, reflexes, memory.
- It's like you're an actual person now.
- Thank you.
I have started to see
a lot of things more clearly.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, Mommy.
Hi, muffin. Mommy missed you.
Yes, she did.
I've never seen
such a perfect case study...
...for an article on effects of
multiyear carbon monoxide poisoning.
We could get published.
Why don't you come by
the hospital? We'll look.
Let me see your belly.
Let me see your belly. I could eat you.
Let's go out here
and see some fun stuff.
Your woman is not happy.
- What are you talking about?
- Fresh air has made me intuitive.
That woman
wants to be home with her child.
She'll never say it, but it's true.
- Alex.
- I am not here to talk to you.
- I'm here to see my dad.
- I just wanted to apologize, that's all.
There's nothing you can say
to make it okay.
You are just not the man
I thought I loved.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey. Hey.
You want the truth? You ready?
I had a supercomputer in my head,
okay? And it was melting my brain.
Keep walking. Normal thoughts.
So how do you like
working private sector?
It's hard, right?
Figuring everything out...
...choosing the right small business
accounting program.
You're probably not feeling too chatty.
Probably feeling bad we took down
the best so easily.
Probably too easily.
We were supposed to catch you.
- Sarah, wait. Don't move.
- Oh, my God. What?
We're trying to be normal and all...
...but if we were in spy mode we'd
think it was interesting timing...
...that you made a new friend...
- I'm Jane.
Who wanted to hang out
with you immediately post-mission.
A new friend who was as good as I was
at passing a lie detector.
And we might wonder if the Viper
didn't use a decoy, like we did...
...to make Morgan feel safe
and come out of hiding.
And we might think that
getting rid of his guards by, say...
...planting a car bomb
might be a really great way to go.
Okay, here's a spy thought:
Don't move your foot.
Okay.
I'm looking for Morgan Grimes.
You have to understand this
all happened a couple years ago.
I can't give you names, details
because it's confidential.
But there were e-mails
and there were supercomputers.
It wound up in my brain.
And I zoomed.
My word, not theirs. The supercomputer
that I got was flawed...
...which is why all this behavior...
...was happening. I'm sorry.
You have to believe me.
My brain was melting. You know?
You look overwhelmed.
I'll let you process that.
I'm sure the manager's around
here somewhere.
- I'll find him.
- Got to go now.
No, Morgan. What are you doing?
Seriously. You always do this.
You little barbarian son of a bitch.
Oh. Help, help. Help.
Skip, pull the fire alarm.
Someone plug the hose.
Everyone run to safety. I'm saving you.
No apologies for any of this, Jeffrey.
I just needed you back, man.
Pineapple.
Yep. Yep. That's a bomb.
And it's a nice one.
Okay.
Listen to me.
This is what's happening, okay?
There is an elusive assassin
and she is hunting me, okay?
- You are legitimately insane.
- What? No. No, no, no.
Please, please, look, look, look.
- Okay. It's all right, stay calm.
- Okay, she's there.
I know, I know.
I'm gonna rip your face off.
No. Shh, Casey, listen to me.
We have the wrong person.
The real Viper is a lady.
And she's here, hunting us.
Northeast corner of the store.
Get Alex to the broom closet.
You wanna live,
you're gonna take care of my daughter.
Of course. Listen to me.
We're gonna move
when I say move, okay?
Move.
I'm getting some texts.
Jane is in the Buy More
and Casey's locked in the Castle.
We'll be there
in less than 90 seconds.
Okay.
Uh, you remember how to do this, right?
Yeah. Yeah. Maybe, kind of, yeah.
I think so. It's normally the red wire.
Or the green wire. It's normally the red
or the green wire, I'm not really sure.
- I want you to wait in here.
- Okay.
Don't you move till I get back.
She's after me.
- I'm not gonna put you in danger.
- Okay.
I love you.
You don't have to say it back at me.
Would've been romantic but it's fine.
It's fine. Good.
I can't believe I trusted Jane
to be who she said.
I must have been desperate
for a friend.
Oh, hey, hey.
Don't beat yourself up.
And don't move your foot, really,
because this is a very nasty bomb.
- Up with the leg.
- Okay.
Keep that leg. Up with that leg.
There we go. There we are.
- Hello.
- Jane?
Jane, it's Sarah.
I'm so sorry I'm running late.
I'm having a really bad day and
I just need somebody to talk to.
Well, just come to the restaurant.
We'll workshop it.
No, I'm so upset,
I don't think I can drive.
Well, just get in the car,
turn it on and get here.
- I can't. My hands are shaking.
- Honey, look, I'm really sorry, okay?
I'm not gonna be able to help you
right now.
- I gotta go.
- No, wait.
Jane, I want to tell you something.
I feel really badly.
You've been so open and honest
and sweet with me...
...and I'm excited to have a new friend.
- Yeah?
But I've been lying to you.
About a couple of things.
I'm a spy. Boy, it feels good
to say that to a real friend.
You're amazing at what you do.
I really trusted you.
- And I don't do that very often.
- Well, you shouldn't.
Wait, wait, stop. I have your bomb.
Which means it's disarmed. Bye.
Thanks. I thought
maybe stepping into the middle of this...
...might have been a bad idea
after all, so...
I miss knowing kung fu.
Remarkable work.
The Viper's perfect record
has been broken.
Uh, boom.
- Suck it.
- Sorry about that, sir.
I'm obviously relieved
the mix-up was righted.
I would never want you
to complete your mission...
...after the CIA called it off.
I am one of the good guys.
In front of these witnesses,
on a recorded feed, the hit is off?
Yes. It's official, the hit is off.
All right, our business here is done.
Good luck running a spy business
with no Intersect, huh?
See you never.
He's a quippy bastard.
- Can someone get us out of this hole?
- My pleasure. Follow me.
- Decker took that well.
- Yeah, he did.
I'll take care of it.
- So we need to talk.
- Whatever.
We're no longer friends, I get it.
Like I care.
I do care.
I wish you were a better person.
But unfortunately, you need to learn
there are repercussions for your actions.
- Hmm.
- So you're under arrest.
What?
- For what?
- Attempted homicide.
Jeff.
Jeffrey.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will be used
against you in a court of law.
Morgan, we're not gonna
get back together.
You told me you were done
with spy life...
...and clearly you lied to me
in a million different ways.
You're my hero,
but you are not my boyfriend.
- Okay.
- I'm sorry.
- No, it's okay. I get it.
- But, um, we can still be friends.
And I'm really glad
we're both here tonight.
Me too.
We're putting out some hors d'oeuvres
if you guys wanna come in.
- Is my dad here yet?
- Uh, he's coming a little late.
You haven't said anything yet
that made me think you're still the man.
I have a reputation to repair.
This will get done.
You need to understand, however,
that I have to protect my cover.
Obviously. Which means...
Neutralizing everyone
who knows who I am.
Walker, Grimes, Casey,
Bartowski, Casey's daughter.
You have approval on everyone
but Bartowski and Walker.
Now get it done.
John Casey.
Your life is over if you...
So tell me about your day.
Fun parts only, please.
Hmm. Fun parts only. Well, this week,
I had to pose as Morgan Grimes. Heh.
You would need some serious hormone
injections to get a beard like that.
Okay, okay. Fortunately for me,
my wife likes me baby smooth.
I do. My husband was the best
human target a wife could ever ask for.
Aw, this is fun.
Talking openly about our days.
- It's the best.
- Hey, everybody.
- Sorry, I'm late.
- No, perfect timing.
- We're about to sit down. I'll trade you.
- Thanks.
Hey, Dad. Where were you?
- Oh, just had an errand to run, heh.
- Oh.
May I? Cheers.
Uh, I'd like to make a toast.
Chuck and I have been a little sad
this week that we aren't normal people.
I've been having a hard time
with the fact I have no real friends.
But I look around here
at all of you today and I realize...
...that because of Chuck, I do.
Nobody in the world is closer than
we all are. So, thank you and cheers.
Cheers.
I, too, have an announcement.
- I'm going back to work.
- Well, what?
Wait, I thought you were happy
at home.
No, I was just putting on a front,
you know? I was going nuts.
Ellie is stepping up and taking care
of baby Clara for a while.
Yes, it was too soon for me to go back,
anyway. I missed her too much.
Yeah. She's totally saving me.
One more mommy and me class,
I would've lost my mind.
- Hey.
Ahem. I wanted to tell you that you could
probably, uh, ixnay on the killing me thing.
Because I'm not gonna bother
Alex anymore.
Hmm. You should move back in.
- Really?
Uh-huh.
- Got you a gift.
- Come on, really?
- Indiana Jones.
Mm-hm.
- I like these?
- You did.
Holding out on me?
Is this the only three?
You're not, like, keeping the good ones
for yourself or...
- There's just the three.
- Thanks, man.
Hey. I got it. Ahem.
- Decker, what is this?
- We're looking for John Casey.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
John Casey. You're under arrest.
For murder.