Here's a couple things you might
need to know or maybe just forgot.
- Why'd you bring us here?
- I need you to do a job for me.
We've been tracking a computer
super-virus named the Omen.
Bring it back to me, Casey goes free.
The virus is too dangerous to be released
to the world. It could wipe out everything.
- What do you plan to do with it?
- What do you plan to do with it, John?
You're gonna break me
out of here alone?
Prisoner transfer, Section 38.
- Give me one reason not to kill you.
- It'll only further prove your guilt.
- Let's go right now.
- Hey, Decker, you forgetting something?
So, Verbanski blew up Decker.
That was pretty messed up.
Now the CIA wants to frame me
for something awful. That's bad too.
But there is something else
going on here.
Something personal.
Who's after us, Sarah?
I don't know. We'll get the team together
and figure this out.
They were supposed to be here
an hour ago. Did they get caught?
You wanna explain to me
what I'm doing in the ducts of Castle?
This is our Castle, our secret base.
Maybe my plan was
a bit overly cautious, okay?
But Verbanski
was very complimentary of it.
- Egh. Should have gone in the front door.
- Whoa, you're a fugitive, okay?
There's a mysterious CIA plot to destroy
you, Chuck and Sarah. Perhaps even me.
Agh, keep your ego in check,
will you, Grimes?
Okay. What if, though?
- What if Castle's been compromised?
- That's...
Actually a very fine point.
Good job on the breakout.
That was actually...
I'm proud of you, moron.
Did you just compliment me
and insult me?
We're here.
Chuck, hey. Stand back.
Sorry we're late.
Someone needed a sandwich.
Then someone needed a fruit cup, so...
Well, we're just happy
that you're back.
- Where's Verbanski?
- Well, since she disposed of Decker...
...she felt it best to stay out
of the country till things die down.
Just when things were getting going
between you two.
So painful. I mean, that hurts.
Man, it's tough.
- I just said what I was thinking out loud.
- I'm sorry, Casey.
Yeah, she was a hell of a woman.
Still is. She's not dead and neither am I.
Let's get on with it.
Right. Well, before Decker blew up,
he was after this, the Omen...
...a computer virus that can erase
100 zettabytes of data per second.
Whoa, 100 zettabytes?
Is that a real thing?
It could take down the Internet,
crash planes...
...and erase every database in the world.
Yeah, it's real.
If the people trying to frame Chuck are
inside the CIA, we need to find Beckman.
Or she can find you.
This is an official communiqué.
I requested to tell you myself.
For the murder of Agent Decker...
...as well as the crime of treason
against the United States...
...the CIA is placing all of you
under arrest.
- What? General, how can you do this?
- I'd ask your team the same.
If you know what's good for you,
you'll stay put. Agents are on the way.
I put my trust in you for years
and look what you've become: Traitors.
Gen... How could she...?
Even Beckman's against us?
How did this happen?
You clever dame.
- What are you doing?
- She's amazing.
What are you talking about?
Look, Morse code. She was giving us
a warning, telling us to run.
We have exactly five minutes
before the CIA charges in.
- What? She said all that?
- We need to get out of here.
Let's get to my father's cabin and access
the CIA database using his Orion system.
- Find out who's after us.
- I'll find Beckman.
Let you know
when I found something.
Look, I know we've been chased before,
but I got a bad feeling about this.
It's like we're being hunted.
- Chuck, it's okay. We can handle it.
- Damn right.
But if we are, I need to get
to the apartment, wipe my computer.
Too dangerous. The complex
is probably surrounded by agents.
Then I go.
Makes sense. I'm not a fugitive.
They're not hunting me. I can do this.
Okay, I'll show you what to do.
You all right?
- You ready to go?
- Yeah.
Babe, you ready to go?
Don't come in here.
I'm still getting ready.
Babe?
Okay, ready.
Wow.
Heh, it is so awesome
that you're my wife.
Thank you. Honey, are you sure
Clara's gonna be okay?
Babe, Clara's fine.
She's with my parents.
This is what we wanted, remember?
Fancy dinner, nice hotel.
Mini vacay.
Right. Been way too long since
we've had time just the two of us.
It's gonna be a great night, I promise.
And I have a little surprise for you.
Mm.
I might have a little surprise
for you too.
One more move and I will end you.
Damn it.
And I was trying to be discreet.
- Man.
- Morgan?
- Yeah, yeah, it's me.
- Morgan.
What are you doing
breaking into your own apartment?
Doing a favor for your dad.
And not trying to be seen, but, heh...
We broke him out of jail.
The CIA's sort of hunting him.
I know. The authorities contacted me.
I just thought maybe he would be here.
No, the whole team's on the lam.
He's not coming back here.
Not for a while, anyway. But, uh, okay.
How have you been?
Are you all right?
Go, I got it.
Okay.
Please. Whoa, yeah, sure.
I mean, you could at least wipe your feet
before you come traipsing through here.
Robyn Cunnings. Special agent, CIA.
I'm looking for John Casey
and the rest of your team.
Where are they?
I don't know.
Technically I'm not part
of the spy team anymore, so I...
What are you two doing here, anyway?
He's my boyfriend. You know,
we're just hanging out at the apartment.
The apartment that I live in.
Yeah, with her father.
- You live with your girlfriend's father?
- Yes, I do. Yes, I do.
Seems a little awkward, sure,
but it works, you know, for us.
- It's clear. He's not here.
- See? We told you.
We don't know where my dad is.
But I want him safe. He's a good man.
Good men don't go on the run.
If you see him or help him,
you'll be aiding and abetting a fugitive.
Enjoy the rest of your evening.
We'll be right outside.
Nice. That was good. You all right?
- Yeah.
- You did great. It was perfect.
- I'm your boyfriend, huh?
- Ugh, that was a lie, Morgan.
Don't get so excited.
Not that excited.
I know we'll fix this, but do you think
they'll bring Ellie in for questioning?
- Man, I wish I could call her.
- I know.
But they could've tapped her phone
and we don't want her implicated.
Right, right, right.
We're not staying at this cabin, right?
This thing's gonna blow over.
- I'm not disappearing on my sister, am I?
- No, why would you say that?
Us wanted by the CIA, my family history.
I'm just saying.
We won't disappear like your parents.
We're just hiding out for a little while.
Everyone's gonna be fine.
Reservation for two under Woodcomb.
I'm sorry, I don't have
a reservation under that name.
Oh, you know what?
Check "Bartowski."
Boss, we've got a lock
on the Bartowskis.
Excellent. Let's get on it, then.
I used Chuck's Open Table account.
He loves the points.
Here we are. Table for two.
Mr. And Mrs. Bartowski, right this way.
- To a very special night.
- And a few little surprises.
Babe, you look beautiful.
Thank you.
I, uh, wanted something a little different,
so I borrowed a dress from Sarah.
She wore it on a mission
in Bulgaria once. How wild is that?
Ever wonder what it would be like if we
lived a life of mystery and adventure?
- Like Chuck and Sarah?
- Like spies.
Well, you know,
spy work does run in our family.
There's no reason why you and I
can't pretend to be spies for tonight.
Man, I'm glad we're not on the lam
forever, because I gotta tell you...
...standing here, I'm feeling a little bit
like I'm becoming my father.
I imagine this is what he felt like
the first day he had to leave us.
- All alone in exile.
- That won't happen.
- Not if I've got anything to do with it.
- It's like my family's thing or something.
- The Bartowski Curse.
- The what?
Every Bartowski
has put their family in danger...
...then had to leave them
in order to protect them, and I'm next.
Look, there is no such thing
as the Bartowski Curse.
You're not gonna be like
your father. You know why?
Because you've got me.
You're not alone.
Access granted.
Okay, okay. It worked.
We're in the CIA's mainframe.
Okay, let's figure out
who Decker was working for.
Who's behind this.
There's an active case file,
but no lead agent listed.
Not even the CIA knows who's in charge.
It's a dead end.
So we're gonna be spies?
What do you say, Six Pack,
are you in?
Well, all right, Hot Mama.
Maybe we should come up with
a code word in case things get too hot.
How about "martini"?
And we can communicate
with hand gestures.
When we need to send a signal
to one another...
...we can just tug on our ear like so.
Babe, you look so cool
when you do that.
May I take these plates?
Well, if you'll excuse me,
it's time to bring out your surprise.
Copy that.
Wait. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
- They have an ID on the target.
- It says they found us.
They're closing in. Gotta get out of here.
We have to run, for real this time.
Sarah, this is exactly what
I was afraid of.
I'm sorry.
I know that you're not ready for this.
Nobody's ever ready
for something like this. We gotta go.
- Well, how long are we talking here?
- I don't know.
But this has nothing to do
with your parents. It has to do with us.
Trust me.
I've been on the run my entire life.
And the only way this is gonna work
is if we stick together, okay?
Okay, okay, fine, but there's one thing
I can't leave without.
- What?
- My P.A.N.T.S.
Your pants?
You got it.
I will get you your P.A.N.T.S.
It would be an honor.
Hey, listen. I love you, man.
Chuck's going on the run
and needs pants?
Well, they're his secret P.A.N.T.S.
You know what?
It's best I just show you mine.
Watch your hand. Ready?
Okay, here you go.
What's so special about them?
Oh, not so fast. Not so fast.
Since we were kids,
Chuck and I each had a box of P.A.N.T.S.
Private Artifacts Never to Share.
We kind of went through
an acronym phase. You know. Anyways.
This is where we kept
our most sacred possessions.
- In case of a fire, this is what we save.
- And you both have these?
Well, you know,
Chuck's generally neurotic.
And I was just terrified
of my house burning down...
...since, you know,
my house burned down.
Here we go, 2000 Sangiovese.
Little surprise for the wife.
Same bottle we had at our wedding.
- She is gonna love it.
- I'm thrilled for you, really.
Perfect.
You okay, bro?
Project Eagle is in effect. I'm here to take
you and your wife to a secret location.
We should leave quickly.
Project Eagle?
Your limo's just outside.
I'll be waiting there for you and your wife.
My wife. Project Eagle, mm? Right. Heh.
Be right there.
Are we surrounded?
Are there too many guys?
No, that's just it.
There's nobody out there.
- Could they have made a mistake?
- They must have.
- What's the matter?
- Nothing. Just kind of weird.
It's a reminder from Open Table to review
my dining experience from tonight.
- Ellie must have used your account.
- She always does. I love the points!
That means the operatives think
that Ellie and Devon...
Are us.
- Oh.
- Aw, come on, babe...
...you're harshing on my spy vibe.
I'm sorry, I thought it was off.
There. Done.
- Straight to voice mail again.
- No answer from Devon either.
Oh, God. Sarah,
I think Ellie and Awesome were taken.
- Honey, this is...
- Exactly what we needed.
Yes.
All my ex's live in Texas
And Texas is the place
I'd dearly love to be
Took you long enough to find me.
This is where we come
in our darkest hours.
Iran-Contra, Nicaragua.
The Clinton years.
A group inside the CIA
is conspiring to destroy Chuck.
- Who's behind it?
- I don't know.
I need one of the conspirators.
In the meantime...
...I'm doing everything I can
to help Chuck and Sarah from here.
But they're being hunted as we speak.
And so is their family.
- Ha!
- This is totally great.
God, this car is so rad, babe. Ha, ha.
- Where we going, anyway?
- Well, I don't know, Sixer. You tell me.
You, uh... You sure your driver
has his livery license?
- My driver? This is your surprise.
- My surprise?
My surprise was a bottle of Sangiovese
at the restaurant.
Are you telling me
neither one of us booked this car?
Must be some mistake.
We'll just talk to him.
- No, no, no, don't do that.
- What? Why?
Project Eagle, the limo. What if
we open that thing and he shoots us?
- I've seen it in the movies.
- Ha, ha...
Babe,
what if we're on a real spy mission?
- Martini!
Please, tell me you're not about
to do something foolish.
Me, foolish? No. Just preparing the gear
I need to get Chuck's P.A.N.T. S...
...without being seen by those large
scary agents waiting outside for us.
And how exactly are you planning
on doing that?
That's easy. Hop out the side window.
Climb onto the roof.
Shoot a cord to Chuck's.
Zip-line across. Sneak into the patio.
Grab Chuck's P.A.N.T.S.
In and out, never even being seen.
Easy. At least it was...
...when I had a computer in my brain.
- That is crazy.
Not only are you gonna get caught,
but you'll probably break your neck.
Oh, thanks. Look.
I know I was a jerk
and I know that you're mad at me.
And I deserve that, okay?
I've made many, many poor decisions.
This is not one of them, okay?
I have to help my friend.
Morgan, wait. I have a better idea.
Hi. Yes, um,
I'd like to report an emergency.
Yeah, my crazy ex-boyfriend
is outside my house.
I think he might do something
really dangerous.
Yeah, that's right.
Okay, he's 6 feet tall and he has
blond hair and he's wearing a black suit.
Could you hurry, please?
Because I'm really, really scared.
Thank you.
There. Okay,
so as soon as you hear the sirens, just go.
- I think I bought you about 10 minutes.
- That was...
...diabolical.
- Honey, we have to form a plan.
- Babe, deep breath.
It's gonna be okay. I have an idea.
- Okay, I'm listening.
- All right.
We need to dive out of the car.
We'll be fine.
- All we need is a sturdy combat roll.
- Ah, I can't do it.
Of course you can.
You have done way harder things.
- We need to just open the door, roll out.
- You don't understand.
I went to Agent Provocateur
and got an outfit.
The panties were optional
and I didn't opt to wear them.
- Really?
- Surprise.
Whoa.
Casey. Casey, finally.
We got big problems.
Ellie and Awesome were abducted.
- Yeah, I know.
- You know?
Yeah.
They were taken by Beckman's men.
- Don't worry. She's helping us.
- Oh, thank God.
We have to get her agent
on the phone, okay?
Ellie and Awesome are probably
freaking out. I'll meet up with the car...
...bring them to Beckman myself.
- Roger that.
Yes, general?
- What kind of lingerie was it again?
- Devon, concentrate!
Okay. Babe, babe,
the car is slowing down. We can do this.
Just like Chuck and Sarah.
Tuck and roll. Okay, ready?
Ready. No peeking.
One, two, three!
- Babe, babe, are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
We gotta get out of here.
General, we may have a problem.
See? They're safe with Beckman's men.
We have nothing to worry about.
I'll track them down
and I'll call you back.
Looks like you lost your passengers.
Robyn, what are you doing here?
Oh, Simms.
- I think we lost him.
- Yeah, for now.
Oh, God!
Mr. And Mrs. Bartowski.
No, there's a mistake, okay?
We're the Woodcombs.
Chuck's my brother, though.
Who are you?
Robyn Cunnings, special agent
with the CIA. Somebody's after you.
- Don't worry. I work with your brother.
- You work with Chuck? Where's Chuck?
He's on his way, but I was closer,
so he sent me to get you.
Please, you have to come
with us immediately.
I'm here to help.
Okay, let's go.
Oh, no, is that?
Sarah, where are they?
Thank you.
No, thank you, Mr. Woodcomb.
It's now or never, Morgan.
Move like the wind.
The coded message
was from Decker's men.
They were following Ellie and Awesome,
mistaking them for us.
They shot Simms to cover their tracks.
We have to find whoever is in charge
and stop this.
If they think Ellie and Awesome know
about the Omen, they'll torture them.
Why are we sitting here?
What's the plan?
I'm sorry, Chuck, but for now, we wait.
- They'll call to set up a meet.
- How can we just wait?
Ellie and Awesome are probably having
their fingernails ripped out as we speak.
Babe, it's like a real masseuse.
I can literally feel her fingers
on my spine.
Or his or whoever's, but you know.
- Gotta get one of these in the living room.
- Sounds great.
Mr. And Mrs. Woodcomb, again,
I'm so sorry for the inconvenience.
Your brother will pick you up soon.
In the meantime,
I hope these accommodations suffice.
We reserve this room
only for the most regarded of spies.
Can I offer you anything to drink?
A soda pop? Some water, perhaps?
Actually, we were on a date tonight.
So some wine, if possible.
Sangiovese, perhaps?
It would be my pleasure.
Bring that insufferable woman
a bottle of wine...
...and get me Chuck Bartowski
on the phone.
Oh. Ellie, thank God.
Lovely sister you have.
Husband's not so bad, either.
Can't say I'm fond of them
long-term, though.
I don't know who the hell you are, but if
you touch one hair on my sister's head...
Come on, Chuck. Spare us both.
They're comfortable for now
and I prefer it stay that way.
But if things get complicated,
I can't guarantee their safety.
Let me tell you
how this is gonna work.
What'd they say?
We have three hours
to deliver the Omen...
...or they kill Ellie and Awesome.
Mm.
- They're bluffing.
- We need to start making a fake to deliver.
What if they figure out it's a fake?
I know you're scared,
but we just can't hand over a weapon.
It's bigger than us, Bartowski.
It's national security.
I promise we will take
every precaution.
I will not let them do anything
to your sister.
You guys are the pros.
You know what you're doing.
So let's go with the fake.
Hey.
Look, I know you're concerned.
Talk to me.
I'm scared. This is a mistake.
This whole plan is a mistake.
Giving them a fake virus is a mistake.
Ellie and Awesome are in danger.
We need to give them the real virus
to get them back. I have to do it alone.
You don't have to do it alone.
There are people here who are with you.
I'm with you,
and I happen to think you're right.
This is my curse. Don't you understand?
People I love are in danger. It's my fault.
- I need to fix it.
- Forget the curse.
I'll go convince Casey and Beckman
that your plan is the right thing to do.
Then we'll go together.
You heard them. They're...
They'll never be on board with this.
Trust me. I will talk to them.
- And what if they say no?
- It's gonna take some time, okay?
- Okay, fine. I'll wait right here.
- Okay.
Honey, I can't find my phone.
Probably just fell out
when we rolled out of the car.
Yeah, you're probably right.
I'm sorry, there was no Sangiovese.
But, uh, I managed to rustle up
some Chardonnay.
My apologies if it's not that good.
It's only 2009.
No worries, bro. This'll be fine.
Hardly. I forgot the ice.
Oh.
But we did find this in the car.
Oh, heh.
Thank you.
See, babe?
All's well that ends well, huh?
Right. Heh.
- Anyway, I'll go get the ice.
- Okay.
- What the hell are you doing?
- They're gonna kill us.
What? He just brought us wine.
No, I've been in this situation before.
The CIA doesn't bring you wine.
They stole my phone
and they called Chuck with it.
So it's clearly some
sort of ransom situation.
I don't know... We gotta find another way
to get out of here.
I think we're making a mistake.
Ellie and Awesome are not spies.
They're civilians.
We know what this group is capable of.
Fake could put them over the edge.
They're savages.
Reckless and single-minded.
I think we need to support Chuck.
This is his family
and it's my family too now...
...and we need to do everything
we can to protect them.
Let's get the Omen and find Chuck.
Boss, I think you need to look at this.
Hi, there. It's me, Chuck Bartowski.
From the phone call?
Right on time.
Well, hand over the Omen.
You didn't think I was actually dumb
enough to bring it with me, did you?
It's hidden.
Release my family
or you can spend the rest of your lives...
...searching for a virus
you're never gonna find.
Follow me.
What the hell? How did this happen?
I guess you've never met my sister.
Upstairs clear.
No sign of the Woodcombs.
Copy that.
Orders are shoot to kill on sight.
- This is really hardcore.
- I told you.
I'm not giving you anything until I know
my sister and her husband are safe.
Ha!
You're not exactly in a position
to bargain now, are you?
There's something
I'm known for, Chuck.
Some people call it torture.
I like to think of it
as more of an art form.
You're going to give me
exactly what I want.
And I'm very, very good at this.
- Honey, Chuck came to save us.
- He's in trouble, babe.
- We have to help him.
- We can't just go down there.
- We need a tactical advantage.
- Okay.
I can handle anything
you throw at me.
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
They always say that.
So sad.
Bring out the Toy.
Whoa, whoa, really? Really?
That's the Toy?
I don't think children should be involved
with that device in any way, shape or form.
Shh, shh.
Okay, all the lights are hooked up
to that electrical panel.
If we can get that guard away, we can
short the circuits, cause a blackout.
That's genius, babe.
Okay, okay, you cause a distraction.
I'll blow the power
and I'll go grab Chuck.
We can do this, honey. Like real spies.
Babe, right now we are real spies.
Do you ever cry, Chuck?
Sometimes,
particularly during sports movies.
Field of Dreams is just gut-wrenching,
but also uplifting.
A good cry is cathartic.
I need a piece of metal,
something to short the fuse.
Uh... Oh, here, here, here.
You can't jam metal
in the circuit breaker.
- You're gonna burn your hands.
- Right, I need something to insulate it.
- Here, shirt.
- Right, shirt.
Whoa.
- You look hot.
- So do you.
- I love you.
- Yeah.
One last chance.
Omen or pain?
The Omen or pain?
Shouldn't there be a third option? Heh.
What are you doing?
- Who, me?
- Where's your shirt?
Heh. It's kind of a long story.
Let me tell you the short one.
This is going to be very, very painful.
Here we go.
Hey!
What was that?
Sorry, Chuck.
There's usually a backup generator.
Oh.
Just FYI.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe he'd do the drop
on his own without me.
He thinks it's the Bartowski Curse, that
he can protect me by leaving me behind.
- And instead, he's walking into a trap.
- Let's just hope he's smart.
If he gives up the Omen,
they're all dead.
Thanks for trying to save me.
I really do appreciate it.
No sweat, man. It just kind of
seemed like the right thing to do.
Are you done?
Tell me where you hid the Omen
or I permanently change this man's face.
Not the face. No.
Out the front doors, 30 paces south,
under the yellow rosebush to the right.
You're joking.
You're not joking.
Oh, my God. Thank you.
- It's gonna be okay.
- Rescuing Bartowskis is our business.
I'm a little upset I didn't get
to use the Toy. It's truly my favorite part.
Do you have any idea
how much damage that virus will cause?
In truth, Chuck,
the virus is just a piece of the plan.
- What do you mean?
- Means I don't know.
I'm just doing my job,
cleaning up Decker's mess.
- I release the virus and then I'm done.
- What happens now?
That's the real surprise, isn't it?
You've pissed off
a lot of powerful people, Chuck.
There. The Omen is officially
unleashed upon the world.
Sorry, I'm afraid
I don't need you anymore.
You still don't know
who you're dealing with, do you?
Right now there's a spy in your midst.
She'll take you and all your men down
to save her husband.
Your sister? The doctor?
Are you kidding me? Again?
All clear.
- Put down the gun.
- Now.
Walker. Casey.
- I give up.
- Robyn Cunnings.
You don't get off that easy.
Safe. Come on out.
Chuck. Devon, honey, are you okay?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm good, I'm good.
Mm. Mm, I'm just really cold.
I love you. Mm, I love you.
We are so not meant to be spies.
Don't worry. I'm fine too, really.
I love you so much.
- You're upset. I can see you're upset.
- This isn't over.
Hey, Sarah... Guys?
I'm still... I'm still tied.
I'm still bound.
Little help.
Looks like we found a conspirator.
You're gonna tell me everything.
What exactly the plan is.
Who you're working for. All of it.
I have nothing to say to you.
You're not my general.
You know, we found something
interesting at the factory.
I'm very excited to see how it works.
I believe you call it the Toy.
Robyn has confessed
to the conspiracy.
I am happy to say
on behalf of the U.S. Government...
...all charges against this team
have been dropped.
Oh, and Casey, your record shall
be expunged. You're free to go home.
Hmm.
General, that's all fantastic news,
uh, but what about the Omen virus?
- Who did Robyn work for?
- Robyn didn't know.
But we have our top people working on
the virus. For now, well done, team.
It was a bit like old times, wasn't it?
So...
...no living on the lam,
running from the law.
Sounded a little romantic, didn't it?
- You're still mad?
- You left without me.
I'm sorry, Sarah.
I'm sorry. It was stupid.
I didn't wanna take you down with me...
...and my family's curse.
- There is no curse.
You're not your father. You're not fated
to be alone or hurt anybody.
Those things happen because of the
choices that people make, that you make.
You're right. I'll never do it again,
leave without you.
The Bartowski Family Curse ends here,
and not with me, with us.
If you ever go out alone again,
just remember, I'm a trained assassin.
- Noted.
- Good.
Wouldn't shoot me, would you?
Yeah? Great news, man.
The agents are dispersing.
I wonder what's going on.
Yup, you got it, Chuck.
Mission aborted.
I'll see you soon. Okay.
Great news. We're not on the lam.
- Don't need Chuck's P.A.N.T.S.
- That's great.
But you just got it.
It's all right. I'll shoot over to the
apartment and put it back. No problem.
Just gotta ask,
what's in Chuck's P.A.N.T. S?
No, no, no. Not allowed.
There's something
I can show you, however.
I want you to have this. Uh...
You know, in case something
terrible has happened to me.
You keep an eye on it.
- Last night was nuts, huh?
- Heh. Crazy.
It was crazy. It was.
But despite all the craziness,
kind of a nice date.
Morgan, that was not a date.
Yeah, no, well,
not in the conventional sense, right?
- I should get going.
- Heh. Okay.
Okay. Um...
Thank you for everything.
- Yes. You too.
- All right.
Ugh.
I know that I am supposed to be tired
and a little freaked out...
...but last night was...
- Kind of incredible.
Yeah.
When you cracked that baddie over the
head with the bottle, that was pretty hot.
I was gonna say the same thing
when you took out that electrical panel.
What were you saying earlier
about Agent Provocateur?
- So all's forgiven?
- Maybe.
Okay, fine, all's forgiven.
Oh, something's wrong
with the computer.
You mean all the computers.
What is going on?
It's the Omen virus.
- It's affecting our entire system.
- It's not just our system.
That is the Internet.
That is everybody.
Oh, my God. This is all my fault.
I let it out and now the code is digging in.
It's hiding in every networked computer
in the world, just waiting.
Waiting for what?
I don't know.