I'm Chuck.
Here are things you need to know.
Come on. Carmichael Industries.
The independence and freedom
to do what we want.
I had no idea I had such strong feelings
for him. I have to disappear for a while.
All members of Carmichael Industries
have a position at the CIA.
If we go back,
it's just gonna be missions and secrets.
- I don't wanna go back.
- Okay. All we need is each other.
So, Mr. Carmichael...
...tell me...
...how do you feel like dying today?
Honestly?
You're gonna make me decide?
I find it says a lot about a man.
You know, I don't know.
Can't you just pick something?
- I've got a lot on my plate now.
- Like what?
Running your own company.
You know, there's a lot of responsibility
that comes with that.
Not that I don't care about
recovering spent nuclear fuel rods.
I do, but you gotta keep your eye
on the bottom line.
And with missions,
the bottom line is cash, man.
You know, with all these
private security firms out there...
...I think maybe I'm coming at this
the wrong way.
Maybe Carmichael Industries
needs a new hook.
Almost there, Chuck.
You're very good at talking.
Exactly. Any spy can sneak
into a building and snap a few necks.
But what are we doing right now,
the two of us?
We're talking
about our hopes and our dreams.
So you're spies that care?
You're a genius. That's inspired.
I'm gonna use that. Can I use that?
I'm glad I could help you, Mr. Carmichael.
I think I'll start
by cutting out your tongue.
That would be a horrible idea.
I would not do that.
Especially with a blunt object.
Drop it, baldy.
Oh, my God. Chuck, are you okay?
We just had a breakthrough.
Do you think it's okay to touch that
without a radiation suit?
Shouldn't be any worse
than a couple dozen X-rays.
We'll be fine
as long as no one's pregnant.
Ha. Okay, Casey,
I'm gonna let you take that. Let's go.
Don't tell me
you're getting sentimental.
Welcome back, Gertrude.
Good to see you, Gertrude.
I missed you, Gertrude.
Just nod your head
if you agree with any of this.
- Didn't hear you come in.
- That's because I took off my heels.
Among other things.
I guess you heard
you're not wanted for murder anymore.
Beckman put a lid
on that Decker thing.
Turns out, he was just a patsy, just...
I didn't fly halfway across the world
to be debriefed.
- Uh-uh.
- That's your job, John.
Mm.
I thought you said
you were coming to bed.
Have you been up all night long?
That bad guy got me thinking.
The one who tried
to cut your tongue out?
Our mission statement. We spend so
much time focusing on spy missions...
...that we've lost sight of the...
The, you know, uh, "what are we doing,
why are we here" mission.
Are you feeling okay?
That pizza that Morgan left
in the fridge is starting to turn.
I have never thought more clearly
in my life.
Ah. "The things we feel,
but do not share."
What can we, Carmichael Industries,
offer our clients...
...that other security firms can't? Go.
- Discount electronics?
- We care, Sarah. We care.
C-A-R-E. Clandestine Agents
Relating Emotionally. Get it?
- Uh...
- You hate it.
No, I think it's very interesting.
I just, uh...
I just feel very queasy suddenly.
Oh. Maybe the pizza was bad.
Who told you you could get dressed?
It's a work day, remember?
First of all, I have something for you.
Open it.
It's, uh, a sweater.
- Why is it so soft?
- It's cashmere.
It doesn't feel flame-retardant.
It's the perfect weight
for a winter night in South Beach.
- What's in South Beach?
- The second part of your surprise.
You and I are going to Miami...
...for three nights at the Maya.
In the middle of the week?
I can't just take off and sun my buns
in Miami. No, no, no.
I have a job. Two, technically.
Right, right. I get it.
Well, uh, I'll call you later.
- Okay.
- Good.
Hey.
Don't forget your new sweater.
Why are we looking at surveillance
footage from this morning?
I don't know yet.
Ever since I got my brain cleaned,
I've had this suspicion...
...that something's happening
behind the scenes.
Wait a minute.
Is that?
Bingo. John Casey wearing a deep
V-neck cashmere sweater.
Who are you, John Casey?
What's he doing sneaking around the
Buy More hours before his shift starts?
Maybe he's here to meet somebody.
Those two. Of course they're in on it.
In on what? They're probably doing it
in the home theater room like I do.
Not likely. I'm gonna need
some three-by-five cards, stat.
- Okay.
- Stat.
Ooh. I gotta say, I'm grooving
on that deep V, Casey.
What do you got here?
"Clandestine Agents
Relating Emotionally."
- CARE?
Mm-hm.
You really think
this is what our clients want?
A private security firm
that holds their hands...
...builds their self-esteem,
tells them they're special?
Isn't that what everyone wants,
Casey?
And it's no coincidence
that we booked our first client in forever...
...hours after I put my CARE statement
on our website.
- We have a website?
- Who's the client?
Hey.
I told you I was working.
- Yeah.
- So am I.
You're the...? She's the client?
May I remind you that you
have your own personal-security firm.
My personnel are stretched a bit thin.
Besides, your company
offers a level of service...
...that other companies
just don't offer.
- You care.
- We care.
And I intend
to take full advantage of that.
See?
Mission statement working already.
Rocky Falcone,
cologne-wearing scumbag.
He's murdered his way...
...into becoming one
of the biggest arms dealers in Miami.
We have some business that he insists
on conducting face-to-face.
- You'll act as protection.
- Where's the meet?
- Miami.
- Mm. What a coincidence.
Is it okay if I make the retainer fee...
...payable to Carmichael Industries?
- Sure.
Actually, I'm gonna pay the whole fee
right up front.
We haven't said yes to...
- Yes.
Meet you on the runway
bright and early.
That way
we can catch some pool time.
Sounds good. See you in the a.m.
What is your problem?
Yeah, seriously, what is your problem?
That was not very caring, Casey.
An above-board arms deal in Miami?
Sounds like a vacation.
Haven't you had enough kidnapping,
torture and bloodshed?
Besides, we haven't made a cent
in months...
...and your girlfriend
has deep pockets.
She's not my girlfriend.
Whatever you wanna call her,
she's our new client.
Pack your bags, lover boy.
We're going to South Beach.
Are you going out of town?
Yeah, something came up.
I have to leave for a couple days.
- Movie night.
- It's okay, we'll do it next week.
Don't worry,
I have already chosen what we'll watch.
"Downton Abbey.
An upstairs-downstairs costume drama
in early 1900s England."
Something tells me, not gonna be
a lot of explosions in that.
Are you kidding? What about the bombs
they drop on Edwardian convention?
Uh, listen, I... Yeah.
It's okay, you don't have to explain.
You're my hero.
Please pardon the speculative nature
of my research.
This is just the first stab at what I think
our coworkers are really up to.
Okay.
Obviously, some of my deductions
are quite tenuous...
...but if you'll bear with me for...
- You think they're spies?
Casey and Sarah? Yes.
Probably NSA or CIA.
Chuck is some kind of asset.
The only thing left to figure out
is this.
There's a fourth member of their team.
He's their secret weapon.
- What are you guys doing?
- He's seen too much. Grab him.
Okay. What are you guys doing?
Guys, guys, guys, guys, guys.
You see how he slipped out like that?
Maybe he's our mystery agent.
Wait, wait, easy. Easy there, Jeffrey.
I was with you
on the whole conspiracy theory...
...but seriously, this loser, a spy?
I mean, come on.
Yeah, I mean, come on.
He's gonna tell Chuck we're on to him.
Fine. We'll kill him.
What? No. Guys,
I'm not gonna tell Chuck squat, all right?
I've been conducting my own investigation
and you guys are absolutely right.
You nailed it.
There is a mystery agent.
I've tracked him down.
And, uh, heh, I got him.
Are you, uh...?
This is gonna blow your mind.
You're gonna be, like, "What?
There's no way he's, you know..."
But, boom, there he is.
If that's not James Bond,
I don't know what is, right?
Of course.
Hello, darling.
Oh, garçon, uh, another daiquiri for me.
- And you?
- Just another sparkling water, please.
You heard the lady.
Put that on Miss Verbanski's room.
Thank you very much.
Chuck, Sarah, stay focused on the mission.
Gertrude, you have a bogey
closing from your 9.
Walker, do you have a positive ID?
Uh, negative on Falcone, but it could be
another one of his heavies.
- Your call, Casey.
- I'll handle it.
- Package for Miss Verbanski.
- I'll take that.
Thank you.
A little jumpy, John?
Thought he was one of Falcone's.
Didn't know what he had.
It's a little something
that I found for you in the lobby.
- What the hell is it?
- It's a swimsuit, John.
Your job is to blend in around here,
and I'd like you to put it on, please.
Change room right there.
Oh, God.
Look, I mean, honestly, Falcone is not
gonna be showing his face down here.
You wanna go, uh, take a little dip
in the hot tub with me?
No.
No, I don't think that's a good idea.
No booze, no Jacuzz,
what's gotten into my wife?
Look, stay put
and take care of the client.
I'm gonna go check on Casey, okay?
Casey?
Just a minute.
Oh, God, I'm coming in.
I can't do it, Walker.
Gertrude, she doesn't listen
to what I'm trying to tell her.
I can sympathize.
- Thank you.
- You're putting on that suit.
- Like hell.
- This is a dream mission.
I'm not gonna let you screw it up.
Do you know know many skimpy outfits
I have put on?
Did you hear me complain
when I had to put on a catsuit...
...or 7-inch platform high heels
or a belly-dancing outfit?
Belly dancing?
Okay, that was private.
Look, just put on the banana hammock
and stop whining.
You okay, Walker?
You seem a little emotional these days.
Shut up.
- Guys, I lost Verbanski.
- What? What do you mean?
Falcone must've scoped our security.
Verbanski? Verbanski?
- She's not responding on comms.
- Her signal is still transmitting.
I'm showing her at the far west corner
of the hotel.
Casey, I need your help.
We're coming in.
Falcone must be holding her
in the Presidential Suite.
- Where's Falcone?
- We're meeting him for dinner, John.
In the meantime,
I suggest we work up an appetite.
I'll show you what's under mine
if you show me what's under yours.
You've been
a naughty, naughty colonel.
What is it?
Sarah, what's wrong?
Everything.
It's all wrong.
Very smart, Miss Verbanski.
Meeting in public,
bringing in your own security team.
It's like you don't, uh, trust me.
Easy, Casey.
This is my price.
And this is mine. Provided
the merchandise meets my specs.
Some woman, your boss.
I have a private weapons range.
Meet me there at midnight.
And don't forget your checkbook.
Are you seriously considering
going to an unsecured location?
John, I want those guns,
and when I want something...
Any... Ahem. Anyhoo, I'd like to...
...uh, on behalf of our team,
propose a toast...
...to you because, honestly, kudos.
I like how you do business. Heh.
Know what I mean?
This op is top-shelf.
Well, you know, at Verbanski Corp, we
have a work hard, play hard philosophy.
Here's to playing harder.
Excuse me. I'll be at the bar.
All right. Don't worry.
I got this. I got this.
Put it on your tab, Mr. Verbanski?
Mind if I give you a little advice?
Use the word "care,"
I'm gonna take this glass...
...shove it down your throat, and punch you
in the stomach so it shatters.
Okay. Uh, it's not spy advice.
It's actually relationship advice.
She doesn't want a relationship.
She wants a lackey, a lapdog,
a beefcake.
What is Verbanski really trying
to tell you, John, huh?
Because even tough women
like Gertrude and Sarah...
...they're giving out secret signals
that you need to be sensitive to.
We spend so much time sharpening our
spy senses that we forget to use this...
...this guy, the heart. You know.
And you need to learn
how to listen with your heart.
Come on. I'll show you how it's done.
Are you all ready to order?
Oh, uh, I think
I might need a couple extra minutes.
Hmm. You just kind of...
You have to listen to her,
listen to her, okay?
I know what she wants before she
knows what she wants. Observe.
Actually, I'd love to order for my lady.
If you don't mind, hon.
Uh, I think to wet her whistle,
she'll start with a glass of your Barolo.
Uh, I'm so wrong. We're on vacation.
Vodka martini... up.
Thank you very much.
Entrée, bone-in rib eye, extra rare.
I'm talking blue
or as blue as you can find.
As in mooing on the plate.
It's bad? I don't do a good cow.
She's like a book...
...and I'm an emotional speed-reader,
my friend.
What's going on, bro?
Devon, you have been targeted.
Targeted? What? Who?
Jeff and Lester. They think that
you're some international super-spy.
Those idiots? Why?
Because I told them.
Maybe it's because
Jeff is no longer an idiot.
But those two stumbled
upon our actual spy operation.
- You see?
- Gotcha.
You need me
to throw them off the scent.
Ah. Hey, now you're thinking like a spy.
Here's the key question,
can you act like one?
Can I go formal?
I've secured the U-238.
This device will make you more powerful
than you ever dreamed.
Location forthcoming.
Wait, wait, wait.
Are you sure you don't want us
to do a little recon before it's too late?
It's not my first arms deal.
I'm good for my half.
And you?
Miss Verbanski, do you always
dress your security this well?
Looks soft.
Just show us the guns, huh?
Yeah.
I present to you the Aegis.
Please, have a try.
Casey, don't we need ear protection
or something?
Ah. Not bad. Not bad.
Verbanski Corp will take full delivery.
Three million dollars.
No deal.
Actually, I'll take your money.
But you can leave me your guns.
Casey, why aren't they dead?
What your boss didn't tell you
is that the Aegis has a safety feature.
Each gun can be coded
so that it can't be fired...
...at someone carrying an Aegis
with the same code.
It's a way of preventing, uh, friendly fire.
Ingenious, no?
Quite.
Except my team's weapons
don't have that safety feature.
And it would be a shame
if someone got shot.
The price just changed, Rock.
How does free grab you?
Would someone like to explain to me
what the heck is going on?
So this was your plan all along.
We were the loser team you hired so
Rocky would think you were vulnerable.
- Nice.
- No. I still need you, John.
Rocky is just the first piece
of the puzzle.
The real mission starts now.
I'm out.
Casey, wait.
Whoa, hey. Whoa, whoa, whoa,
team meeting, team meeting.
Casey, if you quit now,
we'll be lucky to see the retainer.
Besides, what did we talk about at the
restaurant? What did we talk about?
Are you using this?
I think you owe it to our client.
Listen to her signals.
What is she telling you?
You think I need to be more sensitive?
More in tune
with my girlfriend's emotions?
- You're one to talk.
- What's that supposed to mean?
You've got your head
so far up your new CARE manifesto...
...you don't even realize your wife
thinks she's pregnant and is hiding it.
What, are you crazy?
There's no way she could be pregnant.
I'd have to be the most clueless,
insensitive, uncaring...
Uh, Chuck...
Sarah, I'm sorry
I didn't exactly pick up on your signals.
No, I'm sorry.
I should have just told you.
It felt like if I said it out loud,
it would become real.
It's changing, it's changing,
it's changing.
- What is that? An equal sign, an arrow?
- A peace sign?
Is that an option?
Uh...
Uh, okay, that means no.
I'm not pregnant.
Okay, all right.
- And you feel?
- Strange.
Maybe a little relieved.
Same.
But this whole thing has gotten me
thinking about our lives, our future.
- Chuck...
- I mean, Sarah...
...is the spy lifestyle really
where we wanna be raising our kids...
...putting ourselves in danger?
- Chuck.
- Yeah?
- You're spiraling.
- Mm-hm.
I need you back in immediately.
I was telling Casey the truth.
I leveraged Rocky Falcone
to give up his supplier.
Pedro St. Germaine is notorious.
Guns and narcotics that come up
from the south flow through him.
He has an enormous FBI bounty
on his head if I'm not mistaken.
That's where the real mission comes in.
The FBI hired me to find St. Germaine.
And Falcone kindly gave up
his exact location in the Everglades.
We're in.
We'll be in Miami by nightfall.
- I think we should discuss this.
- Discuss what?
I don't think it's safe for prospective
parents to be in a situation like this.
Cute. I just figured you'd wanna finish the
mission and take some of the proceeds...
Wait. I was just saying
maybe we should talk about...
- And she hung up.
- Chuck, stop spiraling.
I'm... I'm not spiraling.
You're spiraling.
Ooh. Yeah, cashmere, nice.
Do you mind?
I have a tailor who can make me
two sweaters out of this bad boy.
- Rough mission?
- I don't wanna talk about it.
Okay, that's no problem.
Tons to talk about.
Lot of stuff going on.
Verbanski
wasn't bringing me a mission.
It was an all-expenses-paid vacation.
Sun, sand, sex.
The nerve of that woman.
I'm not a kept man. I'm a spy, damn it.
Don't I know it. Trust me.
In fact...
...I might have a little spy work for you.
- What kind of spy work do you have?
Hmm.
I'm making the drop now.
I have my eyes on the drop spot.
Ten-four. Let's go.
Okay.
It's oddly comfortable running in heels.
Perfect. Come on.
Just so you know,
I'm keeping these shoes.
Easy. Calm down, Jeffrey.
Get out of here!
We strike from the east entrance.
Take St. Germaine alive.
Figured it was only a matter of time
before that rat Falcone sold me out.
You waving that gun around for show
or are you gonna use it?
Yeah? I take it this is an apology.
I got your girlfriend, so, uh,
you might wanna listen up.
You got her all tied up, do you?
Uh, yeah, yeah, she is.
Uh-huh. And she needs her big, strong
boyfriend to come rescue her, right?
Again, correct.
And bring $10 million cash.
That's a nice detail.
Look, you tell Verbanski
she fooled me once...
...she's not gonna fool me again,
got it?
She said you'd be playing hardball.
Don't pay him anything, Casey!
I can handle it myself!
Didn't I tell you to shut up?
Gertrude? Gertrude?
So $10 million by tonight or she dies.
Okay.
Ten mil, good to go.
- Think they'll check if it's counterfeit?
- Oh, I'm pretty sure they will.
If all goes according to plan, they're not
gonna be in any condition to check.
Undetectable if the case is searched.
Walker,
when I say the code word "care"...
...you start so I can get to my weapon.
- And my job would be?
- You're getaway driver.
You don't want to have anything to do
with this. It's gonna be a bloodbath.
Be ready for extraction
when the time comes.
Okay, let's do it.
Oh, hey, Walker, listen.
You sure you're not, uh?
- I'm not pregnant.
- Okay.
- This is gonna be dangerous.
- I know. I get how dangerous it is.
Let's go.
- Stop.
- I'm unarmed.
I'm here for a trade
with St. Germaine.
There's a guy here who says he
wants to make a trade with St. Germaine.
Copy that.
- What if we had a baby at home?
- Excuse me?
What if we had a baby relying on us
to come home...
...and something happened?
- Something?
Something, anything.
We didn't come home.
Who would raise the kids?
What would happen then?
Honey, we don't have a baby,
let alone babies, plural.
Not now, but we will.
Spying and parenting
just don't go together.
Sarah, you are spiraling, okay?
Take a deep breath.
- Everything's gonna be fine, I promise.
- Okay.
- You sure?
- Yeah. We need to split up.
Your knight in shining armor
has arrived.
Let's see what you brought me.
I'm almost to the compound, Casey.
Sarah? I'm coming.
- Sarah, are you okay?
- Yeah. I'm fine, I'm fine, I'm fine.
It was just a flash grenade,
but I can't see.
I could have handled this myself.
I couldn't leave you out here
in the swamp.
Because I care.
Okay, that's Casey. You've gotta go.
- I'm not gonna leave you.
- No. I'll be fine.
Please, just take my gun
in case something goes wrong, okay?
I'm not gonna need it.
I have the Aegis.
I love you. Be safe.
I said, I care.
Maybe I care too much.
I've been working so hard
on my spy senses too.
My eyes, my ears, my fists.
What I should've been working on
is this.
John, stop. Stop. Please stop.
No, I can't, Gertrude...
...because I love you.
And I need you to know
how much I care.
I care a lot.
I don't know who you're trying to signal,
man, but it all stops right now.
Go, go, go.
Sorry I'm late.
I've got the Aegis. They can't hit us.
We need to get to cover.
I am the cover.
- Move, move, move.
- Aah. Aah.
Move!
I heard your speech.
It's great that you're opening up
your heart like that.
Yeah.
Move, move!
Good show.
Very entertaining.
But shotguns ain't got safeties.
Oh...
Don't worry. I wore my seatbelt.
- Hey.
Everything all right?
Yeah, I'm just doing some thinking.
Uh, I have a small confession to make.
Part of me was kind of hoping
that I was pregnant.
I've thought a lot about that too...
...and, yeah,
I think it'd be kind of exciting.
I mean, it's not like I want a baby
right this second.
- But it's not the worst idea in the world.
- No. No, it's not.
Listen to us, talking about kids
and a house and a real family.
Did you think we'd ever be talking
about this?
Nope.
Especially not with such a huge nerd.
Ha, ha.
I thought we were past this.
Just open it.
Stops anything
this side of a thirty-aught-six.
I saw you eyeing that guard's vest
in Miami.
Look, I'm...
I'm sorry for dragging you
on a glorified vacation.
I guess it was just my misguided way
of saying that I...
...wanna be close to you.
Thanks. Hmm.
I feel the same.
I know
Miami wasn't really your scene.
But my next mission
is in a much better place.
- Hmm?
- Mm-hm. Dresden.
Ah. Dresden. Harsh, cold.
Come with me.
Two months, real danger.
Who knows? We could both get shot.
You know I'd love to.
But, uh, two months is a long time
to be away from here.
Hmm. Well...
...when you're ready...
...I'll be there.
Unless, of course, you have
another woman behind the scenes.
No.
Not exactly.
So I have this friend.
She's out of town right now, but I'd like
for you to meet her sometime.
Friend?
Like a girlfriend?
No, not like a girlfriend.
Yeah, actually, like a girlfriend.
Well, I would, uh, love to meet her.
Perfect.
- Oh, no.
- What?
The housemaid is laying out
coffee spoons with the dinner service.
There is gonna be hell to pay
at Downton Abbey tonight.
So Devon Woodcomb...
...who, last time I checked...
...was an extremely handsome
medical doctor...
...and you think
he's building a nuclear bomb?
- We know the location of the bomb.
- We don't just think it, we know it.
Voilà.
That's a Outback coupon.
So it is.
Voilà.
Come with us.
Let's blow this thing wide open.
Yeah, fine.
I've only walked.53 miles today.
Another few steps wouldn't hurt me.
You, sir, are an American hero.
He's up to something.
What on earth?
After we open this door,
there's no going back.
Let's do this. I'm still at 1,500 steps.
Oh, careful, careful, careful.
What are you doing here?
How'd you find this place?
Uh, the better question is,
what are you doing here?
Really, what are you doing here?
I'm confused.
Ellie doesn't like my workout equipment
around the house...
...so I figured this would be perfect.
But the U-238.
It was being delivered here.
You mean this?
About to make my biceps go nuclear.
Then why all the secrecy?
Well, some of these exercise techniques
aren't exactly legal in the U.S.
If you catch my drift.
Are you two happy?
Let the statuesque man
work out in peace.
Is that a pedometer?
- Got a whole box of them upstairs.
- Phew. Sweet.
- I'll work you out a deal.
- Gotta work out sometime, Big Mike.
- I like your style.
- Do a lot of working out.
It's too easy.
Well?
The whole search...
...worthless.
There's no spies, no secret base.
Nothing.
Ah, Jeffrey, you know...
...maybe this wasn't a search
for a secret spy base.
Maybe this was a search
for friendship.
How do you mean?
I don't know. I just wanted
to say something to cheer you up.
Would you just come here?
Okay, buddy? Okay?
- Let's get out of here. This place reeks.
- Thank you.
What the?
- It's still wet.
- Oh.
- Oh, yeah.
- Remember when I was at Pine Ridge?
The, uh, mental institution? Yeah.
It was so dreary, they'd actually
put fake backdrops in the windows.
That's pretty cruel.
I always knew it was fake.
Um, where are we going with this,
buddy?
I guess what I'm trying to say is...
...it's not always easy
to trick a mental patient.
I knew it.
We were right. Lester.
Jeffrey? Jeffrey?
Oh, crap.
I think we've got a problem.
Yeah, yeah, I'd call it that.