Hi, I'm Chuck. Here are a few things
that you might need to know:
There are repercussions
for your actions.
- So you're under arrest.
- For what?
Attempted homicide.
John Casey,
you're under arrest for murder.
Visiting hours are in effect.
All inmates with visiting passes
report to visitation area.
How you holding up?
Well, the government I proudly served
for 20 years...
...has locked me up
with the scum of the earth.
I'm great.
Hold out your hand.
- What is that?
- We have a plan to get you out of here.
Just take it.
You have any idea how hard it is...
...to shrink blueprints to this size?
Guy at Kinko's thought I was crazy.
Put that away. I am not breaking out.
There is a very strong case
against you.
Escape might be your only option
to get your life back.
If I break out of prison, I'm a fugitive.
I don't run from the law. I am the law.
Now, Decker has me in here for a reason.
I'm gonna sit tight, keep my head down,
you figure out what his angle is, okay?
- Fine.
- You gonna be okay in here?
Yeah.
If that one doesn't drive me insane.
Okay, I admit it. I tried to poison you
to keep you subordinate.
- What is the big deal?
- I could have died.
But you didn't.
All right, look, recently I put some
people that I care about through, uh...
Through some rough times.
That's the thing. True friendship is...
It's confusing, isn't it?
Mm.
Look, guys, please...
...just, aah, tell me what I have to do
to get out of this place.
It's so simple. Okay. Jeff has agreed to
drop all charges under one condition.
Okay.
You promise
not to poison him anymore.
- Sorry, I can't promise that.
- Wake up, man.
You are gonna get yourself killed.
Doesn't matter. I don't care.
Good luck in prison.
Good luck finding
a better Indian guy in your life...
...or at the Buy More.
And I will see you both in hell.
Which is just what I call
visiting hours.
John, let's go back inside,
bench press some poundage.
I'm gonna look like a Hinjew
Michelangelo by the time I get out.
Hi, you. Johnny, move.
I told him I was in here
for parking tickets.
It takes every fiber of my being not
to drop that barbell right on his throat.
Visiting hours are now over.
I gotta get back in there.
Check into Decker.
But be careful,
he's capable of anything.
Thank you. I can't help feeling like
Casey going to prison is all my fault.
What? Why would you say that?
I'm the genius
who started a spy company...
...and convinced you
to work with me.
Decker wanted Casey in jail
no matter what.
Whether we worked for ourselves
or the CIA, it doesn't really matter.
And I'm not saying that
to make you feel better.
Well, maybe a little.
- Thank you.
- Chuck, you've got...
- Sarah, you got a...
- Oh, no.
Honey... Uhn.
Sorry for the theatrics getting you here.
Sometimes it's just more fun to knock
somebody out and toss them in a van.
Why'd you bring us here?
I need you to do a job for me.
You throw our partner in jail
and now you want a favor from us?
In exchange,
I will make all of his charges disappear.
Think of Mr. Casey
as a giant slab of leverage.
And we all know that stubborn bastard
will rot in prison unless I say otherwise.
You have the entire CIA
under your thumb. Why us?
This mission involves some extremely
dangerous technological terrorism.
Sure, I have agents
who can write code...
...but none who can do it as well as you
can and handle themselves in the field.
There's no room for error here.
We need you.
Okay.
We're listening.
We've been tracking a computer
super virus named the Omen.
Tech has only been able to uncover
bits and pieces.
They assured me
they've never seen anything like it.
Metamorphic code capable of erasing
a hundred zettabytes of data per second.
What does any of that mean?
It means this virus could essentially
wipe out every database in the world...
...in, oh, five seconds.
And just as we were zeroing in
on its origin, all signs of it disappeared.
That's why I need you.
Locate the Omen, bring it back to me,
Mr. Casey goes free.
And what if we say no?
I have men on the inside who can make
your friend's life a living hell.
Though, to be honest, I imagine hell
will have no trouble finding him in there.
No fights. Keep your nose clean.
Harder than I thought.
What do you think you're doing, inmate?
Sorry if I got too physical.
It's the uniform.
Don't apologize. I actually enjoyed it.
Thought you would.
I'm glad you came.
I have something...
I'm all for business...
...but wouldn't you like
to take advantage...
...of your state-given right?
What right is that?
A conjugal visit.
I would very much like
to take advantage.
I thought you might.
I'm assuming
you don't wanna stay over.
Ha. Maybe next time.
- What's on your mind?
- Bartowski and Walker are good spies...
...but I don't like that they're down
a man. Decker's up to something.
So you want my team to track them,
make sure they're safe?
Not your team. You.
I figure you could take my place.
Right, I'm gonna take orders
from Ward and June Cleaver.
It was just a suggestion.
Well, stop making suggestions.
Okay. I'm done.
It is hard to say no to you.
I know.
I hate this. Do you remember why
we started Carmichael Industries?
Corporate discount
on the pinball machine, right?
Ha. We did it to gain independence.
And where are we now?
Beholden to Decker, the exact type of
person we said we'd never deal with.
- Stop it. We're doing this for Casey.
- I know, I know.
All right, let's find us a virus,
shall we?
Uh... What is happening? Is that...?
Is that chardonnay?
Wow, I haven't seen this
in a long time.
We used to call this routine
The Routine.
- That's very creative.
- Yeah.
Yeah, Chuck has quite a reputation
as a hacker, you know?
They used to call him The Piranha.
Swordfish, right?
The movie is based on him.
Doesn't talk about it,
he didn't think it wasn't an A-plus film.
- I thought it was pretty good.
- It was okay.
A lot of plot holes,
and those hacker scenes were just, like:
Someone coded the name
into the Telix script.
Little inside joke for anyone running
viral countermeasures.
When The Piranha got really
into a decoding session...
...he could get a bit giddy.
- Yeah, it's kind of cute.
- Yeah, it's also super nerdy.
It's definitely that too.
Got it. The name was encrypted.
I ran an elliptic curve algorithm to find
the key. Of course after that, it was cake.
Hello, Colin Davis,
the man behind the Omen virus.
Coming your way in three, two, one.
Guy was a head programmer
at The Collective...
...a rogue group
of technological terrorists...
...who sell viruses
to the highest bidder.
Three months ago,
he disappeared with the virus.
Drop off the grid. Crazy. I like that.
Well, Mr. Colin Davis, let's see if you left
us any clues as to where you went.
Shoot. I promised Jeff that I was gonna
help him with this whole Lester thing.
All right, you guys will be okay here.
Oh, make sure that he eats.
He goes overboard
with the chardonnay.
Calls it his thinking juice.
- Ahh.
- Ahh. Thanks, buddy.
- I love you.
- Love you.
How's the brain, Mr. Grimes?
It's okay, thanks.
Casey sent me to help
with this Decker situation.
So if you'd be so kind as to take me
to the newlyweds.
I can't... I can't bring guests
down to Castle.
Are you really gonna make me
use this?
- You'd shoot me?
- I'd beat you over the head with it.
This is Davis' last known location.
Must have brought the virus here.
Some kind of encampment
behind this barrier.
Looks like some
separatist compound.
There could be militia training
back there.
Casey would have loved this mission.
And you're aware that you're gonna
get yourselves killed without Casey?
Decided to let her in
after we had an adult conversation.
What are you doing here, Verbanski?
Ease up. I'm not here to steal
any of your precious secrets.
I'm here because I'm going on
this mission with you.
Oh, is that right?
Look, we both want Casey out of jail.
You want your partner back, and I...
I hate to see the competition struggle
like this.
As far as I can tell,
you need a sniper on this mission.
Well, I've done some pretty amazing
sniper work on "Call of Duty."
I believe I've made my point.
Well, the sniper rifles
are behind you in the armory.
I'll bring my own.
Things can get really nasty
really fast...
...if you're not running
with a crowd in here.
- Is that a fact?
- You look like you can use some friends.
And we could use some muscle like you
in the yard.
I'll expect your answer tonight.
Hmm.
Dude, this place is no joke. Especially
for a guy with unpaid parking tickets.
What do you want?
Look, I've seen Caged Heat.
I know how to survive in prison.
You gotta be the shot-caller,
and I figured out a way to do that.
You know, Caged Heat
was a women's prison movie.
Well, the lessons remain the same,
John.
Hey, homes.
Got that 12-gauge you wanted, man.
Word.
- Drop it in my cell.
- Done.
All right. Easier than I thought.
- That sounds like some military drill.
- I'll look for cover.
Get ready for action.
Okay, this is definitely not a militia.
Sarah.
- Sarah, I think we walked into a cult.
- Way ahead of you.
Strip. Now.
What...? What are you doing?
What are you doing?
Joining a cult. Strip. Come on.
Now, keep a close eye.
I really have no place to hide a gun.
Not too close an eye, though.
I'm serious, for real.
Calm down.
No one's looking at anything.
Not much to look at, anyway.
That is not fair.
I have nothing to be ashamed of.
Children, are you lost?
Can I help the new arrivals
find their way?
We were told to come here to seek
enlightenment.
Then enlightenment you shall find.
Please, help yourself to some robes.
Welcome to
the Church of the Eternal Wind.
- Thank you.
We'll just...
We have uninvited guests.
Find out who they are.
We have a situation.
Oh-ho. Ha.
It's a little... Little chilly under here.
These are very short robes, huh?
Well, the church believes
that the spirit enters from underneath.
Well, that's a totally natural
entry point.
That's an interesting pendant.
I imagine it has
some kind of significance for you?
All members of the church
wear a pendant...
...to remind them of their past lives. I
worked on Wall Street, lived the fast life.
Until I came here.
Not looking for a life story here.
Figure out where Davis is, locate
the virus. My patience is wearing thin.
My wife and I were looking for an escape
from our everyday chaos.
Our friend, Colin Davis
recommended we come...
...and check out your church here.
- Colin. What a caring man.
But now we call him Moon Meadow.
That's his wind name.
Do you know where we could find
Moon Meadow?
- We'd love to see him.
- Mm.
I believe he's leading a drum circle
in the garden.
It's mostly free-form,
experimental drumming...
...but there'll definitely be
some jamming as well.
- Sounds like fun.
- Let's go check it out.
Hey.
How you holding up, man?
I didn't think it would be this hard
without Lester around.
I'm starting to forget him.
I can't even picture what Lester
looks like anymore.
Close your eyes.
Imagine David Beckham.
Lester's a shorter, feminine version
of his wife.
Right. I can see him now.
Look, when I went through my
dark period, I alienated a lot of friends.
But I was able to realize
what I was about to lose...
...before it was too late. We have to make
sure he knows what's slipping away.
I get it. This reminds me of the time
my dad tried to win back my mom...
...when he heard
she was having sex with Uncle Steve.
They ended up as a threesome.
I had a messed-up childhood.
Yeah, you did.
But you know what? It actually gives me
a great idea how to handle Lester.
It's not a threesome.
These people dropped everything
and came here.
Yeah, it's crazy.
I don't know what I'd do
if I left the spy life.
I'm so caught up in it,
I can't think of a world outside of it.
You're really good at computers.
You love them.
Yeah, maybe.
We got eyes on Davis.
I'm in position to shoot
any and all of these filthy hippies.
- It's almost like Casey never left.
- Yeah.
Stay focused.
This is over as soon as we find the virus.
So let's just get in and get out.
I found their clothes.
And these were with them.
Wrap up the Phish concert.
Make a move.
Ah-ah-ah! Whoo!
You got some skills.
As do you, my friend.
So you worked in tech, huh?
Oh, a lifetime ago.
And this... This would've been
my crowning achievement.
Till I walked away.
You know, I used to work in computers
as well.
- You mind if I take a look?
- Oh, no, I couldn't.
It's against church policy
to ever remove your pendant.
But I do take it off twice a month,
when I shower.
Ah.
Intruders! We have intruders!
We've been made.
You get the chip,
I'll take care of the guards.
After her. Go, go, go.
Stop!
- Leave me alone!
- Colin!
Colin, I'm trying to help you.
- Don't help me!
- Come on.
Stop!
Too much tree cover.
I don't have a shot. I'm coming down.
- Wait up.
- Go away.
I'm trying to help.
Some of our members
have a checkered past.
They pay a lot of money for
enlightenment, as well as protection.
Looks like you walked
into the wrong cult, bitch.
Colin!
Oh.
No, it's okay.
I vowed never to let anybody have
this virus, no matter what I had to do.
Davis.
No! No. Stop. Come on.
Come on.
Come on. Get it out of there.
Give me the chip. Give me the chip.
Davis? Davis?
Huh? Huh?
Where's the chip?
Huh?
I hid it.
- Inside him.
- So he swallowed it.
Yes, he did.
Hey. Honey.
- Hey, you all right?
- Yeah, never better.
Good. I need your help.
Davis swallowed the chip.
We gotta get him out of here now.
Okay, let's cover up his...
Guys, can we find him some pants?
Decision time.
You gonna join us?
Not interested.
Thought you might say that.
Come on!
Hey.
Hey!
You touch one hair on his head,
and I will pull your plug.
Mark my words, son. Step back
or your nights will get real long.
Real long. Step back.
- What the hell?
- I told you.
I figured out a way
to become the shot-caller.
Now, any of these people get out
of line, and I will pull their plugs.
Literally. I've been using
my Buy More skills...
...to set up cable and Internet
for the inmates.
- Of course you have.
- In fact...
...I got a shipment
of 12-gauge electrical wire...
...that is making installations a snap.
These monsters are petrified because I
can take their tech away at any moment.
- That sounds like a good plan.
- I know.
All right, I'll see you in the yard.
Please let me go. This is a mistake.
Look, I promise you
we're not gonna hurt you.
We just need to wait for the chip to,
you know, complete its journey.
- Then you can go.
- You don't understand.
The virus is too dangerous
to be released.
It could wipe out everything.
I knew I should've destroyed it, but...
It was my finest work.
You know, I just couldn't.
Hey. Uh...
I understand.
I tried to get out of that life.
It's sucking me back in.
It's like I'm trying to outrun something
I shouldn't have done in the first place.
I get it, Colin. Believe me, I do. And I
assure you, we're the good guys here.
I hope to God
you're telling me the truth.
There are two parts to the virus:
A chip and a distribution device.
It's like a modded USB drive.
You insert the chip into the device,
and the virus can be uploaded...
...to any system.
I'm hoping you didn't swallow
the device, as well.
No, it's still locked up at The Collective,
my former employer.
Right. Right, right, right.
So, what you're saying, then...
...is we just need to sneak past a few
hackers and get the device back?
No, it's not that easy. There are
some extremely dangerous people...
...selling these viruses.
- Can you help us get in?
- No.
Best I can do is show you
where they're storing the device.
Okay, great. That's a great start.
Thank you. I'll go grab a computer.
Is there anything I can get
you while I'm up?
Our kitchen's fully stocked.
Sandwich? Nachos?
We have some of those gourmet
jellybeans.
Do you have the kind that tastes
like buttered popcorn?
I think I can make that happen.
A snack? Casey's in lockdown
and this jerk wants jelly beans?
We should just cut him open
and get that chip out right now.
You know, I know that we're not
partners or friends...
...but are you okay? You seem to be
on edge since we started the mission.
I'm fine.
- We can talk about it if you want.
- No, no, no.
We don't talk. Okay? I'm just off.
- Stop trying to be my shrink.
- Okay.
Is it, um...
...about Casey?
I just noticed that you have
some emotions for him.
Can we stop with this garbage
and just get to work?
You can still have feelings for somebody
and be a spy.
Oh, and be like you and Mr. Hospitality?
That's my fate? No.
No, no, no.
So I've been noticing Lester popping up
online about the same time every day.
- Fancy prison.
- Yeah, right.
So look, we initiate a chat, and then...
...we begin
Operation: Scare Lester Straight.
You ready?
Hello, friends. Guess you couldn't live
without me. Huh?
Hey, listen,
I'm sorry to tell you this...
...but we've been interviewing people
to fill your spot at the Buy More.
Oh, come on. Right.
What, are you gonna just replace me?
Actually, he just showed up.
- Who's this fool?
- This is our new Nerd Herder.
- Vali Chandrasekaren.
- Oh, come on!
That is a pretty stupid name.
Where are you from, Mr. Fake Name?
Look at my face. You can't tell I'm
from Montreal? Like all true Hinjews.
- Oh, no, you did not.
- I did. And I am.
I just wanted to say thanks
for giving up your spot.
Some great people here. I'm excited
to start getting to know everybody.
Lester, you should hear
this guy's singing voice.
- Like an angel.
- Come on. It really is though.
Oh, Canada
- That's just a little bit, you know.
- My word.
Many people say it's the type of voice
that would go perfectly with a keytar.
May I have a moment alone
with Jeffrey, please?
Of course. Sure, sure.
- Hmm?
- Well done, well done.
Yeah, yeah, perfect. You nailed it.
Your voice... Wow.
- You really underplayed it.
- It was fun.
- Yeah. You earned this.
- Okay, this one's just Wi-Fi?
The Indian Modeling Agency
said you'd give me...
...one of the good ones
if I helped you out, so...
- You know, this comes out of my salary.
- Don't care one bit.
Jackpot.
Who's the new guy?
Don't worry about it. I'll find out myself.
You know, it is amazing. They're like
little popcorn pills, you know?
Whoa, whoa. What are you doing?
He agreed to help.
I just wanted to extend
our full hospitality to our guest...
...make sure he's perfectly comfortable
while we wait patiently for the chip.
- I was just telling your partner...
- He's not my partner. Go on.
The Collective has an unbreakable
security system...
...but it does have one weakness.
- It can be manipulated from the inside.
Man, these jelly beans taste funny.
Just speeding up the process
a little bit.
You've got something on your shirt.
- Oh, God.
- Oh, my God!
Keep it in the can.
Keep it in the trash can.
What do you think? Do I look like
a hacker? Is the beanie overkill?
You look perfect.
Okay, I found a duct opening
on the east corner, just below the roof.
We have our entry. At 2200 hours,
we'll be in the server room...
...waiting for you to override
the security system.
- Got it. Be careful, babe.
- You too.
I'm here for a job.
You realize what happens
if you don't get the job?
I do.
Welcome to The Collective.
The very best of the very best.
You said that you want a job.
Let's prove it.
- Sit.
- Okay. Hi. Howdy.
Freddy is my best programmer.
If you can prove your skills
up against him, then you have the job.
But if you fail...
...you might not be so fortunate.
- So a good old-fashioned hack off, huh?
Great. Perfect. I'm just gonna take a
moment to get prepared, if you don't...
Don't mind.
Boom.
Oh. Once you've had Rombauer,
you just can't go back...
...to any other chardonnay, right?
- Who are you?
I've been out of the game
for a while...
...but they used to call me The Piranha.
- There's no way.
Let's do this, huh?
Okay, the first person that hacks
into Federal Reserve...
...and transfers one penny into secure
account wins. Are we clear?
Begin.
Freddy's an expert at subverting
complex security systems.
He is the reason our own system
is so secure.
Oh, yeah. I can tell. He did a great job.
That's my man.
You seem to know your way
around a computer.
Oh, I'm sorry, are we still talking?
I'm kind of busy here.
You have a little hiccup there
at the bottom of your page.
A compiler can't optimize a value away
like that. If you don't mind.
There you go. Rookie mistake.
I'm sure it won't happen again.
Oh, I'm losing.
Better get back to work.
I forgot something.
I'm really good at this.
The servers are in here somewhere.
Can you pull up the schematics?
- Verbanski!
- Fine, I love Casey. Just... Just...
Jeez, stop grilling me.
So do you wanna talk about it?
I've been a wreck since
Casey went to prison.
I had no idea
I had such strong feelings for him.
Now I'm petrified that this
could turn into something.
You're looking at it the wrong way.
What, we're gonna have some kids
and I quit because it's too dangerous?
Relationships
are about communication.
Big life changes
don't just spring up on you.
Hey, stop!
I couldn't imagine my life
away from this.
Do you think it's gonna be that bad?
Sarah, girls like us,
we don't just leave the spy business.
I've been doing this since I was 16.
Never had another job.
I wouldn't even know what to do
if I did.
Stop right there!
How about you?
Could you do anything else?
Thanks.
This might be it.
Chuck, I've got the device.
Let's get out of here.
Thanks for the help.
Hope you enjoy losing.
- Done.
One penny, transferred out of the
Federal Reserve into a secure account.
Easy.
Little too easy if you ask me.
Honestly, who wants a penny?
So...
I hacked into the Buy More
and got us all flat screens.
- All right.
- With extended warranties, I might add.
You are clearly very talented.
Unfortunately, I don't care
that you are talented.
We have all the flat screens
that we need.
Whoa, uh... Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Before you use that,
I've got a little business tip for you.
And what is that?
You should really look into finding
a better security expert.
- Freddy! Alarms!
- Fixed it.
Find him!
Guys, I'm in trouble.
Coming your way.
I don't think I got the job. Heh.
Let's get out of here.
Go, go, go.
Your plan worked. As soon as Lester
saw the other better Lester...
...he changed his tune.
- That's fantastic.
He said he wouldn't poison me anymore,
so I dropped the charges.
- He'll be back at work tomorrow.
- Mm. Man, I can't wait.
This wasn't about me and Lester,
was it?
Hmm? I don't know.
There's someone who hasn't forgiven
your dick-ish behavior...
...and you need to right that wrong.
I'm talking about John Casey.
I know, dude.
I'm not brain damaged. Oh.
I'm sorry. Too soon? That's... I don't...
- You want me to do the talking?
- No. It was supposed to be me and Chuck.
We don't wanna do anything
to spook Decker.
You should probably
make yourself scarce.
So I've been... I've been thinking
about life after the spy game.
What do you mean?
You know, maybe you're right.
I'm great with computers.
Maybe Carmichael Industries
isn't a spy firm.
Maybe it's a tech company.
What do you think?
Sarah?
Well, what would my job be
at Carmichael Industries?
I mean, what would I do?
Well, you'd...
He's here.
- Did you bring the virus?
- The deal...
...it's still good?
John Casey goes free?
Here.
What are you planning
on doing with it?
This? The real question is:
What do you plan to do with it, Chuck?
What are you talking about?
I got some good footage of you
and your team...
...in possession of the most dangerous
computer virus in the world.
Smile. Ha-ha-ha.
Don't worry, we'll release the virus,
but you'll get the blame.
That should get you on the
FBI's most wanted list pretty quickly.
So this was a setup. You set us up?
Now that I think of it,
it was pretty irresponsible...
...to release Casey into the hands
of his criminal colleagues.
That's enough of this nonsense.
You release Casey now.
Gertrude, what's happening
is bigger than just me.
The plan is in motion.
It's too late for all of you.
It's just a shame that Casey
had to be the first to die.
Give me one reason not to kill you.
Go ahead.
It'll only further prove your guilt.
So I suggest you get your hands off
of me and get a little head start...
...because soon, people will be hunting
Chuck the way they hunted Bin Laden.
Go.
Let's go. Let's go right now.
Hey, Decker.
Aren't you forgetting something?
Don't worry.
I left a little consolation prize.
- He deserved that.
- Go.
Go, go, go! Come on!
Come on! Come on!
So it was all a setup, huh?
Chuck was gonna be the fall guy, and
you were never getting out of here alive.
John, your team needs you now.
Okay. What do we do about Decker?
I already took care of him.
You didn't.
I have to disappear for a while.
Yeah. I understand.
We could've been something.
Still can be.
Perhaps someday.
Surveillance changes shifts
in two minutes.
We gotta get into the heating ducts
before they realize you're gone.
You're gonna break me out alone?
No. I found someone who cares
about you as much as I do.
Huh.
Prisoner transfer from CB-11,
section 3-8.
Copy that.
I missed you, big guy.
What plan was Decker talking about?
Why would he wanna frame you?
I don't know, but I intend to find out.
If he was telling the truth, then we're
already in deeper than we know.
Sarah, I was wrong
about quitting the spy life.
Because right now, we've gotta be
the best spies we've ever been, okay?