I'm Chuck. Here are things
you might need to know.
Omen. A computer virus that can erase
a hundred zettabytes of data per second.
It could take down the Internet
and erase every database.
In truth, Chuck,
the virus is just a piece of the plan.
- What happens now?
- That's the real surprise, isn't it?
There. The Omen is officially unleashed
upon the world.
I'm not leaving
without my money back.
Christmas cheer? Try Christmas fear.
A virus dubbed "the Omen"
has infected computers worldwide...
...and it has Christmas shoppers
in a panic.
Are their hard drives in danger
of being erased?
Or is the virus a gag
that does nothing?
Why panic? Ask yourself:
- "What would baby Jesus do?"
- And you are?
I'm Michael Tucker, assistant manager
of Burbank Buy More.
I want customers to remember
the true meaning of Christmas...
...and get back to what you're supposed
to be doing: Buying stuff.
Like this iPad, a bargain for 599.
Honestly, it's overpriced.
You can get this on the Internet.
See, everything is fine here
at the Buy More. Totally fine.
No computer virus problems here.
Dear God. Jeffrey. I need your help,
buddy. These people are animals.
The virus is everywhere and nobody
knows how to stop it. Nobody knows.
What is going on here?
Authorities do not know...
...who is responsible for the Omen virus...
...but assume
it is an act of cyberterrorism.
Every prison cell in here is connected
to the mainframe.
What if the Omen virus hits us?
You worry too much.
Take another snort of almond-milk nog.
Do you hear that?
Ellie, relax.
We are so behind. We are
so crazy behind and I can't find it.
- Find what?
- The star for the Christmas tree.
- The one that Dad gave me.
- Deep breaths, namaste-style.
Devon, it's Christmas Eve,
we are having a party in six hours.
We don't have a tree,
we don't have decorations...
I am Eleanor Woodcomb.
- What are you doing?
- I am Eleanor Woodcomb.
Saying your name aloud helps
to calm you.
Reminds you you're in control
of your own actions.
- I am Eleanor Woodcomb.
Yeah, that didn't work.
Okay.
What are you freaking out about?
Because Christmas
was my first memory, okay?
The presents,
the smell of fresh-baked cookies.
I know Clara is young...
...but I thought that maybe it could be
her first memory too and I just...
I want everything to be perfect.
All right, what's gonna turn that frown
upside down?
A real tree, lights, fake snow,
and a picture of Clara on Santa's lap?
- That's a tall order, babe.
- I know.
But that is why I recruited someone
onto our team.
- Ellie.
- Sarah, I need an update.
It's okay.
Project Santa is under control.
I got the decorations from your list.
Get the tree and snow.
- Thanks.
- Okay, bye.
- Hey, Sarah.
- Your sister is in full Christmas mode.
It wouldn't be Christmas with the
Bartowskis without a little bit of trauma.
- Speaking of...
- No progress on the virus?
Whoever's behind this is a ghost.
Untraceable.
No such thing.
They just haven't slipped up yet.
When they do? Carmichael Industries
will take them down.
But for now, I promise,
nobody is gonna ruin our Christmas.
Just everyone else's.
Chuck, it's gonna be okay. Look, I'm
gonna lock up Castle and come home.
Oh, by the way, will you tell Casey...
...uh, Mr. Pippers, the Preppy Polar Bear,
has arrived.
Mr. Pippers? Really?
Oh, man, that's, like,
our favorite childhood toy, right?
- One of, yeah.
- Top five. Maybe.
But still our generation.
- Not really yours.
- Got it on eBay.
Alex's mom said she used to run around
with a little bear thing like that.
It's still in its original package.
I thought it was a good idea.
Dumb, huh?
No.
It's actually quite touching.
Like you're feeling
real human emotion.
Don't you ever say that again,
and don't breathe a word of this to Alex.
No. No. My lips are sealed. Presents
are sacred in the Grimes family.
- Gentlemen.
- General.
We have an emergency.
We know who's behind this.
Merry Christmas, Sarah.
- Miss me?
- Not for a second.
That's no way
to treat an old boyfriend.
Just give up, Walker.
You're no match for the Intersect.
Comfy?
No?
Good.
Sixty-nine percent complete.
Only a couple more hours
before the virus activates.
What are you doing, Shaw?
You're the one behind the Omen?
The plan?
Surprise.
Why?
Why stay in jail
when I could break out...
...release the virus...
...and take over the CIA?
Oops.
Gave away my plan.
Sarah, thank God. Shaw broke out
of prison. Where are you?
- Sarah?
- Hello, nerd.
Do me a favor?
Turn on the monitor.
Merry Christmas.
Hey, can I tell you a story?
You untie Sarah right now.
There's this tradition in Germany,
where Santa Claus...
...or Krampus, as they call him...
...visits all the naughty children
on Christmas Eve.
But instead of giving them coal...
...he wakes them up,
and the naughtiest of children...
...never see Christmas Day.
- Let her go.
- Or what?
No Sarah, no Intersect.
You're worthless, Chuck.
Put Castle on lockdown.
Do everything I say or she dies.
Get my drift?
- Why are you doing this?
- Because you put me in jail?
Because of our last fight?
Because you tried to kill me?
So much history, Chuck.
Could be anything.
- Fine. What do you want?
- The CIA base downtown.
Break into Decker's office,
retrieve the Macau device, bring it to me.
What is it? What does it look like?
Figure it out. You have three hours.
Don't you hurt her.
Impressed?
I implicated Chuck
in a massive conspiracy...
...and captured his girl.
All from an 8-by-8 cell.
You?
- Working with Clyde Decker? How?
- Decker was a slug.
He tried to interrogate me and in
one flash, I knew all his filthy secrets.
A little blackmail and his entire team
was working for me.
You know what the best part is?
There's nothing that Chuck can do
to stop me.
What now, Chuck?
Chuck?
Oh, boy.
This is bad. This is really bad.
He is shutting down.
Then we take care of Shaw ourselves.
But he has the Intersect. We're gonna
need a plan, a really good plan.
I've got the plan.
Daniel Shaw murdered my father
and now he has my wife.
He's gonna wish he never left
that prison cell.
That plan's kind of vague.
Morgan, I need you to reverse-engineer
that virus. Use the nerds.
They're better than any computer expert
in the CIA.
We need to figure out
what happens when that virus activates.
- I'm on it.
- Casey, find alternate routes into Castle.
I need options
in case I can't get the device.
Whoa, whoa, hold on.
You're gonna break into the CIA?
Decker's office is on level five.
Omega level.
You go in alone, it's suicide.
Who said anything
about going in there alone?
The Macau device was stolen two
months ago from a Chinese company.
It compresses huge quantities of data
to fit onto a single computer hard drive.
Why would Shaw want it?
I have no idea.
What's the best way
to get into the CIA?
There's only one way in.
With me.
I can't tell you how happy I am
to hear you say that...
...but you're putting yourself
on the line.
This is my team.
And nobody, especially Shaw,
is going to take us down.
I got off the phone
with Buy More Corporate.
They wanna know everything
there is to know about Omen virus.
What happens when it activates? To
stop it, we need to know its next move.
Fold.
No. You are the only ones...
...that understand C-plus-plus
and other languages.
I need you to crack this thing. Do it now.
- Yeah. NI.
- What?
- Not interested.
- Thank you.
It's an immature response, I know,
but I too am under-incentivized.
Until this virus is cracked, nobody's
buying any crap at the Buy More.
Which means no double overtime
and no Christmas bonus.
True. But it seems a little above
and beyond our usual duties.
- Name your price.
- I got this.
Ahem, I would like a 6-inch
classic Italian B.M.T. From Subway. Boom.
- I was going to say a trip to the Bahamas.
- Subway. Done. I'll make it a footlong.
Nice. Make mine flatbread, boys.
I'm going into Castle,
in through the ducts.
All right. Hey, be careful.
It's a war zone.
Some Scrooge stole Christmas
right out of the Buy More.
Sorry to bother you.
Maybe we should just forget it.
You kidding?
Getting this angel her picture
might be the only cheer I get...
...to spread around here this year.
Let Santa just grab his suit.
Damn hell.
What kind of monster steals a Santa suit
on Christmas Eve...
...but leaves the eyebrows?
I am Eleanor Woodcomb.
Babe, don't worry,
I'm calling in the big guns.
Chuck, there's been a robbery
at the Buy More.
Now, brace yourself:
The Santa suit is gone.
Oh, that's terrible.
Sounds like someone could use
a dose of the Christmas spirit.
Promise me that you and Sarah will
make it in time for Christmas dinner.
- Ellie really needs her family right now.
- Yeah.
Yeah, of course, buddy.
We wouldn't miss it for the world.
My wife has been kidnapped...
...and I'm officially ruining Christmas
for the children of Burbank.
We have a CIA Christmas party
to crash.
Now, let's go save our girl.
Why's it getting so cold in here?
Tapped into the internal generator...
...lowered the temperature
to stop the mainframe from overheating.
Once the virus activates, the resulting
data influx could fry it in seconds.
You with me?
No, you're not.
If you were,
you would've brought a coat, silly.
You're going into hypothermic shock.
Soon,
you'll be in and out of consciousness...
...until finally,
your heart stops beating.
Why don't you just kill me?
Kill you?
This is about you.
Why do you think I wanted you in Castle
and I sent Chuck to the CIA?
Both know
that you're the superior spy.
- I've missed you.
- You're insane.
What we had was special.
I know you felt it.
You've laid in bed at night
thinking about me beside you.
I'd rather be dead.
Got what I needed.
This is Sarah Walker...
...and Daniel Shaw
is in complete control of me.
I don't know what your plan is,
but it's not gonna work.
Shaw's so handsome and smart.
- I bet he reads a lot of books.
- You think you can beat Chuck?
You're not half the man that he is.
This isn't about Chuck, Sarah.
This really is about you.
See, I'm finally gonna crush your soul.
The way that you crushed mine.
Mm, twelve inches of bubbly cheese,
spicy pepperoni and ham.
You really should try
the Fresh Fit option.
No offense. Thank you.
What have we got so far?
All right, so if this virus hits
at the expected rate and magnitude...
...everything electronic will shut down:
Traffic lights, computers.
God, can you imagine a world
without the Internet?
What if it's up to us?
Two Buy More employees left...
...to stop the Omen virus
and save the world.
Come on. Government
has their best people working on this.
Right?
God, I hate corporate Christmas parties.
Everyone turns into sloppy,
embarrassing messes.
Well, hello, Diane.
Oh, Stan, not again.
How about joining me
at the punch bowl?
Enough.
You're embarrassing yourself, Stan.
Well,
if that's gonna be your attitude...
Stan Lee is a spy? That is so weird.
Los Angeles spies.
Now, focus. The woman by the giant
Subway sandwich is your target.
Mm-hm.
- Colonel Caroline Hayne.
She's in charge of internal security
with electronic access...
...to every room,
including Decker's office.
- So, what's our next move?
- Seduce her, Bartowski.
Steal her key card.
She's a notorious tight ass, except
for one night of the year. Tonight.
Six hot toddies and men
are running for cover.
You're sure I'm her type?
You're drawing breath
and you're in a Santa suit.
Ho-ho-ho!
Oh, Merry Christmas.
Ahem, or happy Hanukkah.
Whichever is applicable.
You look like you want some alone time
with old Saint Nick.
I wanna sit on your lap.
Come here.
Ahh. Whoo.
I don't think Mrs. Claus would approve
of any "shenanigans," you know?
Well, it's a good thing Mrs. Claus
is a no-show.
Oh, ha, ha.
Oh, that seems inappropriate. Ha-ha-ha.
- Aah.
- Ooh, yeah. Naughty Santa.
- Ah.
- That's just how I like it.
Oh.
- Caroline.
- Diane.
Mr. Claus, I will personally escort you
off the premises.
Oh, what a shame.
Merry Christmas. Happy Kwanzaa.
Pull yourself together.
Play a little cat-and-mouse?
Fine.
But I'll find you.
I know you're unarmed.
The armory's been on lockdown.
You can't hide.
I know every secret...
...every mission...
...and every mistake.
Scar on your left hand?
Calgary, 2004.
You never tried catching throwing stars
after that, did you?
I know everything, Sarah.
I know everything.
You're upset with me.
That's obvious.
But do you really think I wanna spend
the holidays with you?
That I wouldn't rather be
with my family?
It's a trick question, Sarah.
Because you shot my wife
in cold blood.
You brought this all upon yourself.
Very disappointing, Casey.
We have less than a minute
before a team figures we've broken in.
Never took Decker
for much of an art collector.
Think I found it.
Col. Hayne accessed Decker's office,
but I'm looking at her.
She's in the bullpen.
We got a code five.
This way, Colonel Hayne.
- Our minute came and went.
- Mm.
What are we gonna do?
No place to hide.
Pucker up, Bartowski.
You're about to become a man.
Like a bar mitzvah?
Or something that's a bit...?
I mean, what exactly are you...?
Santa?
Retreat immediately
or I will see you court-martialed.
Hmph.
- I brush my teeth before I...
- We never speak of this again.
Never ever.
Shaw, I've got the device.
- Chuck, it's me.
- Sarah, oh, my God. Are you okay?
Yeah. I escaped Shaw
and I'm hiding in Castle.
But Shaw's still down here. Hurry.
I'm on my way.
I know, I know. It's a madhouse.
Jeff and Lester made some progress.
- How'd your day go?
- I got the device and Sarah's in Castle.
Sarah. Hey, is everything okay?
Casey disarmed Shaw. He's locked up.
- Thank God. I'll be there soon.
- Hurry up, dear.
- Everything all right?
- Sarah says that Casey took down Shaw.
Yes. Nice. Way to go.
But she called me dear.
She never calls me dear.
- Shaw's using her somehow.
- Oh, crap.
Last time he was in control,
he blew up the Buy More.
- We've got to get these people out.
- I tried, Morgan.
But we haven't made a single sale
all night.
- I'm sorry.
- No, don't be.
Don't be, buddy. It's okay.
Attention Buy More shoppers, um...
I know everyone's a little scared
about this Omen virus.
But, uh, you should not be waiting in line
on Christmas Eve.
- Yeah.
- It's not about the gifts.
It's about spending time
with your friends and your family.
And eggnog and cheer.
Spreading lots of cheer.
So, uh, as of now,
the Buy More is officially closed.
- What?
- Yeah. Sorry.
Cheers. Thank you, come again
and shop at Buy More.
Sorry. Sorry. You have to...
You're gonna have to kind of...
- Thanks, buddy.
- Come on, son, I'll drive you home.
Your mama's cooking us
a big, fat, honey-glazed ham.
Oh, I'm gonna stay here
and close up shop.
Can you make sure everyone
gets out safe?
- All right. All right.
- Okay.
Hey. What's happening?
Ellie, what are you...? What are you...?
We're, uh...
We're closing down for the night.
Yeah, the picture with Santa
was a bust.
I sent Devon and Clara home.
Mom's flight's cancelled.
Sarah was supposed to help...
...and she's not answering her phone.
Have you heard from her?
Yeah, uh, sort of.
She's kind of busy.
Chuck, what's going on?
It's Shaw.
He kidnapped Sarah.
Daniel Shaw, who killed Dad?
- What can I do?
- Uh.
I hate to say this. Just go home.
- I wanna help.
- Ellie, please go home, okay?
I have to know that you're safe.
Okay, but, um, call me. Call me as soon
as you know something.
Yes. Yes. Okay.
Chuck, you be careful.
I love you.
Ugh, you sick son of a bitch.
Just wanted to see
if any of the old fire was still there.
No. Ice-cold.
This was Mary Bartowski's, wasn't it?
I think I'll keep it.
Token of our last night together.
I had no idea she was your wife,
Shaw.
I had no idea who you were.
I was just...
I was just on an assignment.
Hmm.
- Is that supposed to make me better?
- I was just a young agent.
I was just doing my job, okay?
You, of all people...
...need to understand that.
Really?
Well, what about the pit
you dug out of my chest?
- Is that supposed to fill it in?
- Is this going to?
You were a good man, Shaw.
You can be that man again.
Just stop what you're doing, please.
Okay?
You can let this...
You can let this all go.
I know you're in pain
and you want this to stop...
...but not yet.
Not until you feel a pain more
excruciating than you ever imagined.
Chuck is coming up with a way
to stop you as we speak.
This whole Omen virus,
end of the world, apocalyptic thingy...
...it's a hoax. It's a hoax.
The virus is designed
to suck information out of computers...
...and move information to a location.
But it's not doing that.
Absolutely not.
Or it's not doing that
with our computers.
It looks like this virus
is targeting government computers.
I think it's a real-life conspiracy.
Problem is no one computer can hold
all that information.
- Ha, ha, I mean, right? Right?
- Yeah, of course not.
Morgan, it's not going into a computer.
Shaw is using the Macau device to
relocate the CIA database into his brain.
He's trying to create
the Intersect 3.0.
Oh, crap. With the CIA's databases wiped
clean, they'll rely on Shaw for their intel.
They'll have to make him a spy again.
Gentlemen. Gentlemen, uh.
The Buy More is closed.
You can go home.
- Happy holidays. Drink some water.
- Water can only dilute this feeling.
Plus, fish have sex in it.
- Let's go for a run.
- Great idea.
Chuck, tell me you got some kind of
an idea here because I'm a little scared.
No, don't freak out. I've got an idea.
- Okay. Just hope it works.
- Me too.
Seeing as how our lives
kind of depend on it.
You knew that already.
- Yeah.
- Mm-hm.
You've got the device.
Let Sarah go and take me instead.
And why would I trust you?
Look at the monitor.
Buy More's empty.
You can come up here and kill me.
As long as Sarah's safe.
Pitiful.
Good, you're awake.
You know
what the ultimate revenge is?
Spending Christmas Eve with you?
I'm gonna let you live.
I want you to watch
while I kill your husband.
Chuck has a plan.
So do I.
And I've spent the last two years
in prison perfecting it.
You killed my wife.
Now you're gonna suffer, just like I did.
You're gonna spend the rest of your life
without Chuck.
Hi, I'm Mr. Pippers, the Preppy Polar Bear.
You can leave a message
by pressing the heart on my paw.
Have fun.
Alex.
Dad.
I just want you to know
that I'm proud of you.
And I'm sorry I haven't been there
for you all these years.
And I'm really sorry...
...that I'm having to tell you this
recorded on an electronic bear.
Electronic bear.
I'm unarmed.
You can shoot me now,
if that's your plan.
But for some reason,
I don't think it is.
Oh, you're absolutely right.
It's very important that I enjoy this.
Really?
Well, that's a nice idea, Shaw.
However, if I remember correctly...
...the last time we were face to face,
I kicked your ass.
I've made sure
that'll never happen again.
No Intersect to help you this time,
Chuck.
I wouldn't be too sure about that.
I've been training for a while now.
Oh, really?
Well...
...can you compete
with the Intersect 3.0?
I can practically catch a bullet
in my teeth.
But you did some push-ups?
You hit the heavy bag?
Oh, just so you know,
while you're begging for mercy...
...your wife is watching.
I've spent every waking second in jail
thinking about this moment.
This time...
...I'm gonna kill you.
Agh.
You seriously underestimate
the power of the Nerd Herd.
- The Omen virus. You put it...
- Inside your head.
Instead of downloading
the Intersect 3.0, you removed it.
And it turns out that's the last flash
you're ever gonna have.
I'm a much bigger nerd
than you thought I was.
Oh, jeez.
Hey. Hey. Hey.
Wake up. Wake...
Oh, my God,
you're like a little ice cube.
Hang in there. I got this. I got this.
Uh, I'm gonna pick you up with the chair.
All right, so just bear with me. Okay.
Holy cow. Oh, man.
Agh.
One, two...
I'm still gonna kill you.
Like to see you try.
I've been working on that one.
- That one's for Sarah.
- Is that all you got?
I got a little bit more.
All right, listen to me.
You're gonna have to wake up.
Wake up because you're bolted in here
and I don't have a key.
What are...? You're shot.
You're bleeding.
Shut up, numbnuts.
We gotta get her out of here.
- Get her.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
"Dear? Hurry up, dear?"
Sloppy, Shaw.
Won't happen again.
That was for my dad.
You're good, Chuck.
But you're not lucky.
That was for me.
Nice shot, sis.
But I told you to stay at home.
I'm Eleanor Woodcomb.
Since when do I do what I'm told?
That man took our father away
from us, Chuck.
I wasn't gonna let him take
anybody else.
Merry Christmas, Ellie.
Merry Christmas, Chuck.
Authorities have confirmed
that the Omen virus...
...was planted by a terrorist
named Daniel Shaw.
A private security team stopped him
before the virus was activated.
And although they've chosen
to remain anonymous...
...we here at KCKH
wanna say thank you...
...and also wish our viewers
a happy holiday.
And now, onto other news,
where a dog barks like a duck...
All members of Carmichael Industries
have a position open to them at the CIA.
The agency would be lucky
to have you back.
Well, we couldn't have done it
without you. So thanks, colleague.
With that, I'll bid you farewell
and merry Christmas.
Do you have a place
to spend the holidays?
You could come to our place.
But I think my Christmas party's
a bust.
No, no, no.
Your Christmas party is not a bust, sis.
Don't you know that when you roll
with General Diane Beckman...
...you roll in style?
General...
...don't you think the CIA
could help us throw...
...just a little eensy-weensy Bartowski
family Christmas party?
You're talking
about American tax dollars at work.
Oh, hell, let's do it.
That's the spirit.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Without Mom and Dad around,
it could never be the perfect Christmas...
...but I hope you know
that you'll always have me.
I do.
Felt pretty good taking down Shaw.
Mm.
I think Dad would be proud.
I know he would be.
I miss him.
Me too.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
Merry Christmas.
I, uh, made a recording
when things got a little grim.
It's just that...
It's probably better
I tell you in person.
I love you.
I love you too, Dad.
I know it's, uh, just a little bear.
It's not gonna make up
for all the lost holidays.
No, it's...
It's perfect.
You know, that Grimes kid,
he's not that bad.
You should maybe give him
another chance.
It was fun, man.
Like old times,
before you got all smart.
It's actually the only Christmas Eve
I remember.
I'm usually drunk
on Manischewitz by now.
I miss that.
- Thank you.
- For defeating Daniel Shaw?
For stopping the Omen virus?
Or was it me getting us invited
to rejoin the CIA?
- For saving me.
- Technically, Morgan saved you.
Because of all the saving...
...I wasn't able to get you your gift
in time for Christmas.
However...
An oldie, but a goodie.
I hope that this will suffice for now.
Thank you.
- Smile.
Oh, now, she'll always be able
to remember her first Christmas.
- Merry Christmas.
Chuck, you should know that, um,
while I was tied up in Castle...
...Shaw kissed me.
Well, as long as we're airing things out,
you should know...
...that Beckman kissed me.
Walker, a word?
Uh, General, I know about the, um...
- With you and Chuck.
- We have to make sacrifices for the job.
Shaw requested a meet with you.
I suggest you don't go.
What?
I'm glad you came.
I'll be locked in solitary
the rest of my life.
But one thing's gonna keep me warm
at night.
Little something I put into motion
that you'll never be able to stop.
Do you remember Hungary?
Does Chuck know about the baby?