Something terrible
happened last summer,
and I have no memory of what,
or who, hurt me.
We live,
at least in the summer,
on Beechwood Island.
Our island was a fairy tale,
filled with kings and queens
and castles.
No. No, no, no, no, no, no.
On it, we could be anything.
Tag!
You're it.
You seem different.
In a good way?
In a new way.
I mean, at a certain point,
are you even really married?
My marriage is just fine.
So was mine,
until it wasn't.
I imagine the divorce
must be draining, though.
Mostly on my bank account.
He's hired
a private investigator.
I saw him writing
me a letter,
with a beach flower
he had dried and pressed.
And then something happened.
I knew how I felt.
Oh, God.
Mom.
Cadence.
Oh, my God, Cadence.
What happened to me?
You're OK.
Sam, Sam, Sam, she's awake!
She's awake, she's awake.
♪ With your feet
on the air ♪
♪ And your head
on the ground ♪
OK, you're OK.
OK, let's rip this.
You're OK.
♪ Try this trick
and spin it ♪
Here's what I do remember.
I shared a perfect kiss with
Gat on the beach in June,
and I woke up
in the hospital in August.
♪ Where is my mind ♪
Everything that
happened in between
is lost in the black hole
of my brain injury.
♪ Where is my mind ♪
The doctors tell us
it's normal...
normal to experience amnesia
after trauma,
normal for patients
to change their appearance,
to need painkillers
to manage the migraines.
My family won't tell me
what happened
the night of my accident.
The Liars haven't spoken to me
all year.
The pills only work
for the headaches.
♪ Where is my mind ♪
But to cure the heartache,
I need to know the truth.
And so I have to return
to Beechwood.
♪ Where is my mind ♪♪
You didn't have to wait up.
Oh, I don't sleep anymore.
Cady, look at you.
Are you feeling OK?
Nothing painkillers
and vodka can't fix.
She's kidding, she's kidding.
That's, um,
that's her humor now.
That's different.
Yeah, Dad's
three-quarter-life crisis.
Calls it New Clairmont.
It's nothing
like it used to be.
She's hoping that being here
will jog her memory.
My doctor said that
being in a familiar setting
might help, but that...
that isn't familiar at all.
New Clairmont is jarring,
but this is still Beechwood.
Come on,
let's get some sleep.
Everyone's so excited
to see you in the morning.
- Are they?
Yes, they are.
It's all they've been
talking about for weeks.
Come on.
♪ Flower and the thorn ♪
♪ You took my hand
and I took yours ♪
♪ My heart was stolen ♪
All the secrets
of summer '16
are still here
on the island...
in the sand
where Gat first kissed me,
on the shore
where I washed up,
barely breathing,
two months later.
And I won't stop until
I have the whole story.
I do think you're pretty.
My story.
You're so pretty
it's distracting.
I don't want to lie anymore.
♪ Out of the ashes
we come alive ♪
♪ For eternity we'll survive ♪
♪ We can live forever ♪
♪ We will be here forever ♪
♪ Everlasting,
live from within ♪
♪ Out of the ashes ♪
♪ We come alive ♪♪
Cady, I once read
that the best days
deliver a series
of small astonishments.
This candy expresses
my feelings inadequately.
From Gat.
I need to tell you something.
What's better,
a guy giving you
a dried beach flower
or a candy?
That's not from a guy-guy.
This is Gat.
Gat sends you weird
little notes all the time.
Well, maybe Gat
is a guy-guy now.
Ugh, we had a moment.
I knew there was a vibe.
I mean,
I guess
I'll be happy for you
instead of despairing the fact
that the Liars dynamic
will be changed forever.
See, that's the thing,
right?
The other day,
I saw him writing me a letter,
and he put a dried beach flower
inside the envelope.
But then he changed his mind,
and he put a taffy in it
instead, which he's done
a million times before
in, like, a friend way.
So maybe that's his way
of saying that I...
Maybe he's just contemplating
the potential fallout.
As should you, Cady.
I will.
I am!
All right, I'm out.
Wait, what did you
come up here for?
Oh, it's not
worth talking about
while you're all heart-eyes.
I um...
You focus on Gat.
Get yourself alone
together and see
if he wants any more moments.
Hey, guys.
Thanks, Lydia.
You're the best.
Thank you for the present.
Yeah.
Yeah, no big deal.
Uh, girls,
please come make a plate.
- I know that there's so
many... -What do you guys want?
Mirren,
aren't you gonna eat?
No, I'm feeling
kind of pukey.
- Mm.
Your tummy always hurts
when you're keeping a secret.
Tummy, Johnny?
Stomach. I'm not five.
Right.
Yeah, you're a grown-up who
has somehow sexted yourself
into eternal virginity.
Who was...who was
the guy who brought you
a drink at the party boat?
Golf bro,
looked like his name was
something like Shep Calloway.
Winchester Prescott.
Tucker Asherton.
Oh, well, if it
isn't Brody Sheffield.
Good morning, Sinclairs.
- Hey, baby.
- Oh, my gosh, you're here.
- Bonbon, Liberty...
- I missed you so much.
Oh, I missed you tornadoes.
- Oh, bug.
- Oh!
I thought you
missed your flight.
Oh, I...I did,
so I woke up
at the crack of dawn
and I made the drive in.
Figured I'd sneak in from the
service dock and surprise you,
but Harris blew my cover.
Wow!
Look at that.
That's fantastic, little bug.
You drew that
water with pencils?
Look at how the light
dances through it.
I'm glad you could tear
yourself away from the office.
Oh, the office
will always be there.
Getting crushed by you
on the golf course,
however, is a rare treat.
Ah, Harris's favorite
Father's Day tradition...
disappearing to the club
all morning.
To give you space to prepare
your favorite tradition,
the feast.
Oh, I see.
Tee time, 7:00 a.m.
Tomorrow.
Hope you haven't
gotten too rusty.
Bring your A-game, boomer.
Hey, Ed, what do you say
we take the boat into town,
get some ice cream?
- Littles, Liars, you in?
- Sure, Dad!
- I'm in!
- Ed?
You in, bro?
Sure thing, bro.
I think that Gat and Cady
were actually planning
on staying here.
No, no, no.
I'm down for ice cream.
Yeah, same.
Awesome.
♪ Oh, I know ♪
♪ Spiraling is miserable ♪
♪ I should probably go
back home ♪
♪ Why does that feel
difficult, difficult... ♪
Can I tell you
guys something,
and you swear to not tell
a single soul?
Yeah.
OK.
I saw my mom last night
having sex with Salty Dan.
Oh, fuck.
Wait, like,
the harbor service guy?
Yeah, the delivery pirate.
He had her all pressed up
on the boathouse.
Their legs were just going...
you know, there's one there...
Ugh! Ugh, gross.
Sorry.
Enough detail about Aunt Bess
getting railed, please.
Yeah, well,
I can't eat and I can't sleep.
I'm gonna develop a weird
sex complex, obviously, so...
I'm gonna have to
tell my dad.
I mean, I don't know,
maybe talk to your mom first.
There could be a reasonable
explanation, right?
Like what, fish boy is on my
parents' celeb hall pass list?
Look, there's no excuse
for cheating.
Ever.
We're supposed to
have values...
honor, dignity.
Wait, did your dad...
I don't want
to talk about it.
You guys ready to head home?
- Yeah.
Let's do it.
Do you guys want to go
to the bookstore?
We could leave the, uh,
boat taxi for you guys
to take later.
Uh, if Gat wants to.
No, I just--I'm gonna wait
for the Fourth of July sale.
Yeah, we can go back
to Beechwood.
♪ Oh, I know ♪
♪ Spiraling is miserable ♪
What's it mean?
♪ I'd be someone
no one knows ♪
♪ I guess I'm just difficult,
difficult ♪♪
- Oh!
- Oh, no.
I thought we were gonna go
sit on the beach
and have real adult
conversations.
I mean, we're almost
done here, Bess.
Please?
I have mimosas.
Ooh, I'd love one.
Thank you.
No OJ.
Well, waft it over here.
I will enjoy it vicariously.
Yes, because enjoying things
through your nose
always ended very well for you.
Why are you so on edge, Care?
Children.
Boyfriend.
Parents.
Fair.
Must be really hard
for you both,
not being
the favorite daughter.
Oh, we'll see about that.
My Father's Day gift
is excellent this year.
That's just Penny
for expensive.
Don't you have
a divorce to pay for?
Meh.
Well, I went sentimental
with mine.
- Mm.
- Ever the suck-up.
This year, I just want him
to see that Ed and I
have our shit together.
It's a little late
for boyfriend approval,
don't you think?
Oh, my God.
Unless you're about
to ask him to pay
for some big Indian wedding.
Oh, Carrie.
Focus.
Tomorrow night,
we gauge his reactions
to the gifts,
and then we meet
and convene post-feast
and crown the winning daughter.
And what am I going to win?
The winner can wear
my black pearl necklace
to the end-of-summer gala.
Wow.
Mom, um, competing
for parental love
has lasting consequences
on children.
Did you know that?
Well, when your dad
is happy,
we are all happy.
May the best woman win.
Dude, I'm telling you,
you gotta sit back
and let your money make money.
How much are we talking?
I mean,
I didn't win the Powerball.
But, you know, I want to
give Carrie some security
without Sinclair strings
attached.
Maybe put a dent
in Gat's college tuition.
Yeah. Yeah.
You know, on second thought,
I think it's best
if I refer you to someone
a little more small-time.
My firm prefers a little more
zeros and commas
than you're working with.
Hey. I got you.
Thanks.
13 points?
Unfortunately, it
doesn't...that does not count.
What about that
doesn't count?
What do you mean?
Mirren, tell him.
That's not...
OK, Gat is a
cheater.
Oh, real mature, Johnny.
You guys are so...oh, my God!
Ow!
OK, OK, OK!
Off the...oh my God.
OK, OK, OK.
- Idiots!
- OK.
What's the point of this?
You're gonna ruin the game.
- What?
- What are you doing?
Stop, bitch! Oh!
- Oh, no, Gat.
- Come on.
Serious?
You guys, come on.
Cadence.
Hi.
Shit.
Oh, my God.
- Oh, Cady.
- Hey.
Thank God you're here.
All that testosterone
in there was seriously
- starting to poison my soul.
- OK.
Cady,
you got to settle this,
because we're playing dirty
word Scrabble and Gat says
that "douche" doesn't count.
It means water.
- So go to New Clairmont and
tell Harris that you're parched
and you need a cold glass
of douche.
You're not gonna do it.
I know I look terrible.
Gat still thinks you're hot.
Careful, bro, those old-ass
shorts do not hide a boner.
OK, Johnny, shut the fuck up.
Cady, you don't...
you don't look terrible.
Yeah, I like your haircut.
It's very
Saint Laurent circa Y2K.
Yours is cool too.
Oh, thank you.
It's symbolic.
Lobster roll?
Since when do the moms
let us skip family meals?
- Oh, I'm not hanging around
that cold new house.
Those people will be
fine without me.
You're so skinny.
Have the moms asked you
for any diet tips yet?
Right.
Traumatic brain injury,
the next big fitness fad.
Don't joke.
We really were scared.
You were?
Cady, of course we were.
All year long, you didn't
come to the hospital or call.
I thought you were mad at me,
but I can't remember
what I did wrong.
My mom just thought
you needed space, so...
and I got this new boyfriend.
I got really distracted
by all the intercourse.
My call went to voicemail.
Sorry, I don't do voicemail.
I'm not a psychopath.
Yeah, my parents,
um, they took my phone.
The screens make
my migraines worse.
Well, you're safe here
in the land of no Wi-Fi.
Shall we start a new game?
How bad is it?
I mean, the amnesia and just...
I mean, just everything.
Some of my memories
are coming back, but...
like, I went down to
Taft Beach last night
to try to remember
the night of the accident,
but I just couldn't.
Maybe your brain
did you a favor
deleting that particular file.
Guys, just stop, OK?
I can handle it.
Was I swimming?
What, did I...did I fall?
We weren't there.
None of us were.
Why?
Why was I all alone?
We don't know.
None of us know why
you wound up in the water.
Cadence!
I'm fine, Mom.
Relax.
Hey, nice hat, Aunt Pen.
Harris is up at
the New Clairmont patio.
Go and say hello, Cady.
I will later.
No, you slept in.
Your cousins have already
visited with him today.
Oh, my God.
All right, I'm coming.
Hey, Cadence.
We just thought
you needed some time.
We're really sorry.
"Douche" counts.
If you wouldn't say it to
Tipper, it's a dirty word.
Thank you!
But you spelled it wrong,
Johnny.
- What?
- No points.
You did!
You spelled it with an O.
It's D-O-U.
Pathetic. I quit.
This game sucks.
Oh, you're such
a sore loser, dude.
Because you...
So Gat had two
perfect opportunities
for you guys
to be alone together,
and he blew them off.
I wish I could just
ask him what he thinks.
But sometimes moments are
just fleeting, you know?
At least you know now.
You can be cool.
You can just go back
to being normal.
Pretend nothing ever happened.
Right,
but he's not acting normal.
That's the problem.
What up?
Hey, you guys want
to play Scrabble?
- Yes.
- Can we do it stoned?
How was the water?
Oh, see, Johnny can
kick my ass in tennis,
but not in a swim race.
Whatever, dude.
My shorts got more drag.
- Ew.
- Ew. Stop, Johnny.
- That is gross.
- So gross.
Here, I got the good shit.
Hey.
Oh, hey, is that next
on your reading list?
This one?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I finished that
Andrew Jackson biography.
It was actually
really interesting.
Oh, here we go.
If you skip
the Trail of Tears lecture,
I'll give you five
Andrew Jacksons.
Dude, you gotta admit,
it's fucked up
he's still on our money.
Besides, don't you guys
ever think about, like,
who was on this island
before Harris?
Harris's dad?
All I'm saying is
that there should be limits
to what one person can own.
That's it.
Can you just shut up?
Can we just play?
Shut up forever.
Shut up and Scrabble,
seriously.
You know what, guys?
My...my letters suck.
I forfeit.
I'm gonna go find a new book.
Wait, Gat.
Seriously, let him go, OK?
Ever since he got back
from India,
he's been obsessed with
the evils of colonization.
I'm over it.
So the appraisal
authentication,
and the original
bill of sale
from when my family
acquired it in 1949.
Mm.
Thatcher,
hello.
Are you staying for dinner?
Uh, no.
No, my, uh...my boat's waiting.
I'll arrange for transport
for next week.
Mm-hmm.
My Sotheby's guy
will be ecstatic.
Thank you.
You're selling the Thornton?
Well, your dad hates it.
Only because
your dad loved it.
I'm replacing it
with a Britteridge
Harris has been on about,
a Father's Day gift.
Well, you should
have had Ed sell it.
He's kind of killing it.
Did Carrie tell you he's
curating Spike Lee's vineyard
collection this summer?
Hmm.
Thatcher will be, um,
more discreet.
I don't intend to discuss
the sale with your father.
It's none of his concern.
The Thornton is a...
it's a Taft heirloom,
not a Sinclair asset.
So you're putting
the funds from the sale
into a separate account and
buying the new piece for Dad
with Dad's money?
I am not some 1950s
housewife, Penny,
who's collecting an allowance
from her husband
to get her hair done.
I am selling
my favorite piece
to alleviate
your cash flow issues.
So don't give me that face.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
I didn't mean that tone.
I was up very late with Lydia
planning the feast,
and I'm just...
I'm so tired.
When I asked for your help,
I thought you would
write a check,
not pull off an art heist.
Look, I...
I didn't pry into why
your divorce is so messy
because, well,
I have always believed
that women are entitled
to our secrets.
But your father is also
entitled to his peace of mind,
and if he sees such
a big transaction,
he won't settle
for your vague answers.
Go fetch.
Go get it.
Go get it, go get it,
go get it.
Beautiful day.
No garish party boat to
interrupt your tranquility.
Oh.
I suppose I didn't notice.
Right. Um...
uh, Harris, I, uh,
wanted to talk to you.
You know, Carrie and I have
been together for a decade,
and out of utmost respect,
I'm here to ask...
Carrie thinks it's outdated
to ask a man
for his daughter's hand
in marriage.
Antiquated, she says.
Yeah, but you
value tradition, so...
Mm-hmm.
Well, per Roman tradition,
the suitor would offer
the father
a symbolic gold coin
for his blessing.
That's what Brody did.
I thought it was a nice touch.
Hmm.
- I'm kidding.
- Oh.
Right.
Yeah.
You know, I suppose you're an
improvement over her eloping
with a junkie who would
ultimately abandon her
with two kids
and terrible credit.
Oh, you suppose?
No, I'm just wondering...
Why now?
You seem content
without making it official.
Yeah, I mean...
yeah, my parents
are traditional too,
and they have opinions about
kids out of wedlock.
We want to add to our family.
Hurry up.
Sit.
Salute.
Good boy, Franklin.
Yeah, most people, they slack
off with their training.
It's important to never
let a dog forget his place,
think he's a person.
Diligence is key.
A little positive
reinforcement works, too.
What did I miss?
Well,
darling,
I was just welcoming
this young man to the family.
Oh, Ed, congratulations!
I have something for you...
my mother's wedding ring.
Well, I ought to clean up
my old golf clubs for Brody.
Oh, don't mind him.
Hey.
I don't tell you to shut up.
I would never say that to you.
I know.
I just...
I don't know
how to be you and me,
ever since...
I was just trying
to act normal, and I...
I said something
that I didn't mean.
Can I?
But I do not
want you to shut up.
Maybe I should.
Look, I know I...
I know I've been annoying.
You...you said
I was acting different.
You're right.
I feel different.
I like that you're different.
I like that you care
so much
about the things
we don't understand.
We don't really
want you to shut up.
When we say that,
we just mean we love you.
We should go downstairs,
I think.
Cady.
Shut up.
♪ I feel I've known
you all my life ♪
♪ I just hope we don't
run out of time ♪
♪ The one constant you ♪
I'm interrupting.
No, no, no, no, no, sir.
Yes, I most certainly am.
Uh, we're just looking at...
Books.
Have you read
"First Base and Beyond"?
Uh...
Ah.
Ooh.
Well, you...
you might like this.
Thank you.
Watch yourself, young man.
Pardon me?
Your head.
Watch yourself
or you could get hurt.
Mm.
There you are.
Do you remember summer '11?
We played Tipper's favorite
record so much we warped it.
Sounded all messed up.
Yeah, "Tapestry."
Mm-hmm.
I'm scared memories
are like that.
Like, if you play one favorite
memory too many times,
you might warp it.
Change it.
What's your favorite memory?
All year,
the last thing I remembered
from summer '16
was you kissing me
on the beach.
I kept going back to it every
time I was scared or sick.
But maybe I warped it.
You know, maybe I'm wrong
about how perfect it felt.
Maybe it was just a kiss.
It wasn't.
It...it was perfect.
Then why didn't you call?
All year,
I thought you hated me.
And you were so hot
and cold last summer,
I thought I must have
done something
so unforgivable
the night of the accident
that you wouldn't have...
We're not allowed
to talk about summer '16.
What?
All right, listen.
Penny gathered
everybody up for this...
this big meeting today...
Whoa, whoa.
Since when do any of you
obey the moms' rules?
Listen, she said
it could trigger
your...your migraines so bad
that you spend days in bed.
Look, we...
we all decided that...
You all decided?
Jesus, Gat.
Listen to me, please.
You have to let it go.
Can we please just be here,
me and you?
Please?
I'm so tired.
I'm gonna go.
Cady, please.
You know what, maybe you're
the unforgivable one.
Maybe I don't forgive you
for bailing on me all year,
and then looking at me like
you are, and touching me...
That night fucked me up
as well, all right?
That's...that's why I can't
fucking talk about it.
Look.
That kiss,
that kiss on the beach,
that was my favorite
memory, too.
It really was.
I'm telling you, Cady,
I am telling you,
nothing else matters.
Don't you trust me?
I don't remember.
- That was bad.
- That was fine.
- You think it's fine?
- You think it's bad?
He gave you a book.
He gave me
"Wuthering Heights."
There you are.
Triple-decker s'mores, anyone?
Hey.
What's up?
Nothing.
We were just, uh,
talking about tomorrow.
You know,
my dad and I used to go
to the museum before
the Father's Day feast,
but, well...
Hey, let's do something
awesome, then, all right?
Mm-hmm.
Like, replace all Harris's
gifts with glitter bombs.
That's not exactly
what I had in mind.
Or, or, or...you know
those foam parties in Ibiza?
Mm.
If we could get
into the sprinkler system
and load it with
industrial-strength soap,
- then we...
- Get the gardener fired.
I mean...
Oh, my God, Gat.
Dude, you used to be fun.
Johnny, just lay off him.
Look, not everyone has...
has a private island to ruin,
all right?
You'll contaminate
the irrigation,
- wreck the ecosystem, and...
- OK, Gat.
- What, what?
- We get it, bro, we get it.
Like, we're roasting
marshmallows on stolen land.
Johnny.
What...what should I do?
Do you want me to tell
Harris to return
Beechwood to the Wampanoag?
Do you want me to hurl my
emergency Amex into the sea?
Fine, Gat, fine.
You know, of course
I won't be able to take
you to all those Knicks games.
You love those games, right?
But you never ask
about the ticket prices.
You're being an asshole,
all right?
Yeah.
Yeah, I am an asshole.
I was born this way, bro.
It's a fucking
congenital privilege.
I've embraced it.
And guess what, dude?
It's better than being the
type of asshole who pretends
to be all holier
than everybody
when they're actually
the fucking asshole.
Be fucking real, dude.
Do you think you haven't
caused destruction this summer?
Do you think that you aren't
wrecking a perfectly good
- ecosystem, right fucking now?
- What are you saying?
- Fuck you!
- No, fuck you!
Really?
Stop!
- You want to fucking go, dude?
- Don't fucking touch me!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, walk it off. Go.
You're such
a fucking hypocrite.
What the heck?
You all right?
You're up early.
Yeah, couldn't sleep.
Yeah, same.
Came to find coffee.
Do you...
Uh, what happened last night?
You and Johnny,
you're just, like,
not getting along all
of a sudden.
I don't...things are
different this summer.
Yeah, I get that.
But why was he calling
you a hypocrite?
I think...
he feels like
I'm making some bad choices.
Like what?
Like me?
OK, well, then he can
mind his own business.
He's just being
protective of you.
That's it.
Well, the one person I don't
need protecting from is you.
Right?
Yeah.
I should go get dressed.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Just tell me, why didn't...
why didn't you give me
the beach flower?
The what?
You wrote me a letter,
like you always do.
And I saw you
put a flower inside of it,
but then...
Oh.
What, did you think
it was too much?
Yeah.
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Yeah, too much.
I mean, we just
made out, right?
Yeah.
Totally.
I have to go get ready
for the feast.
I hate Father's Day.
Happy Father's Day.
Oh.
Oh!
Would you look at that?
- The Britteridge.
- Mm-hmm.
How did you know?
- Oh.
- Mm-hmm.
It makes the room feel much
more grand, don't you think?
Mm.
Yeah, you were right.
It's...it's much better.
Yeah.
Don't tell me you want
to display that Thornton
in the Boston house.
No.
No, no.
That is...is just
going away to storage.
It's gonna be a problem
for the next generation.
Thank you.
Of course.
I do love
when you wear these.
I know you do.
Well.
Shall we, my liege?
Oh.
If you insist, my lady.
- Yeah.
- Mm.
Oh.
My queen.
Ready?
Man of the hour!
All hail the king!
No, this fanfare is absurd.
It's just...it's ridiculous.
You girls, you're all grown.
- Dad.
- It's tradition!
Oh, tradition,
all right, all right.
- Oh, yes.
- Your cape, Granddad.
The cape, the cape.
Yeah.
- You little traitor.
- Sorry, Granddad.
- Here you go.
- Aw.
- Yeah!
- Speech!
All right. All right.
My loyal subjects...
I thank you for another
wonderful gathering
to celebrate a bountiful summer
in the land of milk and honey.
Hear, hear!
Cady, about earlier...
As I look upon
the generations,
I'm reminded of a father's
most noble duty...
to produce a son.
- Oops.
- Oh.
And if that fails,
to see to his daughters'
every outlandish whim,
even if it means wearing
a gingham tablecloth
decade after decade.
But, as always, I command you,
bow to Queen Tipper...
Oh, stop.
Without whom
I would most certainly be
a malevolent ruler
with blighted crops
and a castle of ice.
- No.
- He wouldn't.
And now we feast.
♪ In this stress dream ♪
♪ Every day is Halloween ♪
♪ I had a panic attack
on the Underground ♪
♪ Man, I felt
like a circus freak ♪
♪ But I'm going down
swinging ♪
♪ Oh, I'm going down
♪ So let it rain ♪
♪ On my fading light ♪
♪ I can take it ♪
♪ Give me hellfire ♪
♪ Watch me keep my cool
tonight ♪
tonight ♪♪
I wanted to tell you.
Actually, I wanted him
to tell you.
Who's Raquel?
She sucks.
She's a total trash goblin.
Don't lie.
Fine.
Uh, I don't know.
She's just a girl.
And we went to a Knicks game.
She was cool, I guess.
She had, like, three hot dogs.
Who are we talking about?
Uh, Gat's girlfriend.
I'm really sorry, Cady.
Not a big deal.
His behavior makes
complete sense now.
It's fine.
I'm sorry.
Earlier, I was a jerk
this morning.
- You're good.
- No, I'm not.
Look, I don't like this.
We haven't talked all feast.
Really?
Is there something important
you forgot to tell me?
Presents!
Time for presents!
The time has come!
Get this party started.
- It's time!
- Girls, come on in.
Come on, everyone.
- To the king!
- Come on.
Where are you sitting?
Hey, guys.
Come on, come on, let's go.
In your seats, everyone.
Hear ye, hear ye.
May I present your youngest
heir, Princess Bess.
Oh, Princess Bess.
Let's see what you have.
My king, I offer you...
Mm-hmm.
...a gift of memory.
Ooh, OK.
All right.
- What is it, Dad?
- Oh, my...
It's all of our home videos,
digitized and optimized.
Greatest hits of the '90s,
rescued from the VHS graveyard.
Oh, fantastic.
Look at that.
And now, Princess Penny,
what do you have to offer?
It is the gift
of practicality.
All the bells and whistles.
- It'll catch the fish for you.
- Oh, my God.
And finally, Princess Carrie.
The gift of majesty.
Ooh.
Would you look at that?
The Sinclair family crest!
Oh, thank you, honey.
Beautiful, honey.
Oh, that...
look at that.
Oh, it's wonderful.
It's a wonderful thing.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
Happy Father's Day, Dad.
- Thank you.
- Happy Father's Day.
- It is a happy Father's Day.
You've all done
a wonderful job, thank you.
All my children.
I'm sure today must have
been difficult for you,
what with Sam not here and all,
but I find the best way
to feel better
is to appear perfectly fine.
So you go take a moment,
and then chin up
and shoulders back.
♪ I think about you ♪
Remember who you are.
♪ Day and night,
it's only right ♪
♪ Day and night ♪
♪ It's only right ♪
♪ Oh ♪
Sorry.
I...I wanted to
tell you about her.
So tell me now.
Who is she?
Look, I met her in India, OK?
But it turns out that
she lives a train stop
away from me in Brooklyn.
And our moms
were friends, and...
I like her a lot.
She gets me.
Well, I don't.
I thought I knew you.
But the Gat that
I knew, my Gat,
he would never kiss me
while he had a girlfriend.
He wouldn't keep us
both secret.
Maybe you don't
know me, then, Cady.
You've never met my mom.
You've never seen my room
over the air shaft.
You only know me here,
Cady, OK?
OK, you're...you're like
this royal family.
I mean, everyone is rich
and white except for me,
Ed, and the staff.
None of that matters to us.
It matters to me.
It matters to me because
you don't see any of it.
You don't.
How when you eat
Harris's dessert,
Lydia gets chewed off for not
serving what he asked.
How...how messing
with the sprinklers
- gets Paolo in trouble.
- Paolo?
The groundskeeper.
That's Henry.
Oh, my God.
Henry got fired last year.
He got blamed when our dance
party wrecked the tennis court.
You didn't know, right?
I didn't. I'm sorry.
You guys never say
thank you when they serve you.
You don't pick up
after yourselves.
Why would you care to ask the
guy mowing the lawn his name?
I have waited so long
for you to see me.
The truth is,
people like me just
exist in the
background of the story
you tell about yourselves.
That's it.
That is bullshit, Gat.
You're my best friend.
I have been in love with you
since we were 12.
You never saw.
And then out of nowhere,
you're...you're finally here,
looking back at me.
So forgive me for not wanting
to blow up my fucking life
just because you were
in the mood to hook up.
I'm sorry, all right?
That is not true.
Stop saying that.
You're the one
who kissed me, Gat.
Twice!
I wish I never did.
I hate myself for it, OK?
Cady, I didn't mean...
I'm sorry.
♪ Hey ♪
♪ When you're coming apart ♪
♪ When you're
coming up empty ♪
♪ Like a shot in the dark ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ When you're
closing your eyes ♪
♪ I know that you're tired ♪
♪ Let me tell you again ♪
♪ All the light ♪
♪ I'm seeing ♪
♪ Is coming from you ♪
♪ All the love
you're needing ♪
♪ Is coming from you ♪
♪ And it never ends ♪
♪ And it never ends,
and it never ends ♪
♪ And it never ends ♪
♪ All the love ♪
♪ You're needing ♪
♪ Is coming from you ♪
♪ And it never ends ♪
♪ And it never ends,
and it never ends ♪♪
- Hey, listen,
I was thinking maybe
I should hold on
to your medication
just so that I can,
you know, monitor better.
Did I try to kill myself
that night in the water?
What?
Is that why
you're telling everyone
not to talk about it
with me?
Because you're scared
I'll do it again?
You didn't try
to hurt yourself.
Then why?
Why?
- Oh.
- Why?
Why did you forbid everyone
from talking to me
about my own fucking life?
Cadence,
Sinclairs don't yell.
We don't yell,
we don't curse,
we don't air our problems
in mixed company.
I've lived my entire life
by your dumb Sinclairian rules,
and they're not
working anymore, Mom.
They work if you follow them.
What?
Why are you doing this to me?
I am doing my fucking best.
I spent 17 nights
in that hospital chair.
I took you to every
neurologist in New England.
When you couldn't
handle school,
I relearned fucking calculus
so you wouldn't fall behind.
I cleaned up your vomit,
I lay awake listening
to your nightmares, and I
brought you back to this place.
The doctors said it was best
not to overwhelm you.
They said it was best
if you remember on your own,
that it is best
to manage your pain.
So that is what I am doing.
I am doing my best.
Post-traumatic amnesia
is caused
by brain injury
or a disturbing event...
an attack, an assault.
Mom, did somebody hurt me?
Just take a deep breath
and calm down.
Right.
Chin up,
shoulders back.
Don't let it
ruin your summer.
He's just a guy.
Cady.
I don't know
if I'm a good person.
Me neither.
I'm winging it.
Hey, you want to steal a bottle
of something from the moms,
get drunk at the
lighthouse, and talk shit
about Gat and his
useless motorcycle license?
Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
Molting?
Is that the word
you're looking for?
- Oh, God.
- But, like, in a cute way.
How come we never have
Mother's Day on Beechwood?
Because all I want on my
special day is some peace...
And quiet.
Precisely.
Oh,
and here I am having it,
with my three favorite women
in the world.
Well, he loved it.
You outdid yourself.
Oh, but don't think
that we don't know
that you paid the Littles
a silver dollar each
to go along with that bit.
Shh, shh, shh.
The queen's secrets are key
to all family rituals.
It's very delicate.
You'll see someday.
All right.
What was the verdict?
Which of us was tonight's
favorite daughter?
Let's be real,
we don't stand a chance.
None of us is gonna be
his favorite daughter.
We grew up, we got messy,
and Harris hates mess.
♪ Soon within my tapestry ♪
So his favorite
is always going to be
the daughter
that didn't grow up.
♪ He sat down
on a river rock ♪
♪ And turned into a toad ♪
♪ It seemed that
he had fallen ♪
♪ Into someone's
wicked spell ♪
- Rosemary!
- Hi, Mom!
- Oh, good girl.
- I love you.
Hi, Daddy! I love you!
♪ As I watched him sorrow ♪
- ♪ There suddenly appeared ♪
- - Good girl.
♪ A figure gray and ghostly ♪
♪ Beneath a flowing beard ♪♪
I think
it's about that time, ladies.
Yes.
I'm gonna
wake this one up.
Mom.
Yeah, Bess, what are we doing?
Mom, it's time to wake up.
Mom.
Mom?
Mom? Mom?
Help, help, help, help!
Help!
Gat was right
about one thing.
Beechwood is a fairy tale,
and our castle's made of sand,
and we ignore
signs of trouble.
We pretend our pain away.
But not every fable
ends happily.
Some stories
have no hero at all.
Sometimes
all the king's horses
and all the king's men
never do put the broken
pieces together again.
Sometimes...
The castle crumbles.
♪ It takes an ocean
not to break ♪
♪ Company ♪
♪ It's a terrible love ♪
♪ And I'm walking
with spiders ♪
♪ It's a terrible love ♪
♪ That I'm walking in ♪
♪ It takes an ocean
not to break ♪