Kids, time to go!
Coming, Carla.
And I said I liked her name.
Cocoa's a nice name. Isn't it?
Yes. It is.
Come on, Bobby. Let's go.
All right. Let's go.
Good morning.
- Peggy.
- Good morning, Don.
Good morning, Mr. Draper.
Hollis.
You hear about Marilyn? Poor thing.
It's very upsetting.
I can't say I'm surprised.
The few things I know about her.
You just don't imagine her
ever being alone.
She was so famous.
Some people just hide in plain sight.
My mother and sister keep calling.
Suicide is disturbing.
I keep thinking about Joe DiMaggio.
We're lucky Playtex didn't go
for that Jackie/Marilyn campaign.
We'd have to pull everything indefinitely.
Yes, that's true.
I've never taken pills,
even when I had a headache.
Mr. Draper, good morning.
Would you like coffee?
I already had some.
They're waiting for you
in the conference room.
Do you need to go home?
No. Of course not.
I have Warren, and I have Todd.
Todd is a mail boy.
Why do you have him?
I'm paying him.
I'm sorry.
I don't understand this stupid blood drive.
You just hate that Media wins every year.
Wins what? How do you win a blood drive?
What do you win?
I don't know.
You're the best or something.
I'll be lucky if Accounts
can get eight people.
Well, Campbell's afraid of needles,
Duck doesn't give two craps.
Good morning.
Good morning, fellas.
Is this program already in progress?
We're expecting our most
successful blood drive ever.
Yes. Tell me everything.
I think we're very organized.
Creative, our department,
will be at 75 to 80%  participation.
Of course, I'm assuming you are in.
I am.
Do Kurt and Smitty count as one person?
Why don't you bore me with the details?
We're gonna take the lockers
out of the break room,
put 'em in the hallway in the morning.
There will be two litters, three nurses,
at least one old lady serving refreshments,
and pIenty of chairs.
Kinsey, I want you to pull
every intern and Iackey--
switchboard, elevator men.
Find out who wants to be
a copywriter for the day.
DoIlar a head.
That's not fair.
You're in Accounts.
You should have thought of it.
Just to be clear,
do I get the dollar for each person I get,
or do they get it for giving blood?
The people giving blood.
This is for mankind, Kinsey.
That's the money they'd make
actually being in the art department.
So what is the prize?
Helping another human being.
Also, there will be women fainting.
I'd think you'd like that.
If this was a flat-out athletic competition,
Accounts would win,
without a doubt.
What an elegant surrender.
And put up more posters.
I can't believe I have to say that
to you people.
Apparently, if we get 1 00%  participation,
which Media will do its best to aid,
they're going to put us in the Times.
I booked a photographer, just in case.
Good.
NBC's having the Mitch Miller
concert on Thursday.
Any chance I could show
you and Mrs. Draper off?
We'd love to, but--
. . .my kid is sick.
You'll know what that means soon enough.
Shot down.
That was quick.
What do we have today?
The 1 0:00 with Miss Holloway
to go over traffic for new business,
4:00 with Ron Venincasa
from Ace Hardware,
and Mr. Sterling moved the meeting
with Boston Edison to 5.
I assume to have it bleed
into the cocktail hour.
May I?
There was a bit of confusion last night.
I think I made a terrible mistake.
What happened?
Your daughter called and asked
when you would be back
from your business trip
because her mother wasn't sure.
You don't have to tell me anything,
but I didn't know what to say.
I said Wednesday.
I know I should have said I don't know.
Mrs. Draper is working out some things.
I understand.
I'm sure it won't come up again.
I thought it would be over by now,
I guess, and there'd be no need to--
I'm sorry about that.
It goes without saying that this is personal,
and I'd appreciate your keeping it that way.
Of course.
I'd also avoid giving me concerned looks.
Mr. Draper, I hope you've noticed
I'm a discreet person.
I don't know you at all,
and this is personal,
and it's not up for discussion.
Of course.
If you need anything,
I'm right out there.
I'm at the Roosevelt
if there's an emergency.
In an interview just weeks before her death,
Miss Monroe angrily protested to a reporter
about attacks on stars.
"We're what's okay with
the movie business," she said.
"Management is what's
wrong with the business."
Mr. Campbell, Miss Olson,
and Mr. Romano are here.
Send them in.
My oldest just turned 30,
and she's had a string of bad beaux.
It's very upsetting.
Can I get you kids anything?
- I'm fine.
- I'll have something.
They're probably walking over.
Dress rehearsal, Freddie.
I'll do introductions.
Jeff Hartung's wife just had a baby.
Boy or girl?
That's good.
Then I talk about Volkswagen.
No. Don said we only
bring up Volkswagen
if they don't like what we've presented.
Okay. Then I throw it to you, Freddie.
Thank you, Freddie.
"I just got a brand-new
Samsonite Silhouette,
"and I hate it.
"Don't get me wrong.
"I love the shape, the size, the color,
"and I love the Silhouette
because it's a Samsonite,
so I know we're gonna go
lots of places together,"
see lots of things,
collect a lifetime of memories.
I hate my Silhouette because it's empty.
Then Sal.
Shouldn't the artwork come first?
What about unveiIing it?
You know how excited they get.
Freddie?
What the hell, Freddie?
What--
What were we talking about?
Two types of travelers.
Freddie, do you have
another pair of trousers here?
Why?
Jesus.
I'll fix this.
I'm gonna-- I need a minute.
I gotta think.
Freddie?
Is he dead?
No, he's not dead. He passed out.
He's fine.
The Hartungs are at reception.
We'll be right there. Thanks, Abigail.
He can't leave this room.
They're all from Colorado.
I guess I could push it until tomorrow,
book them another night at the Carlyle.
Should I just cancel it?
I should talk to Don.
That's not necessary.
I can handle this.
Fine.
Jesus. It's a suitcase.
Peggy, you can do it, right?
You think it's gonna be better tomorrow?
Shit.
It'll be fine.
We'll tell them Freddie's sick. It's true.
I'll go to reception.
You two go to the conference room
and act like you've been waiting,
but don't look mad.
Someone telI Freddie's girl it's cancelled.
I don't want him wandering in.
It's disgusting.
There's no need for that.
Can I speak to you for a minute?
Carla?
I forgot you were coming by.
Are you okay?
I haven't been feeling weIl.
Oh, no, Betty.
You and Don are still
coming tonight, l hope.
We'd love to.
I just don't think I'Il be up to it.
That ruins things.
Well, you wanted to borrow
the black chiffon, right?
Come upstairs.
Are you sure?
I don't know who I'm gonna talk to.
Raymond has to work these things.
And I got you out of bed?
I am so sorry.
Give me the black one, and I'll go.
Nonsense.
I think my waist is higher than yours.
What do you have that's generous?
I don't know.
How about this?
You'll look like sherbet.
Long white gloves.
I can't wear those after Gypsy.
Think you'll be better
by lunch on Thursday?
I'm looking forward to it.
This is youthful.
It doesn't matter. I'm invisible.
That's not true.
Raymond's sweet about it,
but he's so easy to please.
That's sweet.
It is.
I think, what did I do to deserve him?
Then I spend his money on Dr. Weinberg.
I got my diagnosis the other day.
I'm bored .
That's too bad.
I saw Arthur have a fight with Tara,
and I have been having
ridiculous dreams since.
I wish you'd come ride with us again.
It reaIly takes the pressure off.
Think you can carry this?
No, ma'am.
You shouldn't talk to him so much.
I know. It's embarrassing.
It's a switch you can flip
on and off, you know.
Really?
You don't even think about this, do you?
Don's perfect.
Can we talk at lunch?
I'm really not feeling well.
Take them all.
No. Just these two.
That's it for today.
Many's the time I've dreamed
of finding you like this.
What are you doing here?
You're right.
I'll just get all my beIongings,
- and I'lI leave.
- It's 4:30.
You're supposed to be
sitting in a bar somewhere
waiting for Boston Edison.
How often do you come in here?
Not that often.
What's wrong, Red?
Do you miss me?
She was so young.
Not you, too.
Yes, I'm just another frivolous secretary.
It's a terrible tragedy,
but that woman's a stranger.
Roosevelt--
I hated him, but I felt like I knew him.
A lot of peopIe felt like they knew her.
You should be sensitive to that.
Hey. You're not like her.
Physically, a little,
but don't tell me that makes you sad.
It's not a joke.
This worId destroyed her.
ReaIly? She was a movie star
who had everything and everybody,
and she threw it away.
But, hey, if you want to be sad.
One day you'll lose someone
who's important to you.
You'll see.
It's very painful.
Are you feeling better, Mommy?
Yes. I'll join you next time.
I'm surprised Daddy let you in the car.
You kids should go to bed .
Wash your face and brush your teeth.
I'll tuck you in.
Good night.
You just came back.
Now you're leaving again?
It'll go by like that.
Come here.
It won't be that long, Salamander.
Go.
Listen, she called my office.
She did? When?
Monday.
What do you want me to say?
I think she expected you
over the weekend.
You said you didn't want me here,
and then you do.
I didn't want them involved in this.
Obviously, that's impossible.
What do you want to do?
I mean, how Iong is this going to go on?
We have to tell them something.
Like what?
Okay. How about. . .
I'm working on an account.
They're putting me up in Philadelphia,
but I'lI be home every weekend.
Jesus. Did you just think that up?
Or I could just come home.
Bets, what do you want?
Listen, if your mind's made up,
I'm not gonna taIk you into it.
I thought you can talk
anyone into anything.
Good night.
Would you like coffee?
And a bear claw.
What's this?
I thought you could use
a few more shirts in your rotation.
Thank you. Submit your receipt.
Your correspondence is on your desk.
Let me get you breakfast.
I'lI be right back.
And Mr. Kinsey said
that l have to drag you,
if necessary, to the blood drive.
You're not a fainter, are you?
I don't faint, but I might cry after.
Peggy.
Hello, Freddie.
How'd it go yesterday?
I Ieft word with Abigail. They loved it.
Good. Good.
I was thinking about
letting you talk anyway.
I have to apologize
for putting you in that spot.
Freddie, it's over.
There's no reason to talk about it.
Of course.
Did they ask about me?
We told them you were sick.
That's good.
So on Monday,
when they get back to Colorado,
I'll give them a caIl and sew things up.
That's a great idea.
Bobby.
Mrs. Draper. I'm sorry to bother you.
It's okay, Carla.
It's a beautiful day.
I'm going to take the children out again.
ls that good?
Whatever they want.
Can I do anything for you?
If you want, I can draw a bath.
No, thank you.
I've been married
almost 20 years, you know.
I really don't want to talk about this.
I'm sorry.
Carla. . . .
I haven't been sleeping very well.
You know what helps?
Splash cold water
on your face and go outside.
You'lI notice things
are right where you left them.
I'm usually part of the meeting
before the meeting.
Relax, Don. Sit down.
This is all being done in the right way.
Campbell.
Well, Don, I'm afraid
we have some bad news.
We were on the launch pad
yesterday for Samsonite,
and Freddie Rumsen pissed his pants.
What?
He's not talking about nerves here.
He's taIking about a wet pair of pants.
Really?
How'd the presentation go?
Don, it's conduct unbefitting.
Of Freddie Rumsen?
We're lucky Campbell here
grabbed the controls.
He locked Rumsen up
and threw Peggy OIson in.
We're lucky the bench is deep.
We have to cut him loose.
Is that necessary?
The man is a train wreck.
We at least need to get him
off this account.
They called already.
They're thrilled with Peggy.
No. I don't want him
on any of my accounts.
This could have happened in a meeting.
But it didn't.
That'll be all, boys.
Thank you for bringing this
to our attention.
We're not doing him any favors
keeping him around.
Duck's a teetotaler.
He's been gunning
for Freddie since day 1 .
He's got a point.
We can't even tell Cooper about this.
You know his whole thing with germs.
I don't think it's in my contract
that Duck can fire someone
in my department.
You don't have a contract.
And I can fire anyone I want to.
We really don't have a choice.
You can still get him to give blood.
The agencies will laugh about this,
but the clients,
they already think we're all like that.
We'll say it's a six-month leave of absence
so he can go for the cure.
He'll know what that means.
You don't want to throw him away.
Your loyalty is starting
to become a Iiability.
Let's do this before he finds out.
We don't need any more accidents.
Dinner tonight.
You need to call the missus?
I'll make it.
Mr. Case.
Betty.
How are you?
It's a beautiful day.
Have you just ridden,
or are you about to ride?
I can never tell whether
you're before or after.
I'm on my way out.
It's good to see you.
How are your children?
They're wonderful.
Have you seen Sara Beth lately?
I think so. Monday, maybe?
That's good news.
I'm glad she came.
Why?
Nothing.
I had noticed she seemed distracted.
I shouldn't have said anything.
Is there anything I can do?
No. But she'd be glad
to know you're concerned.
I think you make her feel better.
She talks about you a lot.
I didn't mean to embarrass you.
You know what?
The three of us should go to lunch
and have some fun.
It would cheer her up.
It's a great idea.
Thursday?
Café Soleil in Old Town.
1 :00.
I'll pick up the check.
See you then.
That was nothing.
I'm thinking of doing it again.
You should smoke a cigarette right now.
I know they said not to,
but I'm telling you,
my knees buckled.
I thought I was gonna perform
a full Freddie Rumsen.
Jesus.
Hello, Don. We're in the lead.
Turns out Hollis has a novel.
Good.
Too bad Freddie made
his donation yesterday.
He's a real wizz in advertising.
Jesus.
What are you doing?
What do you mean?
That's none of your business.
Freddie had a bad day.
Can't you find something else to do
besides dining on the drama
of other people's lives
like a bunch of teenage girls?
Sorry, Don. It's funny.
Sure.
It's just a man's name, right?
Could you leave us alone for a moment?
Truth to tell, I was a little nervous.
I'd never given one of those
funny speeches before
where you say what you don't mean.
Freddie, we've reached a decision.
You're gonna take
a six-month leave of absence.
Is that necessary?
The door wiIl be open.
It was a snafu.
Isn't the embarrassment enough?
Full salary. You dry out, come back,
we'll see where we are.
Clients love me. I keep up with them.
We have laughs.
Monday morning, I'll be good as new.
I promise.
There's a line, Freddie,
and you wet it.
You see? We're laughing about it.
What's the big deal?
You remember Bob Peebles?
How mean he was?
He fired his secretary,
and he threw all her things
out the window,
including her keys.
That was good for morale.
What is this about?
Duck PhiIlips?
He's as dry as a bone.
He doesn't understand this business.
Freddie, my father would
have fired you for this.
Your father drank more
than the two of you put together.
He used to come in
with his shirt on inside-out.
He admired you.
I , however, had different
feelings at the time.
When we first met,
Bonny Prince Sterling here
thought I was a coward
because I was in the Signal Corps.
I didn't know it was only
for his last six months.
I thought he was a typist.
Turns out before that,
he was in charge of killing people--
and by people, I mean Germans.
It was a long time ago.
Come on. Be proud.
What was it? Like 1 5 of them.
That's impressive.
Look, l can be completely in control.
My podiatrist went to Hazleton.
Came back a new man with great stories.
Only drinks beer now.
It's the best thing, Freddie.
Well, I guess you get dealt
the hand you get dealt, right?
I can pull myself together.
I got a great book.
Maybe l'll head to PhilIy or Boston.
They're all dying to do what we do here.
You know l'll recommend you.
Fantastic. So this couId be good.
There's a lot of great towns.
My father sold greeting cards.
He used to come into the kitchen,
unroll this map on the table,
and put a finger on a spot
and say something like,
"Memphis. Who wants
to live in Memphis?"
I'd say, "Not me."
We had only been in Springfield
for nine months.
Meanwhile, here we are.
To New York.
Come on. Let's make a night of it.
Really?
AbsoluteIy.
To Monday morning.
It'll be here faster than you think.
Hold off on the menus.
We're going to take another lap first.
Bring some bread.
Give me 5 bucks.
No. Sorry. Don.
Can I help you gentlemen?
Swordfish.
And who are you here to see?
You can't do that now.
I just gave you the money.
Come on. Do we look like cops?
Sir?
I have a very good friend--
I can't remember the guy's name.
How about if I give you our names?
I'm Dick Dollars,
this is Mike Moneybags,
and this--
Tilden Katz.
Fine.
Here.
That's a 20.
Gentlemen.
Is it Milwaukee?
Yes, it is.
Son of a bitch.
The Chuck-a-luck.
Going to need some cocktails.
Hey, isn't that the champ back there?
For another couple of months.
You're crazy.
Nobody's gonna beat him.
Hey, loosen up.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Just in time.
Canadian Club neat,
Wolfschmidt Gibson,
Granddad rocks.
Pete Campbell.
I would have never thought
I was in his way.
You know, you bet badly.
Obviously.
No. I mean you win a few times,
you got to start really putting it out there.
You kept betting the same thing.
You're so good at this,
why don't you quit your job?
See? He's having a great time.
Hello, there.
Are we winners or losers?
Losers tonight,
but winners in general.
You know, BBDO hired a colored kid.
What do you think of that?
I think I'm glad I'm not that kid.
I'm sorry.
Can we get you a drink or something?
No.
I'm sorry. Were you interested?
No, I'm fine. Thank you.
I know what's going on.
You come in too early.
You got dry cleaning
moving in and out.
I can't remember the Iast time it was
you went out spur of the moment.
Send off Freddie,
I had to send off Freddie.
Come on.
I've been in your particular situation.
I heard you chaired the blood drive.
Where are you, the Stanhope?
The Biltmore?
- Roger.
- Did she kick you out? You leave?
There's nothing to talk about.
Look, people make mistakes.
You feel bad about it.
You think things over,
and in the end,
you do the grand gesture for her.
It'll be easy for you . You're creative.
Roger, will you stop?
All I'm gonna say is
do you want to be right,
or do you want to be married?
I know marriage isn't a natural state,
but you do it.
Why?
I don't know.
The kids.
Again!
And don't fool yourself.
There are other things.
Think about when you met her.
Okay. I'm sorry.
You're so secretive.
Hey, Don.
Look who's here.
If it isn't the man
in the gray flannel suit.
What the hell was that for?
We're gonna go.
Don't worry about it.
I'm sure it's not the first time
he's been punched in the face.
Hey, Floyd.
How'd I do?
I'm sure there are 20 people
who want to thank you for that.
It wasn't exactly a fair match-up.
I think that's gonna do it for me.
Yeah. Me, too.
It's getting late.
- This was a nice evening.
- Hold on.
Don and I are going to the East Side.
You take it.
AbsoluteIy.
l'd like to stay and get
all sentimental with you,
but l got to go and give
a Chinaman a music lesson.
Want to watch how I do it,
unzipping the fly and everything?
Yeah. Go to heIl.
Take him to McCann.
This was fun.
Good.
I'm gonna miss you.
You're talented.
I don't know.
Thank you, Freddie.
It means a lot.
What am l gonna do?
What am l going to tell Violet?
I don't know.
It sounded like you had a plan.
I'm not kidding, Don.
What am l gonna do?
It's not an ending.
It's a fresh start.
If I don't go into that office every day,
who am I?
Where do you live, Freddie?
1 52 Riverside Drive.
Apartment 604.
No matter what he says,
take him there.
Good night, Freddie.
Good-bye, Don.
See, I find if I stick
with the clear liquors--
vodka, gin-- I know where I stand.
I'm the opposite.
So what do you think,
because you gave blood,
the whiskey made you a little angry?
That was a real
Archibald Whitman maneuver.
Who's that?
This hothead drunk I used to know.
Jimmy Barrett's a weaseI. Enjoy.
So what's going on with you?
I'm at the Roosevelt.
See? That wasn't so hard.
I really don't want to discuss it, Roger.
Why? Because you feel so bad?
l've been there.
No, I don't feel bad at all.
I mean, sometimes.
Mostly, I'm just relieved.
Really?
Did you falI in love?
No.
That'd be easier.
Then I'd know what to do.
Easier--
There's some incredible woman,
and someone's gonna end up with her,
but it can't be you.
Why not?
'Cause we're married.
I don't know.
It's your life.
You don't know how long it's gonna be,
but you know it's got a bad ending.
You have to move forward.
As soon as you can
figure out what that is.
Two coronaries.
Gotta move forward.
It's your life.
I mean, this can't be it, right?
We're in it together.
That's true.
You wanted to see me?
Close the door.
That was quite a presentation you gave.
The Samsonite people are thrilled.
That's good to hear.
They've requested that you be reassigned
as the copywriter on their account.
What about Freddie?
Freddie's decided
to take a few months off.
He did? When's he coming back?
It doesn't matter.
You'll be taking over all of his business.
Are you sure?
You know, I really don't like
walking into an ambush
from Duck and Pete Campbell.
I don't know why anyone
had to know about that.
Even me?
No, of course you,
but. . .
I just thought that--
I Iove Freddie.
What's your point?
Don't feel bad about
being good at your job.
I wish it hadn't happened this way.
That's the way it happened.
Congratulations.
- Miss Olson--
- In a minute.
You couldn't keep your mouth shut.
Mr. Campbell.
Do you know what you did
to Freddie Rumsen?
For just cause.
You didn't have to tell Don.
You told on Mr. Rumsen?
Do you mind?
It would have gotten out anyway.
Right, and he'd be some legend
in one of those stupid stories.
Remember the guy who wet his pants
before the big meeting?
Instead, he's finished.
Why do you feel bad for him?
Those people always blame
their problems on society.
He did it to himself.
Those people have no self-control.
lf it wasn't for him,
I'd stilI be a secretary.
If it wasn't for me,
you'd still be a junior copywriter.
I refuse to feel bad .
We're going to get raises.
You could get his office.
Now, I'll go first.
Congratulations, Peggy.
Congratulations, Pete.
Good to see you.
This is me.
It's nice to see you.
What are you doing here?
Betty invited me for lunch,
but we're gonna need
another place setting.
We're gonna be three.
Betty didn't say you'd be joining us.
I hope I'm not intruding.
She thought it'd be fun.
It will be.
It's just gotten infinitely more fun.
I think I need whatever you're having.
It's a gin and tonic.
Nothing speciaI.
It's perfect.
Keep stirring.
Bobby, go get two spoons.
So with Indian Point open now,
we should be able to use
even a modest safety record.
We were spitballing about a cartoon turtle.
Kids. Keeps it friendly and nature-loving,
and then we just hammer
the Ravenswood area
until they're ready for the next plant.
You on board with that?
Yes.
I want to see schedules,
and I want to see this turtle.
He doesn't want to be disturbed.
Hello, Don.
Hello, Mona. Jane, it's okay.
Just stop.
What?
I don't even know what to say to you.
About what?
Don't act innocent.
He's leaving me for his secretary.
Roger?
He's in love,
and you said it was great.
Mona, I didn't say anything.
"It's your life.
You have to move forward."
Mona, I didn't mean it that way.
25 years of marriage.
I want you to calm down.
Don't make me make a scene.
We should talk about this.
You can talk to Margaret.
Listen, Don, I can explain.
I want her off my desk.
Subtitled By J.R. Media Services, Inc.
Burbank, CA