Previously on Dexter...
I'm pregnant.
I just think I'm gonna be a lousy
father. I don't wanna screw the kid up.
Who are we kidding ?
You're gonna be a great father.
- What do you have on Freebo, Maria ?
- Ramon.
- We're working on some new angles.
- Which means you've got shit.
He's obsessed.
He's drinking more than usual.
He's not going to stop looking for Oscar's
killer until it takes him all the way down.
I only have one person
I can trust any more.
Yourself.
I was thinking of you.
- What you need ?
- I need Freebo.
Come on man, what,
you Google him or something ?
Why wouldn't they want to support
a colleague during his shining moment ?
You're like the foulest person I've ever met.
I'm gonna do you a favor.
Call this guy.
Tell him you wanna cash in
one of my coupons.
He's an informant
from my days in Narcotics.
You, uh, you looking for
anything special tonight ?
Might be more than an hour.
Take a pass, Sergeant.
I hate anyone
who disgraces the badge.
Are we good ?
You keep your dick in your pants
and then we're good.
Rita, we're connected. I feel you.
You're what makes me real.
And that's how I know I wanna marry you.
Yes ! Yes, we will marry you.
There are many ways
to stop the heart.
Electric shock.
Bad diet.
Sever the aorta -
my personal favorite.
But to start one beating, this is a first.
There. That's the heart.
Oh, Dex, that's our baby.
Our baby. It's incredible.
Rita, gushing with the runaway emotion
any parent would feel
seeing their unborn child for the first time.
Any parent except me.
I'd say you're at nine to ten weeks.
All I feel is her hand clenching mine.
She's stronger than she looks.
Can we get a picture to show the kids ?
I can no longer deny
that I'm going to be a father.
Up until now,
I've been avoiding its inevitability.
It's like a lamp in a room
that's always been there.
And now it's suddenly turned on.
Don't worry.
Everything looks perfectly normal.
Yes.
Front or back pocket ?
- You lost me.
- The picture of the baby.
Front or back pocket ?
- How'd you know I'd have it with me ?
- You're a first-time dad, aren't you ?
Ah !
Oh, this is amazing !
This is a human life.
It is... overwhelming.
This picture right here makes it real.
Your life is gonna change forever, man.
Hey ! We're playing here !
You could kill somebody !
Sorry.
I got half my mind
still in the office, you know ?
Oh, there's your ball.
So I got this case, you know ?
South Beach guy
kills his wife on a cruise ship.
And I got no jurisdiction because
she goes missing in international waters.
My only hope right now is the Feds.
- How do you know he's guilty ?
- Oh, he's guilty.
Five years ago, he kills his first wife.
Drug overdose.
His pills. No alibi.
Then he uses her money to hire this legal
dream team to confuse the jury and...
They had to let him go.
Dexter, my hands are tied by the law,
and the defense attorneys
get to wipe their asses with it.
And everything that I believe in
is compromised.
That's you.
It seems Miguel and I
understand each other
better than either one of us knows.
I could do us both a favor
and look into this wife killer.
When it comes to my brand of justice,
I don't have to compromise.
Ooh.
Sliced it.
Yeah.
Thank you again for inviting us.
That massage was amazing.
We spend enough money
to be members here.
At least now I have somebody
to go to the spa with.
All of that stuff,
that's not for men, right, Dex ?
Lying naked on a table, helpless,
no thanks.
So, Rita, why don't you tell Dexter
my great idea ?
Great idea ?
Well, Syl has offered to list
my house with her agency
so we can buy something
bigger together.
You're just throwing money away
on that apartment.
And that way you can move in sooner.
I was actually thinking
I might keep my place.
You were ?
Well, I could always sublet it.
At some point we're gonna need
a bigger home.
You definitely need something
that you can grow into.
This is how Custer must have felt,
surrounded on all sides, doomed.
So why don't we talk about all this
after we eat ?
Oh, the line's thinning.
Come on, Rita.
You have got to try these crêpes.
It's going to be OK. Trust me.
I'm so sorry, man.
Syl, she gets these ideas in her head,
and it's like you can't stop her.
I guess I always knew at some point
I'd have to give up my place.
I just didn't think it'd be so soon.
Every man needs his privacy.
Some more than others.
But that's why God created golf.
How many times have I walked
down this sidewalk ?
Sun in my face.
Cool ocean breeze on my skin.
Taken a dip in the pool to relax,
appreciating the wisdom
of those three little words -
no children allowed.
Are those times gone forever ?
Before I even think about
following up on Miguel's lead,
I need to make sure
Ethan Turner meets my code.
How can Rita expect me
to just pick up and move ?
This is my home.
My sanctuary.
Careful.
Leave it.
Not really Rita's style.
But it's mine.
Not any more, son.
In marriage, everything's 50-50.
What's yours... is Rita's.
Better hope she doesn't insist
on a place with central air.
Rita and Syl may be busy planning my life
and where I'll live.
But there are some things
I still control.
Right on time. You're getting pretty good
at this secret meeting stuff.
Yeah, well, we've done it enough.
With bumpkus to show for it.
It's "bupkus".
Not "bumpkus". It's Yiddish.
No, it's not.
- You wanna bet ?
- How much ?
Make it a million.
I'll take a check.
Where's your guy ?
In the alley behind you.
Wonderful.
I love the smell of ass in the morning.
Hey, you're the one that's been
all over mine for leads.
Don't be hating where I find them.
I know, I know.
Well, you better split before we get made.
Well, that's cute.
- What ?
- You. Trying to protect me like that.
It's cute.
I'm trying to protect my investigation.
Uh-huh.
And fuck you.
- What the hell ?
- He wasn't like this earlier.
I'm trying to find whoever's skinning people,
not to stage an intervention.
You think your murders
are somehow connected to Freebo ?
He used to score from Freebo.
It's worth a shot, right ?
Excuse me.
Anyone in there ?
Anyone fucking in there at all ?
I'll bet you're real good with kids too.
Hey, Tilly.
Hey, I got that H for you, man.
- Where ?
- It's right here.
But listen, I need you to think
real hard for me first, Tilly.
Now, when was the last time
you saw Freebo ?
Fucker's gone, man.
Wendell said he's not coming back.
Who the fuck is Wendell ?
You wanna see Freebo,
you gotta go through Wendell.
Sheriff 2-1,
this is dispatch. Wagon is on its way.
Metro Homicide.
What are we doing at a sheriff's
crime scene anyway ?
- Sheriff, you're blocking my light.
- Whoa, Jesus.
- Excuse me.
- Sheriffs are responding
to a bulletin I issued regarding
any victims with missing skin.
Excuse me.
Same MO as our torture murder ?
Remember, you two are just here
to observe. This is the sheriff's turf.
They're gonna investigate the scene,
see what they can come up with.
What's up with him ?
He doesn't joke around anymore.
He dresses better. He's polite.
Maybe someone pointed out
the error in his ways.
- Who called this in ?
- Neighbors.
I just got off the phone
with the sheriff's department.
They've confirmed their skinning victim
is related to ours.
That gives us three victims. They're sending
someone over to look at our case files,
and we'll be establishing
a joint investigation.
- This is our investigation, Lieutenant.
- You can't expect us to give over our files.
No one is giving over anything.
It's a matter of professional courtesy.
We're still in charge.
Now, I've had the sheriff's lab send over
all forensics. I want both your input.
- My slate's clear.
- I'll talk with the medical examiner.
Another four-hour erection ?
Anything else ?
I've got Unis bringing in a 15-year-old kid
named Wendell Owens.
He was Freebo's doorman, which means
he might be able to connect the dots
between his boss and why people
who knew him keep winding up dead.
I may be one of those dots.
He's a minor.
Get consent from a parent to question him.
I'll make sure everything's
done by the book.
All right, I want updates on the hour.
- Good work, partner.
- Yeah, right.
Wendell.
I doubt this boy would recognize me
from the day I met his dead boss.
But why take the chance ?
Dexter Morgan.
Hey, Dex.
Listen, I'm gonna have to cancel our lunch.
- Everything all right ?
- Rough morning, man.
Feds informed me that they're not gonna
move forward on this cruise ship case.
Lack of evidence.
Got a witness puts this son of a bitch
on the deck with his wife
just before she went missing,
and he's still gonna walk. Again !
Did I mention he left his first wife's
teenage daughters penniless ?
No need.
A whole family destroyed.
We could meet later if you want.
No, no, I'm gonna be in court, man.
How 'bout tomorrow ?
I may have plans. I'll let you know.
There's due diligence to be done.
How long is this gonna take ?
The sooner you tell me where we can find
your mom, the sooner you're outta here.
She wasn't at your house.
We can't reach her by phone.
Does she have a job ?
She does what she has to do.
Same as me.
You know, I was about your age
when my mom died.
Suddenly, my father's
raising two teenagers by himself,
so I get how hard it is
for a single parent to always be there.
Yeah, I bet you had it real bad.
No, I didn't.
My dad worked really hard to get me
and my brother the things he didn't have.
So I got why he wasn't always home.
But after a while, I even stopped
looking for him at my softball games.
Didn't mean he didn't love me,
didn't mean it didn't hurt.
You played softball for real ?
First base.
But you don't look gay.
You hungry ?
Yeah, but not for any
of that vending machine shit.
Well, I'll tell you what, if you're brave
enough, there's a roach coach outside.
I'm buying.
OK, I'll take some burgers, fries
and onion rings.
Deal.
Partner, would you keep an eye
on our guest ?
- Getting anywhere with the kid ?
- Sort of.
- You and Rita set a date yet ?
- Not yet.
- Well, are you gonna move in with her first ?
- Where's this going ?
I need to know, so I can break the lease
on my place and move into yours.
What makes everybody think
I'm just gonna give up my apartment ?
Maybe cause you're getting married.
Like there's room for Rita
and the kids at your place.
No offense, but you're the last person
who needs a fuck pad.
Dexter. Officer Morgan.
Can you tell me
where I might find Lieutenant LaGuerta ?
Thank you so much.
Guess we know who the sheriff's
department sent to look into our files.
Big fucking mistake.
That guy's wound way too tight.
And coming from me,
that's saying something.
You gonna take the fridge ?
- Thank you.
- They keep getting younger, huh ?
- Who'd this one kill ?
- The boy's not a suspect.
We think he was working for Freebo.
I have to say, I'm surprised the sheriff's
department chose you as their liaison.
I'm not here to make friends.
I'm here to do my job.
I've known you your entire adult life, Ramon,
so let's cut the bullshit.
You're using this case
to insert yourself into Miami Metro's
investigation of your brother's death.
If our victim can help track down
my brother's killer in the process,
so be it.
As one lieutenant to another,
you know I could go over your head
and get you pulled off this assignment.
But I'm not gonna do that.
I know you and Oscar were close
and he meant a great deal to me as well.
So you will have
this department's full cooperation
to a point.
If it turns out that these cases
are not connected, the cooperation ends.
¿ Entiendes ?
Claro.
I need to thank Miguel for introducing me
to a new hobby.
And for supporting an old one.
After the first wife's money ran out,
Ethan didn't take long to find the next
wealthy woman to woo, marry,
and throw overboard.
Maybe I can return the favor
on that last part.
Have both tanks delivered to the ship.
- I'll need a dive skin too.
- You got it.
Heading out to sea ?
Caribbean cruise.
Leaving tomorrow.
Do you know any good
dive schools around here ?
Yeah. But they all require hours
for certification.
If I were you, I'd cut a few corners,
head over to Bimini.
They'll have you under the water
in less than a day.
Bimini. That's close.
I could be there and back in my boat.
The water's beautiful there.
It's my first port of call.
Maybe I could take the wife, get her off
my back for never doing anything with her.
You'll have more fun if you don't.
I'm sure I will.
There you are.
Good news. Wendell's mother
finally answered her phone.
- Patrol's bringing her upstairs now.
- Yes. Thank the baby fucking Jesus.
You do know I'm Catholic, right ?
I'm sorry, but I've had that kid
at my desk all afternoon.
Hey, you ever hear the word
"bumpkus" ?
I think it's "bupkus".
- Shit.
- Yeah, hold on now.
There's this cold case
I'm looking at, a dead john.
Now, when you were working vice, did you
bust the same places over and over again ?
Um, not really.
Most guys are regulars,
so word gets out quick if a place is hot.
So we'd move the decoys around.
But if you really want to know about
paying for sex, you should talk to Masuka.
Hey, Vince, hold up.
Did you get a chance to look at the sheriff's
department forensics regarding their vic ?
I fucking would, if they'd fucking send them.
I've called four fucking times.
Man ! Somebody needs a hug.
I'd offer, but I don't know what I'd catch.
Can I go now ?
You know, I can take inappropriate Masuka.
I can take porn-loving Masuka.
I can even take flatulent Masuka.
But this dress-shoe-wearing,
"please and thank you" zombie Masuka
is fucking creeping me out.
What's going on ?
Maybe I'm realizing no one
around here is my friend.
The only time you people even acknowledge
me is when you want something.
That's not so.
We put you on our bowling team.
Only to keep everyone's handicap higher
to sandbag the other teams.
- OK, that's true, but...
- Not one person read my paper.
Not one fucking person showed up
at the conference I spoke at.
This is about your stupid paper ?
You guys just don't get it.
You hurt my feelings.
What the fuck ?
Where's the kid ?
The mother wouldn't give consent.
I had to cut him loose.
Did you explain to her
how important it was that we talk to him ?
The moment I brought up Freebo's name,
she clammed up.
Word is the last person who talked to
the cops about Freebo wound up dead.
I spent all day getting through to that kid.
He would have talked, or he would have
convinced his mother to let him talk.
- She was never gonna cooperate.
- You coulda waited until I got back.
Look, this is no reflection
on the work you did here.
No, it's a reflection on how little
you think of me and my work.
You think I cut this kid loose
to make you look bad ?
I'm not sure any more.
Partner.
Hey, baby. You want a date ?
Hey, sugar. What you look...
You have got to be kidding me.
I'm not here for that, honest.
Your... You know, your...
- You're blushing.
- I'm not.
So what, uh, what are you doing
down here, Sergeant ?
Cause I gotta get back to work.
I came here because I...
I wanted to know if...
if you'd like to grab
something to eat sometime.
You know, to talk.
And to eat.
I'm not interested.
I rarely date cops.
"Rarely," does that mean "never" ?
If I meant "never",
I would have said "never".
Dex, is that you ?
I'm in the kitchen.
- What smells so good ?
- It's a surprise.
Look. Brochures of houses.
I know it's fast. But Syl and I spent
the whole day doing drive-bys,
and these are the ones
I fell in love with.
All of them ?
Well, they're in great school districts,
big yards, plenty of bedrooms,
central air.
I thought we could go through these
after dinner and have Syl
schedule some showings for tomorrow.
I understand that, as man and wife,
Rita and I will have to live
under the same roof.
So why is it the only word
echoing in my head is...
No.
No ?
Um...
OK, I guess we don't
have to look at all of them.
No.
"No" doesn't really work
in a relationship, Dexter.
"Can we talk about it ?"
is a little more productive.
I'm sorry,
but I don't want to look at houses.
Not now anyway.
Fine, that's all you had to say.
If Syl and I go out to look tomorrow in the
morning, can you watch Astor and Cody ?
No, I'm going fishing tomorrow.
I'm gonna be gone all day.
And you were gonna tell me this when ?
Rita, this is the first
I'm hearing about house hunting.
I can't just drop everything at the last minute
because you want me to.
Dinner will be ready in five minutes.
It's a roast.
Your favorite.
I double-checked
Ethan's ship itinerary.
He's in Bimini today only.
Gives me one shot
to head him off at the pass.
Sorry, Rita, but right now I need this
more than a big yard and a two-car garage.
Hey !
Ahoy.
Let me guess - Syl ?
She might have mentioned
that Rita and she were going house hunting
because a certain gilipollas
decided that he'd rather go fishing.
- Gilipollas ?
- You don't wanna know.
So this is the boat you keep talking about,
huh ? Wow, she's a beauty.
- You gonna take me out on her sometime ?
- Sure thing.
So what brings you out here ?
Thought maybe we could grab some food
before you go out.
Kind of like a rain check for yesterday.
Ah, can't leave the boat.
Everything's onboard.
Olvidate. OK.
Don't worry about it.
So where are they biting ?
Um, heading up north, Mercy Reef.
Always had good luck there.
I got half a mind to postpone the
arraignment that I have and just go with you.
Please don't.
Nah. I gotta be in court.
Ah !
I'm gonna try to put out some fire
that your lieutenant started.
But I'm glad I caught you, you know ?
Hey, how 'bout whatever you catch,
we put on the grill tonight ?
Wish me luck.
Thanks for coming in early.
Lieutenant Prado wanted to get us
all up to speed on the Skinner case.
Thank you.
This is our vic's boyfriend.
Now, no one's seen him
since the night in question.
We could use your help
tracking him down.
Soderquist, Ramos, you're on it.
I was also hoping I could speak with
a couple of your previous witnesses.
"Speak with" as in
we didn't do it right the first time ?
Cases evolve.
Witnesses change their story.
Junior personnel, they make mistakes.
No disrespect.
Actually, it's a lot of disrespect.
You've come into our house twice.
You not only insult our police work,
now you're insulting one of the most
dedicated officers I've ever partnered with.
Yes, you.
It's bullshit, my man.
Let's not lose sight of the fact
that we want the same thing here -
to find whoever is responsible
for these murders.
Uh, there is one slight problem.
Your case has nothing to do with our case.
- The vic wasn't skinned ?
- Not like our previous victims.
There were minute traces of ink
in the papillary and reticular...
English.
Someone dug out a tattoo
from the back of her neck.
Postmortem.
Which is another reason why
I don't think we're looking at the same killer.
It's all right here
in the county medical examiner's report.
That's your opinion.
My lab thinks differently.
Let me see that.
- You're not taking this seriously, are you ?
- In a fucking heartbeat.
Do you know how many times
Vince Masuka's been published ?
He's our lead forensic investigator.
And there's no one better.
Our victim was strangled,
the same as yours.
Hemorrhaging in the eyes and bruising
would lead one to conclude strangulation.
Unless you're me.
You were so busy playing hide the sausage
with the ME's report,
you were hoping I'd miss the cotton fibers
in the nose and airways.
Your victim was smothered.
That's not opinion. That's science.
And science is one cold-hearted bitch
with a 14-inch strap-on.
- And he's back.
- Well, I think we're through here.
I'm not so sure your lieutenant
would agree, Sergeant.
Then you don't know her
as well as you thought, Lieutenant.
Ethan.
Apparently Ethan is looking for more
than adventure on the high seas.
Both of his deceased wives had prenups.
In a divorce, he would have
been lucky to keep the Rolex.
But he wanted it all.
Ethan made a choice.
And pretty soon, you're gonna
have to make one too, Dex.
Ethan chose to be rich
rather than married.
I, on the other hand,
chose to stay with Doris, even after...
You cheated on her ?
You think you and I
are so different, don't you ?
I'm nothing like you.
Really ?
You're here and Rita's back home.
You're cheating on her
and you don't even realize it.
I'll make time for my dark passenger
and for Rita.
It's about priorities, Dexter.
You're gonna have to choose
which one is your mistress
and which one is your wife.
And more importantly,
which one comes first.
Harry, you missed a spot.
Oh, hi, baby.
Hi, Mom.
Attention,
all Atlantic Sun Cruise passengers,
this is Bebay, your cruise director.
The next sea taxi is leaving Bimini
for our ship in 20 minutes.
It looked much bigger from out here.
You could always knock out a wall or two.
It's easier than you think.
How about the kitchen ?
Well, the bay window was nice.
But those cabinets...
Don't get bogged down in the cosmetic stuff.
How did it feel when you were inside ?
Like a home.
God, you're good.
You're my friend, Rita. I wouldn't
put you in something I didn't believe in.
And I believe that this home
can work for you.
For your family.
Oh...
What are the rules about using the
bathroom in a house you're showing ?
- No rules. You gotta go, you gotta go.
- All right.
Can I see your venture
passport, sir ? Thank you.
Keep coming.
Excuse me, sir. Can I take a look
at your venture passport ? Thank you.
Ma'am, could I see your pass ?
Thank you.
Attention all
Atlantic Sun Cruise passengers,
this is Bebay, your cruise director.
The sea taxi is departing Bimini
for our ship in five minutes.
Please remember that the last sea taxi of
the evening leaves the ship at 10:45 tonight.
All visitors, guests,
anyone who doesn't belong on board
must disembark at that time.
It'll be tight.
But I think both Ethan Turner and I
will be off the ship by that time.
Of course, only one of us
will be doing so because he wants to.
Rita ?
I'm bleeding.
Oh, my God.
All right, there's a hospital five blocks away.
Waiting for an ambulance
is only gonna take time.
- What about Dexter ?
- We'll call from the car.
Those things will kill you, you know ?
I'll talk to you later.
I've been by here four times
looking for you.
What for ?
The other cop said you couldn't talk to me.
Well, he's right. I can't. Officially.
But unofficially,
there's no reason you can't call me
just in case there's something
you want to tell me about your ex-boss.
Burgers, fries and onion rings.
I know the situation with
your mom not being around really sucks.
But if things get really bad,
you use that card and call me, OK ?
I kept my nose outta Freebo's business.
It was safer that way.
Do you have any idea where he is ?
No.
I know he was into someone
for some major cash.
He was pretty scared.
That's probably why
he's hiding out somewhere.
That explains why someone's trying so hard
to find him. They want their money back.
- So are we done ?
- We're done.
- Oh, yeah, one other thing.
- Yeah ?
When you find that jerk-off, tell him
he still owes me three weeks' pay.
Thanks.
Watch yourself out here, OK ?
OK.
- Miguel, thank God you're here.
- How is she ?
They rushed her to prenatal ICU
but they won't tell me a thing. I'm not family.
OK.
Miss. Hi, my name is Miguel Prado.
I'm the Assistant District Attorney.
I need you to find your chief of staff,
Dr. Reynolds, and have him call...
- I'm just an admit nurse. You're...
- Hey, call him.
Right now.
I feel so bad for Rita. She's all alone.
Baby, baby, Reynolds is gonna make sure
she gets the best care in Miami.
Why isn't Dexter back ?
I've been calling all day.
Goddamn it,
the father should be here.
I enjoyed shuffling through your iPod
to make sure that no one hears us.
Of course, most of your shipmates
are up on the blue deck.
It's happy hour.
Just the two of us.
# Ch-ch-ch-changes
# Turn and face the strange
# Ch-ch-ch-changes... #
Oh, it's too bad
I have to make this quick.
I'm usually all for a stimulating conversation
at times like this.
But the last sea taxi leaves in an hour.
# Time may change me... #
I've been going through
some changes myself lately.
I'm getting married.
I've got a baby on the way. Me.
Even though my life
may never be the same,
I want to thank you for reminding me
how important it is to take time for oneself.
# Ch-ch-ch-changes... #
Savor these moments alone.
# Changes
# Oh, look out you rock and rollers
And here I am. Paradox personified.
Taking life.
Creating life.
With the ship anchored away from shore,
the Gulf Stream will be Ethan's last cruise.
Bon voyage.
This isn't like Dexter.
Something's wrong.
Sweetie, I know this is difficult,
but you need to stay calm.
I sent the coast guard to look for him.
He wasn't at his fishing spot.
Maybe he's back at the marina by now.
Then why hasn't he called ?
Anton, open up. It's me.
I tried calling. I got a lead.
I know why someone's looking
for you-know-who.
Hurry up if you want your money.
Yes, I was wrong about...
bupkus.
Hi.
Hi. Is Anton here ?
He's in the shower.
Oh, he'll be out soon, cause I think
we used up all the hot water.
I can get him.
Oh, no, that's all right.
Just, um, have him call Debra Morgan.
It's important.
- Are you sure you don't want me to...
- Thanks.
What ?
Hello, Debra.
This is Miguel Prado.
Have you heard from Dexter ?
Uh, no. Why ?
Well, we're at the hospital
with Rita right now.
- Hospital ? Everything all right ?
- Debra, we need to find your brother.
Ethan Turner was incapable of compromise.
He loved his wives' money
more than he loved them.
And in the end, it cost him dearly.
I don't wanna be like Ethan.
Maybe my days of coming
and going as I please are over.
But that doesn't mean my life is over.
Not as long as I have my boat
and the open water.
There are some things
I can keep to myself.
You have 12 unheard messages.
Dex, it's me.
I'm on my way to the hospital.
I think there's something
wrong with the baby.
The baby ?
The baby's fine.
They said if I stay on bed rest
the next few days that I can...
we can go home tomorrow.
I don't know what I would have done
if I'd lost the baby and you weren't here.
- Hey.
- And nobody could find you.
I'm here now.
And I'm not going anywhere.
I think maybe we should wait
to find a house until after we're married.
Just name the date.
I'm ready.
I'd like to walk down the aisle
before I start to show.
Whatever you want.
I may never be able to feel
our baby's heartbeat emotionally.
But I know now I can't ignore it either.
And for some reason I can't explain,
I'm relieved to know it's still here.
Fishing ?
That's where you were all night ?
Deb...
You can't make me feel any worse
than I already do.
Well, I hope this was
a big wake-up call for you.
Cause you're gonna be a father
before you know it.
Yeah, I see that now.
My life is changing.
And if it'll make you happy,
my place is yours.
What'll make me happy
is you being there for that kid.
For homework and plays.
And softball games.
Don't you dare be like Dad.
That's never gonna happen.
Quite a night, huh ?
I should have been here.
Well, Syl and I were.
That's what friends are for.
- I owe you one.
- I just may take you up on that someday.
You know, my office got the strangest fax
tonight from Atlantic Sun Cruises.
Remember that guy whose wife
disappeared on some cruise ?
Get this, he was reported missing
about an hour ago.
Where was it that you say you went fishing ?
Mercy Reef.
Yeah, Mercy Reef.
That's what I thought you said.
Cause when I sent the coast guard
over there, they couldn't find you.
The ocean's a big place.
Or maybe you weren't at Mercy Reef.
Where else would I have been ?
Bimini's... What, 40 miles away ?
- I went fishing. You watched me leave.
- You were on that cruise ship.
Do you know how crazy that sounds ?
You were on that cruise ship
finishing what I couldn't.
Wasn't me.
You were making sure that Ethan Turner
could never hurt another innocent soul.
It's getting late. You should go.
It's OK.
Dexter, you and I, we're the same.
No one is like me.
You're wrong.
Hey, you... You're wrong.
Don't you see what happened today ?
I gave you the chance to avenge two women
whom the system failed,
and just like I hoped,
you seized that opportunity.
It's not like that.
Dexter...
You don't have to lie to me.
Don't you understand ?
Hey, I see who you are.
No, you can't.
No one can.
You have nothing to explain to me.
Nothing to apologize for.
Ever.
I'm with you.
I'm behind you.
And I respect you.
I better get home.
Syl will be waiting up.
Good night, Dexter.
When Harry saw
what I truly was, he was repulsed.
It destroyed my brother,
consumed Lila.
But not Miguel Prado.
Somehow he looks at me
and he's...
proud.