Previously on Dexter.
I just got off the phone
with the Sheriff's Department.
They've confirmed
their skinning victim is related to ours.
That gives us three victims.
I've got Unis bringing in
a 15-year-old kid named Wendell Owens.
He was Freebo's doorman.
But if things get really bad,
you use that card and call me, OK ?
You think I cut this kid loose
to make you look bad ?
I'm not sure any more...
partner.
You know a Joey Quinn ?
Cooperation with IA has its upside.
Yuki, that's not gonna happen.
Ramon's obsessed.
He's not going to stop
looking for Oscar's killer
until it takes him all the way down.
- Is there a problem here ?
- Yeah, Sergeant.
Your people don't know
what the fuck they're doing.
That guy is wound way too tight.
Where ya been, Dexter ?
- How are you, Camilla ?
- Ah. I've been better.
Are you, uh, looking for
anything special tonight ?
Might be more than an hour.
Take a pass... Sergeant.
Anton, open up. It's me.
- Hi.
The Chicky Hines conviction.
My people have come across evidence
that could get the case reopened.
Prado know you're
coming to me with this ?
Don't you see what happened today ?
I gave you the chance to avenge
two women whom the system failed,
and just like I hoped,
you seized that opportunity.
I see who you are. I am with you.
Behind you.
And I respect you.
He's tired. Keep on reeling.
You got him.
Here he comes ! Come here !
Come here !
Oh, yeah ! Oh, shit !
Ah, ah.
- Ah... ah !
- Tranquilo. Coge.
That's gonna be some
mighty fine eatin'.
Hey, man, on the grill
with Syl's mango-and-lime salsa.
Our house tomorrow night.
Check with the little woman...
who's getting bigger as we speak.
I could get used to the simple joys
of male bonding.
- Hey, how 'bout a... brewski ?
- OK.
Ah, that looks good.
So, Dex...
Ahh.
What was it like, man ?
In Bimini.
Flat, mostly. Lots of mangroves.
- Talking about Ethan Turner.
- What about him ?
What did it feel like to, uh...
take him out, hmm ?
To end his life.
So much for the simple joys
of male bonding.
Like I could explain
or Miguel could understand.
You put people on death row.
You must know what it's like.
Oh, no, but there's, like,
an ocean of bureaucracy
of briefs and appeals between me
and that bad guy taking his last breath.
I'm asking you what did it feel like
to use your hands, to...
to make this a better place ?
It felt... right.
Felt like justice.
I've got, like, five floors of prosecutors
and the whole police department at
my fingertips, and you did what I couldn't.
You came through for me, Dex.
I been sleepin' like a baby ever since.
It's hot today, huh ?
Like I said the other night,
I know you, Dexter.
I see who you are.
We're like-minded. Hmm ?
Together, we can make a difference.
We ?
Miguel, my amigo, claims to know me.
On some level,
I suppose maybe that's true.
Who are you kidding ?
He knows about Freebo.
He detailed me
to the Ethan Turner kill.
He's seen me with blood on my hands
and hasn't blinked.
Miguel's got no clue
what's really going on inside you.
The urge, the ritual.
Miguel has really gone out of his way
to understand who I am...
which is more than you ever did.
Well, I understood.
I just couldn't accept it.
And Miguel won't either.
You didn't want me to have any friends.
You think Miguel's a pal ?
Your wingman ?
You might wanna put
that notion to the test...
see how like-minded
you and Miguel really are.
Every time you let
someone get close,
it ends badly.
I do need to consider
my spotty record connecting
with others.
But Miguel's not going away.
I need to make him
understand the risks.
When he does, he'll wanna rethink
the like-minded thing.
Just because he can gut a fish
doesn't qualify him to hang with me while I...
do what I do best.
You need a jump ? I have cables.
Skinner struck again.
Super-hard this time.
The victim's name was Wendell Owen.
He was 15-years-old.
It's more collateral damage
in our search for fucking Freebo.
Wendell Owens ?
I brought him in
for questioning the other day.
I thought I remembered
hearing his name somewhere.
He might have been mixed up
with some lowlifes,
but Wendell was
a pretty decent kid.
Go do your thing.
I just need a minute.
Body's still warm. Putting time of death
about three hours ago.
Unlike the two previous victims,
this one died from
the skinning process itself.
Jesus Christ.
Freebo's probably in another galaxy,
and the Skinner doesn't even know it.
Meanwhile, he's stepping up his game.
Maybe we let the press know
Freebo got outta Dodge,
might get this guy
to put down his Ginsu knife.
Or he'll keep looking,
take his horror show on the road,
become somebody else's nightmare.
No, I wanna nail
whoever's doing this.
He's definitely not learning to do this
on the fly. He's had plenty of practice.
You run this through
the national database,
see if a similar MO
comes up anywhere else.
What I need to find right now
is a target to present to Miguel
with a high degree
of difficulty and jeopardy.
So that he truly understands
that he's in way over his head.
Dex. I have a question.
It's serious.
I can't ask any of the other cops.
- I'm all yours.
- It's about the Skinner.
His last two victims,
Wendell and Javier,
they were both killed
after I was done questioning them.
Do you think the Skinner's
drafting off my investigation ?
I don't know.
Anything's possible.
Because I'm freaking out that whoever's
looking for Freebo is using me to track him.
Who else knows you brought Wendell in ?
His mom, um...
all the cops in the station.
Anton.
Ramon Prado.
Miguel's brother.
The law and order hard-ass sheriff
who's been obsessed about finding Freebo
for killing his little brother ?
There's your motive.
Do we seriously think
that Ramon, a fellow cop,
could do something this sick ?
Like a career in law enforcement
precludes violent behavior ?
Can you imagine the shitstorm
this is gonna create if I'm wrong ?
It'll create a worse
shitstorm if you're right.
- Hey, keep me in the loop.
- Yeah.
Ramon's got anger issues.
I don't want you getting hurt.
Aw. You do care about me.
Wait till you see the wine cellar
at The Forge. It is legendary !
They even have a bottle
of Château d'Yquem...
belonged to Thomas Jefferson.
I'm kind of a Cuba Libre kinda girl myself.
Ellen, it's me. Nicely done.
Handing Miguel Prado
his head on a pike today -
make the Hines motion stick,
he could be disbarred. Bravissimo.
I was gonna talk to you about this,
if and when my motion's upheld.
How about we talk about it now ?
OK.
Miguel's been playing fast and loose
for a long time with legal ethics.
The Chicky Hines case
is just one example
on a very long list
of prosecutorial misconduct.
I came to you with information
to help your client,
not for you to trump up some witch-hunt
against my friend and colleague.
You can't possibly believe
he's either of those things
if you really knew Miguel.
Believe me, I know Miguel.
I will explain everything over dinner.
No, thanks.
I'm not feeling especially
social right now.
Hey.
Hope I'm not interrupting.
No, I'm alone. Come on in.
- Taking the night off ?
- Mm...
- So, um... beer ?
- Sure.
Pot ?
Fuck you.
Sounded kind of upset on the phone.
I'm kind of upset in person too.
Um... you didn't talk to anyone
about me bringing Wendell in
for questioning ?
No. I don't talk to anybody
about anything.
I try to keep the whole CI thing
under wraps, you know ?
Then how the hell did it get out ?
Well, it's a pretty safe bet
Wendell didn't tell anybody.
You should have seen
what this sicko did to him.
I'm glad I didn't.
What would make anyone go that hard
on some street kid, for Christ's sakes ?
There's this guy I'm lookin' at,
he's a cop who had a beef with Freebo.
He saw me in the station
when I was questioning Wendell.
Wouldn't be the first
time the boys in blue
handled their own business, right ?
I can't rule out that I put
Wendell in the crosshairs.
He trusted me enough
to cooperate and...
look what happened to him.
Hey, look...
even if you're right,
you couldn't have known, right ?
Don't beat yourself up.
It's what I do best, huh ?
I should go.
All right.
Hey, um...
Hey, look, um...
that girl from
the other night was...
was nothing serious.
Uh, well... it's none
of my business anyway.
Yeah, right.
Right.
Jenna Kendrick.
One of the first crime scenes
I worked blood spatter.
This was somebody's daughter.
And that was done to her
by this animal.
Clemson Galt.
Aryan affiliated.
Took a claw hammer to her
for getting pregnant.
He was arrested for murder,
even confessed to his cellmate.
He called it "hammer time".
They get a conviction ?
Galt's Aryan affiliates
either got witnesses to recant
or made them disappear.
Verdict came back not guilty.
That type of stuff happens way too often.
Galt's doing 15 to 20 for armed robbery
in a supermax upstate.
Well, that's something, at least.
Get him off the streets.
Only he's still running things
from his prison cell.
The wife and three kids
of an Aryan defector,
killed with a claw hammer.
While you're sleeping like a baby,
this is who's keeping me up nights.
Justice comes at a price,
one that Miguel is about to discover
he can't afford.
This asshole doesn't
deserve to breathe, OK ?
You're not gonna get
any argument with me about that.
But he's in custody.
In a supermax, no less.
That's always been the problem.
You're the big-deal law enforcement guy.
I bet you could get us access.
That's beyond dangerous, Dexter.
That's crazy !
I knew if I appealed to reason,
Miguel would eventually
understand the downside.
Never mind that my fingerprints
will be all over this !
Reason leads to self-preservation,
a potent force.
We both would be seriously
exposed here.
I just need to sit back.
He'll see the pros are heavily
outweighed by the cons,
and we'll be back to mojitos
and barbecues.
Yeah, when you get right down to it,
I guess Ethan Turner was
an accident of opportunity,
a once-in-a-lifetime thing.
What about Freebo ?
Another accident of opportunity ?
Well, that situation
just sort of... unfolded.
You're right.
We both have too much to lose.
Hey, we took out
the garbage... twice.
We should quit while we're ahead.
No.
I owe you this one, Dexter.
You stuck your neck out for me twice now.
- No, you don't owe me.
- Fair is fair.
And I won't let you down.
But we need to come up
with a real plan.
Again... we.
Miguel surprised me last night.
I expected him to say no
and he gave me a definite maybe instead.
Hey. No doughnuts today ?
Not today, Vince.
Talk about your passive aggressive.
Clemson Galt has been
on my top ten list for years,
and Miguel could be a big help.
But the goal here
isn't to satisfy my need,
it's to get Miguel
to find some other hobby.
Dexter. Got a minute ?
- Who's sick ?
- Uh, remember Camilla from records ?
She's in the hospital. It's not looking good,
so I got everyone to sign.
Camilla's sick ?
Sorry, I thought you knew.
Lung cancer. It's terminal.
Just like Gene.
Camilla's husband.
My folks used to play cards with them
when Deb and I were growing up.
He died just last year.
Lung cancer too.
- Smokers ?
- Chimneys.
- Life catches up.
- Yeah.
So does death.
It's a shame. She's a good person.
It sounds like she was a friend.
A good friend.
Those are in short supply these days.
Camilla's at Good Samaritan.
You could drop that off,
let her know she's in our prayers.
- I'll do that.
- Thanks.
Detective Gianna.
Sergeant Batista, Miami Metro Homicide.
How can I help you, Sergeant ?
I was, uh, wondering, Detective.
Maybe we could...
see each other.
As... As in a... a date ?
Well, yeah.
You could call it that.
Look, um, Sergeant,
let's be clear.
Cause being clear
will save us both a lot of agita.
Hey ! I, uh...
I don't date. Ever.
Do you eat... ever ?
Sometimes.
Good nutrition's important.
I'll tell you what, Sergeant.
I get hungry enough, I will call you.
Angel ?
What ?
Can I throw something at you
that might sound a little crazy ?
Crazy ? From you ?
- Ramon Prado.
- What about him ?
Do we like him for the Skinner ?
OK, that's not a little crazy.
He has access to all of our records,
so he knows exactly who I've been talking to.
And we've all seen him up close -
this is not a stable guy.
- He's a fucking whack job.
- I looked into his work schedule.
He was off duty
when the last two murders went down.
You seriously wanna look
at Ramon Prado for multiple homicide ?
If only to rule him out.
Not only have we not found the perp
that killed Miguel Prado's little brother,
now you wanna investigate
his other brother for murder ?
In a nutshell.
Can't ignore something
just cause it's messy.
If I'm right, this is huge.
And if you're wrong,
everyone involved will be shitting blood
due to acts I'd rather not describe.
Thanks for that, Sarge.
I've got a gut feeling.
You, uh, wanna go
to the Lieutenant with this ?
I can't go to LaGuerta with this.
You follow up, off the grid,
- and it's on you.
- Thank you, Sarge.
Ramon's off duty tonight and tomorrow.
I'll set up on him, see what shakes loose.
- If you need company...
- I've got it covered.
And try to be discreet, will you ?
For a change ?
Yeah.
Dexter.
You came.
I also brought you these.
But it looks like somebody beat me to it.
Oh, well...
a new mom in Maternity
donated them to Terminal Care.
Talk about irony, huh ?
You know, Dexter,
my whole life
I've been searching for...
The meaning of life ?
The perfect...
Key lime pie.
And what do I get
when I'm about to croak ?
Fucking pie crust, Reddi-wip,
and green Jell-O.
I'll see what I can do about finding you
the perfect Key lime pie.
You'd better do it fast.
Next thing to go is the appetite.
Gene always had this thing
about lighting my cigarette.
And he'd pass it to me...
before he lit his own.
Sweet, sweet man.
Then... Then it all caught up to him.
I watched him wither to a skeleton.
My six-foot tall,
200-pound husband,
shitting all over himself.
His last breath was a mercy.
Dying I can do.
Hell, I'm doing it.
The pain sure is a bear, though.
How bad ?
The worst part
of the whole damn thing...
not losing my life...
my time on this earth...
is losing my... my...
Dignity.
- Ah, that fish was great.
- You don't think Miguel overcooked it ?
A bit, but the mango salsa
saved the day.
Thank you.
So do you like what you do ?
I mean, real estate.
I can't imagine doing anything else.
Yeah, I decided
that losing my job at the hotel
is not a bad thing but a good thing.
So I'm looking around.
Well, with your people skills,
you'd be great at real estate.
You think ?
How 'bout you start work tomorrow ?
I'm... I'm sorry, what ?
I need an assistant.
Having someone I can trust
is everything.
Salud.
Listen, I've been giving a lot of thought
to this Clemson Galt thing.
Good.
Digame.
What if we were to travel upstate
and arrange an interview with him ?
About ?
A career criminal
with a record like his,
he's gotta be an encyclopedia of intel
on tons of other cases.
We would just need
to get Galt alone long enough
to make it look like
another prisoner did the deed.
Last week, an inmate is found
in a prison hallway
drowned in a bucket of water.
This stuff happens all day long
in places like that.
An inmate is found dead
in custody, Dexter,
you got inquiries and investigations.
You got the bleeding hearts
comin' outta the woodwork
whining about prison reform.
Ha. It doesn't sound
like much of a plan.
That is the plan...
so that Miguel finally
includes himself out.
But, um...
I'm in the middle of trying
a racketeering case right now.
Money laundering.
The Aryans, they're masters
at moving cash around.
I subpoena Galt
as an expert witness,
Corrections transports him
down here to testify.
Then Galt is within our reach, hmm ?
And on my turf.
I'm guessing it would take a long time
to set something like that up.
It would.
But I've already issued the subpoena.
Galt'll be here tomorrow night.
Only... he's gonna be a no-show
on the witness stand the next morning.
Swing by the courthouse tomorrow,
I'll walk you through all the details.
Coño, say thank you, Dexter.
Miguel seems to have
way more aptitude
and appetite for this
than I ever imagined.
Just calling to check in.
Just having a look-see
in Ramon Prado's car.
- Deb, you really need to...
- Relax.
He's scarfing down his second plate
of arroz con pollo
at a restaurant up the block.
He's got a wife and kids at home,
got the night off,
so why is he eating alone ?
Well, maybe the wife's arroz con pollo
isn't pollo enough.
You find anything interesting ?
A set of German steel filet knives,
a couple of straight razors,
and, like, 12 pounds of human skin.
Just be careful out there, will you ?
Yes, sir.
Deb's got her mission.
I've got mine.
Hey, I can get out
and give you a great big hug
so everyone can see
what good friends we are...
or you can talk to me.
You know, after 12 hours
on surveillance detail,
how 'bout you blow me instead ?
I've been given the directive to either step up
my investigation of Quinn or close it.
Because you haven't found dick.
If you weren't such a fuckwad, I'd almost
feel sorry for you for working for IA.
Where careers go to die.
You need to get next to Quinn,
be his go-to girl.
You'll be wearing a wire.
Are you on crack ? How many times
have I told you to eat shit ?
What the fuck makes you think
I'm suddenly willing to play now ?
Because if you don't,
I'll put the word out
that you've been cooperating all along.
Everyone'll think you're a rat anyway.
Hard to believe
even you would sink that low.
- So that door right over there ?
- Hmm.
Check this out. That's supposed
to be kept locked, and it never is.
The smokers use it
as a short cut to get outside.
Short cut to a shorter life.
You know, statistically, most escapes
happen out of a courthouse.
The security's a little bit more lax,
the defendant is wearing
a suit and a tie.
It makes it easy for him
to just walk away.
Easier for us to cover our tracks.
That too.
Señor, ¿ cuánto ?
- No, no, por favor.
- ¿ Está seguro ?
- Si, señor.
- Good, good !
Must be good to be you.
Sometimes.
Coño.
Thanks for helping out.
Real reason she's blindfolded -
so she doesn't have to watch
everything she stands for
get pissed on
by someone like Ellen Wolf.
You know, she had this client once
who threw a five-year-old
into an industrial washer for talking dirty.
She got him off with six months
in a mental hospital.
Diminished fucking capacity.
Hey.
She probably got paid more on that
than you took home in a year.
And I gotta tell you, I'm very disappointed
with your boss over there.
I never thought that she, of all people,
would hurt me like this
and throw in with these
fucking bottom feeders.
My dad used to say be careful
what you think you know about someone.
You're probably wrong.
Smart man.
Well, sometimes.
Maria !
I appreciate your, um, cooperation
in the deposition.
I've never had a problem
telling the truth.
We've got, uh, more than enough
to get the Hines conviction set aside.
And you've set the stage for your
smear campaign against a stand-up guy.
Nice.
You know, you ever wanna hear
the unexpurgated version of your guy,
come find me, OK ?
It's like a church.
Yeah.
The holding cell
is through that door.
Connects to a hallway,
then goes out to a parking garage.
On your right,
there's gonna be an emergency exit.
And that deadbolt
is gonna be taped...
open.
Why risk it all ?
Your career, reputation, freedom.
You could just walk away.
You didn't walk away
from Ethan Turner.
Because you understand, Dexter,
that we're living in...
we're living in crucial times,
crucial times that demand
extraordinary measures.
Miguel's convinced himself
he wants this kill tonight
for lofty and noble reasons.
I'm not quite as high-minded.
You didn't answer my question.
Asshole drunk dad...
maybe I'm still trying to clean up the mess
that I couldn't when I was a kid, I don't know.
Come on, I'll, uh,
show you where you're gonna
be hooking up with Galt.
Morgan, what's the hurry ?
- You meeting someone ?
- More like avoiding someone.
Hey, this is me not telling you
I'm tailing Ramon Prado again tonight.
Well, this is me not hearing
a word you're saying.
I'm also unofficially and off the record
telling you to be smart and watch your ass.
Excuse me, Officer.
Sergeant. How can I help you ?
I was just, uh...
...released for this legal thing.
- You were arrested.
- And released. Totally victimless.
Only I live, like, a million miles
away from here, and I really need a ride.
How 'bout the bus ?
How 'bout you take me home
and I think of some victimless way
of saying thank you ?
I'll have Dispatch call you a cab.
Just like that ?
Just like that.
Agent Batista.
Sergeant, Barbara Gianna here.
So happens, uh...
I'm hungry.
Hungry enough to...
to see if you are too.
Are you asking me out
on a date, Detective ?
I don't date, Sergeant. Ever.
Marino's Trattoria, 7:30 ?
Aren't you gonna ask me
if I really turned over a new leaf ?
It could be I'm just not
partial to redheads.
I have no idea what
you're talking about, Detective.
I'll see you at 7:30.
Delivered fresh daily
from a little bakery down in Key Largo.
Supposed to be the best in the Keys.
Well, it's not.
Pardon my bluntness, but...
this pie is green.
Means they used food coloring.
Something purists frown on ?
Which I'd be doing right now,
except even my face hurts.
The other thing they fucked up -
this wasn't made
with condensed milk.
No, it's fresh and organic.
Only they didn't have
fresh milk in the Keys
back in the day.
Oh.
Here comes Miss Morphine.
Bringer of bad dreams
and less pain.
Dexter.
If you're as serious
about Key lime pie as I am...
you can do better.
Tonight's the night.
But it feels different.
I won't be alone. Uncharted territory
for me, not without risk.
And strangely exhilarating.
So, what do you think ?
Best pizza night ever.
No, I meant about Syl's job offer.
If real estate's something you're
interested in, I think you should go for it.
And Syl's great at what she does.
In a market this bad,
she's still always closing.
And I could learn a lot, I just...
But ?
Well, what if I...
see a side to her that I don't like ?
I guess that's the risk you run
when you go into business
with somebody, especially a friend.
Makes things more complicated,
no doubt about it.
Still... without my friend Syl,
I wouldn't have this opportunity.
So I think I'm gonna take the risk
and jump in with both feet
and see if this new thing calls to me.
- It's getting late.
- You don't wanna stay ?
Miguel and I have a...
early morning run.
I can sleep in longer
if I stay at my place.
Don't be surprised if he's a no-show.
What makes you say that ?
He's been a complete wreck lately.
Not sleeping, terrible mood.
I mean, Syl thinks something's
really bothering him.
I saw him today. He seemed fine.
Well, you may be his buddy,
but you're not his wife.
And besides, it's not like you can hide
anything from your partner.
So true.
Why would you want to ?
Looks like Miguel's
got a bad case of nerves about tonight.
He isn't sleeping
like a baby any more.
If you're gonna bail out of this,
now would be a good time.
What the hell are you
dressed like that for ?
I figured the more the merrier.
Why don't we swing by
and pick up Rita and the kids ?
Bring them along too.
What makes you think
you can count on Miguel ?
He's just a little jumpy.
He's new at this.
Mark my words, Dex, he'll give you up
in a heartbeat to save his own ass.
This is not a guy who wants to spend
the rest of his life in a cage.
Just one more thing
Miguel and I have in common.
You don't know
what you're getting into.
You've never had to rely
on anyone else before, Dexter.
Because you taught me
loneliness is an art form.
But guess what, I finally have a life
with a family and now a friend...
who I trust.
We only see two things in people...
what we wanna see
and what they wanna show us.
You don't know Miguel
any more than he knows you.
You aren't seriously gonna
lecture me on relationships
after the debris field you left behind.
No matter how close
two people are,
an infinite distance separates them.
Look at you and me.
Mind if I get a picture with you, jefe ?
- You got a cam... Oh.
- Oh, yeah.
No hayproblema. Tiralo.
Gracias.
Any truth you're gonna run for DA ?
Uh... if I do,
I'm gonna need your support.
You got it, jefe.
Thanks, Officer.
You listen to me, pulled pork.
I got no clue why the fuck
you dragged me down here
in all this humidity,
but you can suck my white dick,
you think I'm helping
your spic ass with shit.
This all ends right here,
right now, Clemson.
This makes us even.
When you walk out the door,
one of your Nazi pals is waiting for you
in the parking garage.
From now on,
all of the threats to my family,
they stop, understand ?
I knew my Aryan brothers
would come through, ese.
- Thanks.
- Mm-hm.
Hey, have any arrangements
been made
in case this guy's testimony runs a little long
and he has to stay another day ?
We're holding a spot for him
in protective at Miami-Dade.
Good man. Appreciate it.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I got a witness in there, man,
that's taking a nap.
I'm gonna really need him fresh for court
in a couple of hours.
I gotta put a county wristband on him.
Just take a second.
Clem Galt.
I'm your wheel man.
Welcome home.
Heil Hitler.
- Let's get the fuck outta here.
- Ride's this way.
Have you out of the country
by lunch time.
Fuck !
- Shit ! What's going on here ?
I don't know. Come on.
I'll get you outta here.
We just gotta get to the car.
Galt had to have an accomplice.
Just set up a perimeter around this building
right away. No one should get in or out.
- Fuckin' spic set us up.
- This guy cannot get away !
- And I'm gonna return the favor.
- That's mighty white of you.
Galt's right.
He's selling you out.
Never underestimate the capacity
of other people to let you down.
It's not the time, Dad.
There he goes.
Looking out for number one.
Which is what you should have done.
Like the man said,
nobody gets in or out.
Might as well give up.
No sense risking death by cop.
If you keep Miguel's involvement secret,
he might let you off with a few years.
Stop.
Unless they find those blood slides
when they toss your apartment.
Stop !
Hola, amigo.
I'm gonna drop you off at your car.
Then I'll meet you at the stash house
as soon as I can get outta here.
- Wait for me, huh ?
- Thanks for this.
That's what friends are for.
Hey, I'm gonna do a loop
around the building
until you get more backup here, OK ?
You got it, jefe.
Gimme a fucking break, Ramon.
Don't fucking lie to me !
Aah !
You can make this stop right now...
if you tell me where he is.
I don't know.
You're making this
very hard on yourself, Felipe.
Whoa.
You scared the fuckmother out of me.
You're the one that called me.
What do we got ?
Kidnapping, for starters.
- Who's the special guest ?
- That's Felipe Cepeda.
He's one of Freebo's hemp suppliers.
I questioned him a couple of weeks ago.
Now Ramon's got a few
questions of his own for him.
Well, so far, I've only heard one -
"where's Freebo ?"
I'm just waiting for the skinning to start.
Oye. Tell me where he is.
I don't know !
OK.
Nothing like a nice cold soda pop
before a good skinning.
Aah !
Fuck, that's gotta hurt.
- Wait, wait.
- Wait ?
We need to be sure he's the Skinner.
Felipe...
you have some answers for me now ?
I don't get it. I don't get it.
- That's not the Skinner's MO.
- Maybe he's just warming up.
Here he goes.
Vete.
He's not the Skinner.
I gotta take this. Don't go anywhere.
Hello.
So Ramon Prado's a sick fuck,
but he's not the sick fuck
we're looking for.
I'll talk to you about it over breakfast.
I gotta go.
What's up ?
So, why are you calling us in
at midnight ?
We've picked up Ramon Prado.
He's, uh... outside.
We got a Uni watching him
to keep his mouth shut.
For what ?
Kidnapping. False imprisonment.
And torture.
- Are you sure ?
- We witnessed it ourselves.
- My God, I...
- We can't give him a pass on this.
I...
Shit.
No, we can't.
Thank you for being politic at least.
I woulda perp-walked him
right through here.
Morgan insisted we be discreet
out of respect for his family.
Were you aware
of this investigation ?
- Yes, I was.
- And you didn't inform me ?
I wanted something solid
before involving you.
Thank you for that.
Morgan, you handled
a tough situation the smart way.
How do you wanna do this ?
Book him.
I'll notify the family.
That went well.
Internal Affairs
is investigating you.
What ?
They've been giving me
a sandpaper enema to wear a fucking wire.
- This has been going on for a while.
- Yes.
- And you're finally telling me.
- I'm finally telling you.
Do you wanna tell me why this IA chick
is so gung ho to bring you down ?
Wait. Does this IA chick
go by the name of Yuki Amado ?
As a matter of fact, yes.
You wanna tell me what's going on ?
Yeah. Yuki and I have a... history.
It's a totally personal vendetta on her part.
I'll handle it.
I appreciate the heads-up, though.
Even in prison, I'm sure
you heard about the big slump
in the real-estate market.
What the fuck ?
Shit !
There is an upside
to the downturn, though.
Plenty of empty houses.
Do you recognize this one ?
It's where you killed Jenna Kendrick.
I got no idea what the hell
you're talking about.
I'm talking about hammer time, Clemson.
No.
You got me mixed up
with somebody else.
You can't imagine how much
I've been looking forward to this.
And none of it
would be happening
if it weren't for my... friend...
Miguel Prado. You remember him ?
He really came through tonight.
In a big way.
I never had a partner before.
I had my doubts initially,
but everything worked out.
But this part, the ritual...
the connection and certainty...
followed by that pristine silence...
is for me.
And me alone.
Miguel will be disappointed.
I'll explain to him I took Galt
straight to the cemetery
and dumped him in a grave
after the screw-up at the courthouse.
Truth is, I'm not ready
to share this part of me
with anyone else just yet.
Present company excepted.
I'm not sure I ever will be ready.
Even if Miguel senses my deception,
he'll forgive me this one small untruth.
Dexter.
How can I be so sure ?
Because after tonight,
I can honestly say
I know who Miguel Prado really is...
my first good friend.
And those are in short supply
these days.