Last season on Dexter...
The butchered bodies were
submerged inside these garbage bags...
Did you hear that ?
30 bags. Do you know what that means ?
There might be
a new mass murderer out there
- way worse than the Ice Truck Killer.
- Uh-oh.
Eight confirmed victims
of the Bay Harbor Butcher.
That's what the press is calling
whoever dumped those bodies offshore.
Last thing Miami needs
is another serial killer.
- Any idea who the FBI is sending ?
- Some guy named Lundy.
We have positive IDs
on all 18 of our complete bodies.
All 13 were either tried for murder
or at least suspected of murder.
Bay Harbor Butcher ? Give me one
shot, I'd put a bullet in the fucker's head.
You really feel that way ?
If Dad taught us one thing,
it's the value of human life.
Yeah, but I think we had
different homework assignments.
Tell me the truth.
Are you an addict ?
Yes, I have an addiction.
- I'm Dexter.
- Hi, Dexter.
There's my sponsor.
So tell me, exactly how full of shit are you ?
This woman sees me.
Somehow she's able to make me feel OK
about what I am.
You're going to tell me
all your deepest, darkest secrets.
Laura Moser, my mother,
she was murdered.
I've never told anyone that before.
Did you find out what happened to the
men responsible for your mother's murder ?
Santos Jimenez. Turned state's evidence,
went into witness protection.
- Where are you ?
- I've decided to look up
someone from my past.
1976 !
You slaughtered her
cause she stole cocaine.
She was a snitch for a cop.
She was fucking him.
It seems my foster father and
my biological mother were having an affair.
Did he blame himself for her death ?
Is that why he took me in ?
Or was he just using her ?
Was he using me ?
But there ain't no paper trail
on the early years of Dexter Morgan.
Your past is a bigger mystery
than fucking Jimmy Hoffa.
Back... off.
Ow ! Fuck !
If Dexter files a complaint,
you will be kicked off the force.
He's hiding something, Maria.
I can feel it.
I need some blood slides analyzed.
I'm about to be found out
at work for what I really am.
- You don't understand.
- Why don't you make me ?
- Who the fuck are you ?
- Oh, pardon my tits.
How could you do this to Rita,
not to mention her kids ?
You and Lila
stayed in a hotel together.
It's over, Dexter.
I'm sure that you heard we have a suspect
in the Bay Harbor Butcher case.
Sergeant James Doakes.
He had the slides.
Carefully hidden in the trunk of his car
at the airport.
Jesus Christ, Morgan.
You're the Bay Harbor Butcher.
You sure about that ?
You might want to check with Lundy.
What's it gonna be, Morgan ?
Kill me now or set me free !
Don't worry,
I'll send the FBI your way soon enough.
So you're still gonna try to frame me ?
Mission accomplished.
After tomorrow, I'll be out of reach.
Permanently.
- You're going somewhere ?
- Goodbye, Lila.
Welcome. Previous
destinations. Starting route guidance.
Hey ! Who's out there ?
Anybody out there ?
- Who put you in there ?
- His name is Dexter Morgan.
I found out that he's the Bay Harbor Butcher.
Please, just open this gate !
- Poor thing, all alone.
- I'm OK.
Not you. Dexter.
What the fuck are you doing ? Turn that off !
Do you understand this is murder ?
- What were you thinking ? Are you insane ?
- I was trying to bring us back together.
The Lila experiment
is officially over.
Could have had it all, Dexter.
I've never put much weight
into the idea of a higher power,
but if I didn't know better,
I'd have to believe that some force out there
wants me to keep doing what I'm doing.
You wanted to be close to me, Lila ?
This is the most I have to offer.
You taught me to accept what I am.
Thank you.
The code is mine now
and mine alone.
So too are the relationships I cultivate.
My father might not approve,
but I'm no longer his disciple.
I'm a master now.
An idea transcended into life.
Ah, life.
Life is a ritual.
Routine.
Control.
And an essential part of that routine...
regular oral hygiene.
There we go.
A few minutes, that'll numb right up.
So how was your summer, Dexter ?
I went to the carnival.
I even won a prize.
Hope you stayed away
from all the sweet stuff.
Usually I'm good,
but sometimes I indulge.
I also made it a point to meet new people.
Can never have too many friends.
Now, this temporary crown
is gonna go way in the back.
So there may be some blood.
- Not a problem.
- OK.
- So you still have your boat ?
- Oh, you bet.
It's the only place
I can really let everything go.
That's great. I'm gonna have you up
and out on that water in no time.
For someone who needs to spend his life
pretending to be normal,
I've been able to finally settle in...
...to a nice, normal world.
And Rita is the scaffolding
that holds that world in place.
What are you thinking ?
Life is good.
Hmm.
Here you go, buddy. OK, Astor, you're up.
Mickey Mouse, unicorns or starfish ?
Just plain, round pancakes, Dexter.
She's growing up.
It starts with pancakes ?
It starts when it starts.
Hey, Dexter ?
Um, can you come to Dad Day
at my school tomorrow ?
Just tell me what to do.
There's Charlotte.
- Bye, Mom. See you, Dexter.
- Bye, Mom.
- Bye.
- Get your bag.
You hear that ?
Hear what ?
The calm.
Everything's falling into place
for the first time in my life.
I've got these terrific kids.
There's no more drama haunting me.
And I have this great,
generous, gentle guy.
Most normal people
enjoy a sacred pact with society -
live a good life
and society will take care of you.
But if society drops the ball,
then someone else has to pick up the slack.
That's where I come in.
Fred Bowman, AKA Freebo.
Kills two college girls
and skates on a state police screw-up,
otherwise known as Florida's
catch and release program.
He does the deed, gets away with murder
and falls off the radar.
Everyone's radar but mine.
You got a birthday coming up, Dad.
What to get the man
who had everything ?
How about... Freebo ?
- Morning, Dex.
- Dexter the doughnut guy.
Part of my routine.
But let the record show
I'm not the only one with a daily ritual.
Angel Batista - bear claw.
Vince Masuka - lemon custard.
Mmm, better than sex.
Actually, no, it's not.
Hey, I need a favor. Do you think
you can proof an article I'm writing for FQ ?
- Forensics Quarterly.
- Right, yeah.
- They reached out cause I was the LFI...
- Lead forensic investigator.
- ... on the BHB.
- Bay Harbor Butcher.
- Hey.
- No biggie. I've been published before.
- "Dear Penthouse" doesn't count.
- Hey, that letter was famous.
- Death by pastry.
You changed your hair.
- Makes you look younger.
- I don't wanna look younger.
Bad call, then. By the way,
nice work on the Rinaldi case.
Yeah, well, murder-suicide.
Pretty straightforward.
Well, still, I mean,
your report was spot-on, right ?
All right.
Quinn's been in Homicide two weeks
and he noticed.
- Noticed what ?
- My hair.
I changed my hairstyle
for the first time since I was eight.
Oh, yeah. It's short... er. Shorter.
- Quinn, he's showing off his detective skills.
- You think he thinks I'm a potential lay ?
That is not happening. As long as you're
not noticing things, you've also not noticed
that I've given up men, liquor and smokes
for the last 27 days.
This is you remembering
Dad's birthday though, right ?
Dad. Birthday. Right.
Blue room, 7:30, like always.
- I tried calling you last night.
- I, uh, wasn't home.
I also tried your cell phone. You're wearing
the same pants you had on yesterday.
That shirt's the backup
you keep in your locker.
Ayúdeme aqui. I thought part
of your restructuring our department
was you staying out of our personal lives.
Anything you want me to know ?
Know this. I went out and had a great time
last night, and you should be happy for me.
Besides, since when do you care ?
Since this. Follow me.
OK, guys, listen up.
I just got word from upstairs that
Angel will no longer be
Detective Batista.
What ?
In two days,
he will be Detective Sergeant Batista.
Sorry for all the red tape and the hoops.
Nobody deserves it more than you, Angel.
When this is really official...
when I can trade this in for that gold badge...
drinks are on me.
Angel gets his wings.
Know what this means ?
Pay raise ?
No, dildo, it means he's my supervisor
which means I'm a lock
for my detective shield.
- Where are you going ?
- Research.
Dex. Typos, grammar,
something could be clearer, whatever.
Haircut ?
Yep.
Time to get the lay of the land
on Freebo and his...
pink house.
What you need ?
Freebo. I need Freebo.
- And you know him how ?
- He sells the best shit anywhere.
Come on, man, what,
you Google him or something ?
Know what ? Fuck it.
- There's other dope spots.
- Hey, come here !
Don't walk away all "fuck you" on me.
- What ?
- Ding, ding.
I'm looking to hold some product.
Ordinarily, I don't accept new clientele,
but I've had a desultory third quarter.
Mmm !
Oh, come on !
Need a little more hook
before breaking to the pocket.
You know, I bought this TV for six grand
but I'll let you have it for three.
More interested in scoring some tar.
Oh, another yuppie turns to the dark side.
- I need a hit.
- Jeez, Teegan, I'm transacting here.
- One toot.
- Did you hear what I said ?
Fuck off, Teegan.
Fine, I guess your dick
can suck itself from now on.
Stupid cunt's gonna
redefine "short-term relationship".
- Catch my drift ?
- Yeah, I catch your drift.
And I'm entirely confident
you've earned the privilege
of being repurposed as fish food.
Narcotics raided this place
at noon today.
The drug rats won't return
to their nest for a while.
Plenty of time
to do what I have to do.
Raw. You like it raw.
- Excuse me ?
- The sugar. You like the raw stuff.
It's my job to notice things.
Morgan, right ?
- Do I know you ?
- New haircut. It's cute.
- All right, who the fuck are you ?
- Yuki Amado, Internal Affairs.
And ?
- You know a Joey Quinn ?
- Why ?
Well, he started drawing our attention
back when he was in Narcotics.
He's in your orbit now.
I don't know the guy
except to hand in my paperwork.
Be really cool if you could
get next to him, you know ?
- Do a little recon.
- Are you high ?
No, never been.
Well...
Yuki, that's not gonna happen.
Cooperation with IA
has its upside in the department.
- Yeah, maybe for rodents.
- OK.
Well, it was nice to finally meet you.
In person, you know.
Bye.
And what is it
you think Quinn did exactly ?
Mm ! Mm-mm. You don't get
to blow me off and still ask questions.
Loud music.
Cover of darkness.
Perfect.
Get off ! No !
Freebo, get back here !
- Who are you ?
Shit ! Oh !
Yo, Freebo, man.
What the fuck happened back there ?
I went to kill Freebo
and ended up killing a total stranger.
I've never killed anyone
I didn't completely vet before,
whose guilt I wasn't absolutely certain of.
I did something wholly inside the moment
and wholly outside the code.
Something spontaneous.
Who did I just kill ?
Freebo's doorman.
I... am... fucked.
Just a matter of time
before someone calls it in.
- Hey, you.
- Dexter, hey.
I know it's not one of our regular nights
but... can you come over ?
Uh, sure. Everything OK ?
Yeah. Just...
Just missing you, that's all.
God, you're on fire lately.
Are you complaining ?
I'm complying.
Where are you ?
I'm right here.
In a safe place.
God created pudding
and then He rested.
Pudding of chocolate.
Manna from heaven.
What are the kids gonna do
for dessert tomorrow ?
Tangerines.
Dexter Morgan.
Yes, I'm happy
with my long-distance provider.
What the hell ever happened
to "do not call" ? It's three in the morning.
Not in India.
I have an insanely busy morning
tomorrow,
so I'll be gone
before you and the kids wake up.
Dexter, you've been working
such killer hours lately.
Just hold me till you have to go.
Just a matter of time.
Morning, Sergeant.
How long for you to get
to 118 Calendar ?
Um, 20, 30 minutes.
- I got it, Dex.
- Got what ?
Only the case that's
gonna get me my shield. It's huge.
Angel put me on it. Officially on it.
Huge ?
- Who the hell are you ?
- Bet you're wondering who the hell he is.
Who he is is what makes this case huge.
That's Miguel Prado.
He's that ADA who's been on a mission
to put away as many bad guys as he can.
You know ?
"A safe Miami is the only Miami. "
A safe Miami
and we're all unemployed.
Why's he look so familiar ?
He just made
the cover of Florida magazine.
Top prosecutor in the state
three years in a row.
He and LaGuerta go way back.
You know, that whole cubano thing.
The other guy is Ramon Prado,
Miguel's middle brother.
He's a lieutenant
with the sheriff's department.
Made himself quite the reputation
for being a law-and-order hard-ass.
And...
Oscar.
- Prado ?
- As in "baby brother".
So much for spontaneity.
What was he doing in a dump like this ?
They're saying he was
a coach at a youth club.
Came here to confront the scumbag
about selling shit to his kids.
- Talk about wrong place at the wrong time.
- Tell me about it.
- Find anything ?
- Yeah.
Dead guy with a hole in his chest.
This window's cracked
and there's blood on the wall.
- Who shut these drapes ?
- Probably the first on scene.
Some dipshit rookie
who's still outside puking.
So what do we got ?
Signs of a majorly big struggle here, there,
everywhere. Single stab wound to the chest.
- You read my article yet ?
- Started it. So far it's really good.
Awesome.
God.
Cómo te dejaron a Oscarcito.
Te fallé.
Whoever did this...
he's already wishing he was dead.
Someone really stepped on his dick
with this one.
There were so many lessons
in the vaunted code of Harry.
Twisted commandments handed down
from the only God I ever worshipped.
One through ten...
Don't get caught.
That I got covered.
But killing someone
without knowing if he's guilty...
I'd love some help on this one...
but my God is dead now.
Man's best friend, eh, Dex ?
Not today.
Hey, my sister said that LaGuerta
knows this Miguel Prado pretty well.
Way back when, when Mig...
Hey, what's up ? Way back when,
when Miguel was in law school
and Maria was just starting
in law enforcement, they hooked up.
Hooked up ?
Between us, for Maria, Miguel Prado
will always be the one that got away.
Prelim has the victim,
Oscar Prado, 26, dead.
Dead from a single stab wound
to the chest.
The deceased's brother, ADA Miguel Prado,
informed me at the scene
that Oscar went to confront
one Fred Bowman, street name Freebo,
for selling drugs to some youth-club kids.
Morgan ?
Freebo's the guy that killed two co-eds
in the Everglades and got away with it.
So the way it looks,
Oscar Prado died a hero.
Also, our team found a shitload of, uh...
a substantial amount of drugs in the house.
Any leads on his whereabouts ?
That part of the neighborhood isn't
exactly police-friendly but I'm staying on it.
- Talk to me about forensics.
- Evidence indicates this was no hit-and-run.
It was a furious close-in battle. Whoever...
Or is it "whomever" ?
- "Whoever" is good.
- Whoever did this got in a lucky shot
or was really good at handling a blade.
According to the ME, the aorta
was cleanly severed in one penetration.
- Not easy to do.
- Any luck finding the weapon ?
It's not on or near the premises.
We've checked roofs, sewers, trash bins
in a five-block radius.
Our conclusion -
the assailant took it with him.
Dexter, what's the blood saying ?
Pretty much what everyone else is. I have
some second level on-scene work to do.
- I'll get back to you ASAP.
- Get it to Sergeant Batista.
Full disclosure.
I've had a personal relationship
with the Prado family for many years.
And it goes a lot further
than the whole cubano thing.
Sergeant ?
Stating the obvious, Lieutenant,
I like Freebo for this.
Me too.
Morgan ?
Yes, ma'am ?
Hit the streets harder.
Learn what you can learn.
Uh, all due respect, Lieutenant,
if Freebo did this, he's not in Miami.
I mean, he's in the wind.
We can sit around
on our asses and speculate
on where we think
the prime suspect may or may not be,
- or we can actually go and look for him.
- Hmm.
As a Miami prosecutor,
I have dedicated my career to fighting crime,
to making our streets safe for everyone.
Every family -
white, black, Latino, Asian -
deserves the full measure
of our devotion to their dignity.
And now that crime has touched my family
in the most profound way imaginable,
I grieve equally for every family
that has been visited
with the same unimaginable news
that we have received today.
Our beautiful city is a city of families.
And the untimely taking of any of us
touches all of us.
My parents brought
my brother Ramon and me...
Part of my ritual has
always been getting to know my victims,
confirming their guilt beyond all doubt.
Oscar Prado tried to kill Freebo,
then he tried to kill me.
No way he was there on some
noble youth-club mission.
He's got to be guilty of something.
Aren't we all ?
So I ask again...
Who are you ?
Two speeding tickets
and an illegal U-turn.
Talk about outside the code of Harry.
Harry finds me in a pool of blood,
turns me into his own
personal vendetta machine,
and when he sees the monster
he created in action, he kills himself.
Deb can drink to his honor
on her own.
Any luck
in the land of reluctant witnesses ?
One house I play good cop,
the next I play bad cop.
I still can't get shit
from anybody in that neighborhood.
- You know what the problem is, right ?
- Wait, Quinn, let me guess. The "cop" part ?
No, they don't owe you anything.
There's no incentive.
Which skews the balance of power
way in their direction, right ?
Here, let me do you a favor.
Call this guy. Tell him you know me.
Tell him you want to cash in
one of my coupons.
- Coupons ?
- Yeah. He's a CI from my days in Narcotics.
He's got a hook in him
that's not coming out anytime soon.
- What do you want in return ?
- For you to remember that I did you a solid.
- What, not even a "thank you" ?
- Thank you.
Stop looking at my ass.
Yeah, of course...
Detective.
Officer. You're Anton ?
In the flesh.
You got something you want to show me ?
Oh, yeah, I've seen him before.
- Really ? Where ?
- In the news.
Isn't that that guy you let walk
on those co-ed killings ?
Now that there
was a fine piece of police work.
- You know him from the newspaper ?
- I saw him on CNN.
- OK. That's all you got ?
- That's all you got.
If this is you and Quinn fucking with me,
I'm really not in the mood.
If you need something for that temper,
I got a man down the street with some real
mellow weed can take that edge right off.
- I don't take advice from drug dealers, so...
- Drug dealer ? Oh, never that !
A drug user.
Occasionally.
- Strictly weed though, Officer. Strictly weed.
- Then how'd you become Quinn's snitch ?
I got caught up in a drug bust. Quinn told me
that if I blew the whistle on the bigger fish,
I'd stay out of jail. So I listened.
Attentively.
Yeah, well... you know,
it never hurts an occasional drug user
- to have more than one friend on the force.
- That's the thing, Officer...
- I got enough friends.
- All right, well, I'm outta here.
Yeah, well, you have a good one, you hear ?
What about this Prado guy ?
And to determine the impact site,
the exact point
where force encounters a body,
you have to distinguish
the geometric differences
between back-spatter,
satellite spatter,
- misting and arterial spurting.
- Gross !
Shut up.
You remember how before
when Katie's dad
- was talking about being a surgeon ?
- Yeah.
And sometimes how he has to
cut into bodies and there's blood ?
But he saves lives.
Do you save lives ?
OK, you know how there's good guys
and there's bad guys ?
So you catch bad guys ?
Well, not directly, but I help.
Do you have a uniform ?
Lab coat.
A gun ?
No.
- He's got a badge.
- It's a laminate.
Well, thank you so much for taking time
from your busy schedule, Mr. Morgan,
- to come and talk to the children.
- It was a real learning experience.
Looks like
I really got through to 'em, huh ?
It would have sucked even worse
if I didn't have a dad today.
Thanks for inviting me, buddy.
If anyone should have father
issues - anger, rejection, abandonment -
it's Cody.
And what's he do ?
He moves on.
How does that happen ?
- I was so bad you're crying ?
- No, no.
No, it's just...
just something I've always wanted.
You being here for the kids,
it's all so wonderfully uncomplicated.
Hello ?
Mr. Morgan, this is Miguel Prado.
I need to see you.
Right away.
So much for uncomplicated.
It almost feels like a piece of art.
Thank you, sir.
But to me it's more like a story.
Tell me that story, Mr. Morgan.
- The encounter started over here.
- Mmm.
The scuff marks on the linoleum,
the crumpling of the throw rug,
they all have a directional quality
that leads to...
Now this is where your brother and Freebo...
He's my lieutenant's prime suspect...
But you know that.
There was a brutal struggle.
I gotta say, it looks like
your brother fought like a hero...
but he was overmatched and sustained
a fatal stab wound to his chest.
Everything about the blood suggests
that your brother bled out almost instantly.
- He didn't suffer ?
- Blood never lies.
So now I know how he died.
The question is why.
One more thing, Mr. Morgan.
Why would a blood spatter analyst
spend time searching
the sheriff department's database
for information on my dead brother ?
Um...
Like you, sir, I wanted to understand
what happened here.
I thought that knowing some details
about your brother's life
would help me make sense
out of his death.
In your line of work, Mr. Morgan,
is it usual for you to get so involved ?
I just sounded like a prosecutor there.
I'm sorry.
It's not a problem, sir, and no,
it's not usual for me to get so involved,
but this one, this death, got to me.
It's just...
It seems so unreal that, uh...
he's gone.
Yeah, I know.
So a man dies, Mr. Morgan, and what's left,
his soul ? And what is that exactly ?
I really couldn't tell you.
Cause some people say
the soul just lives on forever.
- I hope not.
- Which makes you a cynic.
It makes me a scientist.
So no one you've ever loved has died ?
My father died when I was in my 20s.
And you don't believe that...
that his soul,
call it his life force, is still here ?
Somehow it's living inside you ?
Because I...
- I should have been there for him.
- You can't blame yourself, sir.
That's easier said than done,
Mr. Morgan.
Do me a favor. You really want
to get to know my brother like you say,
come to his wake tonight.
Come see how much and how...
how fully he was loved.
OK.
I've taken up enough of your day.
Thank you.
Dexter.
These reports final ?
Blood specimens I collected all came back
belonging to Oscar Prado.
Trace prints on and around the victim
all point to Freebo.
Anyone out there talking ?
Officer Morgan was hitting up
the usual firewall of clammed-up witnesses
and non-witnesses,
so I put her in touch with an old CI of mine.
- Hopefully...
- Hey, Quinn.
That CI you put me on
was totally useless for Freebo.
- Sadly, it's not a perfect world.
- Yeah.
For all we know,
Freebo's in Nebraska by now.
- I guess you don't owe me that favor, then.
- How come he gets favors ?
Oh, he doesn't.
But what the CI told me about the victim...
he wasn't some hero coach who went
into the hood and took one for the team.
What do you mean ?
Oscar Prado was into Freebo
for some serious cash.
Now why would someone be
into a drug dealer for big bucks ?
- Shh !
- Because Oscar Prado,
the pride of Little Havana,
was a fucking junkie !
Thanks, Maria.
Good one, Morgan.
She's been in better moods.
- I didn't exactly brighten her day.
- No, you didn't.
Excuse me for doing my fucking job.
You see any other supercops
coming in here with any leads ?
- You're definitely amazing but you gotta...
- I know, be aware of my surroundings,
take the temperature of the room
before I open my mouth.
- It's a bad habit. I admit it.
- Well, look on the bright side.
Now that you've given up
men, booze and cigarettes,
running your mouth's
the only bad habit you have left.
That's right.
I'm a model of fucking perfection.
- You remember what today is, right ?
- How could I forget ?
7:30. I'll buy your first drink.
You wanted to see me ?
Siéntate.
I need you to think about
Debra Morgan's continued involvement
on the Oscar Prado case.
You want me to throw her under the bus
for being overzealous ?
It's not about zeal. It's about tact and
sensitivity. It's also about the real world.
This case is as high profile as it gets.
Óyeme, Angel.
Morgan is resourceful and tenacious and
usually the right amount of pain-in-the-ass.
But there are political ramifications.
My history with Miguel Prado aside,
this case is just too big for her.
Just say the word
and I will follow your orders.
Becoming a Homicide sergeant
is more than just a bump in pay scale.
It's a quantum leap in responsibility.
All part of moving up the chain.
If I bounce her, she'll hate me.
You're her boss, Angel, not her friend.
It's up to you.
He touched many people,
many hearts.
Qué bien que viniste.
- Can I get another cranberry juice ?
- That makes three. Problems down under ?
Jeez, I like the fucking taste, OK ?
Miss you, Dad.
- My condolences.
- Thank you for coming.
Losing my brother,
it's going to leave a pain in my heart
that I don't think is ever going to heal.
You have a brother, Dexter ?
No, just the one loud sister.
What she said back at the station,
it's OK.
I know my brother was a good man.
But I can't say that he suffered
from the tragedy of perfection.
Who does ?
Who indeed ?
Hey, brother. The mayor's here.
You attacked me with a knife
in a dope dealer's house.
No, Oscar, you certainly did not suffer
from the tragedy of perfection.
Then why does this feel so wrong ?
Why in your death
are you still so alive in my life ?
Did you know him well ?
Not as well as I thought.
Sorry.
Cuervo Black.
Thanks.
Harry.
- What the hell is that ?
- Cranberry juice. That gonna be a problem ?
Not even close to a problem.
But the taste, kind of funky.
You know, by the time my dad
was my age, he already had his shield.
Kinda why I'm here.
I'm taking you off
the Oscar Prado case.
I come up with grade-A intel
on Oscar Prado,
and I'm getting tossed off the case
for being a little loud ?
In a nutshell.
- LaGuerta put you up to this ?
- It was my decision.
I'll tell you one thing, Angel...
I'm not letting anyone
get in the way of me getting my shield.
There's only one person in this department
who can get in your way.
Who ?
You.
Can I get a real fucking drink, please ?
My sister still lives her life
trying to please our father.
Me...
I'm following the lead
of an eight-year-old kid.
I'm moving on.
Thank you for last night.
It was a nice surprise.
This is where I wanted to be.
Again ?
All I want is chocolate pudding... and you.
Not necessarily in that order.
Morgan.
- Where the fuck were you last night ?
- Rita's.
- It wasn't Rita's night.
- Turns out it was.
- I called you.
- I know.
- And you ignored me ?
- Not you. Harry.
Deb...
I'm in a whole 'nother place when it comes
to Dad. I'm working out some personal stuff.
You are such a fucking guy.
What is this, you gotta kill your father so you
can become your own man kind of bullshit ?
Dad wasn't perfect...
but he was there for you.
- Deb, wait.
- What ?
I'm sorry I didn't notice your haircut.
So what is it ? Is it too short,
too young, too dorky, what ?
It's beautiful.
Beautiful ?
You just said "beautiful".
Yeah, I did, cause it is.
Looks like you honored Dad
for both of us last night anyway.
I had some help.
You getting along
with the new boss man ?
Oh, fuck him. He took me off
the Oscar Prado case and put me on this.
Some dead-end Jane Doe.
A couple of ladies of the night
called this in...
Oh, Madre de Dios.
Could you turn that thing off ?!
We'll work quietly.
About halfway through your article, Vince.
So far, very moving.
Yeah, I was trying to make
second-tier chromosomal analysis sexy.
Glad you're picking up on it.
- Strangled.
- No blood. I'm the blood guy.
- Why call me in ?
- Because of this.
- Looks like our evildoer had an agenda.
- Maybe it was a tattoo or something.
Dex, I need to know
if this was ante or postmortem.
Teegan.
Freebo's girlfriend.
Looks like he's still in Miami.
Oye.
- You talk to Morgan yet ?
- Yep.
How'd she take it ?
- There were curse words involved.
- You did good.
Sergeant.
Way to be.
Thank you.
There you go, Dexter.
Good as new.
Hold the elevator. Hold...
Asshole.
Sorry. Sergeant Asshole.
Vamos, Masuka, Quinn.
iVamos !
We got some celebrating to do.
- You can still drink after last night ?
- A man has his needs.
You can go back to your
cute little cranberry juice.
Nah, it tastes like shit. I'm gonna
have a mojito or ten on you, Sarge.
Morgan.
You so have the wrong person.
Oh, there's a good reason
why Quinn's of interest to IA.
No, understand me. When I say
you have the wrong person, I mean me.
These people are more than badge
numbers to me. They're my friends.
- They're my family.
- Shh ! Listen.
That's the sound of your shield
calling for help.
Harry said that what was inside me
would be there forever.
And that I wouldn't be able to change.
He was half right.
Killing Oscar Prado
was a bell I can't un-ring.
I have moved on from my father, but
I still need his code, now more than ever.
But it has to evolve,
become my own.
Change is good.
Hey, you.
Hey, yourself.
This music again ?
Chocolate pudding again ?
- Oh, shit.
- What ?
I've done this before.
- What do you mean ?
- I'm pregnant.