(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
(BUZZING)
Frankie, where are you?
Welcome to the chop shop, cugine.
You can't kill me twice, Sally Boy.
I'm already fucking dead, remember?
I'm the boss, Michael.
What you had belongs to me.
Even the girl I loved?
What's mine is mine.
What's yours is mine.
(GRUNTS)
Well...
...this is mine too, Sally.
Now you can have it.
- VAFFANCUL'.
- (SCREAMS)
Fuck Ben Kingsley.
Danny Baldwin
took him to fucking acting school.
Very well directed, Morgan.
I think there's potentially more money
in this than in the porn we've done.
So, what do we think?
We need the extra scene or not?
I like it the way it is.
I don't know, Chrissy,
these audiences today love blood.
I tend to agree with Carlo.
I'm thinking one more sexy kill.
When Michael follows Centrella
to the strip club...
...what if he chop up
one of the women?
Who, as fate would have it...
...was, at one time,
Sally Boy's mistress.
Two extra shoot days,
at a minimum.
Kid, if it buys us
a bullshit theatrical release...
(CELL PHONE BUZZING)
I'd have to get more money
from Tony.
I want this fucking thing
out there.
- Yeah, T, what's up?
- You talk to the guy with the mattresses?
I'm in editing.
We just saw the cut of Cleaver.
- And?
- Awesome as is.
The lawyer called though.
We might have to change the title.
The Eldridge Cleaver estate,
they want an injunction.
Listen, if you wanna see some of it,
we're finishing the ADR after lunch.
- What's that again?
- Sound dubbing.
Just call this dispatcher, huh?
It's a holiday weekend.
Thousands of people
will be out at the beach.
I'm on it.
- He coming down?
- Please.
He don't give two shits
about production.
It's a little boring, I gotta say.
I mean, that was surprising to me.
Mr. Sacrimoni, how are you today?
Isn't that for you to tell me?
I wish I had better news.
Based on the latest pictures...
...the cancer has continued
to metastasize from the lungs.
We now show masses
in the mediastinal lymph nodes...
...both kidneys and the brain.
The headaches.
So...
...the lobectomy, radiation...
...the goddamn chemo...
...what was all that?
(COUGHS) For kicks?
Those were our options at the time.
- Now what are our options?
- Limited to the extent...
...that I wouldn't recommend any.
We're looking at stage four
small-cell carcinoma of the lungs.
- And there's no stage five.
- That's correct.
How long?
Difficult to say.
- I have seen miracles over the years.
- Forget the miracles.
Three months.
Give or take.
Thank you for your candor.
We have a plane back to Springfield.
How you doing, John?
It's funny.
Ironic. Whichever.
I got here...
...I quit smoking after 38 years.
Exercised, ate right.
And for what?
Even still...
...it was the right move.
(GATE BUZZING OPEN)
(TV NEWS ANCHOR)
One hundred degrees again
for the afternoon high temperature...
...in Springfield. We see
some shadows on the ground...
(INMATE)
Hey, yo, fuck you.
Oh, there she is, my girl.
- How are you, sweetie?
- All right.
- Hey, Dad.
- Hi, honey.
Sit down.
What did Rosen say?
- How's the hotel? You all settled in?
- It's fine.
How are you, angel?
You look beautiful.
- I'm good. Eric sends his love.
- That's nice.
John, what about Rosen?
I don't know. I...
I don't know, sweetie, I'm...
- I'm very, very sick.
- Oh, my God.
(CRYING)
All right, don't cry.
Don't cry. You don't have to make it
any harder than it is, all right?
No physical contact, please.
- I love you, John.
- I love you too, sweetie.
- Daddy.
- I know. I know.
Ladies, no contact.
All right.
You come back,
you see me again tomorrow.
We'll have more time, huh?
Could I bum one of those?
It's casual though, right?
Well, it's your cousin's movie premiere.
We should dress accordingly.
It's what they call
a cast and crew screening.
It's in the city, Tony.
With an after party at some rooftop bar
in the Meatpacking District.
That place is very chic now.
Meatpackers?
I'm a happily married man.
I'm telling you, it's not dress-up.
Speaking of dress-up,
Christopher told me...
...Kelli is having her wedding dress
made into an outfit...
...for the baby to be christened in.
Oh, sweet.
(BURPS)
You all right?
- You taking a date to the screening?
- If I can meet a normal guy, maybe.
I heard that.
What, Finn wasn't normal?
I don't intend to discuss Finn.
What about that guy
in your MCAT review?
Oh, please, he's completely
fixated on his O-chem final.
He wants to be a doctor.
Tell him it's educational.
There's body parts
all over this movie.
Hey, screw the movie.
I just wanna hang with celebs.
Why? You think you're gonna
get to sleep with Paris Hilton?
What? No.
Stop fidgeting
and eat your noodles.
- I don't want this.
- Where are you going?
The bathroom. Jesus.
MEOW
You two have a fight?
I don't know.
Keep an eye on his temp, and we'll
finish out the week on the Ceftin.
You rest now.
I'll see you in the morning.
- He should be on heparin.
- Excuse me?
Listen to him. Check his ABG.
I'm gonna have to ask you again
to not interfere, Warren.
I'm gonna change your sheets.
So, what are you,
the world's smartest orderly?
These days I am.
Twenty-two years
a practicing oncologist...
...specializing in cancers of the liver.
Roll to your right, please.
Let me spare us the awkwardness.
I killed my wife.
Not that it's any justification...
...I had reason to suspect she was
cheating on me with her chiropractor.
- Jesus.
- Granted...
...I was abusing cocaine at the time,
and alcohol...
...but I came home one day...
...shot her four times.
Twice in the head.
I killed her aunt too.
I didn't know she was there.
Roll over, please.
And the mailman.
At that point, I had to fully commit.
Why are you here, exactly?
I've been accused of being part
of a certain Italian-American subculture.
(LAUGHS)
Hey, I know who you are.
I meant what's wrong with you?
- Lungs.
- I been wanting to meet you, actually.
I saw you on Bill Kurtis.
- Warren Feldman.
- John Sacrimoni.
Good to know you.
- I take it you've done chemo, huh?
- Twice.
Mind if I take a look at your chart?
What about Gunga Din?
Gupte? Fuck him.
Oh, you're seeing Rosen.
They let me fly to Cleveland,
my expense.
- You know him?
- I saw him speak once...
...at an ASCO conference in Georgia.
- Good man.
- But?
Actually, very few people know this,
but he really can't walk on water.
What was his prognosis?
Three months.
- With the treatment you've had?
- What do you mean?
You got a window
of one to three years.
What about the metastasis?
Two rounds of Paraplatin,
docetaxel and Platinol...
...concurrent with radiation?
Come on, any cancer inside you
has slowed to a crawl.
Why is he so fucking negative?
We tell the patient three months,
he lives a year, who looks like a hero?
I'll see you around, John.
You take it easy. Hang in there.
Oh, fuck me.
Tony, morning.
You got a sec?
As I told you, my partner and I are with
the Joint Terror Task Force now.
You're around Port Newark
often enough.
We're concerned about what might come
through there from the Middle East.
Yeah, and?
Let's talk terror funding.
Most of it comes about
through illegal enterprise.
Our pitch is this, and it's the same
we gave Christopher Moltisanti.
Maybe he never mentioned it.
If you or any of your people
ever heard of anything going down...
...Middle Easterners, Pakistanis...
...you'd be helping us a lot
if you let us know.
I think there's a word for that.
Your daughter takes
premed classes in New York.
She use the tunnels?
Just something to keep in mind.
That's the last time
I'm going down for the paper.
You tell that fucking Polack
to get here early...
...and bring up the paper with her...
...or she can go clean
somebody else's fucking toilets.
What happened?
It's too dangerous.
Has been for years.
May I have your attention, please?
May I have your attention?
Welcome to the premiere of Cleaver...
...the story of a young man
who goes to pieces...
...then manages to find himself again.
(SCATTERED LAUGHTER)
In all seriousness, however...
...I'd like to say a few words.
Much like a child,
a film has many parents.
That is to say, many individuals...
...who act like parents...
...or that by aversion...
...the film is their baby.
I, as an executive producer...
...am one of those individuals.
Two more examples
are here with me tonight.
Ladies and gentlemen,
my co-EP, Christopher Moltisanti...
...and our director, Morgan Yam.
Yeah. Hey.
I know you're all psyched
to see the movie...
...so I'm not gonna give
a big speech here.
I just wanna give a shout-out...
...to the man who, without him...
...this whole thing would be impossible.
Where is he?
Anthony Soprano, everybody.
- Hey!
- All right, Ton.
Once he came onboard,
the whole thing fell together.
And all the other investors too.
Plus my wife, Kelli,
and our new baby. I love you guys.
Okay, then. Cell phones off,
and hope you like the movie.
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYING)
You don't know what?
He's a fucking rat!
- But we can't really prove it.
- You're gonna argue with me?
No, it's just, I mean,
he's practically like your own son.
Sorry, Sally,
I think you ought to give him a pass.
I didn't ask you
what you fucking think.
Motherfucking son of a...
- That's you.
- No.
- No, it is.
- You find where this pezzanovante is...
...and you bring him
to the butcher shop.
They're gonna find pieces of this kid
all over fucking Canarsie.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
- Yeah.
- I'm sure he's fine, sweetie.
- You gotta relax.
- But for Michael to have not called...
The wedding's in two days.
Who, the Guatemalan?
What time is he gonna be there?
I hate to say this, but the truth is
he ain't good enough for you.
I mean, he's a good kid.
What you need is a man.
Tell him to put it in the trunk.
You know how long
I been waiting to do that?
(DOMINIQUE MOANING)
Dad, that was neat at the end,
the creepy figurine and the crucifix.
I'm glad you caught that, Alexandra.
Very observant.
The sacred and the propane.
There's a ton of people
wearing T-shirts here. I told you.
Is it so horrible you look nice?
I'm starving. I need to eat
something already.
I asked if you wanted popcorn.
- You want me to make you a plate?
- Yeah.
- What?
- What? I'll give you what.
Come here.
The fucking boss down in the cellar.
White bathrobe.
Where'd you get that?
I don't know. Artistic choice.
Seriously though, I'm very proud.
Whatever else happens,
you made a movie, Christopher.
Nobody can take that away.
Hundred years from now,
we're dead and gone...
...people will be watching
this fucking thing.
You know how much
Imperia vodka I scored...
...just from this party alone?
I had a couple of cases
put down in your car too.
Look at this.
The family of early man.
And...
Great, thank you.
Hey, Danny.
Danny, come here.
Take a picture with us.
- Hey, boys. How are you?
- Phil Leotardo.
Larry and I hung out at the set.
I don't know if you know this...
...but the actors,
they don't make up what they say.
- It's true. Even De Niro, the girl told me.
- The script girl.
- Lorenzo Barese.
- Hey, how you doing, my friend?
- You getting enough to eat?
- Bryan Rawley, U.S. Marshal's Service.
Terms of your bail
confine you to your home, sir.
- Say hello to Danny?
- Yeah.
- Larry!
- Call the fucking lawyer!
- Excuse us, excuse us.
- Leave him alone, you bastards!
Jesus Christ.
There's Danny's manager.
I better go talk to him.
There he is.
- So how was Florida?
- Hot and sticky, like my balls.
I spoke to Ginny. She's a wreck.
John's in the cancer ward. She's down
the road in some fucking motel.
Poor prick. Prison's not bad enough,
fucking lung cancer to boot.
Tell me about it.
Quintuple bypass...
...then the infection,
seven months of physical therapy.
I'm just now starting
to get back to myself again.
Sausage, cioppino,
anything spicy...
...put me back in the emergency room
I'm not careful.
(SIGHS)
But all in all, we're lucky fucks.
I tell myself that every day.
So now you're back, how about
you straighten that family out?
Not for me, Anthony.
Obviously, healthwise,
being a boss is a young man's game.
Between the joint fitters
and the carpenters...
...those envelopes are light
over 10 percent each week.
I feel it too.
Well, word on the street
is Gerry's the favorite to take over.
He's my protégé.
I don't stand in his way.
Oh, there's a ringing endorsement.
- Hey, Tony. How are you?
- Doc. Doc. Good.
- You know Danny?
- How you doing, Mr. Soprano?
Got a ticket on the Jersey Turnpike.
Broken windshield wiper.
- I said he should talk to you.
- I'll take care of it.
- That's not necessary.
- Let's take a picture here.
All right, chill out, Doc.
If you're Phil Leotardo,
you cannot be happy...
...with the state of affairs,
despite appearances.
We're joined now via satellite
from Bainbridge Island, Washington...
...by Jerry's fellow mob expert
Manny Safier...
...the author of the new book
The Wise Guide to Wiseguys.
Manny, welcome to the program.
How goes the book tour?
Thank you, Geraldo. Excellent.
- Jerry, how are you?
- Manny.
So we're discussing the apparent mob
power vacuum here in New York City.
Are you shocked that there's still
no successor to John Sacrimoni?
Not really. I mean...
...the last 10, 12 years,
that's been a dysfunctional family.
And as Jerry said earlier,
there are several viable candidates.
Well, viable, I don't know.
You had Phil Leotardo
as the logical successor, but...
You also have
Gerardo "Gerry" Torciano...
...also Faustino "Doc" Santoro,
who I believe is the frontrunner.
- Then...
- Surprised you haven't mentioned...
...Carmine Lupertazzi, Jr.
I was about to before you interrupted.
In fact, if you take a look
at my book, in chapter 14...
This Santoro thing,
I called it a year ago.
Hey.
Thank you for coming, Anthony.
I know it's a long trip.
What, and miss a chance
to see Missouri?
So how's Ginny today?
She went with Allegra
to buy some stuff for the kitchenette.
Good, clear her mind.
Reason I asked you here today,
she's a bright kid, your sister...
...but business...
My life insurance,
I wanna put her on a monthly stipend.
Probably a good idea.
Not all the doctors agree...
...but if I do only have a few months,
I wanna take care of all this now.
Wait a second.
Which doctor doesn't agree?
Feldman, the guy I told you about.
- The wife murderer?
- He's still a doctor, Anthony.
He was a highly-respected oncologist.
- I know, but, John...
- He reviewed my case.
He says I could hang on for years.
You're right.
He still has the knowledge.
I mean, O.J.'s no less
of a running back, right?
Let me ask you something,
Anthony.
How will I be remembered?
A wonderful husband.
A loving father.
- On the street though, I mean.
- From what I know, you were well-liked.
Respected across the board,
despite the allocution even.
God knows guys have actually
named names...
...for a hell of a lot less than what
you were looking at. The only nega...
What?
Well, when Carmine died
and you took over...
...people felt you changed...
...became a little trigger-happy, maybe?
A hothead.
God forbid any of them
would find themselves in that position.
It's a thankless job.
- What are you, hung-over?
- What? I had two glasses of wine.
Why are you so pissy?
- The portrayal of that guy in the movie.
- What guy?
- The boss, Tony.
- What about him?
- It was based on you.
- Yeah, I know, you said, the yelling.
- No, it wasn't just the yelling.
- Imitation's a form of flattery.
- You think that was flattering?
- It was okay.
- He's a tough prick, that Baldwin.
- What about the girlfriend?
- What girlfriend?
- The cleaver guy.
The lead character.
His entire motive for revenge.
I don't know.
You lost me, Carm.
Sally Boy, the boss,
he fucked the guy's fiancée.
The thing with Adriana?
I told you it never fucking happened.
Well, apparently,
your nephew feels otherwise.
Ro pointed it out to me. If she saw it,
that means other people did.
- It's a movie. It's fictional.
- It's a revenge fantasy, Tony...
...which ends with the boss's head
split open by a meat cleaver.
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
Oh, there he is.
Good time last night?
Yeah, it was all right.
How about you?
Well, Gab had fucking nightmares.
- Club soda, hon.
- Sure.
So, what did you think
of the movie?
You know, Chrissy's the last person
I would have confused with Marty...
...but I gotta say, it wasn't bad.
- Is he around?
- Chrissy? No.
He don't come around here
no more, you know that.
That Baldwin was pretty good, huh?
He was a mean fuck.
I'll give him that.
And that girl that played
the fiancée, she was hot.
You know, the one he was fucking.
It's weird how it works,
the creative process.
I'm watching that movie
Edward Scissorhands, when:
All of a sudden, it hits me.
What if instead of a pair of scissors,
it's a meat cleaver instead?
A couple of years later,
you got a movie.
Originally, I thought a ball-peen hammer,
but a cleaver's better.
I tell you, it's like I'm living
somebody else's life.
You're just not comfortable
with success yet. I know. It's scary.
Feel the fear and do it anyway.
- Without chemicals either.
- (CUPS CLINK) Yeah.
So Kelli, the baby.
Good, fucking great.
She's a doll.
She cries a lot though.
The baby, not Kelli.
I hope you're taking the time
to reflect on all this.
- Savor the good stuff.
- Yeah. No, I am.
There's my other sober buddy.
- Is that an FBI guy?
- Your tax dollars at work.
- Does he follow you around all the time?
- They drop in and out. It's fun.
Look, seriously, think where you were
just three months ago.
You came into that meeting, you were
so fucked up you could barely talk.
And that woman friend
was even worse.
I've been trying to do what you said,
hold back a little...
...steer clear of old habits,
same people.
Must be hard though,
given your lifestyle.
They already misinterpret
I don't wanna hang around so much.
Fucking Paulie especially.
Have you explained how hard it is
to be around alcohol?
- How familiar surroundings set it off?
- They don't give a fuck.
"But he's fucking my wife, Carmine.
I want him dead," Jimmy says.
"He will be," he said, "but not
just right now. He earns too much."
Eight years later,
Jimmy gets a call one day.
"Remember that guy we were talking
about who was fucking your wife?
He can go."
The guy wasn't making him
money no more.
And that was Carmine Lupertazzi.
- Holy fucking shit.
- Yeah.
There you are. We went...
John, what the hell are you doing?
- What?
- You're smoking.
- So?
- Daddy, you're on oxygen.
Hey, Warren, pardon me, I'm sorry.
- Just calm down, all right?
- Calm down? I don't fucking believe you.
(SIGHS)
What do I got to lose, Gin?
- What's the difference?
- You told me Dr. Feldman...
...doesn't agree with the others.
Yeah, well...
- Miracles do happen, John.
- Not to this family they don't.
You know,
it's that kind of attitude...
...that probably brought this on
in the first place.
You gonna start with that again?
What about all these six-year-olds
with leukemia?
What's that from,
all their negative thinking?
(COUGHING)
All due respect, he's a great guy, Doc,
but boss material?
The important thing
is we all work together...
...whoever winds up in the driver's seat.
Yeah, Phil, though, I'll never get it.
The man was my mentor.
It was right there for the taking.
His heart, Gerry.
What was he gonna do?
That's my point though,
what you just said.
Johnny goes away,
it's Phil's turn in the driver's seat...
...and his heart gives out.
- Right.
- His heart.
- I know. What?
- It's a metaphor.
He lost his balls is what I'm saying.
Just say it then.
- Walt fucking Whitman over here.
- I'll tell you later, okay?
- Ladies.
- Hey.
- Am I right?
- How you doing?
Should we get some more wine?
This fucking waiter on sabbatical?
What's the name of that Sangiovese
we had at Quattro Gatti?
The night your...
(SOUND DROPS OUT)
(SCREAMING)
Come on.
Let's go.
Yeah, give me five dimes apiece
on St. Louis...
...Minnesota and Baltimore.
I would have invited you to play,
but we already had our fourth.
You're not happy.
Let's order.
- What can I get you?
- Seared ahi, mixed greens...
...and an iced tea, please.
Philly cheesesteak.
You know what? Give me
an Arnold Palmer instead of the iced tea.
I always enjoy those,
but it never occurs to me to order one.
What the fuck, Carmine?
This family of yours.
Fucking senile Doc Santoro
uses one of my guys as a diversion?
Sil could have got hurt.
Doc showed a lack of respect.
This fucking leadership, boy.
Step up, Carmine.
Get your hands around this thing.
You know you got the support.
You never thought
you'd mutter those words, did you?
What do you want me to say?
I hear you, Tony, and I'm flattered.
But boss? I don't think so.
Especially now that Doc
has cemented his position.
Phil was bad enough in the top spot,
but him I could have lived with.
Here you go.
There was a time
I was obsessed with being in charge.
- You remember?
- Right, so do it.
One night around then,
I had this dream.
It's my pop's 100th birthday,
even though he'd been dead for years.
The whole family's there.
Grandkids, everybody.
He's wearing one of these
gold paper crowns, like at Burger King.
Anyway, I give him his present,
this mellifluous box, ribbons...
He opens it up, then looks at me.
This gaze of absolute disappointment.
There's nothing in the box.
So he hands it back to me.
"Go fill it up," he says.
- "Come back when I'm 200."
- So go for it, Carmine.
Fulfill that part of yourself.
We have this ritual
at my house for years.
Our kids are in boarding school.
Every night I come home from work,
I strip down, jump naked in the pool.
Nicole brings me a Scotch and water.
We sit, relax a little, talk.
I go up to bed, the air conditioning.
She brings me
a light dinner on a tray.
One night, during all that fighting
with John, I come home, I'm exhausted.
So tired, so tense,
I skip the pool.
I go right upstairs, flop on the bed.
Nicole comes up with a drink.
She says, "Darling,
I think it's time you took a rest."
I say, "I'm gonna.
We're gonna take a vacation."
She says, "That's not what I meant.
I don't wanna be the wealthiest widow
on Long Island. I want you to quit now."
I'm not ashamed to say
that she made me cry.
That wonderful, loving woman.
That dream with my father,
the empty box...
...it wasn't about being boss.
It was about being happy.
Warren, hi.
Hi, hon. How's he doing?
Listen, I've been meaning
to talk to you about the smoking.
John shared with me
how upset you were.
Psychologically, when a person's
told they're dying...
...it's the ultimate loss of control.
- To hear him wheeze like that...
- I know. It doesn't make any sense.
I do know he's a leader.
I suspect his smoking, on some level,
is an attempt to die as he lived...
...in total control.
Years ago, I asked him
to stop for me and the kids.
I lost 27 pounds.
He couldn't quit smoking?
I gotta go.
Goodbye, Caitlin.
I'll see you soon, muffin.
Oh, my God.
I love these little hands.
Thanks so much for watching her.
You'd think we're planning
a coronation instead of a christening.
- We all set?
- You know what? I'd better pee.
Oh, goody, I get to keep holding you.
So how you doing? Tony said
you got an offer on the house you built.
Two, actually, yes.
Ivana Trump.
You know, I gotta be honest.
I am very disappointed at what you did.
- What are you talking about?
- Your movie.
The boss sleeping
with the other guy's fiancée?
What?
Like that wasn't based
on Tony and Ade?
What? No.
Carmela, I didn't even write it.
"Story by Christopher Moltisanti." Isn't
that what it said up there on the screen?
Yeah, but that's just
for the Writers Guild health insurance.
- Oh, really?
- Come on, you can't be serious.
She's an Oriental, for chrissake.
- Have you heard from Ade lately?
- No. Why would I hear from her?
- Would it be so surprising?
- She left me for some other guy.
Is it any wonder? Her poor mother
is so upset, she's practically delusional.
She's convinced herself
that Ade is dead.
Her mother's an alky. You know that.
Yeah, regardless, Christopher.
You're my cousin,
and I love you, Carmela...
...but I don't like
what you're inferring here...
...either with the movie
or with how I treated Adriana.
Kelli comes out,
tell her I went to smoke.
There's my pal. How you doing?
Billy Bathgate. They had it in the library.
I thought of you.
I don't know if you heard,
but Gerry Torciano...
...he was hit last week in Brooklyn.
- Who?
- Gerry Torciano.
It was all over the news.
They whacked him in some restaurant.
Did you know him?
Yeah.
I don't know. Good guy.
It's hard to breathe.
I'll talk to Gupte...
...see if I can get him
to up the Beclovent.
I'm dying, aren't I?
It's not good. I won't lie to you.
The aggressiveness surprises me.
I gotta concur with Rosen.
I appreciate everything
you've done, Warren.
- (DOORBELL RINGING)
- (KNOCKING ON DOOR)
- Who is it?
- You don't answer your phone?
I shut the ringer.
It's the middle of the night.
Honey, what's wrong?
Nothing, sweetie,
it's fine. Go back to sleep.
It ain't fine.
We got a problem.
The whole sequence
with Sally Boy banging the fiancée...
...you gotta tell Tony
that was your idea.
- It wasn't my idea.
- What are you, fucking stupid now?
He probably thinks
I put it in to embarrass him.
- Why did you put it in there?
- It was an idea.
I don't know. Who knows
where they fucking come from?
Isaac Newton invented gravity because
some asshole hit him with an apple.
It's bad enough that I don't get credit
for my own ideas.
Now I'm supposed
to take responsibility...
...for some shit
that's gonna get me in trouble?
Fuck that, man.
Humanitas Award.
What's that?
Humanitas.
From the Paulist brothers...
...for writing themes
of socially redeeming...
Look out the window. You see
a fucking Hollywood sign out there?
Maybe you talk
to your agent like that...
...but don't ever get fucking
snippy on me again.
The fucking scary thing was
I didn't know what happened...
...till after the shot was fired.
It was fucking weird.
- Tony, hey. Gentlemen.
- Hey, how are you?
T.J. Hooker.
J.T., actually, but...
I'm looking for Chris.
I'm supposed to meet him.
What, here?
The thing is, he left me a message,
but this fucking Verizon is...
- Mind if I wait?
- Yeah, sit down.
- Diet Coke, please.
- You got it.
- So, what did you think of Cleaver?
- Oh, it's good. You know...
Congratulations.
I hope we're gonna see
some money soon.
Yeah.
As a writer, you can never tell,
you know? You come up with an idea...
...you don't know how the audience will
respond. Just because I like something...
...I think of,
doesn't mean anyone else will.
Well, that's the challenge, huh?
It is challenging sometimes,
inventing characters, how they interact.
The boss, Sally Boy, for example,
his whole persona...
...I stole that from Broderick Crawford
in Born Yesterday.
What's that?
Garson Kanin, 1950. It's terrific.
William Holden falls in love
with Crawford's girlfriend...
...played by Judy Holliday.
- The black girl, the singer.
- No, that's Billie Holiday.
Although Judy's character
in the movie is named Billie too...
...so I can see why you're confused.
I never seen it.
Why would I be confused?
Anyway, the Sally Boy character
is based on Crawford.
Sort of a big, burly guy.
The love triangle, the cuckolding
of Michael, sleeping with the fiancée...
...very similar
to the Holden-Holliday dynamic.
So the whole thing was your idea.
With apologies to Garson Kanin.
- What happened to your head?
- What?
Cabinet.
If I see Chrissy,
I'll tell him you were looking for him.
Now listen to me, you two heels.
I mean business.
I got too much at stake here.
You got something that belongs to me.
If you wanna get out of here alive, give it
back. Now, I'm no blowhard. Tell him.
He's no blowhard.
He's had people killed before.
Was about six years ago,
there was this...
Shut up! You ain't gonna be
telling nobody nothing pretty soon.
This is the image of me
he leaves to the world.
I remember when he was born,
I would hold him in my arms.
An adorable kid too.
Big eyes.
You always talk about him
more like a son.
Well, in some ways he was,
especially after his dad died.
He was little.
I used to give him rides.
I'd put him in the basket
of the butcher bike...
...and pedal him around...
...back when Satriale's
made deliveries.
I reminded him of that recently.
- He didn't remember.
- But you do.
We had fun.
All those memories, and for what?
All I am to him is some asshole bully.
You're hurt.
His dad, Dickie...
...was like my me to him.
- A mentor.
- Yeah, but more than that...
...a friend...
...a fucking guy
you could look up to.
And the hope is,
that you pass that shit down...
...the respect and the love.
And all I did for this fucking kid,
and he fucking hates me so much.
I'm sure on some level
he loves you too.
Yeah? Take that home.
Judge for yourself.
Last five minutes
should answer that question.
I'm not going to do that.
- Not a horror fan?
- It's what you think that matters.
I think he fucking despises me.
It's pretty obvious.
Wants to see me dead.
Without invalidating your feelings...
...is it possible that on some level...
...you're reading into all this?
I've been coming here for years.
I know too much
about the subconscious now.
Look, sweetie...
...they're nice and clean
like you like them.
Mommy, he can't really hear you.
They're right here by the bed.
- My...
- What, baby? Your what?
You want more morphine, Daddy?
- Mother.
- Grandma? What, Daddy?
Is he hallucinating?
- She's here.
- I don't know. He could be.
Sometimes they see
people who've passed.
John, look at me, baby.
John.
You want a cigarette, baby? John.
You can't do that
when you're on my fucking team?
Hey, Ton,
Anthony Infante to see you.
Send him in.
There he is. X-ray specs.
- How's John?
- That's why I'm here, Tony.
John passed away late this morning.
- Oh, fuck, you're kidding me.
- Shit.
I only wish.
He was a great guy, John.
Sorry for your loss.
Thanks.
Honestly, though, it was for the best.
What are you gonna do?
I beat cancer,
but it took him out.
Ride the painted pony,
let the spinning wheel glide.
John Sacrimoni, a buon' anima.
A buon' anima, Johnny Sack.
We're here to celebrate
what would have been my brother's...
...your uncle's, 47th birthday.
Blow it out for him.
(BLOWING)
(CHEERING)
Right here at this bar, this seat...
...was Uncle Billy's favorite place
in the whole world.
- More than Shea Stadium?
- More than Shea Stadium.
He'd sit with his friends
and tell stories about his family...
...who he loved more than anything
and was so very proud of.
From now on,
his ashes will be right here...
...so when his friends come to visit,
he can see them.
- Can he see us now?
- Yeah.
- Who knows who is Leonardo da Vinci?
- I do.
- Matty.
- Yeah, he wrote The Da Vinci Code.
- No.
- Another man wrote that...
...but it's a hideous,
sacrilegious book.
- Annabella.
- He was a painter of the Mona Lisa.
Very good. He was not only a painter,
he did medical drawings...
...and he designed a tank
for the army.
Leonardo was a great Italian, and that
was our name originally, Leonardo.
But many years ago, when my grandpa
came over from Sicily...
...they changed it at Ellis Island
to Leotardo.
What did they do that for?
Because they're stupid,
that's why, and jealous.
They disrespected
a proud Italian heritage...
...and named us
after a ballet costume.
- Marissa.
- That's for modern.
- In ballet, you wear tutus.
- It doesn't make a difference.
- That's right, it doesn't.
- Can we have cake now?
How you doing, Phil? You okay?
Forty-seven. He was a fucking kid.
Me, I'm an old man.
I'd like to do it over.
Boy, let me tell you.
I fucking compromised everything.
No, what are you talking about?
Twenty years inside,
not a fucking peep.
For what?
To protect the likes
of Rusty fucking Millio, Doc Santoro?
You were a man, Phil.
That's saying a lot nowadays.
That cocksucking piece of shit,
Tony Soprano's cousin...
I can't even say his name.
Murdered Billie.
And what did I do about it?
My weakness.
Sometimes I think
it's in my DNA.
My family took shit from the medigans
the minute we got off the boat.
Come on. What the fuck
are you talking about?
Leotardo.
That's my fucking legacy.
No more, Butchie.
No more of this.
(MUSIC PLAYING)