I am
on a lecture circuit.
I'm going around
to all the branches,
and I am telling them my
secret recipe for success.
I have now memorized
all of your names.
Shirty, mole, lazy
eye, Mexico, baldy.
Hi, Kelly.
Screw you.
Excuse me.
Screw you, too.
You forgot her birthday.
...and I turn
it on and I say,
"Prepare yourself for the
Utica Chain Store Massacre."
How's Jim?
We're engaged.
Oh, my God.
I'm so happy for you.
Wow. Thank you.
"Kelly Kapoor spent April 1995 to December
1996 at Berks County Youth Center."
Juvie.
You remember Holly?
She used to work for HR.
She was the love of my life.
She just left and
I never got closure.
And I feel like I need to go
to Nashua and get closure.
Okay. Let's go.
Two.
I didn't eat lunch.
I didn't eat
all my lunch.
Hello, everyone.
Ice cream. Nice, Kevin.
Looks good.
It... Yeah.
Angela, you're more
chipper than usual.
I am proud to announce that there is
a new addition to the Martin family.
She's hypo-allergenic, she doesn't
struggle when you try to dress her,
she's a third-generation
show cat.
Her father was in
Meet the Parents.
Needless to say, she's
very, very expensive.
How much?
$7,000.
For a cat? I can get
you a kid for that.
Where did you get
that kind of money?
I sold Andy's engagement
ring on eBay.
Wait, you didn't
give it back?
He wouldn't
have wanted that.
Her name is Princess Lady.
Seven grand. I've got to
see that little bitch.
I have something better than a picture.
Come on.
You have your
cats on Nanny Cam.
Yeah. I mean, I usually try to
take leave when I get a new cat,
but I'm out of
vacation days,
and this company still doesn't
recognize cat maternity.
I mean, somebody has a kid,
oh, sure, take off a year.
She's right. I had my second
kid just for the vacation.
Right. Anyways,
I just want to make sure
Princess Lady is
acclimating well.
She means more
to me than anyone.
Any cat, you mean.
And person.
So, detour. We're now adding
Nashua to the lecture circuit,
so Michael can confront Holly
and get some closure.
Nashua actually sounded
very excited on the phone.
I don't think they get
a lot of visitors.
Because their office is only
accessible by cross-country skis.
I've been driving too long.
- What did you do?
- Stop yelling at me!
What did you do?
I didn't do anything.
What did you
learn in there?
I'll bet you
learned things, huh?
Like how to
fashion a shiv.
Hey, what the
hell's going on?
Why don't you tell Jim where
you were from ages 14 to 15?
I was kicking it.
In juvie.
What?
Juvie-nile detention center.
Where they send teenagers.
Yep.
For re...
Got it.
What did you do, huh?
Hey, Dwight,
sounds like she was 14,
so maybe we want
to go a little easy.
If she's old enough
to get married,
she's old enough
to follow the law.
What did you do?
My boyfriend dumped me,
so I stole his boat.
He told me it was his boat.
It was actually his father's.
I just thought it'd
be really romantic,
like Thelma & Louise,
but with, like, a boat.
And it was the worst
year of my life.
And I can't believe
that you guys are
making me talk about
this on my birthday.
I thought you said
yesterday was your birthday.
Hey, you know what?
I got you a cake.
You did?
I want to see the cake.
And, ta-dah.
I hate it.
How do you hate it?
It's a cake.
Well, there's no
flowers or toys or...
I mean,
there's nothing on it.
Where did you even
find a cake like this?
It doesn't even
have my name on it.
Do you guys know
what my name is?
My name is Kelly.
Right.
I forgot if there was an "E"
between the "L" and the "Y."
I still don't know.
I don't even know what the theme is!
What's the theme?
It's birthday.
Frosting.
Those aren't themes.
There's always a theme.
Nice job on
the cake, bozo.
Okay, you know what? Next time,
I'll let you get the cake
and I get to scream
at the birthday girl.
Okay, a little bit
more closer to the sign.
Yeah.
Do I look okay?
You look good.
Hi.
Hi, can I help you?
Yes, you can.
I am Michael Scott,
Regional Manager of
the Scranton Branch.
Yes, we were expecting you.
Have a seat.
Thank you.
Um...
Is Holly Flax
anywhere here?
Actually, she's on an HR retreat
for the next three days.
She's not here?
But if you need to get in
touch with her immediately,
you could talk to A.J.
He's a salesman here.
A.J.
Yeah, he's her boyfriend.
He's just over there.
She has a boyfriend.
I'm so sorry, Michael.
How could she do
this to me, Pam?
She's not doing
it to hurt you.
I can't do the
presentation, I can't.
Just thinking
about seeing him,
and thinking about him
getting to hold her
and getting to kiss
her is just... Oh, God.
Listen, when Jim
was dating Karen,
I didn't want
to come to work.
It was awful,
I hated it.
I wanted to quit, but...
Just, please, come on.
I'm going through
something, okay?
You know,
when Holly gets back,
everyone will tell her
what a great job you did.
And then she'll realize
what she's missing.
And then she'll move back to Scranton,
and her boyfriend will die.
Yeah, maybe. Maybe.
One step at a time.
You can do this.
I can do this.
It could be snacks or...
But why would we...
Is that what
I think it is?
Good God!
That one ugly cat is
humping Princess Lady.
- No!
- Awesome.
Stop it, Mr. Ash!
Bad cat, that is very bad.
You stop it right now.
I swear he is fixed.
I know fixed, that ain't fixed.
No way.
No, now listen,
you can't let what you see
here sully your
image of them.
They are good,
decent cats.
I got to go.
I'll be back in an hour.
Oh, stop that!
The other one's watching.
Okay, so all we need
is a theme.
And cups, and ice,
and punch, and a cake.
Busy.
Hey, what's that show that
she's always talking about?
Is this how
you are with Pam?
Because she must want to
shoot herself in the face.
You know what?
I could use a little help.
I'm a little busy.
We have a lot to do,
and you are
putting up a very
effeminate sign.
Is that what you've been doing?
Making a sign?
It's not effeminate.
It's festive.
You've been
making that sign
for something that we could just
announce to the whole office?
Hey, everybody,
the party's now at 3:00!
I know, I just read
it on the sign.
Good morning,
Viet-Nashua!
Sales. Sales is what
brings us together today.
How do we deal
with clients who say,
"Frankly, my dear, I don't
give a damn about paper,"
and get them to
show us the money?
Well, we are going
to find out today.
Show of hands, how many
of you are salesmen?
Let's see the salesmen.
Oh, okay. Well, I know what
the rest of you are thinking.
"Wow, yuck, salesmen are
the worst, they are awful.
"They are so arrogant. They think the
whole place revolves around them.
"Handsome, good listeners, funny.
Mr. Wonderful."
So, okay, you're a salesman,
what's your name?
A.J.
A.J. What kind of name is A.J.?
What, do you race cars?
I'm a salesman, that's
why I raised my hand.
Ouch. Okay. Good.
You're funny,
very good and funny.
Tell me, A.J., are you dating?
Is there somebody you date?
Yeah. Why,
you interested?
I have a question about
discounts from distributors.
Yep, we will get to you.
Okay, so you're
dating somebody.
Um...
Is it serious?
It's pretty serious. Yes.
Does she ever
talk about me?
Oh, God.
Excuse me?
What does this
have to do with sales?
It's all connected,
shut up.
Does she ever
mention Michael Scott?
No. What are you
talking about?
Does it feel good?
Does what feel good?
Your life. Oh, wow.
My legs are
sort of giving out.
Long drive in the car,
so let me...
...just continue.
Oh, wow. Okay.
Michael, get off the floor.
Yeah, yeah,
I can't do this, Pam.
Just read the cards.
No, no, no.
Michael, you have to do it.
No, I'm okay.
I'm all right.
Okay. Okay.
That was weird, huh?
It's all part of
the presentation.
It was confusing, right?
Because confusing situations happen
to us all the time in our jobs.
I'm just trying to bridge the
gap between what just happened
and the fact that I'm going to be
doing the rest of the presentation.
Sales is like a box
of chocolates.
You never know which
vendor you're gonna get.
Forrest Gump.
Blazer, freckles, penguin,
K. D. Lang,
Holly's boyfriend.
These mnemonic devices
help to make a connection,
and then also to
help you memorize names.
I have a chainsaw!
Cutting down
the competition.
- Where is that bad cat?
- You know who you are.
Excuse me, Petals,
I'm looking for Mr. Ash.
He's a bad cat.
Bad, bad cat.
Do you hear me?
Bad. You are bad.
No, you look at me
when I talk to you.
Do you hear me,
Mr. Ash? Look at me.
This is getting weird.
Is she cleaning the cat
with her tongue?
Has this been on
the entire time?
I have no idea.
I was looking at pictures
of food on my computer.
Well, sorry I'm late.
I want to get
that image out of my head.
The psychological issues
that go behind licking a cat
are not things
I want to go into.
Also, I'm pretty sure
she coughed up a hairball.
Don't look up.
Want some pie?
No.
I went through Holly's things.
What?
I stole a sleeve
of her sweater.
Oh, Michael.
I also stole something
off of her computer.
A document called "Dear
Michael." You did what?
I shouldn't have done it. It just...
I couldn't help it.
She never sent it to you?
No, she didn't.
I'm going to read it.
No.
Yes.
No, under no circumstances
can you read that letter.
It's a violation
of her trust.
How?
Because she didn't send it to you.
I know, I know.
You're right, you're right.
I could read it.
No, I wouldn't...
Yeah, I could read it.
No, you don't
have to do that.
Go get your laptop.
Okay.
What? I'm not
in love with her.
You have to write
my suggestions down, too.
I'm not writing "horse hunt." I
don't even know what that means.
It's in the name.
Okay, so far, our ideal party consists
of beer, fights to the death,
cupcakes, blood pudding,
blood, touch football,
mating, charades and,
yes, horse hunting.
You're right. Forget horse hunting.
It's stupid.
Look, is there a birthday that
you remember that you loved?
Here's one.
It was dark, warm, wet.
A sudden burst of light, an intense
pressure like I'd never felt before.
Father dressed in white pulls me
forward, mother bites the cord.
Okay, stop.
Forever stop that story.
That's disgusting and it doesn't count.
So give me another one.
Schrutes don't
celebrate birthdays, idiot.
It started as a
Depression-era practicality
and then moved on to
an awesome tradition
that I look
forward to every year.
What about you?
Actually, when I was
seven, my dad took me
to the Natural History
Museum in New York,
and we looked at
fossils all day.
And at the end of the day, he got
me a little plastic triceratops.
It was awesome.
That's cool. Hey, you know what's
even cooler than triceratops?
Every other dinosaur
that ever existed.
Didn't see
that one coming.
It's deleted.
She still has
feelings for you.
She said that?
Is that what it said?
What did it say?
I can't tell
you specifically,
but it's not over.
You're sure?
Okay.
Happy birthday.
Surprise.
It's... Hey, hey,
it's not a surprise.
This doesn't look good.
What? You have a cake.
You have a delicious cake with
your name spelled correctly?
I told you. You haven't
heard our theme, though.
You don't hear a theme.
You see it.
Why is there
a Chiclet on my cake?
That's the best part. That represents
a pillow. Or a television.
Our theme, if you will.
Because the fun part
is you get to decide
on an hour of television
or an hour of napping.
That's our theme.
Cool.
Yeah?
I love it.
Oh, yes! Okay, good.
So what's it
going to be, Kapoor?
Can she pick
a half hour of each?
No.
Then pick TV.
- Pick a nap.
- No, no. TV.
Watching TV at
work is really cool.
Pick a nap. Nothing
good is on right now.
Bonnie Hunt is on.
You know what? I have been
watching TV all week.
I choose nap.
All right.
Okay, nap it is.
Everyone out! Get out.
We're going to be
eating cake at our desks.
Let's go. Move it.
Let's go, go, go, go, go, come on.
I got this.
This is for you.
And happy birthday, Kell.
Thank you.
Okay. You've got one hour.
I'm too excited to sleep.
Mmm.
Great cake.
Thanks.
Birthday time is over.
Now go make up for
all the work you missed
when you were
taking your nap.
Many happy returns.
I feel great.
So good to have closure.
We should go apologize
to Roy or something.
No. We don't
need to do that.
Who have I wronged?
Oh! Oh!
What about that fat guy from
Stamford that I insulted?
We should find him.
You mean Tony.
Jabba the Hutt,
Pizza the Hut.
Fat guys like pizza, pepperoni
pizza, Pepperoni Tony.
Oh, Michael.
Man, was he fat.
So, so fat.
You know what?
Forget it.
I know me. When I saw him I would
never be able to apologize to him.
Too fat. Big, fat fatty.