- Previously, on From...
- There's darkness in the forest.
Nightmares you can't even
begin to imagine.
- Anghkooey!
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no. Don't touch me.
Don't touch me.
- Hey! Hey! You okay?
- Did you see them?
- See what? See who?
- What the fuck?
Eloise said that's where
my mother went that night.
The night that bad things happened,
she went to save
the children locked in the tower.
- This mean a lot to you?
- Please.
Yeah? Fuck you.
You ever come near my mom again,
I will drag your fucking psycho ass
into that box myself.
We pulled something out of that thing.
Only problem is
we gotta figure out how to get this
inside another one of those things
without getting ourselves killed.
Make some silver bullets.
You think this place
is one big experiment, right?
And it never occurred to you that some
of the people here might be in on it?
I mean, they'd have to be. How else
do you keep the experiment on track?
- Randall, what the fuck?
- New plan.
Elgin had a dream that he was drowning
and then he started spitting up water,
- and you had cicadas in your dreams, and...
- When the music box started playing,
one of them jumped out
and it burned my arm.
Are you honestly saying that
our fucking dreams can hurt us now?
Do you hear that?
Help me!
Please. Please, I need help.
She said...
she said she was gonna take a nap.
I was downstairs.
And I heard her screaming.
I came in, I started shaking her and...
trying to wake her up, and she kept...
She was talking in her sleep.
Saying something over and over.
And then she...
Something cracked inside her, and her body
and her face...
God. Jesus.
What did she say?
What?
You said she was talking.
What did she say?
I... I don't... I...
- Hey, Reggie.
- I can't... No.
Reggie, hey. Listen, Reggie.
I need you to tell me what she said.
Okay.
It was...
"They touch, they break...
they steal."
"No one here is free."
And then she just...
Her face just fucking...
And was she still asleep?
Are you sure she was asleep?
- Yes, I'm fucking sure!
- Okay, okay. I...
Okay.
Okay. We need to...
Yeah. Okay. Okay. Okay.
- Is everything all right?
- Oh, yeah,
little man, everything's great.
Hey, do me a favor.
Do you mind heading home for me, okay?
And do you mind
if your sister stays here for a bit?
Thanks, bud.
Yeah, go on home.
I'll be right behind you.
Okay.
Later.
- We go, you come help make dinner.
- All right.
Kenny.
Listen, we gotta...
we gotta tell the people door-to-door.
Okay, we got 30 minutes left of daylight.
You and Julie cover the town,
I'll go to Colony House.
Reggie will come with me.
We can't leave anyone alone.
What about Sara?
Boyd, what's going on?
What happened in there?
Something killed Paula.
But it's not dark yet. I don't...
There's something else here now.
Something new.
It's not safe for anyone
to go to sleep tonight. Okay?
My dad, he's out at the RV.
Okay.
- Randall. What the fuck?
- It's a new plan.
- I'm gonna fucking kill you.
- Oh, yeah?
What are you doing?
- Donna, I'm so sorry.
- Don't apologize to her.
We were right. She's fucking part of this.
Part of what?
I saw you. Up at the clinic.
Yeah. That's right, I followed you.
They were carrying
one of their "monsters" out of the clinic.
What are they? Some kind of animatronic?
You got a faulty model, huh?
- That was a body, you dumb shit.
- Okay.
Boyd killed one of them.
- He what?
- He killed one of the monsters.
So now they can fucking die?
It's funny how suddenly
the rules fucking change
- once someone catches out your bullshit.
- Are you fucking kidding me?
I thought you'd be more...
This was your idea.
No. This?
This... this is fucking crazy.
This was not part of the plan.
She's part of the reason we're still here.
- Fuck her!
- We are not doing this.
You know what I'm startin' to think, Jim?
Maybe you just put this shit
in my head to see what I would do.
How do I know
that you're not part of this, huh?
'Cause my house collapsed on top of me.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
- Jim.
- You wanna dance, Jim?
Drop the fucking knife.
You gonna shoot me?
Okay.
Now, stand over there.
You all right, Jim?
I'm so sorry,
this wasn't supposed to happen.
- Get her.
- Just get me off this fuckin' tree.
We got about five minutes
to get in that van
and get back to town. Who's got the key?
- I don't know.
- Jim.
You mean these keys?
- Hey, don't...
- Hey...
- Oh, fuck.
- Are you outta your goddamn mind?
Guess we're gonna have to stay
the night and see what happens, huh?
Julie, come back inside, honey.
I shouldn't have let him go,
I should've stopped him.
- He's gonna be okay.
- Hey!
The hell's goin' on?
Victor says we can't go to sleep.
Julie, come inside, honey. Come on.
We can't just leave him out there.
Can we go get him?
No, no. Mom's right. Dad's gonna be fine.
- We just... We need to stay inside.
- Yeah.
- I wanna get Dad.
- Hey.
Boyd isn't gonna let
anything happen to your father.
The best thing
we can do for Dad is to be safe.
Thank you for doing this.
I know you don't wanna be here.
I'm not doing it for you.
Things here feel different now.
They feel wrong.
It felt that way out in the forest.
Did Boyd ever tell you
what happened out there?
The further we went out,
the more it felt like...
Boyd said it was like this place feeds
on our pain.
But what if it does more than that?
What do you mean?
Nathan was always terrified of cicadas.
When we were kids, our stepfather
would take us
on these week-long camping trips.
And all night long,
the cicadas would buzz outside our tent.
Nathan would cry the whole night.
He thought they were monsters.
What if the people who die here...
What if their fears
become part of the forest?
What if that really is
Nathan's nightmare out there?
- He's in here.
- Tell me what happened.
She... she went to sleep
and something... broke her.
Where's Donna?
I'm supposed to talk to Donna.
- Donna's not here right now.
- She left the clinic hours ago.
- Did she say where she was going?
- Yeah, she said she was coming here.
We're all gonna fuckin' die.
No, hey, Reggie. Look at me. Listen.
You need to tell me
exactly what Boyd said.
We can't go to sleep.
No one goes to sleep.
Okay, okay, great.
Then that's what we focus on.
Yeah? Wherever Donna is,
she and Boyd are gonna figure this out.
So how about right now,
we just focus on doing our part, yeah?
How about you and I
go get you a change of clothes,
and everybody partner up.
Make sure nobody falls asleep, yeah?
Yeah, for how long?
We'll figure that out
when we get to it, yeah?
Hey, Elgin, partner up.
Come on, guys, let's go.
- You guys doing okay?
- Is there maybe a room we could use?
Yeah, yeah.
- Thanks.
- Come on.
Hey, come on.
- You okay?
- Come on, we'll get you upstairs.
What do you mean we can't go to sleep?
Jim, why the hell do you think
I'm out here? Your daughter is terrified.
Just put that over there for me, please.
Okay.
Are you fuckin' kidding me?
Pick a lane, Jim.
Don't you see what this is?
- Not now.
- We come out here,
we actually have them by the balls,
and Sheriff fuckin' DoReady
comes out here with a new story
and you're just like...
No wonder your family's a fuckin' mess.
- Son of a...
- Hey, hey, hey, hey!
- What...
- Jim!
Hey, hey, hey! What the...
Fuck!
Hold on, hold on. Now hold on. Yeah, yeah.
I am only gonna say this one time, okay?
Whatever stupid fuckin' ideas
you got locked
in that rock-hard head of yours,
they are gonna get you killed.
Or worse off,
they're gonna get one of us killed.
And I'm not planning
on dying here tonight.
Shut the fuck up and sit down.
Yes, sir.
And you.
After all the shit
you've been through here, huh?
- You still think this is a fuckin' game?
- I was trying to...
It wasn't supposed to happen this way.
So you led a pig to shit and now
you're surprised he made a mess?
Hey, fuck you.
Fuck you.
I've gotta get back to my family.
- Yeah.
- These old vans,
they've got a pretty basic
ignition system even without the keys,
I think I can probably...
Hey, I'm not gonna lose another person
to "probably," you got me?
We are barely making it through right now,
do you understand what I'm saying?
Hey, I said sit down.
I'm not listening
to this shit all fuckin' night. Okay?
Sit down.
All right. I don't know what your deal is,
whether you're part of this,
or you're just fuckin' dumber than...
I lost my wife here.
My friend bled to death in my arms,
and you still think I'm lyin'?
You want proof? What if I tie your ass up
to one of those trees out there?
Let you find out for yourself.
This the freaky sex room?
First night's rough for some people.
It can get unpredictable.
I'm gonna go grab a few supplies, okay?
You're gonna be okay for a minute?
- Give me a hand?
- Yeah.
- She looks pretty rough.
- Yeah, tonight's gonna be the hardest.
I'm gonna need a pot, washcloth,
and probably some extra linens.
Yeah. Yeah, of course.
All right, look,
I don't really know how to ask this,
but this whole thing about not sleeping,
I mean, do we need to be worried?
About the baby, I mean,
they sleep in there, right?
I mean, if she were further along,
then yeah, maybe.
- But she's six, maybe seven weeks at most.
- Okay.
Look, of all things
we need to worry about tonight,
I promise you that's not one of them.
I mean, yeah, you know...
It's just weird, you know, it's like...
I just... there's a person
growing inside of my fiancée.
And anywhere else in the world,
I mean, that would be great.
You know, I would be thrilled, which I am.
But here, you know, I just...
I just keep expecting
that at any second
it's gonna come bursting out of her
with, like, with fangs,
- and claws.
- If it's any consolation,
pregnancy's weird,
no matter where you are.
I mean, it's beautiful,
but it's fucking weird.
We're just used to it
because we see it every day.
It's like the magic ball of fire.
The what?
It's this thing from med school.
The whole world. Even the parts
that we think we understand,
it's all really just one big mystery.
Floating through space
around a giant ball of magic fire
that keeps us warm
from a million miles away. I mean, it's...
it's fucking insane.
We're just used to it, that's all.
Pregnancy's weird.
I can't believe he had a sister.
How do you forget something like that?
I don't know, but you should've seen
his face when we opened the trunk.
It was awful.
Here. Look at this.
See this one.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, see the color of those uniforms.
These are civil war soldiers.
And why the fuck
would a little girl draw pictures of...
Wait. No, the pictures came from
the stories his mother used to tell.
All right, then why the fuck am I having
visions of a story some dead woman told
forty years ago?
Do you wanna see something really weird?
Look at this.
So Victor said his mother wanted
to rescue the children that were locked
in the tower.
That it was the only way
to get everyone home.
Since I got here, I've had dreams
about walking up
the steps of a tower just like this.
I mean, all this time I thought
the children were trying to scare me,
but what if
they're just asking for my help?
Okay, everyone come. Sit.
Hey, Ethan. Away from the window.
What are we doing?
We play. Feel better.
Yeah. I mean, if we can't go to sleep,
might as well have some fun.
Right?
Is my dad gonna die?
What? No. No, Dad is gonna be fine.
Are we gonna die?
No, no one is gonna die.
When Victor was little, everyone died.
- All at the same time.
- It won't happen like that again.
How do you know?
Look, I know
things are really scary right now,
but remember what the Cromenockle
would do when she got scared?
- She would always say...
- It doesn't matter!
She's not real!
Doesn't matter what she did.
It's just a stupid story.
My mother used to say
that everything is a story.
And we're the ones
who get to decide how it ends.
What about her story?
Did it end the way she wanted?
Ethan!
- Be good.
- I don't wanna play any games.
I'm so sorry.
So whatever was in your blood
that killed the creature,
- that creature's blood is...
- Bile.
- The what?
- It doesn't matter.
The point is, if it works,
- we're all walking back to town.
- And if it doesn't?
What do you care?
None of it's real, right?
- Why don't you let him do it?
- What?
He's not afraid to go outside,
so give him your gun,
see if these monster killers really work.
One way or another,
we get rid of the problem.
But make up your mind. They're coming.
- How many are there?
- I can see a few.
- Are they close?
- They're getting a lot fucking closer.
All right.
Showtime.
Hey, wait.
You're not gonna let him do this, are you?
He's a big boy. He can choose.
They're over here too.
Boyd.
It's gotta be now. You going or not?
All right.
If you have any second thoughts...
you better get your ass right back here.
- What the fuck?
- Hold on. What's goin' on?
- They've stopped.
- They stopped here too.
What?
Something's wrong.
They don't just do that.
- Do what?
- They don't just stop like that.
Fuck's sake, you people are just crazy.
Hey...
Oh, no, no. no.
Get the fuck away from me!
No, Mari, no. What are you doing?
- We have to get out of here.
- Stop.
- We have to go right now.
No, you don't understand.
There's something in here.
- It's just me.
- There's something in the room.
- It's just me and you, okay?
- No.
- There's nothing in here.
- It was a...
You told me once
that when you first went through this,
you saw a lot of things
that weren't there.
There was a guy downstairs.
He said that... that we...
He said that we can't go to sleep,
and that's all.
We know what the monsters look like here,
and they're all outside.
As long as you're in here
and you're awake, you're safe, okay?
- Now, please...
- Don't touch me.
- Mari.
- Don't fucking touch me!
Okay. I'm sorry.
You're sorry? Yeah. This is your fault.
You fucking... You disappeared.
I couldn't eat. I couldn't sleep.
You fucking did this to me. You fucking...
I'm sorry.
- I didn't... I'm sorry.
- It's okay. I'm fine.
- We're okay.
- No!
No, we are not fine. We are not okay.
Just... Fuck!
I don't wanna be this.
- I don't wanna be this.
- Hey. Hey.
Come here.
I'm right here, okay?
- You're okay. I'm right here.
- I'm sorry.
You're doing great, okay?
Come here.
We should put these on.
I don't think you have to do that.
Yes, I do.
Guess that one is mine.
Which one is yours?
Your mom once told me how grateful she was
that you were all together when you...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I shouldn't have said that.
I...
I never really had the chance to...
I just want you to know that I'm sorry.
And I... I know...
I know it doesn't mean anything,
but if I could go back and...
and change what happened,
- I... I would.
- Stop.
I know...
it's painful for you...
seeing me every day.
For you.
- For your mom.
- Okay.
I told Boyd I wanted
to go back out in the forest,
that way, maybe, I could still help,
and he wouldn't have to...
I don't care!
All right? I don't care.
I don't give a shit what you want,
what you feel.
You don't get to sit here
and have a pity party.
Because you're a murderer.
You're a murderer and you...
should have gone in the box the second
that Boyd found out what you did.
I know what I've done.
I can never...
I'll never be able to take it back.
I've ruined people's lives.
What I did to you.
- Yeah, you do.
- To your mom.
- No. No.
- You guys were like family to me.
- And your dad...
- Shut the fuck up!
Shut the fuck up!
Don't fucking talk about my dad!
No.
- Excuse me?
- I said no.
I didn't ask for any of this.
You think you're the only one
who lost something?
I've lost everything!
Everything I was,
and everything I could have been is gone.
This place destroyed
the only person I ever get to be,
and I'm tired.
I'm tired of being afraid,
and I am tired of being ashamed.
I don't want to be here anymore. I don't...
I don't want to be your monster anymore.
I just want it to be over.
Okay. Okay, you want out?
Boyd keeps a spare gun
in the top left-hand drawer.
Do what the fuck you wanna do.
Wake up! Wake up!
You can't go to sleep.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Are you listening to me?
The talisman will not protect you.
There is nowhere that you are safe!
- Reggie, stop! You're scaring everyone.
- They should be scared!
You didn't see.
- You don't understand what happens.
- Just take a second.
Hey, get...
Are you okay?
- Hey!
- Hey, you okay?
- Get off of me! Get off of me!
- Hey, hey. Calm down!
Hey, look at me. Stop. Breathe. Breathe.
- It's okay, it's okay.
- She was... She was my...
- I know, it's okay. It's all right.
- We're gonna die tonight.
- Tomorrow, every one of you is gonna die!
- Get him upstairs.
- Get him upstairs. Go.
- Get him out of here now!
- Hey, calm down.
- You don't understand.
- Stop! Let go of me, please! Stop!
- It's okay.
The thing,
it's in fucking pieces. How is it?
What are they waiting for?
- What are you doing?
- I gotta go outside
- and see if this thing works.
- No, Boyd. You can't!
Listen to me!
I've heard this music before, Donna.
And every time it plays, bad shit follows.
We gotta get the fuck out of here, okay?
- Oh, shit.
- Jesus!
- What the fuck!
- Fuck!
Fuck this, man.
There is no way, there's no space up here.
Hey, Jim, Jim, Jim.
- Hey, come here, come here. Come, come!
- What?
- Come here. Come, come here.
- Whatever happens, be ready to run.
- Okay.
No, fuck this. Fuck this. Fuck this.
- Hey! Hey!
- Hey!
Donna, move. Move.
Okay. Donna.
Hey, if you wanna see your family again,
- you get that fuckin' thing and go, okay?
- I got it.
Go! Go!
Boyd.
Shit.
Come back to me.
Boyd, come on!
Jesus Christ. What the fuck?
Help me! Help me!
Put that away.
Why?
It's what everyone wants.
Isn't it?
You were the one
who said I belonged in the box.
That's different.
How?
Put the fucking gun away.
If I was in the box...
it would be out of your hands.
It wouldn't be you killing me,
it would be this place.
I don't want to cause you anymore pain.
So we'll pretend that we're in the box.
And we'll let this place decide.
What the fuck are you talking about?
How many should we use?
One?
Sara.
Two?
- Hey. All right. Okay, hey, knock it off.
- Okay.
- Just two.
- Hey, that's enough.
Okay, hey, hey, hey.
No.
You don't get to decide.
Sara, it's okay.
Hey, Sara, stop!
Hey!
What the fuck is wrong with you?
- Yeah, so this is where you can hold...
- Okay.
- Hey.
- And you can tell 'cause it's...
- You doing okay?
- ...all taut and tight like that.
So you take... Just hold what you want.
You see, it's right there
Hey, how you guys doing?
- He's teaching me how to crochet.
- You are?
- Yeah.
- Good. Keeping her up?
You're doing a great job, you know?
The way you handled everything tonight.
You're gonna be a great mom.
You're pregnant?
Yeah.
- How did you know?
- Sweetie,
I've had four kids
and seven grandchildren.
I know an expecting mother when I see one.
Hey.
Hey, what's wrong?
I just remembered my dream.
Donna's back.
- Stop.
- It'll help.
I'm thirsty.
I'll go get you some juice, okay?
Don't go.
I'll be right back, okay?
No.
It's not real. No! No!
No! No! No! Kristi! Kristi!
Kristi!
Get them off me! They're all over me.
- They're everywhere. I can't...
- There's...
there's... there's nothing on you.
I don't see anything.
Okay, just...
Just breathe, just breathe, baby.
Breathe in. Just breathe, just breathe.
I know, everybody, listen,
I understand. I...
How long do we have to stay awake?
- Yeah. What the fuck?
- If I... If...
- Why is this happening?
- Everybody just calm down,
all right? Just calm down.
We know you're scared.
We are trying to figure this out.
But the best thing you can do right now
- is just hang tight and do what Boyd...
- Get out of my way, okay?
- Hey, Jim!
- I gotta get back to my family, okay?
Listen to me. Every time that door opens,
it puts everybody here at risk.
When the fuck are we not at risk?
Hey! Stand down! Stand down!
- I need help up here.
- Fuck, that fucking door stays closed!
- Fuck!
- Mari!
Fuck.
He goes fucking nowhere. Get back.
- Come on, we gotta figure this out.
- Okay.
Marielle. Hey. Hey, hey.
- Marielle. Marielle.
- Hey, what happened?
I just left for a second. What the fuck
is wrong with her eyeballs? Look.
Marielle.
- Boyd, what the fuck is going on?
- Okay, okay, okay.
Just do something. Do something!
Boyd, do something!
No, hey, hey. Kristi, Kristi. No, no.
No, no, buddy, buddy.
Look at me. Hey, hey. Look at me.
Look at me, look at me.
She doesn't need her fiancé right now.
She needs a doctor. Okay?
So, calm down. All right?
And do your job, okay?
How? There's... there's nothing
medically I can do for her. I don't...
- I don't know how to help her.
- I know, hey.
I don't know how to help her.
- You can help her.
- Just fuck off, please.
Okay, hey, everybody. Clear out.
- Get the fuck out of here.
- Let's go. Give 'em space.
Listen to me. Hey, hey.
You help her by holding on,
do you understand?
She's still breathing. She's still here.
- You gotta calm down...
- Dad.
...get your shit together, and hold on.
- Not now.
Look, I think you need to hear this.
- Hey.
- I got this, go.
This whole time,
I felt like there was something that...
Like there was a reason
why I had that dream on the bus.
Like there was something
I was supposed to remember.
And I don't know but when Fatima said
she was pregnant, it all...
- I'm sorry.
- All right.
No, no, it's okay.
- I didn't... Yeah.
- About the dream.
There was this boy...
all dressed in white and...
he kept repeating
the same phrase, over and over.
"Here they come, they come for three,
unless you stop the melody."
Oh, wait. I know that one.
It's an old nursery rhyme.
My grandmother used to sing it to me.
They come... No.
They touch, they break, they steal
No one here is free
Here they come, they come for three
Unless you stop the melody
You realize what you're saying
sounds completely batfuck crazy?
Well, you were the one
that said everything's connected.
This. This is a connection.
What if Victor's mom is right?
What if saving those children
is how we all go home?
Get them off me!
Mom!
What's wrong? Julie! Julie, Julie! Stop!
- What's wrong with her?
- Julie, Julie. Julie, stop that!
- Oh, my god. Stop. What's wrong?
- Julie!
- What happened?
- Mom.
- Talk to me, sweetie, please.
- Get them off me!
- I can't, I can't.
Julie. Julie.