Previously on From...
I hear their voices.
They said it was
the only way to go home!
Sara, just tell me
what you did.
I left the door open.
I saw something
that wasn't there.
- What?
- I saw two children
standing in the middle
of the road, staring at me.
Is this Jim?
I am not saying
ignore it.
You already got people's hopes
up with your goddamn tower.
All the more
reason that we--
To keep our fucking
mouths shut.
What's
about to happen,
it's gonna
save everyone.
Where's my mom?
I want my mom!
Ethan, run!
Nathan, please!
I spent the entire night
with her,
and that scalpel she used,
she took it from my clinic.
This is not your fault.
How exactly
are you gonna tell Kenny
that Sara killed his dad?
I did what I had to do!
She was valuable!
She-- she may
still be valuable!
They tore him to pieces,
and you knew!
Kenny, please.
You watch your
own fucking six.
There's a symbol
that I keep seeing.
Look at this.
Look. This guy...
he must have been
seeing it, too.
That's you, right?
This could be the key to
getting the hell out of here.
Stay away from me!
Welcome to
your new home.
Hop on up.
Every night,
those things come.
There really
is no way out.
Hi. Are you
comfortable in there?
You think this is scary?
Huh?
Hiya.
You think
this is scary?
What am I
supposed to be?
Huh? Am I supposed to
be pissing myself? Huh?
Heh. Well, you
can't get in here,
'cause there's a fucking rock
in the fucking window!
Yeah. Yeah, that's real
fucking scary.
I'm not afraid
of you.
You understand me?
See ya.
Where you goin'?
Hey!
Huh? Hey!
Huh?
I'm fucking talking to you.
Don't fucking
walk away from me.
You don't fucking walk
away from me!
Oh, God. That motherfucking...
" plays]
♪ When I was just a little boy ♪
♪ I asked my father ♪
♪ "What will I be?" ♪
♪ "Will I be handsome?" ♪
♪ "Will I be rich?" ♪
♪ Here's what he said to me ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ Whatever will be will be ♪
♪ The future's not ours to see ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ What will be will be ♪
♪ Now I have
children of my own♪
♪ They ask their father ♪
♪ "What will I be?" ♪
♪ "Will I be pretty?" ♪
♪ "Will I be rich?" ♪
♪ I tell them tenderly ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ Whatever will be will be ♪
♪ The future's not ours to see ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ What will be will be ♪
Boyd!
Hey! You get
back downstairs.
Stay out of sight.
I'll handle this.
Go!
Coming.
- Where is she?
- Hey, hey, look.
Hey, hey, can
we just calm down?
- Calm down.
- Calm down?
Are you fucking
serious?
There's a lot about this
that you don't understand.
Really? What?
That she hears voices?
That she's important?
Kenny told us.
She's a fucking murderer.
That's what she is.
How could you do this?
She is not going to
hurt anyone!
I don't give a shit what
she's gonna do!
All I care about is what
she's done.
She tried to kill
my fucking kid!
Yes, I know. I know. I know.
I know. I know. I know. I know.
Alright.
So, now what?
We just supposed to pretend
like nothing happened?
What about your rules?
Things have changed.
- How?
- How? Someone put a tower,
a fucking tower,
on Colony House
and told everyone
they were going home!
Now, they're all looking
at me, wondering why
I didn't come back with
all the answers!
We got a busload of people
we don't have resources for,
and a fucking house fell
for no goddamn reason!
So, yeah, if she can help us
figure out what's going on here,
she stays out
of the Box! Period!
- Hey!
- Eh! I told you
to stay
downstairs! Look.
I wanna talk to you.
You need to listen
very fucking carefully.
If you ever come
near my family again,
I swear to God I will
fucking kill you!
Say you understand.
Say you understand!
I do.
Listen. You
have my word--
I don't give a shit
about your word!
Jim, listen.
Don't even.
Fuck!
Goddamn it!
Okay.
You lock the door.
You stay inside.
Where are you going?
Colony House.
Gotta talk to Donna.
I want to make sure she
hears this from my mouth.
Boyd!
I shouldn't be here! I...
I'm not strong
enough for this.
That part I can't
help you with,
so you better figure
it out!
Ethan.
Ethan, I promise if
you let me in,
it's just me, okay?
There's nobody else
out here.
Ethan, come on.
Please let me in.
Julie, what's
going on?
He heard us last night
talking about Sara.
Now, he won't
come out.
Ethan?
Honey, I promise no
one's going to hurt you.
Yeah. Your mom and I,
we're never gonna let anybody
hurt you.
It's like, uh, with
the Cromenockle?
When she's afraid to
go inside of the cave.
I wanna see her.
I wanna see Sara.
Okay. So, hi.
They're not exactly
chocolate chip, but they're
the best I could do.
Mm.
Here. Careful.
It's hot.
Thank you.
Alright. Ready?
What are they?
Okay. So, they're these bread
crisps that Tian-Chen makes.
They're, like, a cross
between a cracker and a chip.
They're actually
really good. Okay?
Huh.
Right? Okay. Don't get
crumbs in the bed.
Thanks.
I have a surprise
for you.
What?
Um... okay.
Close your eyes.
Open them.
Shut up.
How-- how-- how
do even you have this?
Are you kidding? I haven't
gone anywhere without it
since you...
For a long time,
it still smelled
like you.
Now, it just smells.
I still remember the last time
I saw you wearing it.
Hey.
Hmm?
Where'd you go?
Nowhere.
Kristi, what's wrong?
Nothing.
It's stupid.
Okay.
Tell me anyway.
What if I'm not
the same anymore?
I've just...
...seen things here.
I've had to
do things that--
Hey.
You're still you.
I'm still me.
The rest of it,
we'll figure it
out together.
Hmm?
Every ounce, every
inch, remember?
What are you doing?
Sorry. I, uh--
That's my coat.
- No, this is--
- What's going on?
That girl's here,
the one who killed
her brother.
Please, I just...
- Get the fuck out.
- I don't want any trouble.
You can't have your house back.
Look. She has my coat.
This is my
brother's jacket.
Not anymore it's not.
Put it down and
get the fuck out.
I just
want our things.
There's something
special that I...
The rest of your stuff
is gone. We packed it up.
We-- we gave it to
Kenny's mom for storage.
There was this small ceramic
ornament about this big.
Do you remember?
He just fucking
told you no!
Look. It was creepy
having your stuff here,
and it's really creepy
that you're here right now,
so please just put
the coat down and go away.
- Please.
- Get the fuck out.
Yeah. Okay.
Yeah.
Ah.
Excuse me, bud.
You don't look good.
Tom's dead.
Bar's closed.
- What are you doing?
- Oh, what do you care?
I'm trying to figure
out the symbol
that you refuse to
help me with,
despite the fact that you
clearly know something
- you're not telling me.
- Well, I'll tell you what I can.
- Really?
- Yeah.
First, you have to
do something for me.
Oh.
So, now you need something
from me, you're--
You know what?
First of all, fuck off,
and second
of all, fuck off!
Okay.
Wait!
What do you want?
Mm.
I want you to play.
The fuck is
wrong with you?
If you play, I'll tell you
about the man in the photo.
You tell me about the photo
first. Then I play.
Mm, no.
Just give me
the fuckin' violin.
Not here.
Come.
The fuck?
- Come with me!
- Okay! Alright!
This took me all
fucking night.
There's no way I'm letting
him anywhere near that--
Tabby.
How can you even
consider this, Jim?
After Thomas...
Because the doctors
all said
that we should let him
lead sometimes,
and they also said
that we have to let him
work through things
in his own way
and to be there to
support him when he asks.
Anyways, I'll be there,
right there with him.
- I'm coming with you.
- Tabby.
Look. I don't give a shit
what the doctors said.
We're living in
a fucking nightmare,
and that bitch tried
to kill my kid.
Please let me
do this.
Mom?
Hey... Hey.
I remember what
you told me yesterday
about this place,
how scary it is.
Mm-hmm.
When you're on
a quest,
we have to face
the scary things.
That's how you take
their power away.
Yeah.
Stay with
Daddy, okay?
And do exactly
what he tells you.
- Okay.
What were you
fucking doing, Boyd?
By the rules of
this town,
the rules
you created,
that girl should
have gone in the Box
the second
you found her.
Listen. Father Khatri--
Khatri's fucking dead.
Don't you
lay this on him.
You made your
own call here, Boyd.
You told people you
were coming back with answers,
and instead, you came back
with a psychopath
who killed not one
but four people.
And because she's special,
she doesn't have to go
in the Box? Do you
hear what that sounds like?
She knew things!
Out in the forest,
she knew things
she couldn't
possibly have known!
Okay. Great.
- So what?
- What do you mean, "So what?"
I mean, we're still
fuckin' here.
Voices or no voices,
do you see a yellow brick
fuckin' road leading us home?
Because I sure don't.
I just see someone who may
have just betrayed
the one thing this place
still has going for it.
And what's that?
Faith. In you.
- You want the truth?
- I mean...
I don't think this has anything
to do with going home.
I think this
is about Abby.
I think you
shot your wife,
and every
morning since,
you wake up wishing
you'd done more,
that you'd
been there for her,
helped her,
fixed her.
But Abby's dead, Boyd.
And Sara's a killer.
You gonna have my
back on this or not?
Okay.
What do
you want, Boyd?
You want my approval?
Y-You want absolution?
'Cause you're
not gonna get it here.
What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
What did
Tian-Chen say?
How does she feel
about Sara being back?
- I haven't--
- Yeah. Well, maybe you should.
Sara?
He has something
he wants to say to you.
Everyone thought
you died.
But you didn't.
You lived.
Out in the woods.
Only monsters
live in the woods.
I thought
we were friends.
But we're not.
You're a monster.
And I'm not
afraid of you.
Okay.
- Where are we going?
- It's just a little further.
Listen. You want me to play
something for you, I'll play,
but I'm not gonna wander around
with you all day while you--
It's strange.
The trees,
they're changing.
The fuck does
that mean?
Oh. Well,
this is, uh...
Did you do all this?
After everyone...
Once I was alone,
I-- I didn't want to look
at the cars anymore,
so I put them where I
couldn't see them.
There's more
past the rocks,
a lot more,
but those
were already here.
Come on.
I'm sorry about
what happened yesterday.
I don't like when
people touch my things,
and when I
heard you play...
Uh, sometimes,
I get angry,
and I'm sorry.
Okay.
Here.
- Here what?
- This is where you play.
Oh, thank God. Here.
What do you, uh--
What do you wanna hear?
Play the one
about the star.
The what?
Twinkling star.
This was
your mother's car.
She used to play
it when I was afraid.
And I'd sit up here,
just like this,
and she'd play.
At night,
when we hid,
when I heard
the people screaming,
she'd tell me to think
about the twinkling stars.
And then... I wouldn't
be afraid anymore.
Do you
know that song?
Yeah. Uh... I know it.
Oh. Uh, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to...
I didn't think
anyone would be here.
It's okay.
Plenty of room.
Were you on the bus?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Have you been
here long?
A couple months.
Feels like
much longer.
Do you live
here in town?
I mean, obviously,
you-- you live in town.
I just...
I hadn't seen you
up at the Colony House.
I would've
noticed you.
I, um...
I guess right now,
I live here.
I figured a priest
would live here
or something.
There used to be.
Oh.
I go every Sunday with
my grandma.
Uh, to church,
I mean.
As long as
I can remember.
Is that where you were going
when you were on the bus?
To see
your grandmother?
Yeah. She... uh...
I go see her
every weekend.
I was never
all that religious,
but... it always made
her happy,
you know, me going to
church with her,
and afterwards, we'd spend
the afternoon sitting outside,
making these little
crochet owls.
Really?
It was always
an owl.
And she has
hundreds of 'em.
Uh, she would give them
to every person that she met.
And I-- I
would tell her,
"Grandma, maybe we could try to
switch it up a little bit.
Maybe try a dog or
a bunny or something."
But she'd tell me,
"Elgin, I like
what I like,
and I like owls."
So we made owls.
You must think
I'm really cool.
I was kind of a dork
when I was a kid.
My brother and I,
we used to collect these little
ceramic Christmas ornaments
from the dollar store
in town.
We'd save up
all our money.
We'd go every chance we got,
like, all year round.
We wouldn't even wait
for Christmas.
And then we'd get home,
and we would paint them
with all
these crazy colors.
We had so many at
one point,
we could've decorated
a hundred trees
and still had
some left over.
Nathan's always looked
a lot better than mine.
I thought
they were all gone.
Turns out...
Nathan kept one with him
all these years.
He said it reminded him of
a time when things were...
Is he here now?
Your brother?
He was.
What happened
to the ornament?
It's here...
somewhere. I just...
I think the person who has
it won't wanna give it back.
Hey.
You need some muscle,
I'm happy to talk to 'em.
You're sweet.
How come you don't stay up
at the Colony House?
I mean, the people up there seem
friendly, for the most part.
No reason to be hanging
around an old, musty church.
It always seemed like
such a nice idea...
that no matter what
you did...
if you
were truly sorry...
then God would
forgive you.
Do you
think that's true?
That part
always seemed
a bit like wishful
thinking to me.
Why? Did you do something
that needs forgiving?
I killed my brother.
But it was
an accident.
Right?
- I mean, you wouldn't--
- You'll find out everything
soon enough.
Uh... maybe
I should, uh...
Uh...
It was really nice to
meet you, Elgin.
Yeah.
It was nice, uh...
nice meeting
you, too.
How did it go?
You okay?
I'm not afraid anymore.
Oh, baby,
I'm so proud of you.
Hey. Nice going.
Can you come help me
peel some potatoes for dinner?
I don't wanna peel potatoes.
Okay. Neither do I.
- Go on.
- Let's go.
Come on.
How did he do?
- He did great.
- Yeah? Oh, God.
Life lessons
from the Cromenockle.
Who would
have thought?
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't
have come here.
Wait.
You take from me.
You take him from me.
Yes.
I take care of you.
But you...
you put hate
inside me.
I know why you come.
You wait.
You take and go.
You never come
here, this place.
You never
come again.
- Are you kidding me?
- Kenny, I just--
- Hey!
- Kenny, I--
- What? What?
- I wasn't doing anything.
You weren't doing
anything what? Give me that.
- Kenny, please. Kenny, please!
- What the fuck is in it?
Give me that.
Your stuff? Huh?
This is
your stuff, right?
Is this Nathan's?
What's that?
Give me that.
- Stop. Stop! No! Please!
- Give me it. Give me it.
What is this?
- This important to you? Huh?
- Kenny.
- This is meaningful?
- Kenny, please.
- This mean a lot to you?
- Don't, please.
- Fuck you!
- Oh.
Hey. Hey.
Look. Listen.
Look at me!
I don't care what Boyd says,
and I don't give a shit
how fucking special you
think you are.
You ever come near my
mom again, and I swear to God
I will drag your fucking psycho
ass into that Box myself.
Do you
understand me?
Do you understand?
Yes.
Can I see?
Hold on.
Almost done.
There we go.
Can I see?
Keep in mind... I'm a
little out of practice.
Ooh!
I think we did okay.
- I love it.
- Yeah?
Come here.
I look like me again.
Oh, excuse me. Uh...
Hi.
Hi. I-- I was
looking for Kristi.
Yeah. That's me. Hi.
Sorry. I didn't
mean to interrupt.
Oh, no. It's fine.
How can I help you?
Well, uh...
...since you're
the resident Quincy...
...I was hoping I
could give you this.
Uh, why are you carrying around
liquid morphine?
Mm. Um, when were
you diagnosed?
About a month ago.
I figure that by
the time I need that,
I probably won't be
in any shape to...
I'll take care
of it, okay?
Thank you.
Look what I did.
Ruined such a
nice afternoon.
I'll let you
get back to it.
Oh, well, you're better
off in here, anyway.
Oh, there's lots
of hubbub flying around
now that that
Sara girl's back.
I'm sorry. What?
Kristi, where are
you going?
- Baby, stop!
- No! I have to--
- Stop!
- I have to go!
Hey, just
talk to me!
Hey! Talk to me!
What is going on?
You're not
going anywhere, okay?
Not like this.
Who is Sara?
She killed somebody,
and then she tried to kill
a little boy because I...
We were talking one night.
She was at the clinic,
and... and she asked me what I
would do to see you again.
If it was something bad,
would it be worth it?
And I said yes.
I don't...
I gave
her permission,
and then the next day,
she-- Fuck.
I just wanted to see
you again so badly that I--
I wasn't even
listening to the question,
and now, you're here,
and I'm wondering
if that's my fault,
too. And I just...
No. I just feel like all
I've been doing lately is
- hurting people, and I just--
- No. Hey.
This is
not your fault.
I am here.
Okay?
We're together.
Come inside.
His name
was Christopher.
Christopher.
Come with me.
What?
No. Come on.
It's right over here.
This was his car.
He seemed nice at first,
'cause he made people laugh.
That-- that wasn't an easy
thing to do back then.
People liked him.
And then?
Then he changed.
- Changed how?
- I-- I don't...
I don't like this.
Uh, we should go back.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
- But we had a deal.
- Mm.
Right? I played your
song. I held up my end.
You don't understand.
You shouldn't be asking
these questions.
Why? Why? Why?
- Mm.
- Huh?
Look. I haven't had
a good night's sleep
since I fucking got here,
and I'm-- and I'm seeing things,
things that are scaring
the shit out of me.
And it's-- and it's all
because of this, right here!
And whoever this Christopher
guy was, he saw it, too!
He saw it.
He obsessed over it.
He drew it a thousand
fucking times.
So you playing your whole weird,
creepy mystery man routine,
it's not exactly
helping me feel any better!
When did he
start seeing the symbol?
- I don't know.
- What does it mean?
- I don't know!
- Well, what the fuck
do you know?
I'm sorry.
I'm just...
I know these
things are scary,
and... I know that
these aren't things
that you really
want to talk about, but...
I am at
the end of my rope.
Please.
Everyone died.
When Christopher started
seeing that symbol,
things... changed.
He changed,
and he didn't make
people laugh anymore.
He-- he stopped smiling.
One night, my mother told me
to hide somewhere new,
somewhere different, somewhere
Christopher didn't know,
and when I woke up
the next morning, everyone...
There are
bad things here.
They make people
do bad things.
I'm sorry.
I'm here!
Anghkooey!
Anghkooey.
Anghkooey. Anghkooey.
- Who are you?
- Anghkooey.
- I'm not afraid of you.
Anghkooey, Anghkooey,
Anghkooey, Anghkooey!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Don't touch me! Don't touch me!
Don't! Don't! Don't, please!
Don't, don't, don't, don't,
don't, don't, don't!
Don't touch me! Don't touch me!
Don't touch me!
- Don't touch me, please!
- Anghkooey!
- Please don't touch me!
No, no, no! Don't touch me!
Don't touch me!
Anghkooey, Anghkooey,
Anghkooey, Anghkooey.
No! Don't! No! No!
Don't touch me! Please don't
touch me! Don't touch me!
Don't touch me!
Huh? I don't--
Hey! Hey!
- You okay?
- I don't...
Did you see that?
Your nose is-- your
nose is bleeding.
Did you see that? Did you see
them? Where the fuck...
See? See what?
See who?
What?
Boyd.
Look. I don't wanna
do this right now, Jim.
I'm not here to argue.
I mean, I don't agree
with what you did, but...
...but I looked
at that girl today,
and I didn't see
a psychopath.
I didn't see
a vicious killer.
I saw a broken kid.
And I'm looking
around, and...
I'm seeing a lot of people
pushed to their edge.
Okay.
You ever wonder if
maybe that's the point?
What are you
talking about?
We heard a voice
on the radio.
Yeah. Me and Donna,
right as the storm
was coming in,
and whoever it was,
he knew my name,
knew what my wife was
doing in the house,
in the basement
of our house.
And I thought
maybe I was crazy.
I think people
are watching us.
- I think people are listening.
- Jim--
Now, there
are experiments like this
going all the way
back to World War II.
Look. We don't have to
trust each other.
We don't even have to
like each other.
But we've gotta start
working together on this.
Now, I don't know what
they want from us,
but if you can give me
a more rational explanation
for what's going on here,
I'd love to hear it.
I gotta go, Jim.
Hello?
♪ A candy-colored clown
They call the Sandman♪
♪ Tiptoes through
My room every night♪
Tian-Chen?
♪ Just to sprinkle stardust
And to whisper♪
♪ Go to sleep ♪
Tian-Chen?
♪ Everything is alright ♪
Shit.
♪ I close my eyes ♪
♪ And I drift away ♪
♪ Into the magic night ♪
♪ I softly say ♪
♪ A silent prayer ♪
Like dreamers do♪
♪ Then I fall asleep to dream ♪
♪ My dreams of you ♪
♪ In dreams I walk ♪
♪ With you ♪
♪ In dreams I talk ♪
♪ To you ♪
♪ In dreams you're mine ♪
♪ All the time ♪
♪ We're together ♪
♪ In dreams ♪
♪ But just before ♪
♪ The dawn ♪
♪ I awake ♪
♪ And find you gone ♪
♪ I can't help it ♪
♪ If I try ♪
♪ I remember ♪
♪ When you said ♪
I...
♪ Goodbye ♪
♪ In dreams ♪
I was hoping
we could talk.
♪ You're mine ♪
♪ All the time ♪
♪ We're together ♪
♪ In dreams ♪
♪ It's too bad ♪
♪ That all these things ♪
♪ Can only happen ♪
♪ In my dreams ♪
♪ Only in dreams ♪
♪ In beautiful dreams ♪