Previously on From...
Those things out there...
They like to hunt.
They like to play.
Stop smiling!
You'll feel better,
if you come outside.
I can't fucking
do this anymore.
I feel like I saw that piece
of her start to slip away.
Then it has to be you.
You have to be
that piece of her
that this place
can't take away.
We don't have much time.
I need you to kill me.
My blood
is your blood now.
What if I'm not
the same anymore?
You're still you.
I'm still me.
The rest of it,
we'll figure it out together.
What is she doing here?
She might be helpful
for us to find out
what we're looking
for out there.
No one can know
she's with me.
She killed my dad!
They tore him to pieces
and you knew!
Kenny, please.
You watch
your own fucking six.
I was hoping we could talk.
I'm not really
sure where to start.
I want you to know that
my decision about Sara,
I believe in my heart
is for the good
of everyone
in this town.
But that doesn't
mean that I--
What she did,
what she took from you,
from Kenny,
it doesn't matter
why she did it.
I understand if you...
you hate me for protecting her.
For keeping her a secret.
I know what it's like
when this place--
when it, uh,
takes somebody that you love.
I just--
Listen.
Since I got here,
I've tried to make
people feel safe.
I thought, if there's rules,
if we just stick
to what's right.
Here's what I know.
Things are changing,
and if we don't use
everything we have,
every little thing, I...
I need to do
whatever I can
to get these people home,
to get you and Kenny home,
even if it means...
Ma.
What are you doing here?
Okay.
Huh?
What are you doing here?
No, no, no. It's okay.
It's okay.
I just--
Thanks for your time.
You okay?
Sara? We--
- Oh, sh--
- Boyd?
Hey!
Hey, hey.
You okay?
Sorry, I just--sorry.
Okay. Okay.
Oh, sorry about that.
No, you, um,
you should get that looked at.
Oh.
Sorry to be a bother.
You take him see Kristi.
Mm-mm.
No, no. I'm okay.
I'm--I'm fine. Thanks.
I'm okay. Thank you.
Yup.
All right. Okay.
- No, no.
- All right. All right.
Okay, let's go.
Okay, thanks.
Yeah.
" plays]
♪ When I was just a little boy ♪
♪ I asked my father ♪
♪ "What will I be?" ♪
♪ "Will I be handsome?" ♪
♪ "Will I be rich?" ♪
♪ Here's what he said to me ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ Whatever will be will be ♪
♪ The future's not ours to see ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ What will be will be ♪
♪ Now I have
children of my own♪
♪ They ask their father ♪
♪ "What will I be?" ♪
♪ "Will I be pretty?" ♪
♪ "Will I be rich?" ♪
♪ I tell them tenderly ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ Whatever will be will be ♪
♪ The future's not ours to see ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ What will be will be ♪
That's the last of the potatoes.
Hope Donna's planning on
bringing some of this back.
This ready to go?
Yeah, let me give you a hand.
I got it.
Trouble in paradise?
- That the last of it?
- Yup.
That's everything.
We're gonna be fine.
We all keep our heads,
stick to the rations,
we'll get through this.
We're gonna be dealing with
this most of the night
down at the Liu house,
so I need you
to oversee the lock-up.
Remember, make sure
cans on all the doors.
Hey, um, what do we tell
people about the food?
Oh, for now?
As little as possible.
Just say, uh...
we're working
out a new system.
We don't want anyone
to panic.
You guys gonna be all right?
Yeah.
Yeah, we got this.
Hm.
Hey, have you
seen the--
What is this?
You went
through my bag?
I was looking
for a hair clip.
Look.
It's just--You said that
you were going
to see your aunt.
That's why you were on the bus,
Yeah, because I didn't
want you to...
It's not a big deal.
Not a big--
You lied to me.
Because I didn't
want you to worry.
Everything's under control.
You were on your way to rehab
and you ended up here.
There's--Nothing about
that is under control.
I mean, you were doing so well,
I don't under--
When did you start
using again?
Don't say it like that.
I'm not--
It's just been
a few months.
This is
'cause I disappeared.
It was because
of a lot of things.
Look, I was gonna tell you,
I just--
Fuck.
Where are you going?
No, don't do that,
you don't have to do that.
Listen to me!
We have a very limited supply
of medication here,
and what we have is vital!
I can't risk
anything going missing!
This doesn't have to
be a big deal, okay?
I was already gonna stop,
so we can just do it here.
We can do it now.
This doesn't have to be--
Can you please just stop
and talk to me!
Shit! I got it!
Would you just please
stop doing that!?
Doing what?
Stop panicking like I'm some
junkie who's gonna like--
You know,
this is why I didn't tell you.
Did you take anything
from here?
Tell me the truth.
It was just
a little bit of morphine
so I could even myself out
a bit. That's all.
Okay? You can put
it back in the cabinet.
I'm not gonna take anything--
Marielle.
Yeah, fine,
Do whatever
the fuck you want!
- Where are you going?
- For a walk!
So you can hide
all your valuables from
your junkie-ass girlfriend!
You can't go outside.
It'll be dark out soon.
Fuck you!
Yeah, I noticed that myself.
Leaves changing colors,
falling off the trees.
Never seen that before.
Yeah.
Look...
Kenny,
I-I know that--
You know, um,
you look like you're--
you're walking better now,
so I'm...
um, you've probably
got it from here.
God damn it!
Boyd, what happened?
It's starting to hurt now.
You can't always see them,
but I can feel them now.
Boyd, what are--
What are you talking about?
Look, I-I can't...
When I went out
to the forest,
something happened
to me out there,
something I don't understand--
I got something--
something in me now.
Worms, they're crawling
underneath my skin.
And--And--
You--
You hear that?
Boyd?
Boyd!
Boyd, where are you going?
What's going on?
Boyd?
Did you see her? She--
We should go.
It's gonna get dark soon.
Yeah.
Here, man.
Thanks, Ellis.
Of course.
Hey, let's, uh,
hang those at the front.
Yup.
Hey.
- Hi.
- Can I help?
- Nope.
- No?
- Done.
- Yeah. Cool.
How are the windows?
Uh, they're covering up
the last of them now.
Great.
Hey, hey.
We okay?
Yeah. Yeah, we're fine.
Huh.
One thing at a time here, Boyd.
You're not listening
to me. It's not--
What?
It's what he did.
That's what I'm trying to--
Okay, so you're saying
someone did this to you?
Yeah. Look. Here.
Here.
He cut me here,
and then he put
his bloody wrist
up against my arm and said,
"My blood is your blood now."
And then whatever
was inside of him
came out of him
and went into me.
And then...
and then
the place disappeared.
Boyd--
Look, I--
There's nothing I can say
that makes this sound logical.
Okay.
I got worms under my skin.
And--And--
And it feels like something--
like something's
coming for me now. It's...
Boyd, I don't--
I don't see anything.
The guy who did
this to me, all right?
Whatever these things are,
they had been feeding
on him for years.
And he passed it on to me,
because they
wouldn't let him die.
You imagine that?
It was so bad that
all he wanted to do was die.
All right, you...
you don't have to
believe me right now.
I just need you to
promise me that if this--
if things get bad, if I...
Hey, promise me.
That you--
you'll put
an end to things
before it goes too far.
Boyd, what are you
asking me to do?
I don't wanna die
like Martin died.
So I guess you're
staying the night.
Yeah, yeah.
I just--
I figured, you know.
I hope that's okay.
Yeah.
Yeah, of course.
Did he tell you
about the worms?
Yeah.
Did you see anything?
You mean, did I see anything
crawling under his skin?
No, but he's been
through a lot.
You know, this is how it--
this is how it started
with my dad back home.
There would be moments
where he'd just seem like
a completely different person,
say things that
he would never say.
We'd rationalize it.
Say he was just tired,
say he was under
a lot of stress.
Then one day he just...
Hey.
It's too early
to start worrying
about things
like that, okay?
I mean, there are cases
where Parkinson's can lead
to dementia, but it happens
way later on, 'kay?
But it does
happen though.
Yeah.
Like this?
Remember, only two tablespoons
of salt per jar.
We've got a limited supply,
we gotta make it last.
Well, how long is it
gonna last like this?
We do things right,
it should keep to a year.
That way we can ration
what we've got now
and not worry
about it spoiling.
Please tell me this
isn't all there is.
We've already planted new crops,
we're setting--
Donna, there's barely
a month's worth of food here.
Even with rations,
you're gonna--
Well, people need to
know how bad it is.
All that's gonna do
is make people panic.
Kinda like what's
happening to you now.
You should've told us sooner.
And when was I supposed
to do that, Jim?
When you were stuck under
the house that fell on you?
Just trying to do
our best here.
That's all part of it.
Part of what?
It's exactly what
they would want.
They would be trying to
increase the stress level.
Jim.
What do you mean,
we don't have enough food?
It's okay, buddy.
Come on,
let's get back to business.
- Are you okay?
- What the--
Jesus!
No, no, no, no!
I'm sorry.
What the fuck!
I'm so, so--
I'm sorry.
I'm putting it down. Look.
Sorry about that.
I apol--I apologize.
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
No.
Here's the thing.
Any time you say
that we're fine,
it means that we're not fine.
'Kay, what was
I supposed to do?
My dad asked me
not to tell anyone.
Ellis, I'm not "anyone".
We're supposed to
be getting married!
We can't just keep
things from each other!
I need to know that--
Look, your dad never should've
put you in that position
to begin with.
Sara murdered people.
And the fact that
he didn't tell anyone--
he didn't tell Kenny!--
that's not right.
He didn't have a choice.
There's always
a choice.
He put people in danger
by bringing her back here!
He made this place
less safe!
And you never should
have kept that from me.
I know.
And I'm sorry.
This isn't about
my dad or Sara, is it?
Fatima,
ever since that night
at the Sheriff's
station you've just...
Baby, what's--
what's going on?
Hey! I asked you,
what are you fucking doing?
I saw what you were doing!
You were sneaking food
out of the pantry.
I wasn't! I was
taking some extra food
outta my backpack
and putting it--
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
What the hell's going on?
- They're stealing food!
- What?
Bad enough the storm
wiped out everything we had--
Okay, no, that's not true!
That's not true!
Bullshit.
I saw what you loaded today.
First, the magic radio tower
was gonna get everybody home.
Does it look
like we're home? No.
No, instead we've got
so many people now
we're running out of food,
and they're hiding it
- so nobody panics.
- Just stop.
Look, nobody
is hiding anything.
Oh, why don't you
shut the fuck up?
I'm sick and tired of all your
smiley-happy bullshit from you.
Okay, whoa, whoa, you better
watch your fucking mouth!
We can't have
new people stealing
what little food we have!
They have to go.
- Go on! Get outside.
- Dale.
- Go. Get outside!
- Hey, hey!
Look, look, no one
is trying to hurt you--
- Get outside!
- Dale, come on!
Get off me!
No!
Oh God, oh fuck,
I'm sorry.
Fucking stabbed me.
Get him outta here!
Ellis, I didn't mean to!
I'm sorry!
Hey, can you, um... Here.
Oh my God. Oh my God.
Here, here.
It's okay.
You're okay, you hear me?
You're gonna be fine.
Here, let's sit him
right down here.
All right. We got ya.
That's right.
Okay, down.
I'm sorry. Here, let me
just take a quick look.
You're okay.
Hey, can you grab me
some more towels?
Yeah, yeah!
Pass me--
pass me that thing.
Here, here.
You're okay. You're okay.
Here,
just hold pressure on it.
You're okay.
You're gonna be okay.
Some stains
you can't wash clean.
This how we're all
gonna end up?
Like Bing-Qian? Like you?
Look, whether you get out
of this place or not, Boyd,
we all end up the same.
I'm not talking about dying.
I'm talking about dying
with your insides on the floor,
screaming while some thing
tears you apart.
These things inside me,
whatever they are,
they're getting worse.
So it would seem.
I'm proud of you, though.
You know that?
The sheriff I knew
would have never
asked for help,
never admitted weakness.
You were the most stubborn
asshole I have ever met.
Things change.
Yes, they do.
You know,
those people upstairs...
...they probably all think
you've gone crazy.
Have I?
I don't know.
I mean, you're standing
here in this basement
talking to a figment
of your imagination.
But, hey,
sometimes crazy
is the most rational
response you could have.
The point is,
you did what you could, Boyd.
You tried.
Not every story
gets a happy ending.
Mine didn't.
Bing-Qian's didn't.
Abby's didn't.
You are still the worst
fucking priest I've ever met.
So maybe imagine
a better version next time.
Yeah, right.
Boyd.
Who were you talking to?
Nobody, just thinking
out loud.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Who were you talking to?
Get out of my way.
You're not leaving this room
until I know it's safe.
Excuse me?
Look, Marielle told us
what happened upstairs.
All right?
Then I come down here--
Khatri!
I was talking
to Father Khatri.
I know how this looks.
I do!
But something
happened to me out there!
I came back with
something inside my body!
I don't understand
how it's possible!
All I know
is that it's real!
And I'm fucking terrified!
You have to keep
pressure on it, okay?
We're gonna get you
to the clinic.
Donna took the truck.
We'll take the van.
It's parked right by the shed.
No, you can't.
It's too dangerous.
Look, we've got lookouts
at all the windows. It's okay.
I think we're all clear.
- Okay.
- No, no, no.
Ellis, there is nothing
we can do for you here.
You need to get
to the clinic.
Then we can wait
until the morning.
No! We're not--
We're not. Hey!
Can you help me out here?
Come on. We're going.
Let's go.
Up, up, up.
We're going.
Come on, buddy.
I know, I know, I know.
Hold on.
Okay.
That's right. That's right.
Hey! Do you see anything?
Wait! Hold on.
There's one coming up the hill.
- Well, how far?
- I don't know. Fifty yards.
- I can't, I can't, I can't.
- No, no--
- I can't run. I can't run.
- We have--We have time.
You're okay, you're okay.
Meet me at the steps!
What? Wait!
Where you going?
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Oh, shit.
Oh, no. No. Shit.
I know, I know.
Go, go, go, go, go!
I know.
I gotcha. I gotcha.
Here, take
this jacket off.
Go, go, go, go,
go, go, go!
Hey, stay!
You're okay. Just breathe.
- I know.
- I can't breathe.
Just keep,
just keep it there.
I can't--
Here! That road!
Get on that road!
Yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just keep the pressure on.
Keep the pressure.
You're okay. Look at me.
You're okay.
- Can't breathe.
- You're okay. You're okay.
You're okay. You're okay.
- Can you go any faster?
- Yeah.
I know. I know.
Just, here, hold my hand.
You're okay. You're okay.
- What happened?
- I don't know.
Can you go any faster?
I know, I know, I know.
Hey, we're almost there!
- I know. I know.
- Fatima?
What?
You see any of
those things outside?
Uh, uh, no.
I think we're okay.
- I think we're okay.
- Can't breathe.
You're okay.
Hi, I'm right here.
We're almost there, guys!
I see it!
Stay with me!
- I--
- Kristi's right there.
- We're gonna see Kristi.
- Hey, just hold on.
- We're almost there!
- Easy, easy.
All right. You're all right.
Come on.
All right, all right.
You're all right. Come on.
Put your arm around me.
I know. I know.
Okay, come here.
Help me up.
Slow, slow, slow.
You got it.
Hold my shoulder.
If you want me to leave,
I can go up to Colony House
- for a little bit.
- No.
No, Mari. That's not--
- Kristi! Help!
- Kristi, open the door!
Fuck.
- Kristi!
- Open the door!
- Open up!
- Jesus.
What happened?
Uh, there was a fight.
Dale had a knife.
Okay.
- Bring him inside, okay?
- Yeah.
Boyd! Kenny!
I'm gonna need you up here!
Ellis, you okay?
- Ellis!
- I can't breathe!
Sit him down here!
I can't breathe!
- How long ago did this happen?
- Twenty-five minutes.
Keep pressure!
Ellis?
What's--Hey, what happened?
What's--What--
- He was stabbed.
- Kristi, what's happening?
Keep that pillow up!
Hey, buddy. Okay, okay.
Keep pressure. Keep pressure
on the wound, okay?
- You're okay.
- Can you breathe for me, Ellis?
Okay.
I'm afraid of blood
filling his chest cavity.
Okay, buddy,
that's it.
- Look at me. Look at me.
- It's okay, baby.
Keep pressure, okay?
- I can't breathe!
- Come on.
Breathe in again.
Kristi, what's happening?
- You're okay.
- Can I do something?
His chest is tensioning.
I need to relieve the pressure.
Where do you
keep your saline?
- You can't be in here right now.
- Kristi, come on!
I swear to you, I'm fine.
Hey, what is going on?
Top shelf of the supply closet.
Kenny, I need you around here.
Buddy? Buddy?
Lift up. Pressure.
Okay, just let me
clean the area.
This'll sting.
Shit!
Buddy? Hey, buddy.
Hey, you can breathe.
You--
Just a little poke.
- What's that for?
- I just need to see
if it's air or blood
compressing his lungs.
Can you grab this post
for me, please?
- Right here, grab it for me?
- All right.
Hey, guys, I'm gonna have
to come in here.
Hey, let's let Kristi
work. Come here. Come.
You're gonna be okay.
'Kay? Trust me.
- You're gonna be fine.
- You got it.
There's blood in
his chest cavity.
- We need to move fast!
- Let her work.
It's gonna be okay.
Hey. You're gonna be fine.
Ellis!
Give her--
We've gotta give her--
What? What?
I'm gonna need a scalpel
and, um, some rags.
Oh yeah.
Yeah, okay, good.
Gonna make
a little incision, okay?
Here.
Here. Rags.
- Hold this.
- All right.
There's gonna be
a lot of blood, okay?
- Forceps.
Okay, ready?
All right.
Okay.
All right, Ellis, we're gonna
relieve the pressure, all right?
Ugh.
Shit.
Deep breaths Ellis, okay?
Relax your arm
for me if you can.
We're just gonna
let that drain.
I can't. I can't.
I can't lose him.
Hey, hey.
Look at me. Look at me.
He is not going
anywhere, okay?
Look, hey,
do I look nervous?
Did Kristi look nervous?
Look, he's fine?
Hey.
Sit down. Sit down.
Hey, just breathe.
Breathe.
You're all right. You're okay.
You just--just breathe.
All right?
Hey, you all right?
Yeah, um,
I'm not really good with blood.
- Hey.
- Hey, is he okay?
I was able to relieve
the pressure in his chest,
but he's lost a lot of blood.
His heart's
trying to compensate,
but unless we get him
more blood soon,
his organs are
gonna start to fail.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
- Hey, hey.
- But we aren't there yet, okay?
Boyd, what's his blood type?
O-negative.
We're both O-negative.
Okay. Great.
That's great. Come in.
Come on.
Wait, what's going on?
We're gonna use Boyd's blood
to do a transfusion.
I know it sounds scary,
but, trust me, it's a very--
Wait, wait, wait.
No, no.
You can't.
You... You can't
put my blood into him.
- Boyd--
- If you use my blood,
whatever's inside me
is going to go into him!
Boyd, just take a second and
listen to what you're saying--
I'm not fucking crazy!
These things,
I can feel them.
Even if I can't see them,
I can feel them!
Boyd, if you don't do this,
Ellis is going to die.
Even if what
you're saying is true,
it can't be worse than dying.
You tell that to
the guy who did this to me.
We have to find another way.
You can't just--
Boyd, you need
to sit down
and let Kristi do her work.
Hey.
Kenny, please--
Sit down!
If you do this,
you have no idea--
Just--God!
Oh, my God!
Damn it!
I can see them.
Jesus.
Guys, can somebody
do something!
We need to get him--We need
to get him O-negative blood.
I--
We need to do this now.
Give it to me.
What?
You told Kristi about
the guy in the cave,
that he cut you and pressed his
wound against your cut, right?
Well, if he gave it to you,
that probably means that
he can pass it
on to someone else.
As long as you get
the transfusion done,
we'll figure out
the rest later.
No.
- Boyd!
- No, no. No!
No, there's a nightmare
happening under my skin,
you understand me?
I can feel it
getting stronger.
I have no idea what will
happen if I pass it...
on to you.
Boyd.
Boyd, what
are you doing?
- Boyd?
- Boyd!
- I got an idea.
Wait, where are you going?
It has to go somewhere, right?
Boyd!
- Boyd, where--
- Boyd!
What are you doing?
Where you at?
Want some fresh blood?
Fresh meat?
I'm right here.
Come get me!
I know you're out there.
I know you hear me.
You wanna play games?
I'm right here!
I'm ready!
Come on!
All you fucking do
is knock on our doors,
knock on
our fucking windows!
You wanna play games!
Well, I'm standing
right here!
I fuckin'--
That's right.
Come on.
Come get me.
That's right.
There.
What you waiting for?
You want it?
My blood is your blood now, motherfucker.
I like this game.
Okay.
It's okay.
We're okay now.
The transfusion,
we need to start.
Just watch it
on that last step.
- Okay.
- You got it.
You can put the bag over
on that chair by the table.
Okay.
Well, that wasn't
so bad, huh?
Yeah.
In fact, I'd
venture so far
as to say
it was almost fun.
Somethin' interesting
up there?
What if this house
falls down, too?
That is not
gonna happen.
How do you know?
Because I don't think
your parents
are gonna dig another
giant hole in the floor.
Can I tell you
a secret?
Of course you can.
I told my mom and dad
I wasn't scared,
but I am.
I don't wanna be
on a quest anymore.
I wanna go home.
Okay.
Can I tell you
a secret?
I'm a little
scared, too.
Really?
Yup.
But guess what?
What?
That's a good thing.
Why?
My mom told me something
when I was about your age,
and I think it might
have been the smartest thing
anyone ever told me.
You wanna hear it?
Yeah.
She said that fear
is something
that lives inside us.
Just like hope
or joy or love.
They're all things
that make us special.
But fear might be
the most important one of all.
Why?
Because without fear,
we wouldn't know
how to be brave.
Fear is what
makes us heroes.
Aw.
Hey, kiddo.
You, sir, are done.
All right. Okay.
Uh-uh. You should
lie down for a little bit.
I'm okay.
Kr--Kristi.
I am okay.
All right?
You get it.
Hey, Ellis.
- Mm.
- Hey.
How you doing?
How's your breathing?
Oh, I can breathe.
Good.
I'm, uh,
I'm gonna get some new sheets.
Clean you up, okay?
Thank you.
Hey.
Hi.
You still mad at me?
Shut up.
Sorry.
No.
You get some rest.
Where you going?
I'll be right back.
Hey.
You okay?
I almost lost him.
But you didn't, okay?
You didn't.
Those things
under Boyd's skin--
the--the--
I mean, this fucking place.
How is that--
I know.
I can't...
Hey.
I need to
ask you something.
And I need you to promise me
that you won't tell anyone.
Yeah. Of course.
Do you have
any pregnancy tests?
We should've listened to you.
We should have trusted you.
It all worked out.
That's all that matters.
Has it moved?
Nope.
Is it... dead?
Well, we'll find out
soon enough.