This programme contains strong
language and scenes of surgery
RUMBLE OF THUNDER
LAUGHTER
Oh!
Argh!
THEME MUSIC
FEARFUL: Why did
you move next door?
HAMMERING
DOG BARKS
Keep coming around by me
Keep coming out of nowhere
Keep coming out
of nowhere...
Are you OK for drinks? Erm,
yeah, we're both good, thanks.
Yeah, I'm fine.
FAINT: How long is
this going to last?
Oi! What?
If Gemma found out we'd invited his
bit on the side... Hey, be nice.
Come on.
Wow, OK, Lotts,
what culinary delights have
you made for us tonight?
We're having spelt-battered
pollock in a satay sauce.
Oh, my God. It looks
amazing. Thank you so much.
It's all Lottie's handiwork.
I'm only the humble sous-chef.
Lottie is an insane cook.
You are in for such a treat.
I'm allergic to gluten
and I don't eat fish.
What?
I... I didn't know that.
No, I, erm...
Well, perhaps you could
pick the vegetables out.
We can... We can make you something
else, Alyssa. It's no problem.
No, it's fine. It's
totally my fault.
Sorry, I keep forgetting.
It's quite a recent diagnosis.
No, of course, yeah. It
must be a right pain.
What happens when you eat it?
Well, it's more of an intolerance.
I just... It don't feel good.
Yeah, but, darling, you've got
to... You've got to eat something.
Honestly, I ate earlier. I'll
just drink wine. I'm good.
OK.
So, Ben says you work
together. That must be intense.
JACOB CHUCKLES
We try to avoid it
as much as possible.
But it's not always possible.
Do you even do
operations together?
Like, how does that
work? Who's in charge?
Well, erm... CHARLOTTE LAUGHS
What? A surgeon and an anaesthetist
are equals on the surgical team.
BEN LAUGHS
Like all anaesthetists, Jacob
is very touchy about his status.
Well, yeah, it's no big
deal. We're just in charge
of whether you live
or die. Yeah, sure.
But, no, seriously, I mean, my
job is 99% boredom and 1% panic.
In answer to your question, yes,
a surgeon is always in charge
during an operation and, yes,
he does exactly as I tell him.
Wow. At home and at work.
Well, you see, the
key to our marriage is
I let Lottie think she's in
charge, but really it's me.
Don't seem like it
to me. BEN LAUGHS
All right.
Mm! Oh, my God.
Mm.
So how long have you
two been together?
Well, our 20 year anniversary is
coming up. Oh, God, he's remembered.
Probably about the same year
you were born, isn't it?
Not quite.
The fish is sensational.
Can you hand me
the wine, please?
I'm, erm... I'm sorry
if I was a bit rude.
Oh, it's fine.
Look, it's not personal. You
seem like a really nice girl.
I'm not a girl.
I'm a grown woman.
Not in his eyes.
Who pissed on your chips?
You know, if you don't eat carbs
because you don't want a fat arse,
you should just be
honest and say so.
Ladies, hey, how's
everything going?
Mm.
Oh, Lotts, come on, let me...
Please, let me do the washing-up.
You've spoilt us so
much this evening.
It's all going in the dishwasher.
We're all good, Ben. Really? Yeah.
OK. Erm...
OK.
All right? Yeah. Charlotte
and I were just discussing
her forthright views
on fat arses and carbs.
HENRY: What's all
the bloody noise?
Oh, Dad, I thought
you'd gone to bed.
Come on, Henry. Let's get
you back upstairs, all right?
Don't you tell me
what to do, young man!
Hello, Henry. It's...
It's me. It's Ben.
Who?
Ben. How are you?
Oh, I've never been better.
How are the girls, Gemma?
Such lovely daughters.
Oh, Henry, sorry, no, this...
Actually, this is Alyssa.
Is she, 'eck!
Her name's Gemma
and you're married
and you have two
beautiful daughters.
Ben had a roving eye, but you
tamed him, didn't you, Gemma?
OK.
I think we're going to... Yeah,
yeah... get you up to bed, Dad.
Come on, let's get you all
comfy. Be back in a sec. Sure.
God, she was awful.
Lottie, we've got to accept the
fact that he's moved on, all right?
Here you go. Thanks.
Why? Do you think he's in love?
I don't know. Maybe he is.
I'm sure I'm taking things
extremely personally,
but Gem's my best friend.
I don't know why you're being
so moralistic about an age gap.
I mean, who cares? Is this
you laying the groundwork
so you can hook up
with a younger model?
God, no. Can't be arsed. I'm
exhausted enough as it is.
Well, I hope you're
not too exhausted.
Lottie, it's not
even sex Wednesday.
Don't mock my sex schedule.
I'm a very busy woman.
Unless you've got
a better offer.
Oh, I couldn't possibly comment.
Hmm? Mm.
MOBILE PHONE RINGS
Oh, God.
Shit.
Hi, Brandon.
WHISPER: Hi, Brandon.
CHARLOTTE CHUCKLES
What's his blood oxygen level?
Yeah, OK. Yeah, I'm coming in.
Yeah, I'll be there
as soon as I can. Bye.
Sorry.
It's OK. Here you go.
Ooh. You have a nice
time with him. Thank you.
Sorry.
It's all right.
I didn't hear you get
back. Was it a late one?
Isn't it always? Tricky
patient, but we got there.
Looks like they're keeping
the street pervert busy.
I don't know. I feel
quite sorry for him.
He must be pretty lonely.
Thanks, Amber.
Oh, please tell me
I don't have her.
Bad news. Oh, God.
Who the hell is Mia Eldegard?
She's probably some agency
nurse who doesn't know
how to hold a scalpel.
See you in theatre. Yep.
Thanks.
JACOB HUMS
Oh, this is Leo
Pandian, Viraj's son.
Hi. Pleasure to meet you.
Hello. Pleasure to meet you.
Pleasure to meet you.
And this is SPOC.
SPOC? Single point of contact.
This is where you'll get
your schedules for your day,
liaise with colleagues,
deal with admin queries.
It's entirely your
responsibility to know when
and where you're needed,
are we clear? Of course.
Oh, and down there on the right
are the consultants' offices.
Please do not disturb the doctors
in their office unless it's urgent
or you have an appointment.
Are you listening?
Do not disturb doctors in
their office unless it's urgent
or I have an appointment.
Where was it you
were from? Sweden?
Norway.
Well, you might think
that makes you exotic,
but we have all sorts in here, so
don't go thinking you're special.
I wouldn't do that.
Everybody, this is Mia, our
new scrub nurse from Sweden.
Hello. Hi. There is tea
and coffee available,
but you will have to
bring in your own mug
as we are trying to cut
down on our use of plastic.
Unwashed mugs will
be confiscated.
Hello. Hi. I'm Yvonne.
Mia. Would you like
a nice cup of tea?
I'm more of a coffee girl,
but I don't have my own mug.
We've got plenty to go 'round.
Well, hello fair
Scandi maiden. Hi.
I'm Jaden. Ignore the
hideous old windbag.
So, you're from Sweden? No,
I'm actually from Norway.
A city called Trondheim.
And you? Oh, I'm a Londoner born
and bred, but I have been...
NORTHERN ACCENT: .. "up
north" for a long time now.
Nice accent. And you,
where are you from?
Christ, sorry!
Oh, sorry. It's
fine. It's OK. Erm...
Go and get changed.
It's fine. Sorry.
Hi. Morning.
I'm Mia.
Mia Eldegard.
Mm-hm. You're in
my theatre today.
Do you have experience
as a cardiac scrub nurse?
Plenty. Back in Norway.
Sure, but I imagine our
systems are different, so...
Norwegians have hearts, too.
Can't imagine it's that different?
Well, I will see you in
theatre for the team brief,
preferably with some clothes on.
Sure.
Please do not address
your surgeon in that tone.
Particularly not
in your underwear.
Morning, Gloria.
DOG BARKS
Come along, Mr Snuffles.
Nothing to see here!
DOG BARKS
You missed a load.
Henry.
I'm only ribbing you.
You're doing a grand job.
Well, my supervisor will be
along soon to tell me different.
HENRY LAUGHS How much
more of this nonsense?
Another 19 hours.
And then I'm a fully
rehabilitated citizen.
Not that thE street
will see it that way.
Well, more fool them.
How about a sarnie? Did
you make me one this time?
Ham and piccalilli, you said.
Oh, ruddy marvellous!
Don't tell your daughter
I'm feeding you.
She won't take kindly to you
wandering the streets to see me.
I'm so bloody bored, Alan.
Bored out of my mind!
I know that feeling.
I just wish our Sally would
hurry up and come back.
Sally's not here
any more, Henry.
Do you remember?
Oh.
That's awfully sad, isn't it?
It is.
Do you fancy a cup of
tea? I've got a flask.
Now you're talking.
Brandon, this is Mia,
the new scrub nurse.
Hi.
I'm assisting Her Majesty.
Watch yourself. She's a
bit of a ball breaker.
Surely you're not scared
of strong women, Brandon.
Is that how nurses talk
to doctors in Norway?
Is this how male doctors talk
about female doctors in England?
Morning, team. Have
you all met Mia?
Morning, all.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
We have three patients today. First
up, coronary artery bypass grafting,
followed by an aortic
valve replacement,
and finally a pericardiectomy.
Any patient concerns?
Yeah, I'm a little concerned about
the airway of the last patient.
He has COPD grade three, so it
might be a difficult airway.
I might be needed on site post-op,
so if we could move him to first up?
I'm afraid not. Sorry if that
means you need to work late.
Why not? Because I would like
Brandon to lead on the bypass
grafting, so I think it's important
we get that one out of the way.
What do you think, Brandon?
Are you ready to lead?
Absolutely.
Great.
I am needed in ITU. You
know what you're doing?
I'll be back to discuss the
grafting plan we made with angio.
Got it.
So, Mia, let me show you how
it's done. Suction, please.
How was your weekend?
Yeah, not bad.
Smashing marathon training.
Did an 18-miler on Sunday.
MACHINE BEEPS FASTER
What do you need?
More gauze, please.
Shit.
ALARM SOUNDS
Doctor?
Do you need the liga clip?
The patient looks oozy.
Erm...
Doctor?
Suction, please.
I need more light. I
can't see what's bleeding.
Get me two units
of blood. Be quick.
His mean pressures are low.
Giving a small bolus of
adrenaline to try and get control.
Get Ms Roberts back
here, and immediately.
You really should
try the liga clip.
Diathermy won't work.
It's suprasternal vein.
Shit.
Where's the bleed?
What's going on?
Bleeding from the
suprasternal vein.
Or it could be anomalous
vein. Diathermy made it worse.
Can we cut the alarms, please?
Don't do anything.
More gauze and hold pressure.
Yeah. Orange liga clip.
You burned the vein
and then retracted.
You should have clipped it.
Mia, get me two 0 Vicryl.
Mia, next one.
When you cut a vessel...
..you must always remember
there are two parts.
Great, Mia. Help me
retract the incision.
I see you've kept the
orange clips. Good thinking.
Yeah, we're looking good here.
Mean pressure is good.
Really great work.
Thanks, surgeon.
More suction.
Hi.
Oh, cheers.
Is he seeing someone?
He's got a really
smug look on him.
What's happening with the
divorce? Is it definite? Oh, yeah.
He's on the fast track
out of a 15-year marriage.
The girls are so upset.
God, I'm so sorry.
You see the corporate types
sniffing around the department?
Yeah, yeah, I certainly did.
Investors for the new wing.
Thank you. Thanks.
The Pandian Foundation.
I'm afraid we're going be seeing
a lot more of them. Great.
Why? Do you know them?
One of the sons vaguely.
Really?
Oh, well, look, in that case,
let me introduce you, because...
..well, strictly between you and
me, the new wing is going to need
a technical director.
Would it mean working
with the Pandian family?
In an ideal world, yeah.
Why? Would that be a problem?
You know, I appreciate the
thought, but I don't think
I could be bothered with
the extra paperwork. Really?
OK. I thought you'd
jump at that chance.
Sorry. Sorry. Excuse me.
Hi.
Who's that?
Mia. She's a new nurse.
Very talented, actually.
Is she indeed?
Right.
Hi.
I'm Mia.
Gemma. Senior management.
So watch what you say.
We just had our
first op together.
You were very good. Saved
you-know-who's bacon.
It was nothing.
So, are you settling in then?
Yeah, but I'm desperate
to find a place to rent.
Do you know anywhere good?
There's that house next to you,
where the gun toting school
teacher used to live. Gun toting?
You should tell you the whole
story one day. It's a wild ride.
And it's definitely available?
Erm, not on a nurse's pay grade.
What she means is it's quite
fancy 'round her way. No offence.
None taken.
I feel like she's
giving me the eye.
Doctors and nurses tend to
stick to their own socially.
So, I'm not supposed
to sit here?
I wouldn't get on the wrong
side of Annette. Oh, I... Sorry.
You're fine. Stay where you are.
Thanks.
She broke my heart and
now she mends them.
Dr Charlotte Roberts.
Look at you. Oh, my God. Leo.
Wow. It's been how long?
A little while.
I always meant to get in
touch. Let's not go there, eh?
So, consultant surgeon hotshot.
Oh, you can talk. You live quite
the life, you big globe trotter.
I've seen the pictures. Ooh, so
you've been stalking me on socials.
Ah! I might have.
Well, anyway, I'm back.
How come?
Dad's ill. Like, properly ill.
On the way out.
Oh, Leo, I'm so sorry.
He's just been admitted
here, actually.
Getting the best care, of
course. Oh, that's good to hear.
Well, I'll, erm...
I'll let you get on.
You've got lives
to save, no doubt.
I'll see you soon.
You will.
Bye. Bye.
How are we feeling?
MUMBLING OK.
It's OK, you'll be
fine for a minute.
On a scale one to ten, how
much pain are you in right now?
Eight, eight-and-a-half.
OK, well, let's see if we
can get that down a bit.
I'm going to look after you.
Ah.
Mm.
MACHINE BEEPS FASTER
ALARM PINGS
MUFFLED DIALOGUE
Mm-hm.
Yep.
And this is for the front? Yeah.
OK.
All right! Thank you. Bye.
Hi!
Hi.
Thank you SO much for the
recommendation, I love it.
You... you don't mind, do you?
As soon as I saw it, I
knew I have to have it.
It's perfect.
Oh, well...
Welcome to the street. Thanks.
Can I give you a
hand with anything?
Oh, no - I only
have one suitcase.
Uh, I left most of
my stuff back home.
OK, well I will
let you settle in.
Thanks.
Hi!
I am Mia.
I just moved in to 49.
I'm Alan.
Number 37.
It's really nice of
you to be doing that.
Do you fancy a coffee?
You look like you
could use a break.
No.
I'd better... better get on.
I won't bite, I'm
just being friendly.
Come on! HER FOOTSTEPS RECEDE
MUGS CLINK Listen, Mia...
..everyone will tell you, so I
might as well tell you myself. My...
COFFEE MACHINE BEEPS
..endeavours out there
aren't entirely public spirited.
It's community service.
NEARBY: I know.
I saw it on your vest.
I don't need to know why.
HER FOOTSTEPS APPROACH
We've all done things.
It's like Fort Knox in here.
Locks everywhere.
Is that Pete's doing?
No, I've just had them fitted.
Very sensible.
Keep people out.
Anything I can keep
an eye out for?
It's all right. Thanks, Alan.
Glad to have made my first
friend on the street.
Bloody hell. I know, right?
That's a bit keen.
It's totally weird.
She barely knows me, and
Gemma was just joking.
Hmm, I don't know.
Maybe we're just being buttoned
up and British about it.
Maybe it's totally normal
behaviour back in Norway.
Yeah, maybe.
I don't know. I'm not impressed.
Anyway, how the hell can she
afford that on a nurse's salary?
Hmm... Well, I guess we'll find out
more now that she's our neighbour!
Yeah.
Anyway, you won't complain.
A hot young nurse to
ogle at next door.
Oh, I'm too classy to ogle.
Ha - you are not!
What if she's actually
obsessed with you?
She's a stalker who's run away
from the icy fjords to haunt you.
Shut up.
Can you see if
dad wants a cuppa?
Damn, I think I've left
the teabags in the car.
Can you get them? Mm. Yep.
HIS FOOTSTEPS RECEDE
METALLIC SQUEAKING
DISTORTED VOICES ECHO
SHE SIGHS
KNOCKING ON WINDOW
DISTORTED LULLABY ECHOES
DISTORTED: Put it
down! Put it down!
DISTORTED SCREAM ECHOES
Lottie?
I am so sorry, we thought
he was in his room.
Oh, no, it's fine.
I'm just glad he's OK.
Dad? Oh...
Hey.
I thought it was our house!
No, it's fine,
Dad. Nobody minds.
Come on... Uh, can I offer
anyone anything to drink?
No, thank you. We
need to get him back.
Come on, Dad. Mm. Yeah.
Well, you know, why don't you
stay and have a drink? And I'll...
I'll get him back. Yeah. Come
on, Henry. Let's get you home.
Don't you tell me
what to do, lad!
I'll see you back there, all right?
Dad, I'll be there in a minute, OK?
I'm so sorry about all of this.
Oh, don't be. DOOR CLOSES
You must be really
worried about him.
Yeah.
The good days were outweighing
the bad until recently,
but he's definitely
getting worse.
I'm sorry.
I never got you anything,
what would you like?
Uh, just a glass
of water. Thanks.
So, what brought you here?
Just wanted a change,
and I've always fancied
living in the UK.
Why Leeds?
Actually, it was the first hospital
that accepted my application.
Thanks. But also, fun fact...
..my dad was a big
Leeds United fan.
SHE CHUCKLES Ah.
So, I grew up hearing about all
the players like Harry Kewell,
Lucas Radebe.
Well, you can catch a
match when he visits.
Yeah, no. That
won't be happening.
Wow, that's vintage. Do
they still make those?
Yeah, I don't do modern tech.
Really? Yeah, I hate it all.
I'm not on social
media or anything.
That's pretty unusual
for someone your age.
Come on. There can't be that
much of an age gap between us.
Please!
I will take the
compliment. SHE LAUGHS
FRONT DOOR CLOSES,
FOOTSTEPS APPROACH
You were gone a while.
Just being friendly.
So, is she a stalker
or not? SHE LAUGHS
Haven't worked that out yet.
How's Dad?
He's gone to bed.
I think he had a bit of a fright
when he realised he'd
gone to the wrong house.
Lottie... Don't.
HE SIGHS We can't
avoid it any longer.
You've never liked him, you
just want him out of the way.
Hey, that is not fair!
You know it's the
other way around.
I've always liked your dad.
He just thinks you
could have done better.
SHE SIGHS He doesn't
mean all that.
Lottie, look, I'm a grown-up. I can
cope with your dad's indifference.
But we are two very busy
people with stressful jobs.
Now... And he needs round the
clock supervision we can't provide.
Look...
..he's not getting any
better... SHE SIGHS
..so let's just do it now
while he can still adjust
to living in a new place.
Mm?
SHE SIGHS It's all right.
KNOCKING ON DOOR
MUSIC BOX PLAYS LULLABY
But you speak English, right?
Maybe.
Let's do that, then.
And start over.
So...
..my name is Isak.
I'm a psychologist, and
I'm here to help you.
We're not going far.
Do you want to sit
in the front? Ah.
Here we are, Dad.
This is your new home.
Looks awful.
And this is your
corridor, Henry...
..where I know you're going
to make lots of new friends.
Sally won't stand for this.
Mum's not here any
more. Remember, Dad?
She won't stand for it!
CRYING: She won't stand for it!
Calm down. It's a
big move, Henry.
And it will take a bit
of getting used to...
..but we're all here
to help you settle in.
Shall we get you a cup of tea?
Can we do that?
A nice cup of tea? Go on.
Hey, it's OK. Mm.
DOORBELL CHIMES
SHE SIGHS
Hey. Hi.
Um...
I... I heard about your dad,
and I thought you might need
cheering up or something?
Well, I've already got one
of those on the go, but...
..yeah, do come in.
Just as well you came round,
or I would've been forced
to watch a shitty romcom.
Well, then, I clearly
came at the right time.
Oh, exactly.
Cheers. Cheers.
Jacob not in?
No, he's out with the lads. Ooh!
Who's that?
Oh...
That's just an old flame
from back in the day.
SHE GASPS You look so beautiful.
SHE SCOFFS
And so fun!
Yeah, and look at me now.
Sat on my sofa
alone drinking wine.
Well, if you're missing your
youth, let's go find it.
And do what? Go out.
Oh, God, no, thanks.
I'm really not in the mood.
I can get you in the mood.
SHE SIGHS I'm not
even dressed right.
Well, then, go get
dressed. I can wait.
Come on, show me the city.
SHE SIGHS
Honestly, I am so out of touch,
I wouldn't even know where to go!
Some doctors mentioned a
couple of bars we could try?
I'm serious. Let
me cheer you up.
Just one drink.
HER WORDS ECHO,
DANCE MUSIC PLAYS
CHARLOTTE SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY
You know? Yeah, that's
exactly how I feel.
I don't want to be
responsible for another human
for the rest of my life.
Exactly! Thank you.
Honestly, wait till
you get to my age.
People are so rude. They
just ask you outright, like,
"Why don't you have any kids?"
"Don't you think you'll
regret it when you're older?"
That is so fucking rude!
So fucking rude. Unbelievable.
Oh, thank you. Oh, no,
no... Yes, yes, yes.
CHARLOTTE GROANS
Cheers.Cheers.
Oh, I'm too old for this!
Oh, you've got to stop going on
about being old, it's ridiculous!
You're young and you're hot!
Actually, I learned a
new saying the other day.
Which is?
"In for a pound,
in for a penny."
It's... It's "in for a penny,
in for a pound." Oh, yeah. Shit!
SHE LAUGHS Sorry,
of course. Yeah,
"In for a penny,
in for a pound."
In for a penny. Whoo! God...
MUSIC: Till The
Dawn by DJ Thera
I am so high
Whenever you are near to me
Swear I can fly
Without any fear and free...
Look who's there. What the hell?
Yeah, Brandon did say
they might end up here.
Oh, I see you got a better offer
than I night at home by yourself.
Yep! Huh!
You guys have been at it!
I'm fine. Don't judge her,
I'm a VERY bad influence.
I'm just jealous you got
her to go out drinking.
She always says no
to me! I do not.
HE SCOFFS When was the last
time we went out for a drink?
Well, you're here now, so...
We'll have three more
sambucas, please!
Oh, sambucas?
Let's make love till the dawn
Yeah, yeah
Let's make lovin'
Oh
Nowhere else I'd rather be
When I'm by your side
So, let's make
love till the dawn
Yeah
Till the sun comes up...
You know, you're one of those guys
that just knows how handsome he is.
I like it.
What am I supposed
to say to that?
I don't know.
You make a really cute couple.
CHARLOTTE SIGHS All right?
Oh, shit.
I've got to go show some face - I'm
supposed to be on a lads' night out!
Hey, I'll see you in a bit.
THEY MOAN
THEY LAUGH
What's your sex life like?
You are very forward.
Do you know that?
SHE LAUGHS So I've been told.
Is that...
..a Norwegian thing?
Or a Mia thing? Or...?
A bit of both.
So, go on, tell me. I
bet it's pretty good.
What do you guys get up to?
I'm NOT getting into this. I...
I have to be your
boss at work, so...
Hey, what on earth is Lottie
doing with that nurse?
Yeah, she's our new neighbour.
In your neck of the woods?
How's she paying for that?
CHUCKLING: Yeah, Lottie
thinks it's a bit weird.
I mean, I do too,
I suppose, but...
But I don't know, it's kind of
kind of interesting, right? Is it?
I mean, like, what's
she doing here?
Hmm...
Mm, right, you want
another? Want another?
Whoa, OK, OK. Home time. Sorry!
HE LAUGHS Home time, I think.
And perhaps you should
take Lottie with you
before she embarrasses
herself, OK?
What?
What? Says the guy dating a girl
young enough to be his daughter?
Yeah. Let me get you a cab. No.
HE SCOFFS Fuck off.
NO AUDIO
Subtitles by Red Bee Media