Hey.
Hi.
You look nice.
Thanks. So do you.
I can't deal with this tension between us.
Yes, it's awful.
- Then why didn't you say anything?
- Why didn't you?
I just did.
- Do you want me to leave?
- What? No, that's so mean. Uh...
Then do you wanna try and talk about it?
Morgan would literally kill me
if this party wasn't 100% about her.
Let's put it aside for now. We can table...
- Don't say it "table it."
- I wasn't gonna say it.
I was gonna say "table it."
So what should we do?
Fake it.
Nobody else is so beautiful
In the dark
- Oh, oh, oh
- Giving your love
Giving your love, giving your all
Oh, oh, oh...
Can I get a big smile?
Thank you.
Oh, baby...
Hello!
To remind you of who you are...
- Hey, guys. Thank you for coming.
- Andy.
- I'm just gonna...
- Hi!
- Hey!
- Hi! You're wearing white.
I bought it when we were in a fight,
to make a statement.
I didn't get another option.
- That's fun.
- Morgan!
Congratulations, you look beautiful.
We're so excited to be here.
This is an amazing engagement party.
Okay. Calm down.
Take a picture of me. Yeah.
- Yes. Oh yeah!
- You want horizontal or vertical?
- Actually, hold on.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- No, actually.
Oh, you guys are taking pictures.
Hey, let us get in one. Yeah.
- Okay, we got it.
- I think we got.
- No, I don't think we got it.
- Hey, buddy.
Oh. Guys, this party kind of rules.
Of who you are
Now, baby, like nobody...
This dress is really working for me.
Yes, this inappropriately white dress
looks so good.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Giving your love, giving your all
- Oh, oh, oh
- Giving your love...
- I'm gonna get a drink.
- Okay.
No reason Now, baby...
- Why are you smiling so weird?
- Huh?
You're definitely
doing something weird with your face.
I don't think I'm smiling weird.
Baby...
- I don't know.
- You okay?
You...
- The nose crinkle was off-putting.
- The nose crinkle.
- The fuck was up with the nose crinkle?
- Like a toddler.
When you lose yourself...
Am I crazy, or are we having a little fun?
That was me faking it.
Nothing has changed.
Oh. Wow, you're really good at that.
Come on. I don't wanna fight with you.
I hate it when people say that.
We don't have to be fighting.
The answer is right in front of us.
Say what needs to be said.
- Hey.
Hi!
I saw you two lovers
whispering sweet nothings.
Did you two just do it in the bathroom?
I know we're in the past
I should be okay with that
Something keeps me from letting go...
- Hey. This place is amazing.
- Hey.
- Yeah.
- Andy's a therapist?
Yeah. I think he, like, overcharges
his famous clients or something?
I don't know.
Are you having fun?
- Mm-hmm.
- Good.
Yeah, I mean, I just got here,
but yeah. Yeah.
And you. You excited?
Yeah, I'm so excited.
You know, I can't believe this is my life.
It's, like, amazing.
Yeah, it is.
I'm really happy for you, Morgan.
Hm. Good.
God, I'm just
really happy, you know?
This is what bliss feels like, I guess.
Are you crying?
Yeah. Yeah. Maybe a little. I don't know.
I'm just very overwhelmed and
maybe a little bit hungry, and I just...
I'm just so happy.
Okay. Take a deep breath for me. Okay?
What's going on?
Are you sure these are happy tears?
In another life...
Um...
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. I feel weird. I feel like...
like, maybe I don't like him anymore?
- Thank God.
- I don't know. I'm on the fence.
I'm not sure. You know? I don't know.
Whoa!
- Okay, yeah.
- Yeah.
Which way would you like me to push you?
Because I will do whichever way you want.
- Right, um...
- Yep.
I think I need you to push me
to break up with him.
I need you to tell me
all the things you've been holding back
because I'm pretty sure I wanna break up,
but I just need some things to push me
over the edge so I don't go back.
Are you sure? I will let it rip,
but I need to confirm this is not a trap.
- Yes. Give it to me.
- Okay, all right.
At Purim, he berated a waiter
for stepping on his foot
and said, "These are brand-new loafers."
I don't love that.
No. He also texted Mom one time
at 11:00 p.m. and said,
"I had the weirdest dream about you."
He did that to Dad too.
I have, like, 50 more.
Do you know what really bothers me
about him?
Is that he weaponizes things
I said to him in therapy
when I thought I was in a safe space.
It feels very intrusive.
You need to do it now
while it's still fresh.
- What? No.
- You need to do it.
- Here? No, that's insane. Joanne.
- Unfortunately, yes.
- Oh my God.
- Go. Go do it right now.
You're crazy.
- Hey, listen.
- Yes.
It is gonna be okay.
Are you okay?
Yes. Yes. I'm good. I'm fine. I'm great.
Go ruin Andy's life. Okay?
Okay. Okay, I'm going. I can do this.
Morgan's breaking up with Andy.
Deposits, my gloss is poppin'...
- What?
- Yeah. Right now.
At their engagement party?
Well, she had a strong feeling.
She acted on it.
Wow!
Imagine that's hard for you to understand.
Taking action based on a strong feeling.
Oh shit! This is my song!
- Hey.
- Yo, I, uh...
- Record me.
- I'm in the middle of something.
- Check this out.
- Doing what?
I see it, I like it
I want it, I got it...
Come on, Jo. Our situation is different.
You know that. I love you.
It might be hard for you to remember,
but you love me, too, okay?
- You can just admit it.
- Obviously, I love you, Noah.
That's the problem. Is this... Are you
worried about what people will think?
- Is this a people-pleasing thing?
- No.
Oh shit. I fucked it up.
Shit, I fucked it up.
Uh, start again. Start again.
I'm just trying to protect us long-term.
Being married to a rabbi
is a very specific lifestyle.
What if down the road you don't want that?
Rebecca said something really similar
to that at Miriam's bat mitzvah.
The way it shine...
You should marry Rebecca. I'm sure
she's still available. You can reach out.
Okay. I'm gonna go take a walk.
Actually, no. You know what?
Why don't you take a walk?
I want it, I got it...
Go cool down. Come back
when you can have a conversation.
I got it, I want it, I got it
You like my hair? Gee, thanks, just...
- Did you get it? Did you get it?
- I got it.
Nice. That one's going straight to grid.
- Yeah, baby.
- Might even pay to boost it.
Black card is my business...
Okay. Well, it didn't work.
We're still together.
What? How did he convince you to stay?
He knows all my behavioral patterns.
He said the inner child in me
is afraid of being in love.
I was, like, "Is the inner child in me
afraid of being in love?"
I don't know. I'm not a professional.
- Just marry him, I guess.
- What? I thought you hated him.
That was when I believed in love
and thought any of us get to be happy.
That was 20 seconds ago.
What is wrong with you?
Where's Noah? He can help us solve this.
Honestly, Morgan, at least
he wants to marry you. Okay?
You should be grateful
because a bird in the hand
and the devil you know,
and all that stuff.
Can you not speak in riddles
at such a crucial time?
At least he knows he wants
to be with you. So just marry him.
You can get divorced.
That could be your brand.
Yeah.
- Yeah. Okay. Maybe you're right.
- Yeah.
- I don't wanna be on the apps anymore.
- Nobody does.
Okay, well,
I'll call up the wedding planner
and book up Santa Barbara.
It's gonna be beautiful.
'Cause bank on me
Is the only thing I wanna say
Okay, I think I know what we need.
Oh, I'm listening.
Let's just give ourselves six months.
Six months to just enjoy each other,
and we can take all the pressure off.
- That is...
- Photo?
Big smile for me.
Closer together.
That's your big idea, Noah? To give me
a half a year to think about it?
- I don't think so. No, thank you.
- Thank you.
- No, I'm tired of waiting around.
- No.
I'm... How old do you think I am?
- I...
- You know what? Don't answer that.
No, I think it's a wonderful time,
which... Joanne! Hi, honey.
I'm eating the most fantastic thing.
Like a delicious noodle birthday cake,
and I love it.
No. Honey, it's kugel.
Not as good as the kind I make.
Why is Morgan even serving kugel?
What the hell is kugel?
A Jewish food that Morgan knows I love,
and now she loves it, too,
because she copies everything I do.
Okay, Grumpy. What's wrong?
Nothing.
I mean, I'm...
I'm upset because of Morgan.
She wants out of this Dr. Andy thing,
but she doesn't know
how to break free. Okay?
She doesn't like him anymore.
- Oh, that's horrible.
- She looks happy.
No, she's not. And I blacked out
and told her just marry him anyway,
even though she hates him, which I know
is terrible advice, but I was in a mood.
- Joanne, that's terrible advice.
- I know. I just said that, Mom.
Andy has this, like,
weird force of will though.
He would make an amazing cult leader.
Okay.
Fasten your seat belts. I'm going in.
I'd make an amazing cult leader.
I'm handsome enough.
Give me that. May I have that? Thank you.
Here, drink this.
- What?
- I hope it's strong.
Just drink it.
'Cause I need you to wake up.
Okay. Okay, Mom. I'll drink it.
I didn't leave your father,
even though I knew I should have
years before he left me.
And you know why I couldn't?
It was because I...
Well, all of us have these voices
in our heads telling us
we'll never find anyone else,
or we don't deserve happiness.
Or, you know,
maybe it's our fault we're not happy.
I just think that,
I don't know, maybe I'm just impossible
to please, you know?
Like, Dr. Andy puts me
on such a high pedestal. You know?
But that's not what you want.
You want an equal partnership.
Someone who holds you accountable,
but sees the best in you.
Don't make the mistake I made.
You know? Trust your gut.
Demand what's best for you.
I'm doing it. I'm doing it.
I'm doing it. I'm doing it. I'm doing it.
It's over. It's over, Andy.
It's over. Okay, no more. Hi.
I was... Hey, how are y...
No. No. Fuck.
What's going on?
Okay.
Andy, I am breaking up with you
once and for all.
Whoa, Morgan.
I know that you're scared, but...
Don't do that, okay? I'm not scared.
At least not in the way
that you're saying that.
I'm scared I'm not gonna
follow through on breaking up with you,
and that we're just gonna end up together,
and that's not what I want.
Oh.
Listen, Andy.
I need you to repeat
my words back to me. Okay?
Okay.
This relationship is over.
- Listen, you made me feel...
No, no, not that, just...
- I thought you wanted me to repeat...
- No, not this part. Just listen. Okay?
You made me feel like I was special.
You know, like, you saw
all the darkest parts of me,
and you found them endearing,
and I don't know,
it made me ignore things
that I should have paid attention to.
And if I'm being
really honest with myself...
Joanne's relationship
made me rush into this with you,
and I wanted to catch up with her,
but that's not how I wanna live my life.
I see.
Well, as your fiancé,
I am utterly heartbroken.
Um, but as your therapist, I am...
I'm really proud of you, Morgan.
Thank you.
So she, like,
really wants to move in.
It's not just she really wants to move in.
She wants to move forward.
And I do too.
I need more time.
How are you and Esther?
I don't wanna rub it in, but we've been
doing really well the last couple days.
- Really? Good. No. That makes me happy.
- Yeah.
I was getting worried we were gonna be
one of those couples
where one person wakes up,
like, 20 years in,
and they realize
they hate the other person.
So I just, like, took the pressure off.
You know?
Do you ever think
that it just shouldn't be this hard?
I don't hear melodies
I just hear words
When you say you love me
That's why it hurts
We used to sing symphonies
Now we can't carry a tune...
Hey, sorry to interrupt.
Can I talk to you for a second?
Yeah.
The way I used...
- Hi.
We have so many things going in our favor.
I know. I was just thinking that
'cause my mom was saying something
about seeing the best in your partner...
Ayin tovah.
To look at your partner with a good eye.
I do that with you.
I do that with you too.
We used to be colorful...
There are a hundred different ways
I could convince you to be with me,
but I'm not gonna do that.
Nothing good happens when it's forced.
I don't wanna be the person
who's asking you to be someone different.
We can't start our life that way.
You'd wake up in 20 years, you'd hate me.
Okay.
Sorry, so what are you saying?
I'm saying I'm all out of ideas. I don't...
I don't have any more.
There's no need to lie
The right thing's the...
- So you're just giving up?
- It's not giving up.
It's not giving up.
It is accepting the truth
of our situation.
Is this happening right now?
Are we breaking up right now?
I don't know what other choice we have.
I love you.
We used to sing...
But we can't keep doing this.
It's too hard.
Now we can't carry a tune...
Please tell Morgan
I'm sorry I had to leave.
The way I used to
I wanna hear melodies
Fourth time's a charm
Or something like that
Bleach on my cloth...
How you doing?
- I'm good.
- Oh, good.
I've noticed
you haven't been yourself lately.
Oh, that's a start.
So
I am going to stay out of your way.
Flashes of fire, but I'm coming back...
I've been trying to figure this out
for us or
for you.
Yeah.
Reigniting the spark, as they say.
Gosh.
You're the greatest guy
in the whole world.
And the best dad.
- And just a fantastic, lovable weirdo.
- Mm-hmm.
You've been gone, back
But can't let you go...
You've honestly done everything for me.
And I know how hard you've tried.
I do.
I did everything just...
But it's... But it's not working.
Can't let you go...
It's not working, and I...
And I don't know why.
But what I do know
is that it's me right now,
and I can't fix it while we're together.
I can't believe I just said that.
My love
You love me back...
That makes two of us.
You and me both
Have been intense
Took it too far and you know it
Spray paint the car
When you're hurting
Even though everything's burning
I want you to know it's all worth it
My hands are right on your back
And yours on my shoulder
Don't see eye to eye
But we're nose to nose tonight
Just can't let you go
Everything's on my back
You wanna dance?
Go
We dance in the smoke
We dance in the smoke...
This night is so fucked.
It is so fucked.
Do you need me to, like, beat anybody up
for you? Are you okay?
No, I feel pretty good about my decision.
People are probably gonna start calling me
the runaway bride or whatever, but...
This is only your first time.
It's not like this was the wedding.
Yeah.
Are you trying to give yourself
a nickname?
I'm just saying people are probably
gonna call me that.
Okay. I'll call...
I'll call you that if you want.
Dancing with you...
Hey, um...
I'm really sorry about Esther.
Yeah.
Know it
Spray paint the...
I mean, if she thinks
that she can just, like, go out there
and see what life is
on the other side without me,
and I'll just, like, wait
and take her back...
know it's all worth it...
she's absolutely right.
Yeah.
I mean, if this is for life,
I gotta ride with her.
You're a good guy.
It's almost like I'm too good to be true.
- Except I'm real.
- Okay.
I'm right here. I'm real.
Can't let you go
We dance in the smoke
Dance in the smoke
Dancing with you
Oh, hi.
Hi.
Are you okay?
You take my hand...
No.
- Do you wanna talk about it?
- No.
My mouth is dry...
You look horrible. Let's do you.
Let's go down to the water
The water...
If the world...
I think Noah and I are really done.
I can't really talk about it though,
'cause I'm afraid I'm gonna start crying.
That doesn't even make sense.
You know how when something big happens,
you start to think about all these little,
like, random things?
Like, I'm really gonna miss Shabbat.
Which is so deranged.
Like, I'm gonna miss being told to put
away my phone on Friday nights.
And I love being superstitious.
I say pooh, pooh, pooh
to things all the time now,
just 'cause it makes me feel good.
Of course. Pooh, pooh, pooh is so good.
So keep doing Shabbat.
You're basically Jewish.
I wish.
No. Joanne, I'm serious. Like...
I feel like you have this idea
of being Jewish
that's so much more complicated
than it actually is.
I mean, you feel Jewish to me.
You're warm and cozy.
You always wanna chat about everything.
You'd be a pretty good get for us.
Well, you're not warm and cozy.
Well, you're not...
Funny, see? You're funny.
That's Jewish.
You love to overshare.
God, no matter how much I resisted,
you literally forced me
to be friends with you.
Forced. I mean, you're a true kibitzer.
You're always getting
in everybody's business.
You ever heard of a yenta, Joanne?
That's you.
You're a yenta.
I'm a yenta?
Yeah, of course you are.
I mean, you're obsessed with your family,
even though they are so nuts. Jewish.
You're always eating the challah
before you're supposed to. We all do that.
Jewish. Like, I don't really know
what you're waiting for.
Whether it's a sign,
or the waters to part, or what, but...
The whole thing is just a feeling,
and enjoying all those little things
is the feeling.
With or without Noah, you're Jewish.
I have to go.
I...
Leave it on the line
See you cutting down
On things you like
Smiling like
You're not spitting out spite
I could hardly recognize you
No one's making you stay
Know I hate it
When you look at me that way
I try with you
And you're holding your breath
Too scared of where it's gonna take ya
Feels like you're looking for a sign
Like a green light, green eyes
Everybody has what you want...
Hey.
Hey, where's Joanne?
I think she left.
- She left?
- I think so.
Oh, I bite my tongue
Can you swallow your pride?
Do you really even want it?
Is it ruining your life?
Please love me
Love me like you used to...
None of it matters. You are my soulmate.
That's it.
I don't care if you're Jewish.
I don't care if you're not Jewish.
I choose you.
Every time.
Well, you're in luck.
How to love you
Tell me how to hold you
I'll be who you want to
Baby, let me know
Show me how to please you
Baby, this is real
I'll be who you want to
Babe, please make me feel