- [HIGH-PITCHED RINGING]
- [CREAKING]
[DOG BARKING]
[GROANING]
[GRUNTS]
- Ranger!
- [RANGER] Baba!
[BABA VOSS GROANS] Lion. Where's Lion?
- [GRUNTS]
- [BABA VOSS] Help me up.
- Watch my arm. [GROANS, STRAINS]
- [DOG BARKS]
- [GROANING, BREATHING HEAVILY]
- Here. Here.
[LU GROANS]
Lion! [PANTS]
Lion!
- [RANGER] Baba. Lulu?
- [FINGERS SNAPPING]
[BABA VOSS PANTING] Here.
I'm sorry.
[RANGER]
Whatever that was, it tore her to pieces.
[GROANING]
[INHALES SHARPLY, EXHALES]
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
What kind of creature did this?
They were Trivantians.
[RANGER] This far from the border?
It was revenge. For Edo.
- So they were here for you.
- [RANGER] Lu.
I told you
he would bring death to our door.
[SUCKS TEETH, GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING, PANTING]
I'm sorry about that.
She's not wrong. [BREATHES HEAVILY]
I brought them here.
And now Bow Lion is dead.
[SIGHS]
It doesn't make sense.
If I'm the Trivantians,
and I have this kind of power,
why wait until now to use it?
Could've obliterated you
and all the armies of Paya
at Greenhill Gap.
They didn't have it yet.
And now they do.
[TAMACTI JUN] Nellicut, Wallen and Yarnes.
- [MAGHRA] You know them?
- Yes.
All Witchfinders once under my command.
These are the men who killed Row Vano.
Followers of Lucien Bray.
[BELLS JINGLING]
Punishment for murder is death.
The punishment for being a witch is death.
If there were witches,
which there are not,
that law no longer exists.
[WALLEN] You may be queen,
but you are not our god.
You simply saying something doesn't exist
does not make it so.
[MAGHRA] It was spoken words
that declared them witches to begin with.
Words from the one true God,
and not the mother of witches.
- Heretic! [SPITS]
- [TAMACTI JUN GASPS]
[SHOUTS, PANTING] You fool.
Lucien Bray cares nothing for you.
He'll welcome your deaths
as martyrs for his cause.
I was trying to save your lives.
This is where a smarter man would've
begged mercy from a merciful queen.
Instead, you're gonna hang.
Not for your beliefs,
but because you're idiots.
[GRUNTS]
Tamacti.
How can I sentence them to death
when I spare my own sister,
who murdered hundreds?
- [TAMACTI JUN] They did burn a man alive.
- She's done so much worse.
[TAMACTI JUN] Maybe when they're killed,
you can find it within yourself
to deal with Sibeth.
So you think
I should kill them for practice?
No. What I'm saying is their deaths serve
a greater good, law and order.
And if your sister's death is
the pathway to peace with Trivantes...
So this has nothing to do with
her crimes against you.
I understand why you might think that.
But remember,
I didn't ask for this position.
I didn't even want it.
I didn't want this one either.
Well, then,
we can be miserable fools together.
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
[SIGHS]
You're thinking of going back
down the mountain.
[SIGHS] They did not bring the God Thunder
this far east just to kill me.
The Trivantians will be moving on Paya.
Maybe.
That's a problem for down there.
It will be a problem up here
when the Trivantian army arrives.
It seems as if they already have.
I am sorry about your home.
[RANGER INHALES DEEPLY]
I can build another.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
I have to go warn Maghra.
[RANGER BREATHES DEEPLY]
Then this is goodbye.
[FINGERS SNAPPING]
Thank you for everything.
[SNIFFS, SIGHS]
Your wound smells clean.
It should heal nicely.
[GROANS]
- Remember... stay alive.
- [GRUNTS]
Beware of wolves, Baba Voss.
[BABA VOSS] Beware of wolves, Ranger.
Goodbye, Lion.
[BLADE SHARPENING]
Who approaches?
[TAMACTI JUN] Those who used to serve
under me still know my voice.
We no longer recognize
your authority, heretic.
Regardless, Shiloh, I'm confident
your skull will recognize my blade.
What do you want, Tamacti Jun?
Just a word... with you.
[LUCIEN] We all swore the same oath.
I can't imagine you take any pleasure
in fighting your brothers and sisters.
I do not.
Yet you arrested three of us
who now await execution
by your heretic queen.
It was you who sent these men
to their deaths.
[LUCIEN] They upheld their sacred vow.
I'm sure that'll be of great comfort
to their families.
How many more of your own people
will you sacrifice?
As many as it takes.
And you should be standing
right here beside me.
Your queen has sinned before God...
Not here to debate!
Pathetic.
This ends today.
No more speeches. No more gatherings.
Retire in silence.
And if I don't?
Then I will retire you.
I was hoping you might say that.
[BOTH GRUNTING, SHOUTING]
[LUCIEN SHOUTS]
[SHOUTS]
- [TAMACTI JUN GRUNTS]
- [SHOUTS]
[PANTING]
- [TAMACTI JUN SHOUTS]
- [GRUNTS]
[BOTH STRAINING]
[SHOUTS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[BONE CRACKS]
[PANTS, GRUNTS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
[BOTH GRUNTING, PANTING, STRAINING]
[PANTING]
You've gotten slow in your old age.
- [GROANS]
- Still too fast for you.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
- [TAMACTI JUN SHOUTS]
- [GROANS]
[BOTH PANTING]
- Lucien!
- Stand down!
[LUCIEN PANTING]
You were a soldier of God.
A man of faith.
What happened to you?
I died, Lucien.
[PANTING]
I went to the place where the dead go.
And I've got to tell you,
it wasn't as we were told.
I was disappointed.
You were bewitched!
[SIGHS] Brother,
you don't know the half of it.
[BREATHES HEAVILY] What...
- [GRUNTS]
- [SHOUTING]
[TAMACTI JUN BREATHING HEAVILY]
Go home.
All of you.
[LUCIEN BREATHING HEAVILY]
[TAMACTI JUN] This church is closed.
- [HARLAN BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [TROVERE MOANING]
- [SCREAMING, MOANING]
- [HARLAN GRUNTING]
- [SIGHS]
- [BOTH PANTING]
You're very good at that.
- I like to think I'm a considerate host.
- Ah, but I'm still angry with you.
You don't seem angry.
I shouldn't be here anymore.
Well, I'm pleased that you are.
I'm serious.
I should be back in Trivantes
with Sibeth in chains. [SIGHS]
I'll have her for you soon enough.
[BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY]
My government is not known
for being patient, Harlan.
Well, in my experience,
patience, like most things,
comes at a price.
Keep talking. [BREATHES HEAVILY]
I will arrange for an extra shipment
of coal to be transported immediately
at half the regular price.
At no cost.
As I said, no cost.
[BREATHES HEAVILY, SWALLOWS]
And another such shipment
for every day your queen stalls.
- [GRUNTS]
- Are you trying to break me?
Oh, on the contrary,
Maghra has clearly asked you
to convince me.
Now I'm offering you
an incentive to convince her.
I suppose it's the least I can do
in the name of peace.
Mmm, that's the spirit.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
Now you can get back to convincing me.
[WOLFFE COOING]
[MAGHRA] He eats more
than both the twins did combined.
If you left him here,
you wouldn't be burdened
with his crying for me.
It's not as if I'm going anywhere.
Soothing Wolffe is not a burden.
Visiting you is the chore.
So I hear you've arrested the Witchfinders
who defied my edict.
Good for you.
[SCOFFS]
Tell me, when will they be executed?
Don't waver now, Maghra.
You'll confirm the weakness
of your character to all.
The council will eat you alive.
Some might think of the sparing of lives
as strength of character.
No, they won't. Not from you.
As queen, sometimes you have to do things
others might consider evil,
even you might consider evil,
for the good of the kingdom.
You serve no one
if you don't enforce the law.
No one would've dared do what these
Witchfinders did while I was queen.
[INHALES DEEPLY, STAMMERS]
And if I felt it necessary for any reason
to pledge the sacrifice
of my own sister to the enemy...
[WHISPERING] No.
...I'd make damn sure
I fulfilled that promise.
You don't know what you're talking about.
I know the Trivantians arrived a day ago,
and yet here I am, alive and well.
- You're here 'cause the baby needs to eat.
- [SCOFFS, CHUCKLES]
You have plenty of wet nurses.
Would you really use my son
as an excuse for your own failings?
If I were in your place,
I'd have handed them your head already.
They don't want your head, Sibeth.
They want you. Alive.
And don't worry.
I'll be out of excuses soon enough,
and then you'll be
on your way to Trivantes.
I'll be back when the baby's done nursing.
[FINGERS SNAPPING]
[SOLDIER SNORING]
[SOLDIER SNORTS]
[SNORING CONTINUES]
Don't raise your voice.
[SIGHS]
[GRUNTS]
You.
You can see?
You're Jerlamarel's son.
Oloman, right?
I know your sister...
Haniwa.
Haniwa?
[SCOFFS]
Is she alive?
She doesn't like you very much.
No, I'm sure she doesn't.
- Those fire weapons. You made them?
- [SIGHS]
I had no choice.
Well, you have one now.
- What are you doing?
- I'm cutting you free.
No, no, no. Stop.
[SIGHS] You don't understand.
They have my family.
If I run, they'll kill them.
Same way they killed my father.
Tormada killed Jerlamarel?
No.
Edo Voss did.
Edo?
Are you sure?
[SIGHS] I was there.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
- Those weapons?
- Technology of the ancients.
Compressed coal
that explodes when ignited.
They're called bombs.
I don't care what they're called.
You have to stop making them.
Thousands will die.
Where's your family being held?
At my father's compound.
[INHALES DEEPLY] Okay.
I will get you out of here.
You'll go free your family.
And I'll go back to Trivantes.
When the Triangle learns Tormada's been
working with the sighted to build weapons,
he'll be stripped of his rank
and put on trial.
[SIGHS]
You're wrong.
What?
Tormada just ended the Ganite War.
He'll be given a hero's welcome.
- He broke the law.
- He won.
[SIGHS]
Besides, we've already built
many more bombs.
[SOLDIER COUGHS]
[SIGHS]
How many?
Hundreds.
[SIGHS]
Okay, new plan.
We go free your family.
Then we destroy the bombs.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[MADDOX] Tormada will be disappointed.
He had such high hopes for you.
- [WREN GRUNTS, SCREAMS]
- [SHOUTS]
- [WREN STRAINING]
[WREN STRAINING, CHOKING]
He'll have your corpse to study at least.
[LAUGHING]
[GROANS, LAUGHING]
[GROANS, GRUNTS]
Oloman!
[SCREAMS]
[MADDOX SHOUTS]
[GRUNTS, PANTING]
I needed him alive, fools!
Stop her!
Stop! [SHOUTS INDISTINCTLY]
[STRAINS, GRUNTS]
You're getting pretty good at that.
- [HORSE WHINNIES]
- Thanks.
Is that Toad's horse?
Yes.
Did you ever imagine
you'd miss a Witchfinder?
I could never have imagined any of this.
Do you mean Wolffe?
- Don't.
- Kofun.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GRUNTS]
[CHARLOTTE] He's going through a lot.
[HANIWA SIGHS]
He is too sensitive.
Or maybe you're not sensitive enough.
Must you speak every thought
that pops into your head? [SIGHS]
Kofun became a father before he was ready.
He feels ashamed and confused.
So why is he punishing me?
It's not my fault.
No, but it is your responsibility.
Feeling responsible for someone
can be a great weight.
[SIGHS]
Kofun has his son.
You have Kofun.
And I've got you.
- [KOFUN SIGHS]
- [CHARLOTTE SCOFFS]
And how often do you punish me for that?
I'm sorry. I don't mean to.
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
Everything is a mess.
[CHARLOTTE SIGHS]
You're thinking of Row Vano.
They burned him alive.
They would have burned me too.
[CHARLOTTE] Hey.
I will never let that happen.
Don't they understand
how much easier it would be
for me to kill them?
[CHUCKLES]
[HANIWA]
I could kill ten a day if I wanted.
From a hundred feet away.
They would never know who it was.
And then you would be
everything they fear you are.
I think maybe they should start fearing us
more than they do.
Kofun.
Are you gonna keep standing there
pretending you don't have a son?
[SIBETH SIGHS]
Jerlamarel had his failings,
but at least
he never denied your existence.
[SIBETH] Mmm.
[SIGHS, CHUCKLES]
Come here.
- Feel him in your arms.
- I-I can't.
Try.
- Huh? [CHUCKLES]
- [WOLFFE COOING]
[KOFUN BREATHING SHAKILY]
[SIBETH SIGHS]
[CHUCKLES]
You made him.
[CHUCKLES LIGHTLY]
[SIBETH]
I understand this is difficult for you,
but we are your family now.
It falls to you to protect Wolffie.
And his mother.
Kofun, stay.
This is where you belong!
- Kofun, what are you do... [GASPS]
- I'm leaving.
[SIBETH] Trouble in paradise.
Haven't you hurt him enough?
[SIBETH] Hurt him?
I mothered his child.
I... I gave him purpose.
[WOLFFE COOING]
What is it in you?
This thing that needs to strike
at everyone around you.
I don't know.
Might be the same thing
that gave me the strength to rule.
That strength you so sorely lack.
I loved you.
[CLICKS TONGUE] And you still do.
[WOLFFE CRYING]
Oh, Wolffe. It's all right.
It was wrong of me
to allow you this time with Wolffe.
You'll only corrupt him.
As you have my son.
I'm not done feeding him, Maghra.
- [WHISPERING] It's all right.
- Give him back.
[MAGHRA] It's all right.
- He needs his mother.
- He will never know his mother.
I'm done with you, Sibeth.
You want me to show strength?
I'll start here.
Guard!
[SIBETH] Maghra?
Maghra!
[HARLAN] I'm sure the queen will be
joining us in a matter of heartbeats.
[TROVERE CHUCKLES]
You'll forgive me if I'm less confident,
given the queen hasn't deigned
to grant me an audience until now.
[HARLAN] She means no offense.
It's been a particularly bad day.
A bad day?
If I don't have Sibeth in chains soon,
there will be a lot of bad days to follow.
[SIGHS]
- You seem tense.
- [SCOFFS]
I am fucking the queen's husband
in enemy territory
while the fates of two nations
hang in the balance.
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
Fair point.
[EXHALES SHARPLY] Harlan.
All will be well, okay?
You just need to relax.
You're not making it easy.
You're the one who's fucking
the queen's husband in enemy territory.
My apologies, Ambassador Trovere,
for not greeting you sooner.
It's been a trying time.
Not to worry.
I am well taken care of by Lord Harlan.
Yes, he's much better company than I am.
Will you be joining us, my queen?
Unfortunately not.
There are some pressing affairs of state
that need my immediate attention.
I just wanted to come by
and wish you Godspeed
on your journey home.
I'm sorry, Your Majesty.
I-I would have thought
Lord Harlan conveyed to you
that I cannot leave
until my mandate has been satisfied.
- My sister.
- That's right.
And I can only imagine
how painful this is for you.
You can have her.
She'll be in your hands
by the rise of the God Flame.
Then on behalf of the government
of Trivantes,
I thank you for your hospitality.
Yes, thank you.
[BELLS JINGLE]
Well, that was easy.
[SIGHS]
- Hello?
- [DOG BARKING]
[BABA VOSS] Oh.
It's okay. No, no. No.
Good boy. Stay.
- Baba?
- [BABA VOSS SIGHS DEEPLY]
[DOG BARKING]
- [YELPS]
- Maghra.
- Maghra. Maghra, please.
- [GRUNTING]
Where were you? [SNIFFLES]
Why did you leave us?
[MAGHRA CRYING, SNIFFING]
[SNIFFS]
What happened to you?
[SNIFFLES] They found me.
Who found you?
The Trivantians.
You were in Trivantes?
No, they're here with a... This new weapon.
Something big, uh, like God Thunder.
Fire and force.
It... [SNIFFLES]
It ripped open the ground beneath me.
Bow Lion is dead.
What? What... Why are you...
What are you talking about?
It tore her to more pieces
than I could gather and bury.
All right. All right.
What... What is this weapon?
I don't know.
But they did not build it to kill me.
They will come here to win their war.
Baba. Baba. We are no longer at war.
I've spent the time since you left
negotiating peace with the Trivantians.
Well, then you have been lied to.
While you were negotiating,
those soldiers were
in the Northern Mountains
with weapons
more powerful than you can imagine.
No soldier can stand up to that thunder.
The... The Trivantian ambassador is here.
She seemed intent on achieving peace.
The ambassador is here?
You need to lock her up
and find what you can.
I-I cannot lock up Ambassador Trovere
without any proof.
[SCOFFS] It would end our treaty
before it's been signed.
You are not listening.
There is no peace. There never was.
- You have been deceived.
- [SIGHS]
Has it maybe occurred to you
that it is you who's been deceived?
Can you even be sure
it was Trivantians who attacked you?
- Maghra...
- Baba, you've been away for a long time.
You have no idea
what's been happening here.
You're right.
I was not here.
And I will apologize for that later.
[SNIFFLES]
But right now, I am telling you
that there are Trivantian soldiers in Paya
with a weapon
that will tear your kingdom apart.
You need to ready your armies to march.
You would have us go to war?
You're already at war! [PANTING]
And the longer you hide from it,
the more we will pay.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SNIFFLES, GROWLS]
Baba.
- [BABA VOSS] No.
- Baba!
[SOLDIER GRUNTING, CHOKING]
[BABA VOSS GRUNTING]
Where's the ambassador?
[SOLDIER STRAINING]
Huh? Where is the ambassador?
[STRAINING STOPS]
[GROWLING]
[SOLDIERS GRUNTING, CHOKING]
- [TROVERE GASPS, PANTING]
- [BABA VOSS SHUSHES]
- Be still.
- [WHIMPERS]
Are you the ambassador?
[PANTING CONTINUES]
That's right.
What is the meaning of this? Who are you?
I will be asking the questions,
and you will be answering them.
Wait, Ba... Baba Voss?
What is this?
- Harlan?
- Yeah.
Baba Voss? [GASPS]
- Oh, please, please don't kill me.
- He's not gonna kill you.
Baba, release her now
or I'll have you thrown in jail.
- Quiet.
- Have you lost your fucking mind?
Harlan, shut up.
I'm not gonna ask you again.
Good, 'cause it's getting annoying!
Does Maghra even know you're here?
- [BABA VOSS] Does she know you're here?
- Fuck you.
- [WHISTLE BLOWS]
- [BABA VOSS GRUNTS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [SOLDIERS SHOUTING]
- [BREATHING SHAKILY]
- That's a bad idea.
[BABA VOSS SCREAMS, GRUNTS]
- [SOLDIERS SHOUTING]
- [GASPS]
- [BARKS]
- [SCREAMS]
[SOLDIER SHOUTS]
- [SOLDIER 2 SHOUTS]
- [GROWLS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
- [BONE SNAPS]
- [SOLDIER 2 SCREAMS]
- [BABA VOSS SHOUTS]
- [SOLDIER 3 SHOUTS]
[GRUNTS]
[ALL GRUNTING, SHOUTING]
- [GRUNTING] Nice one. Nice.
- Nice, brother.
[STRAINING]
[SCREAMS]
[PANTING] The great traitor, Baba Voss.
I will execute you where you stand.
Ambassador. Ambassador.
While you're rightfully upset
at the intrusion,
I would just advise caution.
- He attacked me.
- And he will be made to pay.
- I'm just saying...
- [PANTING]
...we're in the final stage of a peace
treaty you've worked so hard to achieve.
There is no peace. You are a liar.
Baba Voss,
you have never been one for words.
Now is a good time
to keep your mouth shut.
Her army is in Paya
with weapons of thunder and fire.
Even now they are moving
across the Northern Mountains.
For fuck's sake. Thunder and fire?
What are you talking about?
I will not be called a liar
by this treasonous scum!
[SNARLS]
- [CHOKING]
- [SOLDIER GRUNTS]
Stop, all of you, by my command.
And Maghra. Excellent.
[HANIWA PANTING]
- [SOLDIER GRUNTS]
- [MAGHRA] I said stop!
Trovere.
Please.
Stand down.
[GASPS]
- [BELLS JINGLE]
- Stand down.
[WHIMPERS]
- Haniwa.
- [WHIMPERING]
In all my years,
I have never witnessed such a blatant
breach of diplomatic protocols.
He injured my soldiers,
and he attacked me in my own bed.
[GROANS]
Baba, what have you done?
You are being deceived, my love.
You've given me no time
to consider your words.
You left me no choice.
And you leave me with none.
Your reckless behavior has put our peace
and the lives of every Payan at risk.
Arrest Baba Voss immediately.
Mama! No!
[MAGHRA] Place him under guard at my house
until I return.
If he resists, confine him to the dungeon.
[BABA VOSS]
It's all right, Haniwa. I will not resist.
Ambassador Trovere, I assure you
I would never do anything
to jeopardize the peace we have forged.
Let me remind you,
in case you've forgotten,
your sister murdered our peace delegates
the last time our two nations met
under the terms of a truce.
I understand.
And believe me when I say
I am nothing like my sister.
I hope you will accept my sincere apology.
Forgive me if, at this moment,
I am not sure I will.
When did he get back?
- Tonight.
- [HARLAN SCOFFS]
Well, didn't waste any time, did he?
Harlan.
He may have just cost us everything.
Harlan, what if he's right?
You mean the Trivantians have
a new weapon of fire and thunder?
But instead of attack us,
they go all the way
into the Northern Mountains
to attack one man?
Yeah.
I'll see what I can do
to soothe the ambassador.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
[SNIFFS]
Whose baby is this?
We need to talk.
It is ours.
No.
Harlan.
Of course not.
- You may have abandoned me...
- [GROWLS]
...but I did not do the same.
Then whose?
His name is Wolffe.
He's Kofun's.
- Kofun's? [GROANS]
- Baba, there's so much I have to tell you.
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
Why is the baby with you?
Why is it not with the mother?
The mother is Sibeth.
- What? How is that?
- She seduced him.
- She's a prisoner.
- Before that.
Baba, we've been dealing with a lot
while you've been gone.
[SIGHING] Oh, no. [STAMMERS]
If this is Kofun's child,
then why is it not with him?
He's having a hard time
accepting the child as his own.
[BABA VOSS SIGHS]
And so the baby is in your care?
Where's Paris?
Where is Paris?
[BABA VOSS SCREAMING]
Sibeth!
[SCREAMING]
[MAGHRA] Baba! Stop.
We are turning Sibeth in
to the Trivantians in the morning.
I promise you, nothing you would do
will compare to what they will do to her.
- [GROWLING] Sibeth!
- Baba, stop!
- Where is she?
- Guards!