- [PEOPLE CHATTERING]
- [SIBETH BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GASPS, EXHALES SHARPLY]
[CHUCKLES]
[DOG GROWLS]
- [DOG BARKING]
- [BREATHING SHAKILY]
[DOG SNIFFING]
[ROYAL GUARD 1] Here we go.
[BREATHING SHAKILY CONTINUES]
[HORSE WHINNIES]
[ROYAL GUARD 1] Got something.
[BARKING CONTINUES, LOUDER]
Over here.
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[SQUELCHES]
[ROYAL GUARD 2] Check it out.
[ROYAL GUARD 1] Over this way.
[ROYAL GUARD 1] In the stables.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GROANS, GAGS]
[DOG BARKING, PANTING]
[DOG PANTING]
[ROYAL GUARD 1] Come on.
Nothing here but horses. Let's go.
Let's check this out.
Hey! Get outta here.
Find someplace else to shit.
[PENNSAN] Coming through.
[ROYAL GUARD 3] Thank you, sir.
[BABA VOSS INHALES SHARPLY, SIGHS]
- [BREATHES HEAVILY]
- [PANTING]
Listen, I have to go away
for a little while.
And I know you would like to come with me,
but you make too much noise.
Even when I tell you to be quiet.
Which makes it harder for me to kill
the people who I need to kill.
But, most importantly...
I need you to watch over this boy.
He's my grandson. Wolffe.
A boy named Wolffe and a dog named No.
[CHUCKLES, INHALES SHARPLY]
I know you will protect him
and keep him safe.
And if that evil mother of his tries
to take him again,
you have my permission
to tear her throat out
and eat her face.
Okay?
Good boy.
[GROANS, SIGHS]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
[HAWK CRIES]
[CHARLOTTE] I'm not saying I blame you.
I'm not one to blame.
I'm just saying
I'm surprised you left Maghra alone
when Sibeth's yet to be captured.
[BABA VOSS] Sibeth would be insane
to return to the palace.
- [CHARLOTTE] Sibeth is insane.
- [BABA VOSS GROANS]
[WREN, HANIWA CHATTERING]
I don't recognize this terrain.
Are you sure you're following the map?
[SIGHS] I have to make
a stop along the way.
[CHARLOTTE SMACKS LIPS]
This is not along the way.
[STUTTERS] Dad.
My son?
[KOFUN INHALES DEEPLY, SIGHS]
I'm sorry.
For what?
I don't know what I was thinking.
I... [INHALES DEEPLY]
I freed Sibeth.
And, you know, she's gone,
and it's my fault.
[BABA VOSS INHALES SHARPLY, SIGHS]
I have many things that I am sorry for.
Many regrets.
But I never regret anything
that I did for my children.
Okay?
When you were freeing Sibeth,
you were thinking like a father,
not a traitor.
You were doing it for your son.
Don't ever apologize about that.
Thank you.
How is your back?
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
Um, it hurts when I breathe. [CHUCKLES]
Yes. That pain is good.
It reminds us that we're still alive.
- [KOFUN] Yeah.
- [BABA VOSS] Yes.
- [GROANS]
- [BABA VOSS] Stay alive, my boy.
- [KOFUN SPLUTTERS, SIGHS]
- [BABA VOSS GROANS, CHUCKLES]
[HARLAN]
From the moment Sibeth arrived in Pennsa,
I knew she was gonna be a problem.
I just didn't realize
quite how much of a problem.
I'd like to think
I would've been more decisive.
- Maybe had her killed in her sleep.
- [CHUCKLES]
So, instead, you married Maghra.
Yeah.
Seemed the best way
to keep a seat at my own table.
And how has that worked out?
Has its moments.
And does Maghra know?
Know what?
That you're in love with her.
[CHUCKLES]
I suppose she'd have to be a fool
not to know.
Well, I think she's a fool for knowing
and doing nothing about it.
She's a married fool.
- And that's what I tell myself about you.
- Ha!
At least I get you into my bed
now and then. [SIGHS]
I imagine you're not as lucky
with your queen.
[GUNTAR WHISTLES] Whoa.
- Who's there?
- [SOLDIERS GRUNT]
- Calm your men. They're with me.
- Stand down.
Guntar!
Yeah.
Well, this is where I leave you.
- [GRUNTS]
- What? Where are you going?
Guntar and Pelz are associates of mine.
I'm gonna travel the rest
of the way together,
then I'll meet you at your house.
I can give you knots
and call you a diplomatic emissary.
No, we know other, quieter ways in.
It's better for all concerned.
- You don't trust me.
- Course not.
That's what I like about you.
[CHUCKLES]
[LAUGHS] Yes.
[FINGERS SNAPPING]
Come here. My brother.
[LAUGHS]
[KOFUN] What happened here?
[BABA VOSS] This is where we were attacked
by Tormada's bombs.
It's like the earth was torn apart.
[KOFUN SIGHS]
This is where Bow Lion was killed.
[INHALES DEEPLY, SIGHS]
This is a weapon of the ancestors.
Built by the Trivantian army.
They are called bombs.
[RANGER] I felt the earth come apart.
If the Trivantians have weapons
that can do this,
no one will be able to stop them.
We know where the bombs are.
We are on our way to destroy them now.
[LU] And you've come here
to drag Ranger into it.
Haven't you done enough to us,
Baba Voss? [SIGHS]
You fled Trivantes just as I did.
And when they invade,
you will find yourself back in there.
Mmm, maybe. Maybe not.
There's no coal in these mountains.
No fruit. Just the wolves and us.
And they have always left us alone.
Who cares who rules below?
- You say that now.
- [LU] I say it always.
We belong to no nation.
And we will fight for no nation.
Baba, you know I have no love
for the Trivantians.
But I have no reason to fight for Paya.
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
I will give you one, then.
Tormada.
Shut up.
Does it really surprise you
to know that he wields this weapon?
Fuck you, Baba Voss.
[RANGER SIGHS]
He'll come.
[HANIWA CHUCKLES]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
[CHICKENS SQUAWKING]
[SQUAWKING CONTINUES]
Did it have to be chickens?
[CHUCKLES] Chicken shit does
throw the dogs off.
Yeah, it throws me off a little too.
Well, you didn't give me
very much time to plan.
Fair enough.
[GUNTAR] All right, listen.
We're gonna be waiting
for you at the usual place.
Come and find me when it's time to leave.
Fine. What are you doing now?
Well... [SMACKS LIPS] ...I guess
I'll have to sell these fucking chickens.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
[SIBETH] Ah, ah, ah!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SIGHS]
[COUGHS]
[GAGS, GASPS]
[COUGHING]
[GASPS]
[GRUNTS]
[INSECTS SKITTERING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[COUGHS, SNIFFS]
Mmm! [SNIFFS]
[HUMMING]
[WOLVES HOWLING]
[HOWLING CONTINUES]
[SIGHS] You smell like a farm.
I'm painfully aware. Thank you.
So... [SIGHS] ...tell me about the Bank.
Her name is Nevla.
She's a politician but also a patriot.
If there's a rogue faction
in the government, she'll root it out.
If she believes you.
If she doesn't,
this will be a very short conversation.
- [BREATHES DEEPLY]
- [CHUCKLES]
[STAFF TAPPING]
Announcing the High Councillor, the Bank.
Councillor.
Roscoe, wait outside.
Ambassador Trovere.
I assume you have the former queen
tucked away somewhere.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
There's been a bit of a wrinkle.
- A wrinkle?
- [INHALES SHARPLY]
She brought me instead.
[SNIFFS]
And who are you?
I'm Harlan.
Lord of Pennsa,
husband to Queen Maghra of Paya.
Have you lost your mind?
I assure you,
you'll want to hear what he has to say.
Everything depends on it.
[THE BANK INHALES DEEPLY] Lord Harlan.
Your reputation precedes you.
Oh, that's unfortunate.
But I assure you, I am here to help.
You see...
a rogue faction of your army is set
to march on Pennsa
with advanced weapons
developed by a scientist named Tormada.
Now, these weapons have the power
to flatten buildings, cities even.
And, yes, they will attack us first.
But make no mistake,
this is a coup against your government.
You're insane.
- That's... beside the point...
- Harlan.
He is not lying.
[INHALES DEEPLY] The last Payan queen
accused us of drowning an entire city.
Now this Payan queen accuses us
of a sneak attack
with some fantastical weapon.
Now, let's be clear.
I'm not accusing your government.
Although, it's likely your buddy,
the Military, is involved somewhere.
You need to stop talking.
He needs to stop talking now.
Trovere, a word.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
[YAWNS]
[WHISTLING]
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
[STAFF TAPPING, APPROACHING]
[SIGHS]
[TROVERE]
My God, Harlan. Have you no fear at all?
Oh, come on.
She was either gonna believe us or not.
She doesn't believe us.
[SIGHS]
But she doesn't not believe us. [SIGHS]
She clearly senses something is amiss.
[HARLAN] Really?
She told me
Tormada is actually in the city.
He is scheduled
to address the Triangle tomorrow.
Interesting.
So, what do we do?
We do nothing.
We make ourselves scarce.
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
Nevla knows a military scientist
couldn't command the army
without help from someone higher up.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
She will quietly investigate. [SIGHS]
In the meantime,
no one can know I've returned,
or Sibeth's absence will become a problem.
Understood.
So...
dinner?
[HOWLING]
[ALL HOWLING]
[HOWLING CONTINUES]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
You're gonna make it very hard
for me to leave.
[TROVERE INHALES DEEPLY]
What if you just didn't?
[CHUCKLES] Didn't what?
[INHALES DEEPLY]
What is really waiting for you
back in Pennsa?
- [CHUCKLES]
- [SIGHS]
I have devoted my whole life
to building that city.
And the queen took it from you overnight.
Now you're a guest in your own house.
In a marriage of convenience.
None of which suits a man
of your independent nature,
if I'm being honest.
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
Leave it behind you.
[SIGHS] We can have
a wonderful life together here.
You can... You can build something new.
[SIGHS]
Trivantes has much more to offer you.
And so do I.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
It's a very appealing offer. [SIGHS]
[TROVERE SIGHS]
But not one you can accept.
It's my city.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
Are you sure this is about Pennsa?
Yeah. What else?
[SIGHS, GROANS]
She will never love you, Harlan.
[SIGHS]
And yet...
I can't bring myself to desert her.
You're better than she deserves.
You're better than I deserve.
And still, we both end up alone.
[RANGER]
Both of your children are sighted.
They're lucky you took them in
and protected them as you did.
[BABA VOSS] Sometimes I think
they would've been better served
if I had taken their sight as babies.
[RANGER]
We'll never know, so no use wondering.
[CHUCKLES]
When you were up on the mountain with me,
your heart was here with them.
Now you're with them,
but your tread is no lighter.
What will it take?
Well, ask again when we've destroyed
those weapons, my friend.
The weapons built by Edo's people.
So you still blame yourself.
You and I come from the same place.
We have enough to atone for as it is.
Taking on the sins of others
is just greedy, if you ask me.
But if you want to feel guilt
about something,
feel guilty about dragging me
from the comfort of my home
to go on this endless walk.
- [LAUGHS]
- [SIGHS]
[TORMADA] If you think about it,
it's a beautiful process.
We dig the coal out of the earth,
we heat it to the same temperature
at which it was forged
in the earth's core.
And that same fantastic, unimaginable heat
that once formed it
in the molten depths of our planet
now causes its immediate deterioration.
And with that deterioration,
we find the true prize.
We release the energy it's been storing,
like a hidden treasure,
since it was formed.
It's as though we were stealing
the very power of creation itself
from inside the Earth.
And then, of course,
we use that power as a weapon.
One that can obliterate our enemies
in a matter of seconds.
[MURMURING]
Which may sound like a nasty, unworthy use
of such a magnificent feat
of nature and science,
but when you consider the alternative,
the battlefields of bloody combat,
the vulgar stabbing and clubbing of war,
it's quite an elegant solution, I think.
Our victory was fast and decisive.
Only a handful of our soldiers fell,
while we decimated their entire army
in a matter of minutes.
- Their entire army?
- [TORMADA] Mmm.
You are exaggerating, of course.
No, he is not.
Dispatches from the western front
say the same thing.
Total annihilation in a matter of moments.
That's very impressive.
How many of these weapons have you built?
[TORMADA] Almost 200, and more every day.
Now is the time to act,
quickly and decisively,
and unleash them on our enemies.
Which enemies do you mean?
Well, Paya for starters.
What Tormada means to say is
the mere demonstration
of these new weapons
will allow us to change the dynamic
of our negotiations for the better.
[TORMADA] No, Councillor.
What I mean to say is that my bombs
will allow us to conquer their kingdom
and claim it as our own.
Your bombs?
[MURMURING]
You have forgotten your place, Tormada.
They are not your weapons.
They belong to the republic.
And how, and if, they are used
will be decided by this council!
Hmm. Agree to disagree, Councillor.
They are, in fact, my bombs.
They are under my control, are they not?
And as a decorated general
such as yourself would know,
whoever controls the weapons owns the day.
[MURMURING]
You insubordinate bastard!
- Tormada is right.
- What?
Our empire grows weaker by the day
because this council seeks
to appease our enemies
instead of defeating them.
What are you saying, Councillor?
I'm saying this council has lost its way.
Someone needs to give Trivantes
the leadership it deserves.
Careful, Nevla.
Your words border on treason.
Well, then, let's have no more words.
- [CLAMORING]
- [THE MILITARY] Nevla, what are you doing?
- Don't do this!
- [FUSE HISSING]
[CLAMORING CONTINUES]
- Trovere?
- [PANTING]
- We have to go. Now!
- W... Wait, what's happening?
We can't be here. Hurry!
Well, no.
Will you just tell me what's going on...
[DEBRIS CRASHING]
[PEOPLE OF THE TRIANGLE SCREAMING, CRYING]
[LEAVES RUSTLING]
[TWIG SNAPS]
[LEAVES RUSTLE]
[RABBIT NIBBLING]
[GRUNTS]
No. [PANTS]
[WHIMPERING]
- [WAILS]
- [THUNDERCLAP]
[INHALES DEEPLY, WAILS]
[HARLAN] Mmm.
[GRUNTS]
- [GROANS]
- [TROVERE] You're okay. Just relax.
[SIGHS] You've had quite a shock.
What was that?
It was Tormada's weapon.
He destroyed the Triangle.
What?
He killed the entire council?
Not all.
Not the Bank.
Nevla.
She was a part of it.
[TROVERE] Yes.
And so are you.
Tormada, Nevla...
and you.
The third side of the Triangle.
I was given no choice.
This has been planned
ever since Greenhill Gap.
The Triangle was corrupted.
Nevla and Tormada approached me
to replace the People.
- There was no saying no to them.
- Fine. Fine.
But what am I doing here? Huh?
What role do I play
in this little revolution of yours?
I couldn't leave you in Pennsa to die.
[HARLAN SCOFFS]
Are you serious?
You've just witnessed the power
of these bombs.
These weapons change everything.
Paya is finished.
Why die for it?
Before your queen, who loves another,
when you could live
at the top of the new order? [SOBS]
[BREATHES SHAKILY, SIGHS DEEPLY]
[KISSES]
I love you.
Oh, I've risked everything
to save you. [KISSES]
I'm sorry it had to be done this way,
but... [INHALES DEEPLY]
...now you have to choose.
Choose?
What?
You or... prison?
- Death, what?
- [SIGHS]
No, of course not. [INHALES DEEPLY]
If you want to go back to Pennsa,
I will grieve for you,
but I won't stop you.
[SIGHING]
You've always been a survivor, Harlan.
It's time to survive.
[THUNDERCLAP]
[PANTING, GRUNTING]
[TAMACTI JUN]
It's warmer inside the palace, you know.
Where do you think she is?
[TAMACTI JUN] I don't know.
Three times now, I've tried to kill her.
And each time she deserved it more.
And yet, as I sit here
and listen to this storm,
I find myself wondering
if she is warm and dry.
[TAMACTI JUN] Your sister has a unique way
of getting inside peoples' souls.
You think we'll find her?
After this storm,
our dogs will be useless.
She could be running west.
She could return.
She could be already facedown somewhere.
I just want to be free of her.
I suspect
we'll never be totally free of her.
Not even when she's dead.
You're a great comfort, Tamacti Jun.
If I relied on my charm,
I would have been finished ages ago.
[TORMADA] I want him gone. Immediately.
And by gone, I mean dead.
No. He will be an asset.
If you don't have the stomach for it,
I'll do it myself.
You will not.
I'm telling you, he can help us.
- [TORMADA] He is a liability.
- [NEVLA] Enough.
We cannot be arguing amongst ourselves.
Need I remind you, if we do not succeed,
we will be hanged for insurrection.
You speak as if
we were part of a petty coup.
We assassinated two-thirds
of the Triangle.
This is a coup.
And for it to succeed,
we need to gain the trust of the people.
The Payan queen's husband
will not inspire trust.
He will do exactly that
if Queen Maghra's own husband
has turned on her and joined us.
Oh, you overestimate
your own appeal, Trovere.
[SCOFFS]
She would undo all of our hard work
because she fell in love with a Payan.
Harlan is smart enough
to pick the winning side.
He is intimately knowledgeable
about every aspect of Pennsa's defenses
and mining operations.
He will be an invaluable asset
to our new government.
I am right about him.
[NEVLA] And if you're not?
[INHALES SHARPLY] I'll kill him myself.
Tormada rides out tomorrow.
You will accompany him.
If you want to bring Harlan along,
then so be it.
But, Trovere...
this is no time to be sentimental.
Hmm.
[SIGHS, BREATHES HEAVILY]
[KOFUN] How do you know Ranger?
We grew up together. In Trivantes.
Served together.
After I killed my father,
it was Ranger who helped me escape.
He gave me his own knots
to help me get past the gate.
Edo found out and threw him in jail.
[KOFUN] You must have meant a lot to him.
I owe him my life.
So, why does he hate Tormada so much?
Tormada used prisoners
for his experiments.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
He believed he could restore sight.
He never succeeded, but...
[SIGHS] ...many suffered in his attempts.
[KOFUN] So that's why he has
the scars on his face?
[BABA VOSS] Tormada cut him open,
over and over again.
Over many years.
Tormada sounds like someone worth killing.
Yes. Slowly.
And many times over.
[PANTING, GRUNTING]
Ah!
Ah! Ah!
Ah, ah! Ah!
[YELPING]
[SHOUTING]
[MOANING]
[CHUCKLING]
[LAUGHING]
[SIGHS]
[GROANS, SIGHS]
[GRUNTS, PANTING]
[LAUGHING]
[RATTLING]
[RATTLING CONTINUES]
Oh, fuck.
- [HISSES]
- [SCREAMS]
[GRUNTING]
[GASPS, COUGHS]
[INHALES DEEPLY, WAILS]
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTING, PANTING]
[SIBETH] Maghra.
[GRUNTS, BABBLES]
It won't work, Maghra!
[MAGHRA GRUNTING]
I will not be put down like this.
- [LAUGHS]
- [PANTING]
[GRUNTING]
I can hear you.
I can hear you, you dumb bitch!
[GRUNTS, SHOUTS]
[PANTING]
[LAUGHING]
[BABBLING]
I... [LAUGHING] Oh...
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SNAKE RATTLES]
[RATTLING]
Why did you stop?
[SHEENA] My mask keeps slipping.
Then work without it.
She can't.
If she breathes in any of this,
it will burn her lungs.
[GUARD] Stay at your station.
I'll just fix her mask.
[GRUNTS, GASPS]
[GUARD] Finish your work.
[GRUNTING]
- [GUARD] Lock her up!
- [SHEVA PANTING]
[GUARD 2] Go! You heard him.
[GUARD 2] Walk! Hurry up.
[WHISPERING] What do you see?
I don't see anything.
- [BABA VOSS] I don't sense any archers.
- [HANIWA SIGHS] There are no archers.
[BABA VOSS] No archers means what?
[SIGHS] It means they are fortified
with more soldiers on the ground.
Yes, my love.
You and Wren, take Lu, go inside.
Go find the children and bring them back.
If they are sighted children,
that's where I belong.
Fine. Gonna need a distraction.
[FENCE RATTLING]
- Form up.
- [GUARD 3] Sir.
Someone's at the back fence.
[GROANS]
- You two, come with me.
- [GUARD 3] Yes, sir.
[CHARLOTTE CLICKING TONGUE]
[GRUNTS]
- [GRUNTING]
- [GUARD SCREAMS]
[SHOUTS]
[GUARD GROANS]
- [SHOUTS]
- [GROANS]
They're not here.
Would they have been moved to Trivantes?
No. This is where they build the bombs.
They need them here.
Come on.
[CLATTERS]
[GUARD] Pick it up.
Now get back to work.
[GRUNTS, GROANS]
[LU STRAINING]
[SHOUTS]
[GRUNTS]
- [LU SHOUTING, STRAINING]
- [GUARD 2 GRUNTS]
[SHOUTS]
[SHOUTING]
It's okay. You're safe.
- [SCREAMS]
- [GRUNTS]
[GUARD GROANS]
- [SHEENA] They took Sheva.
- [HANIWA] Where?
The back of the dormitory.
They lock us there as punishment.
[EXHALES DEEPLY] Okay.
Um, take them to the woods out back.
I'll find Sheva.
[GRUNTING]
[GUARD SCREAMS]
- [BONE SNAPS]
- [GUARD 2 SHOUTS]
[RANGER GRUNTS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[WHISPERING] Sheva?
Sheva?
Sheva.
[SHEVA] Haniwa?
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SNIFFS, BREATHING HEAVILY]
What are you doing here?
[HANIWA] It's okay. I'm here to help.
- I don't believe you.
- I don't have time to argue.
We're here to destroy the bombs.
We already got the other kids out.
Just tell me where the bombs are.
- You know about the bombs?
- Sheva.
They're in the storehouse
behind the main house.
Okay. Um, head to the woods in the back.
My friends have your brothers and sisters.
They'll get them somewhere safe.
Oloman won't know where to find us.
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
Oloman is dead.
What?
How?
[HANIWA] He was killed by the Trivantians.
Sheva, We can't stay here. I'm sorry.
Here.
Come.
[KOFUN SHOUTS, GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
[BOTH STRAINING]
- [STRAINS, SHOUTS]
- [BONE SNAPS]
[GUARD 2 SHOUTING]
[GRUNTS, GROANS]
[GUARD 3 SCREAMS, GURGLES]
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
[GRUNTS] They're down.
- Who is that?
- She's with us.
- [HOOFBEATS APPROACHING]
- [KOFUN BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [KOFUN] Trivantians.
- [BABA VOSS] How many?
[BREATHING HEAVILY] Too many.
Everyone inside.
Ranger.
[RANGER] Okay.
[SOLDIER SHOUTS]
[PANTING] Harlan.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
Hmm.
[GRUNTS]
Oh. [CHUCKLES]
[LAUGHS]
[RATTLES]
[LAUGHING]
[SNIFFS]
[GRUNTS]
Mmm.
[CHUCKLES]
We are facing a crisis
unlike any we have ever known.
The Trivantians now have weapons
that can destroy entire cities.
They're coming to Pennsa
to do exactly that.
What do you mean, "entire cities"?
They've built weapons of the ancestors.
Weapons like thunder and fire,
capable of tearing up the earth itself.
That's absurd. They're lying
to influence the terms of the treaty.
[MAGHRA] I wish that were true.
It makes more sense than believing
they have this fantastical weapon
you speak of.
Your Highness,
let us not be fooled by their lies...
Please. Please.
I don't blame you for not believing.
It sounds impossible.
And no one will be happier than me
if I am wrong.
But it is my duty, and yours,
to protect the Payan people.
And I have heard enough
to believe that we are in grave danger.
So, as your queen,
I am asking you to put aside your doubts
and do your duty.
We've sent a group
to destroy these weapons
before they can reach our city.
But we must be prepared for the worst.
We are going to be invaded.
And if we have any hope of stopping them,
we will need not just every soldier
but every woman and man who can fight.
Lady Benik.
Will I have your personal guard?
Of course, my queen.
[MAGHRA] Lord Diego?
We will all yield our entire staffs
to the fight.
[MAGHRA] Lord Torrance?
My queen.
Tamacti Jun.
We will need the Witchfinders as well.
They must be convinced to join us.
You executed three of them
just the other day.
But I spared the rest.
We will have to try.
[LUCIEN] Great and mighty God Flame,
warm us with your grace.
Grant us the strength
in these troubled times
to cling to our faith
and execute your will.
Ever since Kanzua fell,
it feels like
the Payan Kingdom has lost its way.
The Payan citizens are counting on us
to hold the line.
So that's what we will do.
And I know, like you do...
we're going to get bloody doing it.
They've already hung some of us,
and we may all swing
when this is through.
But like you, I will die a holy death
before I live an unholy life.
- Lucien.
- Not now, Shiloh.
The queen is here.
Queen Maghra. This is a surprise.
Maghra is not your queen.