[FIRE CRACKLES]
[MAGHRA] I can't let him go in alone.
[TAMACTI JUN] It's too late.
By now, he's already there.
[HANIWA] Then we follow.
Kofun, Wren and I can catch up to him.
Even if he does kill Sibeth,
how does he think he's gonna get out?
[SIGHS] He doesn't think he'll get out.
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
- We have to go.
- Yes.
[TAMACTI JUN] No.
We have the entire population
of Pennsa inside this tunnel,
and we are nowhere near its end yet.
If she starts
hurling her God Thunder again,
this place may very well
become a mass grave.
There was a time to fight,
and that time has passed.
But my father is fighting.
Well, let's hope he's doing it
very quietly then. [BREATHES HEAVILY]
[BREATHES HEAVILY] You want one?
[WITCHFINDER] No, thank you.
More for me.
[GASPS, GURGLING]
[GRUNTS, EXHALES SHARPLY]
So, do we have an actual plan?
Find the queen and kill her.
That's more of a goal than a plan.
[BELLS JINGLE]
[TORMADA]
You're gonna frighten people with that.
People are already frightened of me.
[CHUCKLES] Yes, I suppose they are.
- But not you.
- Well, don't take it personally.
I just don't fear people
the way others do.
Why is that?
[INHALES SHARPLY]
You're not a particularly large man.
No. In fact, I was the runt of the litter.
But I was smarter than everyone else.
Smart enough to know
there were other paths to power.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
Edo Voss was a giant of a man,
but because of that, he thought too small.
He wanted to use the sighted
to guide his armies.
He didn't even think about the fact
that they could read the books
of our ancestors.
Unlock knowledge
that could change the face of warfare.
I spent my entire life searching
for a power
that didn't come from how hard
you could swing your sword.
And now here I am,
sitting across from you.
Able to destroy entire cities
without an army.
That's something Edo
never even dreamed of.
Which reminds me.
It seems to me we should have heard
from Maghra by now.
At what point do we assume
that she's made other plans?
Maghra decides nothing quickly. [SIGHS]
No doubt her family is trying
to convince her to fight.
But her twisted sense
of virtue will not be able to resist
the idea of sacrificing her own life
for her people.
[TORMADA CHUCKLES] If you say so.
Tormada.
Yes.
Have your bombs ready, just in case.
They always are, my queen.
It should be me facing her, not him.
Your sacrifice would earn us nothing
and leave your people without a queen.
So, I must surrender my husband?
If that's what comes with it. Yes.
No. [BREATHES SHAKILY, SNIFFLES]
Maghra. Stay the course. Stay the course.
This moment right here
may very well be
the moment for which you were born.
[EXHALES DEEPLY, SNIFFLES]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[PENNSAN 1] ♪ Let the river run ♪
♪ Let all the dreamers ♪
♪ Wake the nation ♪
♪ Come ♪
♪ The New Jerusalem ♪
[PENNSANS 1, 2] ♪ Silver cities rise ♪
♪ The morning lights ♪
♪ The streets that lead them ♪
♪ And sirens call them on ♪
- ♪ With a song ♪
- [GRUNTS]
♪ It's asking ♪
♪ For the taking ♪
♪ Trembling, shaking ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ My heart is aching ♪
♪ We're coming to the edge ♪
♪ Running on the water ♪
♪ Coming through the fog ♪
♪ Sons and daughters ♪
♪ Let the river run ♪
[YELPS]
♪ Let all the dreamers ♪
♪ Wake the nation ♪
♪ Come ♪
♪ The New Jerusalem ♪
[BABA VOSS]
This is her tent. I can smell her.
Then where is she?
- [TORMADA] My queen.
- [SIBETH] You called for me.
[TORMADA] Ayura, tell her what you hear.
Nothing.
Nothing?
No voices. No tools.
No sizzle of pans or fires in the pits.
No babies crying.
Just the muffled sounds of many feet.
Muffled?
[AYURA] Muffled by earth.
They're underground.
[SIBETH] Hiding.
No. They're walking.
A tunnel.
They found a way out.
Ah. You have them ready?
[EXHALES DEEPLY] I do, my queen.
Bomb them.
- Kill them!
- Fire!
[OPERATORS GRUNTING]
Fire!
[INCOMING BOMBS WHISTLING]
Oh, no.
Fuck.
Come.
[GASPS]
- She knows.
- [TAMACTI JUN] Yes.
Keep moving!
- [BOOMING]
- [GROANS, BREATHES SHAKILY]
I said keep moving!
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
[TORMADA] Anything?
No.
Don't stop.
Fire!
[DRUM BEATING]
- Ten-degree turns! Same distance!
- [WARRIORS SHOUTING]
Call it out!
- Ready!
Fire!
[KOFUN] Stop!
[GROUP CLAMORING]
- Kofun?
- Wait here.
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
Kofun.
We have stopped them.
[TORMADA] Excellent.
Hit them again.
Kofun?
Yeah?
Run! Run!
[RUMBLING, CREAKING]
Kofun!
[HANIWA] Kofun!
[GRUNTING]
[GRUNTING, GROANING]
You, uh, think anybody heard that, Baba?
[GRUNTS]
- [WITCHFINDER 2] Who's there?
- [WITCHFINDER 1] Captain?
They're between us!
- New plan?
- New plan.
- [YELLS, GRUNTING]
- Fight!
[TAMACTI JUN] Kofun! [GROANING]
- [KOFUN PANTING]
- [BABY CRYING]
Kofun! [PANTING]
- [COUGHING]
- [PANTING] Kofun.
- [BREATHES HEAVILY, SHRIEKS]
- [COUGHING]
- You all right?
- [COUGHS]
[STAMMERS] I'm okay. Nothing's broke.
- Are you sure?
- Is Wolffe okay?
Yes. [BREATHING HEAVILY]
We can't go any further.
We can't stay here.
[BREATHES HEAVILY] We'll be buried alive.
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
Her bombs are still falling up there.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
If it's come down
to choosing our manner of death,
I'd rather die fighting for our land
than hiding beneath it.
[KOFUN] I agree.
I agree.
Me too.
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
- [AYURA] General.
- [TORMADA] What is it?
- Fighting. Within the camp.
- Witchfinders?
[AYURA]
Not Witchfinders and not Trivantians.
Two men. One of them is very large.
Baba Voss.
They've infiltrated the camp.
Sound the alarm! Intruders in the camp!
[SOLDIERS] Intruders in the camp!
Intruders in the camp!
Intruders! Intruders in the camp!
Well, fuck it.
It was bound to happen at some point.
[SHUSHES]
- [BABA VOSS GRUNTS]
- [YELPS]
They have been through here. Let's go.
Baba, you dead?
No.
- Me neither.
- Head for the bombs.
- [YELLS]
- [GRUNTS]
[GROANING]
[GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS] Argh!
Thanks, Maddox. [YELLS]
[GRUNTING, GROANING]
[YELLS, GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
[GROANING]
[GROANS]
[YELLS]
You getting up? [PANTING]
[STRAINING] Give me a minute.
He's a big fucker. [GROANS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[INCOMING BOMB WHISTLES]
[WHIMPERS, BREATHING SHAKILY]
[BELLS JINGLING]
Maghra.
- Why would she come now?
- [SIBETH] Stop the attack.
[TORMADA]
She hasn't abided with your terms.
My sister is as simple
as she is predictable.
[CHUCKLES] She failed to save her people.
Now she will sacrifice herself
to save what's left of them.
We should continue the attack.
They still have an army.
And in a matter of moments,
it will be our army to command.
- How can you trust that...
- Tormada.
You've come inside me,
and you've bombed a city into submission.
I'd say you're having a good day.
Don't ruin it.
Halt!
[DRUM BEATING]
[TORMADA] Lieutenant Moss!
Every spare soldier should be searching
the camp for intruders!
Yes, sir.
You heard him. Fan out.
Maghra.
[CHUCKLES] I'm so happy you decided
to accept my invitation.
I'm just sorry that it's come to this.
Are you?
I know you think I'm wrong,
but, just like you,
I'm only trying
to do what I feel is right.
By killing innocent citizens?
Don't you ever get tired
of your own self-righteousness?
- I protected you.
- You betrayed me.
That was to protect everyone else.
And round and round we go.
Sibeth.
[SIGHS, SNIFFS]
Let me remind you that you tried
to overthrow me when you were younger.
And now you tried again.
And in both cases,
the dire consequences
of your insurrections
seemed to somehow surprise you. [CHUCKLES]
I wonder what it will take for you
to understand that you are not,
and never will be a queen.
- I never wanted to be queen.
- [INHALES SHARPLY]
I don't think either
of us really believes that.
[BREATHES DEEPLY] It wasn't enough
for you to be the favorite child.
You needed to have everything
that was mine.
Oh, this isn't about us.
- It's not?
- [BREATHES SHAKILY] Sibeth.
We can fix this.
There is still a chance
for everyone to get what they want.
I already have what I want.
You won't kill me.
You might hate me,
but I know you still love me.
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
[BREATHES SHAKILY] You never did suffer
from a lack of confidence. [CHUCKLES]
You're still the sister
I have loved my whole life.
Who braided my hair.
Who made puppets for me.
Who brought me into her bed
when it thundered.
My sister.
Who sung me to sleep
the night Mother died.
Never losing patience.
Never once letting go of my hand.
[SNIFFLES]
[SINGING]
♪ Star shining bright above you ♪
♪ Night breezes seem to whisper ♪
[TOGETHER] ♪ I love you ♪
♪ Birds singing in the sycamore tree ♪
♪ Dream a little dream of me ♪
[SOBBING]
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
I still have to kill you. [WHIMPERING]
There's no other way. [WHIMPERS]
I know. I know.
[SOBBING]
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
[WAILING]
[SNIFFLES]
[GASPS]
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[SOBBING, WHIMPERING]
- [CHUCKLES]
- [BREATHES HEAVILY]
[SOBBING, BREATHING HEAVILY]
Is it done, my queen?
[PANTING] I am not your queen!
Kill her.
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
[YELLING, GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
- Maghra!
- Tamacti.
Formation!
[YELLING]
- [BREATHES HEAVILY] Tamacti.
- [TAMACTI] Right beside you.
- Ready! And!
- [GRUNTING]
- Well, you wanted a fight.
- [BREATHES HEAVILY] That I did.
- [TAMACTI JUN] Kofun!
- Here.
Move!
[GRUNTS]
Resume the attack!
[YELLING, GRUNTING]
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
[CITIZENS SCREAMING, CLAMORING]
[GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
- [GRUNTING]
- [GROANING]
[TORMADA] Fire those bombs!
Flatten the fucking city!
Tormada.
- Tormada!
- Baba Voss!
I was hoping I'd run into you.
[GRUNTING]
Dad!
[GRUNTS]
Stop them!
[GASPS]
Baba Voss! Are you still with us?
- I won't make the same mistake twice.
- Tormada!
[GRUNTS] No! No! No!
[COUGHING] Oh, God!
Fuck! [GROANING]
[GRUNTING]
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
[INCOMING BOMBS WHISTLING]
[VILLAGERS SCREAMING, CRYING]
[GASPING]
[GRUNTING]
[BREATHES HEAVILY] Papa!
- How are you hurt? [BREATHES HEAVILY]
- [GRUNTS]
I am fine.
Do not follow me.
- Where are you going?
- To end this.
Papa, you cannot go.
You are too badly hurt.
Do not follow me.
I will stay with you. [INHALES SHARPLY]
No. I need you to stay here.
I need you to protect me
with your arrows like you always have.
[SOBBING]
[BREATHES HEAVILY] Haniwa.
- [SOBBING]
- [SHUSHES] I love you.
Look at me. I love you.
[SNIFFLES] Remember what I taught you.
[GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
[YELLING]
[GRUNTING, BREATHES HEAVILY]
[GRUNTING]
I am Baba Voss. [GRUNTS]
[SOLDIERS GRUNTING]
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
[SOLDIER YELLING]
[GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [SOLDIERS YELLING]
- [MAGHRA GRUNTING]
[GRUNTING]
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
Maghra.
[PANTING]
Baba.
I see you.
[GRUNTING]
Dad!
[SOBBING] Papa.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
[SHOUTS]
[RHYTHMIC POUNDING]
[MAGHRA] I walk now, every morning,
past the shops and the homes.
I can hear the families inside...
Talking. Sleeping.
Laughing. Crying.
When I listen to them,
I feel like a mother who wakes up at night
to make sure her baby is still breathing.
I know I'm not really outside
to hear them.
It's you I am seeking.
Some last echo of you still bouncing
between the mountains.
You have left behind a vast emptiness
that wakes me up every morning
and forces me outside.
You never wanted any of this.
I know that.
And every day,
I think about what was taken from you.
What I took from you...
in the service of this crown
I'm not even sure I deserve.
Your children feel your absence
every bit as much as I do.
But their futures,
the ones you gave your life to ensure,
stretch out before them
with infinite promise.
Your daughter has followed
in her mother's footsteps
and married a Trivantian.
Two sighted women making their way
in this world.
It won't be easy, and I fear for them.
But I hear the love in their voices
when they speak.
And it warms me to know our Haniwa
has found such a love.
[CHUCKLES]
Shh.
Kofun is coming into his own as a father.
And I know having a son means
not a day will go by
that he doesn't think of his own father.
I find myself drawn
to this terrible place...
whose charred soil holds the remains
of both my sister and my husband.
[CRIES]
And I wonder how anything
will ever grow again in this burned,
ruined earth.
[SNIFFLES]
[INHALES DEEPLY]
I don't know where we go when we die.
But wherever you are,
I hope you have finally found
the peace you tried so hard
to find in life.
- [SIGHS]
- For you and for all of us.
And I hope you can forgive me.
[INHALES DEEPLY, SIGHS]
[NEVLA] No one is denying
the debt we owe Paya
for defeating Tormada
and destroying his weapons.
I myself barely escaped his attack
on our own government.
[MAGHRA] Mmm.
[NEVLA] However, we cannot sign this,
or any treaty,
with a nation that will allow sanctuary
to the sighted.
We've all just borne witness
to the destructive power of vision.
It is the position
of the Trivantian people
that vision simply poses too much
of a risk to all of us.
I understand your position.
But it was not vision
that built Tormada's bombs,
but Tormada's cruel exploitation
of sighted children
that accessed the knowledge
of the ancients.
And it is that destructive knowledge,
not vision itself,
that needs to be outlawed.
The sighted will always be the gateway
to this knowledge.
And there will always
be people like Tormada
who would choose to exploit them.
We stand with three sighted people,
all of whom have played a significant role
in defeating Tormada
- and destroying his bombs.
- [NEVLA] Yes.
And as we said earlier,
we will grant them amnesty.
Why should we need amnesty?
We haven't done anything wrong.
Uh, in fact, i-if it weren't for us,
then Tormada and his bombs
would be destroying your city right now.
Haniwa, now is not the time.
- No? When is the right time?
- [NEVLA] Princess!
I fear you have forgotten
who you're talking to.
I think it is you who has forgotten.
Ambassador, I apologize...
Vision is not coming back!
It's already here.
And if I were you,
I'd be grateful
that we are offering you peace,
because trust me,
you do not want us as an enemy.
- Was that a threat?
- Of course not...
Ambassador, I apologize.
You must understand,
my sister and I have been hunted
our entire lives
simply because of how we were born.
The idea that I
or anyone like me would be a threat
to the unsighted is based simply
on superstition and fear,
and not the reality of who I am.
Because who I am has nothing to do
with the fact that I can see.
I'm a son.
I'm a father.
I'm a Payan.
But most importantly,
I'm your partner in peace.
So, please. [CLICKS FINGERS]
May we continue?
Very well.
Haniwa.
Tak.
- [SIGHS DEEPLY]
- Did she accept?
They agreed to talk more about it
down the road.
But for now?
She has no choice.
She has to think of the kingdom.
We cannot afford another war.
She promised to protect us.
[KOFUN]
She has an entire kingdom to protect.
And as prince and princess, so do we.
You don't really think that you're going
to be king here, do you?
[SIGHS] One of us will succeed Mom.
The people of Paya
would never allow a sighted king.
And even if they did,
the Trivantians wouldn't allow it.
You heard what they said there.
Forget being king or queen, Kofun.
They don't even want us to exist!
- Why are you so angry?
- Why are you not?
We will never belong here.
This isn't our world.
This is where my family is.
[SIGHS]
This is where I'll raise my son.
Your son will always live
in a different world than you.
[SIGHS, SCOFFS]
My children will never forgive me.
You saved thousands of lives,
including theirs.
You formed the beginnings
of a true dialogue with Trivantes.
But vision is once again forbidden.
When I was young,
my father used to fish for salmon.
Every autumn,
he'd bring me down to the river,
and we'd fish.
For the first few days,
we'd usually catch nothing.
Then one day, we'd catch one.
Two.
Hardly enough for a household.
But enough to know
that the next day there'd be more.
Five salmon, ten salmon.
Soon the entire river
would be teeming with salmon.
Vision is coming back.
You and I have met
the first few fish swimming upstream.
More will come.
Some are, no doubt, already here.
Others will follow.
No law, no religion will stop it.
How we choose to handle it
within our borders is our business.
The Trivantians
made their position very clear.
Politicians following a script
they know nothing about.
The war over vision will be fought,
not between Paya and Trivantes,
but within cities.
Within families.
Within our own hearts.
Regardless, nature will have its way.
She always does.
Well...
you seem to have made
your own peace with it.
The single advantage
to being as horribly wrong
as I've been in my life
is that new ideas are easier to accept.
[SNIFFLING]
[SIGHS] Smells like death.
I think Baba always knew
he would die in battle.
He told me once,
death must be earned
every bit as much as life.
With his last breath,
he defeated an entire army.
And by doing so, saved us all.
I think his death was well earned.
You sound a bit envious.
[CHUCKLES] Maybe.
But while I'm still walking here
on this earth,
I'll do my best
to keep you out of trouble.
[SIGHS]
I would be lost without you, Tamacti.
How so very sad for both of us.
[CHUCKLES]
[MAGHRA] I miss him, Ranger.
Baba was a giant man,
so it makes sense
that there's a giant-sized hole
in the space he used to fill.
[SIGHS]
You know, Baba died for you.
For all of us.
But it's important
to remember not that he died for you,
but that he lived for you.
If he was here, that's what he would say.
I hear Lu has arrived.
Yes.
Yes, we head home tomorrow.
You're welcome to stay.
[LAUGHS]
Thanks, um, but, uh, Lu and I,
we don't like crowds or people,
you know, crowds of people.
- Mmm.
- [CHUCKLES]
Well, I could give you a horse.
- Nah. [LAUGHS]
- [CHUCKLES]
- The wolves will just eat it.
[CHUCKLES, SNIFFLES]
[CHARLOTTE] Haniwa!
Charlotte?
[GASPS]
- [CHUCKLES]
- Haniwa!
Charlotte! [LAUGHS]
[CHUCKLES] Hey.
[SIGHS] I didn't know
if you were coming back.
Nah, I'm not back. Not for long anyway.
I just needed to make sure you were okay.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm so sorry to hear about Baba.
Ah.
Then I heard that you
and Wren got married,
and I'm so happy about that.
And now I don't know if I should talk
about the sad thing first
and then the happy thing?
Or do it the other way,
or maybe you don't wanna talk
about it at all.
[CHUCKLING]
How did it go with the Compass?
How are Sheva and the kids?
Well, the little ones are great.
[SIGHS] I don't think Sheva
likes me very much.
But I don't like her either,
so, you know, that'll work out.
Oh. She asked me to give you this.
She said you'd know what it means.
[CHUCKLES]
She wishes you a safe journey.
So... I take it you're going somewhere?
Will you come with us?
Not this time.
- But it's nice to be asked.
- [CHUCKLES]
Who will keep me safe?
- [CHUCKLES, SNIFFLES]
- You have Wren for that now.
And she has you.
I am needed at the Compass.
Jerlamarel's children
will be keeping us busy and...
I get the feeling more will be coming.
They are lucky to have you.
- Ugh, tell that to them.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Little fuckers. [CHUCKLES]
You be careful out there.
You too.
[SOBS]
[HANIWA] Thank you.
[SIGHS]
[CHARLOTTE] It was my pleasure.
I'm not crying.
Will you come find me?
You're the sighted one. [CHUCKLES]
You come find me.
[CHUCKLES]
[SIGHS]
[WREN] Are you sure
you don't want to say goodbye?
It wouldn't go well.
[SIGHS]
I'll see them again.
[MAGHRA] It's getting chilly.
Winter will be here soon.
[KOFUN] Mmm.
It's been almost a year
and still no word from Haniwa.
It could be a while till we hear from her.
Do you ever think about the Alkenny?
Every day.
Just the four of us, always together.
I'm sure we were sometimes cold,
but in my memories it's always warm.
[KOFUN SIGHS]
I thought when I became queen,
I would be able to give us that.
But once we set out
to find the Lavender road,
we were never going
to be that family again.
No.
But we are still a family.
[SNIFFLES]
You handle yourself well with the council.
You've earned their trust.
Maybe... you were born to do this.
Well, Haniwa says the kingdom
would never accept a sighted king.
What do you say?
I know what Dad would say. He would say,
"Think like a blind man.
Your eyes betray you." [CHUCKLES]
I think my eyes have betrayed me.
And they will again.
What are you saying?
[SIGHS] My mother is queen.
My father died trying
to save this kingdom.
If they weren't my people before,
they are now.
I can't fully serve the people or my son
if my sense
of the world is different from theirs.
I'm saying, I think I've seen enough.
I want to live in the same world
as my son.
I want to hear, feel, smell what he does.
[MAGHRA] Kofun.
There's no going back.
You'd have to be absolutely sure.
[KOFUN] I'm sure.
You made it.
You know us?
[GROUP MEMBER] No. Not yet anyway.
But I am so glad you found us.
As I'm sure you can imagine,
everyone here has been
on a journey very similar to your own.
I am Michaela. And you are?
Haniwa.
Wren.
Welcome, Haniwa and Wren.
Well, don't just stand there.
Come down and meet everyone.
[CHUCKLES]
Welcome.
Hi.
Hi. Good to see you. [CHUCKLES]
Hi. [CHUCKLES]