♪ Hey, once I was a boogie singer ♪
♪ Playing in a rock n' roll band. ♪
♪ Play that funky music, white boy ♪
♪ Play that funky music right. ♪
Come on. Come on.
Where the fuck are you?
I think my husband's having an affair.
With a perky-breasted 25-year-old.
It's disappointingly unoriginal.
Question. What tips would
you give your younger self?
Have more fun.
What about you?
Have less fun.
And don't worry what
people think about you.
And... while I think of it, not
to bother with contraception.
- Really?
- Yeah. All those years on the pill!
Turns out, despite my womanly
hips, as the old cow used to say,
it wasn't quite that easy.
I quite... liked your womanly hips.
Are you flirting with me?
Oh, Dougie...
- I'm gonna get that.
- Yeah, I know.
Yeah.
Hello?
Connie!
Connie! Connie!
No sign?
CCTV tracked her to the gates.
The police are bringing dogs.
She slipped away when
the fire engines arrived.
She's still on the grounds.
- Give me a sec, yeah?
- All right.
Connie? Connie? It's me.
Connie, you have to
come down from there.
I did it. I drove them off the bridge.
- Are they going to die?
- No. No.
They, they were in induced comas
in hospital, but they're fine.
They're alive.
Can I see her? Please,
I need to see her.
I want to see Annie.
You know you can't, Connie...
You need to come down from there.
- I'm gonna call the front desk, OK?
- I'll jump. I'm gonna jump.
No. No. No. Please don't do that.
Please don't do that. Stay there.
Oh, Christ...
I should be dead.
I wish I was dead.
I want to die.
We all deserve forgiveness, Connie.
- What would you know?
- I do know.
Because I've done terrible things.
I promise you you're
not alone. Listen to me.
I'm going to tell you
about this woman, Connie,
who's just had a baby.
A beautiful, tiny baby girl.
And this woman is so happy,
because it's what she's
wanted for so many years.
But... as the months go by, she
becomes more and more exhausted,
because the baby will only
sleep for one hour at a time.
And the woman becomes depressed
and ashamed of her depression,
because she's a woman who can fix
anything, but she's truly failing.
So, she...
She takes anti-depressants
and pills to send her to sleep,
and pills to keep her awake.
The baby is a toddler now,
but still she doesn't sleep.
Only now, she's having tantrums.
Awful, screaming tantrums.
And nothing in this mother's
life has prepared her for this.
All of her logic, her
usual tactics, her patience,
- none of it has any effect...
- Dr Robertson?
OK, Connie, down you get.
The corticosteroids
were for the alopecia.
And the lorazepam on the same date?
Well, the antidepressants
weren't proving sufficient.
She was very anxious.
And did you warn her
about possible addiction
and the side effects of lorazepam?
Of course I did. As and when required.
I think we could have had this
conversation over the phone.
And what does "as and
when required" mean?
How often was she taking them?
Why not speak to her husband?
Though I would suggest a different tone,
I think he's been through enough.
The guidelines recommend
that no-one's on lorazepam
for more than four weeks.
You've prescribed them three
times over three months.
Thank you for your time.
You know, all of us at the
school are very shocked.
It's an exceptionally
tight community around here.
It's not that tight, though, is it?
She slipped and no-one caught her.
Hi! It's Josh, isn't it?
I'm your mother's doctor...
I left a message. Is your dad in?
Dad? Dad?!
- Mum's doctor.
- In you go, son.
Come in.
I'm going to take all
this stuff to the hospital.
Ness thought the girls would
like some familiar things.
- Good idea.
- Yeah. She's been amazing.
- How's Josh doing?
- Well, he's, um...
Well, we're all pretty bad.
I'm really sorry, Karl, but
I am going to have to ask you
how Connie seemed to you
in those last few days,
and about her medication.
You may be better off asking her dad.
- She was staying over there.
- Why?
Well, she wasn't herself.
I didn't want the kids
to see her like that.
- Like what?
- Hyper. You know.
Manic.
Listen, I've got to get to the hospital
and the train leaves shortly, so, erm...
Oh, I'll be passing that
way, if you want a lift?
Yeah, yeah, OK. Thanks.
We could pop by her dad's, if you
want? He's only round the corner.
She slept most of the time. She
didn't want me to disturb her.
Oh, my God.
Karl, why don't you wait
downstairs? I'll be down in a minute.
- Are her meds here?
- Um...
OK. Thank you.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Do you have a good life, Kenneth?
Do we know each other?
Oh... Jesus Christ.
I am so sorry I didn't
warn you that I was coming.
I didn't think I'd be
able to go through with it.
Oh...
Oh, God.
Do you mind if we go outside?
I really need a cigarette.
Someone I know, someone special...
... she said to me...
".. why aren't the streets
full of wrecked people?"
I think they are.
I really think they are.
It's OK. It's OK.
It's OK.
You didn't need to write to us.
- It wasn't your fault.
- I know.
Thank you.
Emma?
I didn't know who else to call,
- you were the last number on her phone.
- No problem, mate.
- Hi.
- Are you OK?
- Mm-mm...
- Come on.
- What's going on?
- Look, just get her home.
You all right? I'll get it. Thanks.
Can you get the door, please?
Oh, hey, mate. How are you doing? Erm...
She's a bit worse for wear.
Yeah. Yeah. I can see that. Who are you?
Mary fucking Poppins.
Dougie.
I got a call from a guy in Cheam.
- He tried ringing you...
- What were you doing in Cheam, Emma?
What were you doing?
- Is she gonna be OK?
- Yeah, yeah. Yeah, thanks...
... Dougie.
I've organised another psych for you.
Someone more suitable. Sarah.
I don't want Sarah.
I want YOU.
Sarah's good. You'll like her.
What happened? What did I do?
Why are you so angry with me?
I'm not angry with you. It's me.
You deserve someone better.
They could rip me to shreds in court.
Stop self-flagellating.
Come on! Get on with it.
Ask me one of your stupid questions!
Why did you stop taking all
your medication on August 7th?
♪ Why does the sun go on shining? ♪
♪ Why does the sea rush to shore? ♪
♪ Don't they know ♪
♪ It's the end of the world? ♪
♪ Cos you don't love me anymore ♪
♪ Why do the birds go on singing? ♪
♪ Why do the stars glow above? ♪
♪ Don't they know... ♪
Darling, have you seen Josh?
- Are you all right, Dad?
- Yes, I'll be fine.
- Will Granny be cross with Josh?
- Course not.
He wouldn't miss her funeral.
See, he's outside.
Welcome to the service
of Julia De Cadenet.
Please stand for the first hymn.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
How are my little girls?
My favourite little girls.
- Do you want some champagne?
- No, thanks, I am fine.
- Are you OK?
- No, I'm not, actually.
Piss off!
♪ Yes, I loved her ♪
♪ How I loved her ♪
♪ Though her shoes ♪
♪ Were number nine... ♪
♪ Herring boxes, without topees ♪
♪ Sandals were for Clementine. ♪
♪ Oh, my darling, oh, my darling. ♪
Who wants to go next?
- Me, me, me, I want a go!
- Come on, Annie-Pops!
♪ Lost and gone forever ♪
♪ Dreadful sorry, Clementine. ♪
♪ Oh, my darling, oh, my darling ♪
♪ Oh, my darling, Clementine. ♪
Come on, I'll catch you. I
promise. One, two, three...
OK, guys. That's enough.
Come on, Annie. Let's go.
- OK. It's ice cream time.
- Yeah! Ice cream time.
I think, maybe, I'm just unusual.
No, you're not. You're just pissed
and you've taken too many pills.
Jesus, Con. Someone could've
cracked their skull open.
I'm sorry.
You've got to get
yourself together, Con.
For the kids.
Why don't you go stay with
your dad for a few days?
Get some proper rest.
- I am so sorry, Dad.
- Hey...
Go to sleep, my little honey bee.
For the kids. For the kids.
For the kids.
I don't want to be mad.
Let's go back.
Why did you leave your dad's house?
- It was raining.
- When was it raining?
All day.
It was such a... terrible storm.
Why did you put the children in the car?
Just raining, raining, raining.
My mum. I miss her.
I know, Connie. I know.
♪ Why does the sun go on shining? ♪
♪ Why does the sea rush to shore? ♪
♪ Don't they know ♪
♪ It's the end of the world? ♪
♪ Cos you don't ♪
♪ Love me anymore. ♪
I just don't know what
to do without her, Con...
I've brought you some tea.
Mama!
Mum!
Where are you, Mum?!
I'm scared, Mum! I'm scared!
Connie? Connie?'
Mama?
Mum?
Mama?!
Mama, wait for me.
Mama, where are you?
Mum! Mama!
Mama, wait for me!
Mum!
Where are you? Mum?
Where are you?
Annie! Annie! Wake up, darling!
- Where's Joshie?
- He's at Toby's house.
Come, on darling. We've
got to get out of here.
- Where to?
- Out. It's a surprise.
- Is it Scotland?
- No. Come on, sweetie. Not a sound!
Can Polly come too?
Good girls. Good girls.
I'm gonna put on Granny's song
and you can go back to sleep. OK?
Here we go.
♪ Don't they know ♪
♪ It's the end of the world? ♪
♪ It ended when I lost your love ♪
♪ I wake up in the morning ♪
♪ And I wonder ♪
♪ Why everything's the same ♪
♪ As it was... ♪
♪ I can't understand ♪
♪ No, I can't understand ♪
♪ How life goes on the way it does ♪
♪ Why does my heart ♪
♪ Go on beating...? ♪
♪ Why do these eyes of mine cry? ♪
♪ Don't they know ♪
♪ It's the end of the...? ♪
Mum!
Darling, it's OK.
- Mummy!
- No, shush. It's OK, darling.
It's OK. It's OK. Granny's gonna
save us. Granny's going to save us!
A psychotic episode?
Not necessarily from the
benzodiazepines per se,
I'm not saying that, they
can be very helpful drugs.
- I'm talking about the withdrawal process.
- I see...
Although, might I add,
the General Medical Council
is currently looking into
whether the benzos were incorrectly
prescribed in the first place.
Aside from lorazepam, what else
was Ms Mortensen taking? Remind us.
The antidepressant lofepramine
and corticosteroids.
And she stopped taking all
medication on the... 7th, you say?
- Yes.
- Three days.
Is that usual for benzodiazepine
withdrawal to kick in?
It can be. If it's an acute
withdrawal, which this was.
There are previous case reports of
violent behaviour in this situation.
She should have been on a
gradual withdrawal programme.
People need to be monitored. They
should have a support network.
Obviously, there were
other contributory factors.
She was in the depths of grief.
She had buried her mother
on the 7th, as well.
And grief can be its own kind of hell.
Let's not forget that
she'd recently discovered
her husband was having a relationship
with Polly Jones's mother? Correct?
Ms Mortensen had been through
considerable emotional turmoil
prior to seeking lorazepam. Yes.
So, we could say that
she certainly had motive.
Can you explain to us
what spousal revenge is?
It's what you might call a jealous rage.
Which rather seems to fit with
the actions of Ms Mortensen,
- wouldn't you agree?
- Not at all.
Ms Mortensen was in fact
acting altruistically.
In her acutely psychotic
state that night,
she believed she was saving the
children from a malevolent force.
A malevolent force.
How can you be sure that Ms
Mortensen isn't just fabricating
these psychotic symptoms in
order to get away with this?
Experience. Expertise.
I've seen many a
malingerer over my 30 years,
and not many of them
would go to the lengths
of severely scalding themselves
with hydrochloric acid,
which, by the way, pre-dates
the offence in question.
Her psychosis was not faked.
And I would put it to you, Dr,
that Ms Mortensen is still a danger,
not only to herself, but
to her family and society.
And I would strongly refute that.
Now that she's on the
correct monitored medication,
Ms Mortensen is no more
a danger to herself,
her family or society than you or I.
For who knows what any
one of us is capable of,
given the wrong medication
and the right triggers?
I've just had Foxtons on the phone.
They're going to come
round tomorrow to value it.
I feel like we're betraying her.
Leaving her behind. Moving on.
I thought that's what you wanted?
I need you to listen to me.
There's something I've never told you...
... about that day.
Mummy!
Mummy, are we going to the swings?
We're going later.
Mummy, I want to go on the swings!
We're gonna go later!
Mummy! I want to go on the swings!
Mummy, I want to go on the swings!
Mummy, I want to get out of the buggy!
Hey, Jenny! How's it
going? Getting any sleep?
God, don't ask.
Abigail, you can stop
that, Mummy's talking.
- Oh, Emma. Drop her with me.
- I said stop it!
Oh, you're so kind. You are
just going to have to wait!
It's not a good moment. I'll
let you be. I'll see you soon.
Can you just be quiet!
I need to take this call.
I have had it with you!
Hello? Yes. Is this
about the washing machine?
Well, could you be more specific?
When you say "all day", I mean,
I can't wait in all day, can I?!
Well, could you at least
say morning or afternoon?
Well, can I track you, then?
"I've had it with you".
Those were the last words she heard.
Abigail.
You're right. I never say her name.
You're right to blame me.
I don't blame you.
And I don't blame you at
all for having an affair.
- What?
- With Savannah. Adrian's girlfriend.
What?!
I am not an idiot.
I saw you together. Outside your office.
Arm in arm. You left together.
No. No, no, no, no.
She was trying to rope me in
to organizing a
surprise 50th for Adrian.
Oh, come here, you big idiot.
Spaghetti.
- What time is it?
- You've got hours.
Oh, God, I hate this. I
feel sick. How do I look?
You'll be fine. Want a chill pill?
You are a bad person.
Yeah.
- Hello, love.
- Mummy!
Look at you.
Do they have an electric chair here?
- I am afraid it's not that kind of place, my darling.
- Oh!
Why don't you go and
see my friend Carol,
- see if she will give you some sweets.
- Yeah.
Hello, Joshie.
I'm so sorry, for everything
I've put you through.
You'd better not do it again.
♪ Got to wait to see the day ♪
♪ Got to wait for the light ♪
♪ Got to wait until
the river's dry ♪
♪ When all is said and done ♪
♪ Wanting to belong ♪
♪ Lost along the only run... ♪
Good afternoon, I'm Dr Emma Robertson.
I'm your forensic psychiatrist.
♪ Carry on. ♪