Hello, love.
'Oh, hi. Just, er, just tried you.'
Did you? My volume was down.
'Are you at home?'
I went to early yoga, just finished.
'Er, are you smoking?'
No.
'Oh. What time do you want to leave
this evening?'
Listen, Phil rang.
I've got to go in.
They want me to take on
the Mortensen case.
'What?! I thought you...
'..we'd agreed.' I've said yes.
'Have you?'
SI SIGHS Let's talk later.
'Bye, love.'
Have you got any comments
on the Connie Mortensen case?
Is she faking?
Is she still a danger to society?
Can you stop and chat with us
for a minute?
Do you reckon it was pre-meditated?
Is she faking the amnesia?
You are up for this, aren't you?
Everyone's breathing down my neck
for a report.
You got your alarm, yeah?
She took a hefty bite
out of security.
Good morning, Constance.
I'm Emma Robertson,
I'm your new forensic psychiatrist.
Well, don't you sound
pleased with yourself.
Go on...
have a good look.
I would.
“How on earth did her life
go so wrong?“
Quite easily, as it happens.
So you better watch out...
with your swishy bag
and your sensible shoes...
you could be next.
It's my job to keep you safe...
to treat you.
And the court have asked
for my opinion of your mental state
on the night of the offence.
We need to find out
why you are unable to recall
the events of that night.
I'm going to be recording
our sessions, if that's all right?
Just means I don't need to take
too many notes.
You like poetry, do you?
Ah. Yes, I do.
Now, why don't you tell me...
what happened that night?
You're the expert,
why don't you tell me?
You drove your car into the river,
Constance.
You're lucky to be alive.
There were children in the back.
I'm going to help you remember.
How does that sound?
Well, here we are...
in some fancy part of North London,
where, rumour has it,
there are more therapists
than nut-jobs.
So when you look at it that way...
I think you'll find
I'm the one helping you.
Ooh. No phones in here, Doc.
He's gonna be late home, is he?
That old chestnut.
I think betrayal probably
just begins with disenchantment.
Is that what happened to you?
I'd like to see Josh and Annie now.
That's not going to be possible.
Don't you have kids...
The more you remember about
that night, Constance,
the better your chances.
..or have they flown the nest?
You're no spring chicken.
In fact, I haven't even seen
your qualifications yet.
The other one showed me hers.
Avoidance tactics
won't work with me, Constance.
Connie...
please.
So this is her, is it?
The Yummy Mummy Monster.
Tabloids would pay a fortune
for this.
How long do you think
she's realistically looking at?
She plead not guilty, didn't she?
Mm. Attempted murder, Level 1...
she could be looking at 30 years.
Or a lifetime hospitalised.
Well, that's down to you,
my darling.
Temporary insanity,
she could soon be buzzing round
a Waitrose near you.
That's her and the poor neighbour,
Vanessa Jones.
Mother of the other little girl
in the car.
I must say...
I prefer a modicum of sanity
in my ladies.
Si, I've got files to read.
Em, is this really such a good idea?
My husband was meant to come,
where is he?
And my mum.
When is my mum coming?
Not exactly queueing up,
are they, Tuft y?
It's not really vocational for you,
is it, the caring profession?
You might be fooling all that lot
with your little
lost posh girl thing,
but you ain't fooling me.
You know exactly what you did.
It's just a paracetamol.
Hello, Dr Robertson.
Now, you be a good girl, Constance.
Thank you, Addy.
Off you trot, Fatso.
Good morning, Constance. Connie.
I think I'd like
one of your cigarettes.
Is it menthol,
or did you pop a mint in?
You can't smoke in here.
Oh, I don't smoke.
I always think smoking
is a sign of terrible weakness.
Have you remembered anything
about the night?
How long have you been keeping
little secrets from Si Hubby, then?
Why don't we begin with your
relationship with Vanessa Jones?
It's Ness...
not Vanessa. I'm sorry. Ness.
I wish it was before again.
Before what, Connie?
Before I was skinned,
boned and filleted.
Oi, they're mine, give them back!
Polly, give them back
to the little girl.
I'm not little!
Oh, I am so sorry... Annie!
What's your name. Annie.
Give them back to Annie.
Annie, stop shouting!
And don't swear. Jesus Christ!
I'm really sorry.
Please, don't worry.
No, here. No, honestly.
Polly, she's such a biff er.
Give them back to me.
Look, you've got so many.
Annie, be nice.
Didn't I say?
Share them with the little girl.
Thank you. Follow me!
Right. And now they're best friends.
It's as simple as that.
She's such a flirt.
Can 1? Of course.
Are you local? Yes, are you?
We've just moved to the area.
I thought I hadn't seen you before.
Well, welcome. Thank you.
Polly starts at Meadowside
next week.
Oh, right. It's a great school.
Yeah? Yeah.
You don't know if the first train
in the morning is reliable, do you?
I'm not the best person to ask,
I am afraid.
I work from home.
Mm! Have one.
They taste better than they look.
Thank you.
What do you do?
Nothing spectacular. I write.
Copy-editing, articles,
journo stuff, you know?
You've got some...
No...
Oh, God, you smell fantastic.
Oh, thank you.
What is that?
It's, erm, Jo Malone.
The pomegranate one. Mmm!
Mmm. It's good, right?
Yeah.
It's my partner
that has to be in early.
What does he do?
She, actually.
Sorry.
So, now that the school's got
an Outstanding,
all the bankers are moving in.
You'll see their wives
at the school gates.
They have flick y hair and little
dogs that don't moult or shit.
There's a lot of yoga.
I love your tattoos. Oh, do you?
Mm. I've never dared get one.
Oh, thank you.
Hello, Daddy.
Hey, darling, how are you?
Good. This is us.
Hi, Con.
That's my husband, Karl.
Oh, and that's us. Just here.
Wow.
Yeah, you must come meet Leah
some time.
Definitely. We're so close.
Yeah.
Come on, Polly. Say goodbye.
Bye!
See you, Mum.
'I think my body
was trying to tell me something...
'even back then.
'I felt... a little tug,
as if from the wings.
'Like a warning... perhaps.'
Did it make you uncomfortable,
the fact that she was attracted
to women?
I like cock... Dr Robertson.
I like men.
W hy?
Does it make you uncomfortable?
So...
back to you and Si Hubby.
Professional couple.
Left it a bit late...
just the one kid, I presume?
Little Emmalina.
In pony club and extra Mandarin.
Oh, you'll find that everything's
locked in here, Doctor.
Windows, doors, cupboards, minds...
Do you know what I think, Connie?
I think that you are
seriously underestimating
the gravity of the situation
that you're in.
Attempted murder
carries a long sentence.
YOU can come across as
a little head-mistress y...
you ought to watch that.
I bet Si Hubby's sick to death
of it.
“Have you done this,
have you done that?“
At some stage...
we all take responsibility
for our actions.
And a little smug,
if you don't mind me saying.
You're at it again.
Avoidance tactics.
Would you say
your life's pretty good...
Little Miss Mary Poppins? Hmm?
I mean,
what could possibly go wrong
in your perfect world...
with your important job...
and your expensive
but deathly dull clothes?
And admit it, Doctor...
you have let yourself go.
Unbelievable.
You come home after a busy day
saving people,
to your lovely terraced house...
with the white slatted blinds,
your island kitchen...
and your Pouilly-Fume
cooling in the fridge...
The cheek.
And lovely Si Hubby...
your nice but dim husband,
has cleaned up all the kid mess.
But it's all such a sham, isn't it?
Answer this...
for how long
can you realistically avoid it
when it's all part of
the unspoken contract of a couple?
Yes.
Tonight might have to be THE night.
The Once A Month Duty-Fuck.
And don't get me wrong -
you're a good wife,
you love Si Hubby and all that,
blah, blah, blah...
but it's such a monumental effort,
isn't it?
Come bedtime, perhaps you could
stall for a bit downstairs,
or pretend to be asleep...
working in bed... Hello?
Huh. You didn't hear me come in.
What are you listening to?
Oh, nothing, it's work. Oh.
I see I've got
some catching up to do.
So, how was it?
No biting, altercations?
I've only had a glass or two.
No.
Starving.
Oh, so tell me...
what was Adrian's
new girlfriend like?
Far too good for him.
Susannah? Sahara? Samantha?
Savannah. Savannah.
They're coming round Thursday,
by the way.
I asked Hattie, too. Oh.
I'll do it.
Please tell me your sister's dumped
that dreadful boyfriend.
So come on...
how was the Yummy Mummy Monster?
Monstrously arrogant, actually.
And... don't be tabloid, Si.
Is she faking the amnesia?
Can we not talk shop.
I was thinking that maybe we should
try and get away for the weekend.
I've got orchestra
Saturday afternoon.
Oh, right.
It's just we never really
do anything spontaneous.
Huh. Have I missed something?
Is it my birthday?
Did I win the lottery?
Fine, let's not bother.
Gently, gently, gently...
It's not so bad
once you get going, is it?
Although, let's be honest,
it'd be nice
if he'd hurry up and come.
But fucking is easy, isn't it,
Doctor?
It's kissing that you can't fake.
It's kissing that is
the unbearable intimacy.
Think about it...
that mouth of his...
the disgusting way it eats,
the stupid things it says,
the idiotic expressions it pulls...
that mouth you're stuck with
for the next 30 years.
Oh, I think all of us
use avoidance tactics,
don't you, Dr Robertson?
What are you meant to do with
all the love that's left over,
after someone's gone?
It must go somewhere.
I honestly don't know.
No. You're not much help.
Is Karl often unreliable?
I wasn't talking about him.
It's looking so good, Polly.
Hi, I'm so sorry to interrupt.
Would I be able to grab a selfie
with you?
Yeah, of course.
All my friends will be so jealous.
OK, you're done, darling.
Jade, I'll be back in just a sec.
Mum? Mum, what are you doing?
She's feral enough as it is.
She was desperate!
Use a dock-leaf, darling.
Polly, maybe don't watch, darling.
Come here.
Oh, Con, look, it's that lesbian
who reads the news.
That's Polly's mum, Mum.
Right, I've got to get back to it,
can you two look after them?
You need a break, Con.
You haven't stopped.
Let me go and get you some wine.
All right. I am gagging for some,
but I warn you,
it's £5 a plastic glass.
Oh, don't be fucking ridiculous.
Mum, language, with the children.
Dad, please come down.
Grandad, shoot me,
with a machine gun, in the face!
Bang! Bang, bang, bang, bang, bang!
Be careful.
I'd like to welcome some new members
to our Meadowside family.
I think Leah Worthington
needs no introduction.
And her lovely partner, Vanessa.
So what's a girl got to do
to get her face painted around here?
Well, she has to turn up on time,
for one thing.
Only joking.
Let's see what I can do.
You're wearing my perfume.
So...
did you go home and fuck,
after our little chat yesterday?
How did it make you feel the fact
that she'd copied your perfume?
You did!
Look at you
in your elasticated sports bra,
hoping to get fit by fabric osmosis.
What are you so angry about, Connie?
I want to see Ness. Why?
What is it that you want to say
to her?
Perhaps we need to work that out
first.
You could pretend I'm her.
Talk to me, if you like?
Oh, a little role play.
Did you do
a weekend course in it
We could begin where you left off.
Let's pretend we're at
the face-painting stall.
All right.
There's no need to be scared of me,
Doctor.
I'm not scared of you.
You copied my tattoo...
my perfume. I did.
How does that make you feel?
A bit robbed, to be honest.
Robbed and...
flattered.
No touching.
What stunning eyes you've got.
What did you do, my lovely?
Why are you so full of pain?
What happened?
You're gonna be late for OT.
Oh, I'm so sorry,
I just wanted a room.
Don't worry, it's fine.
I think I should warn you
that the prosecution
might show some evidence
that's going to be disturbing.
I mean, obviously,
we'll try to exclude it
on grounds of relevance...
but I think it's best
you see these photographs now.
Oh, Annie.
Oh, sorry.
It's OK, Doc.
It's just a thing Annie does.
It's a game.
She is always play acting.
It's just a game.
That... is not a game, Constance.
I know it's...
It's OK, Connie.
I want to see my baby.
It's OK.
I want to see my babies.
Where are my babies?
Get me my babies!
We need some help in here, please!
Get me my babies! Get me my babies!
We need PRN Lorazepam now.
I need you to take a breath now,
Connie.
Quickly.
That's it, Connie,
take a breath now.
He was horrible, Savannah.
His room was disgusting,
he never did any work.
He never got up before three.
I can never get up in
the mornings.
That's what she said.
THEY LAUGH Ooh-oh-ooh!
Thank you.
I want to hear about
this hitchhiking trip
round the south of France
cos he wouldn't tell me anything.
Absolutely, yeah. Yes!
No. No, no, no, absolutely.
Don't you dare, Si, no.
I'll just get some more wine.
I'll be back.
Anyway, change the subject.
I wanted to ask Emma about the case.
What's she like?
What?
The Yummy Mummy Monster.
Did the kids die?
The kids survived. But... the papers
got it wrong, didn't they?
Leah Worthington wrote
this beautiful piece about it,
- did you read that?
- I did.
I know someone who used to do
the park run
with the Yummy Monster's husband.
He's really cool, apparently.
One of the kids is in a coma.
That's what it said on the news.
That's right, isn't it?
Mind you, I'd kill my bloody kids
given half a chance.
Have you read what they're saying
about it on Twitter, Emma?
Shit. Storm.
Christ Almighty,
what is gonna happen to her?
She should fry, man.
Oh, shut up, Blair.
Seriously, though, Em.
She is a monster, isn't she?
Patient confidentiality.
Emma can't talk about it.
Excuse me. Loo.
Seriously, though...
Can you imagine that phone call.
“No, no, no,
they've had a great sleep-over,
“yeah, there's just one
tiny weeny little thing...“
Em? It's me. You all right?
KNOCK ON DOOR Em?
Bloody hell.
It wasn't Connie's fault.
That's ABH.
The way they talk...
the vitriol...
it's disgusting!
That Blair bloke,
he's the bloody monster.
Careful what you say,
he might end up my brother-in-law.
I'm always careful what I say,
it's my job!
You've had too much to drink, love,
I'll get them to go.
And I'm gonna have loads more.
It's a day off tomorrow.
No, love, it's Friday tomorrow.
She was shown a photograph today.
Her daughter lying there
on a white sheet...
her little body, tubes everywhere.
Do you know what she did?
She laughed.
She just laughed.
She's not of sound mind, darling.
Do I nag? You do. I don't mind.
Oh, God, listen to them.
“Is she dead? Is she in a coma?“
What do they care?
A dead child is just a dead child.
Don't be cruel, Emma.
Me? Cruel?
You don't even say her name.
Say it, Si. Say our daughter's name.
You look like shit.
You don't look so great yourself.
Do you hate me?
Here.
Shall we talk about Karl?
Do you think the pills
are still working, Con?
Are you happy?
Life is not all about being happy,
Karl.
Are you happy? No.
Well, exactly.
That's just how it is
once you have kids.
I don't even recognise myself
half the time.
Don't be so dramatic.
You're just going through
a rough patch.
Work will come in.
I thought you'd had an order?
Were you just numb?
Wasn't there anything
making you feel alive?
Back at six. Love you.
'She made me feel alive.
'At this age...
'when you really connect
with someone...
'..it's a bit like falling in love.'
Hope you make a lot of nice friends
out there,
but just remember,
there's a lot of bad and beware.
Oh, I know this,
I know this, I know...
I know this.
Oh, I know this! Go on.
Too slow. I know this.
♪ Baby, I'm grieving... ♪
Mm!
♪ Oh, baby, baby... ♪
I don't know this version.
It's a Black version, that's why.
♪ It's hard to get by
Just upon a smile
♪ Oh, ooh
♪ Oh, baby, baby
It's a wild world
♪ I'll always remember you
Like a child. ♪
Ignore him.
It's Karl, I can't, he'll worry.
Sorry!
Tell me more about that other guy.
The big one before Karl.
Oh, it was so complicated.
He was my professor at uni.
Ah. He was married.
Mm-hm.
Bet the sex was good, though.
Have you always been with women?
No, Leah was my first.
Really? Mm.
Do you have a good sex life?
Me and Leah? Yeah. Do you?
Yeah.
I really should make more
of an effort.
Oh, me too.
Like, chuck out the granny pants.
But they're so comfortable!
Well, I suppose I could dig out
the old French maid's outfit.
You dress up?
No, I'm serious! Do you?
Well, many centuries ago.
No way! What?
I'd feel such a plonker! Tell me.
Things like what? OK, well...
I do have a nun's outfit somewhere.
It's because Karl is a Catholic -
they love that shit.
Here.
Sex tip number one, Vanessa...
Mm-hm.
..when getting it from behind,
one must never ever turn around
and try to look sexy.
Because it just doesn't work.
Can I ask you something?
Of course.
How does everyone else function?
I just don't understand.
Why aren't the streets full of...
wrecked people?
Oh, God.
I'm sorry, this is inexcusable...
No, it's OK...
get it all out.
It happens to the best of us.
Oh, I'm just... I apologise,
I don't...
Oh, God... It's OK.
Oh. I'm really, I...
I apologise.
Ooh, red wine, poor you.
It's all right.
You're wearing my jacket.
Hi, I'm Karl Mortensen.
I'm here to see Constance Mortensen.
You're not on the list.
You've got to give 24 hours' notice
to the social worker.
That's just how it is.
I brought her a cake.
That was quick.
Yeah, my fault.
You have to book ahead.
Subtitles by accessibility@itv.com