- Evening, Mr. Draper.
- Hello, Dawn.
- Let me take your coat.
- It's 8:00. Do you mind?
What is this?
Sweet'N Low and Coffee-Mate.
I noticed you were out.
Is this an elaborate plea for coffee?
I can make some.
I really can't stay.
Mrs. Draper did not
call this morning,
but I arranged for a Valentine
bouquet to arrive
in the afternoon her time,
so I'd expect a call here around dinner.
Good girl.
Mohawk Airlines?
Henry Lammott came in?
He just dropped in.
He wanted to meet Lou.
Huh.
Office or conference room?
- Conference room.
- Where did he sit?
- Who?
- Lou.
I don't remember.
How did Diners Club
go on Tuesday?
It got pushed back for
a signing meeting with Handi-Wrap.
More Dow?
How long has that been going on?
I don't know.
It's Mr. Cosgrove.
Clara's terrible with memos.
- What creative team is on it?
- I don't know.
- No other calls?
- No, Mr. Draper.
I know, I know.
I told you, it's for carfare.
Well, I've been thinking
about it a lot, actually.
And you know I don't mind
keeping you aware of things.
But there's something about the money
that makes it feel wrong.
You're doing extra work.
You should get extra pay.
It's no work at all.
So I will continue to do
what I feel comfortable doing for free,
which is answer your phone
and keep you up to date.
That's all I ask for.
No, you asked me to get you
photocopies of the Butler work
and they're locked
in Peggy's office and I can't.
I don't want you to do that.
All right.
Good.
But I want you to take this.
- You take care.
- Of course.
The cleaning woman
comes tomorrow morning.
She says, "You look
like a working girl."
And I thought she meant I looked
low-class like a secretary.
But Petra said
she meant a prostitute.
How the fuck does my mother know
what a prostitute looks like?
How was Sarah?
Below average.
She wants me
to bring her Capezios,
so I don't know
what I'm going to wear.
Is it an open casket?
I didn't ask.
Sergeant Snorkel says we have
to come back on the 12:30.
So back here by 3:00?
The funeral's at 9:00.
We see Sarah, boo-hoo.
Maybe we leave a little early
because Sally's so upset.
We get in a taxi to the cemetery,
but we get out
in Greenwich Village.
Two hours of shopping,
take another pumpkin to Grand Central.
There's a boutique on MacDougal
that has Pocahontas boots.
I am upset, Carol.
Me, too.
I heard her dad's a mess.
She was supposed to be
a great beauty.
Sarah had this picture of her
wearing a bikini on Christmas.
She took it with her.
You know she's gonna
miss school till Easter?
I wish my mom was dead.
I'd stay here till 1975 if I could
get Betty in the ground.
What are you wearing?
I don't have anything black
but my turtleneck,
so I thought I'd wear that with
my brown suede skirt and black tights.
Jesus, Draper.
Is this your first funeral?
Leave the lights off.
How am I gonna find anything?
Why do you have
to do this tonight?
- Hey.
- Didn't you already sign Chevy?
Can't you just add the business
onto their other contract?
Sweetheart, let me
explain this to you.
This is the Southern California
Chevrolet Dealers Association.
Chevy's the factory,
this is the store.
You're not listening to me.
Just has to be there
when he wakes up.
He's so drunk, he doesn't
even know where he is.
That's why it has to be there
when he wakes up
with a note that says,
"You promised to sign this
no matter what."
You are such a big deal.
How'd it go?
- I got 'em.
- Good work.
- Good night, Bonnie.
- Good night.
Hold that, please.
- Hello, New York.
- Howdy.
Oh, Michael,
very nice work on Butler.
Stan, we're going to need
renderings, color.
- How's Monday?
- Today is Friday.
Whew, I'm buried all day
and I have plans tonight.
So you can finish tonight
and have plans all weekend.
- She's gonna find out.
- What?
Maybe if you invite me,
you can have till Tuesday.
We now all know you don't have
plans for Valentine's Day.
Oh.
She has plans.
Look at her calendar.
"February 14,
masturbate gloomily."
Monday is fine.
Who are these from?
Hard to believe
your cat has the money.
Really lovely.
Look at you, every inch a girl.
Is this some kind of joke?
Just tell me now because I don't want
to have to fire you later.
Enjoy your flowers, boss.
Oh.
Happy Valentine's Day, Shirley.
And happy
Valentine's Day to you.
Shirley, I see there's no card,
but I'd like to know who sent me
these beautiful flowers.
Well, actually...
Oh.
I understand now.
Oh, good.
Could you get me some coffee?
What time is it on the coast?
- Pardon?
- 6:00 a.m.
I'll handle it.
Could you get the door?
Ted Chaough's office.
Good morning, Moira.
It's Peggy.
Where are you?
I'm in my office, but I need you
to relay a message to Ted for me.
Oh, okay.
Tell him that I got his message.
No, tell him that
I relayed his message
to the client and...
And what?
There's nothing he can do.
They're not...
they don't want to hear
any more pitches.
The business is gone.
Really?
What account?
He'll know.
Well, the snow's melted,
but not the hearts of New Yorkers.
I just had some old lady
call me a "kike."
- Is that right?
- Yeah.
She was letting
her dog relieve himself
and I said, "Pardon me,
but you want to curb that thing?"
She says, "Mind
your own business, kike."
Maybe it's the hat.
The strangest things
happen to you.
Hey, did you see this?
Ogilvy signed Hershey.
I hadn't heard that.
She hates her because
she got a C in Western Civ.
She corrects my English.
I went to school in England.
Are we going to walk
into school with these?
We'll say they're Sarah's.
Is my purse in your bag?
The senior class sent her flowers
because they're all so concerned.
Half of them think
her name is Sally.
Shit, I must have left it
at the coffee shop.
Maybe in the head shop?
I'm just going to go up
and check at the counter.
- I'll get your fare.
- No, my address book is in there.
- It's everybody I know.
- We can't wait.
There's another train
in a couple hours.
- "Hello, Dawn."
- "Hello, Shirley."
You shouldn't be taking a break
right where you are.
I'm not. I'm getting her coffee.
And I'm taking my time.
- What did she do now?
- It ain't funny.
Charles sent me 12 long-stem roses
in a crystal vase
and she took 'em.
I was right at the photocopier
when she came in
preparing her shit,
and somehow...
'cause I put the card
in my purse,
I guess because it said,
"I love you so"...
she thought they were hers.
Well, it was an honest mistake.
Who the hell
is sending her flowers?
Why didn't you say something?
It was too late.
I tried.
- You tried?
- I really did.
Well, they're hers now.
I'm gonna tell her.
You want those flowers so bad,
you'll take the trouble that comes
with getting them back?
It's not right.
Well, I have two bosses
and one of them hasn't told
his wife he's on leave.
Keep pretending.
That's your job.
Well, you know who I feel
the worst for is Charles.
He'd rather you have a job.
You know that's not true.
"Happy Valentine's, Dawn."
"Good-bye, Shirley."
You look good. Rested.
You said that.
How do I usually look?
It's just that you've been so busy
for the last two years,
you've never
taken me up for lunch.
I figured you're on
some kind of break.
Maybe I'm doing research.
Maybe I want our place to be a little
bit more like Wells Rich Greene.
You'd have to have Mary.
And, you know,
you probably could.
I knew you were gonna tell me
how great it is to work there,
but I didn't think
that's where you'd start.
So you looking to make a change?
I have a job.
And I have a contract
and a noncompete clause.
And I'm a partner.
Look, I don't know what the truth is
and I don't really care.
Someone said you were
dabbling in the LA office
or managing your wife's career.
People say things.
Well, then you probably
heard the one
where you pulled
a major boner in a meeting
and you cried or punched
somebody or something
and that they cut you loose.
I didn't know I was
gonna be interrogated
by the Hooterville
telephone operator.
So it's not true?
You're spoiling the mood.
How about for a second date,
we go see the Knicks?
Right on the floor.
Bradley's having
one hell of a season.
That's a good idea.
Hello?
Can I help you, sweetheart?
Who are you?
I'm Mr. Avery.
You looking for casting?
No, I'm looking for my dad,
Donald Draper.
Uh, well, he's not here.
Did he change offices?
Perfect.
Look, honey, he's not here.
He's probably at home.
You should call him.
You know how to get
an outside line?
Is Joan here?
That's a good idea.
Her office is right down there.
You know, I think
everybody's at lunch.
Have a nice day.
So she's sitting there
on the conference table
Indian-style
in a dress and boots
like some kind of perverted
kindergarten teacher
and she says,
"Well, thank you, Robert.
I know it's the best
you can do."
What did Bob do?
Accepted his death gracefully.
I see a sheep and a wolf.
But which is which?
- How are you, Don?
- Great.
Jim Hobart, Dave Wooster.
We know each other.
So, Dave, how come you'll have lunch
with Don and not with me?
'Cause this is social.
He's not trying to buy us.
Well, what are you
trying to do, Don?
Are you taking lunches now?
No, I'm just looking for love.
Well, on behalf of myself
and all the millionaires
at McCann Erickson,
we'd love a chance to tell you
how handsome you are.
Move along, Jim.
Tell Mary I picked up the check,
because I just did.
I don't have to crap
on McCann for you, do I?
I almost worked there.
Twice.
But you didn't.
Here, I want you to have these.
It smells like
an Italian funeral in there.
So then dessert finally
arrives and the ladies,
on cue, depart to the toilets.
And as we're standing,
Honeywell leans in and says,
"I like what I see."
Now, I thought he was making
a ribald comment about my date,
but he followed up by suggesting
we retire to the bar,
just the two of us.
Is this a partners' meeting
or the most tedious
wireless program I've ever heard?
What?
What did he say?
- We're on the edge of our seats.
- Hello, New York?
- He's saying get to it, Pete.
- Did you kiss the man or not?
- Fine.
Well, he didn't want to say it
in front of the boys from Detroit,
but he wants us
to handle his business.
He rules the SoCal dealerships
with an iron fist.
- That's great.
- Wonderful.
- That's wonderful news.
- It is, isn't it?
They want us to start
on the summer sale.
Sign them right away.
Sit in his yard with a pen
if you have to.
Contract came with the milkman.
I'll get Bob Benson to fly in
from Detroit for the signing.
We don't want the tail
wagging the dog.
They're the Dealers Association.
They bill almost
as much as Chevy does.
They are the dog.
- He's right.
- Just a minute.
Chevy's our client
and they're our entree to GM,
which bills more than
everything on the planet.
I would tell Detroit
we've got this opportunity
and I would ask
for their blessing.
Look, when I brought in Chevy,
I got their very own
Mikey O'Brien laid.
Sorry, sweetheart.
And it wasn't easy. Sorry again.
Pete caught him.
Let Pete mount him.
Can we move on?
This phone call is already
eating into our fee.
Ted, weren't you there
when we signed Chevy?
Roger seems to have failed
to get a head count.
I don't see any reason
to keep score.
Gentlemen, this is good news.
And I have no problem
with flying to Detroit
and briefing Bob and all those...
I'll bring oranges.
Ted? Are you there?
Hello, California?
- Dee, can you hear us?
- Yes, I can.
Dee?
What's wrong with you?
I say up, you say down.
I'm surprised you're
disagreeing with me.
It's common sense.
I think they can't hear us.
We can hear you!
Pete can service the account,
but he will report
to our man in Detroit
where said parties
will be offered
the right of refusal.
I remember very clearly
when Don and I signed Chevy.
Don who?
Our collective ex-wife
who still receives alimony?
- Hang up.
- No.
This is a partners' meeting.
Let's poll the partners,
shall we?
- Aye.
- Aye what?
I agree with Jim.
Moira, fix the phone.
I feel caught off guard
by having a confrontation
over something
that seems rudimentary.
They never said which
of Peggy's accounts we lost.
Call me when you fix
the damn phone.
Let me try out there.
What difference could
that possibly make?
I thought we were gonna
get a new one of these.
And why the hell aren't
we in the conference room?
Do not go after him.
Moira, you can reach me
in my office.
Hello?
Marta?
Oh, I looked everywhere for you.
What are you doing here?
What happened?
Is everything okay?
Obviously not.
- Where were you?
- I was at the office.
What?
I wasn't feeling well.
I left early.
What happened?
Does your mother
know where you are?
What? No.
You're not supposed
to be off campus.
My roommate's mother died
and they let us go to the funeral,
but I lost my purse.
Oh. I'm sorry to hear that.
I just need money for the train.
And I guess I need
a note of excuse.
I'll drive you.
No, it's okay.
You're not feeling well.
I'll be fine.
You really don't have to.
It looks like you have
a lot of work to do.
Come on, it'll be nice.
We'll take a drive.
What's the note supposed to say?
What?
Sally, what do I say?
Just tell the truth.
Where the hell were you?
I was getting your perfume.
- Draper's daughter showed up.
- Sally was here?
I don't know her name.
She was looking for him.
My Lord.
What did you say?
I said he's probably at home.
It's not my problem.
I have to call him.
Call him?
You have to call him?
Okay.
Don't bother apologizing
to me, I guess.
I'm very sorry.
Want to go before we go?
I'm fine.
- Hello.
- It's Dawn.
And I'm really sorry.
I don't know what happened,
but Sally came into the office
and she talked to Lou.
- And what did he say?
- I don't know.
But I wanted you to know
that she might be on her way.
Okay.
Thank you, Dawn.
Do you have to stay?
No.
Let's go.
Hello, Dawn.
Lou said he wanted to see me.
Oh.
Lou, Joan's here to see you.
Actually, I need
to see the both of you.
Get the door.
When I generously agreed
to share Dawn here
with Don Draper,
it was for the purposes
of his correspondence
and incoming phone calls,
not cleaning up his messes.
One of those things
is very time-consuming.
- What happened?
- His daughter came by.
Why are we going
through all this?
I know you can't fire her.
Just move her to another part
of the building.
Lou, I will take care of this.
- What do you mean by that?
- I want my own girl.
- Come along, Dawn.
- In a minute.
Obviously I can say
anything I want.
But you don't want to.
I skipped my lunch
to buy your wife perfume.
If you had been thoughtful
enough to get her a gift
when I told you about it 10 days ago,
I would have been here.
Do you understand?
It's not my problem.
None of this has anything
to do with me.
I'm sorry if I said
the wrong thing.
Was that necessary?
When she comes back
from the ladies',
have her hand over the keys.
New York is on the line.
Do you have to put them
on the contraption?
It's just Mr. Sterling.
- This is Pete.
- It's Roger.
I appreciate you fighting for me.
Well, Jim pled his case
and we decided it's best
to keep the business,
but run it past Detroit.
- Which means Bob gets involved.
- What?
Jim and I had a meaningful
conversation...
I heard your conversation.
You're full of it.
That is just the kind of weakness
that got us in this position
to begin with.
Let me just go to Detroit.
I'm sure...
...something to do with Bob
or my feelings towards Bob,
but it really doesn't.
It's a chance for me to rectify
my status with those people.
And in the end, that's our
best route to new business.
He disconnected.
Why even bring in an account?
They're just gonna take it away.
Sometimes I think maybe I died
and I'm in some kind of...
I don't know if it's heaven
or hell or limbo.
But I don't seem to exist.
No one feels my existence.
Just cash the checks.
You're gonna die one day.
What you're supposed to say is,
"Hey, why don't we just start
our own agency?"
At least the goal would be clear.
I mean, what am I
working for here?
There's two offices.
Yours is only slightly
better than mine.
What am I supposed to do,
work my way up to your office?
You can have my office.
No, that is not the point.
Cutler sent you out here
because you're too moral.
He couldn't look you in
the face and be Machiavelli.
That's not why I'm here.
Why are you here?
All you do is answer
the phone and mope around.
You know what?
We're not talking anymore.
From now on, we'll both
pretend I'm in New York.
Joan wants us to switch desks.
Don't feel bad.
It's not your fault.
I know.
Don't be sore,
but I'm really happy.
I need a box.
She wants you
out front right now.
Okay.
Well, just a few things.
He takes it light
with two Sweet'N Lows.
Always put through his son Earl.
These three lines are Lou's
and this one is Mr. Draper's.
Maybe I should get a pencil.
You know what?
I'll have Mr. Draper's calls
come straight to me at reception.
How old was
your friend's mother?
She's not my friend.
She's my roommate.
Where was the funeral?
81st and Madison.
Where was she buried?
In Queens by the racetrack.
So you left your purse
at the cemetery?
I'm not sure.
That's why it's lost.
Why are you interrogating me?
Because I know
you went to my office.
So I find your story
a little suspicious.
My story?
There's some man in your office.
- We're not talking about me.
- Did you lose your job?
Why were you in the city?
I want to know this minute.
I don't have to tell you anything.
Just stop the car.
- I'm talking to you.
- You're yelling at me.
Why would you just let me
lie to you like that?
Because it's more embarrassing
for me to catch you in a lie
than it is for you to be lying.
So you just laid in wait
like your mother?
Do you know how hard it was
for me to go to your apartment?
I could have run
into that woman.
I could be in the elevator,
she could get in
and I'd have
to stand there smiling
wanting to vomit
while I smell her hairspray.
I'm sorry.
Please, stop.
I'm not stopping the car.
Stop talking.
News five minutes
sooner from WABC New York.
News at 55 and 25.
It's 29 degrees here in New York.
A chilly Valentine's evening to you.
I have to get gas.
The Los Angeles trial
of Sirhan Sirhan...
I have Dee for you.
Who the hell is Dee?
From the Los Angeles office.
She has Mr. Chaough
on the line.
You've got to be kidding me.
Tell him I'm busy.
Do you want me
to take a message?
No, I want you
to leave a message.
I'm sorry, I don't understand.
Tell her to tell Ted
that I have no intention
of talking to him today.
And that's it.
That's all I said.
Okay.
That's what she said.
You know what, Shirley?
I've been thinking about it
and I know it's silly,
but could you please
throw these flowers away?
Why?
I'm sorry, but they're cursed.
No, they're not.
They're beautiful.
Look, I should have
bought you flowers
out of respect,
not because of some holiday.
Are these some symbol
of how much we're loved?
- It's a joke.
- Please, don't.
I'll get you some new ones.
Please, those are my flowers.
They're from my fiancé.
- Since when?
- Since this morning.
Why didn't you tell me?
You didn't give me a chance.
I didn't give you a chance?
They've been sitting
in there all day.
- Now you're just embarrassing me.
- I didn't mean to.
You know what?
You should have never told me.
That would have been
a great gift.
Who cares about
your stupid flowers?
You have a ring on.
We all know that you're engaged.
You did not have
to embarrass me.
Grow up.
10:00 a.m.?
Thank you.
Come in.
I just wanted to say
I was on my way to the club
and I noticed there's been
a change in reception.
I had to shuffle the girls.
Well, I'm all for the national
advancement of colored people,
but I do not believe
they should advance
all the way to the front
of this office.
People can see her
from the elevator.
I'm sorry.
Do you want me to dismiss her
based on the color of her skin?
I said nothing of the kind.
I'm merely suggesting
a rearrangement
of your rearrangement.
Suggesting?
Requesting.
Hello?
- Bonnie?
- Pete?
Hello, Valentine.
What a pleasant surprise.
Did you come to see me work?
Because I wasn't
expecting you till 5:00.
There's been a change of plans.
You're going to be showing me
around your body
at a bungalow
at the Beverly Hills Hotel.
The devil and his temptations.
I will be there at 5:15
unless I get an offer.
You have an offer.
I love my flowers.
And I love you.
But I also love the 15 strangers
who might buy this dump.
Well, excuse me if I don't see
the point right now.
I mean, I landed that whale
and New York just took it away.
And I realized if the system's
rigged against me,
I might as well enjoy myself.
I once sold a house
for $108,000.
Two weeks later, during escrow,
it burned down.
I had driven this Okie couple
around for a year.
Bought lunches,
looked at pictures
of their hideous children.
Do you know where Altadena is?
Might as well be Barstow.
I'd show up and have
to change my blouse
because the sweat stains
were meeting between my breasts.
I could have lived for months
on that commission.
And then it was all gone
because some asshole
barreling down Lake Avenue
threw his cigarette
out the window.
I'm sorry,
but it's not the same.
It's worse.
I'm in sales, too.
Not some housewife complaining
about getting oatmeal out of a carpet.
An act of God, Pete,
that's how you know
when things are really against you.
You don't seem
very upset about it.
'Cause that's the thrill.
Our fortunes
are in other people's hands
and we have to take them.
I want to chew you up
and spit you out.
Put the sign back.
You sure you don't want anything?
I told you, I'm not hungry.
How are your studies?
Spectacular.
Do you want a French fry?
They're cold.
Know what?
I'm gonna get some coffee.
I should probably
call my friends.
They're probably worried.
Want ice cream or something?
Did you even need gas?
I wanted to talk to you.
The reason I didn't tell you
I wasn't working
was because I didn't
want anyone to know.
Got it.
I didn't behave well.
I said the wrong things
to the wrong people
at the wrong time.
What did you say?
I told the truth about myself.
But it wasn't the right time... then.
So they made me
take some time off and...
I was ashamed.
What was the truth?
Nothing you don't know.
So what are you gonna do?
I don't know.
It's kind of up to them.
If you're not going to work,
why don't you stay with Megan?
Because I wanted
to be here to fix it.
How?
I don't know.
Do you still love Megan?
Of course I do.
You know I visit
every couple weeks.
I talk to her all the time.
Why don't you just tell her that you
don't want to move to California?
Go ahead.
- Can I get a Coke?
- Sure.
- I'm sorry to bother you.
- What do you want, Peggy?
Well, I'd like Shirley off my desk.
What?
What did she do?
There was an incident today
and I'm not comfortable
with her on my desk.
I shouldn't have to
tell you more than that.
- So just fire her.
- I didn't say that.
She can work anywhere
in the office you want.
I just want someone else.
Fine.
- You can share Moira.
- She hates me.
- Meredith.
- She has the mind of a child.
Damn it, Peggy!
Dawn can't work with Lou.
Neither of them
can work out front.
Scarlett and Harry
are practically married.
- What do you want me to do?
- Fix it!
All I know is that
today was a workday
and I didn't get anything done.
- What do you want?!
- I'm sorry.
Since the meeting was aborted,
I wanted to get some details
regarding Avon.
But perhaps now
is not a good time.
We're just having
some personnel issues.
I just realized
you have two jobs, don't you?
- I'm not complaining.
- Maybe you should.
What are the skills
required down here?
Organization?
Fortitude?
Lack of concern
for being unliked?
I suppose.
Well...
there's an office open upstairs.
It's for an account man,
not the head of personnel.
What do you mean?
Let me know what you decide.
We can talk about
Avon on Monday.
Good night.
- Hello?
- It's me.
Where the hell are you?
We've got you covered
till lights out.
Ankle Fat thinks
you're at a church somewhere
with Sarah crying
on your shoulder.
Thanks, but I'm with my dad.
He wrote me a note.
You're never going to believe
what happened on the train.
There was this creepy
salesman from Milford.
He's really old,
but he keeps smiling at us
and he wants to take us
to the smoker.
- Yolanda said...
- You know what, Carol?
- I should go.
- Well, we hid your booty.
Your sandals, they're in the back
of the closet next to your cleats.
So at least the trip
was worth it.
I'll see you later.
Bye.
What's this?
I sot you a patty melt.
Everything okay?
Mm-hmm.
I don't like
you going to funerals.
It was awful.
Sarah's mom was yellow.
She was wearing this wig.
I hate that you had to see that.
I only went
so I could go shopping.
I doubt that.
I don't know.
Life goes on.
I'm so many people.
Can you see the car from here?
Yes.
Good.
I want you to finish your meal.
I'm gonna go out to the car
and get it running.
Then you walk out.
We're not gonna pay.
Really?
Don't bother with the flowers.
Everyone's gone.
No, these are mine.
They're from my son.
Thank you, Roger.
Well, I bet he's gonna be pretty upset
if he sees you giving them away.
I'm not.
I'm taking them
to my new office.
Up here?
It was suggested that I move
now that I have some accounts.
Jim suggested it?
Do you disagree?
Does it matter?
Well, Rome wasn't built in a day.
Ah, hello.
Hello.
Apparently we're going to finish
that conference call on Monday.
That won't be necessary.
I set Pete straight.
Hmm, glad to hear it.
I'd hate to think of you
as an adversary.
I'd really hate that.
You sure I don't have to go in
and talk to anyone?
No, I have the note.
Happy Valentine's Day.
I love you.