NARRATOR:
Previously on Prison Break:
-The Company's moving Scylla.
-When?
-Tomorrow.
-I messed up.
-What do you mean?
-I mentioned Whistler.
[LINE RINGS]
Hello? Hello?
So you're Feng?
-Susan?
-That's right.
The wall itself
is fortified with steel fiber.
The bad news is that there are both
weight and microphonic sensors...
...that will alert Company security
to the presence of any human being...
...that weighs more than 2 pounds.
LINCOLN:
Michael.
SARA:
You have a hypothalamus hamartoma.
And the doctor feels
that you need surgery.
-Two days.
-No. Tomorrow.
Otherwise, you could die,
and there's no alternative.
[DRILL WHIRRING]
Just a little bit more. Go slow.
[MOUTHS]
You ready?
[VACUUM WHIRRING]
GRETCHEN: You know, there's no way
he deserves any of this.
-Sing it, sister.
-After what he put me through.
I can hardly believe it myself.
Look, what we must do is make sure
that cosmic justice rains down upon him.
But once we obtain
the good general's card...
...there ain't hardly nothing standing in
between us and Mr. Feng's $125 million.
[DOOR OPENS]
[GASPS]
I was born on a mountainside.
Just keep both hands on the camera.
Let's go.
Mm.
[CAMERA PHONE CLICKING]
Oh, yeah.
That's great. Okay.
Thank you so much, Dr. Malden.
-Yeah. He can see you today at 3.
MICHAEL: No.
-You're going.
-We need to finish what we started.
-We can do this.
-I need one more day.
Michael, Dr. Malden
can see you today.
He's given us his word
he won't alert authorities.
If you put this off and you collapse...
...you're gonna be treated
by another doctor.
Do you wanna roll the dice
that they're not gonna call the cops?
There's still so much to do.
All right.
Three o'clock?
SUCRE:
Last time I drill a hole in the wall...
...was with an egg beater
back in Fox River with Michael.
I just can't believe
it's all coming to an end.
And he's not here.
He'll be all right.
SUCRE:
How do you know?
I don't.
I'm just trying to keep us focused.
Hey...
...he's sick.
But I guarantee you,
one thing that'll make him worse...
...going back to jail.
Yeah, if we don't get in there...
...that's where we're all going.
SARA:
He's gonna be okay.
I'm scared too. But a hospital's
the best place for him right now.
He won't go without a plan
to complete the job.
Well...
...Alex and Fernando should be
back soon with the video, right?
Should be, yeah.
So then all we need is the sixth card.
Gretchen's working on that.
-You really think we can trust her?
-With the card?
Absolutely.
Anything else?
Nope.
Eight guards will accompany Scylla
from the bunker up to the garage...
...where a truck will be waiting.
One truck is not going to be
enough security.
That is why I have a full Secret Service
escort to March Air Force Base.
There, it will be brought
aboard a C-130.
We need air support
all the way to River Rock.
Colonel Rififi is lending us
three of his F-18's.
It may be hard for you to believe,
but I do have this under control.
There's nothing for you to worry about.
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
SARA: When the plane lands,
the same precautions will be taken.
Armored truck to guards
to final location.
That's fine.
[SCOFFS]
-Are you going somewhere?
-I have an appointment.
Today?
You told me
there was nothing to worry about.
Just tell me it's not Gretchen.
-This is ridiculous.
-It's personal. I'm not going to discuss it.
-I don't trust her.
-That's nothing new.
I'll be back in an hour.
MICHAEL:
What'd you find out?
You'll be awake the whole time.
The only anesthetic you're gonna need
is minor injections...
...local, two in your forehead
and two in the back of your head.
-And that's for the brace?
-The frame, yeah.
And attaching that is gonna be
the most uncomfortable part.
They're gonna have to secure four pins
into your skull...
...and they're gonna need
a small drill to do it.
-Do we have to listen to this?
-I wanna hear this, Linc.
And then what?
Uh, another CT scan. The doctor will use
the three-dimensional imagery...
...to pinpoint the exact location
of the growth.
And once you have that?
Then it's the gamma knife unit.
They'll fit you with a helmet.
They'll calibrate it
so that each of the 201 holes...
...are aimed directly for the tumor,
and at that point, it's just a matter of--
SELF: I've got two more boxes in the car
that you guys gotta bring in yourself.
All right.
You okay?
-Because the last time I saw you--
-I'm fine. I was just a little dehydrated.
All right, good.
This is the stuff you requested.
Sure this is gonna get you in?
Let us worry about getting in.
You worry about how we're getting out.
I got someone on
Gretchen and Bagwell.
If they try anything,
they're getting taken out.
Nothing's gonna get between us
and Scylla.
You sure you're all right?
Yeah. It's just, you know, we're
breaking into Company headquarters...
...and you'll understand
why we're on edge.
Understood.
When your father approached me
about doing this...
...I felt like I was chasing a ghost
or something...
...but because of the work
you guys have done, today's the day.
We're gonna take
these bastards down.
LINCOLN:
You got it?
MAHONE:
Got it.
We got four hours.
SUCRE: How come?
-I'm going in for treatment.
[SUCRE SIGHS]
MAHONE:
There we go.
Scylla.
MICHAEL:
Obviously, we've got a lot to figure out.
We have to break through two walls,
one concrete and one glass...
...and do it without making a sound.
Hypersensitive parabolic microphones
pointed in all directions.
Floor sensors can detect an added
surface load of just 2 pounds, so...
[REMOTE BEEPS]
...we have to traverse the distance
between the walls...
...without touching the floor.
We need to do all that without generating
any kind of body heat whatsoever.
Of course, they have the latest
in heat-sensing technology.
We make one wrong move...
...the camera goes on,
and General Krantz knows we're inside.
It's amazing. All this security...
...and only one man
has access to video surveillance.
The Company doesn't want any record
of what’s going on.
-Can we access that elevator?
-It's in the middle of the building.
There are 10 layers of security. We
have to go where they're not expecting.
Now, starting with the concrete wall,
you were drilling there, right?
Yes. Fortified with steel fibers,
like you said.
In order to get through that...
...we have to generate
an electromagnetic field.
We have to generate
To have an electromagnetic field
with the force that we want...
...we're gonna need at least a couple
of car batteries. Can you get that?
Yeah, yeah.
We can do this.
[SIGHS]
Uh, what time are we expecting
Gretchen to get that sixth card?
What took you so long?
You know how I get when I'm hungry.
It wasn't easy
getting away from the office.
I could have come to you,
like old times.
I almost wish
there was a mahogany desk in here.
Oh. You're tense.
Take off this jacket.
Let me get in there.
I didn't bring it with me.
My card.
That is what you're looking for, right?
-What are you talking about, your card?
-You forget...
...I'm the one that
taught you how to lie.
I never thought
that at the age of 63...
...I could still have my heart broken.
Why did you feel you needed
to steal my card?
Don't you know that
if you’d waited a little bit longer...
...you'd have had one of your own?
I'm sorry. I'm....
-Who are you selling it to?
-That's not why--
Who?
I'm the mother of your child.
Please, for Emily's sake.
Please, Jonathan. Please.
I love you.
If I ever see you again...
...I'll shoot you on sight.
[DOOR SLAMS]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
Is everything all right, Cole?
I got something important
you need to know.
We're gonna be rich.
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
So here's the question:
How much is it gonna cost me
to get that jacket off of you?
-Excuse me?
-Last day I'm ever gonna see you.
You're all covered up.
I cannot abide. One hundred dollars.
You wanna pay me
to take my clothes off?
-Not all of them, just the jacket.
-Mm.
-Two hundred?
-I'm not gonna strip for you.
Pity an old man.
-You're disgusting.
-And lecherous and vile.
And soon to be wealthy
beyond belief.
One thousand dollars.
Why so modest all of a sudden?
Cole, I need to see you
in my office, now.
[PHONE RINGING]
Thank you for calling GATE.
How can I help you?
It was Mr. White in his office
with the lead stapler.
Cole, yesterday with that Idaho group,
you made this company $35,000.
And I would like to return the favor.
It's our annual cruise.
Seven days and six nights
of nonstop pitching.
I personally clear
$50,000 on most trips.
But for everything you've done...
...it's all yours. The least I could do.
It leaves today.
Go home and pack.
I'll see you in a week.
Unfortunately, I have some business
I need to take care of right here.
SARA:
Okay. So this is how it works.
As soon as the sensors pick up any kind
of a heat source, 90 degrees or more...
...system goes into standby.
A yellow light comes on.
After five seconds, if the heat source
isn't gone, we have an alarm.
We got six seconds to make it across
the hallway and through the glass wall?
-Basically.
-If we get our hands on liquid nitrogen...
...we could regulate the temperature.
Yeah.
MAHONE:
Kill two birds with one stone.
See if you can get some of that.
Hey.
I'm not gonna ask you how you feel.
Good.
About four years
after I joined the bureau...
...my first special agent in charge,
he was diagnosed with liver cancer.
But for him, the hardest part wasn't
the treatment. The hardest part...
...was leaving the office,
because we had this big RICO case...
...that was about to go to trial.
And we're talking thousands of
man-hours and five years of research...
...and the guy was
gonna be in chemo.
And he was scared.
He was scared
we were gonna lose the case...
...and a lot of bad men
were gonna walk.
Let me guess. He had a ragtag band
of criminals ready to pick up the slack.
[TOOLS CLANKING]
Yeah, something like that.
[SIGHS]
We're not gonna let you down,
Michael.
What happened to your boss?
Oh, he was there to see us win.
You sure she's a fed?
Wouldn't take off her jacket for $1000.
She's got a gun under there.
It's a complication.
Well, that's a nice way to put it.
Like you not getting the sixth card.
What are we calling that, a setback?
Relax.
You have any idea
what I've giving up here?
I was guaranteed 50 grand.
You're crying over $50,000?
Are you serious?
I have a job. I make money.
I get mail. People call me "sir."
Working 12-hour days
and eating leftover lo mein.
Something tells me Bagwell
wouldn't last long in this situation.
Yeah, maybe.
But Cole Pfeiffer would.
You wanna pout? You do it tomorrow.
We have work to do.
DRIVER: Is it really worth $125 million?
FENG: It's worth twice as much.
-What if they refuse to hand it over?
-Either we pay for Scylla or we kill for it.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
-Susan.
-Feng.
We need to talk.
[DRILL WHIRRING]
MAHONE: Hey, give me
a second here, guys. Just a second. Shh.
We can't make any noise
above 10 decibels.
-You got two of those?
-Absolutely.
This is gonna work, right?
-It should.
-No, not just that.
The whole thing.
I mean, do we even have a chance?
Just make sure the hole
is in the right place.
[SEAGULLS CAWING]
MICHAEL:
So where are we?
[SIGHS]
Gretchen didn't get us the sixth card.
-We need that sixth card, Don.
-I know.
We don't get the card,
we never crack Scylla.
I know it.
So, what else do we know?
What else do we know?
We know they're moving Scylla today.
We can't waltz into the general's office
and steal that card.
So where does that leave us?
-There has to be a way.
-Not without losing another man.
I spent the week trying
to figure out how to get that card.
Every scenario ends with a gun to
someone's head. That is not acceptable.
Look, Gretchen did pass on
this one piece of information for you.
This could be helpful.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
The buyer just showed up.
SELF: All right, well,
find out what they're up to.
Mr. Feng, so glad
you could come and see us.
I was expecting the next time the three
of us would be in a room together...
...that you'd have something for me.
That was our expectation as well,
but we've hit a few bumps in the road.
Now, to ensure
the item's safe recovery...
...we need your help.
[BOAT HORN BLARING]
It's time to go.
[MICHAEL SIGHS]
All that avails is flight.
Maybe my father
was on to something.
If they all die because we tried
to take down the Company...
...and I survive...
...because I called in sick...
...how am I gonna live with myself?
LINCOLN: You're gonna get through this.
-I'm not going to the hospital.
What?
Linc, just get in the car.
I'm going with you.
If I still had a medical license,
I'd lose it over this.
This is usually given to epileptics.
It will suppress the rapid firing
of neurons for the next three hours...
...making it unlikely
that you'll have a seizure in that time.
But, Michael, any added
mental or physical stress....
-I get it.
-I mean it.
I don't want you to move
unless you absolutely have to.
And as soon as this is over,
I'm taking you to the hospital.
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Hey.
You all right?
This is gonna go exactly as planned.
I promise.
I'm not praying for me.
LINCOLN:
Let's go.
You wanted to see me.
It's the second Tuesday of the month.
Don't you have
your Eagles and Angels luncheon?
I figured I'd skip it today.
You called me in here
to confirm my lunch plans?
You were right.
If it weren't for you,
this would be in the wind.
Is she dead?
Let's just say she won't bother
either of us anymore.
But I do want Scylla moved right now.
Mechanics are on the tarmac
inspecting the C-130.
When they sign off,
we'll be ready to move.
Call the other cardholders.
Get them in here.
Did Self call you regarding
the little snafu with the general?
Get out of my way.
Just for clarification's sake...
...the sixth card is part of
the to-do list, right, gentlemen?
[PHONE DIALING]
[LINE DIALING]
[PHONE RINGS]
The game's afoot.
GRETCHEN: Does Michael
have a way to get the card?
I've worked with Michael before,
both with him and against him.
There's no way he's going down there
without a plan to finish the job.
I got a call from a friend.
Heard Scylla was in play.
He wants to know
if he can get in on it.
-A bidding war?
-He's prepared to offer 200.
-Is he for real?
-I don't know.
I've set up a safe house where we can
hear him out. Have a pen?
Just a minute.
1917 Piermont.
1-9-1-7 Piermont.
Got it. I'm on my way.
Good afternoon.
Thank you for calling GATE.
Ahem. I got some last-minute
negotiations with the buyer...
...to speak about.
-I'll be back lickety-split.
-Okay. See you later.
Mm-hm. Can you hold, please?
MICHAEL:
All right.
This is it.
Now, does anyone have any questions
about what they're supposed to do?
The hole you drilled in the wall
this morning...
...once we get over there,
if we make too much noise...
...the sound waves will travel...
...and get picked up
by the sensors on the other side.
So from this point on,
we need absolute silence.
Alex, good luck.
You too.
You all ready?
All right.
We have to break through two walls,
one concrete and one glass...
...and do it without making a sound.
In order to get through that, we have
to generate an electromagnetic field.
To have an electromagnetic field
with the force that we want...
...we're gonna need at least a couple
of car batteries.
MICHAEL: Starting with the concrete
wall, you were drilling there, right?
Yes. Fortified with steel fibers,
just like you said.
[ELECTRICITY BUZZING]
[VACUUM WHIRRING]
[LINCOLN SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
[LINCOLN GRUNTING]
You sure this is it?
-1917 Piermont Avenue.
-Okay.
When was the last time
you swept a room?
The academy.
Just follow my lead...
...because Gretchen and Bagwell
have no respect for human life.
-Okay? They go for a weapon, you shoot.
-Okay.
They try to run, you shoot.
They do anything than
kneel down, hands behind--
-I shoot.
-Don't miss.
MAN:
Agent Self.
We've been waiting.
[CHATTERING]
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
That's Feng. He's got them.
When Scofield and Burrows walk through,
give them an opportunity to surrender.
If we can avoid confrontation,
that's the best-case scenario.
There's no way they're gonna
hand it over without a fight.
If they take that position,
we'll respond.
A hundred and twenty-five
million dollars.
Only cherry
that could top this sunny day.
You can keep your Burrows
and your Mahone and your Sucre.
Just leave Scofield for me.
We got a green light on the C-130.
It's time.
[GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
[PANTING]
[MICHAEL PANTING]
[GRUNTS]
Okay, thank you.
Oren, Tuxhorn and Edison
are standing by.
Scuderi was in Las Vegas.
You think we could get the state
of Nevada to outlaw gambling?
I somehow doubt that.
His plane will touch down
within an hour.
-Then you can make your lunch.
-I would rather stay.
Now, more than ever, we need
the support of law enforcement.
I will call you
when we're ready to move.
-General, I--
-There's nothing more to worry about.
Lisa?
Very good work.
[GLASS SCRAPING]
[SIGHS]
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
I need a team downstairs. Now.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
[ENGLISH SDH]