I'm Chuck. Here's a couple
of things you need to know.
I had a fiancée. Now she thinks I'm dead.
Alex.
You got a daughter, Casey.
- Do you think Ellie's happy in your marriage?
- Of course. Did she say something?
This is about your father.
There are some bad people looking for him.
Including a man named John Casey.
I knew it.
You downloaded the Intersect 2.0.
The Intersect,
it can have a negative effect on the brain.
Your dreams are all proof of stress...
...likely leading
to serious mental deterioration.
So, what did you wanna tell me?
About the doctor?
He said that I'm fine.
Wait a minute. You dreamt Shaw was alive?
Chuck, you saw him die.
It's called the Governor.
It governs my neural network.
Control the power of the Intersect.
Could that work for the 2.0?
It will. I'm gonna make you one.
So how's everything, uh--?
How's everything coming?
Same as last time you asked me.
Can I get you anything?
Like a-- Like a juice? Or coffee?
Maybe a breakfast sandwich?
I'm fine, Charles. Just relax.
Relax. That's good.
That's good.
Is this really gonna work?
This whole Governor thingy?
I'm still alive, aren't I?
Look, based on the schematics
of my own Governor...
...I'm gonna create a new one
that'll control Intersect 2.0 before--
Before what? Before I go nuts? Because
that's exactly what The Ring wants.
Your brain is working fine so far.
Who wouldn't be paranoid in your shoes?
Your cover's blown, base discovered...
...your dead partner and
girlfriend's ex-lover was a double agent.
- Way to talk me down, Dad.
- What I-- What I'm trying to say is...
...your courage makes me very proud.
But there's some battles
you have to walk away from.
What are you saying, run? Turn my back
on everyone that I care about?
There may come a time
when if you wanna protect them...
...you have to go.
- Go where?
- Vacation.
Dad was saying he thinks I might need
to get out of here, take a little break.
Well, he's right.
You've been a little nervous.
So is this what you two
have been working on?
Yeah, a little family heirloom
Dad's just sprucing up for me.
He doesn't need you looking over
his shoulder. You can use some fresh air.
She's right, Charles. Smell the roses.
I'd really rather not, Dad.
Seasonal allergies. Runs in the family.
Listen to the man.
He knows what's best for you.
Dude. You don't look so hot, buddy.
Compared to normal level of hotness,
you've lost a little sizzle.
I'm looking for my wife, Morgan.
She didn't come home last night.
- You don't say.
- I do say.
Why would I know where Ellie is? Heh.
Why did you think there was something
wrong with our marriage?
No reason. You know, just kind of--
Don't BS me. If something is up with Ellie,
I wanna know about it now.
Oh, boy.
She's having an affair.
She's cheating on you, bro.
What? That's impossible.
Casey intercepted an illicit phone message
and he played it for me.
- Ellie would never--
- Devon.
- Whoa.
- I'm sorry.
You just called me Devon.
Yeah. Well, this is no time for frivolity.
I need to see you.
Devon thinks I'm at the hospital.
It's getting harder and harder to lie.
I know.
How could she do this to us?
I need to call my wife.
I gotta get in on some of this Ellie action.
That is why I choose not to get married.
That's why I ward them off.
I need to call my husband.
It's weird, I'm not getting a signal.
It's blocked.
We can't have enemy operatives...
- ...like John Casey tracking you.
- He's on the loose?
He had fled by the time our team
got to your apartment.
- I have to call Chuck. I have to protect him.
- Ellie.
We're in the process of bringing
your brother in. You're safe here.
And John Casey knows better
than to show his face soon.
One apple pie.
And one cup of coffee.
Black and bitter.
Actually, I didn't order yet.
I ordered for you. It was easy.
You always get the same thing.
And you always sit in the same seat
facing the door.
A creature of habit, what can I say?
- What happened to your face?
- Hmm?
Kitchen accident. It's nothing.
Hey, how'd that, uh, criminal psych final
of yours go?
Piece of cake.
I'm set to graduate next week.
Your days of slinging pie are numbered.
Don't worry. I'll make sure the next girl
gets your order right.
You won't even miss me, John.
Thanks, Alex.
All of these people,
any of whom could be Ring agents.
Come on. Switch off your spy mode.
- You're gonna drive yourself crazy.
- I've been down that road, haven't I?
Well, the CIA shrink said that you have
nothing to worry about, remember?
Other than The Ring trying
to kill my father...
...or me imagining that Shaw
is still out there and trying to kill me.
Look, your father is safe and not only that,
but he's here with you, which is great.
And Shaw? Shaw is dead.
I know what you went through.
You have to start putting it behind you.
- What if I can't?
- Mm. Then there is always blueberries.
How is this possibly supposed to make--?
Oh, my God, these are amazing blueberries.
Mm-hm. Wait till you try them with cream.
Be right back.
But--
Beautiful day, isn't it?
- Well, you have a good one. Thank you.
- Those look so good.
Oh, sorry, sorry, sorry.
Excuse me.
Ma'am. Whoa, excuse me.
I gotta go.
I must be losing my mind.
Sure this isn't one
of your Intersect dreams?
Yes. As a matter of fact, I am sure.
Okay, Shaw is alive.
He was taunting me.
We have to call Beckman.
Already tried.
Her assistant said that she's indisposed.
Indisposed?
What is that supposed to mean?
The guy that I killed
is back from the dead.
A guy who, keep in mind,
is a Ring operative.
Who knows our covers, where Castle is.
- What station did you see him in?
- North Hollywood.
- Time?
- Maybe half an hour ago.
- North or southbound?
- South.
Any of this look familiar?
You can't miss Bartowski
running around like a chicken.
Slow it down.
Punch in. Right there, Dad.
Oh, my God. Daniel.
Uh, do we know what station he got off at?
One sec. Let me run
the facial-recognition software.
Hollywood and Western.
Bingo. Where did he exit?
There he is.
What the hell is he doing?
We need to follow Shaw, take him down.
That's one way. Other option
is they're leading you into a trap.
It's not like we're going in
empty-handed.
- You know how I feel about this, Charles.
- Yeah, I do. But I don't have a choice.
Exactly what The Ring wants you to think.
There's always a choice.
What choice would that be, Dad?
To run away?
I'm not you. I'm not gonna spend
the rest of my life in hiding.
I can't leave the ones I love behind.
Let's go.
It's been a long time since I kissed you
Hey, hey, hey. What are you--
--doing here, man?
My life is over.
My wife has given herself
to another man.
Hey. Your wife has given you a pass.
You're now free to mount
whomever you wish to.
If he had been doing more mounting,
he wouldn't be in this situation.
You think that my wife is unfaithful to me
because I'm not satisfying her?
While you're wasting your time
at the gym or the hospital...
...your wife is at home alone,
unoccupied.
So she hired herself a pinch hitter.
Can't believe your missus
has taken on new customers.
It's my dream come true.
Ellie is exactly like Chuck,
but with lady parts.
Okay, I'm gonna go now.
- Unh!
- Whoa, whoa. Come on.
That's the spirit, son. Show the old lady
you know how to swing that bat.
Nice work, guys. Awesome.
- What?
- No, not you, Awesome. That--
General, I wanna thank you in advance
for your testimony.
It's my understanding
you've been in charge of the Intersect...
...since it accidentally was put
into a civilian.
A one Charles Bartowski.
- Is that correct?
- Yes, sir, that is correct.
Is it also correct that the project has fallen
well short of its original expectations?
Yes, sir, also correct.
But if I may add, Agents Bartowski,
Walker and Colonel Casey...
...have proven to be an excellent,
albeit unorthodox team.
The mission is to grab Shaw or kill him.
Whichever's quicker.
Hey, open sesame.
Okay. We'll split up. Each take a floor.
General Merriweather,
members of the tribunal...
...you must understand.
Agent Bartowski has in many ways
exceeded expectations.
I am not denying
that the road has been long and rocky.
But after three years...
...Charles Bartowski is poised to become
the weapon we have always dreamed of.
- Justin. What's going on?
- We've been breached.
- Casey, isn't it?
- Don't worry.
I'm not gonna let anything happen to you,
Ellie. We can handle John Casey.
- You're supposed to be upstairs.
- Searched the whole floor.
Nobody here.
Something wrong with this place.
Look.
It's a government-grade biometric scanner.
You'll never get through that.
Come on, let's go.
Casey, this is not a Ring base.
It's one of ours.
We gotta go find Chuck.
Justin?
- Justin?
- Unh!
Chuck?
Ellie.
Ellie. Ellie, what are you doing here?
What are you doing here?
You just punched a person.
Thought you quit kung fu
in the third grade.
I-- Look, I'll explain later. Right now,
we have to get out of here. Come on.
No. You don't understand.
You've been brought for protection.
Justin is my CIA handler.
CIA handler? You don't understand, okay?
This guy is not CIA.
- Everyone works for an evil organization.
- Jeremy.
Chuck, wait.
In conclusion, general...
...I would stake my reputation
on the success of Agent Bartowski.
- As you were saying, General Beckman?
- What the hell are you doing, Bartowski?
Chuck, what the hell is going on?
Apparently, I have no idea.
- Where's my sister?
- She's being escorted back to her residence.
What was she doing here?
- You are dismissed.
- General, what the hell is going on?
I don't know how else to explain it,
Chuck.
But all our asse-- Careers are on the line.
Committee is here to determine
if Intersect Project is a liability.
Let me talk to them. Shaw is somewhere
in this building, we saw him.
If there is one thing you can do
to protect the Intersect Project...
...it's keep your mouth shut.
Walker, Casey and Bartowski, it's been
brought to this committee's attention...
...the Intersect is unstable, expensive,
and most of all, dangerous.
- That's outrageous.
- Sit down, Chuck.
I'm sorry, general. Generals, this is crazy.
Provide one shred of evidence.
- Who said this?
- I did.
Hello, Chuck.
Sarah.
Shaw?
This man that stands before you
is a Ring operative.
He kidnapped me and he drugged me
and he tried to kill me.
All of that is completely true.
Except for the killing part.
In fact,
I was sanctioned by this committee--
Why was I not apprised of this,
General Merriweather?
Continue, Agent Shaw.
I was acting as a double agent,
working within The Ring.
- That is, until Chuck shot me.
- He's lying. Do not listen to a word he says.
I came here today
to make one thing perfectly clear.
Charles Bartowski is an American hero.
He didn't ask for the Intersect. It's not
Chuck's fault that his brain is deteriorating.
Excuse me, Agent Bartowski
was given a full psychological exam...
- ...and he was cleared for all field work.
- Sarah.
Do you wanna tell her the truth,
or should I?
- What is he talking about, Chuck?
- Dr. Dreyfus' report.
"The subject's mental decline
is both inevitable and irreversible.
Agent Bartowski's mind
will soon succumb to paranoia...
...dementia, psychosis. Possibly worse."
I understand why your boyfriend
didn't wanna worry you.
Sarah, I was gonna tell you.
It is my recommendation
that the Intersect Project be aborted.
Before any decisions are made...
...this committee needs to review
the Intersect's successful missions.
Hugo Panzer.
Taken out by Bartowski's team.
With a combination of a fencing foil,
nunchakus and turbulence.
Alexis White. Died while trying...
- Guys. Casey. Sarah.
- Zip it, Bartowski. Figure a way out later.
No, but-- He's an Intersect.
Daniel Shaw is an Intersect.
Sit down, Agent Bartowski.
It's okay, general. I'm glad you're
seeing this. See, he's not in control.
I'm in complete control.
I realize that what I'm about to do now...
...might come across
as some kind of insane gesture...
...or maybe a completely
insane gesture.
But because I am, in fact, sane...
...and I am certain
that Daniel Shaw is an Intersect...
...I'm just gonna have to prove it to you.
Chuck, no.
- He's supposed to catch it.
- Guards, remove Mr. Bartowski!
No, he's an Intersect.
No, he's an Intersect! Sarah, I'm sorry.
These proceedings are adjourned
until further notice.
We gotta get out. Walked into a trap.
- What about Chuck?
- Nothing we can do for him.
We have to call Washington
and tell them what's going on.
Most of Washington is in that room.
Shaw and The Ring
have taken over the CIA.
He's got the whole chain of command. God
knows how many Ring agents are inside.
It's only a matter of time
before they burn us too.
So you're just gonna run?
It's not just us they're gonna come after.
They'll come after
the people we care about.
- You coming?
- No.
Everything I care about
is inside this building.
Good luck, Agent Walker.
Sarah.
- Ellie.
- Devon...
...I need to talk to you.
Where have you been all night?
I need you to listen to me really carefully.
I have been keeping a secret
and I feel horrible about it.
No, stop. Okay? I just--
I don't think I can hear the words right now.
It's my fault.
I haven't been stepping up to the plate.
- I need you to be strong.
- I can be stronger. I'll double my workouts.
Devon, stop it.
Chuck is in trouble with the CIA.
- What?
- Chuck.
Our Chuck...
...punched a CIA agent in the face today
and they are holding him right now.
You haven't been cheating on me?
What? Devon, what are you talking about?
No, listen. I think he's gonna need a lawyer.
No, no.
Chuck has been with the CIA for years.
I'm so glad you finally know.
What a relief it is to talk.
You don't know.
Oh, no. I just told you.
You are gonna tell me everything you know.
Right now.
Sure.
- Alex.
- Come here for the pie too, Colonel Casey?
- I think it's the best in town.
- There you are.
And you brought a friend.
- Table for two, please.
- Right this way.
Mosley, you're
needed in the conference room, ASAP.
That means run.
Follow you where, Dad?
Chuck.
Here you go.
- Thank you very much.
- You're welcome. Enjoy.
- Pretty girl. So much to live for.
- Mm.
Be a shame if she didn't.
Not hungry?
Why don't you put your hands
on the table, John?
Good.
Mm.
Too much nutmeg.
You're a smart guy, John.
I'm sure you figured it out by now.
You're coming with me.
I gotta say, John...
...I never figured you for a dad.
Well, I'm not a very good one.
- What are you doing?
- Saving your life.
Chuck? Wait. Where are you going?
- Sarah. I have to leave. My dad is coming.
- You can't. Stay and fight.
If you run, they'll put a burn notice on you
and you'll be running forever.
We have to move. Right now.
If you run
there's a bull's-eye on your back.
They will never,
ever stop looking for you.
Everyone you love will be in danger.
- Who do you wanna protect? You or her?
- Dad, please, don't make--
Right now, Charles.
You have to run to protect her.
I'm sorry, Sarah. I'm sorry.
But if I have to choose,
I will always choose to protect you.
Sorry, Alex.
But this is for your own safety.
You have to believe
I would never hurt you.
No, just forcibly kidnap me.
Take it. This is the key to my locker
at the Burbank Buy More.
Everything inside is yours now.
Look, Mr. Casey,
if you want me to hear you...
...let's step out of the car and talk...
...so that I don't feel
like my life is in jeopardy.
Please.
- Okay.
Alex. Wait, wait, wait!
- No, no, no. Wait!
- Unh!
I got an A in my self-defense class.
Oh. Alex.
Alex, I'm your father.
That's impossible.
My father's dead. He was a war hero.
- He died before I was even born.
- No, I didn't.
Stop it.
You were named after your dad, Alex.
You're named after me.
My real name's Alex Coburn.
Please. You have to trust me.
You have to get to your mom
and disappear.
Go, Alex. Run!
CIA! John Casey,
put your hands on top of your head.
The whole generalissimo thing?
I was undercover on a mission.
That's it. That's all I know, babe.
Oh, and you can blame the CIA
for my bachelor party.
Stripper? She was an agent.
Told you I didn't cheat. Faithful.
I can't believe that my brother
and Sarah are spies.
How is my dad involved in all this?
I, uh, have pockets of missing knowledge.
I didn't wanna know
because I didn't wanna lie to you, babe.
Devon, an actual,
legitimate answer exists...
...why my father has been missing
my entire life...
...and you didn't think
to ask that question?
- Correct.
- You need to find me somebody...
...who knows a lot more than you do.
Right now.
Morgan Grimes. The boy that took
my pillow as his date to junior prom...
...knows more about my family than I do.
Here. It's valerian root tea and it'll
give your brain a lovely soothing bath.
I don't want a soothing brain bath, Morgan.
I want answers.
Startling revelation. Yeah. I know.
Well, uh, Chuck has been with the company
for quite a while now.
Suffice to say, all is in hand, so...
No, Morgan. All is not in hand. Okay?
The bad guys have my brother.
Hold on.
Nobody said anything about bad guys.
- What bad guys? The Ring?
- What?
The Ring. A criminal organization
hell-bent on world domination.
All I know is that Justin told me
that John Casey is a double agent.
He's here to gather information
about my dad.
But if Chuck is an agent too
then maybe Casey lied to him...
...and turned him somehow?
Our Eagle Scout? Chuck?
Turned? To the dark side?
No. Not gonna happen.
And any suggestions that
Colonel Jonathan Casey's character...
...is in question, well, I would stake
my entire, albeit, okay, thin reputation...
...on the fact that he
is Uncle Sam's most faithful servant.
Fine. Then one of you geniuses
explain to me...
...why the CIA is holding my brother
against his will.
I don't know.
But I will find out.
You wanted to see me, sir?
I'd be remiss if I didn't tell you
you looked great, Walker.
- Love suits you, I guess.
- Shut up.
This is crap and you know it.
Only two people know what happened that
day in Paris. It's your word against mine.
Chuck saw what happened.
We know you tried to kill me.
But Chuck has become
an unreliable witness.
His mind has been compromised
by the Intersect.
And now that he's escaped,
he seems so guilty.
I'm sorry you had to learn
about his mental deterioration...
...in such a public forum.
Sad that he never told you
in a more intimate setting.
Sam.
Put your hands up
and walk out that door...
...and you're gonna tell the generals
what happened in Paris.
- So move it.
- I knew you'd bite.
Drop it, Agent Walker.
Arrest her. She's gone rogue.
It's a shame.
I remember when nothing affected you.
Now you're as emotional
as your boyfriend.
Sarah and Casey will help Chuck.
You check the dojo.
There's a dojo?
- General Beckman?
- Where's Bartowski?
I hoped to find him in Castle.
There's been some sort of mix-up.
Chuck is being held by the CIA.
You could clear this up. Great.
General Beckman, open the door.
- General, what's happening?
- Open the door, now.
They're shutting down the Intersect Project,
including myself.
They apprehended Colonel Casey.
Agent Walker is in custody.
Bartowski escaped this facility.
He is a wanted man.
I need you to find him.
As much as it pains me to admit,
you are our only hope.
You are our only hope.
Get your hands off--
Dude, did she mean you or me?
Finished it.
Your Governor.
It will activate immediately.
Better?
Yeah.
Yeah. Thanks.
Cell? That's not off the grid, Charles.
Dad, it's Morgan.
I never got a chance to say goodbye.
Hey, buddy. Listen, I gotta go away,
I gotta go on a trip with my dad.
I could be gone for a long time.
Yeah. Stop. Sarah is in CIA custody.
Casey has been taken. Beckman too.
What? When did this hap--? What?
Wait! Dad! Dad!
Dad, we have to go back.
Shaw has got Sarah.
And that's no accident. He doesn't
want her. He's trying to trap you.
He's after this.
I'm your father. You cannot ask me.
Please do not ask me
to put my own son in jeopardy.
I can't just walk away, Dad.
Why did you come back? You came back
because you wanted to protect Ellie and me.
Because you knew
you could never live with yourself...
...if something happened
to somebody that you loved.
If we do this...
...we gotta be smart.
Not think emotionally.
We can do this.
We're Bartowskis.
Ellie.
Chuck,
I thought that the CIA still had you.
- I wish I had time to explain.
- You know what...
...it takes just as long to say that
as to tell me what the hell is going on.
We need your help.
Who is "we," Chuck?
The government? The answer is no.
No. We need your help.
Dad?
I thought that you left.
Look, El,
I know you got a lot of questions...
...but right now,
you have the answers that we need.
This is it.
This is where I would meet Justin.
This is our rendezvous point.
There's gotta be more to it.
Shaw has to have another location,
can't be a dead end.
What are you two whispering about?
No more secrets.
You're forgetting something.
Walk us through what would happen
when you met Justin.
I don't know, Dad, this is it.
I'd sit on this bench and we would talk.
And then he'd get up. He'd leave.
He'd go over there.
Through that door.
The subway again.
We need you to stay here, okay?
You just stay right here, on this bench.
If we're not back in 20 minutes, run.
I need to hear you say it.
I need to know that there's a reason
that you left us.
It's a long story.
I wanna tell you everything,
but I gotta take care of this first, okay?
This is the last time I'm gonna walk away
from you.
I promise.
I love you, baby.
You're not gonna get away
with this, Shaw.
Yes, I will.
Love-struck Bartowski will try to come
save you and this time I'll be ready for him.
And his father.
Over here. Over here.
Dad.
This control panel was manufactured
by McTiernan Industries.
It's a Ring subsidiary.
Fake wall.
Aces, Charles.
All right.
Shaw, Bartowski's infiltrated the base.
Of course he did.
Why won't your boyfriend ever think
with an organ besides his heart?
Ahem. No, sir. Not this one.
Bartowski and his father
found the other base. The Ring base.
Triggered the silent alarm.
Damn it.
Hmm.
Don't know when it happened
but our boy became a man.
Bartowski's a spy.
Picked a good one, Walker.
Finally.
Oh, my God.
This is what I've
been having dreams about.
Dr. Kowambe's medical experiments,
cellular regeneration.
It's identical. They did it.
I can't believe The Ring built one.
They must have saved Shaw's life.
And then turned him into an Intersect.
I was right.
The lab is the proof. It'll vindicate my team,
Shaw will be exposed--
Exposed? Exposed as what?
Uh, the Intersect?
I see you got a fancy new watch there,
Chuck.
Do you mind if I try it on?
Why don't you come over here
and take it?
Actually, I think I'll have my friend
grab it for me.
I don't need a watch to beat you, Shaw.
Come on, aren't you a little curious?
I know I am.
Don't you wanna know how your Intersect
stacks up against mine?
You're right, Chuck.
The fight will be incredible.
We're totally equal now.
Nothing separates us.
Though, there's one thing
that is different.
You can't function when your emotions
have been compromised.
Don't worry about that.
I've never been more calm.
Really? How you feeling now?
No!
Dad. Dad. Dad.
Dad. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hang on. Hang on.
Hang on. Stay with me.
Stay with me. You're gonna be okay.
I promise.
You're special, son.
Always remember.
Unh. You're special.
Check out the fresh fish.
Wait here.
Hello, miss.
- Hi.
I was wondering if I could service you
in some way?
Yes. I guess.
Um, could you tell me
where I could find John Casey's locker?
What exactly is your relationship
to Mr. Casey, if I may be so bold?
He's my friend.
And he asked me to get something
out of his locker.
- He gave me his key.
- That doesn't look like one of our keys.
Shh. Maybe you're talking about
a different John Casey.
Ours doesn't really have any friends.
I'll take it from here.
Morgan Grimes, assistant manager.
- Hi. Alex.
- Alex. Take a walk with me?
- Did you say that belongs to John Casey?
- Yes.
- Um, he does work here, right?
- Of course he does. Yeah.
Who do you work for?
It's okay. You can tell me.
I'm on the inside.
- Um, the Pie Shack in Silverlake.
- Ha, ha. Yeah. Okay.
Come on.
I have a very high level of clearance.
You can't have access to his locker
without knowing what's going on.
I'm sorry. My hands are tied.
I don't know what's going on.
All I know is that this customer, John...
...kidnaps me
and then tells me he's my father.
And now, there's men chasing us.
I'm sorry, I know I don't really know you.
I'm just a little confused right now.
No. It's okay.
I didn't mean to make you upset.
Look, miss, I promise you this...
...if John Casey said he's your father,
it's the truth.
I trust that man. You have nothing
to be afraid of. Not if he's your father.
In fact, this store is as safe as anywhere.
Provided you stay away from those two.
Yeah? Let's go see what's in that locker,
all right? You okay? Yeah.
This isn't a Buy More key,
so I'll have to use mine.
Assistant manager.
That's why I have this. So you know.
Okay. Avid reader. Heh.
Oh, my. Whoa.
How long that's been in there? Yeah.
Oh, check it out.
Think that's gonna work.
Oh, actually, you might wanna stand back.
This could explode.
Mm... Okay.
- He said this was for you?
- Yeah. What is it?
He must have been saving for, like, ever.
Heh. We don't pay that much here.
Morgan. Ellie called.
We need to talk.
Shoot. Whatever you gotta say, you can say
in front of her. She's one of us.
Not this.
Try not to spend it all in one place.
Chuck, what happened?
Are you okay?
Where's your dad?
I'm sorry, guys.
Shaw has won.
Oh, my God.
I'm so sorry.
Don't worry, buddy. We'll get Shaw.
No, we won't.
Love the new defeatist attitude, Chuck.
It suits you.
We'll be leaving momentarily
for the CIA detention facility.
These people won't be seeing
the light of day for some time.
Enjoy this ride together.
Bond. Share old war stories.
Because as soon as the truck stops...
...so do your lives.
We'll figure something out.
It's over.
And there's no one left to save us.
I'm following them now. Are you ready?
We're ready.
I'm warning you, Ellie,
if we do this, there is no turning back.
Our lives are changed forever.
I'm asking one final time.
Are you sure this is what you want?
Yes.
Let's do this.