I'm Chuck. Here's things you need to know:
That was the hospital.
They just offered me a sabbatical.
I'm, uh, Justin,
camp security coordinator.
Devon. Oh, baby, you're burning hot.
Justin!
They left. I took care of the husband,
made it look like malaria.
She doesn't suspect a thing.
Guys, we gotta get this place fixed up.
Actually, I was gonna start
with our place.
- If your offer for me to move in stands.
- Yeah.
It's official.
There is absolutely nothing on TV.
Yeah, Monday nights can be
a bit of a wasteland.
President Jakaya Kuti of Zamibia
arrived in Los Angeles today.
On agenda are diplomatic meetings
and a performance of Beethoven...
...tomorrow by the L.A. City Symphony.
Ugh. Sounds like Beckman.
Hey, jackpot.
Oh, no, no, no, you've made me
watch this before. This is ridiculous.
Sarah, please, you could learn
a lot from spies like these.
Are you kidding me?
Look at these people.
They are breaking
about 17 different rules of protocol.
Sweetheart, I'm not actually implying
that you could learn anything...
...about being a spy from Chevy Chase
or Dan Aykroyd. I was making a joke.
Remember? Jokes?
I love you.
- I'm sorry, I must have fallen asleep.
- Chuck.
I love you.
Oh, Sarah, it feels so good
to finally hear you say that.
Sarah, look outside. Quick.
Finally. I'm so hungry.
Isn't it great we found a place
that delivers Zamibian food?
Zamibian?
- Hello, Chuck.
- Shaw?
Oh, what?
Did you have another bad dream?
- It was about Beethoven and Zamibia.
- Chuck, I'm worried about you.
Every time you fall asleep,
you have a nightmare.
But this one was trying
to tell me something.
- Tell you what?
- General, The Ring is going to try...
...and kill the president of Zamibia at
the Beethoven concert tomorrow night.
Tomorrow night.
Could have done this in the morning.
You know how dear my sleep is to me,
Bartowski.
Look, I'm sorry, Casey and general.
I know that it's very late
and you are obviously very...
...busy. Um, but the president of Zamibia
is in danger.
Did you flash on something, Chuck?
I--
Mm. Uh...
I know it because of my dream.
Your-- Your dream?
I've been having
very, very vivid dreams.
First, I saw the news reports on Kuti,
president of Zamibia...
...but then I saw Beethoven.
Then Shaw was there,
delivering Zamibian food.
Then he tried to kill everyone.
Obviously, Zamibian president...
...is gonna be assassinated by The Ring
at the concert.
General, permission to slap Bartowski.
He had a bad dream.
General, Chuck has been under
a lot of stress with these dreams--
No, Walker,
I think I understand the situation.
And, to be honest,
it makes perfect sense.
Thank you. Thank you, general.
Thank you very much, appreciate that.
What's our assignment?
Chuck, I'm assigning you
to see a CIA therapist.
These dreams you're having are getting
in the way of your work and our sleep.
No. This is crazy. A therapist?
I don't need a therapist, okay?
Therapists are for people
who have real problems. I'm fine.
Are you comfortable, Chuck?
No. No, not particularly, no.
How does this work exactly?
I've only seen movies and stuff like that.
Do you ask me questions? I just answer--
Or is it like word association...
...where you would, like, say "father" --
No, give me another word.
Do you want to talk about your father,
Chuck?
This wasn't my idea, you know?
So, no, I don't really wanna talk
about anything, to be perfectly honest.
Despite your sparkling
conversation skill.
That was-- That was a joke.
I was just--
Just going to town on that pad,
aren't you?
Just a little joke.
Okay, fine, I'll talk.
Ahem. Where do I start? Uh--
Well, okay, my girlfriend just moved in
with me.
The best part of my life, really.
Rock-solid relationship.
Not a problem there. A little distant.
She could be more communicative.
She doesn't say "I love you" back.
Never done this before.
Even though I know she loves me,
I'm just noting it...
...because I know, I know
that she loves me. I know that.
Do you?
Let's get back to your dreams.
It's my belief they are a product of your
subconscious interacting with Intersect.
Wait, what?
How--?
- You know about the Intersect?
- I'm a CIA psychiatrist.
I know everything about you, Chuck.
As far as the Intersect goes,
we've known for some time...
...that it could spur a host
of side effects.
Like dry scalp?
Because I have had
annoyingly dry scalp since--
The Intersect
is extraordinarily powerful.
It has the potential
to overwhelm your mind.
With the end result akin
to something much like...
...insanity.
Insanity?
Doc, I'm not insane.
You're not sure about that. It could be
the Intersect is doing its thing...
...while I'm sleeping. And if that's true,
then President Kuti is in danger.
Slow down, Chuck.
Something is gonna happen tonight.
And if I'm there, we could stop it
and then I'm not crazy.
I'm sorry, Chuck,
but I can't let you do that.
Until further notice, I'm removing you
from field duty.
There he is. Welcome home, pal.
- It's good to be home.
- Hey, look at you. All right.
You know what? Malaria aside,
you look pretty awesome.
I actually feel pretty great.
I'm ready to get back out there.
- I had an important realization.
- That looks don't get you everywhere.
No, Morgan.
You can die as easily
from a mosquito in Africa...
...as you can from a spy in Burbank.
This is what I'm talking about.
Listen, fear is the mind killer.
- Yeah.
- Right.
You can't live scared, bro.
Not for yourself. Not for anyone.
I think it's jammed a little bit
or something. I guess it's broken.
Hey, uh, Ellie.
- I heard Devon has malaria.
- Yeah.
Nasty stuff.
Had it four, maybe five times myself.
Tough to say.
Those meds aren't gonna help him.
What he needs are African snake herbs.
- I might have some back at my place.
- I'll keep that in mind, John. Thank you.
- Okay.
Crazy.
You're not crazy.
Don't freak out.
Chuck, you in there?
Come in.
- Hey.
- How was the doctor's?
- Uh, good. Great, actually.
Yeah, yeah, I'm fine. What about you?
Hear anything from Beckman...
...about anything?
Chuck, I know I'm your partner...
...but I'm also your girlfriend.
And you can tell me anything.
I know that. Of course, I--
Of course, I know that.
Honestly. Hey, I'm fine, okay?
Just a solid good night's rest
and I'm right as rain.
Which I don't totally understand
because rain is kind of all over the place.
- Glad you're okay.
- Thanks.
Nothing like absorbing local culture.
President Jakaya Kuti of Zamibia
will be in town today.
The tiny African nation seeks
to improve its rocky...
Okay, Chuck.
You're watching more cable television...
...than is healthy for a young man.
Talk to me. What's going on?
Buddy, I've been having the strangest
and most vivid dreams I've ever had.
- How vivid are we talking about here?
- Well, they have to do with that guy.
I guess he's handsome.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Me neither. He's president of Zamibia
and he's gonna be at the symphony.
The dream I had made me think--
Made me know that he's in danger, man.
Some doctor thinks it's just the Intersect
playing with my subconscious.
I'm right and nobody believes me.
Sarah doesn't believe you?
S-- Uh.
I'm trying not to involve Sarah.
Things are good between us.
Last thing I want is her to think I'm--
- Crazy.
- Yeah.
Well, here's the thing.
If this guy really is in danger...
...don't you think it's crazy not to help
the president of Zanfiriabiha?
- Zam-- Uh.
- Zamibia.
Yeah. Anyway, I'm gonna help you.
- Thanks, buddy, thank you.
- What's your pant size, Chuck?
I'm just gonna say it.
I need a woman.
It's been far too long, Jeffrey.
A man has needs.
- What's the plan?
- I'll be hitting on all applicable women...
...in Electronics, DVDs, and all around
the entrances and the emergency exits.
You're leaving me Home Appliances?
It's full of lumpy housewives.
- My favorite.
- You're welcome.
OMG, Jefferson, is it a mirage?
No, my eyes do not deceive me.
It is indeed her.
It is Anna Wu. I knew the day she left
to break Morgan's heart...
...she'd come back to break mine.
Crush it.
Hi, guys. Long time no smell.
She remembered our smell.
Annabelle, have you lost weight?
Two, three grams?
Hawaii is treating your body very well.
- Thanks. Is Morgan around?
- Who?
- What now?
- Morgan Grimes.
He does still work here, doesn't he?
- Hey.
- Two tickets to the L.A. City Symphony.
Two tuxedos from the mall.
No cummerbund. Call me crazy.
Well done, you nailed it. Gonna head out
the back. Meet me at the Herder in five.
- Done.
- All right, let's go.
Well, I hate to be the one
to tell you this. I don't really.
But Morgan is in a,
um, very bad place.
- Oh, my God, is he okay?
- No. He's focused, responsible, driven.
- Pains me to see a man end up like that.
- It's pathetic.
Ha. Nice try.
He can't have changed that much.
- Whoa, Anna, what are you doing here?
- In L.A. for a few days. Came to see you.
- There are some things--
- Sorry, don't mean to be rude. I just--
- Duty calls.
- You mean "Call of Duty"?
Come on, Morgan, your game can wait.
Why are you in a tux?
Uh, tux, right.
I'm going to the symphony with Chuck.
The symphony. With Chuck.
My God, can you guys get weirder?
At this point, probably not.
I'd love to catch up.
Why don't you call tomorrow morning,
all right? And, uh, you look good.
Wow.
Excuse me.
Hey, buddy, buddy, that's Kuti up in
the president's box there. Our mission:
Make sure nothing happens to him.
Remember, Morgan...
- ...my code name is Charles Carmichael.
- Yeah, I got it. I got it. Mine's Cobra.
Okay, let's do this.
Great. I'm on a mission with Cobra.
Maybe I am going crazy.
Are you sure you want the box set of ER?
Ha. Hey, but all 15 seasons?
Uh, yeah, I know, Devon,
it's the best show ever.
Okay, fine. I'll see you later. Bye.
Ellie?
Justin? Oh, I'm sorry. This is--
This is bizarre. Why aren't you in Africa?
Did you--? Did you--?
Did you get malaria too?
No, I'm actually here to see you.
Can we go somewhere and talk for a bit?
Somewhere private?
Let me ask you a question.
This whole Anna thing, you know,
I mean, you think she wants me back?
Better question, actually:
Do I take her back?
Didn't she break your heart?
You did hit rock bottom.
Well, bottom, yeah, but rock bottom?
Come on.
Shh.
Later, all right, buddy? Remember,
we're on a mission. Eyes on the president.
- Shh!
- Sorry.
But she's kind of like the love of my life.
When you want to talk about Sarah...
...we talk about Sarah.
I thought you could help me out.
- Hey, hey, that is not fair.
- Shh!
You work for the CIA?
I know it's a lot to process, but meeting
you in Africa wasn't an accident.
Wanted to talk to you, but your husband
got sick before we could fully brief you.
This is about your father, Ellie.
My father.
My father, are you kidding me?
My father is--
He's eccentric, sure.
But the work Stephen J. Bartowski did
in molecular computing...
...has turned out to be brilliant.
Which is why as we speak, there are
some bad people looking for him.
Including a man named John Casey.
He's an NSA double agent. He's been
monitoring you for another organization.
John Casey works with my brother.
You don't have to take my word for it.
Just...
...keep an eye on him.
I caution you about telling anyone
about this.
But what about my brother
and my husband?
Here's the problem.
They're gonna tell you you're crazy.
As crazy as you think I am right now.
We came to you
because we need you, Ellie.
Your father needs you.
What are you doing here?
I thought you had a date with Chuck.
Saw him leave the store in his tux.
Chuck's in a tux?
Pull up surveillance in the store entrance
and the parking lot from 16 minutes ago.
There, there. Roll it back.
There, freeze it.
Concert with Zamibian president. Chuck
is gonna try prove us wrong about Kuti.
I'm gonna kill them both.
Hey, hey. Chuck.
Why are you onstage?
What, buddy? I'm not onstage.
You shot me, Chuck.
What are you doing here?
What are you trying to tell me?
The dream isn't about me, Chuck.
It's about a scientist, Dr. Kowambe.
- I love you.
- Intersect.
Oh, my God, that's him.
That's the guy who's gonna kill Kuti.
- You serious? How do you know?
- I had another dream.
- I gotta get up to the president's box.
- Shh!
Okay, listen, ma'am, put a sock in it.
You, Morgan, stay in the seat.
- What? I could be attacked.
- You're not gonna get attacked.
- There could be a sniper.
- Fine, fine, fine. Here.
Take my backup tranq gun.
For life-or-death situations only.
There.
You take Bartowski.
I got the little elf.
No, Chuck, stop.
I can't let you do this.
Sarah, I had another dream. The guy
who's gonna kill Kuti is in the box now.
You should've told me. I could help.
Sorry, I didn't wanna get you mixed up
in all this dream stuff until I had proof.
I love you. Right now I need you
to believe I'm not crazy.
Okay, well, let's get into that box.
Stand up and walk out of here quietly
or I'll kill you and drag you out of here.
Your choice.
- You--
- What are you reaching for, Morgan?
I've been authorized
to use this tranq gun.
I don't want to. I consider us
as friends now, but I will use this--
Okay, here we go. Shh, shh.
Good evening.
Routine CIA weapons sweep.
- What is the meaning of this?
- That's him. That's the guy right there.
- Dr. Kowambe?
- Yeah, Dr. Kowambe.
Mr. President, who is this person?
- Chuck, take it easy, please.
- I'm taking it easy. Taking it very easy.
Stop!
This man is Africa's
most respected scientist.
This is preposterous. You could at least
have had the pretty one frisk me.
- Out of your mind? What are you doing?
- It's not an assassination attempt.
He had Ring intel in his mouth.
The tooth, tooth! Find the tooth!
This man is clearly insane.
Have this man arrested.
There's hidden data in the tooth.
I can explain everything.
Guys, guys, help me! I'm not crazy!
Sarah!
Explain how it's possible that last night...
...Chuck, aided by the world-class spy...
...that is Morgan Grimes,
managed to elude you...
...and cause an international incident that
the president of the United States...
...had to apologize for. In Zamibian.
Tricky language.
Lots of clicks and vowels.
General, how is Chuck doing?
At the moment, Dr. Dreyfus believes
Chuck's condition...
...is worse than originally diagnosed.
Originally diagnosed?
I-- I don't understand.
I'm sorry. But the doctor believes
the Intersect...
...is overwhelming Chuck's brain.
His mental deterioration
may be unavoidable.
He told me he was fine.
Know that we will do everything possible
for him.
I care about him too.
We'll go this afternoon.
Nothing will make him feel better
than seeing you.
- I can't believe this is happening.
- It's happening, Chuck.
Disturbing as it may be, you're currently
a patient in a psychiatric institution.
Best to come to terms with that
sooner than later.
Wow, you really know
how to make a guy feel better...
...about his situation, doc.
You should meet some other people here
with serious psychiatric issues.
This is Lewis.
Although he currently
prefers the name Merlin.
Is that right? Merlin, like the--?
Like the wizard?
What you in for?
Is it something, uh, sexual?
No. No, it's not. Not sexual at all.
- I've been having troubling dreams.
- Sexual?
Non-sexual troubling dreams.
- Has my team contacted you yet?
- Ugh. Don't hold your breath.
I've been waiting for my team
since '93.
That's enough, Lewis.
What? His team? What team?
Who is this guy? He's nuts.
His spy team.
This is a CIA facility.
Everyone here used to be a spy.
As I don't have to tell you,
it's a stressful job.
People tend to crack.
Everyone here. Spies. Like me.
John?
Anybody home?
Hi, Ellie. What's up?
Hi, John. Um, I just remembered
that you had mentioned something...
...about herbs for Devon's malaria.
- Right. Uh, I'll check.
- Okay.
Here you go.
Make sure he takes them
with some nice, warm goat milk.
Okay, thank you.
Ah.
- Whoa, El, everything okay?
- Okay.
I need you to listen very closely
and I need you to promise me...
- ...that you're not gonna freak out.
- Okay.
I have reason to believe that
our neighbor, John Casey, is a very...
...very bad man. And we need
to get far away from him.
Babe, gotta get that story
about him getting drunk...
...and peeing himself out of your mind.
He was in a bad place. It happens.
No, Devon, I was just in his apartment
and he has guns. Very big guns.
We have to do something.
Okay, okay.
Casey has some serious guns.
Is that creepy? Yes.
Is that illegal? Sadly, no.
You don't believe me.
It's just--
It sounds a little crazy is all.
- You think that I sound crazy?
- Come on, El.
How about I make you a cup of tea?
Chamomile, maybe?
Less caffeine, but still so delicious.
Ha-ha-ha?
Yes, okay, I-- I'm sure that I do.
I do sound crazy.
Tea is great. Thank you.
How are you doing there, pal?
- Is there anything we can do for you?
- Yeah, as a matter of fact.
Need you
to get some evidence analyzed.
That scientist? He's out there,
he's working for The Ring, I'm sure.
Please, Chuck, the way you're talking.
Come on. It's me.
I need to show you something.
Sarah, give me your hand.
Give your boyfriend your hand.
- Is that--?
- Yeah, the tooth.
- Is it yours?
- What? No. That's crazy.
It's Dr. Kowambe's tooth
and it's not real.
It's fake. It contains Ring intel.
Secrets, plans, something.
- In the tooth?
- Yeah. Try to keep up, Casey, okay?
You need to get that analyzed ASAP.
The tooth is the key.
The truth is in the tooth.
Well, we'll, uh-- We'll check that out
and you get some rest there, pal.
We'll come back
and visit you tomorrow.
Chuck.
Sarah, you can't give up on me, okay?
I won't. I'll get it tested.
Time to go, Chuck.
Walker, I hope he's right too, but
don't be disappointed if Bartowski's--
Stop it. He's gonna be right.
Nothing abnormal.
Just a tooth.
Chuck was wrong.
Mm. I'm sorry.
Excuse me. Does this come in burgundy?
I believe that does come in burgundy.
I'll check in the back for you.
- What's going on? Where is Chuck?
- Not now.
Listen, please, please, please.
You gotta tell me. Just let me know
he's okay. Casey, please.
They got him in a lockdown
in a psychiatric facility.
Seems the Intersect's giving him
a bit of hard time.
What? No, man, no. That's crazy.
Morgan, there you are.
Sorry to bother you again...
...do you have a second?
I get that you're assistant manager--
I'd love to. I'd love to. I just--
Now is not really a good time, so...
You look good.
Dissed twice by Morgan Grimes?
I can't believe this is happening.
Right there. Diagonally. Ha-ha-ha.
Oh, thank you.
- Hello?
- Chuck.
Hey, hey, hey, Sarah.
Hey, hey.
Hey, so, uh, what did you find out?
Chuck, we ran every test possible...
...and I'm sorry, it's just a tooth.
Are you sure?
Yeah, but even though you were wrong,
it doesn't mean anything.
The important thing
is to stay positive.
Everything's gonna be okay.
I know.
Thanks for trying.
- May I help you?
- I hope so.
I'm here to see a Charles Bartowski.
There's no record of Dr. Dreyfus
authorizing any after-hours visits.
So if you don't mind, I don't want
to have you escorted from the building.
Of course.
That will not be necessary.
Find me Bartowski.
- Good evening.
- Let me guess.
You're here because of Chuck.
Doctor, I know that there has to be
something more to his condition.
He can't just be deteriorating
in this way.
Why? Because you care about him?
No. You don't understand.
He's not like other people. He is...
...incredibly special.
Ah. Especially to you, I gather.
He needs to be okay.
I-- I need him to be okay.
I'd like to go to the hospital tonight
and talk to him.
Try and figure this out,
and then help him somehow, you know?
Please.
I love him.
Ever tell him that?
Please, doctor, I'm begging you.
You're not the only one.
I'm glad the doctor wants to see me
because I sure wanna see the doctor.
Hey, whoa, there's no need
to be rough or physical.
- Jeez.
- Mr. Bartowski.
Oh. Not the doctor
I was expecting to see.
Why did you take my tooth?
More to the point,
why did you take the wrong tooth?
What? What, the...?
- The wrong tooth?
- The data is in a tooth.
I believe this is the fake one
you are looking for.
I was-- I was right.
I was right. Well, I was wrong.
I was wrong.
Clearly, I was wrong, but I was right.
This is great news.
That means I'm not crazy.
Yes. It also means
as soon as you tell me...
...where you got your information,
and rest assured, you will tell me...
...you are going to die.
Oh, that's not great news.
That's a giant needle. Bad, bad.
- Colored liquid, even worse.
- Yes, it's one of my favorites.
Tetraclydine,
a designer psychotropic cocktail.
God!
In around 10 minutes, you're going to be
extremely forthcoming.
Dr. Dreyfus. Thank God.
Guys.
Guys, guys, help me, help me.
I need you.
- Awesome.
- Take him back to the room.
Ah.
Restrain him.
Ugh. I don't feel so good.
Let him go!
Or suffer the wrath
of Merlin and his army.
Spies, attack!
Damn.
- It was a good idea, Merlin.
- It's over.
No one believes you.
No one's coming for you.
Chuck.
Well, well.
Looks like it's good we came.
You came back for me.
I'll always come back for you.
So will Merlin, Chuck. So will Merlin.
It seems you're owed an apology,
Agent Bartowski.
You were right about Kowambe.
He was illegally harvesting
human organs...
...experimenting with genetic
manipulation and reengineering.
He was scheduled to meet
a Ring operative to sell this research.
Well, that's fantastic.
Not the organ-harvesting stuff,
obviously. That's very, very sad.
So I have a clean bill of health?
It would seem that way, Chuck,
but I can't actually clear you.
Well, then, who can?
So, what did we land on here?
That, uh, my dreams have the potential
to work in concert with my flashes?
Is that where you think we landed?
Oh, come on, doc.
Level with me.
Am I cleared for duty or not?
You were right, Chuck. Your dreams
were caused by the Intersect.
I'm clearing you for duty.
- All right.
- But...
But? But what? Why is there a "but"?
But your dreams are also proof of stress
the Intersect puts on your brain.
And it is my belief that that stress
will continue and intensify...
...likely leading
to serious mental deterioration.
Um...
What does that mean exactly?
Am I okay?
This is a new science.
Time will tell.
But if I may, Chuck...
...I think it's something you should
discuss with your partner, Agent Walker.
Thanks, doc.
Morgan Guillermo Grimes,
I refuse to be denied an audience...
...with Buy More's assistant manager.
If you run off on me one more time,
I swear, I'll call corporate.
She could want you back, man.
That could be an improvised explosive.
Be extremely cool around that.
I owe you an explanation. I'm so sorry.
Last few days have been insane.
I've been trying to get a second
of your time to give you this.
Some stuff you left behind in Hawaii.
Thought you may want it back.
I'm okay without it.
Well...
...here's something else
you may have forgotten.
I gotta hand it to you, Morgan.
You know how to play a girl.
Well, you know, some men have it and---
What are you talking about? I don't--
You know what they say about
not knowing you want something...
...until you can't have it?
It's true.
You've changed, Morgan.
I want you back.
Wow. Really?
If it took me running
to realize that I'm somebody you want...
...I don't think
you're the person I want.
So, yeah, you're right.
I have changed.
I'll see you later.
I don't mind leftovers.
- Hey, Sarah, hey. We need to talk.
- Sure, but--
- No, look, this is very important.
- I love you.
It shouldn't have taken me this long
to say it, but I've never felt this way.
Before you, the only future
I could think about was my next mission.
And now all I can think about
is a future with you.
I love you, Chuck.
I love you too.
So, what did you wanna tell me?
Is it about the doctor? What did he say?
He said that...
...I'm fine.
So...
- Justin?
- Hey.
It's okay. It's just me.
You were right.
Right about everything.
About Casey, about keeping quiet.
My husband thinks
that I am nuts right now.
But I believe you and I wanna help.
So, what can I do?
Do you know
how to contact your father?
If we can let him know what's happening,
we may be able to protect him.
He moves around a lot.
He's really paranoid.
He doesn't trust anyone.
Last time he left, he made sure
I had a way to contact him.
Thank you, Ellie.
And just remember,
you're serving your country.
Shaw.
You're not bleeding anymore.
That's right, Chuck, I'm not.
What does that mean?
It means I'm still alive.
Hey, what's wrong?
Nothing.
Nothing, sorry. Go back to sleep.