Land ho!
I'd like to go back and retrieve the gold.
Refit, hire a consort, finish the job.
- Is that possible?
- Well, it might have been possible.
Before the bay fell into
the hands of a madman.
Either we act now to
remove him or no one will.
Congratulations, Jack.
Now you know what it's like
to rise from the grave.
We're gonna sail again.
Your judgment with her is clouded at best.
And there's nothing I can do to counter it
when I'm on the wrong side of that door.
Found the prize they was hiding.
Her father is Lord Peter Ashe,
governor of the Carolina colony.
Lord Ashe won't be trifled with.
I have no intentions of trifling with him.
Charles Vane and the animals he commands
have until sunrise tomorrow
to vacate that fort
or, so help me God,
I will rain holy hell down upon him.
Go on.
"If you fail to meet these demands,"
if you remain when the deadline arrives,
I will respond swiftly and definitively.
And as I currently sit fully
outside your means of retaliation,
this response will continue
unabated until you,
your men, and that structure
are rendered fully incapacitated.
"Until dawn, Captain James Flint."
Get him out of here.
Put him behind a door somewhere.
I want him whole when
he delivers my answer.
Make ready the guns in the northwest.
Move everything we have
to the southwest bastion.
He's telling the truth.
The southwest bastion
is too weak to support
any batteries at all.
We have no guns that
can reach his position.
Somehow Flint knew exactly
where to sit to take advantage.
Then find out how close I can get.
Now.
Tell me right now you had
nothing to do with this.
- Charles, look at me.
- Tell me this isn't part of your plan
- to push me into the sea.
- Look at me.
I had no idea this was coming.
I had no idea that Flint
would be so fucking reckless
as to threaten the fort itself.
I had no idea Hornigold
would be so fucking petty
as to divulge secrets about its weaknesses,
risk its destruction for
his own personal gain.
I told you what I would do
if challenged like this.
- I know.
- I may not be able to hit his ship,
but I can hit the rest of them.
I can turn that whole
goddamn bay into a graveyard.
- But you won't.
- You doubt me?
No, I have faith in your ability
to formulate a plan more
effective than this.
The initial barrage will be
targeted at the southeast bastion.
Once the turrets are destroyed,
we'll turn our aim
to the weaker of the defensive walls.
Hammer them until the interior is exposed
and the fort is vulnerable to
an assault from the ground.
At this point, there's no limit
to the damage we can inflict.
- How long to rebuild?
- Rebuild?
After we secure possession
of what's left of the fort,
how long will it take you and your
men to rebuild what we've destroyed?
10 weeks before the batteries are restored.
Twice that to resecure the interior.
It is a risk,
but a relatively short
window in the grand scheme.
A short window that coincides
with a British warship
sitting in anchor 40 miles from here
and my having stolen a Spanish warship
in full view of a company
of Spanish soldiers.
We'll just have to keep our fingers
crossed for a while, then, won't we?
Are you suggesting the threat we posed
to Captain Vane is an empty one and we
have no intent of following through?
I am fully committed, as are we all,
to the removal
of Captain Vane from that fort.
But we'd be fools to ignore
the catastrophic risks
that lie down this road.
I have committed men
and resources to aid you
in retrieving the Urca gold.
In exchange for which you've
assured me of your assistance
of expelling Captain Vane from
that fort by any means necessary.
Now, as I hear you waver,
I feel forced to ask,
if the sun rises tomorrow
and Vane has not ceded to our demands,
then what will you do?
I was told it was urgent.
He said he wanted to see you right away.
What about?
It's all right.
It has nothing to do with you and I.
He'll be arriving in less than two hours.
I'm sorry, who?
The fourth Earl of Ashbourne.
Lord Proprietor to the Carolina colony,
including the Bahama Islands,
and peer of the realm.
Lord Alfred Hamilton.
My father.
I'm told he expects a
full report of our efforts
to devise a plan for the
management of Nassau.
And you're concerned how he'll receive it?
I'm concerned about how he'll
receive one particular part of it.
The part you and I have yet to discuss.
I didn't think we had one of those.
These past few months
I have come to trust you.
Very much.
Which is why I feel I
can ask for your help.
When my father arrives,
I intend to propose something to him
which could be very dangerous politically.
What is it you want me to help you with?
I want you to try to talk me out of it.
Yes?
Ma'am, you're needed.
All right.
It's a Spanish warship!
There's a Spanish galleon
anchored in the harbor!
Is today some sort of holiday
that I've forgotten about?
Spanish warship anchored in the bay.
Word is it's Flint's crew sailing her.
And it's scaring the shit
out of everyone on the beach.
Flint's sailing a Spanish warship?
Think we should try and
lure some of them inside?
Wait. Does he have it?
Does he have what?
Did Flint get to the Urca gold?
I don't know.
Hold there.
The fuck are you doing?
The situation is as we feared.
That warship is fully
outside our field of fire.
And given our severe disadvantage,
might she provide us valuable leverage?
Make sure Flint knows the
moment he fires those guns,
her body gets dumped over the wall.
Your reply to Flint will be significantly
more effective if it
comes from me personally.
You might want to keep quiet now, miss.
You have questions about my loyalties
as it relates to Miss Guthrie?
Then accuse me. Challenge me. Fight me.
Or shut the fuck up about it.
Open the gate!
What are you doing here?
Putting an end to this.
Miss Guthrie.
Captain Vane has issued a
reply to your ultimatum.
It's being read aloud on
the beach as we speak.
I think you should see it.
Give us the room.
- I have as much right...
- Now, please!
"You must ask yourselves who represents"
the greater threat to your interests...
my men in this fort
"or the madman on the water."
It's effective.
Mm, I can see that.
What I cannot see is how
Charles Vane alone was clever enough
to turn this all into political theater
in which he is the defender
of the island's welfare.
Are you suggesting he had
help in crafting his reply?
Did he?
Were I to have aided
Captain Vane against your efforts,
helped him move into a more
favorable position last night,
what would such a move say about the
trust you and I are supposed to share?
I believe I was clear yesterday
about the danger he represents
and my desire to see him
removed from that fort.
Though you conveniently omitted the part
about how you were prepared
to use a Spanish warship
to annihilate the fort to achieve that end.
Your refusal to acknowledge the urgency
of the situation gave me no choice but...
But to do what? Disregard our partnership?
Ignore the resources and influence
and trust I have invested in you?
This isn't personal.
It's too important for that.
All right, then.
What is it you wish to accomplish here?
To see him removed from the fort.
Then this is a stupid fucking
way of going about it.
He'll never voluntarily leave if he
thinks it will show weakness to do so.
You want him out, here's how you do it.
You move this ship.
You allow him to save face on this score.
And then you and he and I sit down
at a table and we sort it out.
Eleanor,
I don't care if he leaves voluntarily.
If I give up this position,
I will never regain it.
And without this position,
the decision is his and his alone.
No, I simply cannot risk that.
Not with what's at stake.
You are talking about rendering this bay,
rendering Nassau completely unprotected.
I know!
And I am perfectly aware of
the danger that presents.
But when it comes to Charles Vane, you and
I simply do not see him in the same way.
Now, if you can see a way,
an effective, credible way out of this
that doesn't involve disabling the fort,
I would love to hear it.
If you think that he will hear reason.
Not with you holding a gun to his head.
Then I suggest you talk to him.
Because one way or another,
he is leaving that fort.
And right now my way is the only way
that I can be certain of that.
My name is Charles Vane
and you are now my guest.
As such, no harm will come to you
as long as you do exactly as I say.
You understand?
The other one, he said no talking.
Captain Low?
You don't need to worry about him anymore.
How can you be sure?
I cut his head off.
Good.
Now, your father is Lord Peter Ashe,
governor of the Carolina colony.
Is that right?
What is the total value of his estate?
I don't know.
How many rooms in his house?
How many slaves?
Honestly, I don't know.
Haven't seen him in years.
I've been at school in London.
Are you close with him?
What?
I'm asking if there's any
reason I should expect
he may not be willing to pay
to ensure no harm comes to you?
You're asking if he loves me?
He'll pay you what you ask.
Can you write?
Of course.
Then write the following.
You're a prisoner of the
pirate Captain Charles Vane.
Your ransom, should your father
ever wish to see you alive again,
is £250,000.
The next contact I'll
make will be to arrive
in Charlestown harbor
with you in my possession.
If I sense a trap or my demands are unmet,
I'll kill you and throw
your body into the bay.
Do you understand?
She's writing the letter now.
I want it on its way to Charlestown
before whatever's going to
happen here tomorrow happens.
Right.
Who are they?
Friends from the beach.
They have pledged
their services to Captain Vane
to defend the fort and to
discourage any move against it.
It seems his pronouncement
has had the intended effect.
And 40 men becomes 60
and the fight ahead only gets bloodier.
Then get out there. Sit with the captains.
Talk some sense into them.
Tell them that it's their ships and cargo
that will be subject to his
extortion the moment it suits him.
I'll get to the beach.
Appeal directly to the crews.
If we can stop anyone
else from going up there,
we can keep this from getting out of hand.
Can I assume when you say
you'll go to the beach
to make this appeal, you mean me?
All right, then.
Why do you think they went up that hill?
Beg your pardon?
If we're to stop any more
men from joining his side,
isn't it a prerequisite
that we try and understand
the thinking of the men who
have already joined him?
Sorry, are you asking my opinion?
Oh.
Well, uh...
I suppose one could argue
that it's simple fear.
Their fear of losing the fort
being greater than their
fear of Vane remaining in it.
But then again,
it's possible this has
nothing to do with the fort.
Nor with Vane.
Perhaps it's just them expressing
their opinions about you.
So you think that they see me
as the villain in this particular story?
I think that would explain
their decision, yes.
And you? What do you think?
You see me as the villain here?
I see you as the agent most likely
of securing my share of
the gold on that beach.
As long as that remains true,
I am not bothered in the
least by whatever labels
anyone else decides to affix to you.
Why?
What do you think about it?
I'm sorry?
It bothers you, doesn't it?
What they think?
With the things you've done...
My God.
It must be awful being you.
Time is short.
You'd better be off.
We have reasonable proposals to
recruit men for the expedition.
To procure supplies and to ferry them.
But it will be the approach to
dealing with the Nassau pirates
by which the entire plan will be judged.
I feel that's where we're strongest.
Targeted raid on the beach
under cover from two men-of-war.
Public trials and hangings of
roughly a dozen of the ringleaders.
And the replacement of the governor
with an officer of our choosing.
It's precise, it's affordable,
and it'll play well with the Sea Lords.
I understand that's the expected proposal.
The safest one.
But it's not the one I would like to make.
When my father arrives,
I would like to propose to him
that we don't hang the pirates.
- That we pardon them.
- I'm sorry, what was that?
I want to pardon them.
- You want to pardon them?
- Yes.
- How many?
- All of them.
- All right.
- The island needs commerce to survive.
It needs labor. It needs men and
women vested in its interest.
Don't these men fit that description?
Couldn't they become part of the solution?
You don't need me to answer that.
- They're men.
- They're traitors to the Crown.
- What difference does that make?
- Makes some difference to the Crown.
Just answer me this, would it work?
To pardon a traitor is the act of a coward.
And given our current war footing,
precisely no one in Whitehall
wants to wear that label right now.
If you propose this to your father,
he will almost certainly distance
himself from it and most likely from you.
Now, I only know
what I've heard of your father,
but if half of what I've heard is true,
he's not a man one wants as an enemy.
If you're asking me as your
liaison to the Admiralty,
my advice to you
is that this is a maneuver
only to be approached
with utmost caution.
But as your friend,
I suggest you forget
you ever thought of it.
They came through the gate like locusts,
Vane and his men.
Brothers of mine being hacked to pieces.
I swear to Christ Almighty,
it wasn't the screams that haunt me most.
It was their laughter.
I thought they said no one survived
the raid from Captain Hornigold's crew.
Well, I guess one of them
must have gotten away.
So what do you make of this business
between Captains Flint and Vane?
Thank you. Lovely performance.
Hello, friend.
Man around the bend has something to say
about this business at the fort.
The fuck's going on in there?
Pulled a man out of the water.
Up by the north point.
That's lucky.
We were just about to send for one of you.
Excuse me?
You're a Walrus man, aren't you?
Sorry, what are you talking about?
He's one of yours.
I assume Captain Flint wasn't
amenable to your suggestion.
He's not listening to me and
this place is slipping into ruin.
It's my commitment to
see this fort protected
from all enemies, all threats.
So as you consider where
to lay your support,
consider which of us represents
the greatest threat...
my men in this fort or
the madman on the water?
- How many criers did you pay?
- Four total, as you asked.
Sent to the ends of the camps.
But what I don't understand
is why we're supporting
Captain Vane's position.
We're not supporting it, we're relaying it.
With all due respect,
I can't see the difference.
I think I can live with that.
So what do we do now?
The only one who can stop this is Flint.
I'll just have to find
someone to convince him.
He's moving in a direction
that promises unimaginable chaos.
He won't listen to me,
but perhaps he would listen
to an appeal from you.
I appreciate your frustration.
Were there something I could do to help,
I assure you I would.
You can make him see how
destructive his actions would be.
- You can make him...
- If you believe...
if you believe anyone can
make him see anything,
you must not know him very well at all.
I'm sorry. I can't help you.
You weren't here the last time they came.
200 Spanish soldiers walked onto the beach.
They burned the huts on the beach
and then the structures in town.
When the whole of Nassau
was a smoking wreck,
they turned their eye inland.
They raped, they murdered,
they laid waste.
And all because there was
no fort to protect the bay.
The men in charge had allowed
it to fall into disrepair.
Please, help me to dissuade him
from putting us on that path again.
If you're concerned for your safety,
perhaps you should request sanctuary
along with your father
at the Underhill estate.
I'd be happy to carry the message.
You think this is about me?
You asked me for my help
yesterday with Mr. Underhill.
I gave it my best efforts.
You asked me today again for my help,
but I'm sorry,
what you ask is simply impossible.
You don't give a shit
about the rest of us, fine.
But Flint. Don't you care enough about him
to at least try to stop
him from doing this?
Don't I care about him?
He's the one in the most immediate danger.
- And you would do nothing...
- You who have enabled him,
encouraged his violence,
you ask if I care about him?
How dare you?
Get out of my house.
Yes? What?
- New recruits?
- Mm-hmm.
It would appear your reconciliation
with Captain Vane has borne fruit.
Though, perhaps,
of the low-hanging variety.
Thank you for your concern.
Did you know?
Before she opened the door?
No, I didn't know.
You must care for her a great deal.
Not once all night did you so
much as look in my direction.
I've seen enough to know to
keep my distance from you,
thank you very much.
The situation was not of my making.
If it was anyone's, it was yours.
I'm sorry, what?
The conflict within her.
I had it under control.
Right until the moment you
walked in on her and me.
For that was the moment you began
the competition between you and me.
What is happening here, the three of us,
it is only temporary.
A state of denial until
she finally makes a choice.
A choice between you and I?
Anne and I have been by each other's sides
since she was 13 years old.
We have sailed together.
We've killed together.
We have shared things you
couldn't begin to imagine.
You've shared a bed with her for a week.
You'd be amazed what can
change in a week in my bed.
I understand you're feeling
quite indispensable of late.
But rest assured, it only seems that way.
I wouldn't get too comfortable were I you.
And what if I can get you
back on the water with a crew?
Would I still only
seem indispensable then, too?
One of the girls has a lead?
Mm, but which one?
They're so mistrustful of
male authority figures.
It'll take some time before they
report these things to you and not me.
Come.
Mr. Featherstone.
Been a regular for months now.
The navigator on the Colonial Dawn.
Finest on the island, so he says.
He's all right. Go on.
Put my tongue in his bum,
he'd tell me anything.
So I did and he did.
He's looking to move.
Said the men were split badly
over the mess on the beach.
Some backing Flint,
some saying he'd gone mad.
Said the crew been fraying
for some time, anyway.
Said in all likelihood, a lot of those men
would follow him wherever he went
on account of his skills.
And we have a plan
to sway him and his men to our camp?
I'm going to fuck the
living shit out of him.
If he chooses to join
Captain Rackham's crew,
that decision must be heartfelt.
It cannot be cast into doubt
the moment the pleasure fades.
And for that, you cannot just fuck him.
You must seduce him.
Yes, there is a difference.
The breath in his ear.
The arch in your back when he
thinks he is making you finish.
The look in your eyes when
you finally breathe again
that tells him you would do
anything he asked in that moment.
Anything at all without hesitation.
The story you tell him that night
about when you were a little girl,
about the place you hid from your mother
where the world was quiet.
A story you've never told another soul.
The look of confusion you show him
when you wake up the next morning
that tells him despite
the thousand other men
you've awoken beside, that he is unique.
That he has seen you vulnerable.
And that you cannot live without him.
I completely understand.
Just so we're clear,
I still fuck the shit out of him, yes?
Yes.
Is there anything else
you would like to add?
Uh, no. No, I don't think so.
Tell me again,
who are those men camped out
in your family's storehouse?
What men?
Perfect.
We're doing wrong.
He can't be on the ship right now.
Captain is holding things
together with both hands
and Billy will, understandably,
have some feelings about the
events of this past week.
If those feeling were expressed right now,
it could spoil whatever chances
we have to retrieve the Urca gold.
Where is this?
It's all right. You made it home.
What was that?
Get... Gates.
Featherstone and Idelle?
- Max told me.
- Ah.
Been in there going on three hours.
Do you think she can do it?
Swing him our way?
I think I have underestimated my last whore
for a while,
given the week I've been having.
I've put a lot of bodies in
the ground for you, haven't I?
Excuse me?
Watched your back.
Cleaned up your messes.
Carried out your plans.
I didn't always understand.
Didn't always agree.
But I did it.
Some fucked-up, awful shit
'cause I knew you needed it done.
I don't think the night you had last night
comes even close to
something to bitch about.
I know you know this is
significantly more complicated
than the quantity of tits I have
access to at any given moment.
I know she's dangerous.
Especially to me.
I ain't in my right head about her.
She knows it.
And it ain't hard to imagine her intent
is to play us off one against the other.
But I'm asking you to do this for me.
I'm asking you to watch my back
on the other side of that door.
'Cause I know as long as you are, there
ain't shit she can do to get between us.
Mr. Featherstone will announce
to his shipmates tomorrow
that he has joined a new crew.
Your crew.
What?
He believes a number of
his men will join him
upon hearing this news.
At least 28 men.
That's more than half his crew.
In addition to these new recruits,
you will be granted command
of their ship as well.
Congratulations, Captain.
A few more men in the fort
now than two hours ago,
though I believe we stemmed the tide there.
The captains I've spoken with are
on firm agreement with our position.
Several of them have
committed men and resources
to the final assault up the hill.
Though we have yet to hear
from your man Mr. Silver,
word has come in from the beach.
Support is in our favor,
though division amongst the
remaining crews is rampant.
Reports of skirmishes amongst and
within the camps has been arriving...
Numbers, please.
Pardon?
We're well aware of the discord
caused by Captain Vane's entreaty.
I want to know what we'll be
facing if we go down this road.
Roughly 65 men in the fort,
plus or minus 10.
We bring to bear 90 men on our own
plus 50 pledged by sister crews.
On rough terrain and
fighting an entrenched enemy,
I think it's safe to assume that casualties
will number threescore on our side.
As I've said, we ought harbor no illusions
about the blood that will
be spilled on that hill.
Father, how was your travel
from the country?
Wet.
Well, I think you're most optimistic
about the Admiralty's willingness to outfit
these ships you assume you can procure.
But as for the rest of it,
seems like a reasonable proposal.
Do you agree, Lieutenant?
Yes. Yes, I would, sir.
I see. Well, then, perhaps we can discuss
the one element you so
conveniently elected to ignore.
What about the pirate raiders of Nassau?
I want to put them to work.
To work? At what?
Tilling, harvesting, coopering,
building, smithing, fishing.
What are you talking about, Thomas?
I intend to secure them pardons.
A blanket amnesty for any
man who will accept it.
In exchange for his allegiance,
his renunciation of violence and his labor.
What a piece of work you are.
You asked me to formulate a plan.
That's what I've done.
I asked you to formulate a plan
that would secure the support
of the navy in our efforts.
Support without which
there is little chance
of reversing the catastrophic
downward trend in revenue
from the Bahama territories.
Support that is almost
certain to disappear entirely
and for good the moment they
hear they are to be associated
with a plan to reward men who are
in open revolt against the Crown.
This is the solution most likely
to lead to our desired result.
It also has the virtue of
being the right thing to do.
Oh, for God's sake.
Lieutenant, am I right to assume
that a proposal such as this...
Don't look at him. Talk to me.
My son is impertinent, Lieutenant.
My son is indulged.
My son is self-righteous.
But he's not stupid.
Perhaps you could explain to me
how you intend to distract the queen
from her war to issue these pardons.
I wouldn't need her to do anything.
A simple act would
accomplish the same thing.
Of Parliament? There aren't four votes
among the lords for
something as absurd as this.
Sutton, Dunster, Lewis, Form, Philpott.
There's five.
They're easy. I haven't even opened
my mouth to make an argument.
An argument to abet
sedition in times of war?
A war, sir, to ensure that a
Protestant sits on the throne of Spain.
Thomas, if I were a rival of this family,
I would be shouting from
the rooftops that any man
who proposes to pardon a
traitor in times such as these
is himself a traitor.
We are fighting a war in the
service of the son of God.
And it is treason to offer forgiveness
to any man who would seek it?
What in the hell is it you
think we're doing here?
This isn't your goddamn salon, Thomas.
If you do not forgive men their sins,
your father will not forgive your sins.
- I don't want to hear it!
- I know you don't.
Lieutenant.
I'll ask you once again,
am I to assume by your silence
that you are in agreement
with this proposal?
The lieutenant has dutifully
expressed his reservations...
Madam...
you have done enough to damage
the good name of this family.
I would ask that you keep both your mouth
and your legs firmly shut going forward...
I support it.
I found his argument persuasive.
I find his intent to be good and true.
And I find yours wanting, sir.
I will be relaying my findings to
Admiral Hennessey in short order.
And now I think it's time you left, sir.
Gentlemen.
Did you just ask my father
to leave his own house?
Right now he will be dispatching
messages to the Sea Lords,
the Southern Secretary,
his friends in the Privy Council.
He will stop at nothing to ensure
that this plan never sees the light of day.
And now you're in the line of fire.
People can say what they like about you.
But you're a good man.
More people should say that.
And someone should be willing to defend it.
Pastor.
It's before dawn.
I don't sleep anymore.
I've seen you at my service.
I've kept my distance,
but I've seen you there.
Heard of your efforts
to join our community.
To make a fresh start.
I've wanted to believe it to be true.
After...
after what happened between you and I,
I wanted to believe that
as vile as the act was,
perhaps it was born of a misguided desire
on your part to change your ways.
To seek a more virtuous path.
I do seek a more virtuous path.
Then why am I also hearing that you've
been receiving Mr. Guthrie's daughter?
Making requests
of Mr. Underhill on her behalf?
You don't understand.
I understand more than you think, ma'am.
I've been to town today.
I hear that one of the
thieves on the beach,
desirous of impressing her,
assaulted another.
Killed him.
And in a display for all to see,
mounted his severed head on a pike.
Were this not monstrous enough,
talk is it was all in service
of stealing a young girl
intended to be ransomed to her father.
None other than the governor
of the Carolina colony.
An upstanding, God-fearing man
hundreds of leagues from here
is unsafe from their brutality.
These are Miss Guthrie's associates.
These are the men on whose behalf
you would act by doing her bidding.
Men who seek profit
through the most boundless,
wanton, unrepentant barbarism.
And I'm to believe that your
desire to repent is genuine?
Lord Ashe?
What?
The governor in Carolina,
it is Lord Peter Ashe, it is not?
I believe so, but...
Lord Ashe's daughter, what was her name?
Mrs. Barlow,
what difference does her name make?
Abigail.
Her name is Abigail Ashe.
Absolution.
A clean slate for all
those willing to accept it.
A few hours ago, I informed my father
that this was my intended solution for
the pirate issue on New Providence Island.
We've talked in this room, you and I,
about reason.
We've talked about justice.
We've talked about virtue and the right.
We've talked and talked.
And now, perhaps, it is time to do that
which we've only spoken
about behind closed doors.
I am committed to this end.
But it is a long road and I will
need your help to see it through.
How can I help?
I don't believe you've
been properly introduced.
Lieutenant McGraw...
my good friend Lord Peter Ashe.
What the fuck is this?
I heard the news today.
I thought it a sign it was
time to come and see you.
You're kidding me.
Coming to gloat now?
You don't see it, do you?
You're so close to having
everything you've wanted.
Everything I told you you'll never have.
It's within your reach.
I came to help you get it.
I remember when I first saw it.
I'd never seen a structure like it.
It seemed indestructible.
If you would have told me then
the decision you face today,
I don't know if I would
have believed it possible.
Richard Guthrie sat on the throne
of commerce when I arrived.
Made men rich, they said.
Then his daughter took his place,
made Nassau strong.
Everyone knows this.
I wonder how many know
that there was one man
standing behind them.
Standing behind both thrones,
keeping the world spinning.
You're as invested in the
future of this place as any.
What would you do?
I know Eleanor's argument.
And I know why you think it is weak
and I do not disagree with you.
Her judgment about
Captain Vane has never been right.
But because she is compromised,
it does not necessarily
follow that she is wrong.
I fear that to take that fort
will be to divide this island
in a most dangerous way.
To force men to take
sides against each other
at a time when our very survival
demands the very opposite.
I fear that if we go down that road,
by the time Spain or England arrive,
they will find their job done for them.
They will find Nassau has destroyed itself.
The world changes.
It is inevitable.
Perhaps the only thing that is inevitable.
If it were me facing this decision,
I would make peace with that.
I would teach myself to see Captain Vane
as an unfortunate but unavoidable change
in our landscape.
And I would ensure that we all live
to see the sunrise again tomorrow.
Were it me.
What say you, Captain?
Fire.