♪ Love is like a sin, my love
♪ For the ones that feel it the most
♪ Look at her
with her eyes like a flame
♪ She will love you like a fly
♪ Will never love you again ♪
What?
Ian.
Three victims in five weeks,
spread across London.
Well, vics two and three
have been picked up on camera,
heading home alone after nights out.
We don't know about Monica yet.
The first victim died a month ago.
The second came two weeks later.
The third, a week after that.
And now Monica five days later.
Oh, he's escalating fast.
This ain't just a serial.
This man's on a murder spree.
Three previous victims were found
in Isleworth, Whitton, West Drayfield.
All of them were walking home alone.
Now, the dump sites are far apart,
but broadly similar,
near trading estates.
So the Met think our man may have been
a delivery driver of some sort.
Hence White Van Man.
The Met passed on data taken from
2,000 hours of CCTV footage,
tracked down and eliminated
all vans and other commercial vehicles
within a two kilometre bull's-eye zone.
Those who couldn't be eliminated
were added to the suspect pool.
Tactical Unit 1, under my command,
will focus on last night's murder
of Monica Paul.
Tactical Unit 2 will be based here
under the command of DCI Luther.
You'll review all existing case evidence
pertaining to the previous victims.
Focus on the suspect pool,
eliminate those unidentified vehicles.
Our man is locked into
a pattern of rapid escalation.
He's going to kill again, very soon,
except we are going to catch him
before he gets the chance.
- You all right in here?
- History of a case like this says
he's in our database somewhere.
We just have to prise him out.
I'm sorry to bother you, ma'am.
I thought it best.
Is he fit enough to be questioned?
Officially, it's too early to say.
Unofficially?
He's looking very good.
Police arrested two kids yesterday.
One was drinking battery acid,
the other was eating fireworks.
They charged one
and let the other one off.
Hmm!
Tommy Cooper. Boom, boom.
It was Basil Brush that said,
"Boom, boom."
Oops.
Henry Madsen woke up.
Are you in trouble?
Possibly.
Might be.
Might be in trouble.
I do know that I will be
put under surveillance.
My movements,
my phone calls... Everything.
Why?
I think they're worried that
I might sneak in and finish the job.
Well, you might be mad,
but you're not stupid.
Yeah.
I can't see you any more.
I can't talk to you.
Sorry.
You know? I really am.
But I can't do this any more, not while
this thing is hanging over my head.
- It's over.
- No.
- Yes, Alice, it's over.
I've got to go.
Got work to do.
- No!
- Yes.
No!
Oh!
Mmm.
- Morning, love.
- Morning.
- Not yet! I've got dirty hands.
- Oh?
Grease.
- You all right?
- Yeah, yeah, just washing me hands.
Textbook. After the first kill
he goes into the depressive phase,
can't believe what he's done.
Until the urge builds again,
becomes uncontrollable.
The cooling off periods
get shorter and shorter,
but not this quickly,
so what's driving the escalation?
Do you have any sexual fantasies?
What? Yeah, none that
I'm going to tell you about.
Does the reality ever
live up to the fantasy?
I, um...
Well, no.
- No, not really.
- It can't, can it?
That doesn't account
for the pace of escalation.
No, no, it doesn't. But, I mean,
we're not looking at a release, here.
We're looking at an explosion.
Now what makes a man just let go?
The trigger event is usually
some kind of perceived humiliation.
You know, loss of a job,
loss of a spouse.
I've got to take this.
20?
I just called...
- You okay?
- I'm great.
Well, I've never had an affair before.
So, I don't know what to do.
Is it still called an affair
if I'm sleeping with my wife
behind her lover's back?
Look, I've got to go.
Hello, there.
Coffee's on.
You're up early.
Yeah, I couldn't sleep.
It's been announced that earlier today
the body of a young woman was found
on a playing field
near Wandsworth Common.
Talk about
the government's economic...
- Gray? You home, love?
- Yeah, in here.
Happy birthday.
Gray. I thought you'd forgotten.
Of course I haven't, no.
No, no, never.
Come on, sit...
Sit down, relax.
Open your present.
Oh, gosh.
Oh, goodness gracious. That's...
It's really lovely.
Put it on.
Can you help me with this?
There you go.
How does it look?
Stand up. Let me see.
Come on, stand up, stand up.
It looks lovely.
It looks really lovely.
It's really gorgeous.
Mmm. Mmm.
No, no, no. No, no, no, no, not here.
Graham, not here.
Upstairs, upstairs.
Go on.
♪ Mad world
Something's going to happen
tonight, obviously.
Oh, God. These are terrible...
♪ Mad world
♪ Children waiting for the day they feel
- Hi.
- Hello, Gray!
- You all right? Good to see you, mate.
- Yeah.
Have a seat, have a seat.
Yeah, all right.
Linda, how you doing? Happy birthday!
- So what'll you have to drink, guys?
- White wine, please, big one.
Uh, yeah. Coke, please, mate.
Same again, everyone, yeah?
♪ No one knew me No one knew me
- There you go, madam.
- Thank you.
Enjoy.
So did you get anything nice
for your b-day?
Um, yeah I got this.
He got me a necklace.
I thought he'd forgotten.
When did he give it to you?
Just, well, just before we come out,
which is why I thought he'd forgotten.
Because I didn't get anything
this morning.
♪ I find it hard to tell you ♪
- What's all this?
- Decoupage. The cut-up technique.
Take a bit of text, cut it up,
randomise it, make new text.
- See new patterns.
- Where'd you learn this?
David Bowie.
- It's how he wrote his lyrics.
- You a fan?
Don't I look like a fan?
What, of songs about like aliens
and that?
No, there's a bit more to him
than aliens. I'll make you a tape.
- A what, sorry?
- Ah. You've gone all David Bowie on us.
Yeah, cause of death confirmed.
He chokes them.
No forensics to speak of, no witnesses.
I've just spent a day
interviewing the family.
There's mother, one sister,
one boyfriend, long-term.
Is he on the list?
No, he was pulling a night shift.
I took him through the inventory,
the stuff our man left around her.
- Anything missing?
- Yeah, necklace.
Some of these guys keep news clippings,
photographs, whatever.
- The fact that he likes jewellery...
- Suggests that he's
married, in a relationship.
He'd give the necklace
to his wife, girlfriend.
Every time he sees it,
he's taken back to the kill.
But the suddenness of it?
What sets him off like that?
She's about to leave him.
So it just pushes him over the edge.
We don't need insight into his
tortured soul to understand who he is.
We just need to know who the hell
he is and where the hell he's at.
♪ You know I don't believe you
♪ When you say that you don't need me
♪ Don't don't you want me?
♪ I know that you believe me
♪ When you think
you've changed your mind
♪ You'd better change it back
or we will both be sorry
♪ Don't you want me...
Oh, no, really, really,
I'm really shocked.
Is that meant to be me? It's charming.
It's got your eyes, it's lovely.
♪ Don't you want me, baby?
♪ Don't you want me?
Oh, oh, oh ♪
Wow!
Wow, ladies!
Sorry, love.
Listen, I've got to go to work.
- That's all right, don't worry.
- Happy birthday!
You enjoy yourself.
Look after her for me, mate, won't you?
Make sure she has a good time.
Will do mate, yeah.
Sorry we were running
a bit late tonight, mate.
But, uh, I had to give
her one for her birthday.
You know how she likes it,
good and hard and long.
Tell you the truth,
I'm surprised she can walk.
- See you later.
- Yeah, see you later.
Come on, girls!
Let's see if we can
beat that last one...
Come on, girls!
So why was she walking home by herself?
She was meeting friends
in the pub to talk about the hen night.
She's happy, she's engaged,
she's on home turf.
She's not about to get into
a white van with Jack the lad.
Blitz attack. He jumps out,
clubs her, drags her into the van.
Yeah, no. There was no screams, no sign
of any altercation. That's not him.
She trusted him. He knows her, maybe?
- He can't have known all four of them.
- No, he didn't.
But they trusted him.
They trusted him.
I think we're looking for a taxi driver.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Luther.
Luther!
What's wrong?
Henry Madsen is talking.
The doctors won't let us
anywhere near him, not yet.
So right now,
anything he might say means nothing.
It's inadmissible. Hearsay.
Guv, what's he saying?
Your name.
Right, okay.
Okay.
Ten minutes ago we got this.
This is the south end of Broughton Row.
It's the closest to our hit.
- Is that her?
- Yeah, we think that's her.
Tell me we've got
the number plate.
Number plate. Driver's name,
home address, phone number.
Just triangulating the mobile phone
signal now.
- We've got him locked on.
- Good.
So... Go, go!
Hey, love!
I don't need a cab, thanks.
I don't live that far.
Yeah, no, listen, it's not that, love.
This has just come over the radio.
Some girl's been attacked
just down the road.
- Just past Holywell Avenue.
- Oh, you're joking.
Yeah, apparently he got
away before he could do too much,
but they wanted us to keep an eye out
because he's probably still out there.
I had to stop and tell you, love.
They make us do it.
- Yeah.
- You sure you'll be all right?
- Yeah. It's not far.
- Where do you live?
Um, Lacey Road? Just down that way.
That's past Holywell, isn't it?
I'd hate it if my girl had to
walk home alone, this time of night,
- with all this going on. Hop in.
- I can't. I haven't got any...
Forget about the money. We'll just
get you home safely, all right?
Come Christmas,
give five quid to the dog's home for me.
- Are you sure?
- Get in.
Come on.
Caught you.
Police, step out the vehicle.
Trevor Rowan, I'm arresting you
on suspicion of murder.
You do not have to say anything.
- Not to mention, when questioned...
- I haven't done anything!
Something which you later
rely on in court.
It's all right, love.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, I think
you missed a turn back there,
that was my street, Lacey Road?
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
What's wrong?
Just that you said he was impotent.
He is.
Well, he was.
I don't know, it's come back.
The last few weeks, it's come back.
I hate it.
Do we have to talk about this?
When I'm here, can't I just be here?
He knows, don't he?
About me and you? He absolutely knows.
Hey, babe, please.
No.
Oh...
You all right?
Me?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm good. I'm great!
- Why?
- Oh, no reason, you just seemed...
You sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
♪ Search your heart
♪ Search your soul
♪ And when you find me there
♪ You'll search no more
♪ Don't tell me...
- Stop.
- No.
Stop.
♪ You're not worth fighting for ♪
- I hate that song!
- Oh, you love it, you love it!
- I hate it!
- You love it!
Help!
Hello, you're through to Zoe Luther.
Please leave me a message
after the tone and I'll get back...
His alibi sticks.
He was on Eccleston Road, SW1.
He's not our man.
So there are two taxis
with the same number plate
on the same night in London?
Yeah, no, he just cloned them.
It's easy to do, you know.
So what do we have?
Well, we have this...
He attempts to make a turn
at the end of Broughton Row,
messes up, does a U-turn.
So we checked it out
and it turns out that
Broughton Row used to be a through-way,
but when the hookers moved in,
they locked it off
and made it a rat run.
- This was when?
- March, uh, 2002.
The implication being?
Well, I don't think
he's a real taxi driver.
He tried to be one,
or used to be one but...
Yeah.
Not only is there no law
against owning second-hand taxis,
it's easy and cheap.
How many people
are running around in these things?
There's no database. But it runs into
the high hundreds, early thousands easy.
God.
It's more than you want to think about,
let alone track down.
He could have a different licence plate
for every night of the month.
He's completely anonymous.
One taxi and 20,000 others.
Trusted by default.
He might as well be invisible.
Yeah, and he's on a feeding frenzy.
There'll be another body tomorrow.
And another
and another.
Teller.
Chartwell Hospital's on fire.
Excuse me, sorry.
Sorry, excuse me, thank you.
Uh, Officer?
Fulford.
We're having some trouble with a few
members of the public on Ward 28.
They're refusing to leave the building.
Response is on its way,
but since you're here...
- I'm not supposed to...
- I wouldn't ask
if I didn't think it was an emergency.
I'll wait with the patient.
Ward 28?
Next floor down.
Don't say his name.
Cabbies who've been sacked,
invalided off, retired,
plus a list of drivers who've
tried and failed the Knowledge
over the last 20 years.
Triangulated, cross-reference
with the suspect pool...
Best?
Left with 23 names.
Sergeant Ripley,
would you mind if I borrowed
the Detective Chief Inspector
for a moment?
Um, no, not at all, sir.
Stressful day?
Oh, five victims dead,
possibly another in 12 hours.
Henry Madsen passed away.
- I'm sorry?
- It could be fluke,
unconnected with the fire.
But the fire was arson
and these two events, co-occurring.
Madsen had a permanent guard.
Who was directed away
from his post by some doctor.
What doctor?
Well, quite young, very pretty.
Dark haired and heterochromatic.
Hetero what? I'm sorry?
Different coloured eyes.
Like David Bowie.
But no doctor with
heterochromia of the eyes
is currently employed
by the Chartwell Hospital...
Well, I don't know. Some doctor lost
a contact lens, perhaps?
Probably.
But if not...
If somebody is impersonating,
posing as a doctor, someone
who wants access to Henry Madsen.
Would you have any notion
of who that might be?
I could think of 100 people
that would want to see him dead.
But I'd start off with
the parents of the victims.
Yes, of course.
But the timing, you see,
the timing, it... It chafes my brain.
Why now?
Why today... The day after he wakes up?
I don't know, Martin, we'll just have to
put that down to a big
mystery.
Well, I can see you're busy.
Hello?
Don't worry about the call being traced.
This is a disposable phone.
One conversation,
I wipe it and it goes into
someone else's garbage.
Listen to me, I think I told you
that I don't want to speak to you.
Not today, not tomorrow. Not ever
again.
Well, there's a remarkable
absence of gratitude for you.
Do you know what you've done?
Given you back your wife.
Saved your job.
Saved you from
disgrace and imprisonment.
No, you've committed murder.
All I did was finish
the job you started.
What are you going to do, arrest me?
- Yes! I have to!
- Shall I articulate why you won't?
Stop!
You're the one who made me do it.
You've threatened me.
There's phone traffic
between us to prove it,
including the call I'm making
from this phone.
Empty threats.
You implicate me,
you implicate yourself,
and you're way too
in love with your own genius to do that.
Conspiracy to murder
will just be the start of it.
I can send you to hell.
You'll burn for the rest of your life.
Which is why
I would appreciate some gratitude!
I did it for you! Pig!
Filth! I did it for you!
I want you to stay away!
Do you understand? Stay away from me!
Stay away from my life!
Stay the fuck away! Do you hear me?
What can I do for you, Martin?
Busy day here.
I'd like John Luther's
phone and email records, please.
- Go away.
- I can't.
Whatever it is you're here to tell me,
I don't want to hear it.
So do us a favour,
get yourself an exorcist.
I see.
You already know.
- Know what?
- Zoe's been lying to you.
No, no, no. I don't want to hear it.
All right?
I want you out of my way.
I want you out of my life.
Hah, yes,
I've been hearing that a lot today.
I wish I could help you. But I can't.
So I would like you, please,
to stay away.
- You are completely...
- Right.
You all right, boss?
It was the wife. Ex-wife.
Come in.
Um, those suspects...
- Have you eaten?
- What are you, my nan?
Best hit, Graham Shand, drinking in
the same pub as victim number one.
Failed the Knowledge three times,
the last time in 2002.
Until six weeks ago, he worked nights
at a taxi breakdown and recovery garage.
Formerly decent employee.
Seems to have undergone
some kind of breakdown,
drinking, sexually
inappropriate conduct.
Um, got one. Um, any hard evidence?
No, none. No record of him, his wife,
known friends or family
ever buying a second-hand taxi.
Well, he's had plenty of opportunity
to buy one under the table,
cash in hand, eh?
- Form?
- Uh, none.
I'll get DCI Reed to the house
with a warrant.
- What will we do if he's not there?
- Get him in his weak spot.
- What's that?
- The wife. Always the wife.
Check her out, bring her in.
Nice work.
So what's happening with you and Zoe?
That was her on the phone
just now, right?
- Yes, it was Zoe.
- So are you and she...
No.
Yes. Possibly.
I don't know.
It's nice to see you're happy for me.
You want to know
the real tragedy about marriage?
- No, thanks.
- Women always think men will change,
but they don't.
Men think women won't change,
but they do.
Where'd you get that from,
a fortune cookie?
I need you to stay in this building
until you're cleared to leave.
I'm trying to run an investigation here.
Yeah, and like you say, this is
the best place to run it from, so...
Just do that.
No one.
No one's home.
Yeah, bye.
All right? We're shut.
- Uh, Linda Shand?
- Yeah?
Uh, Mrs Shand,
I'm Detective Sergeant Ripley.
Hang on. Hang on. Who, sorry?
Detective Sergeant Ripley
of the Serious Crime Unit, Hobb Lane.
I wonder if you wouldn't mind
coming with me,
help clear up a few things.
Uh, what sort of thing?
Probably it's nothing, we just need you
to answer a few questions.
About what?
Graham, mostly.
Oh, my God.
What's he done... Has he done something?
If you'd like to come with me?
Oh, I feel sick. Can I just?
Yeah, course.
- Linda?
- What's going on?
- What do you mean?
- The police are here.
- What do they want?
- I don't know!
- Well, did they mention me?
- What did you do?
- What did they say?
- Have you been stealing again?
No, of course I haven't! No!
Then what have you done, Graham?
Well, what did they say? They must have
said something. What did they say?
Give me the phone, give me the phone!
God!
We don't have any other room,
so I have to use the interview room.
Can I get you a drink or anything?
- Uh, yes, some water.
- You want some water? Okay.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
So how are things
with you and your husband?
Fine. Why?
Do you know where he was Friday night?
Yeah, at the pub.
With me and some friends.
It was my birthday.
Was he with you all night?
Not all night, no.
‘Cause he... He went to work.
Work where?
He works at an
all-night recovery garage.
The thing is, Linda, Graham hasn't
worked there for two months now.
You didn't know?
Boss? I'm sorry to interrupt.
It's a bit urgent.
- Right now?
- I'm afraid it can't wait, sir, sorry.
Linda, if you'll excuse me, uh...
I've got to dash.
Come back and we'll finish talking,
all right?
Sorry, talk about what, I...
Soon as I get back,
we'll talk, all right? Sorry.
- I time that all right?
- Perfect.
How is she?
Well, she knows something's not right.
No.
You don't think this approach
is a bit merciless?
No.
Graham knows we're on to him, all right?
And he'll try and kill as many as he can
before we catch him.
If I have to terrify his wife
to stop that happening,
I can live with that.
Thus spake John Luther,
gentleman of the parish.
She knows what her husband is.
Yeah, but maybe not
what he's done.
There is a difference.
There's...
No, no...
No, no, what is this?
What's this? What is that?
What is that?
What... What...
- Linda?
- No, get it off me!
What is that? What is that?
Oh, my God! Oh, my God! No, no, no!
No, no, my God, no, no...
Oh, God!
No! Oh, God, oh, God, oh, God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
What did he do? What did he do? Oh, God!
It's all right.
- Is there a glass for me?
- Of course.
Okay.
I have something I need...
I need to say to, um...
To tell you.
You already know.
Yeah, pretty much.
How?
Well, it hardly takes
an intuitive genius, does it?
Well, why didn't you say something?
Perhaps it's none of my business.
Of course it's your business!
Don't say that.
Please...
It's absolutely your business!
Look, um...
- You know, for what it's worth...
- Oh, Mark!
No, seriously, this is what
I think you should do,
you should make a list
of the reasons why you married him.
And then make another list of
the reasons why you left him.
And then see if
the two lists don't overlap.
I'm so sorry.
He's not what I want. He's just not.
Well, what do you want?
This.
Here.
Right now, with you.
- You all right?
- I can't...
Uh, I know, I know.
- It's all right, okay?
- What's he done?
Hey, Linda, do you mind
if we keep talking?
Yeah?
Linda, how long
have you been married?
Uh...
Um... 20 years.
He said if I ever left him,
he'd kill himself.
And, um, I tried, once.
I, um, packed my bags
and bought a ticket to Cardiff.
And he slashed his wrists in the bath
and he called me
before he called the ambulance.
He didn't even do it properly.
He just sliced at his wrists.
There was lots of blood, lots of drama,
but no real risk to Graham.
Which is the story of his life.
I'm going to ask you some really
difficult
and personal questions. My intention
is not to embarrass you, okay?
Is it about the handbags?
Yes.
Yeah, why don't you tell me
about the handbags?
Early on, oh, we must have been married,
what, a year, 18 months...
He used to nick them.
And, uh, and I confronted him and he...
He cried and, uh, he made up some story.
You reported him?
- No.
- Why?
‘Cause he's my husband.
What did you think he was doing
with the hand bags?
He used to, um,
sniff them and, uh,
touch himself.
I was embarrassed.
And a bit of me thought it was...
A bit of me was scared it was me.
That I was doing something wrong
and that, uh,
somehow, you know, people
would find out and... And they'd laugh.
Look, Linda, I have to tell you, Graham
is involved in a very serious crime.
And these urges,
these urges that he's had,
he's controlled them for a while.
Until suddenly,
this.
He's been murdering young women.
It's not my fault.
What, what's not your fault?
What do you mean by that?
Linda? Hey, hey, look at me.
What's not your fault?
I forgot to erase a text message.
He checks my phone
when I'm in the shower.
He goes down my handbag.
He checks your phone and
found out you were
sleeping with someone?
Who is he, Linda?
It's not my fault.
You need to tell me his name.
Right, here it is, Dennis Keaton,
23 Black Swan Way.
Call him, tell him to keep himself safe.
Graham is punishing her
for being unfaithful.
He's working his way
towards killing her.
Can't do it now, 'cause we've got her,
so he's gonna go for
the next best thing.
Gray?
Straight to answerphone. Guv?
Uh, what was the last number
called from his house?
The last number from a Dennis Keaton
is City Chic Escorts.
Oh, no, no, has he done it before?
No.
Dennis Keaton is dead.
Get me the number
of the hooker that's going there,
put them on speaker for me.
- Oh, hang on a sec.
- What?
Text message from a Layla.
- "Safe arrival, 23 Black Swan Way."
- Oh, no.
Let me see if I can get Reed
on the speaker.
Come on, Layla, pick up the phone.
I'm almost there.
Two, three minutes max.
She's already there.
She's an escort, her name's Layla.
Can't kick the door down.
He'll kill her.
What do you suggest?
I got to be there, boss.
- Come on, I've got to go!
- No.
How quickly can you get there?
Just tell me what to do and it's done.
Ian, I'm going to send Ripley.
Take Linda.
We'll go for that weak spot.
Dennis, is it?
Absolutely.
It's lovely to meet you, Dennis.
I'm Layla.
- May I?
- Yeah.
Well?
Yeah. Yeah.
- So, do we, uh?
- Absolutely.
You're the boss.
But first...
Oh, right, yeah, um...
- 225.
- You're very kind.
So, would you like to show me
where you want me?
Upstairs, if that's okay?
That's absolutely fine.
Dennis, it's my girlfriend.
She likes to check up on me during
dates, to make sure I arrive safely.
- Do you mind?
- No, of course not. Go ahead.
Hello, darling.
Layla, this is Chief Inspector
John Luther.
I need you to
listen to me very carefully.
Keep smiling and act
like this is the agency calling you.
Yeah, yeah, I got here quite safely.
Right, excellent. Okay, can you
get out of the house safely?
Not really, not right now, love.
Listen to me.
I need you to get to a safe place
and just wait for us. We're on our way.
I will. Stop worrying, silly.
Honestly.
Anyway.
Second door on the right.
Can I take your bag?
Of course.
- Can 1...
- What?
Bathroom.
I'd rather you didn't.
Let me in! Come on!
Listen, love. Let me in! Let me in!
Come on! Come on!
Let me in! Let me in, let me in!
- You've got to help me.
- Listen, we're close. Hold on.
Please! Please, come now,
I need you, please!
- Layla, Layla...
- Justin, where are you?
Help me!
I just want to touch you!
I just want to kiss you.
Do you know what I'm going to do to you?
Graham?
Gray? Are you here?
Graham, are you here?
See?
Look at you.
You sad little prick!
Put the hammer down, Graham.
You're all done.
Now, just put it down, all right?
I'm tired, I want to go home.
Ah! Ah!
Graham Shand, I am arresting you
on suspicion of murder.
You do not have to say anything,
but it may harm your defence
if you fail to mention when questioned
something which you
later rely on in court.
Sorry. Excuse me.
20?
Um,
look, I know it's late.
I, uh... I've just called you 100 times.
I know it's difficult.
I just want to hear your voice.
It's just been a way
of saying goodbye properly.
There is love in the world.
Are you sure you're all right?
It's not my fault! It's not my fault.
Yeah, yeah. I'm fine.
All I need you to do is
give me those diamonds.
I don't have them.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::