You're gonna fall, Henry.
Please.
Please!
Alice Morgan is a malignant narcissist.
This is about prestige,
power, self-affirmation.
She killed her parents.
No forensics, no witnesses.
Send her home!
I still love you, Zoe.
You care more about
the dead than the living.
That's where your heart is.
Do you love him?
I didn't ask you for it, did I?
-Hello, John.
Alice.
You may be very, very clever.
But you're wrong.
There is love in the world.
So you lose.
Lima Sierra 219 to Control.
Confirm, we do have a white male down.
Mid 20s, possible gunshot wounds, over.
Received, Lima Sierra 219.
Ambulance en route,
ETA four minutes, over.
♪ Love is like a sin, my love
♪ For the ones
that feel it the most
♪ Look at her
with her eyes like a flame
♪ She will love you like a fly
♪ Will never love you again ♪
Thank you for coming in so early.
As you know, DCI Luther
Is facing a charge of assault
occasioning actual bodily harm.
These are matters we take
very seriously indeed.
But I need to know from you,
Mr North, without prejudice
exactly what happened yesterday.
Did DCI Luther assault you?
Look, uh, the truth is...
DCI Luther was defending himself.
I'm not proud to tell you this,
but I threw the first punch.
And, um, quite honestly,
I thought the police were heavy handed.
I will ask you to sign
a statement to this effect.
That's why I'm here.
This is DI John Luther,
leave a message.
I know how hard that was for you.
I'm fine.
I might work from home today, though.
Thank you.
You might want to try
answering your phone.
Get a reputation for answering
phones and all they do is ring.
You've spoken to Zoe?
- No.
- Ah, well.
Then, you should know that
Mark North gave you a pass.
He's not pressing charges.
So how about we finish
this chat away from the edge?
Do you never do this?
Come up to a really high place and
wonder what it would be like just...
- to fall?
- Fall or jump?
- Same thing.
- I beg to differ.
But, mostly I go home, watch
America's Next Top Model.
Do you not worry you're on the
devil's side without even knowing it?
No.
- Just let it go, John.
- I already let him go.
Just didn't finish the job
off properly, did I?
- And nobody shed a tear.
- That doesn't make it right.
Makes it a little bit
less wrong, though.
So, you going to jump?
Probably not.
Well, then I'm bored of this game.
You going back to the factory?
I've been on 18 hours straight.
I'm going home, mate. You should try it.
I might.
Or I might not.
This is Mike Eppley.
Over here, this is Steve Gorman.
Yeah.
- You knew them?
- A little bit.
- Sorry.
- Don't be sorry.
If you see Gorman and Eppley,
you go blind. See the scene.
Tell me what you see.
Right. Well, Gorman
was shot at close range.
Double tap to the chest.
Entry wounds are two-three inches apart.
That's good shooting, that is.
And this blood here,
it's real but it won't be the shooter's.
It looks staged to me.
Staged. Look, look, look.
This is an execution.
There can't be. There's no
way the shooter would know
that Gorman and Eppley
would attend this call-out.
No, I didn't say he was
targeting Gorman and Eppley.
I said it was an execution.
I don't understand what that means.
Nor do I. Excuse me, bag that.
Grab that. Thank you.
All right.
Morning, Corinne.
Any suspects, John? Off the record?
- You've got my number.
- Yeah, memorised. Six, six, six.
Direct line.
- Anything?
- Yeah, yeah. Could be.
Cobden Lane links Northlight
Road and Stockwood Hill
- here to here. Yeah?
- Yeah.
Less than three minutes after the
shooting, this man crossed the road
half a kilometre from
the Stockwood Hill exit.
Is that it?
- Well, we're lucky to get that.
- Yeah, where does he go?
Um, ducks behind shops on Hamilton Row.
Behind that, there's another lane.
Gives out onto allotments,
gardens, a canal.
No more CCTV?
No. Coverage is spotty at best.
Plus, a lot of cameras
in the area have been vandalised.
Vandalised, when?
Uh, well, four were
reported down...
Four went down Monday night.
Yeah, the shooter would have
taken them out, wouldn't he?
All right, so we need to
review the footage going back seven days
before the sabotage, see if we can't
find our man on his recce.
Can I hear that 999 call again?
Yeah.
There's been a shooting,
a man's lying face down
at the north end of Cobden Lane.
Yeah, listen to that,
that's a very efficient call.
No ambiguity,
just essential information.
People leaving crime scenes, yeah,
they hunch, look at the
ground, avoid eye-contact.
Look at him, straight back,
square shoulders.
He's alert, he's calm,
he's aware of his surroundings.
I bet you any money,
he's armed forces.
What, you get that from this?
You ever been in a pub or bar,
whatever, and you know,
you just know the guy
next to you is a copper?
- Yeah, sometimes.
- Yeah, well, I grew up around soldiers.
The way he walks, talks, shoots.
That's a soldier.
All right, so we need to
look up army personnel
that have suffered
at the hands of the police.
Dig up aggravated arrest
complaints filed by veterans
on behalf of themselves,
friends, family, all right?
It'll be a long list.
Those soldiers coming back
from war don't find it easy.
They get depressed, they drink,
they fight, they get arrested.
Justin, this was an execution.
I'm not saying the assassin
was targeting Gorman and Eppley.
But I'm saying, what if he was
targeting their uniforms?
Hmm?
Right, I get it. I'm on it.
What do you want?
I've been reading
Bertrand Russell to a friend of yours.
"Often, the good suffer,
and the wicked prosper,
"and one hardly knows which
of those is the more annoying."
What are you talking about?
Where... Where are you?
If only he could speak.
What tales he could tell.
What are you playing at, Alice?
- I'm investigating you.
- I don't know what that means.
What it means?
I am curious about how Henry
came to be here like this.
Well there's no need to be curious.
He killed children,
he tried to run away, I caught him,
he fell
And who actually believes that?
Everyone that matters.
Zoe, for example?
Yes.
- Because do you know what I think?
- I can't imagine.
I think you gave in to your true nature,
Just for a second, and let him fall.
And you couldn't take it.
You gave in to guilt and self-loathing.
How am I doing?
Not so well.
But mostly, you were terrified that Zoe
might discover what you'd done
and learn what kind of man
you actually are.
You don't know anything about
me, let alone my marriage.
Well, I can always ask her myself.
See what she says.
Alice, I know this is
Just a sport to you,
but you need to stop.
Just stop.
Don't go anywhere near Zoe.
Anywhere near her.
And don't say a word about this to
anyone, do you understand me?
Why, exactly?
Are you scared of what
I'll find out or what she will?
Hey, have we got anything?
Half a dozen
names hit key markers.
Mostly drunk and disorderly,
aggravated assault.
But I'm thinking,
"Nah, it's not enough for our boy."
All right, then, we'll broaden
the search parameters.
Go back to veterans from the first Gulf
War, Northern Ireland, Falklands...
He's in there somewhere.
Police say the
killer is armed and extremely dangerous.
Members of the public who see him should
not attempt to apprehend him,
but immediately dial 999.
Police, at present,
are refusing to comment
on a possible motive for the murders,
but wish to re-assure the public
that they are doing everything
possible to catch the killer.
Terry Lynch.
Ex-46 Commando, Royal Marines.
Decorated veteran.
Eighteen months ago, killed a police
officer while resisting an arrest.
Yeah, I remember this.
Dennis Sorrel. Decent bloke.
Lynch was in a bar,
got into an argument.
Sorrel was the first responder,
tried to calm things down.
- Lynch glassed him. Sorrel bled out.
- Yeah.
And Lynch pleaded "combat stress”.
That's maybe not
so mad as it sounds.
About 10% of the prison population
is comprised of veterans,
12,000 from Iraq and Afghanistan.
I don't care what Terry Lynch
did at Goose Green, Desert Storm,
Operation Enduring Freedom.
It doesn't give him
a free pass to kill coppers!
Anyway, he can't be our man.
He's inside. "Life without possibility."
Well, this is his son, Owen Lynch.
Also 46 Commando.
Returned from Afghanistan last year.
Forced to leave under
"administrative discharge,"
which means he had
mental health issues.
- Army left him high and dry.
- Got an address?
Uh, statement from his wife, Rachel.
She threw him out because, "The man who
came back wasn't the man who left."
Yeah, well, he's taken it out on her
once too often, she's thrown him out.
And that was the last time
he showed up on the radar,
until Gorman and Eppley last night.
Gorman and Eppley had nothing to do
with his father being sent down?
No.
Is this as bad as it sounds?
Yeah, false alarm. Prank call.
That's me done for the day.
Put the kettle on, over.
Boss! We've got another officer down.
Harthill Estate.
Come on!
Where was the shooter?
As far as we could establish,
he turned the corner
into the street down here.
He just walked right up and shot her.
- Point blank?
- In the abdomen.
- This isn't right.
- Sir?
Well, last night,
he fires four perfect shots in the dark.
And today, in broad daylight,
he messes up and leaves Hanson alive.
That's not right.
It's not right, it's not right.
Oh, no.
Everyone, take cover!
Mother...
After an unprecedented six fatalities
in less than 24 hours, there is
a sense on the streets of London
that the police presence
is being greatly reduced
in response to these killings.
Despite the Metropolitan Police's
strident denials,
can the emergency services
afford to maintain
their 9-9-9 response commitment
to ordinary people of the capital?
This is Corinne Day, BBC News, London.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
No. I've never been shot at before.
You know, there's people
you can speak to these days.
If you need to.
- What, like a counsellor?
- Yeah. Why not?
If my dad knew if I'd seen a counsellor,
he'd shoot me himself.
All right, everyone.
Roll up, roll up.
Orders from on high.
All personnel will be issued with
bullet-proof vests, where available.
Now, I know "where available"
isn't what you want to hear,
but it's the best we can do,
there we go.
Any questions?
Good.
Now, this has been a bad day.
The worst day most of us
have seen on the job.
Looking around, I'm reminded that many
of us are bedraggled old fossils
with quite a few bad days behind us.
So, what we're going to do,
ladies and gents,
is sniff out this bastard,
then show him and the rest of the world
that no one can do this to us.
So, let's get out there and get him.
Let's have it, then!
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
My name is Owen Lynch,
ex-46 Commandos, Royal Marines.
This is my dad...
Terry Lynch,
also 46 Commando, Royal Marines.
He was at Bluff Cove when they shot
down an Argentine jet using rifles.
After that he did two tours
in County Armagh.
His final tour was in
the Helmand province.
Last year, he went to prison for a crime
that would never have been committed
if this country had given him
the respect that he deserved.
But that doesn't happen.
More men who served in the Falklands
have committed suicide since
than died in the war itself.
That may soon be true
of men serving in Iraq and Afghanistan.
My dad was defending himself
from a belligerent arrest.
He shouldn't be in prison for murder.
Police officers will continue
to die until justice is done.
No negotiations will be entered into,
and there will be no
further communication from me.
Freedom for Terry Lynch.
How many views so far?
Thirty thousand and counting.
All major news media outlets
have picked up on it.
It's out there, it's not coming back.
He hardly mentions himself.
Does that not strike you as weird?
I mean, he's just got
back from the war,
his life's in shreds, but this
whole declaration's about
what his dad's done and what his dad's
achieved, where his dad served.
Find out whether
Owen has visited Terry Lynch in prison.
Sir.
I've got to get this.
Stop stalking me, Alice,
you're yesterday's news.
Yes, I heard about the dead policemen.
I was worried about you, John.
About what, that someone
else might get me?
I know how hard men like you
take the death of fellow officers.
It must be like losing family.
I'm not discussing cases with you.
Not even interesting ones?
This isn't interesting, all right?
These are good cops doing good jobs,
being gunned down
on the streets like...
Like what?
That's something we all do,
isn't it in the end...
Judge who's worth more than whom.
Hitler or Gandhi?
The very young, the very old?
But, to be fair, most of us
don't do it to the extent that you do.
But it does mean the difference between
us is one of degree, not category.
- Ask Henry Madsen.
- All right, you win, okay?
You're too clever for me, Alice.
Flattery to appease a malignant
narcissist, that's a frivolous tactic.
Are you afraid of me?
- Yes.
- Why?
- You know why.
- Do you want me to leave you alone?
- Yes, I do.
- Then answer my questions.
- Why?
- To help with my investigation.
I've got means, opportunity.
You still haven't given me motive.
Why did you let Henry Madsen fall?
I can't say what you want to hear, okay?
Do you think Zoe could
clarify the situation for me?
Last time you spoke to Zoe,
you shoved a knife in her ear, so I
think she'll be disinclined to chat.
It wasn't a knife and
I wasn't asking permission.
And believe me, if I pay
her a visit she'll talk.
Hey, listen, I don't
respond well to threats.
Hmm, I think coffee, do you want some?
- Tea.
- Tea? Builder's?
Is it John?
John?
- Have you got a minute?
- Not to argue, I don't.
No, just, I want to ask you something.
Um, I need you to leave London.
Not for long. Just a few days.
Go to your mum and dad's or,
um, Mark's parents, or whatever.
- What's wrong? Why?
- I've received a viable threat.
- What kind of a threat?
- From Alice Morgan.
He's playing mind games, right?
It's a control thing.
He wants to control you. He always did.
You don't know him!
It's pathetic. Honestly...
What is he going to do next?
Is he going to bang you on the head,
drag you to a cave by the hair?
Do you like this kind of thing?
This controlling, macho bullshit?
I can't believe you're
being so childish about this.
I can't believe you let this man
turn you into such an arsehole.
- He received a threat.
- Says him.
Oh, come on, we're not
interrogating your masculinity here!
Yeah, well, we don't have to worry about
that, do we? I'm secure enough
to weather any comparison
you care to make with your ex-husband.
Of course you are. And you shouldn't
be questioning my motives.
It's just...
Look, John knows this stuff,
and if he thinks we should leave,
I honestly think we should
take him seriously.
- Do you know what I think?
- What, this last half hour wasn't it?
You know what I think?
If there was a threat...
If there was a threat,
a genuine threat to your safety,
there would already
be a security detail outside the door.
Zoe, the police look after
their own. He's lying.
I don't know why he's lying,
but he's lying.
That's really not fair.
Well, a simple solution.
Why don't we just pick up
the phone and dial his boss?
See what she thinks about this threat.
- I got what you wanted.
- Footage from the prison?
Okay, so you look here at Owen Lynch's
most recent visit to his dad,
should be just over
two weeks ago. No audio, of course.
No hugs. No smiles.
Owen's nervous. Whatever Terry's saying,
Owen's finding it profoundly stressful.
When did Terry lose his appeal?
Uh, about a month ago.
So this is, what, two weeks ago?
Yeah.
Do you know what we're looking at?
We're looking at Owen
receiving his orders.
Crikey.
Don't tell me.
I've got a visitor.
Gotcha.
Right, you brief John,
I'll trace this number.
Two schoolgirls are coming home
from Sunday school one day,
and one turns to the other
and says, "Do you believe in the devil?"
The other one says,
"Don't be silly, of course not.
"The devil's like Santa.
"It's only your dad."
I always thought that was funny.
The thing is about little boys
is that they
worship their dads like gods.
The more invisible he is,
the more arbitrary in his
punishment and rewards,
the more they crave his approval.
I know what it must
be like for Owen. My dad was a soldier.
1st Armoured Division,
7th Armoured Brigade.
So, Germany, mostly.
Canada, a little bit of Cyprus.
I bet your old man was a right
old hard bastard, wasn't he?
Well, see, it was tough for him, you
see. 'Cause here I am, a big lad,
eager to please,
wanting to care about
the things he cared about,
Army, sports.
No, there was nothing.
He wanted me to box,
and I just wanted to read
books, write, meet girls.
In the end, I just gave up
trying to make him proud,
‘cause I just knew
it was never going to happen.
But this daft bastard,
he hasn't given up, though, has he?
More than anything,
he just wants to make his dad proud.
Now, Terry,
I know you gave him a job to do,
but I don't think you quite
appreciate the implications.
In crimes like this,
half the offenders end up
shooting themselves in the face
and the other half get shot by police.
Your boy's going to die
unless you help him.
Oh, yeah?
By doing what?
Go on camera.
Tell him to stop. Rescind the order.
All right, I could do that, yeah.
- But?
- I need a reduction in sentence.
That's not going to happen,
Terry. You killed a police officer.
I'm not asking for a pardon.
I'm asking for a reduction.
I got life for murder.
It should've been five
years for manslaughter, with diminished.
Now, I'll take that, with time served.
Even if there was a precedent,
there'd be no time.
I don't know about that, 'cause Owen can
look after himself, can't he?
He could be out there
for weeks, mate, before you catch him.
- Weeks and weeks...
- This is your son we're talking about!
And you're sitting
in here, killing him.
Not if you give me what I want.
You're not getting what you want!
Five years with time served
and transfer to an open prison.
Now, if you can do that for me,
you can come back and you can bring
all the cameras that you want.
Boss, we've triangulated the signal.
Static? Mobile?
No movement.
He's keeping his head down.
Sensible boy.
This is Teller. We've got a
possible location for Owen Lynch.
We need to scramble
Tactical Support. Address?
We found a SIM card,
one number listed in the contacts.
Belongs to a pay-as-you-go,
which we've traced to 185 Ellwyn Mews.
That's a vacant property,
overlooked by a trading estate.
Commercial buildings.
Makes for a decent bolt hole.
Owen Lynch won't let himself
get caught. He'd rather die.
Yeah, and nobody seems to be having
much of a problem with that.
Are you worried about something?
Getting shot at, mostly.
That's it, is it?
Be a good boy. Use your words.
It's just, I've been thinking.
- What?
- One number on the SIM card.
- One number.
- One number, one son.
Yeah, I know, but it's niggling me.
On a day like this, if all you've got is
a niggle, you're laughing, mate.
I know, but you're in prison,
got nothing else
to think about but one number,
one important number.
Well, you memorise it, don't you?
You don't write it down.
You memorise it.
Ian, we've got a Special Forces nut job
out there gunning down uniforms.
And this phone is our sole lead.
And we don't ignore leads.
So, all we can do is
go in hard and noisy
and as ready as is
humanly possible to be.
We let Tactical do their job,
and when it's done, we buy them a drink
and tell them their biceps are sexy.
Done?
- Yeah.
- Good, let's go.
Armed police! Lay down your weapons!
Room clear! Room clear! Room clear!
Get out! Get out!
Oh, my God, get out!
Repeat,
CO19 were in the building. People lost.
Get them all ambulances,
and get them now.
C019?
Four confirmed, six injured.
Well, if there's one thing you learn
from being in Iraq,
it's how to make an IED.
- Lynch?
- Still searching.
Helicopters, ground units,
dogs, door to door.
No sign.
But it was a remote-detonated bomb.
He had to be close by, watching.
I mean that puts him within
500 metres, line of sight.
I don't get it.
How could he just slip away like that?
All right, it's not your fault.
He wanted us
to find that SIM card.
I bit down on it like a...
Mars bar. Of course it's my fault.
It's official.
As of five minutes ago,
the Owen Lynch operation
was passed up to Anti-Terrorism.
It's out of our hands.
All they're gonna do
is give Terry Lynch what he wants.
More blood. More dead coppers.
We can't let him do that.
I don't have much choice, do I?
Look, we don't have
to like it, but we do have to accept it.
We're off the case.
Suck it up, move on.
Where are you going?
Guyv.
- What's this now?
- Eppley's radio.
Right, listen, we use Airwave,
right? Secure, digital.
It's impossible for civilians
to buy a scanner and listen in.
And?
Owen swapped them.
He swapped it.
You need to call Anti-Terrorism,
and tell them he's listening
to everything we say.
Okay, I need you to understand,
Detective Chief Inspector,
that to alert them is all we can do.
We can't act on this information
because this case is no longer ours.
All right? Am I being transparent, here?
Tell me if I'm being at all ambiguous.
Because there's nothing
we can do with this, except pass it on.
There's nothing we can do
‘cause no one knows where Owen Lynch is.
And he's going to keep killing until
someone finds him and stops him.
They'll find him.
Oh, yeah? How?
So, here's what's gonna happen.
Anti-Terrorism's gonna go in
big and noisy and Owen dies.
Yeah, well, then, he dies happy,
doesn't he, doing the job he loves.
That's more than
most of us get, isn't it?
Yeah, that's gonna be
a damn sight more than you're gonna get.
What's that then, eh?
You going to bash me up, are you?
Or do you think I can't take a slap?
Oh, I'm sure you can take a slap.
I'm going to send my boy for you.
Yeah, you know, picture the
scene, doorbell rings, click, bang!
Your skull goes splat, straight out.
So, go on then, do your worst.
I'd really like to.
But murdering people leaves
a lot of fuss and bother behind.
So, I thought,
"No, there's got to be another way."
Now, I know a lot of
people in this prison.
Lot of screws, lot of inmates,
lot of nasty people, really.
But they don't bother you.
Because the thing about you, Terry, is
that you're a hard bastard, aren't you?
Mmm?
I mean, you can't be
seen giving into threats
‘cause then you wouldn't
be a hard bastard any more, would you?
And you'd rather die than lose all the
respect that you've earned in here.
I'm gonna strip you of that dignity
and make you the most
reviled prisoner in here.
Oh, I'd like to see you try.
I'm so glad you said that
because everyone
knows I searched your cell.
It would be the easiest thing in the
world to show them that this
is what we found.
- Yeah?
- Go on, have a look.
What've you been up to,
you wonky bastard, eh?
Go on.
I have to tell you,
I haven't been able to
take a look at them myself, but I am
told that none of those little boys
are more than nine years old.
It's giving you
that little thrill, isn't it?
Oh, all right.
There's Terry Lynch the hard man.
But now there's Terry Lynch the nunce.
No, no, no one would believe it.
No one, right? That's what
I thought, no one,
but then I thought to myself,
"Terry's got a boy."
A boy.
And he can get his boy
to do anything he tells him.
Hey, even kill cops.
What do you have to do
to a boy to get him to do that,
eh? To have that kind of control?
Terry, will you tell me?
What did you do to young Owen?
What did you do?
You're a piece of shit! Ain't you?
This is a onetime deal, Terry.
One time only.
So, you better give me what I want.
Have you left yet?
No, we're still here.
What, I don't believe it. Why?
John, it's illegal
to threaten someone's life.
If Alice Morgan threatened me,
why don't you just arrest her?
- I can't, okay?
- Why not?
- It's complicated.
- It always is.
What's this woman got on you?
What have you done?
Listen, I haven't got
time for this, all right.
I just need you to trust me.
Thing is, I'm not sure I do.
If I called Rose Teller,
would she know about this?
- Have you called her?
- Not yet.
Should I?
No, don't do that. Don't call her.
Well, that tells me
everything, doesn't it?
So, what's really going on?
What have you done?
Listen, I need you
to trust me, all right?
At the very least, I need you to lock
your doors, lock your windows.
And if anything happens,
you call me immediately, all right?
So, you were right.
He's lying.
I've had 20 years.
When do I learn, it's 20 years.
God, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
When does this go out?
Lead story, main bulletin,
say ten past 10:00.
- Definitely sure about this?
- Yeah.
Okay, let's go.
And we're rolling.
And as night falls on a stunned capital
as the police, ambulance
and fire crews respond
to 999 calls in full body armour...
Thank you.
Corrine Day has been
talking to Detective Chief Inspector
- fohn Luther.
- Hmm?
- Senior Investigating Officer...
- What?
0f the so-called 999 shootings.
Detective Chief
Inspector Luther,
what do we know about
Owen Lynch's motivation?
We know that Owen prides himself
on being a soldier
from a long line of soldiers,
but we've interviewed his
commanding officers, military doctors,
- psychiatrists...
- Holy shit.
Oh, no, no, no! Sergeant Ripley!
Owen had an impressive
number of kills to his name.
They were very aware
of his character flaws.
What flaws are they?
Well Owen was never soldier material.
He was a, uh, maladjusted child who was
raised on too much TV and video games.
Is any of this even true?
- Not even slightly.
- What we do know,
um, is that on his return
from Afghanistan,
Owen developed severe
sexual difficulties, and, uh, despite
his claims on a so-called mission,
it's quite likely that these murders
are a sexual release.
A way of dealing with
his sexual and personal demons.
God, what's he doing?
He's making
himself into a target,
drawing Lynch's fire from
the police force in general.
This is suicide.
And partly because his dad isn't quite
the hero he'd have us believe.
His dad is an alcoholic.
All right? A wife beater.
Who, incidentally, denies all
knowledge of his son's activities.
And how close
did you say you were to catching him?
Corinne, I've just had a long
conversation with his dad,
who has provided me with vital
information and, uh...
Owen, you'll see me soon.
Thank you,
Corinne, and now to other news.
Prime Minister...
What's that?
Mmm.
Alice Morgan.
A friend of John's.
We've met before, actually.
Leave, right now, please.
Or...
Well, go ahead.
But it won't be good for John.
Bollocks to John.
So, how can we help you?
I've been wondering,
why do you think he does it?
- Why does who do what?
- John. His job.
It takes such a toll.
Why does he put himself through it?
I don't see how this is relevant.
Well, it is. Right this second,
you might actually be helping him.
What do you think compels him to do it?
He believes one life is all we have.
Life and love.
Whoever takes life steals everything.
- And do you agree?
- I don't know.
I think if he'd read
a different book by a different writer
at just the right time in his life,
he'd have been a different man.
He'd have been happier
as a priest than...
Than what?
Than what he is.
It must have been difficult for you.
Impossible, really.
How does anyone compete
with a calling like that?
He wasn't blind.
He knew what it was costing him.
What, like his marriage?
That's part of it, yeah.
- But you don't sound bitter.
- I'm not bitter. I'm...
I'm proud of him.
You just don't
want to be married to him.
Not any more, no.
Why not?
I'm not going to answer that.
Is jt because he tried
to kill Henry Madsen?
- No.
- But that is what you believe.
Do you know what Henry Madsen did?
I have some idea, yes.
He was a freak of nature.
Anyone would be tempted.
We're not talking about anyone,
we're talking about John.
Do you think he tried to kill
him on behalf of the dead?
Well...
I think that answers the question.
It was lovely meeting you both.
Thank you for your time.
Oh, my God.
- He seriously told you nothing?
- He seriously told me nothing.
- Seriously?
- Seriously.
Shit!
Detective Chief
Inspector John Luther to Control. Over.
Boss!
Detective Chief Inspector
John Luther to Control. Over.
This is Control, DCI Luther.
What is your status? Over.
I'm en route to the
Kings Hill Estate. Over.
Please clarify. Over.
There's a flat there that belonged
to one of Terry Lynch's old pals.
Owen used to visit
it when he was a boy.
Now, I'm betting that he's been there,
maybe left something behind
that we can use to find him. Over.
Well, hang back on that. Do not proceed
unassisted to the Kings Hill Estate.
This is now a matter for Anti-Terrorism.
Do not proceed.
Repeat, do not proceed to
the Kings Hill Estate. Over.
Negative.
I'm three minutes away.
I repeat. I am three
minutes away. Over.
We cannot provide armed
backup. Do you read me?
We cannot provide armed backup. Over.
Get CO19 out there.
This is DCI Reed.
We need a first response
tactical unit to the Kings Hill Estate.
It's Owen Lynch.
We have an unarmed, unassisted
officer going in there, so do it now!
He wanted to guarantee that Owen Lynch
overheard him when he made that call.
He brought Eppley's radio to me
so I'd warn Anti-Terrorism
and they'd shut down their comms.
We cleared the airwaves for him.
He's made Owen Lynch hate him.
It's like he's waving a white flag,
stepping onto enemy territory.
As if he's going there to...
- What?
- Boss.
What?
I found John up on the roof
this morning. Right on the edge.
So?
It's just...
I'm not completely sure
he expects to walk away from this.
- C0197?
- ETA, 13 minutes.
That's not quick enough.
He's dead. The bloody idiot, he's dead.
Luther, is it?
John. Yeah.
Why are you here, John?
Because I want you to stop.
You ex-services? You look it.
A lot of coppers are.
Mike Eppley, the man you killed
the other night. He was. But me?
No, I...
I grew up around it.
Lace your hands on
top of your head, John.
- You got a death wish?
- No.
Then what?
Oh, God!
Terry... Terry gave you up, Owen.
I threatened him and he cried
and sobbed like a girl.
And he begged me not to hurt him.
And he just gave you up.
Just like that.
- You liar.
- Ah!
Oh...
You're right.
I am lying. He didn't cry
and he didn't sob.
I just said that to
make you feel better.
No, he just gave you up
because he was frightened.
Hey. Hey!
God!
Oh!
Come on. Owen.
How do you think I knew you were here?
How do you think I found you, eh?
Who else knew you were here?
You didn't... You didn't even
want to be a soldier, did you?
Eh?
You used to piss your bed,
at 11 years old, piss your bed,
and Daddy used to come
in and beat you for it.
And the more he hit you,
the more you pissed your bed.
And you were scared, weren't you?
You were scared of him,
scared of the dogs, scared of...
Shut up!
Get down now! On your face!
Get down! On your knees.
On your knees, get on your knees.
No!
- Get down!
- I told him.
I said, "You're killing your boy!"
You know what he said?
He said, "Well, at least
he dies doing something he loves.”
You recognise that as
something he's said to you before?
Eh?
You're an embarrassment to him, Owen.
He's ashamed of you.
He's ashamed of you,
he's embarrassed of you.
He asked you to do one
thing, just one thing!
And you couldn't
even do that, could you?
You couldn't do it!
He told me all your secrets.
Just so I could humiliate you.
He even told me that when
you got back from the war,
you pissed your bed even more,
and he started laughing.
That's why I'm here, Owen!
That's why I'm here.
I'm just here to tell you the
type of man that your dad is!
Don't die for him, Owen.
God! Don't die for him.
Not him, not him,
not him.
What do I do?
What do you do?
You come with me.
My dad killed one copper.
Look what happened to him.
Owen, you're not your dad.
You're not your dad.
No.
I'm not.
What are you doing?
Jesus Christ! Jesus Christ,
what are you doing?
Do you ever get the feeling
that you've been cheated?
Don't!
Ah!
All right.
Four down, eh?
Two to go.
Jesus.
Ah!
Stay down! Stay down, stay down!
You'll be all right.
Ah!
Okay, Owen,
we know that you're scared.
We know that right now
you feel like you're in enemy territory,
but that's not how it is, okay?
You're protected by the law.
We're not going to hurt you.
We need you to understand
that we're not your enemy.
We know that you're not
responsible for what you did.
Not really. I'd like to
acknowledge that here on record.
In the light of this, we are prepared
to make certain recommendations
when it comes to trial and sentencing.
Owen, as far as we're concerned,
the ultimate responsibility
for the death of these
officers lies with your dad.
It's your dad we want.
But we need your help
if we're going to do that.
If we're going to punish this man for
what he did to you, we need your help.
My name is Owen Lynch.
Sergeant, Royal Marines.
2-5-2-3-3-0-1.
Owen, we're trying to help
you here. Let us help you.
My name is Owen Lynch.
Sergeant, Royal Marines.
- 2-5-2-3-3-0-1.
- Owen.
My name is Owen Lynch.
Sergeant, Royal Marines. 2-5-2-3-3-0-1.
So, what do you have to say
that can't be said on the phone?
If you don't leave Zoe alone, Alice,
I will kill you.
You'd do that, would you?
If that's what it takes to stop you.
Is that what it took
to stop Henry Madsen?
You need to let it be.
I mean, you really do.
Don't worry, I've concluded
my investigation.
I think I got the right man.
I like her, by the way.
Zoe.
I don't know what that
means coming from your mouth.
She's strong.
She has dignity.
She loves you a great deal.
Well, she has a funny way of showing it.
- She knows what you did.
- How do you mean?
She's always known.
It didn't change anything.
It's not why she left.
You made her watch what it did
to you and never told her why.
She couldn't look at
it any more, what you...
Do to yourself.
She felt she'd lost you to the dead.
Why do you do this?
I don't understand. I'm... I'm lost.
Because we're friends.
I want to make you feel better.
We're not friends.
I don't know what we are,
but we're not friends.
Whatever else has happened,
it's in the past.
The past isn't dead, Alice.
It's not even the past.
Are you still frightened of me?
- Yes.
- Because I have no wish to hurt you
and I certainly have no wish to hurt
Zoe. I think she's admirable.
Are you saying you'll leave her alone?
I need you to leave her alone.
Brownie's honour.
One coffee doesn't make us friends.
We think it's blood.
Change the state of play.
You're a police officer.
What you're doing's wrong.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::