["IN STILLER NACHT"
BY PINK MARTINI & THE VON TRAPPS
PLAYING IN GERMAN]
WITH LOVE... THE BOYS
[♪]
[DOG BARKS DISTANTLY]
Hey.
Everything okay?
Can't sleep. Figured I'd get
a jump on work.
[SIGHS]
I was hoping
it was just me.
He never would've been here
if I had...
If I had just--
Jimmy.
The nuns back in Cicero
would send me to hell
for saying it...
but thank God he's dead.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
You want some coffee?
Sure.
[♪]
[TIMER BEEPS]
Got your six-piece bucket
right here.
WOMAN: Thank you.
Enjoy.
Welcome,
can I take your order?
Sir? I would be happy
to help you.
Good afternoon.
May I take your order?
Yeah.
I'd like a 12-piece bucket,
extra spicy.
May I suggest
our signature spice curls?
Sure.
Give me a large
on that.
[♪]
Also, two Cokes
and a side of coleslaw...
[CONTINUES
INAUDIBLY]
[FOOD TRAY CLANGS, RATTLES]
Sorry, Mr. Fring.
[♪]
We are currently in the middle
of a process called discovery.
What is discovery,
you might ask?
It's one of the most important
parts of any case,
because it's when both parties
are able to discover,
if you will,
information that is relevant
to the claims at issue.
Now this brings us to
another key term, "relevance."
If a document or a piece
of evidence is relevant,
that means it has a tendency
to prove or disprove
an element in the case.
This whole thing
is just taking so darn long.
Unfortunately, high-stakes
class actions like these
often move
on a protracted timeline.
WOMAN:
Well, okay.
But some of us don't have
"a protracted timeline,"
if you know what I mean.
My son thinks
I should get my own lawyer.
You have every right
to pursue
independent
legal representation.
Having said that--
Absolutely.
Great to see the next generation
stepping up, isn't it?
Thank you, Ms. Brill.
Hi, everyone.
I'm so glad to be
with you today.
For those of you
who don't know me yet,
I'm your lead attorney,
Howard Hamlin.
Just call me Howard.
And this is my co-counsel,
Cliff Main.
Listen.
I know you all wanna get
to the finish line.
Boy, I sure do.
But I'm gonna level with you.
Truth is, we still have
a ways to go.
Why?
Because we want
the maximum from Sandpiper.
We're pushing to get
an extra 30 percent
on top of the penalty.
Not because we're greedy, no.
Because it's what you deserve.
Now, to get your due,
it may take
a little extra time.
Is it worth it?
I think it is.
Because this isn't just
about money.
It's about people.
It's about you. Sally, right?
[CHUCKLES]
Right. Sally.
And you, sir.
We're sending a message.
We're not gonna let
big corporations
pick the pockets
of hardworking folks.
I wanna live in a world
where people
can trust each other.
And I bet you do too.
CLIFF: Thanks again, both of
you.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming.
Oh, I feel better.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Okay.
Bye now. You take care.
Thank you.
Well, I think we just
put out a major fire.
That was impressive.
Erin, I'll see you
back at the office.
Okay.
Bye, Howard.
Howard, I need a minute.
What's up?
I threw a woman
out of my car,
in the middle of the street?
And I zip,
I just drive right past.
That's what you're saying?
I don't even--
I don't know
how to respond to that.
I'm not asking you to respond.
I just need you to know
that I know.
It wasn't me, Cliff.
Whoever you think--
Yeah, that's the kind of thing
my son used to say.
It was your Jaguar,
your "Namaste" plate.
It was you.
Howard, there's no harm
in asking for help.
You got a lot of people
in your corner.
So there's the baggie
at the country club.
Yes.
After that,
some clients, who you can't name
because of privilege,
make insinuations.
Then on Thursday,
you have a business meeting,
and you witness
a Jaguar speeding past.
Who were you meeting with?
Not sure why that's germane,
but Kim Wexler.
She came to me
for career advice.
All right.
Okay.
Of course.
Cliff, I know
this wasn't easy for you.
You came to me as a friend.
I appreciate it.
You can start today, Howard.
Oh, I will.
Because you're right,
I do have a problem.
Just not
the problem you think.
I have
a Jimmy McGill problem.
Jimmy McGill? Howard!
Excuse me.
Julie.
[JAGUAR CHIRPS]
Cancel my week.
Yes. My whole week.
Howard!
[CAR MOTOR STARTING]
[POP SONG PLAYING INDISTINCTLY
ON CAR RADIO]
[RADIO SHUTS OFF]
[CAR REVS, TIRES SCREECH]
[SCOFFS]
Whoa, hold up.
Justice will be served
in four and a half minutes,
9 a.m. sharp.
I look forward
to sitting down
with each and every
one of you.
Morning rush.
So, that's your station.
Temporarily. Of course.
But check it out:
center stage.
What?
That? It's garbagio,
on its way
to the dumpster, heh.
I know that this place
needs a little TLC.
But this is just day one.
Two weeks from now,
you won't recognize it.
Where's Ms. Wexler?
You mean, my wife?
That's right.
Made an honest woman out of her.
She's blazing her own trail
and I couldn't be prouder.
So it's just...?
Me. Just me. For now.
But think of it this way:
half the work.
[SIGHS]
What happened to
the old folks? Elder law?
Uh, I expanded the mission, uh,
to be more inclusive.
Here at Saul Goodman
and Associates,
we welcome all ages,
all creeds, all stripes.
And who is
this Saul Goodman?
You?
You got it!
What Colonel Sanders is
to chicken,
Saul Goodman is to the law.
Why me?
Because I trust you.
And...
what happened last time,
I-I wanna make it up to you.
I will explain at the end
of the day. Please...
You're--
You're just desperate
and need a warm body.
Good luck.
Where are you going?
Back to the MVD.
I took half a personal day
for this.
What if I double your salary?
My salary at the MVD
or what you were paying me
before?
Whatever's less.
[SCOFFS]
No, whatever's more!
"More" is the word
I'm looking for.
Did I mention...
[EXHALES]
...the signing bonus?
I get a say
in the decorating.
Open for business!
One at a time. Thank you.
I'll be right out.
Viola, hey, over here.
Thanks for meeting me.
VIOLA: Of course.
I wanted to apologize.
Leaving Schweikart, I'm sure
it looked sudden, but...
Sorry I left you in the lurch.
You probably had
to clean up Mesa Verde,
everything
that happened there.
Kevin.
Anyway, I'm sure
it's a lot.
Actually, Mesa Verde
calmed down.
Rich moved me over
to Sandpiper.
Mm. Right.
I think I heard that.
How's it going?
It's pretty interesting
so far.
It's a deep dive
into class action.
We have our first
mediation session
in a couple of weeks.
Oh, already.
Who'd you get?
Hope it's not
Roger Patch.
Oh, God. Patch?
With the vegan patties?
What is in
those things?
It's gotta be
80 percent garlic.
So healthy!
[BOTH LAUGH]
No, it's not--
It's a new guy.
A retired judge,
who lives up in Santa Fe.
Casimiro.
He seems fine. Smells fine.
[CHUCKLES]
Well, then,
you dodged a bullet.
I'm glad you called.
I've been wanting to tell you.
Everyone was so shocked
when you walked away.
I mean...
you were a partner.
I'm sure it seemed very...
weird.
It did at first.
But I get it now.
What you're doing
to help the little guy...
it's incredible.
I'm just getting started.
I really admire you, Kim.
Changing direction
like that.
Sometimes I question
all of it, but...
You make me feel better
about the law.
[CHUCKLES]
JIMMY:
Hit and run, 15 minutes.
Shoplifting?
I can knock that out in 10.
Yeah, 10.
Hey...
This ain't fine dining,
okay?
Our business model
is turning tables.
So Francesca, I'm here.
Remind me again
why I'm making a house call?
Sounds like money.
Okay. Great.
Great work.
[BLUETOOTH BEEPS OFF]
Mr. Ward?
Hi.
[CLEARS THROAT]
I'm an attorney.
I have an appointment
with Mr. Ward.
So, are you Mr. Ward--?
Okay.
Well, good evening to you,
whatever your name is...
[SCOFFS]
Hello, Jimmy.
Mr. Ward, I presume.
As in...
H.O. Ward.
That is really cute,
Howard.
So, wait, that means...
you're the guy
who "shanked some dude
in a rumble
near Central Penn"?
That's very street of you.
I thought it sounded like
a Saul Goodman
kind of case.
All right, so,
what are we doing here?
I'm tired, Jimmy.
You and me. Us.
I'm tired of this.
Aren't you? It's exhausting.
Let's punch
it out.
Are you kidding?
Dead serious.
Hoping you get it
out of your system.
Do I think it will work?
I don't know.
Call it a Hail Mary.
I have the gear.
I rented the ring.
It's just you and me.
And Macky, to ref.
I'm sorry,
but have you lost your mind?
Actually, I'm as clearheaded
as I've ever been in my life.
You didn't even try
to hide your tracks.
The baggie of drugs
at the country club.
The clients you sent
to discredit me.
Another prostitute--
Okay, once again, as usual--
Please.
I could go on.
All roads
lead back to you.
It's Psych 101.
You want to get caught.
So what?
Is this--? It's, like,
pistols at dawn?
I'm trying to give you
what you want.
What I want? I don't...
I think
this is what you want.
You wanna beat
the shit out of me? Legally?
I think you can hold up
your end.
You must have gotten into
a few good scrapes
in the old neighborhood.
Yeah, right,
I could've been
a contender.
Indulge me.
Let's see what we see.
[CHUCKLES]
Thanks for the laughs...
Mr. Ward.
[CHUCKLES]
[♪]
Come on. Come on,
let's go. Come on.
I need you
to keep your mitts up,
protect your face.
Tap gloves.
Come on.
Okay,
go ahead.
Come on, Howard.
Come on.
Yeah! I'm the champ!
Hey, look at me!
Come on.
Here we go. Here we go.
Hit me.
Hey, take a shot.
Come on, take a swing.
Oh!
[GRUNTS]
All right, all right,
all right.
[GRUNTING]
[CHUCKLES]
[GROANS]
Here we go.
[GRUNTING]
Okay. Okay.
You've mistaken my kindness
for weakness.
I'd like to think that tonight
made a difference.
I'd like to think
that this ends it.
Probably not.
[GROANING]
How'd it go?
Pretty much
as expected.
So we're on?
Yes.
Anything in particular
you want me to look for?
No.
I need to know
everything he does
and everyone he talks to.
You got it.
Okay, then.
I'll see you Friday.
[CAR MOTOR STARTS]
[CAR APPROACHING]
What are you doing?
Put the ice pack on it.
I gotta see if this
will work. I mean...
I got court first thing
in the morning.
I can't show up
looking like Leon Spinks.
Why not?
I'd say you'd be
missing a bet.
"I'm Saul Goodman. Pow.
I fight for you."
[JIMMY CHUCKLES]
How'd it go with Viola?
I got a name.
Rand Casimiro, retired judge.
Wow, you wormed it
out of her. Nice work.
I don't know him,
but I found a picture
in the Bar Journal.
Ahh. Love the 'stache.
That's a lot less face
to worry about.
Unless he shaves.
JIMMY:
Are you kidding?
Those handlebars?
No, that's years of grooming.
KIM: True.
"I'll fight for you," huh?
Yeah.
I should have left Howard
standing there like a yutz.
Instead, I let him
suck me into his game.
Why'd I do that?
You had your reasons.
I did?
Like what?
Because you know.
I know.
[SIGHS]
You know what's coming next.
[POP MUSIC PLAYING
INDISTINCTLY FROM CAR]
♪ I'm not the only one
That holds you ♪
♪ I never ever
Should have told you ♪
♪ You're my only... ♪
[SONG CONTINUES, INDISTINCTLY]
[SONG ENDS]
[GRUNTS]
Hey, Mike.
Hey.
You good?
Yep. All quiet.
You guys get dinner?
Yeah. We ate.
"Bike at 5:40"?
Just a kid
dropping off menus.
It was legit.
MIKE:
He asleep?
All right.
Hey.
[BRUSH SCRUBBING]
MIKE:
Part of the reason
we set it up this way
is so you can get
some rest.
No news yet, I take it.
It's a waiting game.
Wherever he is now,
sooner or later,
he's gonna end up
right here.
He can't strike. Not yet.
So.
Tell your men
that we are going out.
The other end of the tunnel
is plugged
with 420 cubic yards of dirt.
Topped with a cement pad,
no one's coming in that way.
I could put more guys
on the place
if that's what
you're thinking.
I'll be upstairs.
[♪]
[LOW ELECTRICAL HUMMING]
[CLICKS]
[SIGHS]
MAN 1 [READING, IN GERMAN]:
"Who scored the winning goal
for Germany
in the 1990 World Cup Final?"
[GAME CHIMING]
WOMAN [IN GERMAN]:
Yes, awesome!
Cool!
"Who was the first
female astronaut?"
Sally Ride,
yes?
Is that right?
Yes, of course.
Valentina Tereshkova.
Sally Ride.
[GAME CHIMES]
Dammit.
BARTENDER [IN GERMAN]:
What can I get you?
MAN 2 [IN GERMAN]:
Martini, please.
BARTENDER:
Vodka or gin?
MAN 2 [IN ENGLISH]:
Give me whatever you like.
BARTENDER [IN ENGLISH]:
You're American?
I guess you could spot us
a mile away.
Yeah, I'm here on business.
BARTENDER: From California?
No. New Mexico.
It's another state.
I mean, it's like California,
just less traffic, you know?
Thank you.
A little town called Jemez.
Jemez?
I almost visited there once.
Almost?
Hm. This close.
Well, I'm sorry
you didn't make it.
It's a beautiful place.
The hot springs.
Yes. That's what I was wanting,
you know, the, uh...
Hm...
[SIGHS]
How do you say?
[SPEAKS IN GERMAN]
The minerals?
Oh, it's similar. Yes.
So relaxing for the muscles.
Well, maybe you'll get
to go there another time.
I don't think so.
But it's a nice idea.
Maybe a trip to Karlovy Vary.
The baths there are wonderful.
To...
Karlovy Vary.
Vary.
[CHUCKLES]
Not far from Prague.
Oh, Prague. Yes. There.
I always wanted
to go visit there.
I'm Ben.
Ben.
Hello.
I'm Margarethe.
Oh, it's very nice
to meet you, Margarethe.
I knew
his work was dangerous,
but I never imagined
such a thing.
Well,
I suppose I tried not to.
That is terrible.
What kind of accident was it?
A cave-in.
A cave-in?
He was able
to save his men,
he got them out,
but then,
the structure collapsed.
So your husband
was a hero.
[CHUCKLES]
He would never accept that.
My Werner was too humble.
What were they building there?
My husband didn't talk
much about his work.
It was very secretive.
Well, surely he must
have told you something.
The lawyers
came to my house,
I asked questions,
they wouldn't say much.
Lawyers.
They went through
Werner's things,
took anything
that they called...
Oh, how do you say it?
Proprietary? I'm sorry,
my English is--
Oh, it's excellent.
[CHUCKLES]
I didn't care about it.
All the boxes of folders,
his papers.
Why do I need
all that stuff?
What about your husband's men?
I mean, they must have said
something to you.
Werner loved seine Jungs,
his boys.
But I never even met them.
What do you mean?
Not even at the funeral?
You'd think they'd want
to pay respect
to the man who saved
their lives.
They sent flowers,
keepsakes, and so on,
but not one of them
showed his face.
Well, that is...
[SIGHS]
It's just not right.
Mm-hm.
Let's speak of something else.
Tell me about New Mexico.
[CHUCKLES]
You would love it.
BEN:
So how do you say it?
[MARGARETHE GIGGLES,
THEN SPEAKS IN GERMAN]
[BEN REPEATS AFTER MARGARETHE]
MARGARETHE: Not bad. Not bad.
BEN: Yeah?
People don't live
in them anymore,
but for centuries, they...
Here we are.
My little cave.
It's nice.
So quiet.
[MARGARETHE GIGGLES]
Ah, yes. All quiet.
[BARCHEN BARKING]
Except for Barchen. Heh.
Oh. Heh, heh.
It means, "Little Bear".
I'd like to invite you in.
But I have work in the morning.
Of course.
No, that's not...
When do you fly home?
Tomorrow.
Well, in another life.
In another life, yes.
Good night.
[♪]
[BARCHEN BARKING]
[LOCK CLICKING]
[IN SPANISH]
Good morning, Little Bear.
You're the man of the house,
aren't you?
Yes. It's all right.
Be quiet. Be quiet.
Shh, shh.
[BARCHEN BARKING]
[IN GERMAN]
Quiet, sweetie.
Why are you so worried?
I forgot my phone,
that's all.
What's the matter with you?
Oh, please!
Come on, I gotta go.
Come now!
Little Bear!
What's the matter with you?
What do you want?
What do you want? Hmm?
I gotta go. Come now.
You stay here, okay?
You stay here. Little Bear!
Stay here!
[♪]