(APM'S HARVEST SANDALWOOD PLAYS)
♪
Oh, come on, you...
Can I gave you a hand?
If I needed a hand,
I'd ask for it,
thank you very much.
There you go, miss. Thanks.
Marion.
How's it going?
Eh. Could be worse.
Brain's still working.
(CHUCKLES) Is it a pastrami day?
Yeah. Uh, one
and a quarter pounds.
You got it.
Not a pound and a half,
you overshot last time.
Oh. Sorry 'bout that.
What do we have here?
Extra-sharp Wisconsin cheddar.
"Extra-sharp," hmm?
Ohh. (SPITS)
You can keep it,
Wisconsin. Ugh.
(SCOOTER WHIRRING)
(WHIRRING CONTINUES)
(ENGINE REVVING)
It wasn't like this
when I came before.
(GRUNTS)
GENE: Need some help?
I'm fine!
Are you sure you
don't want a push?
I'm sure.
(DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE)
What happened to poor Nippy?
Ah. It was my fault.
(SIGHS)
I was driving with
the windows open,
you know, before all this hit.
And, I don't know,
something got into him.
He saw a cat or
something, but he jumped.
Oh, no.
I pulled right over, screaming
my head off, "Nippy!"
Ohh. But he was gone.
Oh, that's terrible.
I hope you find him.
If you could keep an eye out.
Yeah, I will. Sure.
I-I live right over here
on... On Clementine.
This is my route.
When I can get this thing going.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
Maybe just a little push.
♪
Well, if you're sure
you don't mind.
Nah. I'm happy to help.
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
(GENE GRUNTS)
Okay. Throw it in neutral.
(CHUCKLES) And one, two, three.
(GRUNTING)
There you go.
Oh, sorry for the trouble.
Put it back in
drive. Not at all.
Have a nice day. Yeah, you too.
Hope you find Nippy.
Thank you.
♪
Ohh. What in the world?
How ya doing, Marion?
Great. Ah, good.
Are you okay? Oh, yeah.
(OPENING THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
(CLICKING)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(BRAKES SQUEAK)
(ENGINE SHUTS OFF)
(CHILDREN TALKING
INDISTINCTLY IN DISTANCE)
(TAPS FEET)
GENE: Okay, okay, okay.
MARION: Actually, it's
my favorite meal to cook.
Hmm. I like it. And I
think my secret is...
Ma?
MARION: In the kitchen, Jeffie!
I have a little trick.
GENE: I bet it's the
same we do in my family.
An egg. I knew it.
MARION: (CHUCKLES)
And you really work it in.
I mean, you got
to use your hands.
GENE: You are
speaking my language.
MARION: Do you cook?
Uh, just a few
favorites, nothing fancy.
Yeah, simple's best.
I mean, why fuss?
Oh. Jeffie, this is Mr. Takavic.
GENE: Oh, please,
Mr. Takavic was my father.
Call me Gene.
MARION: Don't worry,
hon, he's not an ax murderer.
If he was gonna chop me to bits
he'd have done it already.
Right, Gene?
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
(SCOFFS)
Well, don't just stand there
like a bump on a log, join us.
Sometimes he gets a little
nervous around new people.
Ma... Well, you do.
Now come on.
Grab a glass and sit down.
(JEFF SIGHS, CLEARS THROAT)
Tell him how we met, Gene.
Oh, yeah.
Uh, well, I was
looking for Nippy...
Yeah. His dog, poor thing.
Well, he ran away.
MARION: And Gene here
was putting up posters.
GENE: And your mom was
on her way back from Hansen's.
And my wheels got
stuck in the snow.
Well, that was before the
whole thing conked out.
Yeah, but Gene
here saved the day.
He even fixed my dumb scooter...
With duct tape!
(CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS) Ah.
To Gene. Come on.
Yeah. Ahh...
(MARION CHUCKLES)
Mm.
So your mom tells me
you're a cab driver?
Have you ever driven
anyone famous?
Oh, he sure did.
Tell him, Jeffie.
Sammy Hagar.
No! The Red Rocker?
Hey, I love him. Hey...
♪ I can't drive 55 ♪
That's it! Hey!
(BOTH LAUGH)
What was he like? Big tipper?
I guess. (EGG TIMER DINGS)
Mm. Oh. You know
what? You stay comfy.
I will rescue this
beautiful creation.
Look at that.
(SINGSONG VOICE) Ta-da!
Gene's staying for dinner.
♪
- Original SUB by oakislandtk - www.opensubtitles.org -
Colored HI and improvements by GoldBerg_44
JEFF: Dude, what the fuck?
(NORMAL VOICE) I
know it's awkward, right?
But you don't have
to call me "Dad." Yet.
I don't know what this is about,
but all I have to do
is pick up the phone
and it's bye-bye, Saul Goodman.
Yeah, but you haven't picked
up the phone yet, have you?
Or tried to strong-arm
me for cash.
And guess what? I know why.
Because reward money, blackmail,
that's not gonna
tickle your pickle.
I know what you really want.
Oh, yeah? What's that?
You want in the game.
"The game"? W-What...
What game?
The game.
The one you've been
watching your entire life.
You got your nose
pressed up against the glass,
peerin' in while
the big boys play.
Man, speak English.
What the hell are
you talking about?
The game.
It's right there.
You can see it, but
you can't touch it.
The cars, the clothes, the cash.
The ladies.
It's about knowing
all the angles,
you know, putting
it all on the line
and winning big.
But here you are, Jeffie.
Standing outside
with the suckers.
Tryin' to pay off that
cab, sweatin' the bills,
gettin' older.
It's so close,
but, damn it, you
just can't get in.
Until now.
I can make it happen.
♪
You?
Saul Goodman.
So, here's the deal.
I will show you the game.
And then we're done.
(LOCK CLICKS)
(SIGHS)
MAN: two days.
Caller thinks
it's brother-in-law
with history of violence.
WOMAN: 10-4.
(INDISTINCT TALKING
ON POLICE SCANNER)
MAN 2: Noise
complaint. 50 or so teens.
Parents possibly out of town.
Neighbors say this
is not the first time.
MAN 3: 10-20?
37882 Crestview.
♪
WOMAN 2: Headed that way.
WOMAN 3: Missing
juvenile. Caucasian male.
6'2", 240 pounds.
Last seen at gas station
on Kerrywood and Western.
(SIGHS)
(INDISTINCT TALKING
ON POLICE SCANNER)
MAN 4: Parents called?
WOMAN 4: Got ahold of
Mom. ETA is 20 minutes.
WOMAN 5: 10-23.
(ELECTRICITY BUZZING, SHUTS OFF)
G'night, ladies.
See ya, Gene. Bye.
Yeah.
(SWEEPER WHIRRING)
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
(SIGHS)
(EXHALES SLOWLY)
There a problem?
No, I... I just came
to say thanks. Um...
I'm Gene. From Cinnabon.
Uh, you called the EMTs for me
when I... fainted.
Yeah. I remember you.
"Get a lawyer!"
FRANK: Nick! Do I
detect Cinnabons?
Yeah!
Well, Christ almighty,
get him in here.
I'm sorry about
the lawyer thing.
Just slipped out.
It's a free country.
(GENE SIGHS)
Hi. Uh, Gene Takavic.
Uh... (CHUCKLES)
Hey, Gene. I'm
Frank. This is Nick.
Yeah. Nick here,
um, did me a solid,
so, uh...
Well...
(CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS)
Please, enjoy
yourselves. (CHUCKLES)
Well, God bless ya. (CHUCKLES)
Well, 9:45.
Nick, you wanna grab
yours to-go? Sure. Yeah.
He's gotta check the lot.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Uh...
You want to take a load off?
Grab yourself a cup
of coffee if you'd like.
Yeah. Yeah?
Oh. Okay. (CHUCKLES)
Ohh.
I should not be doing this.
(SIGHS)
(COFFEE POURING)
(SIGHS) Hey, do me a favor,
if you were ever to cross
paths with my wife, shh.
Oh. (BOTH CHUCKLE)
Scout's honor.
Ahh. Oh, man.
I haven't had one
of these in forever.
Watching my waistline.
Yeah, but every now
and then... No harm, right?
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, wow. (CLEARS THROAT)
Mmm.
Mmm. Mm-mm-mmm-mmm-mmm.
So, did you catch
the game last night?
The game?
What the hell is
wrong with those guys?
I can't even talk about it.
Mm.
Really thought
this was the year.
Yeah, me too.
Mm.
You know, Texas
wasn't even ranked.
I know.
Play-calling was crazy.
The worst.
Three downs to
make a foot and a half?
How hard can it be?
Well, you can't win when
Martinez plays like that.
Martinez.
I mean, what's up with him?
You think something's off?
Maybe.
Mm.
Next week, Oklahoma State.
The Okies. Huh?
Uh, that's what we called them.
You ever done the drive?
Topeka, Wichita... Nice.
(CHUCKLES) Well,
then you haven't done it.
(CHUCKLES) Can't beat Memorial.
Damn straight. What
do you love most?
Now, that's a tough one.
FRANK: You think Weedon'll
come through on his home turf?
Yeah. No way!
With that thumb?
Thumb's a dealbreaker.
I'll tell you something.
The Cougar helmet
was the thumb-breaker.
(BOTH LAUGH)
Mmm. Mm-mm-mmm.
Delicious.
Mmm!
Welp...
I should probably
be heading back.
Well, thanks again.
Oh, it's the least I could do.
Have a good one.
Come back anytime.
(SIGHS)
(LALO SCHIFRIN'S JIM
ON THE MOVE PLAYS)
♪
Have a good night,
Gene. Good night, Krista.
Good night. Good night.
♪
Frank?
Gene, Gene, the
Cinnabon machine.
(CHUCKLES) I could smell
ya coming up the hallway.
Oh, I get that all the time.
Here you go, guys.
Hey, can I...
Thanks, Gene. Don't
even ask. Grab a coffee.
FRANK: That was one
hell of a game, huh?
What were you
thinking at halftime?
Well, uh, I was thinking,
"Hey, this could, uh...
"This could be a long
one." (CHUCKLES)
And I tell you, you know who
I'm not bitching about today?
Pelini. Nah. Pelini.
That's... Yeah, the coach.
You know me. I go at
him when things are bad,
but when he does something
good, I'm all about it.
♪
Good night, Gene. Good night!
(FRANK CHUCKLES)
They got him in
there for a reason.
Mm-mmm-mmm. Mmm.
(INAUDIBLE CONVERSATION)
♪
(DOOR BUZZES)
(CHUCKLES)
GENE: Gentlemen!
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(LAUGHS)
I still got it.
Mm-mm-mm-mmm-mmm.
(GENE SIGHING)
Can I help you, sir?
Oh, yeah.
Uh, no thanks.
I'm just browsing.
Okay. Yeah.
Four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine...
fourteen...
fifteen, 17, 18.
Six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
(INHALES SHARPLY)
(SIGHS)
Two...
Eleven, 12, 13, 14, 15.
All right. And...
Seventeen feet.
Right here.
(WHISTLES)
Ribbon it off.
Come on.
All the way, guys.
Okay.
(OVER MEGAPHONE) Check,
check, one, two. One, two.
All right, let's move.
Starting position.
Right down there.
All right, we ready?
And grab your bag!
And go!
That's it! Move! Move!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
One! Armani suits and run!
Two! Air Jordan shoes for you!
Three! Linen shirts for free!
Four! Cashmere
sweaters out the door!
Five! Patagonias to survive!
Six! Swanky
sweatsuits in the mix!
Halt! Ohh. What?
Too many.
You gotta be precise.
Just three of each. Why?
And why do I gotta run
around like an asshole?
I already told you.
Three minutes.
Got it? That's our window.
Yeah, but why three minutes?
Because at three minutes,
that's when security
sees you on the cameras
and the cops haul
your ass to jail, all right?
So let's go. Wait,
there's cameras?
Sure, there's cameras!
They erase the
tapes every 72 hours.
So that's why you only
take three of each.
And only the pricey stuff.
When the store opens
the next morning,
they won't even know
they were robbed.
By the time they do
inventory, abracadabra!
No more Jeffie
on the tape, right?
So, three items, three minutes.
It's easy.
Let's go.
How many of each?
Three.
Pigs get fat, hogs
get slaughtered.
I dunno...
What don't you know?
It's just, this whole
thing... It seems crazy.
Is this too hot for you?
You know, just say so.
You know what? Screw it.
"Crazy"?
I'll tell you what's crazy.
Fifty-year-old high
school chemistry teacher
comes into my office.
The guy is so broke, he
can't pay his own mortgage.
One year later, he's got a pile
of cash as big as a Volkswagen.
That's crazy.
I'll do it.
This sounds good to you?
I think it'll work.
Well, look at you.
You're young.
You're probably, uh,
fast on the feet, huh?
Okay, I-I didn't
say I wouldn't do it.
I just had some questions
about, like, logistics.
Are you in or out?
In.
(SIGHS) Okay.
Back to one.
Check, test, one, two, one, two.
Okay, and ready, set, action!
Move! Move! Move!
Pick up the pace! Go! Go! Go!
One! Armani suits and run!
Two! Air Jordan shoes for you!
Three! Linen shirts for free!
Four! Cashmere
sweaters out the door!
Five! Patagonias to survive!
Six! Swanky
sweatsuits in the mix!
Barbara?
Yes?
Let's ask maintenance
to give this area a polish.
Got it, I'll call now.
Thanks.
Okay, then. Have a good night.
You too.
Excuse me, ma'am?
There's a delivery.
A delivery?
No.
No, no.
Stop.
You are not leaving that
thing on my loading dock.
No way.
Fourteen twelve
Cottonwood Drive...
Dock... Dock D.
Let me see.
Two-stroke engine sprayer pumps?
This is a department store.
Does it look like we
use sprayer pumps here?
Well, we don't.
I was given this address, ma'am.
I need to talk to
your supervisor.
Got it. You stay right here.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
(CELL PHONE
BEEPS) Dispatch. Steve.
Yes, this is Kathy Deutsch,
I'm the manager of a
Lancaster's in Omaha.
And you guys just delivered
something that we did not order.
Really?
Your guy brought a giant
wooden crate onto my loading dock,
seems to be some
kind of spraying system.
The invoice number
is 1-9-6-8-AE35.
Okay, just, uh, give me a
second to catch up here.
Uh... Uh, sprayer pump.
Yeah, I think I got
it. Omaha, right?
Yes, but I run a
department store.
We don't sell
anything like that.
Clearly this is a
mistake you need to fix.
Oh, my God. I'm so sorry, ma'am.
My boss is gonna just...
Ah, great.
Ricky's booked solid. (CHUCKLES)
Ricky?
He's the driver.
Well, Ricky's just gonna have
to put the box back on the truck.
Uh, little problem with that.
Cargo space.
He's got a pickup at
the airport in an hour.
It's a messy one, too.
It's, uh, nine hundred
pounds of Spanish mackerel.
Okay. I'm sorry, but
that's not my problem.
No, I know. It's just... Wow.
I mean, if he's late,
that's gonna stink.
Pun intended. (CHUCKLES)
Gene? Everything okay?
Yep. Oh, I'm just,
uh, putting out fires.
It's a delivery issue.
Don't worry. Okay.
I got it.
Sorry.
You still there?
KATHY: Yes.
Look, I don't know what to
tell you about your fish issue,
it's just I can't have
a huge box just...
I-I understand. It's just... I
mean, we both have people
we have to answer to, right?
Hey, I've got an idea.
Um, I've got an extra truck.
I could drive over there myself.
Great. How long
till you get here?
Well, I'm just
over in Urbandale.
Um, so, if I leave right
now, be there in four hours.
Four hours? No.
No, no, it's fine. I
don't mind the drive.
I'll crank the tunes,
it'll be like old times.
I mean, no, I can't
wait around that long.
We're closing
for the night here.
Oh. Whew.
(SIGHS)
How's this?
Yeah?
If you promise me that...
Ricky will get back here
by 10:00 a.m. tomorrow...
I'll hold the box overnight.
You would do that?
Oh, my God. You're a lifesaver.
What's your name again?
Kathy. Kathy.
Yeah, my guy'll be there,
10:00 a.m. on the dot.
With flowers.
Well, f-flowers
won't be necessary,
but thanks for the thought.
No, thank you.
(SIGHS)
G'night, ladies.
KRISTA: 'Night.
PAULA: Good night, Gene.
(DOOR BUZZES)
Gentlemen. Hey, Gene.
Heya, Gene.
Well, better hit it.
Good luck to Lizzie
on that spelling bee.
She's a little nervous.
Nah, she's gonna be great.
FRANK: Yeah. Hey,
Huskers are back.
(CHUCKLING) Ohh. Probably heard
me screaming all the way in Lincoln.
I was hoarse.
Uh, and Martinez... Ahh.
484 yards? That's a
freshman record! Wow.
You know what? I love that kid.
Hey, if he and
Kinnie keep it up,
I think they still got a shot.
Ohh. Your lips to God's ears.
(CHUCKLES)
Ahh. Okay.
Wow. Mmm.
Mm-mm-mmm.
Hm-hmm.
Hello, gorgeous.
(CHUCKLES)
Mmm.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATES)
(JEFF SIGHS)
One, Armani suits and run.
Armani, Armani, Armani.
Armani.
Armani?
Two, Air Jordan shoes for you.
All right.
Three, linen shirts for free.
One, two, three.
Four, cashmere
sweaters out the door.
No. Yes, yes, yes.
One, two, three.
Five, Patagonias to survive.
FRANK: 6,000 more seats.
GENE: 6,000 more fans.
FRANK: I don't know.
All those luxury suites?
Start saving now.
FRANK: Hm.
Mm, you see that
interview with Pelini?
The guy's feeling his oats.
He can taste it now.
You think he'll ever get
outta Osborne's shadow?
Mm. Osborne... What a career.
GENE: Wow.
I mean, a hall of famer
and a congressman?
FRANK: Mm. Unbelievable.
Seven, spendy dresses
sent from heaven.
Mm-mm-mmm.
'95 team?
Wow. What a line up.
I mean, the "I formation."
FRANK: Well, I'll tell ya, Pelini could
have taken a page outta that book.
Nine, pricey lingerie is mine.
Ten, calfskin
briefcases for men.
GENE: Apples and
oranges, my friend.
Aw. Oh, come on.
Osborne had the great Tommie
Frazier. Frazier. Yeah, sure, sure.
GENE: Huh? Say it
with me. (CHUCKLES)
JEFF: Twelve, luxury
pumps to un-shelve.
GENE: How about that
44-21 win against the Buffs?
Ahh. Be still my heart.
(CHUCKLES)
Mmm. Seventy-six-yard
pass to Reggie Baul and...
And never sacked once.
Wow. You have
got quite a memory.
Yeah, well, uh,
I'll tell you what.
I can remember
every stitch of clothing
I was wearing during that game,
but ask me what I
had for dinner last night
and (WHISTLES) clean slate.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah.
Tell me about it.
(CHUCKLES)
Mm.
Well, I tell ya, if you're
not passing the ball,
that's what's gonna happen.
Mmm.
Eighteen, Kate Spade's queen.
Nineteen, Calvin
leathers on the scene.
Twenty, Uggs look funny.
FRANK: Sure looks pretty,
Huskers red against that green.
It's like Christmas out there.
Ahh! Ugh!
(COUGHING)
You okay?
Mm-hmm. Wrong pipe.
Oh. Oh, okay.
Mmm. Ohh.
So, you think our
guys are gonna move
to the Big Ten
like they're saying?
Big Ten?
Yeah. I mean,
they're just chasing
the, you know, mighty
dollar, if you ask me.
I mean, both powerhouses,
'course. (CHUCKLES)
But, you know,
you got Oklahoma
and Texas over here.
But Michigan, Ohio
State over there.
(SIGHS) I-I don't know.
Guess I like tradition.
(CHUCKLES)
Mmm. Mm-mm-mm-mm-mmm-mmm!
So good.
That center. Mm.
Just amazing.
Mm-mm-mmm.
Wow. Mmm.
(CRYING) Oh, God.
What am I doing?
What?
(CRYING) Look
at me! I don't know.
I-I don't know.
Oh, Jesus.
Gene?
(CRYING)
Oh, God. You...
You have a wife, right, Frank?
Well, yeah. Yeah?
Yeah.
And she's waiting for you.
Look at me.
I got...
I got no one.
My parents are dead.
Oh.
My brother...
My brother is dead.
I, uh...
I got no wife...
No kids.
No friends.
If I died tonight,
no one would care.
What difference would it make?
Gene, buddy...
No, I-I-I'm sure
that you mean a lot to,
you know, to a lot of...
Lots of people.
(GENE SMACKS
TABLE) If I died tonight...
My landlord would
pack up my stuff.
It'd take him three hours.
And Cinnabon would
just hire a new manager.
Gene who?
Poof!
I'd be gone. I'd be...
A...
A ghost.
Less than a ghost. I'd be a...
A sha... Shadow.
I'd just be...
Nothing.
I mean, Frank...
What's the point, Frank?
What's the poi...
(GROANING)
Ah. (CHUCKLES)
Oh, you... I'm so sorry.
You didn't need
to hear any of that.
No, no, no, no, no,
that's... That's okay.
No, that... That is okay.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Everybody has bad days.
You've felt like this?
No, I mean, not me, but people.
I-I think a lot of people.
Yeah, I mean, i-it's just like
life's ups and life's downs.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah.
Hey, you're not gonna
tell Nick, are you?
Oh. (SCOFFS)
No, 'course not.
Well, thanks so
much for listening.
Yeah, no, no. No
p... No problem.
♪
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
CUSTOMER: I don't know.
I'm thinking maybe
blue or black?
What's the occasion?
My sister's wedding.
Oh, very exciting.
Um, what size are you?
Usually a 38 or a 40?
Do you want to try both?
Yeah. Let's do it.
♪
Sir, do you need help?
I'm good.
Well, Barbara's right
here if you need anything.
Mm-hmm.
Kathy, is this it? Yes.
Excuse me, ma'am?
Truck's here to
pick up that big box.
Great, thank you.
Uh, the guy brought flowers.
Really?
♪
(LAUGHTER)
Look. Ooh la la! Ooh la la!
(LAUGHS)
Oh. Check this out.
Buongiorno, ladies!
How much you think
we can get for 'em?
I don't know. Maybe...
Five hundred each?
But shit, man.
Maybe I just keep
'em for myself.
I've been eyeing these Jordans.
You guys enjoying yourselves?
Well, hold onto that feeling.
'Cause this is it.
Yeah, we know.
Well, in case you forget...
You transported stolen goods
with a value exceeding
five thousand dollars.
And the truck you used to do it
was rented in Council
Bluffs, across state lines.
You told us to rent
the truck over there...
Theft from an
Interstate Shipment.
Up to ten years.
Transportation of Stolen
Goods. Another ten years.
Sale of Stolen Goods. Ten years.
Conspiracy to commit
a federal crime...
Whoa, whoa. "Conspiracy"?
It was your idea.
Yeah. It's called mutually
assured destruction.
So, if I go down, you go down.
Man, you don't
have to threaten us.
We're all friends here.
♪
I am not your friend.
And if you get
greedy and you decide
to come back for more, don't.
Gene Takavic, you
never heard of him.
The Cottonwood Mall?
You don't go there.
You see me coming,
you cross to the
other side of the street.
Dude...
Now I need you to
say it. "We're done."
♪
(CHUCKLING) Come on! Say it.
"We're. Done."
Say it.
♪
We're done.
We're... We're done.
MARION: Gene?
Hey, Gene, I see your car!
Gene?
(CLEARS THROAT)
GENE: Well, that's a start.
Looks like your problem
is the master cylinder.
Look at you boys, hard at work.
(SIGHS) Well, Marion,
guys, I got to get going.
I will take another
look next time.
Wait a minute.
No, you can't go
anywhere looking like that.
Come on inside and wash up.
Ma...
Jeffie, don't vex
me. Come on, Gene.
You can help me
with the groceries.
Huh, Gene? Sounds like a plan.
(WATER RUNNING)
MARION: Nice of you
to help Jeffie with his car.
You might not know it, but
my boy's had some tough times.
He, uh... He fell in with a bad
crowd back in Albuquerque.
Albuquerque, huh?
Never been. Lucky you.
But things are so much
better for Jeffie here.
Even more so now
that he knows you.
You're a good influence, Gene.
Oh, where's my brain?
I keep forgetting to
ask you about Nippy.
Nippy?
Oh, oh, right.
You're not gonna
believe this, but, uh,
he was with a family the whole
time, just... Just a few blocks away.
Oh, well, that's wonderful!
Yeah. He's in great shape.
So, after all that...
A happy ending.
Oh, well...
Here you go, ma'am.
Thanks.
And looky here.
For you, m'lady.
Thank you.
Hey, Gene, aren't
you taking lunch?
Huh?
(SIGHS)
Thanks.
♪
(INAUDIBLE CONVERSATION)
(SIGHS)
♪
- Original SUB by oakislandtk - www.opensubtitles.org -
Colored HI and improvements by GoldBerg_44