♪ Old man sitting
by the side of the road ♪
♪ With the lorries rolling by ♪
♪ Blue moon sinking
from the weight of the load ♪
♪ And the buildings
scrape the sky ♪
- ♪ Cold wind ripping down
the alley at dawn... ♪
♪ Dead man lying
by the side of the road ♪
- ♪ With the daylight
in his eyes ♪
♪ Don't let it bring you down ♪
- ♪ It's only castles... ♪
Dad?
I see it.
What is happening?
Why are
the lights doing that?
Somebody call 911!
I'm on it.
I'll call too.
I don't know what's going on,
but there's just--
there's just no signal.
Be faster if we head
to the fire station in New Hope.
They have a paramedic there.
Dad?
I'm getting the car.
I'm not getting
anything either.
Okay. Okay.
Help him.
- Okay. You got him?
- Yeah.
M-Maggie, we should hurry.
- Okay, you got him?
- Come on.
God dammit.
It won't start.
I even tried to pop the clutch.
No, I-I'm getting you
and your boy to the hospital.
All right, come on.
Oh, come on.
Nothing?
What the fuck is happening?
Okay, we're gonna
take Arlo inside.
Whoever did this is still out--
- Dad. Dad. Dad? What's going on?
- Shh. It's okay.
Don?
- It's okay. I know.
Let's go inside.
I'm gonna get a lantern.
Watch your step here.
Nicholas? Come and help me
find candles, please.
Yeah, yeah, I'll...
Go.
Just-- Yup. Okay.
Duke, stop! Stop!
- Stop.
- Ruben, where are they?
- In the house.
- Okay.
Um... help me
saddle up the horses.
We can ride to our place
and get Valeria's car.
Everybody else, can we just
go inside, please? Thanks.
Donald, where you goin'?
Whoever's up there,
they hurt your kid.
You're gonna get help,
and you absolutely should.
But by the time the cavalry
shows up, that sumbitch
gonna be gone, count on it.
So I'm gonna keep the fucker
busy till you get back.
Sound good?
Absolutely.
Don.
Claire. Claire, come on.
- Come on.
- Don! Don.
Come on. Come on, please.
Okay, eyes seem fine.
Arlo, can you follow my finger?
I'm not seeing any broken bones.
Breathing is fine.
Pulse is slow.
God, you're so calm.
When things go wrong,
Mom gets calm.
Whatever happened,
I don't think that this
is your blood.
Oh, thank God.
I'm starting to think
he might have a concussion, though.
I don't have a concussion.
- Arlo.
- Hey. Hey, you. You're back.
- What's going on?
Um, you know, we're just
getting you checked out,
and just getting you
all cleaned up.
Ouch.
"Stop" ouch?
Or "grin and bear it" ouch?
- You faker.
You were faking.
- I'm not a faker.
- Oh, sure you are.
Gotta be the center
of attention.
Okay, now wait.
Aren't you the one
who hid in the oven
just so your parents
could come find you?
What? Shut up.
- I...
Mom, I thought
that story was a secret.
Okay, um, I don't think
that Arlo's faking it.
Doesn't... look like
these are fake, does it?
Looks like someone
might have tried to grab you.
Is that right?
Maybe.
It's gonna be okay, Arlo.
It is?
Absolutely.
I'm your sister. I know things.
So you have to trust me, okay?
You know what?
I think, um, maybe
you're just too dirty
for cotton balls and peroxide.
Meryl, would you mind
grabbing me, um,
the towels
from the linen closet?
- On it.
- And Nicholas,
grab me a couple cold packs
from the downstairs bathroom, please?
And Valeria?
Could you just make sure
that the windows
and doors are closed
and locked downstairs?
Yeah. Yeah, sure.
Of course.
Okay, um...
it's just you and me right now.
I need you to tell me
what happened
and who did this to you.
I don't know who did that.
Okay.
That's okay.
You don't have to know.
- You don't have to know
right now.
I do know one thing.
Okay, what's that?
We need to go.
Go where?
Away from here. Right now.
As fast as--
No, we're not going anywhere.
We're gonna get you cleaned up.
- Okay? Then we can talk--
- Wasp-brave, murder-maker.
Wasp-brave, murder-maker.
- Arlo, you're okay.
Murder-maker. Murder-maker!
I'm right here. Arlo!
- Arlo!
- No!
- Stop it!
- All right, it's okay.
- It's okay...
Arlo?
Hide-die, gun-shot,
teacup-brave.
- Mom? What's wrong with him?
Wow. Um... I'm bleeding.
- Oh, shit.
Meryl, would you?
Yeah, okay.
Hey, hey, hey. Arlo.
- Shh...
I got it. You go. It's okay. Go.
Okay, come with me.
Hey. Hey. Hey.
Feels like waiting
for the other shoe to drop,
but...
at this point, I mean,
how many more shoes
are there left to drop?
Should we help
with the kid? Or...
Maggie's got it handled.
All right, yeah.
I have to do... something.
Well-- Well, you--
- You don't have to do that.
- No, it's fine. I want to.
I wanna do something too.
Maybe I should just walk home
and call 911 from there.
Nobody's gonna mess with me
if I have Duke.
We should all just stay put.
I've just never seen
anything like that.
What was he saying?
I think he's in shock.
Could he have done that
to himself?
Arlo didn't do that to himself.
I-I'm just saying maybe.
Or maybe not. I didn't--
- I didn't mean to--
- We know. It's fine.
You know,
back in the Stone Age,
when I was a little girl,
one day, all of a sudden,
my head, my neck, my glands
just swelled up.
Just all of a sudden.
I-I looked like a balloon.
My mother took one look at me,
and she burst into tears.
They rushed me to the hospital,
they did all kinds of tests,
and...
What was it?
Cat scratch fever.
I-I know. I know.
You can laugh, but--
That's not a real thing.
Except it is.
One of our outdoor cats
had scratched me the day before.
And I had bad headaches.
I had a high fever.
Lasted about a month.
And then, I was good as new.
Wow, cat scratch fever.
All I'm saying is,
stuff happens, right?
I mean, weird things happen
to kids, and...
...it all turns out okay.
But sometimes it doesn't,
does it?
I mean, sometimes kids get stuff
and it turns out really,
really bad.
- Seriously?
- It hurts.
- Stop.
Are you scared?
Are you?
Absolutely petrified.
I... I bet my mom's right.
Arlo got a concussion.
They can make you do
weird stuff.
No, no, but it's crazy.
How did it happen?
Who grabbed him?
What's up with the cars
and the animals,
the power going out--
Just hold still.
Okay.
- What?
You act like your mom's
such a pain in the ass.
Yeah, well, she is.
Your mom's your hero,
and you wanna be just like her.
Is that why you try so hard
at school?
I don't have to try.
You're always studying.
And you're always goofing off.
What do you call a bird
who's, like, too afraid to fly?
What?
Chicken.
Just when I thought
things couldn't get worse.
I'm petrified too.
We can be petrified together.
Yeah.
Maybe we can.
Maybe whoever Arlo ran into
did it.
Fucked with the engines,
cut the power line.
Yeah, I thought of that too.
But why?
Yeah, wouldn't explain
Donald and Claire's truck
either.
Or no signal on our phones.
Yeah, well...
...I'll tell you one thing.
And I can't believe
I'm saying this.
I'm glad Donald's on our side.
Maybe it's some kind
of electromagnetic pulse?
- Like with a nuclear bomb?
- Sure, yeah. Or a solar flare?
I don't know. I don't know
what I'm talking about.
- I don't know anything
about science.
- James.
Oh, sh-shit!
Hey!
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
What's going on?
Why are you wearing that mask?
This is insane. My son is hurt!
- He could've been the one that--
- Our cars won't start.
We don't have cell service.
We don't have power. Uh--
I don't know what's going on,
I don't know
who the hell you are,
but we need help,
and your car is-is working, so--
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- What are you doing?
Hey!
Just a little gauze and tape, okay?
Goat-brave, run-hide...
wasp-die, gun-shot...
I'm not gonna let you
leave again!
Run-ran-hide... woman-go...
Woman-go! Go! Go!
No!
- Listen to me!
Arlo, stop!
It's not me, Mom.
I'm not doing this.
It's...
What's happening?
I don't know.
I'm scared.
I know. I know.
I'm scared too.
Dad says you're never scared.
Oh. I've been scared
lots of times.
When were you scared?
Well...
I was scared
when your sister got lost.
I don't remember that.
Yeah.
You weren't born yet.
Do you know where we found her?
Where?
In the oven.
I was really scared
even after that.
I was scared
for a really long time.
How scared were you?
I was so scared
that I made your dad promise
to never tell anyone about it.
Not ever.
It was our secret.
Will you sing the song?
Now?
- Yeah. Yeah, now.
- Yeah.
- Please.
- Okay.
Okay.
♪ You give me inspiration ♪
♪ You give me love ♪
- ♪ My little lighthouse ♪
♪ And the brilliant things
that you do ♪
♪ I think I could like you ♪
I'm your little lighthouse.
Yeah.
Yeah, you are.
Feels like dominos
are dropping here,
one right after the other.
Animals acting all weird.
The cars.
The kid.
Some kind
of new COVID fever bullshit.
Or...
well, maybe it's just that
Satan got in the boy somehow.
Sorry, Chenoweths.
ER is not gonna cut it.
And insurance doesn't
cover exorcisms,
so you're shit out of... luck!
Oh, Christ.
Oh, shit.
Hey, boy. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, easy, easy.
Gotcha. Okay.
- Gotcha.
Easy.
Easy...
- Oh, Christ.
A dead body...
pitch black...
big, bad fucking dog.
Fan-fucking-tastic.
Those two Xs
are supposed to be us?
That line is this blue line?
And that line goes
all around us?
Fuck this.
We need your car, man!
- Whoa! Fuck!
Jesus.
It's a line of paint
on the fucking ground!
Hey!
Guys!
Donald!
Hey! Hey!
What the...
- What the fuck?
"Don't cross the line."
Yeah. Yeah.
Hey.
Hey, you gotta tell us
what all of this is
right the fuck now!
What does that mean?
Where are you going?
- Hey. Hey...
- Where are you going?
Oh, shit.
This is stupid.
Claire.
Hey, Claire, that was a gunshot.
Okay, why don't you just stay
until Don gets back?
That was probably Donald
taking care of the problem.
Besides, someone needs
to call 911,
get the Sheriff
and an ambulance.
We have a landline.
So, I'll call,
and I'll drive our car
back here.
Claire...
there's someone out there.
I have Duke. I'm going home.
I'll be fine.
That's what I'm gonna do, yes.
Yes. Yes, we are.
I'll be fine. Come on, Duke.
- Come on, Duke.
Claire, hey.
Here.
Thank you.
I'll come right back.
Come on, brave boy.
What the hell was that?
Something is going
very fucking wrong here.
Shit. Hey, look.
Look, look, look.
What is it?
Duke, damn it!
- Fuck!
- Is that Claire?
She's heading
right for the line.
- Hey!
- Hey, Claire! Claire!
Cut it out!
What is wrong with you?
Stop!
Stay back! Claire!
- Duke!
Stop! Hey!
- Dammit!
No, no, no.
Don't cross the line! Hey!
No, Claire! Claire!
Wait, no!
Claire!
- I'm going home!
No, no, no!
Don't cross the line!
The line!
- No, no, no, no, no!
Don't! Don't!
- Stop! Stop! Hey! Hey!
- What are you talking about?
- You do not understand.
- Just--
- Let me go!
No!
Aah!
Oh, my--
Claire.
Claire! Claire!
No!
- Claire! Claire!
Claire! Claire! No!
Maggie!
Claire! Claire!
Everyone back in the house
right now.
We need to go downstairs now.
Arlo?
Run-ran-hide-hid.
Nice... man... gun... shot.
T-- T--
T-- T-- T--
Trap.
Trapped.
Run... ran... hide.
Okay.
He...
He says we need to hide.
Who says?
The man.
What man?
The man in my head.
He says we're trapped.
And we need to hide.
Why?
Because it's coming, Mom.
It's coming.
And it kills everything
that gets in its way.
♪ You give me inspiration ♪
♪ You give me love,
my little lighthouse ♪
♪ And the brilliant things
that you do ♪
♪ I think I could like you ♪
♪ Yes, we could walk
for awhile ♪
♪ Or simply talk for awhile ♪
♪ We could watch a video show ♪
♪ Or catch a picture show,
don't you know ♪
♪ We could shower ♪
♪ Put on a change of clothes
and go where everyone goes ♪
♪ We could stay in ♪
♪ Get a cheap bottle of wine
and dine ♪
♪ And the story so far ♪
♪ Rings like a shotgun
in your head ♪
♪ 'Cause you give me
inspiration ♪
♪ You give me love ♪
♪ My little lighthouse ♪
♪ And the brilliant things
that you do ♪
♪ I think I could like you ♪
♪ Inspiration ♪
♪ Love ♪
♪ Lighthouse ♪
♪ Brilliant ♪
♪ Do ♪
♪ I like you ♪