This is real. It's happening now.
They are here! And they walk among us!
All the meteor activity means
another visitor is coming. A good one.
Everybody takes a sip
- and we walk over the line?
- Yes.
No!
No.
- Stop! Stop!
- No!
You got good visitors, you got bad ones.
When a good one shows
up, a bad one hunts it down.
Fuck!
Fleetwood Mac, cheap
red wine, and sex.
Lots and lots of sex.
That was pretty much
our first year of marriage.
I never thought I'd love
anyone the way I loved William.
That was, until James came along.
I took one look at him, and I said
I would climb mountains
and swim oceans
and fight monsters for that little boy.
And then when William died, I
thought half my love died with him.
I mean, I had half left for James,
but then, that was it.
But it turns out that love is like
anything else. You can't control it.
Because you came
along, and baby meryl,
and Arlo, who popped out early.
Thirty-one weeks.
I'd do anything for those kids.
Yeah, I know.
Looks like the bleeding
has finally stopped.
But where are they? And are they okay?
I just want to see them
with my own two eyes.
And I wanna hug 'em
and tell 'em I love 'em.
And keep them safe. I'm rambling.
And that's fine.
I killed him.
And that's fine too.
Yeah, you're in shock.
Your hands, they've stopped shaking.
It's probably the adrenaline too.
Too bad it won't last for a while.
You're not going anywhere.
But the kids.
Donald and I are on it.
- We'll be right behind you.
- Okay.
They're back.
It's fine, it's fine.
I-I didn't mean to. Mcnab,
he was pointing a gun at us,
and I would never hurt
anybody on purpose,
not a person, not an animal
- I know you wouldn't, honey.
- I don't even like squashing bugs.
You were protecting yourself.
And meryl, and Arlo.
And that's a good thing, honey, okay?
Keeping your friends safe.
I just wanted to help get the liquid.
But mcnab, he had that creepy
mask, and he just grabbed us.
I... dropped the liquid.
W-What are you
talking about, the liquid?
Harbinger, he had this
way for us all to get out.
It was this-this rainbow
liquid. He said it's-it's poison,
but if you drink just a little bit
of it, you can walk over the line.
- Easy... peasy, he said.
- Wait, safely?
Yeah, totally safe.
We got some in a jar, but
that's when we heard a car.
That was mcnab. He was
parked on the other side of the line,
but when he saw the jar of
liquid, he came running at us,
right over the line, and the jar broke.
But I think maybe there's
still some of it left in it.
Take me to mcnab's car.
Meryl, grab the 3 mil
syringe and the ropivacaine.
Gonna need the needle
driver and forceps, please.
Hey, I want him close but not this close.
- Can you...?
- Yeah, yeah, got him.
Come here, bud. Here we go.
Okay.
Look out.
Gonna put you right here, okay?
Hey...
You're sure you're okay, right, Arlo?
I'm okay, dad.
Come here.
Harbinger wants mom to know...
- Who?
- Harbinger.
What does harbinger want?
Harbinger says mcnab is good.
It's the other one, assassin, that's bad.
Harbinger and assassin, got it.
Good man.
Navarros?
What about you? Are you okay?
I'm okay.
You need to go check on your mother.
What? What happened?
Donald, could you...?
Yup, I'll fill you in. Come on, Duke.
- Come on.
- Okay...
- Come on. Duke, come here.
- Sure you got this?
Meryl?
I got this.
Okay.
And you're telling me
Olsen here being dead
doesn't mean we're out of danger?
I mean, yeah, that's
what the kid, Travis, said.
The other visitor, assassin, it could
have just moved into somebody else.
Jesus Christ!
Yeah...
- Well...
- What?
Now, you and I got
here, and then Valeria...
Wait, back up, back up. None
of you actually saw this happen?
That's what I was saying.
Your mom said he cut himself free,
- he came after her...
- Yeah.
At first, I-I figured it
was just-just insanity,
you know, like everything else,
but tell me this doesn't
look like he was shot
while he was sitting up.
While he was still helpless.
- Exactly.
- Fuck.
Means that...
Which means you need to go tell
Maggie and I need to go see my mother.
Come on.
You don't wanna know.
And I don't wanna tell you.
What does that mean?
It means there's something out there.
Something so...
It means they were
dead when we got there.
My god... It means nobody's coming.
But you're okay?
No, I'm not.
Well, what about James? He...
- What about him?
- Well, you...
Well, you... You said they were dead.
But his face.
I did some of that, yeah.
It's over. I ended it.
Okay... This isn't...
Going to come out right.
But it wasn't about you.
And it wasn't about James.
It was about me. There
was something missing.
For me.
I do regret the lying, I regret hurting you,
and if it means losing you,
then I would really, I would really regret...
It just wasn't my intention.
That wasn't your intention?
Are you fucking kidding
me? No, why would i...?
Mom? Dad?
Nicholas.
Here.
- Ruben?
- Dad?
- Here, you just...
- I said, I've got it.
It's fine. I can... I can help you.
Guys?
Get behind me. Slowly.
Slowly.
- Nicholas? You need to shoot it.
- Yeah.
- What?
- Chamber a round. Do it.
- It just wants the liquid.
- Honey, but we need that liquid.
You have to shoot it,
Nicholas. Shoot it now. Now!
Jesus.
It's all true.
It's gone.
God dammit.
So fucking close.
Harbinger's not hurting you, right?
You're okay?
Harbinger trusts me, and I trust him.
And we're being brave, both of us.
Yeah.
Yeah, you sure are.
Meryl said that harbinger
is on some kind of a mission.
Is that right?
Yes.
Okay.
What is it?
To find the machine.
To go to it.
And I must be very quiet.
Why?
So I don't wake them.
Wake who?
They're sleeping, hidden.
The other assassins.
Hidden... in people?
Right.
Okay, and...
And this machine. What
happens when you go to it?
I am the on switch.
What happens when you turn it on?
We prepare.
Prepare for what?
The invasion.
My god.
Wait.
Mom?
She's not in the house.
What are you doing?
We got a problem.
It's not about one
assassin. It's about dozens.
Hundreds, maybe.
All of them sleeping, just
waiting to be woken up.
And the visitor, in your son,
may well be the best hope we have
of surviving this invasion.
That's why he has to come with me.
Please, just put the gun down. Please.
Other than myself and the
boy, I don't know who to trust.
You can't trust the person
who just saved your life?
Mcnab! Hey!
- It's okay. I'm back.
- Back the fuck up!
Let's just talk.
There's no time.
I know about the visitors.
Travis told me everything.
Travis?
Travis is dead.
Olsen too.
That's what it does!
It destroys and kills!
Doesn't stop. Not ever.
I'm not gonna let you
take Arlo. I'm just not.
There's a killer here! It could be
any one of you! And it's after your son.
Okay! Okay. What if you didn't
have to take Arlo to take harbinger?
Have harbinger move
into me. You can take me.
No. None of us are going with him!
- Shut up! Stop!
- Okay, stop. Please...
Stop, stop!
Quick! Go, go, go.
Hey, Donald. Donald...
My god.
Shit.
Hey, you're okay. You're okay.
He's gone.
Not going anywhere.
No, there's no one in there.
We'll go to Arlo's room.
- Hey, lock the door?
- Okay.
- Dad.
- Yeah?
Come with us.
- Honey, I can't.
- But mcnab, he's
yeah, he's still out there
somewhere, I know, but,
we need to find grandma.
'Cause you think she's not herself?
Like Arlo with harbinger,
you think she's assassin.
That's right.
You really believe she'd hurt us?
Yeah.
Meryl, come on.
Hey, mer. Look at me.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Sure you're up for this?
I'm nowhere near up for this.
What is that?
Hey...
- Sh...
- That's you.
- Where the hell have you been?
- Trying to find a way out.
- Mcnab ran off.
- What? I thought he was too hurt.
Maybe he is, maybe he
isn't. But he's out there.
Yeah, my mother is too.
What do you mean? What happened?
I don't even know where to start.
Harbinger...
If it's true that you can leave
Arlo and move to someone else,
then move to me.
No.
Why not?
With harbinger in
me, you can protect us.
You and dad and meryl.
But if harbinger was in
you, I can't protect you.
Okay, there's gotta be another way.
Hey, guys, it's me.
It's Nicholas.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Come in.
My parents told me to come up here.
Is Ellen really...?
Yeah.
She's the last person I'd ever think to be
yeah, I know.
I wish there were something
we could do to help.
I know.
Maybe there is.
Ruben, slow down.
Please.
Hey.
I don't wanna be alone.
Just stay here.
Looks like a lot of answers in here.
It's mostly confusing,
but there is some
stuff that makes sense.
Shh.
Lock the door behind me. Mom?
Meryl.
Okay.
Okay, okay...
Hey.
Hey, Duke.
I don't think it's me.
Not anymore.
I-I don't know where it went,
but it's not in my head.
I can't hear it.
Or... or maybe it's still in
my head, but it's hiding.
Or... Christ.
I could be lying right now,
and I don't even know it,
but I don't know anything.
Are we just gonna leave
grandma tied up like that?
It could still be in Ellen.
It could be in any one of us.
Why don't you go to the kitchen?
When you and Ruben were
off alone, either one of you
we should never split
up when looking for Ellen.
Look, I think that's the bottom line.
We don't know anything.
Except that it's here, and
it's probably in one of us.
And the navarros?
There's nothing at the navarros'.
That's bullshit, James.
It's the only reason we're trapped.
It can't be destroyed. I told you that.
- We didn't even try.
- Ruben, it was killing you.
- What are you...
- what the hell are you doing?
We don't know anything, so
unless you want to tie all of us up...
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
We really can't trust each other, can we?
That's right. On top of being
totally and completely screwed,
we are also now totally
and completely screwed.
- What do we do now?
- Find a fucking way out.
- There is no way out.
- And there's no way to tell
which one of us this is in, right?
No. Travis said no.
That poor fucking kid.
And Olsen? He wasn't
doing it. It was assassin.
What about mcnab? He's
still out there somewhere.
He is, so we keep watch,
no one goes off alone
if they don't have to,
and we stay in groups
as much as possible.
And to keep Arlo safe, we isolate him.
- Yes.
- Nobody goes in and out of his room.
Well, except for meryl and Nicholas.
I think we can all agree it isn't them.
They weren't here when it happened.
Good. Nobody else.
Well, how long are we
supposed to do this?
Until assassin makes...
Some kind of, I don't know, mistake.
Something that shows us who it is.
All right, we stay alert.
We watch each other.
So this is the solution? We do nothing?
Yeah, it is. Unless you got a
better idea, that's what we're doing.
I can't believe we're just gonna sit here
with that thing, that
monster inside one of us.
And we're talking, like assassin
isn't in this room right now,
listening to every word we say.
I am not waiting for this bastard
to decide "enough is enough"
and watch one of us go
apeshit and hope for the best.
Everybody, listen.
Okay, wait. Don't come any closer.
Look, I didn't find
anything about getting out,
but it does say, if we
can just find out who it is,
that there's a way to get
the assassin out of them.
How?
We drown them.