- Ruben!
- James.
Hold on!
We can't just leave it.
Everyone at the house
is in danger. We gotta go.
It's fine if you hate me.
I don't hate you, I feel bad for you.
James was right.
About what?
How cold you can be.
Harbinger says mcnab is good.
It's the other one, assassin, that's bad.
Meryl said that harbinger
is on some kind of a mission.
- What is it?
- To find the machine.
What happens when you turn it on?
We prepare.
Prepare for what?
The invasion.
This is the liquid.
It's yours.
We need to find grandma.
You really believe she'd hurt us?
Yeah.
I don't think it's me. Not anymore.
It could be in any one of us.
It does say if we can
just find out who it is,
there's a way to get
the assassin out of them.
How?
We drown them.
Shit.
Valeria?
For the kids.
I would have done the same thing,
but no one's getting past Nicholas.
Not on my watch.
I remember the barn.
I remember that man, Olsen.
And then
pitch black.
Nothing.
Well, not nothing, but
I mean, I-I tried to cry out.
I know I could have done it,
but I was just... I was just too tired.
And too scared.
I heard something...
Someone was whispering.
Someone awful.
In my head.
They kept whispering, and whispering.
I couldn't make out the words.
And then I was back in the barn.
And you didn't see anyone then?
Maybe a movement, or a shape.
But... I felt like I'd been hit by a truck.
Yeah, I get it.
But... anything could be a clue.
What if we did know?
What if we actually figured out who it is?
Are we really gonna drown someone?
We should do another sweep.
Mcnab's hurt.
He's scared.
In his own fucked up way, he was
trying to help. He's not coming back.
You don't know that.
And this?
This is a waste of time.
- Somebody's gonna see the smoke.
- Yeah?
And think we're burning leaves.
- Ruben, it's Monday.
- So what?
So, ups, fed ex, mailman...
Somebody will come today.
And will they be here before
another one of us dies?
I didn't think so.
Jesus Christ! It's not me.
Well.
That was easy.
Fuck you.
What are we supposed to do, then?
Not stand around a
fucking campfire, that's what.
Someone needs to check
if his... yeah, I'm on it.
Throw one of those on.
Nobody's gonna think "burning leaves"
if you get some black smoke goin'.
Hey.
Bet you forgot about these.
I did.
Still any good?
Ooh. Wow.
That was awful.
Give me one.
Thanks.
Fuck.
Keep expecting
someone to just open fire.
Yeah.
I don't know, I think it's
more targeted than that.
Olsen, he didn't shoot.
He... he insinuated himself.
You know?
He was patient, subtle.
Nothing subtle about navarros.
We can't do this.
"Check for signs of life."
"Put your ear near their
mouth and watch their chest"
I mean, it just sounds insane. It's crazy.
I know.
I know. But...
What if?
I mean, if it were to
actually come down to it.
Then what?
Of all of us, you'd be the one to
- don't do that.
- Don't do what?
Act like I'm not just as
terrified as everybody else.
I'm just saying, you're very good at
very good at what?
Go on.
Very good at being so fucking cold?
That I could drown somebody?
Just... end a life.
Is that what you're saying?
- Maggie...
- And let's say I did that.
And let's say I was actually
able to bring somebody back.
And that somehow, some way,
it actually fucking worked.
Then what?
We figure it out.
What you mean is I figure it out.
No, I mean "we."
Together. We figure it out.
Yeah.
Yeah, you don't get to do that either.
Whatever you're thinking, this isn't that.
So what is it?
Well, if I'm right, it's a way out.
Bullshit.
Follow me.
Keep your rifle pointed
at me the whole time.
I'll show you what I'm gonna do. Then
you can decide if it's bullshit or not.
Or shoot me now.
Otherwise, I'm going.
No sign of mcnab. Nothing's upstairs.
Except Olsen.
Don't think about it.
Well, it's kind of hard not to.
Okay, people need to eat,
and this stuff's all
just gonna go bad, so...
Will you hold this open for me?
Yeah.
This... and this...
Hey.
I didn't sleep.
Obviously.
I was all alone, and
Ruben had already left
and Nicholas was upstairs, safe.
And there was this little bit of light,
and, you know, it was almost dawn,
and just for a minute, I thought about...
Bread pudding.
Ruben loves it. Nicholas, especially.
I wish I could make it. There's this,
restaurant, luckily, where we all go,
just the three of us.
And just for a minute,
I actually felt hopeful.
You know, like somehow
this could all turn out okay.
- It-it's crazy.
- No.
It's not crazy.
- It's not?
- Absolutely not.
Because every once in a while
things actually do turn out okay.
It says there's this family in Maine.
They had masks on.
Real masks, like mcnab's,
and the mom, she
had an assassin in her,
so they tied her up and
drowned her in a lake.
How come nobody's
heard about any of this?
They've been keeping
it a secret on purpose.
It says there's these... Groups online
and that they talk about
being, the... the resistance.
The underground.
It's-it's so... cool.
And it worked. In Maine, they
forced the assassin out and got away.
How did they know?
I guess the mom was herself
when they brought her back.
"Brought her back."
Like, from the dead.
Well, yeah.
You know, I read that, once,
that drowning's just like going to sleep.
You know who wrote that?
Who?
Someone who's never drowned.
James said it won't do anything.
Fuck James. He doesn't know.
The kid, Travis. He said mcnab told him
Travis is dead. And
you're gonna trust mcnab?
We need to go back, Ruben.
Now.
When you moved that
fence line, did I do anything?
- What?
- I could've.
Said something. Got
lawyers involved. But I didn't.
I own plenty without it and I
didn't want to start something.
I don't know what the fuck
this has to do with anything.
It has to do with you and me.
We've known each other a long time.
Been neighbors a long time.
Left each other alone for a long time.
So the fuck what?
So, I don't like the way you do things.
And I bet you got plenty
of problems with me.
We let each other do what
we're gonna do and leave it at that.
What the fuck are you talking about?
I need you to let me
do what I'm gonna do
and leave it at that. That's
what I'm talking about.
God dammit.
So after Olsen, Maggie
was alone with you here.
James was alone when
he went to check on you.
We were all alone at some point
while we were searching for you,
so it could be... me.
Or, Ruben, or Donald,
who found you in here.
Ruben was at the fire.
But I didn't see him while I was there.
We've all been trying to stay as
far away from each other as we can.
Still... Do you need me here?
No, there'll be plenty to cook later on.
Hey.
You all right?
I don't even know anymore.
It's amazing.
I said, don't stare at it.
Yeah, I heard you, it's just... don't.
- James said...
- I know what he said.
But you saw. That woman.
Edward. Brian.
Yeah. Carmen in the woods.
Claire.
We got to try.
Fuck it. Light it up.
I guess the visitors,
harbinger and assassin,
they move from person to
person through their mouths.
It has to be really close.
How close?
Well, it's not like covid.
It's, I don't know, like...
Like what?
Like.
- I don't know.
- Like kissing?
Well... Maybe.
Just not across the room, or...
Across the table.
Like... right next to you.
Right in front of you.
But, like, how close, do you think?
Like...
Like a foot?
I don't know.
Less?
This close?
Closer.
Like this?
I think it's got to be really, really close.
- I should...
- Yeah.
I should probably check on him.
Yeah.
Yeah, you should.
And I'll, I'll stay here.
And I'll keep watch.
- Okay.
- And I'll catch my breath.
That was...
That was a lot.
No, it wasn't.
This is.
Okay.
It's got something to do
with where the machine is.
The machine harbinger's
supposed to turn on.
What is it?
I don't know.
Looks like
like lightning?
Or, like
like a map.
Look, if the two of us were to do it...
And everyone stays as
far away as possible
I mean, the clinic, the barn, the woods.
I mean, maybe. Maybe.
Right, but what happens after?
I mean, you can't revive
someone without mouth-to-mouth,
and you can't do mouth-to-mouth if...
If you're wearing a mask.
Right, and if we somehow
force assassin out of someone
like, out into the open air?
Yeah, and then you took off
your mask to resuscitate them...
Right. What's stopping
assassin from just...
Moving into me?
I don't know.
I mean, all of this is pretty
pointless, considering
one of us could just be
talking to assassin right now.
I'm not assassin.
You're not?
It's me. I can't prove it, but it's true.
That's a relief.
- Maggie...
- I wish I could believe you.
You know, at some point, we're
gonna have to start trusting each other.
Yeah, I didn't trust you before we
found out that one of us could be a killer,
so I'm not sure how I'm
supposed to trust you now.
My god.
This is nuts, not knowing
who's good or bad.
What?
That first time that you
came to my parents'
house for Thanksgiving.
God.
Your mother started it, she
did. What'd she say to your dad?
"Tom, I think you and James
actually look a lot alike."
Your dad, he didn't miss a fuckin' beat.
"Yeah, salt and sugar look a lot alike too,
but one makes everything taste
better and the other one rots your teeth."
It's still there.
You can't destroy it!
But... there's something we can do.
Hey, mom, what is it? What's wrong?
What's wrong?
You have to come with me right now.
No, I can't. I have to stay here.
No, you don't. Not anymore.
- Why not?
- Because.
I know who assassin is.
Wait a second.
It fits!
That's us.
Belknap mountain.
This has to be it.
We've got to show Nicholas.
Nicholas?
I didn't want anyone else to hear.
Or... see.
See what?
- I...
- mom, careful!
It's fine, it's fine.
Okay.
No. What are those?
They're for sedating Arlo.
For capturing harbinger. I
found them in Ellen's room.
Yeah, so she was
lying. She's still assassin.
No, no. No, no, she's not assassin.
So who is?
You are.
Nicholas?
What are we... What
are we doing out here?