Murder.
Maker.
Murder-maker.
- Come here.
- No way.
Oh, come on. Be brave.
It's a tempest in a teacup.
What's a tempest?
It's like a really big storm.
That's what we've got.
A really big tempest
in a teacup.
Yeah. Hey, will you grab me
a piece of paper?
Okay. Ready?
Count of three. Ready?
One, two, and three.
- Three!
- I got it.
I'm gonna go outside and let
him go. You wanna come?
No way. But do it right there
so I can see?
Okay, you got it.
Dad's gonna think
this is awesome.
How about this is our thing?
You and me?
Yeah, cool. Just us.
♪ Everybody seems to wonder ♪
♪ What it's like down here ♪
♪ I gotta get away from this
everyday running around ♪
♪ Everybody knows
this is nowhere... ♪
- Ah...
- Oh.
♪ Everybody knows... ♪
* Everybody knows ♪
♪ Everybody, everybody knows ♪
* Everybody knows
this is nowhere ♪
Hey.
What are you doing?
I was just up in the hayloft
cleaning up
this submarine fort thing
I built for Arlo.
Might repaint Mer's
tea party table too.
It's dumb. I know they don't
go up there anymore.
I just thought, "Why not?"
Are the animals still worked up?
Yeah. Goats... Sagebrush,
especially Ginger.
I don't know. It's weird.
Something got 'em
really spooked.
You, uh, make peace with my mom?
I will.
Okay.
You want me to walk Ginger
down to the clinic
so you can check her out?
Uh, I already closed
everything up for the weekend.
This is hard...
not talking about what's really
going on with us, Maggie.
I told you, James,
I'm not ready to talk.
You ready?
- One...
- One, two, three.
Hey.
Whoa. Okay...
Settle. Settle.
Jeez. Okay.
Hey...
Here.
What's up with you, huh?
Come here.
- Hey.
All right.
Mr. Goat?
Where are you, Mr. Goat?
I am glad that you're here.
You say that now.
- Look, Ellen...
- You know, I-I was lonely.
I-I was living alone.
So that's why I'm thrilled
to be here.
But it's not just because
of that
or because I get to see
these kids grow up, but...
I'm-I'm here for James.
Maggie...
I'm here for you too.
Well, I shouldn't have said
what I said earlier.
Remind me what that was...
You're not a pothead and I don't
think you have an addled brain.
I wish I could get
everybody else stoned
so that people wouldn't stare
at the old lady with the tremor.
Well, one, fuck anybody
who stares.
And two, I really do understand
why you smoke,
and it's fantastic
that it helps you,
and three, it's not you
that I'm angry with.
Look,
it's none of my business,
but if there's anything
that you need...
Thank you.
Well, you also know
that I'm not the easiest person
to help on a good day.
You know, recognizing
that you have a problem
is often the first step.
I appreciate everything that
you're doing, and I apologize
for being a bitch.
That smells wonderful,
and I will now grab the troops
for a lovely family meal.
Hey, have you seen
your brother?
- What?
- That's rotting your brain.
My brain's in better shape
than yours.
Well, one might think so, but...
"Two households,
both alike in dignity,
in fair Verona,
where we lay our scene,
from ancient grudge
break to new mutiny,
where civil blood makes
civil hands unclean.
- From forth the fatal loins
of these two foes..."
- Mmm.
Can you name the four chambers
of a cow's stomach?
Rumen, reticulum, omasum, abomasum.
Gosh, I hope I pass the test.
That's my girl.
- Now, where's Arlo?
- How should I know?
Well, he was up here
a minute ago.
Oh, dinner's ready.
No Arlo?
Oh, no. I-I thought I heard
someone go out,
but I was so into the cooking...
Hey, have you seen Arlo?
He's probably hiding.
He, uh...
he jack-in-the-boxed
out of our closet last week
and it scared the shit
out of me.
Right.
Yeah, he, uh, did the same
thing to me yesterday.
It's the Shanleys.
You gotta be kidding me.
Hey, Maggie,
it's our horse, Scout.
You gotta help him, please.
Dad?
Mer, your brother's MIA.
Can you go look for him?
- I wanna see what's going on.
- Mer, please, can you just
go find him?
I'll go. I'll go. I'm sure
Arlo's just hiding for fun.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Hey... Hey, Scout.
- Hey, boy. Oh...
Okay, you're all right.
I gotcha. Oh...
Nicholas said he did all that
to himself.
What, a rattlesnake scare him?
Might panic, bolt.
But this?
We're sorry for showing up
after hours. If it weren't
an emergency...
Oh, no, it's fine.
Ruben, how about you, me,
and Scout head to the clinic.
Uh, why am I not seeing Arlo?
- It's okay, Mom's got him.
- No, she doesn't.
Okay. Meryl, can you check
the barn and garage?
The rest of us
will double-check the house.
I got him. I got him.
Okay, let's go.
- Arlo?
Arlo!
All right. Easy...
Can you back him out?
Our animals have been
acting strange too.
Must be something.
Oh my God...
What did you do?
Hey, Arlo, you up there?
- Arlo, I'm counting to five.
Anybody else
use a little courage?
I'm certainly not gonna say no.
Yeah, sure thing.
I just rode him out
to check the fence lines.
It's part of my chores.
It was so... weird.
I was telling him "whoa"
to stop,
but that's when Scout started
bucking and neighing.
He got spooked.
And I was calm
like you taught me, Mom,
and I got him to stop.
But then he just put his head
up against the fence
and started moving it back
and forth and back and forth.
But I thought he was maybe
scratching an itch,
but he started doing it
really, really hard.
I could see that he was bleeding
and he just kind of twisted up
against the fence and fell.
It was so scary.
I ran to get Dad.
Maggie's gonna take care
of Scout, okay?
I'm gonna go up
just to be triple-sure,
and then... I guess it's time
to head outside.
Uh, Valeria, could you grab
a couple of flashlights
from the living room, please?
- Mm-hmm.
- Thank you.
Our secret.
This is from his first album.
Oh, I'm impressed.
♪ He's a perfect stranger... ♪
What is that?
Same kind of thing
happened in the car.
I think Dad said it was just,
like, the weather or something.
Hey, uh, do you know
what I like to do?
What?
Uh, whenever I'm,
you know, worried
or sad, or scared,
I like to name the thing
out loud, whatever it is,
and then I add a "but."
What?
Well, "Arlo is missing...
but we're gonna find him."
And, "This is scary,
but I have a little whiskey
to give me courage."
* If you see him
in the subway ♪
♪ He'll be down
at the end of the car ♪
All right...
You ready?
- Whoa.
Okay, nice and easy.
Easy. Okay.
Okay. Steady. Steady.
Easy, easy, easy.
Okay...
The eyes look fine.
We have a few cuts,
but nothing too terrible.
Just like that, we're looking
at a bright-side situation.
What?
If this is bright side,
I don't want to see the dark.
Ah. Well, the nose is why
all the blood.
It's a lot of bleeding
with the nostrils.
If it wasn't his muzzle,
I'd just use staples.
You wanna learn
how to stitch a wound?
Absolutely.
All right.
Let's see.
- Oh, shit.
Shit?
Shit.
I should have seen that.
Hey.
You haven't said anything
to Ruben?
No. I would have told you.
I know, it's just
when you pulled up--
Hi. Nothing?
One of the goats is gone, too.
- One of the goats is gone...
- Something is going on.
Donald Kelly called this morning
asking if we'd seen Duke.
Dog never leaves Claire's side.
All of a sudden,
this morning on a walk,
he just starts getting
squirrelly and runs off?
- Hmm.
- Dad.
Are we worried, like,
for real?
Are we worried? No.
We are not worried.
Arlo is hiding,
or he went after
a missing goat.
Stupid goats are always going
into the woods.
Exactly, then it got dark.
You guys always say
if we get lost to stay put.
That's right. Now Arlo
is sitting there like a goof,
waiting for someone
to come find him.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Take Nicholas, go into the woods
around the back.
We'll go around the front,
meet somewhere in the middle.
- Aye-aye, captain.
- Aye-aye.
Come on, let's go find
that gremlin.
Yup...
Hello?
Is anyone out there?
I... I think I'm lost.
Gunshot... calmate...
Gunshot... Calmate...
men-strange... murder-maker.
Ella esta mintiendo.
Ella esta mintiendo!
Murder-maker. Run-ran-hide.
Calmate... gunshot...
men-strange... murder-maker!
Ella esta mintiendo!
Murder-maker.
Murder-maker!
Arlo!
Come on, Arlo,
enough is enough.
Your family's awesome.
Are you kidding?
Arlo?
- Your dad's funny.
- My dad thinks he's funny.
Okay, well, your mom... I mean,
that was some scary shit.
But now it's just not.
- And what she's doing
with Scout, it's--
- Yeah, she's great...
with animals.
Your grandma's way cool too.
Smokes a ton of pot.
Even cooler.
- It's for pain and stuff.
- Oh.
She's got multiple sclerosis.
Her hands never stop shaking.
No, I, um, I saw that. Yeah.
My parents, they fight a lot.
My mom's always on me
about something.
And now, my stupid brother
has vanished, so.
So, yeah, totally awesome.
Do you wanna hear a joke?
- No.
- Oh...
- Okay, fine, go ahead.
- Okay, so,
what do you call a banana
eating a banana?
What?
"Canabananalism."
- What are you doing?
- What? What do you mean?
"Your family's so awesome..."
"Wanna hear a joke..."
What's...
Arlo? You out there?
- What was that? Shh, shh...
- What was what?
Is that Arlo?
Doesn't sound like Arlo.
It's called
the sternocephalicus.
But the muscle,
it's not what worries me.
If that thing is long enough,
it could have
nicked the jugular,
the carotid.
- Pull it out and...
- Yes.
There's no getting around it, though.
I'm gonna need you
to hold his head real good
this time, okay?
All right. Nice and easy.
Nice and easy.
- Shh.
Okay. Three, two, one.
- Hold tight.
Shh.
Okay... just a little blood.
Okay.
All right,
you're gonna be just fine.
He's gonna be just fine.
You okay?
This bright-side situation
we got goin' on here
all of a sudden...
Whew!
You're all right. Nice and easy.
Arlo!
Did you see the look
Maggie gave me?
Maggie didn't give you a look.
She knows what happened,
but doesn't know
who it happened with.
Okay, well, it's only
a matter of time.
Okay...
Arlo!
Yeah, I'd be really worried
if this was my first rodeo,
but... but this was before
Arlo was born, actually.
Maggie's usually at her best
when bad things happen.
She takes control and does
what needs to be done.
I know. Ruben's the same way.
He's a man on a mission.
Yeah, but not this time.
Maggie couldn't find Meryl
anywhere. Nowhere.
Not-not the barn,
not the hayloft
where I built this little
table and chairs
for her to have her tea parties.
Not the clinic.
Checked every cupboard
and closet in the house.
Up here, down the driveway.
Nothing.
Then I come home from work
and I-I...
I'd never seen Maggie
like that.
I mean,
she was paralyzed, frozen.
Could barely speak.
She just...
just sat there shivering.
Where was Meryl?
In the fucking oven.
- In the oven?
- Yeah.
Yeah, we read her
Hansel and Gretel.
The witch wants to bake them,
you know?
So Mer climbed in
just to see if she could fit,
and... [whistles] ...somehow
closed the door, too.
She wanted us to come find her
but the door was too heavy
and she got stuck.
Good Lord.
Yeah, no way out.
So what does she do?
Kid falls asleep.
And we didn't find her
until we come into the kitchen
to wait for the police.
God, it was so scary.
Kids...
They're just so stupid.
They're stupid.
I mean, I love 'em both so much
it hurts, but...
Why am I telling you this
right now?
'Cause you really are worried.
- Yeah, I guess I am.
- Yeah.
And you love your kids.
- Of course, more than anything.
- Mm-hmm.
And you love Maggie too.
- We found the Kellys' dog.
- And we found Mr. Goat too.
- You guys okay?
- Yeah.
- Good, good, good.
What is that?
Okay. Hey, guys?
Everyone back to the house
right now.
Keep going. Go, go, go.
- Did you find him?
- No, but I will.
What does that mean?
Hey. Where are you going?
Meryl, what are you doing
with the goat?
I found him
in the woods. Dad?
Yeah?
Duke!
Did you happen to see
our son, Arlo?
No, we're just out
looking for our dog. Why?
How long's your son
been missing?
An hour, tops.
James, what are you doing
with the bat?
We saw a coyote.
At least I think it was
a coyote, I'm not sure.
Whatever it was, there was
something wrong with it.
That's why we're here.
That wasn't a coyote you saw.
It was a dog. A big one.
No collar, nothing.
The way he was eyeballin' us...
- We think he was rabid
or something.
- Yeah.
Growlin', hackles up.
We thought for sure
the bastard was gonna lunge,
then he took off.
You got kids.
Wanted to make sure
you had a heads-up.
Jesus Christ, man.
What are you doing?
Hey, if it were my kid...
- It's not your kid.
- Did you not hear
what I just said?
Yeah, I heard you
loud and clear.
There's a rabid dog.
Getting ready to play softball?
You're getting ready to drop
into a fucking war zone.
How about you just show me
where you saw the dog,
and I'll take care of it.
James!
Oh my God.
Arlo!
Arlo...
- Arlo! What happened?
Oh my God.
Maggie, his arms.
- Oh my God.
- Those look like finger marks.
Like-- Like someone
grabbed him.
Hey. Hey...
Who did this to you?
Buzz-goat, wasp-find...
men-strange, murder-maker...
Esta mintiendo!
Run-ran-hide! Run-ran-hide!
Buzz-goat, wasp-find...
men-strange, murder-maker...
- Ella esta mintiendo!
- It's okay.
Run-ran-hide!
Buzz-goat, wasp-find...
men-strange, murder-maker...
ella está mintiendo.
Men-strange, murder-maker!
Ella está mintiendo...
Run-ran-hide!
Oh, my God... Arlo! Arlo? Okay.
Oh my God! Oh my God...
¿Hola?
¿Quien es?
Is someone there?
Ayudame, por favor.
Ayudame!
Please...
help me.
♪ Sit beside
the breakfast table ♪
♪ Think about your troubles ♪
♪ Pour yourself a cup of tea ♪
♪ Then think about the bubbles ♪
♪ You can take your teardrops ♪
♪ And drop 'em in a teacup ♪
♪ Take 'em down
to the riverside ♪
♪ And throw 'em over the side ♪
♪ To be swept up by a current ♪
♪ Then taken to the ocean ♪
♪ To be eaten by some fishes ♪
♪ Who were eaten
by some fishes ♪
♪ And swallowed by a whale ♪
♪ Who grew so old ♪
♪ He decomposed ♪
♪ Doo ♪
♪ He died and left his body ♪
♪ To the bottom of the ocean ♪
♪ Now everybody knows ♪
♪ That when a body decomposes ♪
♪ The basic elements ♪
♪ Are given back to the ocean ♪
♪ And the sea does
what it oughta ♪
♪ And soon there's salty water ♪
♪ Not too good for drinking ♪
♪ 'Cause it tastes just like
a teardrop ♪
♪ So we run it
through a filter ♪
♪ It comes out from a faucet ♪
♪ And it pours into a teapot ♪
♪ Which is just about
to bubble ♪
♪ Now ♪
♪ Think about your troubles ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Oh ♪