We don't know anything,
except that it's here
and it's probably in one of us.
Everyone, listen. If we find out who it is,
there's a way to get
the assassin out of them.
- How?
- We drown them.
It says there's this family in Maine.
The mom, she had an assassin in her,
so they tied her up and
drowned her in a lake.
How did they know?
The mom was herself
when they brought her back.
It says there's these groups online,
and they talk about being the resistance,
the underground.
- I've seen that car before.
- That's fucking Hayden.
Hayden was a member of
our little band of brothers.
Until he preemptively shit the
fucking bed. Told you he's a psycho.
A visitor is made of nothing.
It's like vapor, or air.
Shooting can't kill it.
You can kill the host.
But the visitor, it'll just
hop into somebody else.
I said, don't stare at it.
Light it up.
You can't destroy it!
But there's something we can do.
Hey, mom. What is it?
What's wro... what's wrong?
I know who assassin is.
- I found them in Ellen's room.
- She's still assassin?
No, no. She's not assassin.
So who is?
You are.
Hey.
Yeah. I've got it.
No. Just tell me where mcnab is.
It's still gonna hurt like hell,
but these will help.
All we need is one piece
and that should be
enough for everybody.
There's not enough in there for
anyone to make it over the line alive.
Is there enough for me to
- I think so.
- You think so?
Yeah.
Here we go.
This gonna work?
It has to.
Fucking hell.
Ruben!
Get up! Come on!
Like Nicholas said...
Easy-peasy.
Yeah.
Assassin can't be
killed, so how do we win?
I just... I don't know.
How many people have died now?
Claire.
Carmen.
Edward.
Brian.
There was a woman
beside navarros' barn.
Olsen.
The kid in the basement.
Travis.
He had been shot I don't
know how many times.
He was gonna die. I
think he knew it, too.
He told me all he ever
wanted was some control.
Of his life. Of something, anything.
But...
There was no stopping
what was happening. Was...
Nowhere to go to get help, and...
There was nothing to
do, and if there was.
I'm really sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
Until he turned the gun on himself,
I thought I was gonna
die down there too.
And all I kept thinking... Praying...
Was I hope Maggie
knows how sorry I am.
There was nothing I
could do to save him.
It must have been awful.
It wasn't unfamiliar.
What wasn't?
I-I don't think I've ever
really felt like I've had control.
What do you mean?
Of my life.
My job.
Us. Our life.
The kids. All of it.
It's always felt like it all...
It all just happened somehow.
And then I look at you.
You with work.
You with our kids.
You with everything.
You've always had control.
You've always been in control.
Just.
I think I wanted some of that.
Valeria and I got close at work.
As friends, at first.
And...
Part of it was because
she understood that feeling.
The things in life turning
out the way they did.
Without any say.
I don't know. I liked
being understood that way.
Does that make sense?
Nothing makes sense right now.
I know.
That's not true.
Arlo.
Meryl.
They make sense.
What about us?
I know we don't right now.
Could we make sense again?
I don't know.
Maybe.
Maybe is all I can give you right now.
I'll take maybe.
- We know where to go.
- We can't get out.
Assassin could be in anybody.
Even if we knew who it was,
assassin could move to somebody else.
So we're fucked?
Arlo chenoweth.
What? It's true, isn't it?
There is something we can do.
What?
Assassin.
I don't get it.
Lock the door.
Don't let anybody in except me.
Okay?
Okay.
Are you okay?
It's my mom. Assassin's my mom.
She tried to grab me. I-I got away, but,
I think she was gonna try
to drug Arlo or something.
What... what do you mean?
She had... she had these.
Hey. Okay, we need
to go warn everybody.
- Wait.
- What?
- Let me just say something.
Whatever happens, I'm so
glad we found each other.
- Seriously, I need you to know...
- I left Arlo alone.
Are you really gonna make me tell
you another one of my dumb jokes?
Nicholas, stop...
Meryl, what... what happened?
No! No.
Arlo, what are you
doing out of your room?
It's meryl. She's doing bad things.
Let's go.
All of this...
The blood...
The tears...
The struggling...
Meryl.
Meryl, come on. I know you're
- if only you knew what's coming.
- No.
Listen to me, meryl. I promise
you'd realize just how utterly
insignificant you all are.
Just give me what I want.
No.
No, I can't let you anywhere near Arlo.
Then I'm gonna have to kill you.
Yes, you are.
Maybe not.
Maybe.
I'll just kill her.
No.
No, you won't.
Of course I will.
That's what I thought.
Get your mask on! Your mask!
Get your mask on!
- Grab her legs!
- Jesus!
Go! Let's go!
Drink it, step over the line, and get help.
- I'll go first.
- And then run like hell.
- I didn't have to help you.
- Didn't have to shoot me either.
Nicholas!
What happened?
I-I-I was with mom. She said she
knew who assassin was and then...
- I-I don't remember.
- Let's get you inside.
Guys?
I can't do this!
- You have to, Maggie!
- I can't do it!
Come on, let's go. You have to! Go!
Maggie, wh...
Get her!
Come on...
Come on, meryl...
No.
Meryl...
Please... Come on, meryl...
Meryl! Please...
Come on...
Meryl, please...
Meryl!
My god...
Mom...
Meryl!
James and Maggie
are in there with meryl.
- She's...
- and Valeria?
I... I
I don't know.
Now we're not trapped.
No, we're not.
We need to go.
- Where's mom?
- I'll find mom.
I'll go get Maggie and James...
- And meryl too?
- I'll get everybody.
Stay out of sight. Get to the road.
I'll meet you there. And then
we all get the hell out of here.
In the Van that Olsen
bastard drove up in.
Easy-peasy.
Come on.
Hey... we should all go together.
I gotta go get mom and the chenoweths.
- But dad...
- Hey.
Dad?
You...
You need to run.
Meryl. Meryl, pick up
the syringe and the knife.
Meryl, do it.
Run!
Nicholas, don't look.
- Mom!
- Don't look, Nicholas!
Don't look! It's okay.
No... no... Don't... don't.
- She's...
- Honey, don't look.
Okay? Look at me. Look at me...
Mom?
I know, honey. I know.
- Mom...
- Yes, she's gone.
She's gone. I know, she's gone.
Just look at me.
Dad!
James!
Shit.
Slow is smooth, smooth is fast...
- Mom, that's dad...
- I know it is.
Mom.
Fuck...
Damn it.
Give me the Ketamine.
- What?
- The syringe and the knife.
Stay inside!
None of this will make any difference.
You're wrong. It will.
No.
No, it really won't.
We both know what's
gonna happen now.
Arlo, quick! Quick.
Come on, quickly, quickly.
- No, mom! Mom.
- Arlo...
- Remember the wasp?
- What?
The wasp and the teacup.
Remember the teacup?
Arlo, get back.
Go.
Why don't you just give up?
Because that's not what we do.
You can't win.
We don't have to win.
We just have to trap you.
Help me... Help...
Dad...
- Mom?
- Please...
It's dad!
I know, I know, I know
I know, I know, honey. I'm sorry.
- We can't!
- I know! We have to... Mom... no!
I know... Mom, he'll suffocate!
I know, I know... I know... No...
He'll die, mom.
He'll die.
He's gonna die.
I'm sorry.
Arlo...
Meryl.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry... Meryl, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry...
It's over.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
Someone's got to stay with the animals,
just in case.
You're coming right back, right?
Absolutely we'll be back.
Okay, then.
I'm sorry.
No...
Take that.
It's, still nothing.
Where do we go?
The police? Hospital?
We'll go to the fire station in new hope.
For now.
Meryl.
- What?
- Harbinger says
we need to go to belknap mountain.
We need to make sure
everybody's okay first. Okay?
Harbinger has to turn on the machine.
- I know.
- Whoa.
What is that?
Who here is mcnab?
I-I'm Carol.
And this is Milo.
You found me.
We found you.
It's okay.
They know what's going
on. They're here to help.
I got worried when you
stopped posting on the chat room
and then stopped answering texts.
You know, I figured
you wouldn't be far
from your last location.
You... you figured right.
We have people hurt. We're
trying to get to the fire station.
For sure.
We'll follow you.
Just let me get this
one thing out of my bag.
God, that's Hayden.
What are you doing?!
Get out of the way!
I'm gonna need you to just listen.
Okay?
Listen and look.
Zip ties to hold you.
Ketamine to drug you.
These people, they
were not your friends.
This is real.
The bastards are waking up.
And I'm telling you...
They are everywhere.
Now, you can go it alone.
In which case, I can pretty much
guarantee that you're fucked.
Or you can follow us.
And maybe, just
maybe, you might survive.
The choice is all yours.
So...
What's it gonna be?
We're not going anywhere until
you tell us what the fuck is going on.