Okay, one extra-large virgin margarita.
- Thank you, Richard.
- What took you so long?
Uh, I actually... Uh, I met a girl.
It's called the bartender, she works here.
No, no. It's a real girl.
And I actually got her real phone number.
Check you out, Mr. Casanova.
Where is this individual?
Um, she's right over there.
The tall dude?
No, behind him.
Oh, she must be hiding behind
that attractive girl in the red sweater.
No, it is the attractive girl in the red sweater.
- Oh...
- Please stop looking at her.
She's magnificent.
You sure it's not the tall guy?
Why are we surprised that young Richard
is garnering the attention of ladies?
After all, he's king again.
Women like that.
Okay, so she's a founder hounder.
Come on, no, it's not like that.
But you did tell her that you're the CEO
of your own company?
it came up.
But I mean, honestly, how else was I going to
explain that me and my friends were at a bar?
That is a good point.
Anytime you're near a woman,
it is important to explain why.
Otherwise, they get nervous.
Gentlemen, to Pied Piper's past,
and now present, CEO.
Oh, what about future?
Jared, we'll worry about that later.
Tonight is about Richard.
To Richard.
I think you'll find I'm a pretty tolerant boss,
but, Gleb, your last commit,
you did use spaces over tabs.
Um, I don't know why you'd commit to that.
Uh, so, just tell me why on Earth
you would do something like that.
Is not so big a deal.
They're very much the same. Yes?
Yes, yes, he's right.
They're very much the same.
No, no, sorry, they're not the same.
At least not in my book. Um, um...
One is right, and the other is wrong.
Why didn't anyone tell Gleb to use tabs?
Yeah, we did.
And it's in the company style guide.
I just don't think Gleb realized
how seriously Richard takes this stuff.
Yeah, I've honestly never
understood it myself.
I mean, once the code
goes through the compiler,
there's effectively no difference.
I know, but coders go, like, batshit over it.
At Hooli, I once saw two engineers
get into a fight so vicious,
they almost made physical contact.
What?
Okay, guys, back to work.
Uh, Gleb, Sanjay, everyone,
do you understand tabs?
Yes, yes. You have made this very clear.
As clear as crystal.
Okay.
Good, that's my little thing,
and I'll hand you back to Dinesh now.
He's the man with the plan,
and the pretty cool tan.
-it's not a tan, it's...
- Yeah, I know, I know.
Uh, sorry.
This is how I was born.
Hey, Elisabet. Hi.
Um, before you go, I just wanted to say that
I thought your last commit
was very impressive.
Oh, thank you.
Almost as nice as the fingers that typed it.
- Just call it like I see it.
- Thank you.
Speaking of seeing, I will see you tomorrow.
Yes, you Will.
Bye-bye, Dinesh.
Bye, Elisabet.
Yuck.
What?
You don't actually think she was flirting,
do you?
She works here.
She's paid to interact with you.
Just like that bartender
that Richard thought he was flirting with.
Uh, actually, she's not a bartender.
And for your information,
we've been trading texts.
And we're going for drinks later, so...
Great.
If you go to the bar she works at,
you can probably drink for free.
Again, uh, not a bartender.
Okay? She works at Facebook.
So she makes a lot more money
than I do or you do.
And she's definitely not a founder hounder.
So, sorry.
Yeah, none of that adds up.
Hey, guys, check out Code/Rag.
What, did the Gavin piece post?
Indeed it did.
Oh.
"Gavin Belson's Hooli-Scrub Scandal."
Awesome.
Man, Gavin cannot be happy about this.
Stay close.
Back up, back up.
You're on private property.
Back to the sidewalk.
You're gonna get arrested.
Hey, Gavin!
Hello, I'm...
You know, a hundred years ago,
men like me could've
had people like that killed.
Just like that.
You think captains of industry
like Andrew Carnegie or Cornelius Vanderbilt
would've batted an eyelid? Please.
Times sure have changed.
Or have they?
Of course they have.
And for the better.
Unless...
All right, forget it.
What are we doing about this article?
Can we sue this Cantwell woman for libel?
Gavin, libel laws don't really apply
when what's written is true.
It's my understanding you did in fact
instruct Nucleus engineers
-to obscure negative Hooli search...
- I know what I did.
Forget libel. What about this unnamed
Hooli insider she keeps quoting?
Everything this person is saying is obviously
covered by a nondisclosure agreement.
Let's sue that person.
We don't know who that person is.
And reporters generally
don't give up their sources.
Well, then I'll just have to light a fire
under this reporter's ass, won't I?
You know, there was a time, not so long ago,
when it could've been a literal fire.
But, as discussed, those days are gone.
Unless...
All right, forget it.
You people are useless. Thank you.
You're excused.
It's Gavin Belson for C.J. Cantwell, please.
She'll know what it's regarding.
Now, the stage should be here.
With Yeezy or someone comparable.
Now, I have yet to land on a theme.
Most people who rent Alcatraz for parties
tend to go with the prison theme.
How much would it cost to make this look
as if it were never a prison at all?
Spare no expense.
And if you think it would be cool,
I would love to have
some sort of chocolate moat here,
with little boats floating down it filled
with graham crackers and marshmallows.
It's been a childhood dream of mine.
And get the best chocolatier.
We want to impress.
I'm inviting every asshole
from the Valley to attend.
- You're inviting assholes?
- Absolutely.
Assholes, shit dongles.
Any foe or enemy I've made
over my storied career will be here.
That way, when I take the stage
and unleash the power of Bachmanity,
they'll all be in the front row.
Erlich, uh, can we talk for a second?
What is it, Big Head?
I thought I told you to go
watch something on your iPad.
I think we may have a problem.
That Code/Rag reporter I talked to
says that Gavin Belson
is threatening to sue her
if she doesn't tell him who she spoke to.
- So?
- So, she spoke to me.
No publicity is bad publicity.
This might be great timing.
Exactly the reason that we are partners.
Okay, yeah, except if Gavin finds out
it was me that talked to the reporter,
then he'll know I violated my NDA.
And then he could come after
my entire settlement if that happens.
All two million.
I mean, 20 million.
Big Head, I'm not going to yell.
And I'm not going to hit you.
I'm just gonna ask you nicely,
why in the holy fuck didn't you tell me
you signed an NDA,
you sweet, helpless little piece of shit?
Well, that's the thing about the NDA,
is that the NDA is actually covered
under the NDA.
So if I told you about the NDA,
it would've been a violation of the NDA.
And what about speaking with the reporter?
What would that be?
Yeah. Shit.
So, what do you think I should do?
- I could call her back and...
- No.
Let me handle it.
You go wait in the helicopter.
- Okay.
- Go.
Sasha, I'm going to need to go back
to the mainland.
Oh, is there a problem?
Oh, no, no, no. Full steam ahead.
Mainland.
This is an island.
That's the theme.
Hawaiian.
We'll have a luau.
Yeah, somebody
called me that in high school,
and the nickname just stuck.
Pakistani Denzel?
I mean, I don't see it.
But everybody else does. So...
Maybe they should call him American Dinesh?
Stop.
Only if you stop first.
- No, you stop first.
- You stop first.
- You go first.
- No, I think you should.
Okay, I'll stop. Bye.
What's your end game here?
You think after your tired rap,
she's going to hop on a plane,
fly halfway across the world,
and fuck you?
My motivations are pure.
Her and I have, like, a real connection.
She's so, like, nice
and she's so down-to-Earth,
that it's like she has no idea
how attractive she is.
You don't know how attractive she is.
Packet loss over Estonian broadband
is terrible.
She could be hideous.
Well, I can't imagine that would matter
to Dinesh one iota.
Right.
'Cause she's nice and very talented
and has a great laugh.
And with any luck, she's not a dogface.
How was your date with Winnie?
Uh, well, pretty good,
considering she's still in the other room.
Baller, you got lucky on the first date.
Yeah, did a little bit, not everything.
I mean, I slept in my jeans.
Well, take your time. Hunger is the best sauce.
You're right. Uh...
We did a little bit of under the shirts
and light finger banging.
Oh, hey.
- Hey, I'm Winnie.
- Oh.
Hi, I'm Dinesh.
Hi, I'm Jared.
- It is an honor to meet you.
- Okay.
God, what a pleasure.
Thanks.
I'm Gilfoyle.
Are you a bartender?
I work at Facebook.
As a bartender?
I had a stuffed animal named Winnie.
Oh, wow.
I mean,
it wasn't technically an animal,
I took a Ziploc bag
and I stuffed it with old newspaper,
and then I drew a smile on it.
Okay, well, shall we have some coffee,
milady?
- Sure. Let's do it.
- Okay. All right.
We're already on to Elizabethan nicknames.
This is serious.
They'll be Ren Faire-ing soon.
It's healthy.
And now that Richard's dating, in solidarity,
I think I might get back out there myself.
You make it sound like
you've chosen not to date.
Yeah, absolutely.
I wanted to focus on Pied Piper.
But, yeah, maybe now I'll fan
out my plumage, so to speak,
and see what pretty birdies
might share my nest.
Hey, Jared, if you fuck any pretty birdies
in my server room,
put a tie on the doorknob, won't you?
As a signal. Yeah, good thinking.
Okay, so I'll just get the car keys,
and then give you a lift home.
Okay, milady?
- Milord.
- Oh, milady.
Okay.
So, Richard tells me you guys are building
deep nets into your platform?
Oh, really?
What other company secrets
did he blab to you?
Well, I'm a bartender. I wouldn’t understand
all the science-y talk, right?
Touché.
So you do AI at Facebook?
No, but when I was at MIT,
I did my master's thesis on game-playing AIs.
I did a lot of machine learning stuff.
For gaming? How does that work?
It's on my GitHub.
Do you want to check it out?
Gavin said he was gonna haul me into court,
and have a judge compel me
to give up my source or go to jail.
Okay? I am not going to jail.
No, no one's going to jail, C.J.
Although, if you did,
going to jail for protecting your source
would make you some kind of
First Amendment hero.
It's pretty much the best thing
that can happen to a journalist.
Journalist? I'm a tech blogger, okay?
I write stories for the Internet
about the Internet.
I am not going to jail for that.
I know it is an inconsequential shit job.
It doesn't really contribute to culture
in any way whatsoever.
We've established
that you don't have any journalistic integrity,
but what would it cost to buy you some?
...and then I figured out a way
to train a convolutional net
to play Atari 2600 games.
- Uh-oh.
- What?
Spaces.
Yeah, so what, you guys use tabs?
In this house, yes.
Richard is a bit of a zealot
in the Tabs V. Spaces holy war.
I get that, for his company. Sure.
This goes much deeper.
I think he believes that people
who use spaces are less than.
- Huh...
- I wouldn't mention this to Richard.
You don't want to see him throw a hissy fit.
Okay. Shall we away, milady?
Nice to meet you guys.
Have fun.
- Bye.
I actually kind of liked her.
Too bad Richard's going to fuck it up.
So, you moved the swimming pool?
Yeah, it just felt like it was way too far
from the house, like, crazy far.
So I had this company come
and just move it closer.
Uh-huh. But then you moved it back?
Yeah, turns out the guy who built this place
knew exactly what he was doing,
and the pool was right where it needed to be
the whole time.
But now I know that for sure,
which feels good.
Nelson, do you like being wealthy?
Yeah, oh, man, it's awesome.
So you want to stay wealthy?
- Okay, yeah, sure.
- Great.
Here are the three things
you need to do, all right?
One, stop moving the swimming pool.
Oh, yeah, okay, I can do that. What else?
Two, you need to manage your expenses
and track your receipts
a little bit better than this.
I'm only as good as the information I have.
Oh, you're great.
No, I wasn't fishing for compliments.
And three, I sense that people
are taking advantage of you.
Oh, sorry, hold on.
Oh, it's Erlich, I should probably grab this.
Erlich Bachman, a perfect example.
You gave him signing power
on your personal checking account?
Yeah, he's my business partner.
You're not structured as a corporation.
You're a general partnership.
So he's essentially your spouse.
That's very dangerous.
But I trust him.
He's actually trying to save us money
right now, so hold on.
Hey, man.
Big Head, wondrous news.
I eliminated the Gavin problem,
and at the exact same time,
I closed funding
on our first strategic investment.
We bought a blog.
Oh, cool. How much do blogs cost?
What?
Oh, nothing. We practically stole it from them.
I'm bullshitting.
Half a million dollars.
Let me talk to him, please.
Uh, hey, hey, Erlich, could you talk to
my business manager for a second?
No, I've got to jet, but tell him
I'll see him at the party.
Good day, partner.
Okay, cool.
About the blog...
- Five hundred grand.
- Oh, God.
I know, we practically stole it, right?
Your roommates are really funny.
I like them.
They gave me a little shit.
Oh, well, you can't take that personally.
Oh, it's fine. They gave you shit, too.
Really? What about, like,
my hair or something?
No. They tried to convince me you were
some sort of formatting Nazi
about tabs versus spaces.
What? Me? A Nazi? That's ridiculous.
That's what I said, I mean, I use spaces.
So what?
Mmm...
Yeah, so what?
See, they said you'd have
a hissy fit if you found out.
Mmm-mmm. Hissy fit. Me? No.
I know.
You know. I know.
I mean, make up your mind, guys,
am I a Nazi or am I
a guy who throws hissy fits, you know?
Am I a Nazi who throws hissy fits?
I hope not. That was Hitler.
That was, like, his whole deal.
I mean, that's pretty insensitive
to the Holocaust, don't you think?
'Cause that's, like, what Hitler did.
You know, he just, like,
killed so many people,
so tragic, such a tragic time.
- Yeah.
- I'm so glad we're not doing that anymore.
I mean, we, like I was, you know...
I want them all to die. I don't. I don't care.
I mean, I do care. Don't kill them.
Them... Jews.
Uh, anyway, what do you want to order here?
Is that our P2P protocol?
Yeah, I'm just hacking for fun.
I figured out a way to use our compression
for RTC, so...
Video chat?
Yeah, I think it could be better resolution
than Hooli-Chat.
Even over 3G.
It could just be, like, a fun, cool feature
in the platform, you know.
And then coincidentally you'll finally be able
to see what Elisabet actually looks like.
- Oh, yeah.
- Huh.
I hadn't thought of that.
If you worked half as hard on the platform
as you do trying to ogle
strange Slavic women,
maybe our shares would
finally be worth something.
Hey, uh...
What the hell was that?
Can you give us slightly more, Richard?
Why did you tell Winnie that I think people
who use spaces over tabs are stupid?
Because you do.
No, I don't.
And if I did, which I don't,
why would you say that
behind my back to her?
I mean, things were just
going so well, until she...
That was completely lovely.
Yeah, it was really nice.
You're really something.
I'll give you a call later, okay?
Okay, cool, yeah. Great, sounds good.
Bye, Jared.
Bye.
Jared?
Yeah?
Who was that?
Oh, that was Carol.
So, uh, Jared, did you just have sex with her?
What?
I'm an adult,
and like the rest of you, I'm a sexual being.
You fucked her in the garage?
Well, it's the server room and my bedroom.
What, so you just meet a woman,
and then you have sex with her?
How often does this happen?
Well, if you're asking me how many times
I've been in love, the answer is two.
But the rest, I won't talk about.
It's untoward.
Russ was right, this guy fucks.
Who was that gorgeous gazelle
in the driveway?
Well, I've said all I care to, let's move on.
She let Jared have sex with her.
Jared, nice. Using that dick.
Gents,
I'd like to invite you to what promises to be
the social event of the season.
Bachmanity Insanity.
Alcatraz?
Don't worry, it will be unrecognizable.
Jared, with regards to the...
You need a plus one?
Oh, no, thank you.
I think it's too early for that.
Good idea.
Don't bring sand to the beach,
there's already pussy there.
Richard, I assume you'll be taking
your woman friend?
You know what? Yes.
She and I will be there together.
I'm going to make this work,
despite all your little attempts
to sabotage my relationship.
You can do anything
you put your mind to, Richard.
Including turning Alcatraz into Hawaii.
You Okay?
Yeah. Yeah, all good. Great.
- You know...
- What?
My roommate's going out of town tomorrow,
so if we want to come back here
after Erlich's party...
Oh. Okay, yeah.
Sure, that sounds good to me.
All right, it's a date.
See you then.
Richard, what's wrong?
Nothing. Nothing. Literally, it's all good.
Come on.
- Oh, my God!
- I'm sorry.
Your roommates were right,
you really hate spaces.
No,no,no.
I don't... It's not hate.
Hate's a strong word. Um...
Truth be told,
I do have a slight preference for tabs.
But that's only because I'm anal
and because I prefer precision.
Well, not to pick a fight here,
but if you really care about precision,
wouldn't you use spaces?
- N...
- But whatever.
Once it goes through the compiler,
it's the same thing, right?
Yeah. Yeah, technically, yes.
I guess I just don't understand why you...
Anyone would use spaces over tabs.
Like, if it's all the same,
why not just use tabs?
Because it could look different
on other people's computers.
Tabs create smaller file sizes, all right?
I run a compression company.
Trust me, I've devoted my life
to minimalizing file sizes.
It's what I do.
I mean, I do not get why anyone would use
spaces over tabs.
I mean, why not just use Vim over Emacs?
I do use Vim over Emac.
Oh, God, help us!
Okay. Uh...
You know what?
I just... I don't think this is going to work.
I'm so sorry.
I mean, like, what?
We're going to bring kids into this world
with that over their heads?
That's not really fair to them, don't you think?
Kids? We haven't even slept together.
And guess what,
it's never going to happen now,
because there is no way I'm going to be
with someone who uses spaces over tabs.
Richard.
Wow, okay.
Good bye.
One tab saves you eight spaces.
on!
Oh, my God!
Richard, what happened?
I just tried to go down the stairs
eight steps at a time.
I'm okay, though.
See you around, Richard.
Just making a point.
Huh.
This new video chat protocol
is making your image crystal clear.
Wait one second, Dinesh.
Uh, Dinesh, I can't see you, it's all black.
Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't give the camera
permission to access the video chat, hold on.
Boom!
Yes, I can see you now.
It's me!
Pakistani Denzel!
Yes.
The Denzel who is from Pakistan.
This video quality is great, right?
Looks so sharp.
That's what we do here at Pied Piper.
It's very impressive.
Um, I will have to tell
my boyfriend all about it.
Boyfriend?
You never mentioned a boyfriend.
Oh, no? Um...
This is because he's now just husband.
Um, I keep forgetting to say this, husband,
but it is very good to see you this way,
and we will talk more tomorrow.
Yeah, we'll talk...
Either she froze time,
met and married the man of her dreams,
unfroze time, and hopped back
on to vid chat with you,
or you're the dogface.
Which do you think it is?
I'm on the fence.
What the fuck is going on?
Richard found a girl, you have a girlfriend,
Jared is getting laid with a girl.
Hi, Mom.
Oh, God.
Winnie, Winnie, Winnie, Winnie.
Sweet, sweet Elisabet.
Gentlemen, mahalo for coming.
You must taste the breaded
humuhumunukunukuapua'a,
flown in fresh this a.m.
What is mumu...
It's breaded.
Get ready.
In T-minus five minutes,
Big Head and I are going to take that stage,
and I am going to
ejaculate my success all over
the faces and hair of my fiercest rivals.
Like some sort of vengeful
viscous web of payback.
- Erlich?
- Yes.
One moment.
- Sasha, you are doing an exceptional job.
- Oh.
I mean, I see no evidence
that we are not in Hawaii.
Hmm. We have a problem.
Just, several of our vendors are saying
that your checks have bounced.
Uh, Sasha, hikiki'i. I'll be back.
Big Head, Big Head.
Why are our checks bouncing?
If you had responded
to any of my phone calls,
I would've explained it to you.
And who the fuck are you?
Uh, Erlich,
this is my business manager, Arthur...
Klaiman.
Klaiman. I knew it was something with Clay.
As I was explaining to Mr. Bighetti,
I've finally managed to get a handle
on his finances.
Our finances. Continue.
After your considerable outlay on lifestyle,
this party and half a million dollars
on a website,
you're functionally insolvent.
Big Head, you're broke?
We're broke, dude.
Erlich, it's time.
You have my number.
I left it on your voice mail.
Several times.
Titans of the tech world,
I give you Nelson Bighetti, Erlich Bachman
and Bachmanity!
- Aloha.
- Uh, that means hello.
Oh, and goodbye.
http://hiqve.com/