Doward,
is the device gone?
Aye, sir.
Where's DCI Silva?
She's gone to shower.
And what about her suit -
where's that?
I'm getting rid of it.
No, no, don't do that. I need it.
OK.
OK, good job.
Get Walsh to wash you down.
I can stay if I'm needed, sir.
No, no, no. It's fine. Get washed
down and get out of here.
Come on, arms up.
Might sting a wee bit.
Oh, my God, help!
Help, please!
I'll clean up here.
You go get a hazmat suit and
go and fix our comms wire.
Thank you, sir.
I won't let you down.
Yeah, I don't doubt it.
Best man for the job.
Go on, then.
Help! Ah, ah...
Aargh! Help!
Help!
Fuel To Fire
by Agnes Obel
# Do you want me on your mind?
# Or do you want me to go on?
# I might be yours
as sure as I can say
# Be gone be faraway
# Ooh, ooh, ooh-ooh
# Ooh, ooh, ooh-ooh ooh. #
Sir, they're using sonobuoys
to find us.
More and more are being laid
all the time,
both in front of us and behind us.
They've tried to disable us.
Now they're hunting us.
And we have no intel and no orders
until that comms wire is fixed.
Where's DCI Silva?
Er, she's getting cleaned-up.
Sir, engineer's asking permission to
commence the decontamination?
Tell them to go ahead.
Commencing bleach decontamination of
the missile compartment, all levels.
There's no guarantee it'll work,
sir,
so we'll need to limit access.
EBS masks and a limited exposure
time for anyone who has to go in.
Yes, sir. The coxswain requires
specialist treatment.
He's deteriorating.
Look at those screens.
We still can't send or receive
messages, but even if we could,
we can't signal for
a Casualty Evacuation.
Not until we have a handle on
the tactical situation.
If we don't get him
the drugs he needs,
I don't think he'll survive.
Understood.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
It sounded like he was choking.
Out, out!
It's all right.
I've got you.
OK...
Sir, my eyes were playing up
and so I came to get checked.
Right. Well, there's obviously
nothing we can do now,
so get back on watch
and do the best you can.
Aye, sir.
That's it, nice and easy.
Ben Oakley, I'm arresting you
on suspicion of conspiracy
to murder Jade Antoniak.
You are not obliged to say anything,
but anything you do say will be
noted and may be used in evidence.
Do you understand?
This is you with the GRU officer
known as Peter Ingles.
I don't deny knowing him.
What was your relationship with him?
I'll talk to anyone
who's opposed to nuclear weapons.
He said he wanted Russia
to de-militarise.
Russia can't do that
unless we let go of Trident.
He helped out with some things
that were useful to our operations.
I suggested a few people
he could talk to.
That is it.
You have a photo
on your phone of Ingles
and a member of the Royal Navy.
I'd like you to give us your PIN
so that we can take a look at it.
You've arrested me for something
I didn't do.
And that picture is
private property.
When did you take this photo?
A while ago.
Weeks ago.
Weeks ago? That is odd.
Because this is Jade taking
that exact photograph.
You took a copy of that photo
and then deleted it from her laptop.
Digital forensics are working
on that laptop right now
and they'll be able to
get your phone open.
I need to see that photo you stole.
Now.
I need to be clear with you
about...what happened.
What is your PIN?
4547.
Oh, my God.
Branning.
It's Burke's replacement,
the guy who flew out with Amy.
He's the one who's been
working with Ingles.
Sir?
The police have a name
for the Russian operative.
It's the sonar operator,
Matthew Doward.
I love you.
I'm going be with you...
..for the whole of your life.
I... Mm-hm.
You can't even say it, can you?
Oh...
Come on.
Sir?
I'm picking up banging in the boat.
Banging?
What is...?
Well, that's Morse code.
Where's it coming from?
Somewhere near the bow.
Hey, come on...
Oh, fucking come on!
I can't make it out.
You said it's coming from the bow.
Can you narrow it down?
It's marking stronger
in the lower decks, sir.
Maybe the fore-ends.
All right. I'll go check.
What was that?
Banging.
Sir, may I go off watch?
I'm really not feeling good.
You'll have to wait
until your shift's over.
I'm going to be sick.
OK, Christ... Get out of here.
Sir, the ballast hull valve's open.
High level bilge warnings
from AMS 1, sir..
Ballast hull valve AMS 1 open.
Ship Control, emergency stations.
That's more than a tonne of water
a second coming onto the boat.
How does that end up open?
It's sabotage.
Put guards on all essential systems.
Aye, sir.
Shut bulkhead doors.
Emergency stations,
emergency stations...
Ballast hull valve open AMS 1.
Make the battle short.
Shut bulkhead doors.
117 bulkhead door shut and locked.
Bulkhead shutdown.
117 bulkhead shutdown.
Shit!
No...
Ah... It won't go.
Shit!
Go, go.
Yeah, the ballast hull valve's
been fouled.
Come on! We can't shut it.
No, no, the tank top's off.
It's buggered!
We can't stop the water
flooding the tanks.
This is Commander Fleming
on board HMS Archer.
We've picked up a sound that
may be Vigil in distress.
We have the file ready, sir.
What is that?
It's still being analysed,
but it's below the surface
and it's ongoing.
Five Russian ships have changed
course towards that sound.
If they maintain course,
they'll converge around here.
Carry on.
What else have we got in the area?
The Russians are a lot closer.
Our nearest Type 23 is
30 minutes behind.
What's this?
That's the USS Delaware.
This is an attack on us,
and as our long-standing ally
and under the terms of
the NATO agreement,
I'm requesting your assistance.
To do what?
Delaware's in the area.
Flood them with active sonar
and open the bow-caps.
And how do you think they'll respond
to the Delaware getting ready
to fire torpedoes?
I'm hoping
they'll shit their uniforms.
They believe they're unopposed.
It's our job to change
that perception.
I'll talk to my people.
Thank you.
Sir, we're getting really heavy.
What's our depth now?
200 metres. That's the weight of
the water we're taking on.
Hadlow, what are we looking at?
Valve fully open at 200m depth,
so the water pressure's
about 20 bar.
Unlock the emergency blows.
Sir, I think we've got less
than ten minutes.
After that we'll be too heavy to get
back up, no matter what we do.
Understood.
You're not listening to me!
I loved you.
And I wanted to know you,
and you don't even like that
about me.
Kirsten...
I'm sorry.
Don't go.
Christ!
Oh...
OK.
OK, come on.
Doward...
He's the reason Burke was killed.
To get Doward on the boat.
Christ...
Where's Glover?
He's unconscious.
Can you stand up? Stand up.
Doward will go after him.
Y-you need to tell them,
you need to tell them.
Ship Control, this is Pre...
Their fucking line's dead.
Right, come on. We have to go
through the missile deck.
Come on. On me.
Let's go.
Come on. Let's keep going.
Let's keep going.
Come on.
This area's out of bounds, sir.
You know that.
Doward, I've already reported you.
No, you haven't. I cut the wiring.
What's the point?
You've sunk the boat.
You've killed us all.
Newsome's going to surface this boat
and we're all going to evacuate.
Well, some of us are.
I need you to run now.
You've got to tell them.
Fucking...!
Run! Run now!
Go!
Where is the XO?
Depth? 350 metres.
What if we run the hover?
If we can get it online, it'll help
pump out water, slow our descent?
It's not designed for
anything deeper than 150 metres.
I know, but we do not have
another option.
We are taking on water
in tonnes per second
and pumping it out at tonnes per
minute. We're going to the bottom.
Anderton, initiate the hover.
Hover initiated, sir.
You can't hide in here forever.
That bleach will burn your lungs.
We need to get the spanner
out of that valve!
The bastard's stuck hard!
Ah, open the valve! Full open.
Are you fucking mad?!
Come on, we need to get it loose!
If it gets stuck open,
we'll sink this boat!
Open that fucking valve!
Ship Control.
Ship Control, Walsh here.
Yeah, yeah, comms wire streaming.
Reception starting to come in.
Roger.
The forward bilge tanks
are nearly full.
I need to get that hull valve shut.
Sir, communications fully restored!
We're to contact base immediately,
sir. They advise caution -
a lot of Russian units
closing in on our position.
We can't bloody get back up!
Sir, they're saying
Doward is a Russian spy.
Attention, all stations.
Sonar operator Matthew Doward
is a traitor.
He has sabotaged Vigil.
Apprehend him if you can.
Kill him if you can't. But find him.
Everyone knows what you've done.
Leave her alone!
Shut up. I'll slit her throat.
I'll kill you for this.
Control room, now.
Move now!
Fucking come on!
It's coming, it's coming.
Yeah, got it! The valve, shut it!
Come on!
Get in!
Sir, ballast hull valve is shut.
Sir, we're still dropping.
The hover won't take much more.
They can't cool it fast enough.
We have to give it more time
to pump more water out.
Full ahead. Then on my mark,
full rise on the fore planes,
full rise on the after planes.
Wait for my mark. Full ahead, sir.
Keep your distance.
Sir, the hover motor is smoking.
Keep it running.
Depth? 540 metres.
Ten more metres
and we'll hit crush depth.
Captain...
..the chain of command is changing.
I'm going to give you instructions,
and you're going to execute them
without arguing, or I will slit
this woman's throat.
You understand?
We are going to surface
and make contact with
one of the Russian vessels.
Emergency surface
this submarine now.
Is that an order?
Don't fuck around with me!
Sir, we are still dropping.
545 metres.
All right.
Team, on my mark, execute my orders.
Mark.
Ship Control, do not surface
the submarine.
Come to periscope depth. I will not
give them the satisfaction.
Matthew Doward, I'm arresting you
on suspicion of the murder
of Lieutenant Commander Prentice.
You're not obliged to say anything,
but anything you do say may be noted
and used in evidence.
Do you understand?
Plot their course
over the last hour.
That's where the Delaware
opened her bow caps.
And in response, all
the Russian units have dispersed
from their original positions.
Any more flooding noise? No, sir.
Nothing more.
Well done, everyone.
Get this intel to Vigil.
And if she signals home, I want her
100 miles from anyone
when she does it.
I didn't go through Jade's laptop.
She came to me with the photo.
I recognised Peter.
Did she say why she took it?
Well, she'd seen him
around Dunloch before.
She was convinced he was MI5
and she wanted to make a big story
out of it in the press.
So you told Peter about it
before she could?
No, I...
I told Peter to be more careful
in future, that's all.
I thought that was the end of it.
But then you arranged for them
to meet.
He asked to meet her.
He said he wanted to work with her
like we did,
and that he could tell her
what really happened to Craig Burke.
So what happened at this meeting?
We met at the place
that was arranged.
He was supposed to talk to her...
..but he grabbed her,
dragged her into the water.
I didn't understand
what was happening.
Then he started drowning her.
I just...
I had no idea he was going to do
anything like that.
I ran over.
I would have tried to stop him.
But it was too late.
Did you take her out of the water?
Did you try mouth-to-mouth?
Did you call an ambulance?
I wanted to.
He'd made it look like I was
his accomplice.
You can see that, can't you?
You could have talked to us.
Jade wanted that photograph
out there,
to get rid of the deterrent.
You would have covered it up.
I thought if I could at least do
that... You tried to claim asylum
so that we wouldn't be able
to arrest you for Jade's murder.
You just ran.
So don't play the hero with me.
I tried to do the right thing.
She trusted you...
..and then you sold her out to a man
who you knew to be a Russian spy,
and then you helped them
cover up her murder.
You're going to go to prison
for that for a long time.
Come on.
Hey. Hey!
Hey, it's all good.
They arrested Doward.
The boat's safe.
You're going to be OK.
If he hadn't have heard me
in there...
..I'd have died.
He did his job.
He did it well.
He'd have known that.
What will your report cover?
I'll report my findings
on Jackie, Burke and Doward.
I'll give the Crown Office
the evidence they need
to make their case.
And that's it.
Sir, five minutes
till the helicopter arrives.
Sir, we've treated DCI Silva.
And she'll be monitored
until she's released.
We have stocked up on
atropine and pralidoxime
in case anybody else gets exposed.
Adams is stable,
not likely to get worse.
And Hadlow, Walsh and Kierly, we've
treated for nerve agent exposure,
but they're refusing medevac.
But Vanquish takes over our patrol
in three days.
We can run on a reduced crew.
Sir, with respect, I want to stay.
Me too, sir.
Me too. I'll see it through.
Lieutenant Surgeon,
I shall defer to your judgment.
Well, it's a risk,
but it's only a risk to them.
Carry on, then.
Godspeed, my friend. I'll see you
when we get alongside.
Carry on.
Thank you.
I speak on behalf
of the entire ship's company.
Good luck.
Suspect Matthew Doward
is detained
and requires secure transportation.
Warrant Officer Elliott Glover
needs urgent medical assistance
for nerve gas inhalation.
DCI Amy Silva to be taken
for precautionary assessment.
Welcome home.
Thanks.
Hey, welcome back! How are you?
Good. Erm...
I just want some answers.
MI5 are in. They got your report.
They're ready to have a crack
at Doward.
Do you want to take a look?
Yeah, please.
Maybe you should rest.
No, I really want to see this.
Shall we go through?
Yeah, sure.
Matthew Doward, you are here
because we want answers about the
actions you took on board HMS Vigil.
We have more than enough evidence to
convict from DCI Silva's report...
Are you all right?
..but we'd like your account
of what happened.
What do I get if I help you?
We can talk to the judge
and request a lighter sentence
for your co-operation.
We can put you
somewhere comfortable,
or we can put you in a cage
where you shit in a bucket.
So...
..Jackie Hamilton?
I was told what Jackie
was going to do
in exchange for them
getting her son out.
And the reason that Burke was killed
was because he had the same job
as you?
There's a guy at the Peace Camp -
some old-school CND type.
He told the Russians
to approach Burke.
They went ahead, made an approach...
..but Burke...
..turned them down flat.
So now you've got Burke,
this mouthy wee guy,
knowing crews are being approached
and knowing who Peter Ingles is.
Are you saying that's why
they chose to kill Burke?
It had to be one of
the sonar operators, didn't it,
to get you on board?
But this way, they're getting rid
of someone
who could identify Ingles as well.
You'd have to ask THEM that.
What was the plan
behind the nerve agent?
Jackie Hamilton released
the nerve agent.
She set it off accidentally.
We know that from
DCI Silva's report.
You had threatened her when she
didn't deliver it as you'd ordered.
She opened it
because she didn't trust you
and she wanted to protect the crew.
Your job was to force an evacuation
of the submarine,
with Russian boats standing by
to meet you.
What were you told
would happen next?
Nothing.
A few photographs
and the offer of a tow home.
What?! So he's just...?
He's saying it was just a PR stunt.
We think Russia's aim was
to make the deterrent look bad.
There's a vote coming up
on its funding,
and if questions
were raised about it...
People were killed for that?! No.
But a lot of MPs want Trident gone
but don't want to look soft
on defence. And this...
This would have given them an excuse
to vote against it.
Russia dupes Britain
into scrapping its deterrent -
that's modern warfare.
You seem...relaxed,
given your situation.
I think we all know
how these things work -
one of them for one of me.
And you're confident
Russia want you?
You don't want a trial.
Me giving evidence...
..that's your worst nightmare.
Well, it'll be a closed trial.
And after that, you'll be
kept in isolation -
no visitors, no phone calls,
just you becoming an old man.
We're not going to tell the Russians
that we've got you.
And they're hardly going to come
asking for you, are they?
So, if you think about it...
..you don't really exist.
Why did you decide to work
for Russia?
No comment.
He's a narcissist.
It made him feel special.
Gave him power.
That's all I need to see.
Do you want me to drive you home?
I can take you.
No. I want to see Poppy.
She's missed you.
What?
I dropped her off a present.
It was on your calendar.
Come with me.
To see Poppy?
OK.
What are you going to say
to the press?
You're going to have a hard time
getting MPs to sign off
on new warheads with THIS story
breaking.
I just don't think
they'll vote for it.
Well, that's certainly what
Russia will be hoping.
Are you going to help them?
The Russians tried to bury
this photo.
People were killed to try
and stop this story from coming out.
This was when they had an operative
in the field.
The story's over now.
He's been arrested.
Now a victory for Russia
would be you telling the world
that they managed to get a spy
onboard Vigil.
Which they did! Which they did.
So your argument amounts to, "Please
let the Navy get away with this"?
It's not just about protecting
the Navy, is it?
It's about protecting Britain.
And how exactly does the deterrent
achieve that?
The Cold War is over.
Admiral, there are better ways
to exert our influence
in the world than
the threat of mutual distrust.
Yes, so says China,
so says Russia, so says France.
We all agree. Everyone agrees.
But no-one moves till we all move.
All the more reason for us
to set an example.
And we should start by owning up
to what happened
to the five Scottish trawlermen
who drowned.
Their families deserve some closure.
Or are you going to blame that
on Russia as well?
Of course you will.
I think I need to remind you
of your own actions.
You had photographic evidence
that there was a Russian spy
on board a British
Vanguard Class Submarine...
We had no idea that man
was on Vigil.
..which you choose to hang onto
for political gain
rather than hand it over
to the security services.
Because you would have
covered it up,
just like you did at Port Havers!
We intended to publish
then go straight to the police.
You're talking a matter of hours.
So you say. It doesn't play well,
though, does it? And in this game,
every second counts.
Minutes before that man
was arrested,
he killed one of my officers.
How do you feel about that story
getting out?
I'd like to get this matter
wrapped up today if possible.
I don't see how this benefits anyone
except Russia. But it's up to you.
We'll keep it from the press
this time.
They're ready for you, sir.
We will get nuclear weapons
out of Scotland within my lifetime.
I don't doubt your commitment.
Amy, when I was last here,
Morag and Gordon,
they mentioned the conversations
you've been having about custody,
and they thought that I knew.
But you don't need to say anything.
It's just...
Well, it's just in case
it comes up. They...
They know we're not together now.
OK, I owe you an explanation...
No, you really don't need to...
No, let me just... I want to.
Just let me try.
I got scared.
Why?
I don't know. I just...
Because when it was you and me,
on our own, that was...
Like, I was really happy.
I was happy too.
It's just when we had to be
out in the world...
No. I know, I know. I mean,
I can see how it changed you.
I could see it happen.
Well, it's like you always said.
I have to put everything
in its own little box,
so I just put Poppy in one
and work in another.
And you... I never wanted just
the parts of you that were easy.
Ever.
I know I hurt you, and I'm sorry.
You did hurt me. I just didn't know
how to bring Poppy into this,
not when I had so many questions.
Well, how do you feel now?
You always made it sound so easy
when you said you loved me. Hm.
Aye, well, I don't think
that should be hard.
I find it hard.
But it doesn't mean
that I don't feel it.
I want us to try.
I don't want to go back
to the way things were.
I know... No, I really don't.
I mean, what if you wake up
in 12 months' time
and you're back where you started?
I don't want that to happen.
You know, when I was down there
and I was trapped...
..like, all I could think about
was Poppy...
..and you.
Do you love me?
Yeah.
I love you.
Earlier this month, a Scottish
fishing trawler, the Mhairi Finnea,
went down south of Barra Head,
on the west coast of Scotland.
On examination of the wreck,
we found strong evidence that the
Mhairi Finnea had been dragged down
by a Russian submarine
that snagged her nets.
This submarine was
operating illegally
inside British territorial waters.
We believe the sinking
was probably an accident.
However, this is evidence
of Russian aggression
and Russian incompetence.
I think today has to be
a wake-up call for a lot of people.
We have in this country to be ready
for a new kind of peacekeeping,
on the battlefields of tomorrow,
which will be under the surface
of the sea.
Parliament will shortly be
voting on...
Jade...
..I don't want this world to burn.
And I know you don't want that
either.
I want it safe...
..so we can be in it together.
I got up
early today.
It was still dark, but...
I went down by the side of the loch.
Mum?
I saw the sun come up over the sea
and birds out flying...
..and I thought of how beautiful
this world is...
..and how much I miss
when I'm under the water.
Hey! Hi! Mummy! Hi, darling! Hi!
How are you?
Are you OK? I missed you.
I missed you. I missed you.
And then I thought of you.