..A big fella. He's got a massive
ginger beard.
He's down in the pub all the time!
No.
Oh, how do you not know this guy?
Anyway, see if you see him,
ask him to show you the tattoo.
Yeah, I'm not going to do that,
so you may as well just tell me.
Right, he wants a tattoo
of his girlfriend on his arm.
So, he takes a photo of the two of
them from his mum's place
down to the tattoo parlour.
Now, halfway through the job,
he looks down,
and it's his mum that's getting
tattooed on his arm.
Shut up! No, I swear, mate!
Right, troops, I'm sick of stacking
these fish.
One of yous come and take over.
Louis, you're up, man.
Nice, little shoal under us.
Where's Miller hiding, man?
He's always skiving.
Aye, he'll be sitting on his
phone, the skiver.
What was that?! I don't know.
Check the side.
We're fast!
The wire's tight. Boss, we're stuck!
I said we're fast.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
It won't stop!
Captain, you've got to do
something. Get the bolt-cutters!
Went over the side,
check the red box.
There's cutters in there.
Where is it?
It's jammed, Captain! Cut the wire!
We're caught on something!
Cut the wire before it
pulls us down!
Captain, we're stuck!
Water's coming in.
It's dragging us!
Sir, incoming message from CTF.
Are we close up on the broadcast?
Yes, sir.
Is there no intel signal?
No, nothing, sir.
Mm. Carry on. Pump two tonnes from
M's and O's to C.
We're being dragged under!
Guys, hold on, hold on!
Cut the wire! We can't!
The cutters are gone.
Miller, get up here! Captain!
Get the raft off!
I can't hold on. Give us your hand!
I can't hold on!
Sir, I think I've got something.
Permission to put the sound
on loud-speaker? Go ahead.
What is that?
I think it's a trawler, sir.
We were tracking one.
Yes, but what's happening to it?
Where's Miller?
Get the jackets out!
Did it collide with something?
There's nothing else for miles.
Those are depth implosions.
It's gone down really fast.
Should we go up, sir?
How close was it to us?
Close. I'd say less than a mile.
What kind of size trawler?
Mid-size.
Maybe six crew.
Is it us? No, sir.
And you can't tell me what happened?
It was very sudden.
There's a lot of impact noise.
It's going to take time to
analyse... We don't have time.
Could it have been another
submarine?
If it was, we didn't hear it.
Silent routine.
Revolutions two zero.
Officer of the watch, I have
the submarine.
Ship control, port ten.
Aye, sir, port ten.
Sir, they won't have had time to
radio. It happened too fast.
Face front. Do your job.
We have to go up and help.
Cronin, go and get the coxswain.
Shake Kierly. Aye, sir.
Well, what about the Antares?
A whole crew left to drown.
You are unable to tell me what
happened. Without that information,
I have to prioritise caution.
Sit down. We know there'll be men in
the water up there.
Hey! Hey! Do your fucking job!
You wanted to see me, sir? Yeah,
Coxswain. Get him out of here.
Get Kierly on watch.
She's on her way, sir.
You're going to let them die?
Chief Petty Officer Burke,
obey your orders! And you'll talk to
their wives and kids, eh?
Get Burke out of here.
Come on, out you go. Out you go.
Get him out of here.
Bye, shipwreck.
Kierly, get on this.
Find out what happened, please.
Yes, sir.
What are we doing here?
Back to your bunk and cool off.
# Do you want me on your mind?
# Or do you want me to go on?
# I might be yours
as sure as I can say
# Be gone, be far away
# Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh
# Ooh-ooh-ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh-ooh
# Mm-mm-mm... #
Chief Petty Officer Kierly,
please report to the captain's
quarters.
Chief Petty Officer Kierly, please
report to the captain's quarters.
Sir. Enter.
What have you got on the sinking?
This is the beginning of the event.
That's the trawler's engine
signature - low and steady.
And here,
it looks like an impact caused by
a major hull breach.
But it could also have been
an explosion.
I've only had an hour, sir. This is
going to take... Sir.
I want you and Burke working on this
until you have a definitive answer.
Sir. Shall I shake Burke, sir?
Please.
Get the doctor!
I think he's gone into
cardiac arrest.
Casualty, casualty, casualty!
MC level three, port side.
16 mess. Repeat. Casualty, casualty.
Where is she?
Ah, Christ. What happened? I don't
know. I just found him like that.
Come on, mate!
Come on, Craig!
What's going on?
We found him in cardiac arrest.
How long has he been like this?
Is his chest expanding?
I think he's gone.
Is his airway free? I'll look, do
you want to swap?
Keep going. Keep going.
Do you want to swap? Let me at it.
One and two and three and four.
Come on, man. Come on!
Defib! How long shall we keep going?
That's it, that's it.
One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight...
Prepare to return to periscope
depth. Aye, sir.
Prepare to return to
periscope depth.
Watch Stand Two, prepare to return
to periscope depth.
Cronin, prepare to transmit
a message. Aye, sir.
Amy Silva. Amy, you need to come in
right away.
OK. Have I got time for a shower?
Evening. Amy.
Sir, who else is coming in?
Just you.
Rear Admiral Shaw,
this is DCI Amy Silva.
She's my best detective.
I would even say that to her face.
Well, we'll get straight into it,
if you don't mind.
I have charge of Britain's four
Vanguard-class submarines.
These are the ones with
the nuclear deterrent.
HMS Vigil is one of those boats.
Earlier today, one of her crew
died of a drugs overdose.
What kind of overdose?
They think he snorted heroin.
Snorted it? So is that misadventure
or a deliberate overdose?
All we know is that he was found
dead in his bunk.
Unfortunately, this happened within
British territorial waters,
so we've had to bring it to you.
Yes, it's been the MOD versus
Holyrood all evening.
But the upshot is, the usual
rules apply.
We're to look into it.
When's the submarine due back?
She's not coming back.
At any given moment, one of these
boats is out on active patrol,
ready to fire within 15 minutes.
It's been that way for over
50 years.
We're not going to abandon it
over one man's mistake
and some bureaucratic bullshit.
So, we're to send a detective out
to join HMS Vigil.
Me? You'll be on board
for three days,
finish your paperwork, then they'll
let you off on a raft.
A raft? Yes, it's perfectly safe.
Unless you get hit by a tanker.
What's the dead man's name?
Chief Petty Officer Craig Burke.
These are his service records
and his health records.
Thank you. I'm Lieutenant Commander
Erin Branning.
I'll be the police's
point of contact.
And if I need to interview anyone
under caution, will I fly
a solicitor out to be with
them or...?
Yes, it's a flawed plan, I agree.
Ordinarily, if a crewman died on
board, we'd stow him away
and...get on with it.
But we have our orders.
The crew will, of course,
be told to co-operate.
So, take a look around, see what
his mates knew.
See if there was any bullying going
on... Zero tolerance of bullying
in the Navy. You had problems with
drugs on these submarines before?
We've never had an overdose before.
That's not quite what I asked.
There is no drugs problem on Vigil.
We fly this body out at
the same time.
Get an autopsy done.
We could look into that.
And if I need to speak to
Superintendent Robertson...
Can't call home.
You can receive messages,
but the boat won't signal
unless it's an emergency.
It gives away its position.
Your luggage will need to fit
into this.
It's Silva. L-V-A.
Sorry. Short notice.
No problem.
I'm not going there to assess
the Navy's competence.
How are you with confined spaces?
Amy will get the job done,
don't you worry about that,
Lieutenant Commander Branning.
I don't think they'll be rolling
out the red carpet.
I mean, that's why it had to be you.
You'll be OK?
It's three days.
Yeah, it's fine.
Burke passed a mandatory
drugs test in July.
It just...
..doesn't fit the profile of a user.
No. No.
I'm going to need a junior to speak
to Burke's colleagues and friends.
Someone who can radio me leads.
Aye, that makes sense.
So, I was thinking Kirsten Longacre.
Isn't she doing missing persons?
Yeah, but...
If I can't send messages back,
I'm going to need someone
who knows me,
and I've got a good shorthand
with Kirsten.
OK.
Live from Westminster,
we hear from both sides on
the upcoming
Trident Missile renewal debate,
and the families from the fishing
village Kellan are asking
the coastguard to broaden
the search for a trawler...
So, did you volunteer for this?
The boat went missing off
the coast of Barra Head. No.
Could you have said no?
Well, that didn't come up, so...
It's three days. I can do that.
I used to come out here a lot.
Iain's parents live a few miles
down the road.
What else do you need from me?
Look, anything you can get on Burke.
Any drugs connections.
I've emailed you a police report.
Burke had a fight in a pub
near the base.
There were no charges,
but could be worth looking into.
And, remember, any messages that
you send me
are going to be read by a dozen
people so... So, what?
Nothing erotic, then?
Do you mind staying at my flat
while I'm gone?
Your flat, why? Just for the cat.
You know what she's like
when I'm away.
What the hell is that?
Is that a body?
Oh, shit.
Call it in.
I'm a police officer. I need an
ambulance.
Erm, we're on the road not far from
the Dunloch naval base.
Each Trident missile costs
$66 million and... It's fine!
Sorry. False alarm. Get up now!
Westminster's about to spend
hundreds of millions more
upgrading them...
If someone swerves to avoid you,
they could end up dead. Ow!
Leave her alone! You talk about
killing people -
do you not see the irony there?
Amy? We're going to be late.
Dunloch is in charge of the end
of the world, and they're lying to
us. So speak to your MP.
It's all falling apart, nobody's
doing anything. Here.
You getting run over helps nobody.
Well, it helps me sleep at night!
What about you?
Names, please? DC Kirsten Longacre.
DCI Silva. Amy.
Thanks.
Hello, again. Hey.
Welcome to Dunloch.
If you want to follow me, please.
We need to get you briefed
and into your helicopter
survival suit.
If you're taking your phone on
board,
you need to remove the SIM card.
Yep. Already done it.
Follow me, please.
Look, if you need to tell me
anything and you don't want
to flag it to the Navy, then maybe
just reference
things we've done together.
Like what?
I don't know. Places we've been.
People we know.
DCI Silva, this is Chief Petty
Officer Matthew Doward. Hi. Ma'am.
He'll be flying out with you, to
replace Craig Burke.
If you wait here, I'll just check
they're ready. Thank you.
It's not going to be for long.
Come here.
I'm sorry.
You can't say that now.
They're ready for you.
Wait here.
Let's go!
Fuel feed confidence check.
Cross-feed confirmed.
Hatches and doors, and we're clear
for take-off checks.
Front door is good,
all brakes are off.
We're clear on final.
Have you served on Vigil before?
No. But I've trained with a few
of them.
My usual boat is Virtue.
Much less trouble.
How's that?
No offence, but I'm not really
supposed to be talking to you.
Why not?
Amy, are you ready to rock,
sweetheart?
I think it's going to rain.
Have you got your thermals?
Poppy!
I can't find my hat!
Right, you about ready? Do you know
what I've done with...?
Flask there. OK, let's go. I've done
snacks. OK. No, no, no, no.
Got games. You just need your hat,
which I've found under my coat.
OK. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go!
Roger, this is
Nine November Sierra.
We are at RV point seven-five
degrees, two-two decimal
two-six north. One-one degrees,
zero-one decimal five-seven west.
Relative red two-zero at ten
knots. Over.
We've arrived. Coming up on
RV transfer location.
So, how long do we wait?
RV location two-seven clicks north.
We can stay until fuel's a problem.
Roger, we have visual on boat.
Nine November Sierra, commencing
highline transfer.
Arms up, please!
She's off comm.
Five, four, three, two, steady...
I'm going to take you to
the door. OK.
Listen, do not get caught
under the wire!
And, remember, don't move your arm
or you'll fall out of the harness.
On three, push out and away.
Do not jump up.
On three.
One, two, three! Go!
Line unclipped!
Get down the hatch quickly.
Watch your step!
Keep moving!
Close conning tower, upper lid.
Aye, sir.
Where should I...? Wait there.
DCI Silva. Commander Mark Prentice.
Get your suit off in there. Coxswain
will be along to see you shortly.
Burke's body was meant to be taken
off. Well, too late for that.
Welcome to Vigil.
Officer of the watch,
look out.
Chief Petty Officer Doward
and civilian detective on board.
Conning tower upper lid shut
and clipped.
Conning tower lower lid
shut and clipped.
Alter course, ten degrees to port.
Aye, sir.
Alter course ten degrees to port.
Officer of the watch,
dive the submarine.
Excuse me. Thanks. Sir.
Elliot Glover, coxswain.
Tea? DCI Amy Silva.
Where's Craig Burke? No, thanks.
He's in the, er...
He's in the bomb shop.
Right. Well, I'm going to have
to examine the body.
Right. Well, follow me.
Does this ship have a doctor?
Would you take that for me?
Thank you.
It's a boat.
A submarine's always a boat.
And, yeah, we've Medical Officer
Lieutenant Docherty.
Well, can you have him come
and assist me?
Our Doctor's a "her".
We're eight women, 140 men.
You can help to even things up.
Excuse me.
What's the bomb shop?
It's where we keep the torpedoes.
Oh, you all right? Ow!
If you're not covered in bruises
in the first week,
you're not moving fast enough.
How big is this thing?
It's about the length of two
football pitches and about as tall
as four double-decker buses.
All right, I'm going to need a map.
Here, give me your bag.
I'll take that. Thanks. No worries.
This is the main event.
Know what's in these?
£50 million-worth
of nuclear missiles.
That's the real reason there aren't
many nuclear wars.
Can't afford to replace these.
Lieutenant Docherty, could you mind
assisting DCI Silva?
This is our doctor, our surgeon
and, God help us,
our dentist, if need be, Medical
Officer Lieutenant Tiffany Docherty.
Welcome aboard. How was your flight?
Stay there. Aye, sir.
I got thrown out of an aircraft
with my luggage tied to me.
Still, better than Ryanair.
But you're all right? You're not
injured? What, me? No.
No, I need you to help me
examine Craig Burke.
He was supposed to be flown off.
Right. I'll go get my kit then
and I'll see you down there.
All right. Follow me. This way.
How have the crew been? It's been
tricky, you know,
but they're all professionals,
they've all got a job to do, so...
Mind your head.
How well did you know Craig Burke?
Reasonably. I liked him.
Though it'd been a while since we
served together.
And what do you do?
Coxswain's job is to take care
of people.
Welfare, discipline, morale.
I'm a walking HR department.
Do you think he meant to
kill himself?
Well, he took an overdose,
so it looks like it.
Welcome to the bomb shop.
Where's the body?
Lads.
We could've put him in the galley
freezer, but it's full of food.
The torpedo tube isn't insulated
and sea water's about four degrees,
so the body should still
be in good condition.
Right, now, up top. Nobody in.
Aye, sir.
Go ahead.
Did you do much work on him?
Uh, they'd started doing CPR,
but he was clearly dead.
Who found him?
Engineering Officer Hadlow.
He's new to Vigil.
Been on attack boats up till now.
I'll need to speak to him.
Of course. Do you have a torch?
Will that be admissible as evidence?
It'll further the case.
As for the rest...
..that's up to the courts to decide.
Without a full postmortem,
it's not ideal.
Had he taken any other medication?
I gave him a couple of paracetamol
about an hour before he died.
I ran into him and he said he had
a headache.
Did he present with any other
symptoms
that fit with a drugs overdose?
His pupils were contracted and there
was some spittle round his mouth.
There's a bruise with some bleeding.
It's at the base of his skull.
Did you not see that?
He was dead when I got there.
Airway was clear of obstruction,
paddles failed, CPR failed,
no pulse.
I called it, and they moved him
in here immediately.
Could that have happened when they
pulled him from his bunk?
Yeah, probably cracked a few ribs,
too. Mm-hm. We worked hard.
Did you train in medicine?
I did two years, medical school.
It wasn't for me.
What made you change your mind?
Right, you can put him back.
Can you make sure no-one else can
access the body? Of course.
I need to see the captain.
I'll see if he's available.
No. I need to see him straight away.
Right.
I think Craig Burke may have
been murdered.
But that's absurd.
We found drugs on the body,
with a rolled-up banknote.
I've put them in the safe.
I mean, you can see for yourself.
The heroin looks like the type that
you cook up before injecting.
Heroin's very rarely snorted,
and if it is, they usually use
a finer white powder.
Well, perhaps he didn't know what
he was doing.
After all, he did overdose.
There's powder on the body, and it's
caked around the nostrils,
but there's nothing up inside
the nose.
It looks like it's been rubbed on.
OK, hold on.
There were at least half a dozen
people who tried to help him,
including those people who held
his nose shut
while they were giving him
mouth-to-mouth. So...
Sir, sorry, I agree with you.
I think the idea of murder is...
..is absurd. There's a head injury.
And he complained of a headache
to your doctor
a few hours before he died.
And there's bruising around the jaw.
It's possible that an assault
could've caused a delayed
brain haemorrhage.
That fits with the symptoms that
Lieutenant Docherty observed.
I think the heroin might be someone
trying to cover some things up.
And do you think someone brought
the heroin on board with
all of that in mind?
There's no privacy on this boat.
You can't beat someone to death
in their cabin and get away with it.
Precisely! That's a nine-berth bunk.
I did say there could be
a delay between the assault
and the haemorrhage. If you'd have
flown the body back for an autopsy,
like I requested...
We received no such order.
With all due respect, Captain,
it isn't my job to persuade you.
In my view, this boat is
a crime scene.
You need to return to port so that
we can start a proper enquiry.
I was promised your cooperation.
I take my orders from the Chiefs
of Staff and the Prime Minister.
My duty is to mission,
boat and crew,
and while you are on board
you will obey my orders.
Now, you're with us for three days.
Do your work.
But stay out of our way.
And if I hear the word "murder"
spoken outside this room,
I'll have you confined to quarters.
I can't have that.
Do you understand?
Yeah. Coxswain.
Don't tell me.
You're hungry.
Burke had a fight in a pub.
Do you know anything about that?
If it happens on shore,
then it's none of my business.
I'm just trying to understand
what's going on with him.
When did you last see Burke?
Erm, at the end of his watch.
Where did he go? I'm not sure.
Oh, Adams had a word with him
in the mess.
He's one of our engineers.
He's the guy who gave him CPR.
So, that's who found him?
No, that was, um, Lieutenant Hadlow.
OK, I'll need to speak to
both of them,
and now I need to see Burke's cabin.
That was Burke's bunk.
Is there anywhere else he might have
kept...? Twat!
What the fuck is going on?
Sorry, sir. No offence.
None taken. This is Gary Walsh,
another of our engineers.
This is DCI Silva. She's here just
to look into Burke's death.
Well, there's not much to say,
is there?
He was a druggie and a shite sailor,
and he should've been out the Navy
years ago.
How do you know he was a druggie?
Well, he OD'd for a start! Christ.
Did you see him take drugs?
It's not like he'd be racking up
lines in the mess. OK.
Shall we do this another time?
He's meant to be sleeping.
Is there anything else you need to
see in here?
No, I'm done.
I need to see Adams and Hadlow.
I don't understand why the captain
doesn't want me to look into this.
How are you feeling?
I'm fine. I'm just...
Headache? Yeah, actually.
Yeah, it's the low-oxygen
environment.
Helps slow down fires.
Look, I think you need some rest.
Let me show you to your bunk.
All right. It's an automatic
disciplinary if I step into
the ladies' bunks, so you'll have to
put yourself to bed.
Yours is the top bunk.
Try and get four hours.
Where is she now?
In the ladies' bunk.
What do you think of her?
She's clever.
Once she starts talking to people,
it'll be hard to keep her contained.
Well, I think we need to keep her
on a short lead,
and, um, well, I can sit in on
any interviews.
That's not a bad idea. Mm.
But, Coxswain, I think we'll let you
cover that.
Sir, I really think it should be me
who sits in on...
Those are my orders, XO,
and now I need a word with
the coxswain.
Sir.
I'm not going to saddle her with
that prick for three days.
You'll keep an eye on her,
won't you?
We can't afford a scandal.
No, sir. We can't.
Excuse me!
Can we have a word with you?
Stop!
Hand it over.
Hiya.
Can't you sleep?
No.
It's hard keeping
track of time down here.
Your body clock goes.
Oh, shit.
Oh, it's all right.
You can't lose anything
on a submarine.
Sorry. I didn't bring any spares.
You can't carry your own meds.
What's this for?
I need to know about any medical
conditions.
Anxiety and depression.
What I need is to go for a run.
Yeah, then a dip in the pool.
Listen, if you're struggling,
come and see me.
You wouldn't be the first.
Thanks.
Hi, Jade.
I think we met earlier on the road
to Dunloch.
I'd love to have a wee chat with you
but if you'd like to have
a solicitor present...
I've had my phone call.
I don't need anything else.
OK, then.
So, I gather that you've been
arrested for trespassing onto
Dunloch base? I've been charged with
that before. It's no big deal.
The report says that you were found
in one of the accommodation blocks
and that you had a key on you?
Yeah, they've taken that off me now.
Well, I bet they have. Mm.
Why were you trying to get into
Craig Burke's room?
You've read my statement.
I have read your statement.
Now, what did it say?
It said that he had borrowed a book
from you
and that you went there to get
it back from him.
Tell me, how did you know
each other?
Drank in the same pub.
What, and he just left you a key
to his room, did he?
He's dead anyway,
doesn't really matter.
Who told you he was dead?
Did they tell you HOW he died?
No.
Jade, I'm a police detective.
Now, that is totally separate
from the Navy.
We do not share information
with them.
I'm helping investigate his death.
What, and you know how he died?
I do.
All right. How did he die?
What was your relationship?
He was my boyfriend.
Nobody knew.
Obviously, my friends,
my mates, wouldn't be happy.
Go on, then.
He died of a heroin overdose.
Oh, my God.
Did you know that he used...? What?
He never took heroin!
Addicts often hide, even
from their...
He wasn't an addict!
Are you...? Are you joking?
I spent weekends with him.
We were together every
single second.
He couldn't...
If that's what they're saying...
..then it's the Navy that
killed him. The Na...
Why would you say that? Look at when
the Mhairi Finnea went missing.
The Mhairi Finnea?
You've not read up on that?
No, I haven't.
Everyone knows it's a cover-up.
This is the Navy, yeah?
This is what they do.
This is what they do when they
have a problem.
Oh, my God. Erm...
Fuck. I need to go. Erm...
Can I go now, please? Yes, you can.
DCI Silva,
Chief Petty Officer Adams.
I'd rather we talked in private.
Best you're going to get,
I'm afraid. Adams, sit down.
I've no time for a long one, mate.
Yeah, go on, then.
All right, fella? No, I'm just
a bit under it.
It's all right, though.
What's the question?
I gather you were one of the last
people to see Burke alive?
Yeah. Yeah. I saw him in here.
What time was that?
I don't know exactly.
13.10 maybe? Him and me do the same
watch pattern.
Did the same watch pattern.
Yeah, I got some scran, and then
went and had a kip.
How did he seem? Did you talk?
No. He was a bit off.
If you get a vibe off someone,
you don't push it.
Did anyone else think Burke seemed
a bit off?
Did anyone mention it? Morning.
Hadders said that he'd seen him
on 4 deck.
Asked me how he'd seemed.
Who's Hadders? Hadlow.
Officer. My boss.
Don't tell him Adams calls
him Hadders.
But that's the same person
who found the body? Yeah.
Actually, that was the last time
I saw Burke,
if we're being exact about things.
I went in, tried to help out.
Were you nearby?
Yeah, I was sleeping in the next
bunk space along.
I mean, people don't normally shout
when you're on silent routine,
do they? So, when Hadders shouted,
I was like, bang, awake.
First one to get there.
You saw Burke on this deck?
I, er... I was just...
I was just coming through.
I didn't... I didn't stop
or anything.
But afterwards you asked Adams how
Burke had seemed?
Er, no. No, I don't...
I don't think so.
What time did you see him down here?
12.30, maybe. It was about half an
hour before change of watch.
I didn't stop to talk to him.
And I didn't know him that well.
We never sailed together
or anything.
What was he doing? He was
hanging around.
That's what you do when you're
off watch.
People come down here. It's quiet.
And Burke was definitely off watch?
Yes. He wasn't at his station
and he wasn't in uniform.
He was wearing a green fleece.
Where was he standing, exactly?
There.
Can we get the lights turned down
in here?
Do you still need me?
Yeah. Don't go anywhere.
Control room, it's the coxswain.
Could you get the lights dimmed
on deck 3?
Understood, thank you.
They can only give you
a few minutes.
What's that stuff?
It's called luminol.
Forensics use it to show up any
blood stains.
Is that blood?
I, er... I need to get some
scran now.
Did you see anyone else with Burke?
Write these down. I'll get back
to you later...
No, wait.
When you found his body, what did
you see when you entered the cabin?
I found him in his bunk.
Was his curtain drawn back? No.
I drew it back.
But everyone tells me
how precious sleep is down here.
So, weren't you worried about
waking him up?
I guess, I thought, if he was
asleep...
is that something you've
done before?
Gone into someone's cabin and pulled
their curtain? It's not forbidden.
I have a drill to prep
and I haven't eaten yet.
Write down your questions. I'll
get back to you.
No, sorry, we're not done yet.
You were one of the last people to
see him alive. You're the person who
found his body, and yet you can't
tell me why you went to see him?
I've a tight schedule.
It's change of watch.
I've got to go.
Can't you stop him?
He's an officer. Nothing I can do.
I've looked at the trawler's
sound pattern.
It gets pulled down by the nets.
If you listen to this...
That's the floats on the trawl
banging against something.
It's exactly the same signature
as the audio
you would get from the Antares
sinking. I've cross-referenced it.
Sir, with due respect to Petty
Officer Kierly, that noise
could easily just be the nets
snarling on the trawler as it sinks.
No, it's not.
I'm sure. The trawler gets
pulled down by another sub.
It all fits. And can you classify
the other boat?
Not yet. Message CTF.
We need them to identify that boat.
Aye, sir. Sir.
Captain Newsome, may I speak with
you? It's urgent.
Carry on.
I've found blood and I have
a witness who can put Burke
in the same location.
At least one of your crew members
has a history of violence
involving Burke. Look, you can't
ignore this. You've been told to do
your work without interfering...
I appreciate that your mission
takes priority for you,
but there's a line,
and now we need to message
our superiors.
Where was the blood found?
On one of the missile decks.
Did anything unusual happen on
the day that Burke died?
Was there anything different about
his watch? Yeah.
He snorted heroin. There was
certainly heroin powder
found around his nostrils.
Why were you on silent routine?
Write your report.
We'll send it. Sir?
Two transmissions in one week?
Have your report ready to be sent
within the hour.
Have navigation move the boat out of
the patrol area. Aye, sir.
Cronin, prepare to send a message.
Aye, sir. Thank you.
The police officer's arrived.
Should we give her DCI Silva's
report?
No. That doesn't exist until
the Chiefs of Staff say it does.
Fucking Vigil.
There's going to be some serious
changes on there when she gets back.
Yes, sir.
Hello again.
How can I help you?
I need to message my colleague
on Vigil.
Then I'd like to see Craig Burke's
accommodation.
Most of the families live in
Kirkmouth, but the singletons
all want these. It's a walk to work.
Here we are.
I'm afraid you'll need to
wait outside.
Or I can call you, if that's easier?
Is there a reason?
This is a police investigation.
I'm hardly a member of the public.
I know. But still...
Thank you.
Detective Silva.
Message for you from base.
Thank you.
Slow progress here.
Event at sea.
Could be connected to Burke's death?
Same day. Same area.
Remember my dad's job?
Involves one of those.
What happened is the subject
of my dad's favourite song.
We listened to it when I taught
you Morse.
Dash, dot-dot, dash.
Is an N... No, no.
No, an N is dash-dot.
Dash! Dot-dot, dash.
# On New Year's Eve... #
What is that? Mm! I love this song.
It's my dad's favourite song.
He plays it every time
he gets drunk.
He's from Stornoway.
Oh, it was a terrible tragedy,
affected the whole of the island.
The sinking of the Iolaire.
It's still a big
deal for the trawlermen.
Hey. DCI Silva.
You've been ordered to co-operate,
haven't you? Uh... Yes.
Can you tell me about Burke
and the sinking?
I wasn't there.
I was called to replace him after he
got booted.
You replaced him mid-watch?
Yeah.
I need to know why.
In here.
I have to be at a meeting shortly.
How much longer do you need?
I'm done.
Ready to go.
Anything to report?
No.
Nothing yet.
Thank you.
The day Burke died, a trawler sank.
This is a murder enquiry.
You're obliged to be candid with me.
Be quiet.
Don't accuse me of not being...
I've spoken to Hadlow and Adams.
Burke should still have been on
watch at 12.30.
But Hadlow saw him in
casual clothes.
You dismissed him after you hit
a fishing trawler. Why?
Sit down. Please.
WE didn't hit anyone.
As far as we know, another
submarine did.
Someone sitting right behind us.
Do you understand what that means?
Of course you don't.
You're looking for someone who might
have had a punch-up.
We had an enemy submarine
tracking us,
which oughtn't even be possible.
The entire nuclear deterrent rests
on just three things.
The first, you must have
viable weapons.
And second, your enemy can't ever
know if you'll use them.
Which is why we keep
the letter of last resort
in a safe, inside another safe,
on board this boat.
The final thing is, your enemy
mustn't be able to stop you.
So you stay hidden.
If we've been successfully shadowed
by an enemy submarine,
that is the single most
frightening development
in submarine warfare in my lifetime.
Burke wanted us to go on top to
see if there were any survivors
from the trawler.
The mission required we stay hidden.
I made the right decision.
But we're not at war.
That is an illusion.
We have always been at war.
Emergency stations,
emergency stations, all hands.
Emergency stations, all hands.
Reactor scram, reactor scram,
reduce electrical loads
throughout the submarine. Argh!
Emergency stations, all hands.
What's going on?
The reactor has scrammed.
Repeat, the reactor...
What does that mean? Stay there.
This is not a drill.
Reduce electrical loads throughout
the submarine and report to
ship control.
Thank you.
XO, I have the submarine. Take us up
50 metres.
Up 50 metres. Aye, sir.
Where is she? No-one is allowed to
drive unaccompanied on this base!
Get me the EO.
Full report from engineering.
What's happening? Ship control.
Aye, sir!
Off the top of my head, there's 20
different ways you could kill
Vigil's crew single-handed.
But nobody talks about it.
Not the skipper.
The submarine is in trim, sir.
Not the top brass.
They only want silence.
Status control. Close up!
There's corruption.
And fear.
There's men who are being killed,
and the world's still got no idea.
See, we look like a crew, and that's
all that matters to them.
Not what's underneath.
Can you open the gates, please?
Just wait a minute.
I'm Police Scotland. I'm not
interested in waiting.
I'm heading home.
Open the gates, please.
Just wait a minute, please.
I've had some of them come at me.
They'll come at me again.
I know that.
EO, situation report. Captain,
I have no idea what caused it.
It's a complete reactor shutdown.
EO, we need that propulsion to keep
us at depth. Yes, sir. I know.
XO, sitrep.
Reactor scram. No power to the main
engines, sir.
Amy, hold on.
But if they've left me dead,
under two miles of water,
well, here I am.
And I've got things to tell you.