Know what photokeratitis is?
How about flash blindness?
The same thing, really.
Both caused by excessive
exposure to ultraviolet light.
Cornea burns,
unable to handle the light's intensity.
And you temporarily
lose your vision.
In theory,
pain is only psychological
since the retina has
no pain receptors.
This particular model was
built by Homeland Security
to torture prisoners after 9/11.
Unfortunately, it was banned
after some of those
fuckers went blind for good.
Let me the fuck out!
Or I'll fucking kill you!
Motherfucker,
I will fucking kill you!
Thank you.
Hey, Bunker.
Doctor says you're
gonna be all right.
Hey. Hey, hey.
It's okay. It's okay.
You're safe. Look at me.
It's okay.
You have a fever.
Your body is fighting
off the infection.
I'm gonna lift up your head,
okay?
Hold it down. That's good. Okay.
That's good.
That's it, swallow.
I'm gonna clean you up a little bit more,
okay?
It's gonna sting.
Do you have any idea
what you're even doing?
You're still breathing,
aren't you?
You.
You gonna invite us in?
Colonel Stowe may
have been crazy,
but he was still military
and kept meticulous records.
After Genoa,
CID seized his files.
I tried everything I could
to get my hands on them,
but I kept hitting brick walls.
So, then she came back to you?
Y'all know busting through
walls is my specialty.
Okay, so,
then you stole the Genoa files from CID?
Don't need to steal when you
got the power of persuasion.
Took a little longer
than I would have liked.
Finally got to the right
record clerk in the Pentagon.
In exchange for me
not chopping off his dick,
he graciously supplied
me with a copy of the files.
There was a list of everyone
working on the base that day.
So, you compared it to the
list of casualties?
One name was unaccounted for.
Private contractor
named Leo Fitzpatrick.
I'm guessing you know
how to find this Leo?
Of course, soldier boy.
I've never been
on my own before.
You're not on your own.
Sir?
Nina Cruz.
Send her in.
- Mr. Mayor.
- What is it, Deputy?
The last three guys your
district attorney cut loose
were all royally
fucked up after the fact.
- Vigilante?
- I think it's more than that.
See,
all three releases were connected to you.
Whoever the vigilante is,
they know you've got the DA in your pocket.
Someone's sending you a message.
Sheriff Lotus.
What do you think, Deputy?
I think Brock makes a lot of noise,
but he'd never come after you like that.
Then get me a name.
It could get messy.
Then you'll clean it up.
You hired me to be
your eyes and your ears.
I don't mind doing the cleaning,
but that costs more.
Then you better be worth it.
Sheriff?
Helen,
the damn Internet is broken again.
I'll take a look.
The Bowmans are here to see you.
Oh, shit.
- Shall I bring them upstairs?
- Uh, no. No, I'll do it.
Try to fix this.
- Mr. and Mrs. Bowman.
- Sheriff.
Would you like to come
up to my office and talk?
The county coroner won't
release Rebecca's body to us.
Uh, yes, that's true.
Unfortunately,
the body can't be released
until the coroner has determined
an official cause of death.
The funeral must
be held immediately.
- I understand.
- This is our way.
It's... It's been a week
since our daughter's passing.
I know,
and I assure you my entire department
is working day and night
on your daughter's case.
You have no right
to keep her from us.
- Mrs. Bowman...
- Please, let us put her to rest.
Um...
All right,
let me make some calls.
I'll try to move things along,
okay?
I promise.
Come. Let's go.
Again, I'm sorry for your loss.
With technology crossing
cultural boundaries,
computer ethics are
virtually intractable.
Why?
Well, how can we set a global standard
when cultural relativism
makes it impossible?
And by "we", I mean" thew.
And by "they",
I mean the United States government.
But what they can do is enforce title 18,
section 1030.
If you are caught
accessing a computer
with intent to steal information or
damage a network, you will go to jail.
And when you're out, you'll get a
six-figure gig as a security analyst.
That's it. Go home.
I'll see you all next week.
Hey.
That's great.
Go to the next station!
Please stand clear of the doors.
- I'm on the train.
- Copy. I'm on the move.
Next stop, Wallace Street.
What the fuck, bro?
Asshole.
Move!
- He's on the train.
- Copy.
Hey!
Whoa, whoa.
Move!
About time, soldier boy.
Just get him in the car!
Get the fuck in the car!
Come on,
get the fuck in the car!
- Yeah, got him.
- Jesus fucking Christ, come on!
- Hi, Kurt.
- Maggie.
I heard you were back.
What are you doing here?
I brought you some groceries.
Why?
I don't see anyone else
lining up to help you out.
I don't need any help.
Yeah, of course you don't.
Are you gonna let me in?
Yeah. Yeah.
I haven't, uh,
had time to go through my mail yet.
I called the hospital every
week to check on you.
No one told me.
I asked them not to.
I know that it was Calvin and
his goons that did that to you.
Why didn't you report them?
That you asking or Calvin?
Don't be an asshole.
You know
he'd kill me if he knew I was here.
I want to kill him for
what he did to you.
It's just amazing how
two brothers can be so different
and so alike at the same time.
I have to get home.
- My cell.
- If you need anything.
- Shit. Shit. Shit.
- What?
Calvin.
What the fuck?
Where the fuck are you?
I can't do this, Kurt.
I know.
It's not always gonna be like this.
You think you can
still get him out?
No, I don't. I did.
But after this...
I know there's no
coming back for him.
I just need to figure
out how to put him away.
That's gonna take some time.
Time's not gonna change anything,
Kurt.
What do you want me to do?
Just kill him now.
I can't kill my own brother.
He's Hank's father.
Kurt, when I was a little girl,
my father poisoned me with fear.
He made sure that I
would only ever feel safe
If I was with a
man just like him.
And I just accepted that.
That that's how things would always be.
And then you came back.
For the first time in my life,
I thought things could be different.
But this isn't about me.
I'm terrified that my son is
gonna turn out to be just like Calvin
and just like my father.
Mean, hateful, violent.
I won't let that happen.
You have to trust me, Maggie.
I assume there's a good reason
why this son of a bitch is still breathing.
Hey, Leo.
Jesus Fuck!
Where's Job?
What?
Where the fuck is Job?
I don't know who that is.
Tell me another lie. Please?
See how this works?
Every time you bullshit us,
she's gonna hit you.
When she gets tired,
I'm gonna start.
She hits hard.
I hit harder.
You understand?
You took our friend.
And we want him back.
Untie me,
I'll think about helping you.
Stop!
The boy can't talk if he ain't conscious.
Take Nikita to the kitchen.
Give me and Sugar a minute.
Go!
I'm sorry.
You were just doing
what we all wanted to.
It's just,
everybody disappeared all at once,
you know'?
It's all my fault.
Job knew the risks.
We all did.
I'm not talking about Job.
You know,
I spent nearly two years up in those hills
blaming myself for
everything that happened.
Now that would have been a big
waste of time if this was all your fault.
Everything got so fucked up.
Yeah, it did.
Mr. Fitzpatrick has
had a change of heart.
Really?
You always travel with a handsaw?
Tools of the trade, soldier boy.
It would be best for you if
you told them what you told us.
After Genoa, Job was interrogated
for three months straight.
They worked him for names,
dates, everything.
- But he wouldn't give them shit.
- That stubborn motherfucker.
So, they gave up
and they marked him for EDE.
What the hell is that?
Extended detainment
and exploitation.
It's usually reserved
for enemies of the
state who require
some extra motivation.
So, where is he now'?
- Where the fuck is he?
- They're keeping him in a black site.
A supermax hellhole that makes
Abu Ghraib look like the Four Seasons.
- How do we get in there?
- You don't.
- How?
- No one gets in, period.
- Wrong answer, homes.
- Wait! Wait!
No one gets in, but we might be able
to buy him out if you have the cash.
- Cut his fucking foot off.
- No, don't!
The money is not for me!
Look, the government needs
plausible deniability,
so, these places,
they are completely autonomous.
The guys who are running them,
they answer to no one.
Sometimes, they'll deal.
- How much?
- How much do you have?
So much for early retirement.
Job is gonna be really
pissed that we spent it all.
He'll get over it.
Make the call.
Glad you kept it safe
for us all these months.
Yeah,
I was saving it for a rainy day.
I made the deal.
What are you talking about?
Are you sure? The money is here.
I am staring right at it.
But if he dies, you get nothing,
you hear me?
What the fuck just happened?
- Job is scheduled to go dark.
- What the hell does that mean?
It means they have
no further use for him.
- When?
- Unclear.
It could be two days,
it could be two hours.
You want him back alive,
we need to go now.
Okay,
I'm gonna pretend I didn't see that.
You never heard of
the five-second rule?
You finished with
Rebecca Bowman?
Well, she's Y'd and tied,
but it's gonna be some time
before I finish
the full pathology.
No, we are out of time, Dan.
I need to get this girl's
body home to her family.
I hope you're not asking
me to rush the autopsy
for the victim of an
alleged serial killer.
Tell me what you have so far,
then, all right?
What I've got is an
autopsy in progress.
Don't test me Dan.
Don't fucking test me right now.
Jesus Christ, Brock, relax.
Well, puncture wounds
and tearing of the soft tissue
are consistent
with animal bites,
but they were most
likely caused postmortem.
Right, she was already dead when
he dumped her body in the woods.
- We knew that, right?
- Yes.
But she was still alive when he
filleted her chest and cut her heart out.
That's some real
Temple of Doom shit.
So, it is the same
as the other two girls.
Sick son of a bitch.
I'll bet a week's pay
the tox screen will find
similar traces of Valium
and Demerol in her system.
He probably used just
enough to keep her conscious,
but knock the fight out of her.
God damn it, Dan.
Just give me something.
Anything to catch this asshole.
A fingerprint, a DNA, something.
This guy's good, Brock.
He covers his tracks like a pro.
Fuck you!
You've got nothing, then.
Actually,
I've got the opposite of nothing.
Holy shit.
I haven't seen you in here before,
have I?
You don't look like
our usual clientele.
I'll just have a cup of coffee.
Could I help you with something?
- Um, how much for a piece of pie?
- $3.
That's all I got.
How about a cup of coffee?
I'll pay for the pie.
And a glass of milk?
Sure. Whatever you like.
What's your name?
Cherry.
What's your real name?
Jennifer.
Come on in.
Have a look around.
Where are your parents,
Jennifer?
Don't know. Don't care.
You have your own bathroom,
Jacuzzi tub.
There's plenty of fresh towels.
Clothing in the closet.
Should all fit you nicely.
So, help yourself.
Are you gonna fuck me?
I just want you to
feel comfortable,
nothing more.
You must be tired.
I'll let you get some rest.
You can stay as long as you like.
Hey,
whose room is this?
Someone who was
very special to me.
I'm afraid our time together
has come to an end.
Start walking.
Go!
Keep moving.
Easy. Easy.
I got you. I got you.
I got you.
It's about motherfucking time.
Let's get you home.
- What the fuck is this?
- If you have to ask, you already know.
For future reference,
we don't make deals.
Hey.
I was just wondering.
Do I look like the kind of
motherfucker who wouldn't know that?
Get the fuck up!
What do you want to do with him?
Yeah, Job.
What are you gonna do now?
Can we go now'?
Where are you going?
Stay the fuck away from me.
Hmm.
You ungrateful bitch.
I'm sorry. Please don't hurt me.
No.
I gave you freedom!
I gave you a place to stay!
I gave you everything.
But it was never enough, was it?
Man,
you got all the time in the world.
We got two on the gate.
C-block inmates,
prepare for yard detail.
Yard detail in 15 minutes
for all C-block inmates.
Smokes are being X-rayed...
They'll be waiting for
you on the other side.
Thanks,
but what I really need is for...
you to pull your
head out of your ass.
I don't understand.
What the hell were you thinking
shooting porn in Banshee?
- You talked to Proctor.
- He's getting tired of your fuckups.
And so am I.
I saw an opportunity to earn...
You need to get your priorities straight,
boy.
Scrounging for chump change,
that's for niggers and spies.
Why the fuck are we still
answering to this asshole anyway?
We have an army 10
times bigger than his.
Because I say so.
There are some other
reasons I don't want to get into,
but for your purposes,
that's the only one you need.
Do you hear me?
I hear you.
No more fuckups.
No, sir.
Good. Now get the fuck out
of here before I miss lunch.
It's taco Tuesday.
Kai.
I'm sorry, Miriam.
I can't legally do anything to
make them release the body.
Legally?
Since when has legal ever stopped you?
I'll personally bring
Rebecca home to
you as soon as I possibly can,
I promise.
When Rebecca left us,
I prayed that she'd return.
But when you took her in,
I knew that God had
forsaken my prayers.
Her blood is on your hands, Kai.
And for that,
I will never forgive you.
You rescued me
from that hellhole
and the first place you
bring me back is here?
Baby, you heartless.
I think we could all
use another drink.
This is an 18-year-old
bottle of Glenlivet.
I've been saving it
for a special occasion.
Come on, Job. Drink up.
I just need to get some rest.
Then I'm going to grab
my take from Genoa,
head back into the city,
maybe set myself
up with a penthouse.
What?
Somebody better
start talking now.
Buying them off wasn't cheap.
Leo got away with the bag.
How much?
All of it.
So, after all that time,
I got nothing.
You still got your place in the back,
Job.
No, he's not gonna stay in a back room.
You're gonna come stay with me.
I'm gonna take care of you.
The kids are away. It'll be quiet.
And what about Gordon?
I lost track.
Is he in or is he out?
Gordon didn't make it.
Thank you all,
for coming to get me.
Next time,
you can tell me why it took 20 months.
What the hell is this?
Lucas Hood.
You're under arrest for the
murder of Rebecca Bowman.
Brock, is this a joke?
Sir, I'm sorry,
but we have a warrant.
Brock, you know I didn't do it.
Yeah? Then maybe you want
to tell me how...
your blood ended
up inside of her car.
Nothing?
And I'm guessing you have no
idea how you knocked her up either.
What?
Yeah, Bunker, put the cuffs on this man.
Let's go.
Sir.
Okay, wait a minute. This is...
Hey. Cruz, stand down.
I said stand the fuck down.
Let's go. Get him in the car.
It's okay.
Sorry.
So, did I miss anything
while I was gone?