[Boyd] Previously on From.
Ah! Fuck! Just get
this fucking thing off of me.
[Kenny] Pull! Pull!
- Ah!
- Oh! Shit.
- Are you good?
- [stammers] My ankle.
- It's dislocated.
- All right.
- Let's get her back to camp.
- Okay.
[Boyd] I wanna catch one
of those things.
We need to learn about them.
We catch one.
We make it talk.
[buzzing]
[yelping]
- Hey.
- [panting]
Maybe we switch tonight.
- I'll take the bus.
- Why?
Because I wanna
watch our friends
when they come out
of the woods tonight.
We need to build a fort.
Then I'm gonna tell a story.
Are those the crops?
Yeah. We figured
we'd try composting them.
[Tillie]
Whatever's going on,
I promise it'll pass.
Is my baby okay?
Let's see what
the cards have to say.
- [people shouting]
- [bird cawing]
Miranda used to call it
the bottle tree.
The original's
in a park a few towns over.
Miranda made that for me.
This can't be real.
I found this in the diner.
Pull over right now!
- No!
- No, no!
We're going!
[engine roaring]
- [horns honking]
- Ah!
- [smashing]
- [Henry] Ah!
- [siren wailing]
- Where am I?
There's a tree in the middle
of the road.
Unit 4-5. Unit 4-5.
Hospital, do you copy?
Do you copy?
Unit 4-5. Unit 4-5.
Mechanical en route.
[static hissing on radio]
Copy. Copy.
Just getting static.
Where is everyone?
Should be at least a little
traffic this time of day.
Yeah, well, we're not
gonna move it, so...
- [sighing]
- [driver] My God.
Unit 4-5. Do you copy?
- Oh, my God.
- We're 30, 35 out.
We got a tree blocking the road.
Unit 4-5. Do you copy?
Miss, I need you to get
back in the vehicle.
No.
[crows cawing]
Unit 4-5. Unit 4-5. Do...
[cawing continuing]
[cawing louder]
Just take a detour!
Go around it!
Ma'am, let's get back inside.
- It's not gonna work.
- It's okay.
- We'll take another way.
It's okay. It's okay.
[cawing continuing]
- It's all right.
- It's not gonna work!
It'll be okay.
We'll get you back inside.
- You have to listen to me!
- Come on.
[phone rings]
[ring]
[static crackling]
Hello?
[boy] Ethan? It's Thomas.
Mommy's in trouble.
She's in an ambulance.
What ambulance?
You'll see.
She's on her way,
but you have to help her.
You can't be afraid.
[static crackling]
Who is this?
I told you. It's Thomas.
Who is this really?
What is this?
[static crackling]
Who are you talking to?
He says he's Thomas.
[static crackling]
[boy] Hi, Jim.
You leave my children alone.
But they're not
your children anymore.
[slamming]
[grunting]
[phone bell dings]
[Julie] Dad?
What did he say?
Ethan, I need you to talk to me.
That Mom was alive.
She's on an ambulance.
She needs our help.
["Que Sera, Sera (Whatever Will
Be, Will Be)" playing]
♪ When I was just a little boy ♪
♪ I asked my father ♪
♪ "What will I be?" ♪
♪ "Will I be handsome?" ♪
♪ "Will I be rich?" ♪
♪ Here's what he said to me ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ Whatever will be will be ♪
♪ The future's not ours to see ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ What will be will be ♪
♪ Now I have
children of my own ♪
♪ They ask their father ♪
♪ "What will I be?" ♪
♪ "Will I be pretty?" ♪
♪ "Will I be rich?" ♪
♪ I tell them tenderly ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ Whatever will be will be ♪
♪ The future's not ours to see ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ What will be will be ♪
[indistinct chattering
in background]
What are you waiting for?
Pick it up.
You pick it up. I'm not
touching that thing.
[Nicky] It's dead. What are
you worried about?
That bird just went kamikaze
through a plate-glass window
to get in here.
Whatever bad juju
that thing has,
I don't want any part of it.
And by the way,
I don't mean to ask
the obvious question here,
but do you think it's really
smart to do tarot readings
in a place like this?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to...
Hey, that's enough.
We got plenty to worry about
without people
sniping at each other.
Hey, you all right?
I'm good.
You sure?
[pats]
I had no idea things
were so exciting up here.
Open.
You're good.
Look, this really is
not necessary.
Don't be silly.
I make it a point
to examine all my patients
after they've had encounters
with psychotic birds.
Besides, um, it's helping
take my mind off
of Kristi being
out at that lake.
No. They'll be fine.
They've got shelter.
They've got talismans.
- It's all you need.
- I know.
- [tap running]
- But if it was Ellis,
I would be feeling the same way.
Drink.
It's nice to just be
taking care of a pregnant
Mama bear again.
You look much better.
Your color's improved.
You've been eating
a little more?
Yeah. Finally found
something I could keep down.
Great. Get that baby
nice and strong.
Mm.
We used to play in here.
Not at night.
At nighttime,
everyone had to hide.
There were no talismans then.
But during the daytime,
my sister and I would
play inside the houses.
We pretended that
we were home again.
She always liked
this one the best,
and I never knew why.
You came here with your sister?
My mother, too, but they died.
Just like Nathan,
except I didn't murder them.
Is this enough?
Yeah, that's good.
[grunting]
I don't understand what
we're doing.
I told you, I have to remember.
Remember what?
When I was a boy, my mother
tried to save everyone,
but she died.
And then everyone died,
and I can't remember how or why.
And I think I need to
remember soon.
Why?
Too many things are changing.
It's never snowed here before.
We have to go in the basement.
Up here is for daytime stories.
The basement's for secrets.
Hello? Unit 4-5.
How are we still
in the goddamn woods?
We were right outside the city
when we stopped at that tree.
What does the GPS say?
Same thing it said ten minutes
ago... data unavailable.
We gotta be driving in circles.
The woods aren't this deep.
Okay, fine.
I'll turn around.
No, no, no!
Please don't turn around!
Uh, just... just
keep going forward.
- Whoa. Lady, calm down.
- If you turn around,
you'll be driving
away from town!
What town?
We're looking for the highway.
I know, I know, but, uh...
you have to listen to me.
It's, uh...
It's not safe to stop out here
once it gets dark,
but there's a town up ahead,
and... and people
there can help us.
You just... you just need
to keep going forward, please!
So, you're gonna
watch these things,
get a sense of how
they move and what they do,
and that's gonna what?
Give you some grand insight
into how you're gonna catch one?
Yeah. Something like that.
Yeah. Okay.
I'm sure nothing terrible
is gonna come of that.
Why are you here?
What do you mean?
I said we could switch.
You could be fast asleep by
now in the sheriff's station.
So, why are you here?
That's none of your business.
What the fuck
do you care, anyway?
'Cause if I gotta stand here
all night and listen to you,
I'd at least like
to know why that is.
Look, if you're
gonna do something
that has even
the slightest chance
of getting us
the hell out of here,
no matter how stupid
or ill-advised
that thing might be...
then I wanna help.
Oh. So, now, all of a sudden,
you're a team player.
If you'd seen
the things I've seen,
then you might be, too.
What are you talking about,
seen the things you've seen?
What do you think
I'm talking about, Boyd?
Me, Julie, Marielle,
wherever we were.
Everybody here just talks about
how afraid they are of dying.
Well, I don't think
that's the worst thing
that can happen to you here.
I want out.
[fire crackling]
[pencil scribbling]
[groaning softly]
You should get some sleep.
Tomorrow's gonna be a long day.
Sorry.
Did I wake you up?
No. The, uh, throbbing pain
in my ankle did.
Is there anything I can
do to help make it better?
[groaning]
No, not until, uh, some
of the swelling goes down.
What are you writing?
It's just, uh,
something for my mom.
In Chinese culture,
we write letters to the dead
on high holidays.
It's not really a holiday,
I guess, but...
I think she'd really like that.
Yep.
I meant what I said earlier.
You're not alone here.
Things are different now.
That's all.
Yeah.
It just feels like
all of a sudden...
...everything that I thought
I was fighting for is gone.
And everything that I thought
I was going home to.
And the two people that
I would talk to about that
are you and Mom.
You can still talk to me.
[Jade] Could you maybe
talk in the morning?
Sorry.
[sighs] Fuck it.
[grunts] I'm awake.
Hey.
[groaning]
You guys wanna hear
something crazy?
The night everyone died,
I was in the root cellar.
My mother told Eloise and I
to hide there.
Eloise didn't listen.
But I did.
I stayed until morning.
And when I came out,
there were bodies everywhere.
That was the day that
I met the boy in white.
You know the boy in white?
He's my friend.
He was my only friend all
those years that I was alone.
[creaking]
Couldn't bury them all.
They were just lying there
in the street,
and I... I couldn't bury them.
So the boy in white told me
to gather things that were
precious to them.
To bury those instead.
This stuff...
that'll help you remember
why it happened?
I think so.
Why are we in here?
Because it's a fort.
Why do you need me?
Because I don't want
to do this alone.
I may have to remember
some scary things.
And you're the scariest
person here,
so it won't scare you.
You always this fidgety?
Something's wrong.
Those things should be
all over the place by now.
Really?
These things give
"creature of habit"
a whole new goddamn meaning.
The one in the nurse's uniform?
I'm her first stop every night,
every single night.
She just stands by the glass,
and she hums.
For about ten minutes,
she just stands,
taps on the glass
with her fucking smile.
And there's another one, right?
Likes to sit over there
by the swing.
- Okay.
- Just letting its legs dangle.
There's another couple like
to sit over there
by the pool, just...
Well, you really
watch these things closely.
Yeah, well, there's no TV.
Plus, you guys get to
draw the shades at night.
I got...
Look. The point is,
they got patterns, routines,
all of which should be
happening right now.
Right now.
Ma'am, you're
not making any sense.
I know this road!
There's a town up ahead.
The people there can help us
find the highway again.
- Okay.
- I promise you.
We just need to keep
going that way.
We're... we're here!
The barn is here!
- We're... Stop! Stop here!
- Lady, we're fine, okay?
We're not gonna stop
in the middle of nowhere.
Fuck.
[vehicle approaching]
Oh, shit. What the...
What the fuck?
It's an ambulance,
just like he said!
Hey!
Mom!
Oh, no, no.
Hey, hey, hey!
- [Jim] Get in here!
- I got him.
- [Jim] Hey!
- [Ethan] No!
- [Boyd] Got him.
- No!
- Let's get back inside.
- No! Mom!
You need to stop.
Please stop.
Look, lady. I'm not gonna
tell you again, okay?
Shit.
- What's wrong?
- We got a body in the road.
What if Mom's really out there?
- What's he talking about?
- Uh...
The voice on the phone said
she'd be on an ambulance.
There's somebody lying
in the middle of the road.
No. It's not
a fucking person!
- Hey! Hey!
- Jesus! Hey!
- That is not a fucking person!
- Okay!
We're just gonna calm down, okay?
- No, no, no!
- Go ahead. I got this.
You are not fucking
listening to me.
Where are you going?
Don't go.
- Please don't fucking go!
- Ma'am!
- [officer] Move!
- Ma'am! Ma'am! Ma'am.
- You're gonna fucking die!
- Okay. You need to calm down!
You need to fucking calm down!
They're gonna die!
They're gonna fucking die!
- Jesus.
- Oh, my God.
Ma'am, can you hear me?
- Okay.
- Here. Help me roll her over.
Come on.
Watch her head.
I'm not getting a pulse.
Hey, guys!
Lady's really freaking out
back here.
What the...
- [screeching]
- Aah!
[screeching]
[grunting]
[choking]
Oh, my God!
Aah!
[groaning]
[screeching]
Back up!
[firing shot]
[gun firing twice]
- Okay.
- [Julie] Those were gunshots!
Which means those things are
already out there.
[panting]
Oh, my God. Henry?
- [groaning] What?
- It's okay.
- What?
- We're okay.
If there's even a chance
my wife is out there...
You do what you want.
Okay. Listen.
You gotta stay inside.
Whoever's on that ambulance,
you'll be putting them
in danger if we have to worry
about you, okay?
I need you to
tell me you understand.
- I understand.
- Julie?
Yeah.
We are in real danger right now.
There are things in this town
that will hurt us
if we don't get inside
one of the houses.
- [creature screeching]
- [gasping]
- Ah!
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God!
Oh, mother of God!
- Oh, my God!
- Oh!
Oh, my God! Jim! Jim!
Tabitha.
Help me! Help me!
Please help me, baby!
- Please help us!
- Are there keys?
I don't know! I don't know!
I don't know where they are!
Everybody, out of
the ambulance, now!
Ah!
- Jesus.
- What the fuck?
- Handcuffs.
- What?
You have handcuffs.
Hand me the keys.
I... I... I don't
have them. I... No...
There's a toolkit
on the bus. I got it.
- No! Wait, wait!
- Got it!
All right!
Stay, stay, stay!
- [clanging]
- Runner on the hill!
Runner on the hill!
- [clanging continuing]
- [people talking excitedly]
[panting]
- [firing gun]
- [screeching]
- I think it's a cop.
- [creature screeching]
- What the fuck? [panting]
[firing gun]
[creature screeching]
- [firing gun]
- [glass shattering]
- Ah!
- [people screaming]
- [woman] What was that?
- Nicky's been shot!
[Marielle] Excuse me.
Excuse me.
- [Nicky groans]
- [Ellis] What happened?
- Did she hit her head?
- I don't know.
Get that window boarded up.
Um, here,
get her onto the couch.
- [people shouting]
- [man] Let her have some air.
- [Marielle] Come on.
- All right. All right.
[people chattering]
- [man] Did you see?
- It's Nicky?
Hey, Nicky. I'm Marielle.
I'm gonna help you, okay?
- [man] Easy, easy.
- [Nicky groaning]
Help me roll her onto her side.
Okay. All right.
[Nicky shouting in pain]
Okay. No exit wound.
We need to get this bullet out.
- [rattling, knocking]
- Hey, open up!
- I'm a police officer!
- Hey, move.
- What are you doing?
- [cop] Please! Open the door!
She's a cop. We can't just
leave her out there.
We should wait for Kristi.
Kristi's not back until
tomorrow.
We need to do this now. Hey, I'm
gonna need a lot of things...
uh, tweezers, pliers,
uh, alcohol, and towels.
Okay. Yeah, yeah.
[Nicky shouting in pain]
- [Marielle] I know.
- [Nicky shouting]
- [Marielle] Okay.
- [metal clattering]
[Nicky shouting in pain]
- [Marielle] Yes.
- Oh, my God.
[Nicky shouting in pain]
- Okay.
- [Nicky shouting in pain]
Oh, God. Those things were
coming from everywhere.
- Back off!
- I didn't mean to... No. Listen.
You gotta believe me.
Please, you gotta believe me.
- It must have been a misfire!
- I said back the fuck up!
Oh, God. This isn't real.
This isn't real. This...
this can't be happening.
This isn't real.
- Is there anyone with you?
- What?
- Is there anyone else out there?
- Is she gonna be okay?
How did you get here?
We were in an ambulance.
There was this... this...
this tree.
[insects buzzing]
Where are the...
can't find the fucking keys.
Get the fuck back.
I said get the fuck back!
Oh, sweetie,
it doesn't work that way.
[grunting]
Hey, get back to the bus!
[insects buzzing]
[yelping]
- Hey, Jim!
- Hey. Tools.
- [Jim] Boyd, we got to go.
- [Boyd] Yeah.
[Tabitha] Get something!
Get something!
[Henry groaning]
I can't find the fucking keys!
- Where the...
- Are you looking for these?
Motherfucker! [panting]
- Take them.
- [panting]
We get to keep Randall, though.
- [buzzing]
- [choking, coughing]
Get off me! [grunts]
- [Randall grunting]
- You can't save them all.
Ah! [grunting]
[panting]
[Jim] Boyd, let's go!
We gotta get out of here!
Fuck you! Fuck you!
- Motherfuckers.
- Fuck you!
[engine starts]
Boyd? Boyd, don't you leave me,
you piece of shit!
[creature screeching]
Apply pressure right here.
- [moaning]
- Okay. All right. Good.
- Good. Okay. Good.
- Yeah?
Hey, hey. Are you
sure you've got this?
Yeah. Yeah. I got it.
Sit here.
Hold her legs down.
Okay. Okay. I got it.
- [Marielle] Keep her still.
- [Nicky moaning]
- [Ellis] Come on.
- [Marielle] Okay. Yeah.
- Little sting.
- [Nicky shouting]
I know. I know. I know.
Shit. Okay. Let me see.
- Okay.
- [Marielle] Okay. Let me see.
Bite down. Bite down.
- Hold her very still.
- [Ellis] Come on, Nicky.
- [Marielle] Here we go.
- [Nicky shouting in pain]
- All right. Here we go.
- [shouting]
- I know. I know.
- [Fatima] You got this.
- [Marielle] All right.
- [Fatima] It's okay. It's okay.
[Nicky shouting]
Okay. I think I got it.
Okay.
[Nicky shouting]
Okay. I got it.
Yeah.
Good job.
There's a woman
in the ambulance.
There were two paramedics
outside, and I don't know
where she is, but this is
probably 20 minutes...
It's okay.
- Oh, my God! Yes, yes, yes!
- That's it. That's it.
- Yes! Thank you!
- All right. Can you get up?
- Yes.
- Yeah?
Henry, let's go.
Let's go, Henry.
- And you? Can you walk?
- I think so.
[Henry moaning]
Come on. Come on.
I got you. I got you.
[moaning]
You okay?
[shuts off engine]
- [Boyd] I got him!
- Oh, my God! Hurry!
I got him. I got him. I got him.
I got him. Come here.
- Come here.
- [creature screeching]
I got you. I got you.
Let's go.
[people murmuring quietly]
[Boyd] There you go.
Come on.
[people murmuring excitedly]
- Oh.
- [Boyd] There you go.
- There you go. Close that door.
- [Henry moaning]
[door closes, metal clattering]
[people murmuring]
You okay?
Look.
[people murmuring]
- [man] Bad idea.
- [people murmuring]
Hey, what happened?
Uh, it was a long night.
For everyone, it seems.
[people murmuring]
I fucking told you.
Donna, can we, uh...
Uh, you can. Uh, I'll put you
in a room upstairs.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Come on.
[people murmuring]
That poor girl.
Nicky's gonna be all right.
No. I'm not talking
about Nicky.
I'm talking about Fatima.
That horrible bird.
What if it was a sign?
What's wrong?
Am I awake?
Where are you going?
Help me.
- Please!
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
[chattering in distance]
Can you see anything?
No.
What if they don't come back?
Don't think like that.
They'll come back.
Julie, what happened to you?
What do you mean?
Ever since you fell asleep
and your eyes got all white,
you've been different.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yeah. Yeah. I'm fine.
I don't believe you.
You know I'm not a baby anymore.
You can tell me things.
You wanna know the truth?
I'm really scared.
I saw things that I
don't really understand.
There's things that
I can't even remember.
All I remember
is being more scared
than I've ever been
in my entire life.
And that's the truth.
I haven't told anybody but you.
I'm trying really hard
to be okay.
Can I help?
[chuckles] Hey,
I'm the big sister here.
I'm the one who
takes care of you.
If they don't come back,
it'll just be us.
We have to start taking care
of each other from now on.
They'll come back.
So, the rod was through his eye?
Mm. Well, only when
he was on the tree.
When he walked up to me
with a skull full of blood,
it was just a...
a bloody, empty socket.
- Jesus.
- [Jade sighing]
Yeah. So, that's what
my life's been like lately.
How long has this been
going on for?
The hallucinating?
Pretty much since I got here.
Do you remember that day I took
you down to the root cellar,
told you I saw that
symbol up on the ceiling?
You thought I was crazy?
[sighing]
Tian-Chen saw me in the diner.
I was drawing the symbol over
and over again, losing my mind,
and first, she made me tea.
And then she took me back
into the storage room,
and she, uh...
she pulled out this.
Still have no idea
how she knew it was there.
My mom knew every inch
of that storage room.
[chuckling]
You know, I thought
I was smart enough
to figure this place out, and...
I should have...
Fuck.
She really liked you,
you know? My mom.
I think she tolerated me
more than anything.
[Kenny] No, no, no.
I mean, she really, uh...
She only frowned
at people that she liked.
I mean, the people that
she didn't, she just... ignored.
[chuckles]
[Kristi grunting] Ow.
When you finish that letter,
tell her we all say hi.
[thudding]
- Jesus.
- [whispering] Shh.
It's okay. It's okay.
Shh, shh, shh.
[creaking]
Are you sure those things
you saw today
were hallucinations?
Uh, this belonged
to Mr. Gerber.
He always smelled like onions.
They grow wild in the woods,
so he would pick them
and eat them raw.
[sniffs]
- [rattling]
- Hmm.
Oh. This was from Delores.
She always cried lots.
Mm.
- [grunting]
- What's wrong?
Nothing for Christopher.
Who was Christopher?
He was our friend.
He... he was nice,
but then he started
seeing the symbol,
and then he started
getting scary.
What?
[grunting]
No. This was a mistake. I don't
want to do this anymore.
- Victor.
- No! I said no!
- Victor!
- I said no!
- No, no, no, no!
- Victor!
- No, no!
- Victor! Victor!
- Hey, hey.
- [moaning]
Shh. It's okay.
You don't have to be afraid.
I'm the scariest person
in town, remember?
I know what's missing.
[Christopher in high voice]
Hello, Victor!
His name was Jasper.
I, uh...
I left him.
I just...
I just fucking left.
Oh, my God, Boyd.
You know, I couldn't... I...
I tried to save everybody.
Like, what the fuck
was Tabitha doing
in the back of that
goddamn ambulance? I...
How did she...
Are you sure he...
he's really Victor's father?
Jim, I stood in the house
that Victor grew up in.
Jesus.
His mother, Miranda,
she saw this place
before she even got here.
She had these paintings and...
[sighs]
I think that was the reason
why I was sent there.
The little boy in the tower...
I think he wanted me
to see something,
find something.
[sniffling]
And I tried. [crying]
I just...
I'm so sorry.
Oh, hey, hey, hey. You have
nothing to be sorry about.
You are back, and you are safe.
And that is all that matters.
Okay?
But what if that was
our only chance to go home?
[Nicky shouting in pain]
- Hey.
- [man] Is she all right?
- Oh, shit. Nicky?
- [coughing]
What's wrong with her?
No.
[Fatima]
Oh, my God. What is...
She's bleeding internally.
The bullet must have done
more damage than I...
- Oh, God.
- Nicky, Nicky,
Nicky, stay with me, okay?
You're okay.
Hey, hey, hey.
- Nicky?
- [woman] Come on, Nicky.
Shit.
Come on.
Nicky, stay with me! Nicky?
- [man] No.
- [woman] Oh, no.
Come on. [grunting]
Shit. Come on.
[people murmuring]
Come on. Come on.
[woman] Nicky?
Oh, no.
You see what you've done?
It was an accident.
What's wrong with you,
Officer? Huh?
Something scares you,
you just start shooting, huh?
- Is that right?
- I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
You're sorry, eh?
Come tell Nicky you're sorry!
- Come on now.
- Get the fuck off me!
- Hey!
- Listen!
You come with me
right fucking now!
God! God!
Shut the door.
Look. I'm not really in the
mood for a lecture right now,
so if all we're gonna do...
Hey, Donna?
[sobbing]
Why is this happening?
Why is it just one thing
after another after another?
Why can't they stop?
Why can't they leave us alone?
Um, I don't know.
I don't know.
Oh, Boyd,
I am so fucking scared.
Oh, oh, I'm so fucking scared.
All right.
Jasper belonged to Christopher.
He used to be so much fun.
Christopher would
make us all laugh.
And people didn't
laugh much back then,
so it was very nice
that we could.
But then Christopher
started seeing the symbol,
and he changed.
He didn't make us laugh anymore.
I remember Christopher started
spending more
and more time alone.
And one day...
[dramatic music playing]
♪
[screeches]
Jasper's the one who
can tell us why it happened.
[both grunting softly]
Thanks.
Uh...
I was so mean to her
the other day.
Nah.
Every single person in this
house has been on edge lately.
Yeah, but I just think I'm gonna
sit with her for a little bit.
Yeah. Do you
want me to stay?
No. I think I want to
do this alone.
Okay.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
[kisses]
Okay.
[sighs]
[sniffs]
Better fuckin' days.
- Hear, hear.
- [clinks]
[both groan softly]
[gasping, grunting]
[gasping]
♪