(SOPRANOS THEME SONG)
(SILVIO) Get out of the way.
Remember to say please.
I can't watch this again.
This is the DVD.
This is the advanced bootleg.
These are the alternate takes.
What, are you gonna call Coppola
with ideas on how to fix it?
I do not believe this.
Ho!
Oh, c'mon.
The disc is in there!
You know what scene I love most?
"It was you, Fredo."
Ton', you gonna
go see your uncle first
if you decide to go over there?
Yeah.
That would be smart.
Fucking disc!
Somebody should tell
Paramount Pictures
to get their shit together.
We're gonna be stealing
thousands more of these things.
So, how was junior
last time you saw him?
His life is about
Motrin these days.
Ton', what's your
favorite scene?
I can't have this
conversation again.
Hit eject!
Don Ciccio's villa,
when Vito goes back to Sicily.
The crickets,
the great old house.
Oh, it's fucking beautiful.
Maybe 'cause I'm going
over there, you know?
I was in the Army Signal Corp.
What this thing needs is what we call
a "brogan adjustment."
What's that, you know how?
Yep.
(BIG PUSSY LAUGHING)
(RADIO ANNOUNCER)
This is "1010 wins".
You give us 22 minutes,
we'll give you the world.
(MALE) Temperatures are expected
to drop tomorrow
after another scorching
day in the city.
Right now it's 96 degrees
at Caldwell,
LaGuardia's 94,
and it's 98 in Central Park
and on the Upper East Side...
Great.
It's like this every Sunday
and every Sunday
you say "Great,"
like it's the first time.
Could we please lower
the air conditioning?
I'm doing it for godsake!
I just got this car.
I'm not familiar
with the instrument panel.
(MALE) Get up out
the fucking car!
Take the car, take the car!
Get the fuck out the car!
You nasty bitch,
get the fuck out of here!
Smack the shit out of you.
Go!
Okay, okay, okay!
Churchill, Churchill!
Dammit, man.
Sic 'em, Churchill!
Evan, no!
C'mon, Churchill.
Churchill.
Fucking niggers.
Barry!
Who else, huh?
Who else?!
(PHONE RINGING)
(FEMALE) West Essex
Orthopedic Group.
Mr. Soprano?
Okay if my nephew comes in?
He's got some questions for the doc
about my hip and all.
Of course.
The doctor will be
right with you.
Perhaps your nephew can
help you with your clothes.
You want some help?
I'm not gonna take my pants off
until I know this prick
is gonna X-ray me again.
Hurts like the fucking
Pit and the Pendulum
just to wipe myself.
So what do you
want to talk about?
Going over to the other side.
See that friend of ours
over there.
My car operation.
Lose the miserable puss,
it's mine now.
What's your question?
Our friend, what's
he like to deal with?
What's he like?
Yeah.
I only met him one time.
He came over on
The Michelangelo, 1961.
Now, that was traveling.
The fucking Italian line.
The food, the service,
are you kidding me?
We had some bon voyage
parties on that boat.
He's a serious man, Zi Vittorio.
Serious how?
You know what I mean.
Heads up, sonny boy.
He don't listen to opera,
Vittorio,
which is a fucking break.
Isn't he like
a distant cousin of ours?
It's so far removed by now,
Tonto's a closer cousin to you.
We deal with him through
a guy named Furio Giunta,
he speaks English.
Going to Italy, huh?
Yeah.
Nice, I never went.
It's not over yet.
And we don't get to go?
You got school.
What about mom?
She knows it's a business trip.
Don't you think she might
like a little interlude,
just the two of you?
You know when we'd like
a little interlude, just the two of us?
Right now.
Not my idea to have me
set the table.
Carm, you want me
to help with the roast?
(CARMELA) it's right there
on the counter.
Carm, it's a business trip.
Okay? It is,
it's not worth the jet lag.
Did I say anything?
God!
Naples,
Ischia and Capri.
And, oh, the food.
(SILVERWARE DROPS)
Shit.
Look, I know last year, Tom and Barb,
the trip to the Bahamas,
I said I didn't have time.
You didn't.
It was football season.
Meadow, can you tell
your brother dinner's ready?
It's our busiest months.
Junior's last shipment went
to Naples two months ago.
Thirty containers,
two cars to a container.
Junior had to give the operation
over to who, specifically?
Ray Curto.
Okay, good work, Sal.
There's something else
you should know.
They're talking like the Moltisanti
kid might get his button.
Tony, where's he at
with Junior these days?
They ain't spoke in months.
Are you bein' straight with me?
Oh, Pussy!
What the fuck?
How's it going, colonel?
How you doing, Jimmy?
What'd I hear,
you were in Puerto Rico?
I was playing there once
during the hurricanes,
never again, I said.
Jimmy, let me introduce you
to a friend of ours.
This is Joey from Dover,
Delaware.
No shit!
I live in Dover, here, Jersey.
That's right, I forgot.
Joey, know where they got
the name Dover from?
The cliffs, I'm assuming.
That's right, very good.
Jimmy, does it fucking matter?
Joey, I knew this guy
when he had social graces.
It's for Marisa's oldest's
sixth birthday.
The kids are all grown, aren't they, Puss,
what are ya doin' here?
It's my daughter's birthday.
I'm picking up some shit
for a bachelor party.
I'm trying to think.
Did I ever meet any connected guys
from Delaware?
That fucking box looks heavy.
The answer is...
No, no, no.
Alright look,
I got to go, fellows.
Joey.
Nice to meet you.
You, Mr. Rude Cocksucker,
see you around, baby.
Motherfucker, motherfucker!
Take it easy, that went fine.
He saw me with you.
You come all the way
to a fucking party store
and still somebody's
got to see you?
Sal, listen, that went fine.
Just know this,
you're doing a good job.
(ANDREA BOCELLI PLAYING)
You must be so relieved
Pussy is back.
You must be so happy.
Was a long time.
Did he ever tell you
where he was?
Oh, he don't like to worry me.
Not even a card?
That's got to be a worry.
It's horrible.
Anyway, you must be so happy.
We're back to our old routine.
Ah, I love this song.
Mmm.
Oh honey, I know, your Jackie.
Listen to me, going on about
how happy I am and you a widow.
Que sera sera.
What will be will be.
God, he's so handsome,
this guy too.
He's blind, you know.
Jesus Christ!
Angie.
My god. I'm sure
he's adjusted to it.
Christ, you fucking idiot,
Rosalie!
I'm not happy Sal is back.
Angie!
I'm sad and depressed.
I've thought of killing myself.
Fucking nosy?
Eat your monigott'.
God forgive me.
When he did come home that day,
I was upstairs,
I heard the door
and then his voice, "I'm home."
I fucking wanted to vomit.
After all that worrying
he might be dead,
praying he was okay.
My heart just sank,
and I wished...
he had died.
Oh.
To just come and go
year after year like that.
How dare he!
Have you reached out to him?
That's a good one.
Listen,
and I don't want
my kids to know this.
They found a lump under my arm.
Oh my god.
They biopsed it, I get
the results in a couple days.
Anyway, I told Sal,
he said, "Jesus Christ",
kind of alarmed a little.
Then he went back to doin'
whatever the fuck he was doin'.
Spraying WD-40
on his pocket knife.
Hasn't asked me how I am.
Touch my face, or something
when he comes in.
So Angie, what are you gonna do?
Benign, malignant,
I'm getting a divorce.
(ITALIAN OPERA MUSIC
CONTINUES)
Look at this place.
The mother country.
Here, they make it real.
Vesuvius, Jesus, who's gonna tell Artie
that mural he spent that money on
looks like a used Trojan
compared to this?
You notice the women?
Know what I realized
on the plane?
Even the skanks
are worth fucking!
Those were my feelings too.
Paison, tutto gli
whaddya call it...
Are all the women
good-looking like this?
(LAUGHING)
Hey, you did alright.
Two definite agendas I got,
hit the topless beaches
and see that fucking crater.
I don't care what
anybody says, I'm there.
Look at this fucking place.
It's been here a thousand years.
Hey T, check out the bank.
(MALE)
Anthony Soprano.
Yeah.
I'm Furio Giunta.
Hey, how are you?
Pleased to meet you.
This is the friend of ours
Sil and me been talking to.
This is Paulie,
this is Christopher.
This is Tanno.
Welcome.
My boss Nino say
you can fresh up,
maybe little sleep,
then we will
pick you up at eight.
And he will meet us
for fare la business.
Whoa, whoa, wait a minute.
Nino? I mean,
I never heard of...
I'm sure he's a nice guy
and everything.
But Vittorio
will be there, right?
Maybe no.
Commendatori, you are
already checked in.
Commendatori, like a commander,
I like that, that's respect.
So did you hear?
You're talking about
the Bonpenseiros, right?
Hang on, Gab, call waiting.
It may be Tony from Italy.
Hello?
I didn't sleep
a wink last night,
my god, isn't this awful?
Did you tell Franny Altieri?
Ooh no, she's gonna shit
when she hears this.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
What time Christopher
say he'd get here?
He's got that titanium club
I wanted to give to Don V.
Any time now.
He was just going down
to Corso to buy a gift for Adrianna.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
Nino say we always ask
your Uncle for more cars,
but he was no supplier.
That why I'm here.
Tell him we can fill any orders.
And also mention, no offense,
we were hoping
Zi Vittorio would be here.
Anything you want to talk to Vittorio
about that I don't know?
No.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
Nino is a little disappointed
in your attitude of him.
I'm sorry Nino.
I'm sure that I'll learn much,
doing business with a man like you.
It's an honor.
He said...
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
Why is he busting my balls?
Tell him to get to the fucking point.
Nino is happy to be
at your disposal.
My uncle's problem was he went
to the Russians in Brooklyn,
too much for the cars.
Now, they kept the best stuff
for themself,
shipped it off
to St. Petersburg.
Slovenia and Montenegro,
they got people over there that
profited from those conflicts.
They got fuckin'
bails of liquid cash.
You got contacts
in the markets over there.
Ton', you try this octopus yet?
I'm talking here.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
You're like a fucking child.
With the food and the pussy,
what's going on here, Paulie?
This is a big thing to me, T.
I was never over here, okay?
My brother was and my other
brother the doctor was,
with all his bullshit.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
How mucha you charge-a un car?
Mercedes ML series,
very popular.
In Eastern Europe
you can sell this car for 110,
120 thousand.
My price to you, 90 grand.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
It's manufactured in America.
What did he fucking say?
(SILVERWARE DROPPING)
That's Don Vittorio.
You didn't have to leave
your house tonight.
Annalisa, sweetheart,
how are you?
Don Vittorio, allow me to
present our friend from America.
Anthony Soprano.
Don Vittorio, it's an honor.
Wheelchair, aboolebarda!
Think... something's wrong
with the wheelchair.
He say "Wilshire boulevard".
My name is Annalisa.
I am his daughter.
Piacere.
Piacere, Tony.
Psst.
George-a Washington-a, Bridge-a.
Right, very good,
George Washington Bridge.
Let's talk about something else,
and later we'll talk about the streets.
Ton', you give
this guy a golf club,
he'll probably try to fuck it.
(POP SONG PLAYING)
I come three thousand
fucking miles,
you never said nothing
about this guy Nino,
all of a sudden
he's my blind date?
Nino was in hide from the
police until two day ago.
I don't even think
Mauro Zucca now he's here.
Who the fuck is Mauro Zucca?
Mauro Zucca run this family.
Obviously, Zi Vittorio.
Then I should be talking
to Mauro Zucca.
Mauro Zucca is serving
a life sentence.
Hey you, come here.
Yes, signore.
Can I just get some
macaroni and gravy?
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
Paulo, he doesn't
know what you says,
you mean grapes?
Uva?
Gravy, gravy, tomato sauce.
He wants spaghetti and tomato sauce.
He doesn't like this.
And you thought the Germans
were classless pieces of shit.
Nino, he's insecure.
It effects everything
he says, capice?
I will talk on the side
to the ear of Annalisa.
What the fuck good
is that gonna do?
She is the wife of Mauro Zucca.
Camillo, where's the pisciadood?
Down the stairs, go left.
Ma-jor-digan expressa-way.
Right, Major Deegan Expressway.
I'm sorry if he's hassle you.
You spend a lot
of time in the states?
Papa went, I never been,
English from school,
e filmsa.
When could we get
a chance to talk?
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
Come to our house, stay a while.
I will personally give you
a tour of the... Surroundings area.
Avellino?
Where your family's from.
I don't want to put you out.
No, you should have
been guest to our house.
But with my father
condition now.
I send you the car at nine?
Fine.
Ton'.
I look forward to it, excuse me.
I'm gonna hoof it back
to the excelsior.
I got to take a wicked shit.
Can you stop fucking
interrupting me?
We've been offered a ride here,
you know how these people
are about formalities,
why didn't you use
the one in there?
I didn't have to go then.
(FIRECRACKERS GOING OFF)
He's all right
It's only firecrackers.
It's just a kid.
No, please, he's my son!
Please don't hurt him!
The kid only got
firecrackers on him.
I want to work with you guys!
Who told you this was the
way to go about it?
Don't worry.
This is Naples University.
(CARMELA) We're gettin'
ready to eat.
Oh yeah, forgot
it was dinner time for you.
How's Italy?
The time change
and everything, I forgot, sorry.
How's Italy?
Got to be honest with you.
Pretty freaking good.
We'll have to come back here.
Yeah, right.
So how's the food?
It's okay, lots of fish.
Sounds like you're
working too hard.
Why don't you take the kids
down to Great Wall,
get some Chinese?
You know Tony, don't tell me
how to spend my time.
If I want the excitement
of Chinese food,
I don't need your permission.
It's not permission,
it's just an idea.
You know what?
Fine, I'll hang up.
Well if the trip is as bland
as this phone call.
There's nothing going on.
What do you want me
to say to you, seriously?
You better not say
what you saw, Jimmy.
I'll shove that Elvis shit
right up your ass.
I'll shove a rutabaga
in your mouth Jimmy.
Keep you quiet.
A turnip in there.
Sal!
You're having a nightmare.
(YELLING IN ITALIAN)
I think it was the fuckin' shrimp
hor's d'oeuvres on the plane.
Get some Immodium.
You want to get made,
this is no fucking way.
Tony wants us to hang with Nino,
work out the dock facilities.
I hope we get some spare time.
I'm gonna see
that fuckin' volcano.
(BACKGROUND MUSIC)
(RAP MUSIC PLAYING)
Oh, ho, gratzie.
(WOMAN)
Vincenzo, turn off that radio!
Did you hear me?
(SOUND OF KIDS PLAYING)
(ITALIAN OPERA PLAYING)
Hey.
(ANDREA BOCELLI PLAYING)
This song, Jesus.
Listen, I've been
to Italy many times
and really, you're not
missing all that much.
The amount of sexual harassment
that I was subjected to.
I went one time
with my friend Zane.
Her, they didn't bother,
me, they couldn't keep
their hands to themselves.
Much less the whistling
and the fucking hooting.
It's not Italy.
Do you remember
Angie Bonpensiero?
Angie Belfiore
married Sal Bonpensiero.
Right, she's thinking
of divorcing him.
Halle-fucking-lujeh!
Do you know them?
No I don't know them, but to be
married to a man like that.
A man like what?
The 'tude and the fucking
medieval outlook.
He is such an adoring
father though.
Three beautiful kids
they raised,
who are now from a broken home.
No sons I hope,
three more of his ilk
we don't need.
He's very macho.
Macho, no, try
swaggering mama's boy,
fucking hypocrites, shall we?
Hypocrites?
Carm, come on stop.
Just stop.
Is that how you
see your brother?
I thought we were
talking about Angie.
I mean these OC
pricks especially,
with their goomahs and their
prostitutes, emotional cripples.
And they expect
their wives to live
like the fucking nuns
at Mt. Carmel college.
It's not that simple.
Of course not.
Madonna/whores is the full
equation I believe.
Clothes, appliances, houses.
You are talking about me.
About us.
Carmella, no.
I don't know.
That a woman
of your intelligence,
is content to ask so little
from life and from herself.
I don't know, it's none
of my business.
Marriage is a holy sacrament.
Okay.
Family is a sacred institution.
Roger.
And you trying to fan the flames
with Richie Aprile,
of all people?
Talk about old school.
Carm, Richie, because of his
life experience in prison,
he has a sensitivity
to the plight of women.
Oh my god!
I am not even
gonna touch that one.
But you had me going
for a while there, you really did.
Oh Janice honey,
I got to love ya.
(CARMELA LAUGHING)
(OPERA MUSIC PLAYING)
Collect the toenails...
(THWACK OF A GOLF BALL)
Nice shot.
I shank him.
It's a man's club.
I'll send you one your size.
Whole set.
So Tony, you don't mind
me calling you Tony?
What can I do for you?
Well you can introduce
me to the boss.
You can talk to me.
A fuckin' woman boss?
So what do you want?
Never happen in the States.
Never.
Our men kill each other.
All my brothers, for example,
they all got murdered.
Or they go to prison.
Rome has a war against us.
But our men are
in love to their mama.
So being a woman is not...
come se dic',
comes natural.
We'll I'll be dipped in shit.
You go around like your
father's nursemaid.
I am my father's nursemaid.
Well if an old man carries
the respect of troops,
you keep him around.
I did something
like that myself.
We're cousins.
You hungry?
I could eat.
So, you wanted
to talk about business.
Can I ask you a question?
We not gonna pay
the price on the Mercedes.
Why do you save your
toenail clippings?
Why, you want them?
If your enemy comes
into possession of your nail,
or your hair clippings,
they can make the evil on you.
I'm flattered you wouldn't
trust me with your toenails,
but can I pass without
ruining the moment?
I already burned them.
Nobody gets them.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
Commendatori.
Bon giorno.
Cocksuckers.
A lot of guys today, they become
soft living in America.
One in five guys,
they're a fucking rat.
You can't find anybody over there
that believes in the old ways,
keeping silent,
putting the family first.
So you want Naples guys.
Fucking clairvoyant over here.
That way I get guys with
no ties to anybody over there,
they belong only to me,
110 percent.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
What?
What do I get?
Well, you get an obvious advantage
to havin' your guys in that end.
How much you
pay me for this man?
Pay you?
Your profitability
is gonna go way up.
What are you thinking?
Furio to start.
Furio!
(YELLING IN ITALIAN)
Back up, take it easy.
I'm going to give you
one of my best men.
And all I get is a bunch
of numbers in air.
With all due respect, hon,
I think you're being
a little short-sighted on this.
He's my cousin,
he's one of my best men.
Forget about it,
it's not going to happen.
I'm asking you nice.
Or what?
Hey look, I don't even
think you understand.
I want you to talk
to your husband about this.
My husband, fuck you!
He is never coming back.
So you have to fucking
deal with me!
Up your ass.
(FOOTSTEPS)
Oh, you're up.
Where's my other belt?
Did you look under the bed?
Fuck, yeah.
I just came from
the doctor's office.
Yeah.
The biopsy came back negative.
Yeah good, I'll be back later.
(GENTLE SOBBING)
(BACKGROUND MUSIC)
(MALE): The 3:32 to Mt. Vesuvius
is now leaving at the side entrance.
(KNOCKING)
Pussy.
Yeah.
What the fuck you doing here?
I was in the neighborhood.
That bachelor party, they're looking
for some entertainment.
A sett', you want coffee?
Nah, I'm good.
C'mon, it's on the boil.
(TEAPOT WHISTLING)
(KNOCKING)
Yeah.
Boss say to tell you one hour,
manigamo, dinner.
Manigamo, I want to get
the fuck out of here.
You drive me to the city?
Sure, absolutely.
I have to ask.
What's it like,
working for a woman?
Whaddya gonna do?
A woman boss!
In America you don't have?
No.
What?
Ayy! Tony!
Tony!
Yeah, come down to eat.
Jesus Christ, is that
all your people do?
The lunch we had
would jam a wood chipper.
We need to finish our business.
I said all I'm gonna say.
Alright, I'm coming down.
(DOOR SLAMMING)
(FEMALE)
Vincenzo!
(BARKING)
Have some Amaro.
Indigestion, right?
Cheers.
So what is this place?
My father was born
in this house.
Later we make the new one.
You're born here, and your
kids are raised next door.
That's a nice thing.
You take good care
of your father.
What are you going do,
send him to a ospizio?
Hey, listen...
(SOMETHING DROPPING
ON THE GROUND)
(YELLING IN ITALIAN)
This one has to stay
with until he goes to sleep.
I'll take you
back in the morning.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
Goodnight.
It was horrible what he did.
I might as well
have fucking cancer.
So what did
the lawyer say today?
He said I have a good case,
we're filing Tuesday.
So your gonna take Monday
to think, that's good.
Monday's a Jewish holiday.
Oh.
I'm finished thinking.
Hell, I thought myself
into fuckin' nonexistence.
Well, you are not nonexistent,
and Pussy doesn't
see you that way.
Fuck what he sees!
Not anymore, it's what I see.
God gave me more years, Carmela.
This very morning
God gave me a gift,
and I will use that gift.
I won't waste it,
like I wasted 24 fucking
years with this man.
You know what the church
says about divorce.
Oh please, let
the Pope live with him.
Well, what about the kids?
They're 19, 21, and 24,
it's time we all grew up.
Kevin is just starting his
sophomore year at college.
Aren't you worried
he's gonna realize,
the two stayed together
waiting for him to leave?
Long as he don't
loose his privileges
at our house down the shore,
that's all Kevin cares about.
He's so fond of his father,
that's all I'm saying.
And Terry and Scott
with the money problems,
and the pregnancy,
this is really the example
you want to set,
when your daughter
is struggling very hard
to keep her new marriage
in one piece?
Why you workin'
this hard, Carmela?
Why?
For all of the reasons
I just said.
Because you're my friend,
I'm not even sayin' don't.
I'm just sayin'
at the very least,
you got to ask
yourself these questions.
Terri, they're not even sure
she's gonna be able
to have children of her own.
Sal began to cry
when he heard that.
Oh, honey.
In the end, I know
you're not gonna leave him.
I know you won't do that.
(SINGING IN ITALIAN)
Commanders, Good Morning.
Who are you?
I'm from america.
Are you with NATO?
You cut our ski-lift cable.
Hey Cara Mia, on the way back
bring me one of those plums
from the breakfast tray.
Cosa?
Never mind.
I got to hand it to ya.
Great fruit you got here.
Che bella fruti.
None of them fucking steroids.
Come se dic', steroids?
Steroide.
There ya go.
Who said you're not
a great conversationalist?
Ya fuckin' twat.
There's my little fragolin'.
Ah-ah.
Ah.
Hey, the customer
is always right.
Did I say you should leave?
You know my grandfather was
Napoletan', gran-pappa mio.
He went to America in 1910.
Three thousand miles.
Just a little boy.
All by himself.
Yep, I'm Napoletan'.
Me and Tony both.
Some of the guys are Sigilian'.
Sigilian', se.
Hard-headed bastards,
am I right?
So, what part
of Naples you from?
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
It's right over there.
Ariani el pino?
Your shitting me!
That's where
my grandfather's from!
It's right over there.
We come from the same town.
Our families probably
knew each other.
The island back there
is called Progeda.
Madonn', look at this.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
Got to bring my kids back here.
Show 'em all this.
In the olden time
the Sibylla of Cumae
was the second most
important oracle after Delphi.
I thought Delphi was in Greece.
The Greeks were here.
Way before the Romans,
and before the Greeks
there were somebody else,
and before them somebody else.
"The rulers would come from
across the ancient world,
"to hear the Sibyl's
predictions of their future.
She would sit inside
the cave inhaling gases."
I think I dated this broad.
"Possibly volcanic
though no longer active,
"and would speak
in a voice not her own,
delivering unto them
their fates."
Let's go into the cave.
The Sibyl sat way back there,
see that shaft of light?
Some fucking trip.
The Sibyl were very beautiful,
in most case.
Oh yeah, got
a premonition for me?
You, you're no problem to read.
You are your own worst enemy.
Oh, is that right?
Tell you right now you remind me
of somebody from back home.
Not your wife, your girlfriend?
Oh, I got one,
to answer your question.
But no, not her.
But, she's someone
you want to fuck.
I can tell.
Oh really.
You know, everybody's
their own worst enemy.
So maybe your psychic power
has been overrated a little bit.
You don't want to fuck her?
You don't want to fuck me?
Yeah, I do.
But I don't shit where I eat.
Que cosa?
Non fare la merdo dove...
It's bad business,
we're in business.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
Not at those price.
Alright.
You give me Furio
and I'll work down
the price of the cars to 85.
Posto, okay.
I get more guys,
on my timetable.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
75 thousand.
Okay.
Hey, thanks!
So, how the fuck was it?
Fabulous, I felt right at home.
That's great.
Real good business-wise.
I feel sorry for anyone
who hasn't been.
Especially any Italians.
Someday.
Don't put it off
another second, Pus.
Alright, I fucking heard you.
Where the fuck is Christopher?
He's in the duty free
buying a gift for Ade.
Four days, he's a block away from the
greatest shopping district in the world.
Why the fuck didn't
he think of it then?
(PAULIE)
A broad.
He found out who got eight great
tomatoes in that little bitty can.
Oh fuck him, leave him here.
Go, let's drive.
What's the matter, Tony?
Nothin'.
I tell you we do
real good business-wise?
I got fuckin'
double on those cars.
Here he comes.
Hey, c'mon!
(ANDREA BOCELLI PLAYING)
Hello, I'm home!
(SINGING IN ITALIAN)