Previously, on From...
There's darkness in the forest.
Nightmares you can't
even begin to imagine.
My blood is your blood now.
Every time I see something
really weird, I see this symbol.
I've seen this.
Like in a vision or something?
No, on the walls in the tunnels.
Victor said his mother wanted
to rescue the children
that were locked in the tower.
That it was the only way
to get everyone home.
All this time, I thought
the children were trying to scare me,
but what if
they're just asking for my help?
Do you hear that?
Help me!
Please, please, I need help!
- She was talking in her sleep.
- What did she say?
"They touch, they break, they steal.
No one here is free."
There's something else here now.
Something new.
It's not safe for anyone
to go to sleep tonight.
- Every one of you is gonna fucking die!
- Get him out of here now!
I just remembered my dream.
There was this boy, all dressed in white,
and he kept repeating the same phrase...
"Here they come,
they come for three,
unless you stop the melody."
I know that one.
It's an old nursery rhyme.
They touch, they break, they steal
No one here is free
Here they come, they come for three
Unless you stop the melody
Julie, stop that.
They're upstairs.
Your mom and...
Victor took Ethan to the diner.
Hey, Boyd...
You should go upstairs
just in case they need your help.
That kid should be picking out
a prom dress. Not...
laying in there like...
The problem is
there's too much we don't know.
It's like opening a book
and starting from the middle or...
Try to imagine
what a jigsaw puzzle looks like
when all you have is a few random pieces.
And they're not even the helpful ones,
like corners or edges. Just...
vague. Fucking...
The trick is
you find two pieces that connect.
Then at least you have a place to start.
- Hey, where you going?
- We need to talk to Sara.
Well, if we can't sleep anymore,
then what's the point?
I'm telling you,
we should all just fucking go.
Get some supplies,
set out, and see what we can find.
Boyd tried that already.
Yeah, well, maybe Boyd isn't
the end-all, be-all answer to everything.
What are we even doing out here?
Randall was an asshole.
Yeah, well, you're an asshole, too,
and I wouldn't leave you out here to rot.
Fuck me.
Finally get out of my goddamn room
and I'm on corpse-collecting duty.
Go check out down there. Elgin, this way.
I appreciate you coming.
It feels good to do something useful.
Well, you've done plenty.
That dream of yours? For all we know,
that'll prove to be the answer to this.
- Weird as that fucking sounds.
- Yeah.
Maybe.
You're gonna wanna see this!
- I don't think this guy is dead.
- Shit!
Fuck.
Didn't you say
there would be dead monsters out here?
So much for silver bullets.
All right, get him in the van.
Fuck!
- Get him in the van!
- Okay.
Jesus...
Her pulse is nice and strong,
and she's taking big, deep breaths.
Let's see here.
Oh my god! What's happening?
- What's happening?
- I don't know.
- What's going on?
- What's happening?
- I don't know.
Do something!
- Come on! Julie, can you hear me?
- No!
Marielle. Marielle.
Hey, hey. Look at me. Marielle.
Marielle, talk to me.
So, how is this supposed to help?
When we were in the forest,
you said a little boy in white told you
to get into the tree.
It's the same tree
that put me in the goddamn chamber
where all this started.
So?
Well, it turns out, Elgin had
a dream about a little boy in white.
Told him part of a nursery rhyme.
The same one
Paula kept repeating before she died.
They touch, they break, they steal
No one here is free
Here they come, they come for three
Unless you stop the melody
That make any sense to you?
No.
Anything else you can tell me
about the little boy?
He was trying to help us.
Okay, so, this random little kid running
around a magical forest doing good.
Popping up in people's dreams and...
I don't think he really was a little boy.
Come on. Hey, Sara, listen up.
This is it right now.
When I told you there was a chance
that you could still do some good,
that you could help the people here,
it's right now.
You understand?
Okay.
It's right over there.
All right. This is it.
This whole... whole thing was a...
There was someone chained
to a wall right here.
Right here, then there was a hole
that went down 40, 50 feet. And I had...
- What's wrong?
- I can hear it.
The music. It's here.
- What are you talking about?
- The music box. It's here.
Where?
Right there.
It's here.
- There's... There's no music box here.
- No, look, there is.
- This...
- There is.
I can hear it. I'm telling you. I can...
What's wrong?
- I can hear them screaming.
- What?
There's... There's something...
There's something. It...
It's here.
It's hurting them.
Boyd, what the fuck is going on? What...
Hey, Sara. Sara, talk to me.
Here they come, they come for three
It needs them.
It needs them to stay in.
It needs them to...
Okay. We gotta get her out of here.
Come on.
- Kenny! Come on. Come on, buddy.
- Yeah.
Lift up. There we go.
Come on, let's go out the other side.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I shouldn't have...
- No, no, don't! Stop!
Okay. Okay.
All right.
It's laughing at you.
- What?
- For bringing it back to town.
For setting it free.
It wants to hurt us.
It wants to make us suffer.
It got so excited
when it touched your arm.
How do I stop this?
- Sara, how do I stop this?
- Julie.
- Julie?
Ju... Julie.
- Julie... Julie and the others...
- Yeah.
...they're dying. They're dying.
And when they die, it will be too late.
- You need to make it stop.
- Okay, make what stop?
The music. The music.
You have to make the music stop!
Okay, how?
How do I stop something I can't see?
- I don't know.
- Okay. All right.
Just breathe.
That's it. Just breathe.
Close your eyes. Let's pray.
Yea, though I walk
through the valley of the shadow of death,
I will fear no evil,
for thou art with me...
thy rod and thy staff, they comfort me.
Matthias?
Take the guns and lock them in the shed.
I don't want them in the house.
We managed to make it through the night.
Now we just have to see about today.
Okay.
Jim.
Come on.
There's something I have to do,
and I need you to say it's okay.
The last time Victor saw his mother,
she told him that there were
children locked in a tower.
That if she helped them,
then everyone could go home.
I don't understand.
All these children I've been seeing,
the dreams I've been having about a tower...
what if she was right?
What if the only way
to save Julie is to find that tower?
- Tabby...
- Honey, I know, I know it sounds crazy.
I had a theory about this place
that almost got me killed.
- Well, this is different.
- How?
This just is.
Jim, our daughter is laying in that room
like something out of a nightmare.
She called for me last night,
and I couldn't do anything to help her.
I was just standing there...
and all I could think and see was
Thomas lying on the fucking floor.
I can't, Jim.
We can't sit here hoping for the best.
Victor's mother left this place,
and she never came back.
Whatever she went to do,
she never came back.
Victor had to grow up here alone.
- What if that happens to you?
- I know.
That's why I need you
to tell me that it's okay for me to go.
I have to try this, Jim, please.
When Julie wakes up,
she's gonna be hungry.
- We make her favorite.
- Hey.
- We brought some food.
- Good.
Victor, can I talk
to you for a minute, please?
Is Victor in trouble?
No, no.
You come help me, okay?
You said your mother wanted
to rescue the children
that were locked in the tower.
Do you know the way to the tower?
But I... I know the way
to the bottle tree.
The what?
This is how you get to the tower.
You have to visit the bottle tree.
Can you take me there?
I think so.
Can you give us a second?
Jim...
I have to try this.
I have to at least try.
I just...
I know. I know, baby. I know.
So, what are we supposed to do?
We head back to town.
Wait, what?
She just said that the music box
is here. It's here. We have to find it.
- We have to...
- Yeah, how do you expect we do that?
I don't know, but I'm pretty sure
it's not by going back into town.
People's lives are at stake...
Hey, I don't need
a fucking reminder of what's at stake! I...
There's nothing we can do here. Not yet.
Look, we're dealing with things
that are beyond our scope of...
We know more now
than we knew this morning. That's a win.
- Okay.
So, what are we supposed to tell people?
You tell people that we are working on it.
The best thing we can do now is
help people feel a little more calmer.
Help them feel less afraid.
Can you do that?
Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Good man.
Hey.
You all right?
Why do people always ask that
when the answer is obvious?
Look, man, I'm sorry about last night.
Putting you in that room,
we were just trying to...
It was my fault.
I lost my shit.
Paula was the one
who was good in a crisis.
Oh my God,
I never realized how fragile we are.
How easily we break.
I was downstairs making dinner
like an idiot.
There was nothing you could have done.
This was nobody's fault.
Yeah.
- Nobody's fault.
- Yeah.
How's he doing?
Just can't imagine
what I'd do if something like that...
if it was you.
Hey, come here.
It wasn't me.
Let's get married.
- Today.
- Yeah.
Look, we have no idea what's gonna happen,
or if your dad's gonna find a way to...
If this is the end,
then I want it to end with you.
I wanna get married.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- Yeah?
- Okay, yeah, sure. Yeah.
So, this is what you're doing with my bar?
It's a thought experiment.
I used to find this helpful
when I was developing my...
You died.
Correct.
Okay.
Well, just wanted to make sure
we were on the same page.
Well, are you gonna ask me if I'm real?
I imagine this is
some sort of stress-induced psychosis,
and you will disappear
soon enough on your own.
So, what's all this supposed to do?
It's a way of reorienting
my perspective. I'm trying to...
I'm trying to find
a different way to look at this symbol.
Why?
Because I've been looking at it wrong.
There's gotta be an answer here.
I'm just... I'm not seeing it.
And I just thought...
What, what is it?
You changed the still.
You're welcome.
I think you're overthinking it.
Do you, dead Tom?
In what way?
You already know what you have to do.
Tabitha told you she saw
this symbol down in the tunnels.
The question is how far
are you willing to go to find answers?
Going down
into those tunnels would be insane.
Even if it saves Julie's life?
Oh fuck!
You know, I don't even know
if I'd find anything down there.
Of course you do. It's natural design.
Same reason your brain is in your skull,
your heart's behind your ribs.
Nature will always put
what's most precious
in the spots most difficult to reach.
Nothing about this place is natural.
Wrong.
Nothing about this place is familiar.
There's a difference.
If there's answers to be found...
and granted, that's a big if...
that's where they'll be.
All right, so, I'm supposed to what...
I'm supposed to take advice from...
You ran into a house
that was falling down to save Tabitha,
and she wasn't even there.
And you know what?
Given the choice,
I'd do the same thing again.
Well, then you're a fucking idiot. Like...
You don't make moral choices
based on the outcomes you expect.
You make them based on
whether or not you think they're right.
When I ran into that house,
I wasn't thinking about
the trolley problem or determinism. I...
wasn't thinking of any of that.
There's a 16-year-old girl over there
who needs your help.
Did you bury Paula?
What?
Did you bury Paula yet?
- Jesus Christ.
- I'll do it.
I'll go and find some people to help.
Boyd?
Yeah.
You're doing the best you can.
Fuck!
You putting the guns away?
Yeah, Donna was worried
about leaving them in the house.
That's smart. You need a hand?
No, I'm just about done.
It's okay. It's okay. Yeah, it's okay.
It's just gonna go a little sooner
than the rest of us.
Everything's a system.
Everything's connected.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Fuck my life.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Fucking piece of shit. Come on!
Okay.
Okay, I got this.
Easy peasy.
Easy fucking peasy.
Anybody up there?
I'll tell you what...
if you are up there...
you're a real fucking asshole,
you know that?
You enjoying this?
If Khatri were here, Khatri would say,
"God moves in mysterious ways."
Oh yeah, yeah.
Because Khatri had a plan.
He thought you put him here
for a reason. He...
He thought that we were gonna walk out
into those woods like Butch Cassidy
and the motherfucking Sundance Kid.
He thought that right up until the time
one of those things
slit his fucking throat.
What did he do with his last breaths?
He prayed.
He gasped out that fucking prayer
so that you would know...
so that he could show you
that he had never lost faith.
You know what, motherfucker?
I ain't here to pray.
If you are anything
other than some bedtime fucking story
that we tell ourselves,
then you will tell me why!
Why you made me think I could fix this?
Some kind of fucking hero,
I'm gonna lead these people home,
when all I am is a dumb motherfucker
who keeps getting people killed!
Damn it!
You fuck! You think this is funny?
And you...
you up there somewhere
having a fucking laugh, huh?
Just answer me! Answer me!
Say something!
You know... tampering
with a mailbox is a federal crime.
Come in.
How's she doing?
She's getting worse.
She's... She's getting cold.
Is this really it?
Is this how it ends?
I don't know.
You know, ever since...
she walked off that bus, I actually...
allowed myself to believe
that there was a plan to all of this.
That there was something
we were meant to do here.
But there's no...
there's no grand design.
We're all gonna die here.
And all this would have been for nothing.
You know, my dad used to say...
"It's hard to see the sweater
when you're only just a thread."
I never really knew
what he meant until now.
All the people
that have gotten stuck here...
maybe we aren't the ones
that get to go home.
But maybe...
what we did here...
makes it easier
for the people who come next.
Maybe we're the reason
that they get to go home.
Just because we're only a thread,
it doesn't mean we don't matter.
There you go.
Last thing you need is
Khatri haunting you over everything else.
It's too late for that.
Julie and Marielle.
Randall.
Sara says they're dying.
And once they're gone,
there's no putting
the genie back in the bottle.
Whatever this thing is, it just waits
for us to go to sleep, and then...
Like Paula.
Yeah.
She said the music box is there.
Right there in the clearing,
only it's not there.
Like looking at an instruction manual
with too many pages missing. How am I...
How am I supposed...
I saw my wife last night.
How'd she look?
There's gotta be rules, Donna.
There's gotta be something
I can hold in my hands.
There's gotta... These...
I did this.
I brought this thing back here.
Yep, you sure did.
You also gave a whole bunch
of people a lot more time
than they would have had
if it wasn't for you.
You gave me more time.
Your son is about to get married.
Nothing official, I guess.
It's not like we have a priest anymore.
They're making the most
of whatever time they have.
You should do the same.
Come back to Colony House with me.
I'm not giving up.
Did I say give up?
Boyd, this may be
the last few hours any of us get.
So why don't you just stop
being a goddamn martyr
and come and watch your son get married.
The end of the world will still be here
when the ceremony's done.
Anghkooey!
- Anghkooey!
Did your mother say
anything else about the children?
How was she going to save them?
I don't know.
All she said was that they needed her.
It's... It should be right here. It...
- No, no, no, no, these trees weren't...
- Hey, hey, hey. It was...
It was a long time ago, Victor. Maybe...
Maybe we took the wrong turn.
Over here.
Who put the bottles there?
I don't know.
This is where I found her.
Your mom?
Yeah, after everyone died,
I came looking for her. Her body...
She didn't make it into the tree.
What do you mean "into the tree"?
Come.
It's a faraway tree.
The night the monsters got
into Colony House,
Julie said you both escaped
by climbing into a tree.
And they always take you different places,
and you never know where you'll end up.
But my mother said this one was special.
That it would take her
to the tower, to the children.
And then what?
That's all I remember.
Here.
I...
I put some snacks inside for you.
Here.
- Thank you, Victor.
- Yeah.
Does it hurt to go through?
No, it's just like walking through a door.
Okay. Okay.
Thank you.
Now go back to town.
Be careful.
Yeah.
What are we doing?
He wanted it to be a surprise.
He wanted what to be a surprise?
You're always saying that this view
makes even this place look like a dream.
So I figured...
Is this okay?
This is perfect.
Hey, why don't we just go get him?
He's got a lot on his mind...
Sheriff Stevens!
You made it.
What, are you kidding me?
Wild horses couldn't stop me.
Okay, let's get this show on the road.
Okay, wait.
I know it's not much of an aisle, but...
would you do me the honor?
- All right, you ready?
- Yeah.
You know, you don't have to call me
Sheriff Stevens anymore.
Okay.
Shall we?
Ladies first.
Okay.
My father had a saying.
Well, he had a lot
of sayings actually, but...
my favorite one was always...
"Life is a journey through the unknown."
"And though your eyes
and mind may sometimes deceive you,
your heart will never lie."
My heart's belonged to you
since the moment I met you.
You're the love of my life,
for as long as that life may last.
So, will you, Ellis Stevens,
do me the honor of being my husband?
I will.
I made you something.
- Your turn.
- All right.
It's a tough act to follow.
The day my family and I saw that tree,
our lives changed forever.
But the day
that I saw you get out of that car,
that's the day that my life really began.
There have been...
so many times here where I felt...
like I was stumbling in the dark.
But each and every time,
you were the light that guided me through.
You are my love.
You are my home.
You are my light in dark places.
So...
will you...
Fatima Hassan-Rostami...
will you do me the honor of being my wife?
I will.
Well, the rules say we kiss now.
Boyd?
Where'd you go?
Are you okay, Dad?
"Light in dark places."
I gotta go.
- I'm sorry. Hey.
- It's okay.
I love you guys.
- All right.
- I love you too.
Will we get to see Thomas again?
What?
If we die,
will we get to see Thomas again?
Yeah.
Yeah, we will.
- Grandpa too?
- Grandpa too.
Maybe it won't be so bad then.
She likes to sleep with two pillows.
Let me help you.
Hey. Reggie?
You did this.
Everything was fine
until you went into the forest.
- Hey.
- You're the reason
all this is happening.
Okay. Hey, hey. Listen to me.
Listen to me.
I know you don't understand. I know.
But I think this torch right here,
I think this is gonna help me fix this.
Oh my God!
I'm sorry, Boyd. I always liked you.
Oh God! God!
Fucking...
Fuck.
Please.
Come on.
Oh shit.
What...
Julie. Hey, Julie?
Hey, Julie. Hey, Julie.
Can you hear me?
I'm gonna get you out of here.
I'm gonna get you out of here right now.
We're getting out of here.
Boyd.
Please. Destroying that box
isn't gonna end their suffering.
- You'll only prolong it.
- No...
The people in this town will suffer,
in ways you can't even imagine.
They're all gonna die, screaming.
What's wrong with her?
- Hey! It's okay.
- What's wrong?
What's wrong with her?
Honey. Honey, please.
You think you need to be the hero.
You think you need
to be responsible to save them.
You don't have to suffer anymore.
You don't have to be afraid.
It's okay. None of this matters.
We can be together. I miss you so much.
Wait, so...
Stop, so... So whatever this thing is,
it just lets you come
in here for a little chat?
It knows you won't listen.
It wants you to fight. It wants you
to have hope that you could actually win.
Why?
Because hope is
what makes you willing to suffer.
Hope is what sent you out
into the woods that day.
Hope is what made you leave me alone
when I needed you the most.
It's not your fear
that feeds the forest, Boyd.
It's hope.
Let it go, Boyd.
If they don't die today,
they'll just die tomorrow.
No.
Julie... are you okay?
Are you okay?
Hi.
What's going on?
Honey.
She's okay. You sister's okay.
Hey, baby. It's okay. It's okay.
You're good now.
Fuck you, motherfucker.
You don't break me.
You hear that?
You don't fucking break me!
- Drink this.
- I'm fine.
I know you are. Do it for me.
There's no more buzzing.
Does that mean it's over?
I sure hope so.
Dad?
Where's Mom?
Anghkooey.
Hello?
I'm sorry.
I really am.
This is the only way.
Just a moment.
How are you feeling?
Where am I?
Saint Anthony's Hospital. I'm Dr. Brody.
Three days ago,
a pair of hikers found you in the woods.
You were lying unconscious
on the side of a trail.
No.
Do you remember
what you were doing out there?
No.
No. No, no, no.