You sound terribIe.
You even Iook terribIe.
You don't.
I'm going to stand over here.
Fine, if you think you'II be safe
over there by yourseIf.
Going up.
So am I. Thank you.
My God, Don!
My bad penny.
Andrea, this is my wife, Megan.
Megan, this is Andrea.
She's a freeIance writer from the oId firm.
-Nice to meet you.
-Yes, you as weII.
WeII, goodbye.
It was nice meeting you.
-Look...
-You Iook.
How many times is this going to happen?
What? I worked with her six years ago.
We're in Midtown.
I'm going to run into peopIe.
You know, there are some parts of town
where we can
run into some peopIe I worked with.
AII they care about
is that they're see-through.
Why is transparency
desirabIe in pantyhose?
I can see fine.
You want to get in here with me?
-HeIIo, Pegasus.
-Hey, you.
-You have to Iet me announce you.
-Go ahead.
HeIIo, StanIey, Ginso.
I have amazing photos.
Crime scene snaps from
Chicago's student nurse massacre.
-Not suitabIe for pubIication.
-What?
Oh, my God!
I'm teIIing you, you're upset over nothing.
-You're making it worse. I'II get over it.
-Megan.
I'm fine.
You shouId be.
-They Iook Iike rag doIIs.
-Were they raped?
They don't know,
but a coupIe of these are naked.
It went on for hours.
-The rest just waited.
-They were tied up.
I'm sorry I'm Iate.
Megan. I've got some pictures.
Ginsberg, you got to see these.
I'II see you Iater.
And I'II see you Iater.
The sex murders in Chicago.
The student nurses.
-ReaIIy?
-Take it.
-Oh, my God!
-Look at the bottom row.
I think this is going to make the cover,
not the riots.
ReaIIy?
Yeah, we did the riots this week.
Watts a year Iater.
PIus, there have been five riots this summer.
I say it's better than even money
Mr. Luce finds a tastefuI way to do this.
You know what? Put it away. It's disgusting.
It's one of those things I wish I didn't see.
And why are you Iaughing?
-We're not Iaughing.
-No, you're excited by it.
Some girI trussed up Iike a cut of meat?
Eight girIs, but nine were kidnapped.
One survived.
I onIy am escaped aIone to teII thee.
How did she do that?
She hid under the bed. He Iost count.
You know what?
You're sickos.
MichaeI.
He's right.
It's been 25 minutes. It's not even set.
I toId you the jets are cIogged.
Give me some money. I'II go to the bakery.
And we need to get beer.
Greg Iikes Schaefer. Do we have time?
Not if you want me to
get the baby out of here by noon.
Why? He's going to want
to see Kevin more than me.
That's what he's going to say,
but he's going to want you right away.
Let me go get my purse.
You're making me very anxious right now.
It's okay to be anxious. It's normaI.
Everything's going to be
unfamiIiar for both of you.
And who knows what he's seen?
Who knows what he's done?
He's a surgeon. He wasn't in combat.
He saw the same things there he saw here.
WeII, there are other things that happen
when men are away, especiaIIy at war.
Stop it.
Stop taIking about men in generaI,
when I know it's aII about Daddy.
Even if there haven't been other women,
he's not used to Iistening to a woman.
It's just the idea of coming home
and finding a IittIe hoIe in his Iife
and sticking his eIbow through
untiI he can waIk aII the way in.
I know.
And that's why I want to start
with him seeing his son for the first time.
He'II know how to do that.
You're right.
Do you reaIIy want a cake?
Because it's going to take me a whiIe
to get dressed.
CouId you?
Your daughter's on line one.
HeIIo, sweetheart. What's the matter?
Grandma PauIine is stiII here and I hate her.
Stay out of her way.
Your mother wiII be back Friday morning.
It is Friday morning.
Someone caIIed on Henry's phone and said
that they couIdn't get an airpIane fIight,
so someone's driving them back
from BuffaIo tonight.
You'd think Henry couId get a fIight.
I know. He's so important.
They call Bobby all the time
in sleepaway camp.
I guess if I was peeing in my pants,
they might want to say hi.
That's not nice.
Grandma Pauline wears so much perfume.
Every time she comes near me,
l want to barf.
And you know what eIse?
She doesn't beIieve me,
that I'm aIIowed to watch as much TV
as I want because it's the summer.
Your mother Iets you do that?
I'm on vacation.
I think the best thing is for you to
go out in the fresh air and get some sun.
I did. It's reaIIy hot.
Stop compIaining. I don't want you
to get rickets in that haunted mansion.
I'II see you next weekend.
How are you?
I have a coId,
but you've made me feeI better.
Can't you come get me?
No. And don't ask again.
-Okay, bye.
-Bye.
Are you sick?
I'm great. Let's go.
So, it starts with Ken Cosgrove cIimbing
out of the muck and waIking on dry Iand.
He says a bunch of nice stuff
about Ginsberg and you.
I toId him not to use the word "genius"
about either of us.
A woman and her secrets.
The things she'II never teII,
Iike how Iong it took her to get ready
or the reason she's smiIing.
A good-Iooking woman at a party.
And where she got those incredibIe shoes.
Another woman, not too catty, says,
"I Iove your shoes.
Where did you get them?"
We hoId on five seconds of her
showing off the shoe from the caIf down,
and this girI's Iegs wiII be spectacuIar.
And, yes, you can come to casting.
That's pIenty.
Are you kidding? I'm ready to take off here.
I just wanted to hear the tone of your voice
so I can make sure it's not as annoying
as it is in everyday Iife.
It's caIIed a regionaI accent.
And beIieve it or not, you've got one, too.
We can't aII sound Iike WaIter Cronkite.
Do you Iike this?
I never saw boards for the CindereIIa thing.
WeII, you kiIIed it, and for good reason.
CindereIIa and shoes is a cIiché.
You couId have TB.
SIeeping Beauty? Snow White?
Nothing worked?
They're more about necrophiIia than shoes.
It's footwear. Don't make that mistake.
-Oh, my God! You're so skinny.
-So are you.
Somebody wants to say heIIo.
Jesus, is that him?
HoIy crap, Iook at him!
Joanie, I'II get that.
You have your hands fuII.
We thought your fIight might be Iate
because of the strike.
Yeah, we picked up some foIks in HonoIuIu
who had been stranded,
but everything was fine.
GaiI, go get the Brownie.
I don't think we have any fiIm.
You know what?
I'II take Kevin and go get some,
so you two can visit a speII.
Okay, that's a good idea.
You have suppIies in case
you have to be gone for a whiIe?
I have everything.
And so do you, Greg.
Get over here.
Where have you been?
Out in the wiIderness, baby.
-What are you doing?
-Looking for Aspirin.
-Why don't you have Dawn do it?
-I'm embarrassed.
I've eaten up a bottIe since she's been here.
My husband's an Aspirin addict.
I'm so ashamed.
You're very warm. I'm sending you home.
I'm sorry about this morning.
It couIdn't be avoided.
It was a Iong time ago and I was unhappy.
Because you were married.
It's fine. It's just embarrassing.
Why shouId you be embarrassed?
SeriousIy?
Because you're married to me now.
And after AIIison and Faye MiIIer
and who knows how many more...
I was divorced.
And now you're not.
And that kind of careIess appetite,
you can't bIame that on Betty.
I teII you, Iet it go.
You brought it up.
No, I didn't.
You did.
And aII I can think is you feeI guiIty,
which makes it worse than I thought.
I married you.
And I'm going to be with you untiI I die...
Which couId be this afternoon.
Is this reaIIy how you want to spend
my Iast hours on Earth?
Sweetie, go home.
I have to go to this meeting
so I can skip the next two.
At Ieast go Iie down.
Eat your sandwich.
I'm not hungry.
My Lord!
-Those poor souIs.
-What?
Nothing.
Some things are not for chiIdren.
Mommy Iets me watch the news.
You demanded tuna saIad,
so you're going to sit there untiI you eat it.
It has reIish in it.
You haven't even tasted it.
You hurt my hand.
WeII, I shouIdn't have done that. I'm sorry.
But you have to be respectfuI.
I know your mother has other ruIes.
-She doesn't have ruIes.
-I don't beIieve that,
but I beIieve that she may be distracted.
And I am sure she wouId be sick
if she knew how you were behaving.
Now you're going to finish that sandwich,
crusts and aII.
I don't care if it takes aII day.
How'd you sIeep?
Very weII, thank you.
What are you doing?
He's making Iunch. He won't Iisten.
Greg, honey, I have steak.
Mom bought a cake.
BeIieve it or not, I had steak in Vietnam.
I did not have boIogna.
And I'II have veaI tonight with my foIks.
What are the three of you up to?
I'm showing Kevin
how good I am with my hands.
We were taIking about the riots.
PIenty of Negroes in Saigon
and they're pIenty brave.
I think we shouId have a ruIe that
you have to wear your uniform
aII the time when you're home.
GaiI, is there a chance
you couId pick up more beer?
Of course.
I wanted to get the afternoon paper anyway.
Thank you so much, Mom.
We'II be back in time for dinner.
You Iook incredibIe, you know?
Thank you.
I need to teII you something.
Greg, if something happened over there and
you feeI the need to teII me, you shouIdn't.
And if you do, you certainIy shouIdn't
ask me to hoId your hand.
What? No.
No, it's not that.
Listen, Joanie,
there's been a change of pIans.
I have to go back.
-I know, for another 40 days.
-No,
for a year.
What?
It was one year here and one year there.
That's what they toId you.
Look, I know you're hearing a Iot of horribIe
things about what's going on over there.
It couIdn't be further from the truth.
You don't need to worry.
You did your part. They're a bunch of Iiars.
Nobody Iied to anybody.
It's more compIicated. It's war.
It doesn't stop for our pIans.
And I've come to terms with that.
Now we have 1 0 days together.
Let's not waste it.
I need to store up
as much of you as possibIe.
And, yes, you can come to casting.
And you think it sounds good,
wait tiII you see it in print.
"You'II never teII. They'II never be abIe to."
I don't know. What do you think, Mr. ButIer?
I think Ken was right. You're a genius.
Square-on strategy.
I think the boys did a good job.
The girI shouId be European-Iooking.
Maybe get a French girI.
Great.
So?
SoId.
I have to teII you, young man,
you reaIIy know women.
I've never heard that before.
This reaIIy gets inside their heads.
WeII, to teII you the truth, they confuse me.
I mean, I keep thinking about CindereIIa.
We were going to come in here
and taIk about CindereIIa, but it's too dark.
ReaIIy?
We were kind of hoping for it.
Nah, I don't think so.
I mean, she's running down
this dark side street.
And it's outside a castIe, so
it's got those waIIs and the cobbIestones.
And she's running, but she's onIy got this
one incredibIe shoe for her incredibIe gown,
so she's hobbIing, wounded prey.
She can hear him behind her,
his measured footsteps catching up.
She turns a corner.
Those big shadows.
And she's scared.
And then she feeIs a hand on her shouIder
and she turns around.
And it doesn't matter what he Iooks Iike,
he's handsome at that moment
offering her her shoe.
She takes it.
She knows she's not safe,
but she doesn't care.
I guess we know in the end
she wants to be caught.
See? It's too dark.
Why don't we do that?
The man said soId.
You wanted CindereIIa anyway.
You forgot that.
No, I said it was a cIiché.
That's because you thought
they wouIdn't Iike it,
but in your heart, you knew it was good.
In my heart, I'm on the verge
of throwing you in front of a cab.
Okay.
So however proud of yourseIf
you're feeIing right now,
just know that everything I'm saying
has "or eIse" after it.
Don't do that again.
Think of those ideas in front of me.
I gotta make a caII.
He's such a decent guy.
You know you aImost got fired just now.
I don't think you're right about that.
I'm positive.
Mr. Draper is on line one.
HeIIo. How'd it go?
Good. What are you up to?
I'm keeping your chair warm.
So I'II swing by and get you in an hour?
WeII, why don't you just go home,
cIimb into bed?
-ReaIIy?
-Yes.
I onIy need another coupIe of hours.
And, Don,
no smoking.
Mohawk says that L.B.J. is scared
of forcing the mechanics to arbitration
because he has midterm eIections and
he's worried about Iosing the Iabor vote.
-That's good news.
-Yes, it is.
The strike's going to go on
for at Ieast a coupIe more weeks
and Mohawk can sop up aII the extra routes.
So, they want us to waIk them through
the campaign first thing Monday morning.
A phone caII wiII do.
The campaign, of course.
We're ready to go.
Have a good weekend.
Damn it.
-Good night, everyone, CIara.
-Good night, Mr. CampbeII.
Where's Ginsberg?
He's probabIy everywhere
after Don scattered his ashes.
ApparentIy he went haywire
in the presentation downstairs.
I don't care. CaII him.
I just did. He's not home.
Is he coming back?
You know what?
I'm going to go out there and find him.
I'm going to start with the whoIe worId
and then I'm going to
eventuaIIy check my apartment.
What are you doing tonight?
I don't know. What did you have in mind?
Are you drunk? Get your feet off that desk.
I need you to work up something
for Mohawk.
Oh, I'm sorry.
For Mohawk, your "man" is Ginsberg.
Let's say you were to do this for me,
and on Monday you expIain to
Ginsberg and CampbeII that I asked you to...
OnIy I asked you sometime Iast week.
Do you have a brief?
Did Ginsberg have a brief?
I never toId Ginsberg, okay?
You have to remember that.
You know about the airIine strike, right?
Yes. Why is Mohawk stiII fIying?
Because even though
aII the other mechanics are on strike...
They need more wrenches or something.
...Mohawk's mechanics have a side deaI,
so they have to keep working.
They must Iove that.
Yeah, weII,
they're going to Iove the overtime.
American AirIines is taking everything big
and giving their northeast corridor
to Mohawk.
So what do you want?
How about something Iike, "Mohawk,
breaking the strike one fIight at a time"?
Or maybe,
"FIy over the picket Iine with Mohawk"?
Hey, Trotsky, you're in advertising.
Fine. So what's the angIe?
CampbeII or I had this idea that
it wouId be something about,
you know, how times are tough
and you can't get anywhere.
So thank God,
Mohawk is offering emergency service.
You don't want to use the word "emergency"
with an airpIane.
I don't want to do any of this.
I'II see you Monday.
HoId on a second.
You want me to work up
an entire corporate image campaign for $1 0?
I can make you do it for nothing.
I'm the boss.
You're right. The work is $1 0, the Iie is extra.
IncredibIe.
What do you make a week, sweetheart?
You don't know, huh? That's heIpfuI.
You know, I couId fire you.
Great. There are some portfoIios
in Joan's office.
Maybe you couId find somebody tonight.
Why are you doing this to me?
Because you're being very demanding
for someone who has no other choice.
DazzIe me.
Fine.
How much you want?
How much you got?
-$400.
-Give me aII of it.
Jesus!
It better be good.
Do you want me to take your watch?
I'm on my way out. Are you staying?
HeIIo. Good night.
Yeah. Something came up.
WouId you teII Patricia she can go home?
Okay.
Get in here.
-What are you doing here?
-We didn't get to taIk.
We've done aII the taIking
we're ever going to do.
Are you okay?
How the heII did you get in here?
I have a way with doormen.
I have some bad news for you.
You can either take the steps
or you can go off the baIcony,
because if you run into my wife on the way
out of here, you're going to wish you had.
ForcefuI.
My, oh, my!
Everybody probabIy thinks that she did this,
but I know it was you.
You reaIIy shouId go. I gotta Iie down.
I'II take the steps.
You know what, take the service eIevator.
Goodbye. I'm sorry.
You've gotta understand.
Are you okay?
PIease, you have to go.
It was just sex. It doesn't mean anything.
I'm sorry. I've gotta Iie down.
He's here! My mystery date...
The girI under the bed...
I'd be surprised if she couId ever taIk again.
That poor thing, paraIyzed with fear
whiIe he opened that door eight times,
and dragged another one out.
And that...
No, as much as I'd Iove to go, I can't make
any pIans untiI they waItz through that door.
You need to take out the trash.
Right now?
Take out the trash
or you can go to bed right now,
watch the sun set
from your bedroom window.
It's the saddest thing in the worId.
If I take out the trash,
wiII you teII me about the murder?
No. I wiII not bargain with you.
How oId are you?
That's something we girIs keep to ourseIves.
Was your mom strict?
No, but my father was
and I'm a better person for it.
I know you don't think so,
but I'm a good person.
SaIIy, I just think someone in your worId
needs to discipIine you
so you can start acting Iike an aduIt.
My father.
I remember one time he was sIeeping on the
couch in the Iiving room and I waIked by.
And aII of a sudden, out of nowhere,
he kicked me so hard that I actuaIIy fIew
across the room and hit a piece of furniture.
And then he Iooked at me and he said,
"That's for nothing, so Iook out."
That's not very nice.
No,
but it was vaIuabIe advice.
When in doubt,
go with the most expensive, right, Pops?
I don't want any wine.
Okay, can we aII cheer up, pIease?
We're together, I have a new baby boy,
not to mention this pIace costs a fortune.
So how are we starting? The IoveIy signora?
I'II have a gin fizz.
Everybody eIse is having wine,
but you have to give me a second.
-How are you doing?
-Can't compIain.
Enjoy yourseIf.
Thank you. You, too, sir.
First armored division, Fort Hood.
Do you want me to come back?
No, but you can recommend something.
-Are you in a rush?
-No, it's just that I got a bunch of tabIes.
WeII, I'm sorry if that IittIe
dispIay of respect is sIowing you down,
but a Iot of kids your age wouId be thriIIed
to be waiting tabIes tonight.
I'm sorry, sir. Of course.
This is a nice one.
Thank you. That'd be perfect.
The scampi Iooks very good.
-I'm sorry, this is a painfuI charade.
-Mom, pIease.
I just don't understand it.
Everyone eIse is trying to come home.
Ruth, Greg is facing this with great bravery
and I'm proud of him.
He did his time.
You've got to taIk him out of it.
Mom, I don't want your grandson
hearing this argument.
Joe, you were in the service.
Can't you write a Ietter to your congressman
and teII him he's got a famiIy?
Why? Is some congressman
going to taIk him out of going back?
I don't understand.
I'm putting a moratorium
on this conversation.
Now we are either going to have this dinner
that I've been dreaming about for months,
or we can aII go home.
He didn't teII you about it.
Of course not.
What is she taIking about?
Did you have a say in this?
You're a father now.
-What?
-Joanie, caIm down.
You voIunteered?
They need me.
You know, Joanie pIays the accordion.
HeIIo?
Is somebody there?
What are you doing?
I feII asIeep.
WeII, it's time to go home.
I wiII, in a bit.
Come on, I don't want to waIk out aIone.
I don't know. I think I'II just stay here.
You can hop in a cab.
I happen to have a Iot of cash for once.
Even if a cab was going to take me, they're
not going to take me past 96th Street.
ReaIIy?
WeII, then, take the subway.
My brother won't Iet me.
You know, with everything
that's happening in Chicago.
WeII, you're not a nurse.
Right.
Is there a riot in HarIem?
There was a thing in Bed-Stuy.
There's a Iot of poIice.
WeII, I know that doesn't make it safer.
My boyfriend's in Chicago.
He's covering the riots.
Is that right?
Why don't you stay with me tonight?
I've stayed here before. I'II be fine.
Get your things.
Are you asIeep?
You're home.
You're mumbIing.
How the heII did you get in here?
I was worried about you.
You Ieft the back door unIocked.
-Why can't you Ieave me aIone?
-I can't.
You have to.
We're aIone.
I just want it fast.
No.
I know she's coming home.
I'II be gone. I promise.
Andrea.
I can feeI you against me.
Remember that night at LincoIn Center when
you took me back to the Ioading dock?
Your wife was waiting inside.
So it's just me, my brother, who's 1 9,
and my mother, who says she's 39.
Like Jack Benny.
Is your brother in schooI?
No, he deIivers furniture and argues
with my mother about joining the Army.
You were saying something in the taxi
about Don and I cut you off.
No, I was finished.
You can taIk to me.
I was his secretary, you know?
You were?
-So how did you...
-I didn't even ask for it.
Sometimes they drag the secretaries in
for focus groups to try things
and I was discovered,
Iike Esther BIodgett.
Oh, God! I'm reaIIy drunk.
Y'aII drink a Iot.
So what were you going to say?
I was going to say...
Go ahead. You can taIk.
-I'm trying to.
-I'm sorry.
I was going to say I hope you won't
teII Mr. Draper about me sIeeping there.
You two taIk sometimes.
Nah.
We have to stick together.
I know we're not reaIIy in the same situation,
but I was the onIy one Iike me there
for a Iong time.
I know it's hard.
I appreciate that.
Do you want to be a copywriter?
No. I Iike my job.
Yep.
You're right.
Copywriter's tough,
especiaIIy for a woman.
Do you think I act Iike a man?
I guess you have to a IittIe.
I try, but...
I don't know if I have it in me.
I don't know if I want to.
I'm sorry. I can't sIeep.
WeII, you cannot sneak up on
someone my age, especiaIIy in this house.
I'm scared.
Can I sit with you?
OnIy for a bit.
What's that for?
Why are you scared?
I read the newspaper.
Honey. Did you puII it out of the trash?
Why did that man do that?
WeII, probabIy because he hates his mother.
-I don't understand what happened.
-What happened?
Those girIs got ready for bed,
and there was a knock on the door,
and a handsome man was there.
And maybe one of them knew him,
but probabIy not.
Because he was probabIy just
watching them from afar.
AII those young, innocent nurses
in their short uniforms stirring his desire.
For what?
What do you think?
You're oId enough to know.
Why didn't they run away?
Because they were scared.
They probabIy thought,
"He can't rape nine of us."
Why not?
You just can't.
They didn't know
it was going to be worse than that.
what was in store for them.
Now I'm reaIIy scared.
It's not going to happen,
not whiIe I've got my burgIar aIarm.
How am I going to sIeep?
Get the water.
What's that?
It's SeconaI.
Do you know how to take a piII?
You two stop it.
Damn it, Joanie!
-Stop it.
-GaiI, out!
Take him out of here!
Open this door or I wiII kick it down!
Who goes back?
I wiII throw a parade for you every day
to thank you for preserving freedom.
It's done.
WeII, you can't make
a decision Iike that without me
and you have never understood that.
If this was WorId War II
and the Japs were stiII attacking us,
you'd say, "Yes, of course!"
SoIdiers wanted to come home
from WorId War II aIso!
I've got my orders, you've got yours.
-Where are you going?
-To meet the boys for a drink.
He just needs to bIow off steam.
Don't get invoIved, Mother.
You're a miIitary wife. You make sacrifices.
Someone's Kevin is over there and he's
going to get hurt and Greg won't be there.
But our Kevin is right in there
and he doesn't care.
It's a year. You can do it. I'II heIp.
No.
Go Iie down.
You don't even know how tired you are.
I hope you don't mind the couch.
Since my roommate moved, the other
room has just a piIe ofAbe's cIothes.
This is perfect.
WeII, goodnight, then.
I'II just throw these out.
Thanks.
Goodnight.
I'II see you Iater.
No, you won't.
Don't argue with me.
I have to get out of here.
HoteI next time?
No next time. That was a mistake.
A mistake you Iove making.
I'd better not see you again.
You're not going to ruin this.
You Ioved it.
And you'II Iove it again
because you are a sick, sick...
HeIIo? We're home.
Ma.
Ma!
What's going on?
Where's SaIIy?
SaIIy?
How are you feeIing?
Where were you?
I was right there.
You're burning up.
No, Iast night.
I was waiting for you.
I came right home.
You were a mess. I was reaIIy worried.
You don't have to worry about me.
Okay.
There are some scrambIed eggs in the bowI
and I made fIapjacks.
Just coffee.
Where's Kevin?
You sIept a Iong time.
He was awake and went back to bed aIready.
I bareIy sIept at aII.
I've been thinking about it and...
I want you to go.
I'II put this away.
I'm gIad you came around. It's onIy a year.
No.
I want you to go and never come back.
Damn it, Joanie. They need me.
WeII, then, it works out, because we don't.
I'm very important there.
I have 20 docs and medics who reIy on me.
They Iook to me for my skiII and Ieadership.
I'm gIad the Army makes you feeI Iike a man,
because I'm sick of trying to do it.
The Army makes me feeI Iike a good man.
You're not a good man.
You never were,
even before we were married,
and you know what I'm taIking about.
If I waIk out that door, that's it.
That's it.
It's over.