(SNIFFS)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Is this all you been doing all day?
Cleaned the house.
You wouldn't know.
This is your thing again
now you're back from Sweden?
So this is your thing again now, is it?
What?
Just lazing around.
It's the summer holidays.
You're pathetic.
Really fucking pathetic.
MARIANNE: He'll say, "You think I'm such
a horrible person."
CONNELL: Right.
"I try to be nice to you
and you always throw it back at me."
And does he?
What?
Try to be nice to you.
No.
What?
Nothing.
Do you know how often you've
been back here since I came home?
Yeah.
Why?
Don't know, just...
you don't have to.
That's all.
Well, it's really the only thing I have
to look forward to, so...
(MARIANNE GIGGLES)
("BREATHE" BY CAMELPHAT
AND CHRISTOPH FEAT. JEM COOKE)
♪ I need you to breathe again ♪
♪ You have been hurting so much ♪
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
♪♪
(MUSIC FADES)
(INDISTINCT TV CHATTER)
ANNOUNCER: Against Fermanagh,
it's a great catch, to get it is Brian.
Brilliantly done.
His reading of the game
is exquisite for a player who's so young.
Dean Rock. Stumble and fumble
here this time,
on the part of Brian Fenton.
ANNOUNCER 2: And a lot of pressure
coming on Shaun Patton's kick outs.
We've seen earlier in the game
the two short ones
that were intercepted.
He's going long now
and Dublin are doing extremely well
on their long kick outs.
(INAUDIBLE)
CONNELL: You falling asleep?
No.
I can run you back at halftime
if you want.
Am I in your way?
Not at all, you just seemed
pretty sleepy.
Where did you disappear to last night?
Uh...
I don't know, I was in
the smoking area for a bit.
Did you end up kissing that girl?
No.
I'm really warm.
Do you find it hot in here?
No, but you can open up
the windows there if you want.
(EXHALES)
(DISTANT JINGLING)
Ah, Eric was looking for you
last night, actually.
Did you see him?
Yeah, I saw him.
It's weird.
For some reason he wanted
to apologize to me.
For the way he acted in school.
Really?
Did you accept the apology?
Course I did.
Don't go in for grudges.
(CONNELL CHUCKLES)
Luckily for me.
(LAUGHS SOFTLY)
Do you want an ice cream?
Sure.
Right, back in a sec.
Thank you.
ICE CREAM MAN: Thank you.
How are you, could I get
two rockets please?
ICE CREAM MAN: Two rockets.
Thanks.
Thank you very much, cheers, thank you.
Cheers, thank you.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON TV)
It's nice Eric apologized to you.
I know, people from school have actually
been really nice since I got back.
Though I never make any effort
to see them.
Maybe you should.
Why?
You think I'm being ungrateful?
No, I just mean, like...
it must be kind of lonely for you.
I'm used to it.
Been lonely my whole life, really.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
You weren't lonely when you
were with Helen.
Were you?
I don't know.
- Sometimes.
Mm.
Didn't feel totally myself with her
all the time.
Connell.
Mm‐hmm.
You know when we were dancing
last night.
Yeah.
Mm, what about it?
Did I do something to annoy you?
Why do you say that?
Well, when you walked away
and just left me there,
felt kind of awkward.
I thought maybe you were annoyed with me.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't.
I, um...
I feel like, uh...
our friendship would be
a lot easier if like...
uh, certain things were different.
If what was different?
I don't know, I, um,
things would be a lot less confusing
if there weren't like this...
other element of the relationship.
When we were together in
the first year of college,
were you lonely then?
No.
You?
I was frustrated sometimes,
but not lonely.
I'm never lonely when I'm with you.
Yeah.
That was kind of a perfect time
in my life, to be honest.
I don't think I was ever really
happy before then.
I really wanted you to kiss me
last night.
Oh.
I wanted to kiss you as well, I guess.
Uh...
(CLEARS THROAT)
I guess we just misunderstood each other.
That's okay.
Look, I, uh,
I don't know what the best thing
for us to do is, like, obviously.
It's nice for me to hear you
say that stuff, but like...
At the same time, things haven't worked
out well for us in the past, like...
You know?
You are my best friend,
and I don't...
don't want to lose that for any reason.
Yeah.
I know what you mean.
And I don't want you
to think that I'm...
not being appreciative or anything
because I think you have been...
so supportive of me what with
the depression and everything.
And I'm not
lingering on that too much, but...
you really have been a big help with that.
You don't owe me anything.
No, I know that.
I didn't mean that.
Look, I, I'm just getting anxious now.
I don't want you to think like
I'm rejecting you or anything.
Don't be anxious.
Everything's fine.
Think I might head home now
if that's okay.
I'll drop you.
No.
You don't want to miss the second half.
I'll walk.
I forgot there was a match on,
to be honest.
Okay.
Bye.
(KISSES)
(EXHALES)
That's nice.
I'm just really nervous.
I think it's pretty obvious
I don't want you to leave.
I don't find it obvious what you want.
I want this so much.
It's really nice to hear you say that.
(HEAVY BREATHING)
I've missed you.
It's not like this with other people.
I know, but I like you a lot more
than other people.
Yeah.
I actually don't have any condoms.
That's okay.
- I'm on the pill.
Do you want it like this?
(HEAVY BREATHING)
However you want.
I haven't done this in a while, so...
It's okay.
(MOANING)
Marianne, can we...
can we do this, like, next weekend?
Whenever you want.
Whenever I want, really?
You can do whatever you want with me.
Ah, that's nice.
Do you like hearing me say that?
Yeah, a lot.
(MOANING)
Will you tell me I belong to you?
What do you mean?
Will you hit me?
No, I, uh...
I don't think I want that.
Is that, is that okay?
Do you want, do you want to stop?
Are you okay?
I'm, uh...
I'm sorry, I just didn't,
I didn't, uh, want to do that.
I just, I...
I just, I just think it'd be weird.
Er, uh, no, not weird. I just...
I don't think that'd be
a good idea.
You think I'm weird.
No, I didn't say that.
I just mean I'm...
I don't know, I just don't want it
to be weird between us.
I think I'd better go home now,
if that's okay.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, if that's what you want.
Um...
Listen, let me drive you home
at least, then.
No, I, I want to walk a bit.
(DOOR SLAMS)
(MARIANNE CRYING)
Marianne!
- (DOOR SLAMS)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
♪♪
(HEAVY BREATHING)
(SOBS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON TV)
Where the fuck were you?
Connell's house.
You shouldn't be going over there.
I thought you liked him.
You did when we were in school.
Yeah.
How was I supposed to know
he's fucked in the head?
I suppose you'll have to ask him.
I don't want people
going around town saying
a knacker is riding my sister.
Can I go now, please?
I don't want you to go near him again.
I'm warning you now.
People are talking about you.
I can't imagine what
my life would be like
if I cared what people thought‐‐
(GASPS)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
ALAN: Come back here. Marianne!
(BONES CRACK)
(MARIANNE GASPS)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
♪♪
(PHONE BUZZING)
Hey.
MARIANNE: Hey.
You okay?
MARIANNE: Um, I'm really sorry about this.
I‐I feel like an idiot.
Yeah, uh, about earlier, um...
I was thinking about it as well.
MARIANNE: No, I, I, it's not that.
It's, it's really stupid. I just,
I, I tripped or something
and I‐I've hurt myself.
I'm sorry to call you.
It's, it's, it's nothing.
I just, I don't know what to do.
Where are you?
MARIANNE: I'm at home.
It's, it's not serious.
It, it just hurts that's all.
Okay, I'm on my way now.
I'm getting in the car, okay?
MARIANNE: Okay.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
♪♪
(CAR RADIO BLASTS, STOPS)
(DOORBELL RINGS)
What's happened?
Why have you got blood on you?
I think my nose is broken.
Yeah.
Was it him?
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
♪♪
Okay. Uh...
Uh, get in the car.
Go.
What's going on here?
I didn't do anything.
Huh?
If you ever touch Marianne again,
I'll kill you.
Say one bad word to her ever again
and I'll come back here myself
and I'll kill you.
That's it.
- Do you understand me?
Yes.
Okay.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
I'm sorry to bother you.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know what to do.
No, don't say sorry.
It's good that you called me, okay?
Look at me a second.
No one is ever gonna
hurt you like that again.
Everything's gonna be all right, trust me.
'Cause I love you,
and I'm not gonna let anything
like that happen to you again.
Thank you.
("STRANGE WEATHER"
BY ANNA CALVI FEAT. DAVID BYRNE)
♪♪
♪ She'll take you back ♪
♪ Don't make believe ♪
♪ You want to think it through ♪
♪ I've loved before ♪
♪ I'll love again ♪
♪ I know that yours was true ♪
♪ Wake up slowly ♪
♪ There are blue skies ♪
♪ Cutting white lines ♪
♪ In black matter ♪
♪ See them shining ♪
♪ Through your drunken eyes ♪
♪ Carving silver ♪
♪ In strange weather ♪
♪ I've loved before ♪
♪ I'll love again ♪
♪ I know that yours was true ♪