("DID IT TO MYSELF" BY ORLA GARTLAND)
♪ I woke up to an empty bed ♪
♪ I took a walk to clear my head ♪
♪ I wished you were there instead ♪
♪ But then I shook it off ♪
♪ What the hell did I used to do ♪
♪ I'm even starting to speak like you ♪
♪ And I'm living in my memory,
living in my mouth ♪
♪ Living in the four fuckin' walls
of my house ♪
♪ I feel like a let down ♪
♪ To not be your friend, now ♪
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Hiya. Come on in.
May I get you a drink?
(CHUCKLES) Yeah.
Yeah?
Uh, I'll have a cup of tea.
Tea?
Just through there.
This way?
Yeah.
Grand.
You have a lot of posters.
You don't?
Ah. Too cool.
Don't think "cool" is the first word
most people would associate with me.
What would that be, then?
I don't know.
(CHUCKLES)
Annoying.
Obnoxious.
Argumentative, definitely.
Self‐righteous is probably one.
Uh, arrogant.
Frigid‐‐
No. Stop it. No one says that about you.
People do say I'm annoying.
So what?
People probably say that about me, too.
No, they don't.
No one finds you annoying.
Shy people aren't annoying.
You think I'm shy?
Just because I don't give my opinion
on everything all the time‐‐
You never give an opinion
about anything.
Ever.
You just always know what you think.
I'm not like that.
You must know what you feel, though.
No.
I struggle with that, actually.
I might look back on something and...
think how I felt at the time, but...
when it's happening,
never have any idea.
Then how do you know what you want?
I don't. (CHUCKLES)
Most of the time I don't have a clue.
What about now?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(WHISPERS)
Now can we take our clothes off?
(CHUCKLES) Yeah.
(MARIANNE CHUCKLES)
Yeah.
(MARIANNE CHUCKLING SOFTLY)
You, too.
Right. Yeah.
(EXHALES)
(LAUGHS SOFTLY)
(LAUGHS)
It's a little bit tight.
I don't think‐Turn.
(GRUNTS PLAYFULLY)
Sorry.
Come on.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(MARIANNE LAUGHS SOFTLY)
(BOTH MOANING)
Can I ask you something?
Yeah.
It's not really my business.
Okay.
Do you do this a lot?
What do you mean, "this"?
Coming over to girls' houses
after school and sort of...
seducing them, or whatever.
Is that what you think this is?
Me coming around to your house with some
grand plan of seducing you?
You told me you liked me.
But so do lots of girls.
Yeah, well, I have no idea about that.
I wasn't coming to your house
with any ulterior motive. I just, uh...
I just like talking to you.
Couldn't I say it was you
that was seducing me?
(CHUCKLES) I was trying to.
(CHUCKLES)
I just didn't think it would work.
Ah, well, it did.
There are much prettier girls in school
who like you.
(UNSNAPPING)
(MARIANNE MOANS)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(SIGHS)
(EXHALES)
(ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING)
♪♪
Is that okay?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Yeah.
Yeah, that feels nice.
(EXHALES)
(MOANS)
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
Is that good?
Yeah.
Yeah?
(BOTH MOANING)
(MOANING)
(WHISPERS)
Do you have a condom?
Yeah.
Is that what you want?
Okay.
Is this your first time?
Yeah.
Is that okay?
Well, yeah, it's fine. It's just that...
If you want to stop or anything,
we can...
obviously stop.
I doubt I'll want that.
I know, but, if it hurts or anything,
we can stop. It won't be awkward.
You just... you just say.
Thanks.
(RUSTLING)
I think you're very pretty, by the way.
(MARIANNE LAUGHS SOFTLY)
Don't.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
You all right?
Mm.
Yeah?
Does it hurt?
A bit.
It's nice.
All right.
(BOTH GROANING)
(BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SOFT MOAN)
ERIC:
What the fuck are you playing at, Waldron?
What?
ERIC:
Heard your ma was away on Saturday.
Didn't tell anyone.
What the fuck is going on with that?
Just wasn't thinking.
ROB:
You weren't thinking about the potential
to get wrecked in your free house?
That is literally unimaginable to me.
What'd you get up to instead?
Uh, uh, nothing. Studying.
Ah, Jesus Christ, Waldron. I despair.
Yeah.
I'm the worst.
ERIC: You are the literal worst.
(CHUCKLES)
MS. NEARY: Connell.
Hand those out for me, please?
Yeah.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
♪♪
(BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY)
(PANTING)
(CONNELL EXHALES)
MARIANNE: Was that a good one?
Yeah.
(MARIANNE CHUCKLES)
Yeah, it was class.
Do you remember that football match?
Yeah.
I was watching you play.
And honestly...
you looked so beautiful.
I just kept thinking how much
I wanted to watch you have sex.
(EXHALES)
I mean, not even with me.
With anybody.
How good it would feel.
Is that really weird?
Uh...
Yeah.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Yeah, that's really weird, Marianne.
(MARIANNE SNIFFS, THEN EXHALES)
But I think I understand it.
("HIDE AND SEEK" BY IMOGEN HEAP)
♪ What the hell ♪
♪ Is going on? ♪
♪ The dust has only ♪
♪ Just ♪
♪ Begun to form ♪
♪ Crop circles in the carpet ♪
♪ Sinking, feeling ♪
♪ Spin me 'round again ♪
♪ And rub my eyes ♪
♪ This can't be happening ♪
♪ When busy streets ♪
♪ A mess with people ♪
♪ Would stop to hold ♪
♪ Their heads heavy ♪
Sure you don't mind me being there?
Why would I mind?
It might be a bit weird for you.
Me, and all your friends
in a nightclub together.
Just trying to imagine you selling
raffle tickets at a school event, is all.
Karen asked me.
It would have been a bit churlish
to refuse a rare gesture of friendship.
(CHUCKLES)
Fair enough.
Sure the whole Deb thing's a joke, anyway.
Don't know why they still do it.
Point at any patriarchal structure
in the world and say that.
I hope you don't find it too hard
trying to resist me.
Sure. Don't I always?
Do you?
(WAVES CRASHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(ALL TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
Looking well, Rachel!
(BOYS CHATTERING)
Like Karen.
With a nice personality.
(BOYS LAUGHING)
Very ladylike.
ROB: She probably thinks Waldron's
pure sensitive and emotional
just 'cause he never
fuckin' says anything.
Did you ever think of trying
that technique yourself, Rob, no?
Right, boys. Nice and quick, yeah?
Yeah.
I'm starving.
CONNELL:
Don't be long in there, all right?
I have to get home.
Still going to O'Brian's later, yeah?
Better be.
I'll be there.
Spring rolls, yeah?
ERIC: Yeah.
Here.
I didn't know your mum worked
in the Sheridan's house.
Oh, yeah. No, uh...
She's been there about a year now,
I'd say. Where'd you hear that?
ROB: Alan was telling me.
You know her brother?
Yeah.
ROB: Have you ever been
in there yourself?
Into the mansion?
I've been in there a few times,
all right. Yeah.
What's it like inside?
Oh, it's big, obviously.
(CHUCKLES)
What's Marianne like
in her natural habitat?
I don't know, eh.
Don't see much of her, so...
So she thinks of you as her butler,
does she?
I doubt that.
But your mom is her housemaid,
isn't she?
She's a cleaner. She's there, what,
two, three times a week?
And I don't think
they interact much, so...
Marianne not have a little bell
she could ring
to get her attention, no?
(CHUCKLES)
ERIC: They didn't have spring rolls.
I got you chili chips.
Sound. Thanks.
Jump in there, boys.
(HEAVY BREATHING)
(MOANS)
(BOTH SIGH)
Is there anyone you have
a crush on in school?
(CONNELL LAUGHS)
What?
I'm literally still inside you.
(BOTH CHUCKLING SOFTLY)
What about Rachel?
Why do you say that?
She's pretty.
She clearly likes you.
Mm.
I wouldn't have strong feelings
either way on it.
Mm, but she has a nice...
face.
So do you.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
(CONNELL GROANS)
MARIANNE:
What are you thinking about?
Hmm.
College.
Don't know why I put down law.
Can't remember why
I thought it was a good idea.
Jobs.
Yeah.
But you know, I can't visualize it,
you know?
Can't see myself, like, in a tie...
convicting people of crimes. I just...
didn't know what to put down.
You should change to English.
Do you actually mean that,
or are you joking?
No, I... I actually think you should.
It's‐it's the only subject
you really enjoy.
And you spend all your spare time reading.
Where would I study English in Galway?
You could go into Trinity.
(CHUCKLES)
You're pretty confident
you're gonna get in, are you?
Well, then we'd be in college together.
I bet you'd pretend not to know me
if we bumped into each other.
Sorry.
I would never pretend
to not know you, Connell.
Would you not?
No.
All right.
I'll put down English and Trinity. So...
Really?
Yeah.
Who gives a fuck about a job, anyways?
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
(KEYS CLICKING)
(WATER RUNNING)
(DISHES CLATTERING)
Is the application finished?
Yeah. Nearly done.
I'll submit it tonight.
Mm‐hmm.
Do you want tea?
No, thanks. Alan, tea?
Yeah. Go on.
I thought I might take a look at
Wellington Road next weekend.
Right.
Bathroom needs retiling.
You could pick a color.
Since you're gonna be
the one looking at it.
Yeah?
Thanks. I'd like that.
Don't want to tempt fate, though.
Might not get in.
That's not the attitude, Marianne.
Yeah.
Last push.
It's the loveliest walk along the canal,
just nearby.
We used to cycle along it,
on our way in to class.
MARIANNE: You cycled?
I did.
Like, an actual bike?
(DENISE CHUCKLES)
DENISE: Alan?
I'm going down to the pub.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(SINGING LOUDLY)
Shut the fuck up.
Sing it out. You'll be caught.
Look at him!
Try it now. You try.
(LAUGHING AND INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(VOICES TALKING OVER ONE ANOTHER)
(PHONE CHIMES)
(CHATTERING CONTINUES)
(LAUGHING)
Bare faced lie.
Oh yeah, you bet.
(LAUGHTER)
Stop.
ROB: Here, what about Karen?
No one's asked her yet.
KIERNAN: Sure, take her to the Debs.
No, thanks. I'm holding out for Rachel.
ROB: In your dreams, mate.
She's after Waldron taking her,
isn't that right?
Yeah, well,
I reckon I can swoop in there.
You wouldn't mind, would you, Waldron?
Unless, of course, I can persuade the
lovely Marianne Sheridan to go with me.
(LAUGHING)
How 'bout it, Marianne?
You fancy coming to the Debs with me?
Uh, nope.
Oh.
Oh, you think
you're too good for me, do ya?
Yeah. Pretty much.
(LAUGHING)
Are you serious?
I am. I am too good for you.
ERIC: A man would want to be
fairly desperate before he'd go near you.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
MARIANNE: Okay.
Ugly, flat‐chested bitch.
(BOYS CHUCKLING)
Fuck's sake, man.
(BOYS GIGGLING)
ROB: That's not how you do it.
(RAIN PATTERING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
♪♪
(KNOCKING)
CONNELL: You all right?
How was your weekend?
Oh, it was good, yeah.
Went to the pub.
Couple of 'em ended up
at the Ghost, but...
I was home early enough.
Ended up at the what?
Uh, the Ghost. Ghost House.
What is that?
Behind the school. You know,
uh, the abandoned house there.
Oh.
Never been there? Ah.
I used to hang out there all the time.
I thought everybody knew about it.
Not me.
(CONNELL SIPPING)
I want to see it.
Can you take me?
Mm, sure.
Okay.
Up here.
(SOFT INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
♪♪
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
You all right?
Yeah.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
I would lie down here.
And you could do
anything you wanted to me.
Do you know that?
Do you enjoy making me
feel uncomfortable?
I'm not making you feel anything.
Maybe I should just leave you alone.
No. Marianne, if you did that, I...
If I did that, what?
What do you mean,
if you didn't want to see me anymore?
Well, to be honest,
I'd be a bit surprised,
because it seems like you enjoy it.
Look, I'm sorry. I'm just...
I don't know how to...
You're just making me feel insecure,
like talking about...
not wanting to hang out with each other,
'cause I thought that you liked me.
I do like you.
If you didn't want this anymore,
I'd be upset.
Now that you ask about it,
I wouldn't be happy, all right?
You don't mind that I'm...
ugly?
And flat‐chested, then.
I'm sorry they said that to you.
Is that what you think of me?
They don't even
think that, themselves. Like...
if Eric thought he had
the slightest chance with you,
he'd be talking very differently.
He just...
He thinks you look down on him.
Uh...
I would miss you,
if you didn't want to see me anymore.
Would you miss sleeping with me?
Yeah.
A lot.
Can we go back to my house now?
Yeah.
♪♪
("ANGELES" BY CROSSTIDE)
♪ Someone's always coming around here ♪
♪ Trailing some new give ♪
♪ Says I seen your picture
on a hundred dollar bill ♪
♪ What's a game of chance to you ♪
♪ In this world of real skills ♪
♪ So glad to meet you, Angeles ♪
♪ Picking up the ticket ♪
♪ Shows there's money to be made ♪
♪ Go on, lose the gamble ♪