♪ ♪
♪ I'd swim across
Lake Michigan ♪
♪ I'd sell my shoes ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I'd give my body ♪
♪ To be back again ♪
♪ In the rest of the room ♪
♪ ♪
♪ To be alone ♪
♪ With you ♪
‐
‐ Sorry.
♪ ♪
♪ To be alone with you ♪
‐ Life's a beach, Pudge.
Enjoy the waves.
♪ Alone with you ♪
♪ ♪
♪ To be alone with you ♪
♪ To be alone ♪
‐ Whatever she did,
it's not nice to call someone
a name.
‐ In this case, it is accurate.
She did rat.
‐ Then why are you trying
so hard to get it off?
‐ Thank you.
And thank you for
taking care of me.
I'm sorry I ran off like that.
‐ Well, you did not end up
in a coma, so that's good.
‐ I'm also sorry for
not saying any of this sooner.
I was just embarrassed.
‐ It's okay.
♪ Whoo ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I've never known a man
who loved me ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Whoo ♪
Sorry, Pudge.
Did I wake you?
Sound is an integral part
of the artistic experience
of this video game.
Ever bone snap has been
carefully rendered for
our listening pleasure.
Muting Mortal Kombat
would be like only reading
every other word of Jane Eyre.
‐ Where's The Colonel?
‐ He woke up half an hour ago.
When he saw it was me,
he just, um,
grabbed his things and left.
His loss, right?
That's a rhetorical question,
no need to answer.
‐ Why did you do it?
No one hates rats
as much as you do.
So for you to do
what you did...
‐ I appreciate your concern,
and I promise I will never
do it again.
But that's all I'm gonna
say about it.
In other news, are you
staying here for Thanksgiving?
Because I am.
‐ Thanksgiving?
‐ National holiday.
Native Americans gave us
maize and yams,
and we gave them smallpox.
Ring a bell?
Jake has a lot of
studying to do,
and he says
he can't concentrate
while staring at me,
so I'll be here...all alone,
by myself.
I‐‐um, I was actually thinking
you should stay here too.
In fact,
I have composed a list.
"Why Pudge should stay at
the Creek for Thanksgiving:
"a list by Alaska Young.
"One: because he is
a very conscientious student,
"Pudge has been deprived of
"many wonderful Culver Creek
experiences,
"including but not limited to
"drinking wine with me
in the woods,
"going out late at night
and lying in
"the dewy soccer fields
and reading
"a Kurt Vonnegut book
by moonlight.
"Two: while it will never be
mistaken for
"the fine dining experience
you might have
"in central Florida,
Miss Anne's Diner serves
a surprisingly tasty
Thanksgiving meal."
And three‐‐well, I don't
really have a three,
but one and two were
awfully good.
‐ I'm supposed to go home.
My parents are expecting me.
It's a pretty big holiday
in the Halter household.
♪ ♪
‐ Think it over
once we wake up.
♪ ♪
I'm not flirting.
I'm just tired.
♪ ♪
Extracted from MKV & Synchronized By X Person
Tell your parents yet?
Tell 'em what?
That you ain't
going home for Thanksgiving.
You ain't special, Pudge.
Alaska doesn't like to go home,
but she also doesn't like
to be alone.
Takumi stayed with her
last year,
and now it's your turn.
You think something
amazing is gonna happen,
and she gonna break up
with Jake,
and you're gonna experience
sexual fireworks.
But really, you're just gonna
drink shitty wine
and melt candles.
‐ So many candles.
This is what Alaska does.
What Pudge does is still left
to be determined.
‐ I think he's staying.
‐ He does that,
he's a rat by association,
and we'll have no choice
but to cut him off as well.
I'm not staying.
Yes, Alaska invited me,
but I didn't even consider it.
It's just crazy.
‐ Pudge, are you familiar
with the Indian Springs Treaty
of 1825?
Because you staying here
with Alaska is like
those three rogue
Native Americans
who tried to make a deal
with the white men.
Their own tribe executed them
for being traitors,
and the white men took
their land anyway.
‐ That was dark,
and I don't totally get it.
‐ Don't think with your dick.
That compute?
‐ That was not the moral
of the story.
It was
don't trust white people...
or alternatively,
don't trust people
who are known to be unreliable.
‐ Especially proven rats.
‐ Not to mention,
she has a boyfriend.
And God help us
if you unmoor her
from the rock that is Jake,
which ain't gonna happen.
'Cause she ain't gonna
never get with you.
‐ Bad wine, many candles.
‐ I get it.
I got it.
I'm Orlando bound.
‐ Miles, what's wrong?
‐ Nothing is wrong.
Every time I call,
doesn't mean
something's wrong.
‐ "Every time" you call
implies you call all the time.
‐ Yeah, sorry.
I know I missed a call
last week.
I'm just saving up
some new material
for when I see you in person.
Yeah, about that.
Now, no pressure on
Thanksgiving, Miles.
You don't have to fly in
for the holiday
if you don't want to.
‐ Um...
I don't?
No.
We can drive up
and pick you up.
This way...
Road trip!
We can't wait
to see you, sweetie.
I've already started making
the cranberry sauce.
‐
I hope you're making it
with those golden raisins.
For my golden boy.
Our son is coming home.
We'll see you soon, bud.
‐
Sorry, if I didn't sound
excited enough.
I‐‐I can't wait for
the cranberry sauce.
I hate that shit.
What the hell is it?
Is it a fruit?
Is it Jell‐O?
‐ Sorry.
You're not my mom.
Is this Miles?
It's me, Jake.
‐ Jake, as in Alaska's Jake?
‐ Yeah, I'm not sure
that's the case anymore.
I'm not sure about much, man,
other than I've called
this payphone, like, 40 times,
and she still hasn't
called me back.
‐ Did you get into a fight?
It seemed like
everything was great.
‐ Yeah, 'cause it was
until she ran out on me
when I was saying good‐bye.
And I haven't heard from her
since.
She's totally blowing me off,
and I feel like we're done,
dude.
Can't think of
a single reason why.
♪ ♪
‐ Yeah, nothing comes to mind.
‐ Miles, what's wrong?
‐ I just spoke to you.
What terrible catastrophe
could have befallen me
since then?
Um, actually,
something has come up.
♪ See you again ♪
♪ Time won't save ♪
‐ Hey.
♪ ♪
♪ Time won't save my soul ♪
‐ What are you doing?
‐ Just cozying up
with some Vonnegut
since he'll be
my only companion
this coming week.
I'll tell you all about it
when you get back.
‐ Or we could read it together.
♪ I'll see you again ♪
‐ I'm staying.
♪ Who knows
if I'll see you again ♪
Staying here at school,
remaining focused,
gives me the opportunity
to catch up on my studies.
Plus, the peace and quiet is
gonna be very restorative.
Orlando really is a city
on the go.
That fast‐paced lifestyle
can be very depleting.
I know what you're thinking,
but it's not 'cause
I wanna make out with her.
‐ Hold up.
I've been doing a little
back of the napkin calculations
in my head,
and I've been able to determine
that you're full of shit.
Yo, Takumi!
My mom's here.
Last chance to get a free ride
to the airport.
‐ That's your mom?
I'd love to meet her.
‐ Hey, sweetie!
How you doing?
‐ Pudge, I'm giving you
48 hours
before Alaska breaks your heart
or Jake breaks your face,
and we will not help you
pick up the pieces.
‐ Actually, um,
Alaska and Jake are
kind of on the outs.
‐ It's even worse
than I thought.
My condolences.
♪ ♪
‐
♪ Go ♪
♪ ♪
♪ So one, two, three ♪
♪ Take my hand
and come with me ♪
♪ Because you look so fine ♪
♪ And I really wanna
make you mine ♪
♪ I said you look so fine ♪
♪ And I really wanna
make you mine ♪
The Eagle's on vacation,
but we take no chances.
Dig.
♪ When you look
like that, do ya ♪
‐ Dig?
‐ Dig.
♪ ♪
♪ Big black boots ♪
♪ Long brown hair ♪
♪ She's so sweet
with her get‐back stare ♪
♪ Well, I could see ♪
♪ You home with me ♪
♪ Before I let you get away ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
‐ So, we're making candles?
‐ My reputation precedes me.
♪ I said, "Are you
gonna be my girl" ♪
Hell of a day for you
to decide to sleep in.
We're already behind schedule.
‐ Maybe next time
don't have me consume
large quantities of cheap wine.
‐ You had maybe one glass,
and it's not cheap.
Given how it tastes,
it's actually overpriced.
‐ Wait, behind schedule
for what?
‐ I've long believed
that the creek
that runs behind the school is
connected to Miss Anne's Diner.
Don't you wanna test out
the theory?
Come on.
Put your shoes on!
Come on, let's go!
"In the beginning,
God created the earth...
♪ ♪
"And he looked upon it
in His cosmic loneliness.
♪ ♪
"And God said, 'Let us make
living creatures out of mud,
"'so the mud can see what
We have done.'
"And God created every living
creature that now moveth,
"and one was man.
"Mud as man alone could speak.
"God leaned close
to mud as man sat up,
looked around and spoke."
Whoo!
- Told you.
- Yay.
"Man blinked.
"'What is the purpose of
all this?' he asked politely.
"'Everything must have
a purpose?' asked God.
"'Certainly,' said man.
"'Then I leave it to you
"'To think of one
for all this,' said God.
And He went away."
♪ ♪
Fucking love Vonnegut.
‐ Why don't you go home
for vacations?
‐ Because I hate ghosts
and home is full of 'em.
♪ ♪
I had a theory the creek
would get us down.
I just never thought how
it would get us back.
‐ I have a question for you,
Pudge.
‐ I have an answer for you,
Alaska.
‐ What's your favorite line
from Auden?
‐ Retraction.
I don't have an answer for you.
Never heard of Auden,
much less read him.
‐ Why'd you just assume
he's a man?
And how have you never
heard of him?
You poor, illiterate boy.
‐ So, Auden is a man.
"You shall love
your crooked neighbor
with your crooked heart."
That's my favorite.
It's pretty good.
Pretty good?
Sure, and bufriedos are
pretty good,
and the sun is pretty hot,
and this canoe is pretty heavy.
God, Pudge, it says so much
about love and brokenness.
It's...it's perfect.
God, you're hopeless.
‐
‐ You wanna go porn hunting?
‐ What?
‐ You can't love your neighbors
until you know how crooked
their hearts are.
You don't like porn?
Come on.
♪ ♪
♪ See me coming to town
with my soul ♪
♪ Straight down out of
the world with my fingers ♪
♪ Holding onto
the devil I know ♪
♪ All my troubles will hang
on your trigger ♪
♪ Take your eyes and your mind
from the road ♪
♪ Shoot your mouth if you know
where you're aiming ♪
♪ Don't forget to pick up
what you sow ♪
♪ Talking trash to
the garbage around you ♪
‐ Found it.
♪ Na na na na na ♪
♪ Na na na na na na na ♪
Ooh.
What do we have here?
♪ Na na na na na ♪
‐ Maui wowie!
‐ Aren't you worried
we're gonna get caught?
‐ No, Pudge.
You're right.
Maybe they'll go to The Eagle
and tell him
someone stole
their wine cooler.
♪ Handing out
a confection of venom ♪
♪ Heaven's drunk
from the poison you use ♪
♪ Charm the wolves
with the eyes of a gambler ♪
♪ Now I see
it's a comfort to you ♪
♪ Hammer my bones on
the anvil of daylight ♪
♪ Na na na na ♪
‐ Bingo!
‐ Bitches of Madison County.
‐ Hank is a cinephile,
so this will be delightful.
♪ Na na na na na ♪
She is...vocal.
Yeah, baby!
‐ Think we should turn it down?
‐ No, there's, like,
one teacher on campus,
and I highly doubt
Madame O'Malley is
skulking around with a glass
to the wall.
They just don't make sex
look fun for women.
That girl is just an object.
I mean, look at that.
‐ I am looking.
‐ God, Pudge,
never do it that hard.
‐ No.
Pfft.
I would never.
That would just hurt,
and that is torture.
That is not a man and a woman.
That is a penis and a vagina.
You know,
what's erotic about that?
Where's the kissing?
‐ Well...
Harder, yeah.
‐ I think in
their current position,
they can't really kiss.
‐ Well, that's exactly what
I mean.
Just by how they're doing it
is objectification.
He can't even see her face.
This is what can happen
to women, Pudge.
Please don't tell me this
turns you on.
The answer's clear
and not unimpressive.
‐
It's okay, Pudge.
I don't judge.
You have yet to unlearn
your patriarchal ways
of seeing.
Yes!
‐ I'm bored.
You finish taking care
of business
and find me later.
‐ Why haven't you
called Jake back?
‐ You heard about that?
I spoke to him, actually.
Well, you wouldn't understand.
It's complicated.
When you get older,
I'll tell you all about
the ups and downs of
an adult relationship.
‐ He said that
he called you 40 times,
and you still
haven't called him back.
Is that what adults do?
♪ ♪
‐
‐ Place is so nice.
Yeah.
Thanks for having us.
Your apple juice is ready.
Quite delightful,
full of the vitamins needed
to keep bodies,
both young and old, robust.
You didn't think I'd give you
any of the hard stuff, did you?
‐ Maybe for a minute.
I always suspected you were
a secret badass.
So all this hospitality,
does that mean
we're not in trouble?
It means you're fortunate
I'm the resident advisor
monitoring campus this weekend
and not Mr. Starnes.
He would not be so forgiving.
‐ The Eagle's a jerk,
insecure and small‐minded...
the classic combination of
a petty dictator.
‐ Mr. Starnes is
an admirable educator,
strapped with the thankless
task of protecting
200 self‐involved teenagers.
You can blame Sylvia
for interrupting
your indiscretions.
She needed to stretch her legs.
And that's how I stumbled upon
the two of you
imbibing whatever it was
you were drinking.
Definitely wasn't wine.
‐ Couldn't agree more.
‐ Tastes better
after the second glass.
The damage to your palates are
punishment enough,
that and the fact that
both of you are
spending Thanksgiving
at school.
Why aren't you
with your families?
‐ For me, it's mostly
catch‐up on homework
like your essay question.
I really need to take time
with that one...
didn't want any distractions.
A foolproof plan, Mr. Halter.
And you, Ms. Young?
Thanksgiving at the Creek is
kind of my tradition.
Yours too it seems.
Yeah.
Got no place else to be,
Dr. Hyde?
‐ I'm old and a bachelor.
Don't have much family left.
No kids or grandkids...
or great‐grandkids?
‐ I have two brothers,
but we haven't spoken
in decades.
Dysfunctional family.
Well, that's a topic
I can cozy up to.
Never married,
never wanted kids.
‐ And now you're surrounded by
200 of us.
Kinda ironic.
‐ But you must have been
in love before, right?
‐ That's kind of personal,
don't you think?
‐ It's the holidays.
We're sipping juice,
and Dr. Hyde is
a nimble conversationalist,
so he'll only answer
if he wants to.
‐ Yes, Ms. Young,
I've experienced love once.
That person's not around
anymore.
They ceased being around
many years ago.
‐ It's him, isn't it?
The guy you were in love with.
♪ ♪
‐ That was him.
‐ To love.
♪ ♪
‐ Ooh.
What'd those pie crusts do
to you?
Nobody wants a cracked pie,
Chip.
You can't eat a cracked pie.
Filling just falls out
and leaves you with crust,
cracked crust at that.
Don't think I don't know
you sassing me
'cause you're not using
your words.
I need some allspice,
some cinnamon, some nutmeg.
Thank you.
Hey, how are you?
Is that all?
‐ You gonna tell me
what's wrong with you, Chip?
I'm talking to you, young man.
Give me a straight answer.
Have a nice day.
Come on.
What's wrong?
‐ Everything just sucks, Ma.
Sara broke up with me
because I didn't wanna believe
Alaska was a rat.
Turns out, she is a rat,
and I'm pretty sure Pudge is
falling in love with her.
So I lost Sara,
and I'm losing Pudge.
He's spending Thanksgiving
with her alone at school,
and I'm pretty sure I know
exactly how that's gonna go.
‐ Wait, wait, wait.
They're alone?
‐ Yeah, and Alaska never goes
home for Thanksgiving,
and she convinced Pudge
to stay with her.
I hate 'em both.
They deserve each other.
‐ Look, you don't hate anyone,
Chip.
And what they deserve is
a home‐cooked meal.
You spend six years
in New York
after graduating from NYU,
contemplated Broadway,
but ultimately decided
that theater was too limited.
So you went to Berkeley
to try and save the world,
and that's where you meet him.
Was he a professor too
or a student?
‐ His name was Diego.
He was a bartender.
‐ A student of life,
even better.
‐ He knew everything about
wine and whiskey.
‐ And how'd you meet?
Was it love at first sight?
Love at first sound.
I was leading a march.
It was a "no nukes" rally.
I was a bit of a firebrand
back in the day,
came with teaching
political science.
He was in the audience,
liked what I said,
and sought me out after.
So you were teaching
politics at Berkeley.
When did you switch
to religion?
‐ When he died.
At the time, some people
coined it the plague.
♪ ♪
The plague...
it ravaged a generation,
a whole generation.
♪ ♪
I never thought
I'd outlive him.
He was younger,
so full of life.
Why would I?
One day he was opening
a bottle of Bordeaux
for our anniversary.
Then he began to lose feeling
in his fingers.
He couldn't hold a glass.
Then he couldn't hold my hand,
and six months later,
he was gone.
♪ ♪
"I poured my soul into the dust
by loving a man
who was soon to die
as if he would live forever."
♪ ♪
St. Augustine
from his Confessions .
‐ That's beautiful.
And so was he.
Diego was pure gorgeousness.
You were no slouch either.
‐ Our favorite thing
to do together was read.
Well, actually, I'd read
and he'd listen.
As much as he loved to read,
he loved listening to my voice
even more.
Ideas, Ms. Young....
ideas bonded us.
♪ ♪
‐ You should come with us
tomorrow.
We're going to
Miss Anne's Diner
for Thanksgiving feast,
involving a lot of tater tots.
If it sounds unhealthy
and greasy,
it's just because it is.
‐
Well, I appreciate
the invitation,
but I'm quite all right alone.
Sylvia is more than enough
company.
‐ Well, thank you for the juice
and conversation.
♪ ♪
‐ I'm sorry about Diego.
Don't be sorry.
I wouldn't give up
any of my time with him,
not even the suffering.
Go.
♪ ♪
That poor man.
He put up a good face,
but I could see it.
See what?
His eternal sadness, suffering.
Maybe that's what it is.
The labyrinth.
What if it's suffering?
What if it‐‐you know,
Bolívar wasn't talking about
life or death,
but that part in between?
That part when you‐‐you love
with all your heart
and then your heart breaks...
and you have to keep living
alone.
"How will I ever get out of
this labyrinth" of suffering?
‐ Alaska...
Are you suffering?
‐ Aren't we all?
It's kind of
the human condition.
‐ I mean you, specifically.
‐ Sure, I guess.
Everyone thinks I'm a rat.
no one is talking to me...
completely fucking alone.
♪ ♪
‐ You got me.
And Hyde just poured
his heart out to you.
And what about Jake
and all of his unreturned
phone calls?
‐ You're really worried
about Jake.
‐ Aren't you?
‐ Jake will be just fine.
‐ He didn't seem fine to me.
‐ It's really fucking
complicated.
‐ Well, then explain it.
I wanna understand.
‐ You can't,
so there's no point in trying.
‐ I wanna know everything
about you.
‐ You say that now,
but if you knew the truth,
you'd be running away.
‐ You asked me to come here
with you
and ride canoes
and go porn hunting,
and I did...
Because I'm all in.
No matter what you tell me,
I would never walk away
from you.
♪ ♪
‐ I need to go.
‐ Wait, what?
Alaska!
♪ ♪
Hi.
It's me.
Hey...
I was just heading out
to my aunt's.
Glad you finally called me
back.
‐ Yeah.
Yeah, I'm‐‐I'm sorry about
dodging your calls.
I just...
I just didn't really know
how to tell you.
‐ Tell me what?
‐ That I think
we should break up.
‐ Yeah, kinda felt like
that's where we were heading.
‐ I love you, Jake.
But I'm also kind of using you
as an excuse
for...for not dealing
with things...
For not wanting to be alone.
Takumi says you're my rock.
‐ Yeah, which I take
as a compliment.
I mean, a rock is
something solid you stand on.
It supports you.
‐ Or it keeps you stuck in
one place,
'cause you're too afraid
to leave it.
Also true.
I try to be one of
the good rocks.
‐ You are a great rock, Jake.
And I'm sure happiness is
waiting right on campus,
like, three doors down.
‐ Wait, Alaska.
Is this about‐‐
‐ Good‐bye.
I still love you, Jake
♪ ♪
Hey.
These are for us.
We are sleeping outside.
Get comfortable, Pudge.
♪ ♪
‐
‐ I broke up with Jake.
♪ Into light, into day ♪
‐ Wow.
...really?
It's probably for the best,
right?
♪ ♪
♪ Sunny day on a train ♪
♪ As a dusty record plays ♪
♪ Music box fades
into the rain ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Did all those dreams
turn out ♪
♪ The way they should be ♪
♪ ♪
♪ All the hopes you've had
of what you could be ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Sorrows ♪
Don't ruin it, Pudge.
♪ ♪
‐ I won't.
♪ Really make you happy ♪
♪ Into the haze ♪
♪ Your game ♪
♪ The hideaway from shame ♪
♪ Would you like to change
your name ♪
♪ Into the blame ♪
♪ Drive my car for days ♪
♪ From fear of second place ♪
♪ As you rearrange your face ♪
♪ Away from the race ♪
♪ Did all those dreams
turn out ♪
♪ The way they should be ♪
♪ ♪
♪ All the hopes you've had ♪
♪ Of what you could be ♪
♪ Your sorrows
and your sadness ♪
♪ They shine brightly ♪
♪ All those dreams
really make you happy ♪
♪ ♪
♪ What makes you happy ♪
‐
♪ Did all those dreams ♪
♪ Turn out the way ♪
‐ Colonel.
‐ Shit.
Looks like I got here too late.
‐ What are you doing here?
‐ I've been instructed
to invite you
to Thanksgiving
at Chateau Martin.
Miles, please inform Alaska
she is also invited.
♪ ♪
♪ All those dreams ♪
♪ Really make you happy ♪
‐ Get your shit,
and let's get going.
Dolores is waiting.
♪ ♪
Hey, Dolores!
‐ Welcome to our home.
It's not much,
but y'all gonna have a turkey
the size of the kitchen.
Stop right there, Chip.
You have guests.
‐ That you invited.
We show hospitality
at this house.
Don't mind him.
He's happy y'all are here.
You can get out now.
Chip will give you the tour,
right, son?
I gotta deliver Ms. Wigfield
her pie filling.
This is the bedroom,
kitchenette, TV.
Toilet's in the back
to the left.
That's the grand tour.
Now you get why I hate
rich people.
Sorry if this
makes y'all uncomfortable.
I know this must be foreign
to y'all.
‐ Not to me.
‐ You don't live in a trailer,
so...
‐ Poor is poor.
‐ I suppose.
But my mom paid for
every single thing in here
herself.
In addition to serving
fine cuisine
at Pancake Palace
as a waitress,
she also runs a store
off the porch,
just making sure the neighbors
got canned goods, batteries...
And toilet paper.
‐ I trust you've seen
the place.
‐ They can see the whole place
from standing right here, Ma.
‐ You two take and put
your stuff in my room.
I'm gonna take the sofa,
and Chip is gonna‐‐
‐ Wait, I gotta sleep
in the store, Ma?
‐ No.
‐ I don't mind the store.
- ‐ That's not necessary.
- Nonsense.
He's not surprised.
We always make room
for company.
Now,
it's tradition around here
that nobody eats
without working.
Everybody plays their part.
Miles, have you ever fried
a whole turkey?
♪ Julie ♪
♪ Meet me
by the vending machine ♪
♪ Julie ♪
I'm doing the carving.
‐
‐ Why, because you're a man?
‐ Because I know how to carve
a turkey.
Do you?
‐ I made the mac and cheese.
‐ And Chip and Miles
set the table.
It looks lovely.
Normally,
I would not allow the cooking
to be left to the women,
but better to have
good sexist food
than crappy boy‐prepared food.
‐ Those pumpkin pies
look amazing, Ms. Martin.
Wrong household.
We eat sweet potato pie
over here.
‐ And it's Dolores.
I think you're supposed
to drink white with turkey,
but I don't suppose
I give a shit.
And for you.
Come on, Ma, it's a holiday.
‐ Okay.
‐.
Alaska.
‐ Thank you.
‐ And Miles.
Thank you so much, Dolores.
You're welcome.
Let's say grace.
♪ Moving to London ♪
♪ While the cherry trees are
still in blossom ♪
♪ Julie ♪
Father,
you are mighty and strong...
♪ Hold me ♪
♪ Hold me through
the sweet hereafter ♪
♪ ♪
Man.
Hoo.
‐ That meal was
nothing short of art, Dolores.
‐ Best Thanksgiving ever.
Please don't tell my parents
I said that.
Ma, you are way too good
for the Pancake Palace.
‐ Unless you're gonna pay me
to feed you,
I think I'm going
into work Monday.
‐ Hey, where you going?
We haven't said gratitudes yet.
Sit, sit.
It's good to say thanks
out loud.
Just name something
in particular
that makes you feel blessed
today.
Really?
‐ I can go first.
‐
Thank you.
‐ Um...
I'm thankful for this
amazing food
and good company.
And I'm also thankful to have
a real home for Thanksgiving.
‐
We're happy to have you.
Alaska, you're up.
‐ I am...
Thankful for just having had
the best Thanksgiving
in a decade.
‐ I'm thankful that I am
the smartest person I know
from the trailer park
to Culver Creek.
‐ That dog won't hunt, Chip.
Nope.
The Weekday
Warriors may be rich,
but I got brains and a mama
who will take me further
than they'll ever go.
You're the best thing
on this planet,
even if you are forcing me
to sleep outside.
‐
Shut up.
‐ I love you, Ma.
‐ What about you, Dolores?
‐ Well, I am grateful
for my home...
For steady work
with decent people...
For getting the phone
turned back on last week,
and most importantly...
A boy who loves me...my son.
♪ ♪
As it says in Psalm 95:
"Let us come into His presence
with thanksgiving...
"Let us make a joyful noise
unto Him
"with songs of praise.
♪ ♪
"For the Lord is a great God
and a great king
above all gods."
Do you wanna dry these
or would that be anti‐feminist?
‐ In this context,
I'll say it's acceptable.
Do you know what time it is?
♪ ♪
It is Martin mother‐son
dance time!
♪ ♪
‐ Ma, not right now.
‐ Come on.
♪ ♪
♪ And the sunlight
hurts my eyes ♪
You got it.
Look how nice that is.
♪ And something
without warning, love ♪
♪ Bears heavy on my mind ♪
‐
‐ Okay!
♪ And I know it's gonna be ♪
That's good.
♪ A lovey day ♪
‐ Dance with me, Pudge.
♪ Lovely day ♪
♪ Lovely day, lovely day ♪
♪ Lovely day, lovely day,
a lovely day ♪
♪ Lovely day, lovely day ♪
♪ Lovely day ♪
♪ When the day
that lies ahead of me ♪
♪ Seems impossible to face ♪
♪ ♪
♪ When someone else
instead of me ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Always seems to know
the way ♪
♪ Then I look at you ♪
♪ And I know it's gonna be ♪
♪ ♪
♪ A lovely day ♪
♪ Lovely day, lovely day ♪
♪ Lovely day, lovely day,
lovely day ♪
♪ Lovely day, lovely day ♪
♪ A lovely day ♪
♪ Lovely day, lovely day,
lovely day ♪
♪ A lovely day ♪
♪ When the day
that lies ahead of me ♪
♪ Seems impossible to face ♪
♪ ♪
♪ And when someone else
instead of me ♪
♪ Always seems to know
the way ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Then I look at you ♪
♪ And I know it's gonna be ♪
♪ ♪
♪ A lovely day ♪
♪ Lovely day, lovely day ♪
♪ Lovely day, lovely day,
lovely day ♪
♪ Lovely day ♪
‐
‐ Do you know that Chip built
this whole store for me
on his own?
It was supposed to be
a father‐son project,
but that didn't quite work out.
Chip has a lot of
his dad's ways, I know.
His temper, stubbornness...
with one difference.
He has a big heart, always has.
I know things aren't right
with you two,
but he'll come around.
‐ I think things are better
already, thanks to you.
‐ You don't worry about Chip.
You need to focus on
that Miles.
He sees you.
Girl, he likes what he sees.
And look, you just give Chip
a piece of that
sweet potato pie...
usually does the trick.
♪ ♪
Let's get this stuff done.
‐ I know we just ate,
but Dolores insisted.
‐ I'm stuffed.
Maybe The Colonel wants mine.
Hey!
If‐‐if you want, I can sleep
in the store tonight.
He's not as mad at me
and‐‐and you can have the bed.
‐ It's not necessary, Pudge.
The Colonel and I will be
just fine.
I'll be back.
‐ She wants to sleep in
the same bed...
Together.
Be cool, Miles.
‐ Small trailer, son.
‐ Got it.
‐ I think Pudge
prefers pumpkin.
‐ This ends tonight.
‐ What, our fight?
Détente.
When we pull up
to Culver Creek tomorrow,
things go back to the way
they were.
You're still a rat.
‐ I know I broke our code,
but‐‐
Honor is everything, Alaska.
And people like us,
we gotta have
each other's backs.
‐ I have your back, Colonel.
Do you?
Or would you sell me out too
just to save your own ass?
‐ I would never do that to you.
‐ Is that so?
‐ You know me, Colonel.
We have a bond in
family fucked‐upness.
We're the same.
‐ We are not the same.
'Cause I would never do
what you did.
‐ You have to understand,
I didn't have a choice.
Paul and Marya,
they have each other.
They have their family.
They have their money.
They're fine.
They're fucking fine.
I had to do it!
‐ We can't be friends, Alaska.
And if you give two shits
about Pudge,
you'll cut him loose too,
because his life will be
a living hell at that school
if you're in it.
You wanna make things better?
Leave him alone,
and leave me alone.
Start there.
♪ ♪
‐
Hey.
Are you okay?
‐ I'm fine, Pudge.
Never better.
‐ I didn't say it earlier,
but the thing that
I'm most grateful for...
Is you.
The fuck, Pudge?
Fuck.
Why did you do that?
‐ What do you mean?
‐ You said you wanted
to sleep here...
together...
and maybe I misread
the situation,
but...I just want to make
you feel better.
‐ You thought fucking me
would make me feel better?
You sleep with me
and everything is perfect,
is that what you think?
No.
It's just you broke up
with Jake yesterday,
and then tonight,
I just felt like
maybe things were different.
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
‐ I told you not to ruin it.
I'm sleeping outside.
♪ ♪
♪ I'd swim across
Lake Michigan ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I'd sell my shoes ♪
♪ I'd give my body ♪
♪ To be back again ♪
‐ Can you stop the car, Ma?
♪ In the rest of the room ♪
‐ Here?
‐ Alaska needs to get out.
Can't be seen with her
on campus.
I am not putting
that child out.
‐ It's fine.
I'm okay.
‐ I‐‐I'll come too.
No.
Thanks for everything, Dolores.
♪ To be alone with you ♪
‐ This has gone too far
over some silly rat business.
‐ Serious business, Ma.
No offense, it ain't yours.
‐ Chip, I did not raise you
to put some
juvenile honor code
over treating people right.
Jesus never gave up on a soul
and neither should you.
The possibility of forgiveness
is what makes hope available
to anyone at any time.
‐ Yeah, well,
every time you forgave Dad,
he left a bruise to prove
why you shouldn't have.
♪ ♪
♪ You gave up a wife ♪
I'm not driving any further.
Get out.
Alaska walks, you walk.
‐ I think that means
I should walk.
Thank you so much
for everything, Dolores.
You listen to me.
I gave you all of me.
And your dad,
he gave you what he had left.
And this isn't me making
any excuses for him.
I know what he is.
That's why he's not around
anymore.
You got some ugly in you.
That's for sure.
But unlike your daddy,
you got space for more.
I know you care about
people in need...
That girl right there,
she needs you right now.
She's lonelier than you think.
♪ ♪
♪ Whoo ♪
Extracted from MKV & Synchronized By X Person
♪ ♪