G‐O, go, Culver, go!
♪ Ready for action,
nip it in the bud ♪
♪ We never relaxing,
OutKast is everlasting ♪
♪ Not clashing, not at all ♪
♪ But see my went to do
a little acting ♪
♪ Now that's for anyone asking,
give me one pass 'em ♪
♪ Drip, drip drop,
there it goes, an eargasm ♪
♪ Now you coming out
the side of your face ♪
♪ We tapping right into
your memory banks ♪
♪ Thanks ♪
I hate sports.
I hate people who play them
and people who watch them.
And people
who don't hate people
who play them or watch them.
‐ We don't come to the games
because we like sports, Pudge,
or because we think we have
a chance of winning.
Our athletic teams are so bad,
we don't even have a mascot.
I call us
the Culver Creek Nothings.
We come because I've been
kicked out of
36 games in a row,
and at this point,
my audience demands it.
♪ ♪
Cornbread!
Chicken!
- ‐ Rice!
- Peas!
‐ We got higher SATs!
‐ Enough.
‐ That is poor sportsmanship,
Mr. Martin.
‐ Aren't you worried
you're gonna get in trouble?
‐ Hell no.
Nobody has more school spirit
than The Eagle.
He bleeds green and gold.
He loves it.
Buy!
Sell!
‐ Trade!
Barter!
‐ You're much bigger,
but we're much smarter!
‐ You're out of here!
‐ Whoo!
37!
‐ Let's go.
Hit the bricks.
Come on.
I'll see ya next game.
All right.
Come on, guys.
Come on.
Quiet down!
Be respectful.
♪ I like the way you move ♪
♪ Whoo ♪
♪ I love the way you move ♪
♪ I love the way,
I love the way ♪
♪ The whole room fell silent ♪
♪ The girls all paused
with glee ♪
‐ 38!
♪ Study how to ride
the beat, you big freak ♪
♪ ♪
‐ Martin, I'm warning you.
That's it, get out.
‐ Get out of here!
Get out.
Out!
‐ 39!
Okay, here we go.
Settle down. Settle down.
All right, here we go!
‐ You ever gonna ask her out?
You know that was part of
the deal
when she helped you out
with the jury.
It's been three weeks.
‐ Yeah.
I'm just employing
the Miles Halter
seduction method.
‐
Which is what, you,
smiling shyly at her
from across the gym
until you're both dead?
You know, the only thing
you're worse at than smoking
is seduction.
Come on.
‐ Where are we going?
‐ Hi, guys.
‐ Hi, Lara.
♪ I like the way you move ♪
♪ Ooh, so sexy ♪
‐ Wow.
‐
‐ Am I the only one
who can't wait to see
where this riveting
conversation will lead
Friday night?
‐ Wh‐‐what's Friday night?
‐ It's the night the two of you
are going on
your first date together.
♪ I like the way you move ♪
‐ Yep.
♪ I love the way ♪
Extracted from MKV & Synchronized By X Person
♪ I was working in
the lab late one night ♪
You have nothing
to be worried about.
It's gonna be the most
low pressure date of all time.
‐ Why's that?
‐ Because we're all going.
Smart.
That way we can help fill
the awkward silences.
‐ How do you know there's gonna
be awkward silences?
‐ I've seen you and Lara try
to have a conversation.
It's upsetting.
‐ ‐
But understandable.
I mean, you have literally
nothing in common.
Nada.
‐ That's not true.
We both agree that
cosine‐based equations
are much more challenging
than tangents.
‐ Ooh, the bedrock of
every great relationship.
Pudge, you have been
on a date before, right?
‐ Yeah, of course.
‐ How many?
‐ Um, well,
in the fifth grade‐‐
‐ Post puberty.
‐ At my old school,
we went to see
the Orlando Symphony,
and I sat next to
Shelby Gerstein.
And we shared a box of
Mike and Ikes.
‐ Mike and Ikes?
‐ Stick with silence.
‐ It'll be fine.
Talk is overrated.
Human attraction is all about
eye contact and pheromones.
‐ The real question is,
who's my date?
‐ Your girlfriend's your date.
‐ Yeah, I knew you was gonna
say something like that
and ruin the moment.
Hey, ladies!
If it ain't Abercrombie
and Bitch.
‐
‐ It's nice to see you too,
Chip.
Come on.
‐ You just cannot
help yourself, can you?
‐ This truce just feels weird.
Sure, it's nice not to have
to sniff my shoes
every morning for piss,
but yesterday,
Longwell held the door open
for me,
and I almost punched him
I was so freaked out.
Where you going?
‐ Need more Fanta.
I shall return.
‐ Can you get me one?
‐ 'Sup?
‐ I'm only coming to you
with this
because you helped me study
for chem,
and you were cool with me
cheating off you for the exam.
You guys want the truce
to stay in place and so do we.
Coach said if any of us
got caught
pulling any more pranks,
we'd be kicked off
the basketball team.
‐ Having seen you play,
it could be a blessing.
No eye contact, Hank.
You know the rules.
I just got off the phone
with my old roommate, Paul.
Of Paul and Marya fame,
aka Trifecta Paul?
So named for being kicked out
for sex, booze, and weed?
How is that dude?
‐ He only got caught
because somebody ratted,
and he has a very interesting
theory about who was the rat.
Karma.
The Hindus' explanation
for cause and effect.
The concept evolved
over centuries,
seeking to understand
why man was born
and what happens when we die.
If we live a good life,
are we rewarded
in the next one?
If we hurt others,
what becomes of us then?
Ancient Hindus believed
there's only one fate
worse than death
and that was more life.
Those who live motivated
by transitory pleasures,
self‐interest were destined
to return to this earth.
Recycled, if you will,
forced to commence
their journey
again and again and again.
Those who lived with presence,
self‐examination,
they climb to a higher path
of the gods.
While it's not due
for some time,
I am going to give you
your final exam topic now.
♪ ♪
What is
the most important question
human beings must answer?
♪ ♪
Choose your question wisely
and examine how Buddhism,
Islam, and Christianity
attempt to answer it.
♪ ♪
Mi casa, su casa.
‐ We need to talk.
‐ Sounds serious.
‐ Sit down.
Paul and Marya transferred
to Harsden.
Guess their basketball team is
even shittier than ours,
'cause Paul's on it,
and they'll both be
at the game tonight.
‐ That's great.
I miss Marya so much.
‐ I never realized how uncool
I dressed until this second.
You know,
you're kind of a bad friend
for not talking to me about it.
‐ Both of those shirts
are completely satisfactory.
‐ I'm not going for
satisfactory.
What did Alaska say about
dressing for a first date?
I feel like I should be
kind of formal,
but it is a group thing
and in a gym.
So maybe not too formal.
Hey, a polo with a tie
isn't a thing, right?
I'm just gonna go ask her.
‐ You do realize
you're going on a date
with Lara not Alaska, right?
‐ Hey, man.
‐ Pudge.
‐ You ready to fall in love,
Mr. Halter?
‐ Do you like this?
‐
Not yet.
♪ ♪
‐
Um...I can‐‐I can do that.
I've heard you have
strong feelings
about ironing
and the patriarchal paradigm.
‐ I do indeed, but I like Lara.
And she deserves a man
who presents well.
‐ So, um...
what do I talk to her about?
‐ Just the same stuff
you talk to me about.
‐ Yeah, but it's different
with you.
‐ Get to know her.
Ask her questions.
Practice on me.
‐ Okay.
Um...
Why Alaska?
‐ Always comes up eventually.
...my mom,
she was something of a hippie
when I was kid.
You know,
wore oversize sweaters,
smokes a lot of pot...
and my dad, he was more of
a Republican type.
So when I was born,
she wanted to name me
Harmony Springs Young,
and he wanted to name me
Mary Frances Young.
So on school forms
and everything
up until I was seven,
they named me Mary.
And then I got to choose
my own name.
‐ Okay, but why Alaska?
‐ It's from an Aleut word,
Alyeska.
It means "that which the sea
breaks against."
And I love that.
But at the time,
I was just looking at
my dad's globe,
and...and I saw
Alaska up there.
And it was so big,
just like I wanted to be...
And so damn far away
from Vine Station, Alabama,
just like I wanted to be.
‐ Well, you're all grown up now
and fairly far away from home,
so congratulations.
‐ Getting out isn't that easy.
Hi!
‐
So I‐‐um,
I take it this is Jake.
‐ I think I forgot to tell you,
but tonight's a triple date.
I mean, triple and a half,
because Takumi's also coming.
Jake, this is Pudge.
‐ Hey.
Heard a lot about ya.
Hope your date works out
tonight,
'cause I wouldn't want you
stealing Alaska
out from under me.
‐ God, you're so adorable.
‐ Okay.
Um, I‐I'll see you guys
at the game.
Um, bye.
‐ Hi.
♪ ♪
‐ It's not too late
to turn back.
You and Jake can still enjoy
a nice quiet evening
away from the basketball game.
‐ But then how will Jake
see how much
our beloved team sucks?
Okay.
‐ Do you like basketball?
‐ Not really.
‐ Me too.
I mean, me neither.
I‐‐I don't like it.
‐ I always see you
at the games.
‐ Yeah, no, that's just 'cause
The Colonel has a thing,
you know.
‐ And there's AC in the gym.
‐ Yes.
Yeah, that‐‐that too.
♪ ♪
So, why Lara?
‐ Why what?
‐ I'm sorry.
Um...why is your name Lara?
‐ Um‐‐my parents had
the book of baby names
and they liked it.
‐
‐ Um...
‐ Cool.
That's cool.
‐...
♪ I know you're tired ♪
♪ ♪
Don't sit next to Lara.
‐ Why am I not allowed to sit
next to my date?
One of us has been
a girl her entire life,
and the other one has
never gotten to second base.
So if I were you,
I would sit down,
look cute and be
your pleasantly aloof self.
♪ ♪
‐ Bonsoir, bonsoir.
‐‐...
‐
‐ Merci, merci.
‐ So, Lee,
are you learning French?
‐ un peu.
Un peu.
‐
‐ I've had
a lot of free time
ever since Lois moved out,
so...
‐
I had no idea.
I'm so sorry.
‐ No.
I, um...you know, I mean,
it was a bit of a shock
when she told me
that she was leaving
and actually,
that she had fallen in love
with another man, so...
it's Brayden,
her Muay Thai instructor.
Also my Muay Thai instructor,
so that was‐‐...
All right, yeah!
Here we go!
‐ Go Creek Nothings!
Let's go!
You guys are terrible!
Boo!
You suck.
You definitely suck.
All y'all suck.
‐ Who's that?
Travis Eastman,
nicknamed The Beast
for obvious reasons.
Is that Paul?
He transferred to Harsden?
That's justice for you,
sentenced to attend
an even more
elite private school.
‐ There's Marya.
‐ Marya!
Marya!
‐ What are you doing?
‐
She must not hear me.
♪ ♪
‐
♪ Plus it gets
the ice cold women ♪
♪ To self‐reflect ♪
♪ Echoes of soul‐stuck
cry for help ♪
‐ I'm on.
Hey, Eastman!
I heard your daddy
was Bigfoot
and your mom was Chewbacca,
and y'all communicate
like this:
I know this may not be
a good time,
but my boy Takumi here
hooked up with your girl.
‐ Dude, I told you that
in confidence.
‐ Holy shit.
You were serious?
How'd you pull that off?
‐ Talk later, run now.
24, you out of here!
Hey, that's my thing!
Shit.
Pudge!
Come on.
I have some
first aid training, buddy.
You'll be all right.
‐ I am...concussed.
‐ Is he okay?
‐ I am concussed.
‐ Do you know what happened
to you?
‐ Beast got me.
‐ Do you know where you are?
Triple and a half date.
‐ That's a good sign, Miles.
‐
I'm so sorry.
Yeah, you definitely have
a concussion.
You should get to a hospital.
‐ I...
I have a car.
Let me get the permission slip
from the nurse
and change my clothes.
I have a concussion.
‐ Culver Creek wins by forfeit.
‐ That's the only good call
you made all night, Mr. Clean.
‐ All right, out of here.
‐ No, you out of here.
‐ Get out of here!
‐ 40!
Let's go!
That's what I do!
Come here, give me some!
‐ Marya, I was waving at you.
Didn't see me?
‐ Yeah, I saw you.
I just don't acknowledge rats.
- ‐ What?
- Hey!
Why don't you stay away
from her, you little rat?
We know what you did.
‐ I have no idea
what you're talking about.
‐ It was you.
Just admit it.
Did you want a single
that badly?
I was a good friend to you.
‐ It wasn't me.
I swear.
‐ You were the rat
this whole fucking time?
I expected you
to rat on us,
but your own fucking roommate‐‐
Hey, leave her alone.
‐ How you gonna defend her?
‐ Man, you better back up
the fuck out of my face!
Hey, you wanna fight
for a rat?
Hey!
Is there some sort of dispute
here that I can help settle?
You need to break this up
right now.
- ‐ It wasn't Alaska.
- Bullshit.
‐ She would never do this!
Mr. Martin, that's enough.
Let's go.
‐ It's unacceptable.
Now move.
We're moving.
♪ ♪
‐ Hey, babe, don't worry.
Miles is gonna be okay.
Alaska.
Hey!
Slow down.
What's the matter?
‐ I can't stay here right now.
Hey, Lara's gonna be
right back.
You're gonna be okay.
All right?
♪ ♪
Hospital time, Miles!
Here we go!
Okay.
‐ Am I concussed or is that
a green limousine?
‐ Both.
My dad owns a car service.
This one is retired
from his fleet.
Okay.
I'm feeling
dizziness and nausea,
symptoms commonly
associated with...
‐ I know.
I know.
Okay, M‐‐Miles, Miles,
Miles.
You need to stay awake, okay?
Okay.
Walk it off.
Let go of your anger.
‐ What about my anger?
‐ What are you angry about?
‐ You didn't have to do that.
Do what?
‐ Why is it that you always
have to get involved?
‐ Those assholes were
attacking her.
‐ Those assholes are
my friends,
and maybe they have
a good reason to.
‐ To what?
‐ Think about it.
Why would the Weekday Warriors
rat on their friends?
‐ Who knows why
they do anything?
‐ And you're telling me
that it wasn't you or Miles
or Takumi?
‐ Sure as shit wasn't.
‐ Alaska's the one
with the single now,
and she's the only one who knew
that they would be in there
smoking and having sex.
‐ You seriously think
she did it?
‐ Of course she did it.
But you're never gonna
admit it,
because you're blinded by
who she is...
or who you think that she is.
You always take her side
no matter what.
‐ Come on, that's not true.
Takumi, back me up.
♪ ♪
You really don't have
any alcohol in here,
not even a flask or anything?
‐ You stay away this weekend,
bet by Monday
everyone's moved on.
What kind of
college dorm is this?
‐ That's my roommate's closet,
by the way.
He's Mormon.
‐ I absolutely fucking
promise you
that no one is moving on.
Guess what they're saying
about me.
It's the worst thing
you can be.
‐ What, a murderer, a thief?
‐ The worst thing you can be
at Culver Creek.
I just need you to stop
fucking saying,
"It's not a big deal"
and that
"Everything is gonna be okay,"
because it is and it's not.
‐ Okay.
‐
♪ ♪
Was I just a raging bitch?
I don't like to use that word,
but I feel like
it applies here.
♪ ♪
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
You're so good.
You're such a good listener.
You're so patient beyond
what I or anyone deserves.
I just need to learn
how to quiet
this messed up mind of mine.
♪ ♪
‐ Don't move.
Jake, you in there?
Shit.
‐ Good, you're back.
Let's go to Scarlet's party.
‐ Fiona, hey.
‐ Hi.
I'm gonna assume
that Jake hasn't turned into
a giant cheating douchebag,
and you're Alaska.
It's so nice to meet you.
Jake has said amazing things.
‐ You said something
about a party.
‐ A proper college rager.
‐ I don't know, babe.
It's late,
and you've had a rough night.
‐ Exactly.
A party sounds perfect.
Come on, Sara.
It's a difference of opinion.
It shouldn't be the reason
we break up.
‐ Alaska's the rat, dipshit.
She's dead here.
And if she's still your friend,
then you're dead too.
‐ Only to
your idiot fucking friends.
‐ Chip, do you know
how much I give up for you
every single day?
Look, it's just us here.
So I'm not gonna tell Longwell
or Takumi for that matter,
but you can admit it to me.
Alaska's a rat.
Say it!
‐ I won't.
‐ I always stand up for you.
And you...
you stand up for Alaska.
If you're not gonna pick me
this one time...
I'm done.
It's over.
Okay.
You've made your choice.
‐ Sara.
Sara, don't go.
I love you.
Sara!
‐ Sorry our first date is in
an emergency room.
‐ It's fine.
But you're
my responsibility now,
and I take this very seriously.
At least we're alone,
and I can sit next to you.
‐ Yeah.
The whole aloof thing...
was an overthink.
Not my idea, I swear.
‐ I actually
really like hospitals.
They remind me of being little.
‐ Were you sick
when you were a kid?
No.
Um, my father was a doctor.
I thought he owned
a limo company.
He does now.
But in Romania,
he was a gastroenterologist.
He can't practice here,
so now he's an entrepreneur.
Wow, that's‐‐um,
that's a totally
different thing.
What was it like moving here?
‐ Hard.
We left a lot of family behind
and almost all of our things.
My father, he read about
"the Birmingham boom"
in a magazine,
but when we got here,
it wasn't booming anymore.
There was nothing for us,
not even a church.
My English was better
than my parents,
which made me feel like
I was the parent
and they were the kids.
‐ That‐‐that must have been
kind of fun.
‐ For a minute,
but being a parent is
much harder than you think.
♪ ♪
‐ You're a really cool girl
with interesting
life experiences.
♪ ♪
Holy shit.
Duck.
‐ Um, Miles,
who are we hiding from?
‐ Hyde.
‐ I‐‐I'm hiding but from who?
‐ No, he's here.
This is so awkward.
Why?
'Cause he's at the hospital.
‐ So are we.
‐ Yeah, but he's old and sick
and it's private.
‐ Well, Mr. Halter,
Ms. Buterskaya.
Well, well, well.
I'd shake, but I'm fighting
a bit of a cold.
Nothing serious,
but then pneumonectomy makes
everything serious.
I have one lung.
The slightest cough,
tiniest tickle in the throat
requires the utmost vigilance.
‐ That makes sense.
I've been concussed.
Likely not serious.
But his mother says
you can never be too careful
with head injuries.
‐ Words to live by, indeed.
I'd offer to stay with you,
but they've informed me
a taxi's waiting.
And, I see you have
much more charming company.
Enjoy this time together.
Small moments forge deep bonds.
Here we go, my dear.
♪ ♪
♪ Well, Daft Punk is playing
at my house ♪
♪ My house ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I'll show you the ropes, kid,
show you the ropes ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I bought 15 cases
for my house ♪
♪ My house ♪
♪ ♪
♪ All the furniture ♪
♪ Is in the garage ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Well, Daft Punk is playing
in my house ♪
♪ My house ♪
♪ ♪
♪ You got to set them up,
kid ♪
♪ Set them up ♪
♪ ♪
♪ You got to set 'em up,
ooh, ooh, yeah ♪
♪ You got to set 'em up ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, yeah ♪
♪ You got to set them up ♪
♪ Set them up ♪
♪ Downtown ♪
You know your name?
‐ Um, Miles Halter.
Okay, Miles Halter,
now move your eyes to the left,
towards that pretty girl
over there.
Do you know her name?
‐ Alaska.
Lara.
‐ Forgive him.
He's concussed.
♪ ♪
Whoa.
The Chi in here is really dark.
I need to be alone right now.
‐ Yeah, I'm glad we are.
I meant without you.
Look, I can see you're having
lady problems,
so I'm just gonna fast forward
to the real reason I'm here.
Hank told me before the game
that Marya and Paul thought
Alaska was the rat.
‐ And you didn't say anything?
‐ I did, to Alaska,
and she deflected.
But much like yourself,
I wanted to believe her.
‐ And now you don't?
Because of some
baseless accusation
by dumb‐as‐dog‐shit Paul?
There's more.
The night Paul and Marya
got kicked out,
I saw Alaska leave The Eagle's
house earlier that day.
♪ ♪
‐ What?
It didn't seem weird.
Alaska getting in trouble...
But then
she never mentioned it,
and that did seem weird.
But not so weird that I felt
like I needed to make it
a whole thing,
but now it is a whole thing,
so I thought I should
let you know.
I've tried puzzling it
every which way,
but it all adds up.
Hate to say it, but I think
Paul and Marya are right.
We'll, talk more later...
or not.
‐ Fuck!
‐
You know, puking after a party
is college rite of passage.
Getting it out of the way
in advance of enrolling,
you know,
it's probably a good thing.
I'm actually fine
with getting falling‐down drunk
in front of my boyfriend.
It's more everything else
that's happened tonight.
Which never happens.
I'm...I'm known for how well
I hold my alcohol.
♪ ♪
Wanna talk about it?
You okay?
♪ ♪
Look at all your books.
You know,
I have the same thing.
My Life's Library,
all the books I'm gonna read
before I die.
‐ I've read those books.
I actually don't put them
on my shelf
until I finish them.
It's nerdy, I know.
‐ No.
It's the habit of
a true intellectual.
You're so nice,
so pretty,
incredibly well‐read,
obviously...
Great taste in movies...
Alaska.
It's okay.
I'm not a threat to you.
‐ I know,
because you are
a loving feminist
who doesn't compete
with other women.
I can tell by the photo of
your still‐married parents
that...you come from
a good, stable home.
You're gonna be a good mother,
and Jake's gonna be
a great father.
‐ Alaska,
what are you talking about?
♪ ♪
‐ You don't get it, do you?
You and Jake are perfect
for each other.
‐ Jake and I are not together.
But you should be,
'cause you're both upstanding
high‐end people,
high quality people who deserve
other people
of the same quality.
♪ ♪
I need to go.
‐ Okay.
I can drive you,
or I can‐‐I can get Jake‐‐
‐ No, just tell him
I said good‐bye, okay?
♪ ♪
‐ You sure there's
nowhere else I can drop you?
‐ This is perfect.
♪ ♪
Thanks for picking me up
and not chopping me
into pieces.
♪ ♪
Just when I thought
I had lost faith in humanity.
♪ ♪
‐ I'm glad you're going
to be okay.
I was worried.
‐ Yeah, me too.
Thanks for taking care of me.
‐ It was nothing.
I liked it.
The doctor says you have to be
woken up
every four hours
for the rest of the night.
‐ Yeah, yeah.
I can set my alarm.
‐ If you sleep in my bed,
I could wake you up.
‐... Well,
where would you sleep?
I'm kidding!
Yeah, that seems like
medically sound advice.
We should definitely do that.
‐ Okay.
‐
Hey, stop the car.
‐ What?
‐ Stop the car!
Stop the car!
Alaska,
what are you doing here?
‐ Miles.
Why are you in a green limo?
‐ Um, it‐‐it's‐‐it's Lara's.
I have a concussion.
The basketball game,
and I‐‐I vomited
and went to the hospital.
‐ So you never...
you didn't hear?
‐ Hear what?
Are you okay?
‐ Totally.
I'm just tired...from all
the sex I had with Jake.
We‐‐um, we went back to
his dorm.
‐ Where is he?
Why didn't he drive you home?
‐ Christ almighty, Pudge.
Sometimes people just have
their own shit, okay?
‐ Did you get into a fight?
‐ Let's just make a deal.
I get in that
hideous green gas‐guzzler,
and you stop asking questions.
‐ Okay, but I don't know
how that's a deal.
Hi.
Hi, Alaska.
Evening.
Hi, Mr. Starnes.
Miles is okay.
‐ Happy to hear it.
You haven't seen
Alaska Young, have you?
I'm looking for her.
It seems she left campus
without permission.
‐ Well, we've been
at the hospital, so, ‐‐
There she is,
'cause she came with us.
‐ Go see the nurse
in the morning, Mr. Halter.
‐ Coming?
‐ Alaska seemed pretty upset,
don't you think?
‐ I think Alaska can
take care of herself.
‐ Yeah, probably.
But maybe I should just
go check on her.
Miles.
My room is this way.
‐ Thanks, though,
for everything tonight.
♪ ♪
You said that no one
would find out...
that if I did everything
you said,
everything would be okay.
And it's not,
because everyone knows.
This is all happening
because of you,
and I need your help.
‐ Alaska, this is happening
because of you.
You are in this position
because of the choices
that you made.
Choice one: you brought alcohol
onto campus,
which you knew was against
the rules.
And when confronted
with this infraction,
you had to face choice two:
work with me to identify
other rule‐breakers
and bring them to justice
or go home.
‐
Going home isn't an option.
You don't understand that.
If you kick me out of here,
I'm not gonna get
another scholarship
to another good school,
which means no college.
I'll be stuck there...
in that house forever...
With him.
♪ ♪
‐ Then I suggest you learn
to live here.
There are worse things in life
than being called a rat.
♪ ♪
Hey.
‐ Hey.
I have a concussion.
‐ While you were concussed,
you missed some shit.
Trust me, Pudge, hang on
to your innocence
as long as you can.
The truth will come out
soon enough.
In other news, Sara dumped me.
Round two.
Fight!
Shit.
‐ And you wanna know
what's lame, Pudge?
I really care about her.
I mean, we were hopeless,
poorly matched, but still.
I told her I love her.
I lost my virginity to her.
I don't know.
We fought, like,
94% of the time.
But still...I'm really sad.
Sadder than I thought I'd be,
anyway.
♪ So if you're lonely ♪
‐ I should have been nicer
to her.
♪ You know I'm here waiting ♪
‐ I don't know.
It's sad.
♪ Crosshair ♪
♪ I'm just a shot ♪
‐ It was nice, you know,
having somebody you could
always fight with.
♪ You leave me broken ♪
‐ I'm an angry guy, Pudge.
What do I do with that?
‐ You could fight with me.
‐ I could never be mad at you,
you harmless skinny bastard.
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ I know I won't be ♪
♪ Leaving here with you ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I say you don't know ♪
♪ You say you don't know ♪
♪ I say ♪
♪ Take me out ♪
♪ If I move, this could die ♪
♪ Eyes move, this can die ♪
♪ I want you ♪
♪ To take me out ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Take me out ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I know I won't be ♪
♪ Leaving here ♪
♪ With you ♪
Extracted from MKV & Synchronized By X Person
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh,
ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh,
ooh, ooh ♪
♪ I want you ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh,
ooh, ooh ♪
♪ I want you ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ To take me out ♪
♪ I say you don't know ♪
♪ You say you don't know ♪
♪ I say ♪
♪ Take me out ♪
♪ If I move, this could die ♪
♪ Eyes move, this can die ♪
♪ I want you ♪
♪ To take me out ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Take me out ♪