You wanted me to talk.
I talked.
Done.
- James McGill.
- James.
Hi, it's Robbie Finn from CC Mobile.
- Hi.
- Am I calling at a bad time?
No, it's fine.
Great. Good news.
If you're still interested...
we'd like to offer you
a position at our uptown branch.
- Oh, this is the cell phone store?
- You bet.
You made quite an impression
on Mr. Boyd.
He's talking about starting you off
as shift supervisor.
We can get your training done today,
if that works for you.
James? You still there?
I'm sorry, my plans have changed.
- I'm not gonna be able to take that job.
- Yeah?
- Sorry to hear that.
- Me too.
It's a real shame.
All right. Well,
have yourself a good day, James.
You too.
- You taking off?
- Yeah.
Hey, you want Thai for dinner?
I've got a hankering for that iced tea.
Yeah, that sounds good.
I should be back by 7.
Excellent.
What's up?
I was thinking...
that maybe you should
talk to someone.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I got a name.
He's not far from here.
I've heard good things.
Thought you'd give him a call.
It's a shrink?
It works for a lot of people.
Yeah. Okay.
Yeah. Well, thank you.
I just have to...
I have to check out my schedule and...
Oh, jeez.
I almost forgot to tell you.
I got a job.
- Really?
- Yep.
You're looking at Albuquerque's newest
mobile communications specialist.
I'm a shift supervisor even.
Be very impressed.
Cell phone sales.
I'm selling cell phones.
CC Mobile, I start today.
Jimmy, that...
- That is great.
- Yeah.
It's strictly gainful employment.
And then 10 months from now, poof,
I'm a lawyer again.
All right.
But you'll... Just give him a call
when you get a chance.
Of course. Absolutely.
Okay. Coffee's on.
Have a good first day.
You can count on it.
Mr. Finn, James McGill.
I've been thinking it over,
and I just can't pass up this opportunity.
If the position is still open?
- Hey, Marty.
- Morning, Kim.
- What's on for today?
- Well, let's see.
Papadoumian has settlement
conferences most of the morning.
Judge Clark has a pair
of corporate bankruptcies.
Munsinger looks like
criminal trespassing...
aggravated stalking
and some pleading down.
- Okay. Thanks.
- You got it.
And you'll have another 14 days
from when they file...
to tell me if you want to amend
your request for a pretrial conference...
or keep it the way it is.
I gather you're planning to amend, yes?
- Yes, Your Honor.
- Fine.
We'll reconvene in 30 days for a proper
pretrial conference, shall we?
I'll have an order out tomorrow.
Okay. Next.
CR2003114576,
State v. Scotty Blakey.
Ms. Wexler, do you have a matter
before the court today?
No, Your Honor. Just observing.
All right.
- Counsel.
- Good morning, Your Honor.
Crystal Eitzmann on behalf of the state.
It's your turn.
Oh, okay.
I'm Scotty Blakey, here for myself.
Mr. Blakey, you're here
because I called this case last week.
You didn't show up,
hence the bench warrant.
- Understood?
- Yes.
Your Honor, Mr. Blakey was given
a six-month suspended sentence...
along with the one-year provision.
There's no question this bench warrant
constitutes a violation of a generous deal.
I'm doing the community service.
Munsinger would like to see you
at the next recess.
The first place, the state was prepared
to charge this case as a felony...
and agreed to drop it to a misdemeanor
to avoid wasting time and resources.
In.
Oh, I don't wanna bother you
while you're eating.
Sit. Help me take my mind off
this eggplant and okra.
My wife insists, you know,
cholesterol, yadda, yadda.
Hurt your arm, huh?
Yes.
- Are you researching something?
- No, Your Honor.
Then you're working on
your procedure.
Just observing.
So Howard Hamlin's fine
with one of his associates...
sitting around my court all day,
whiling away the billable hours?
Actually, I left HHM.
- I'm a solo practitioner now.
- No kidding.
Field?
Mainly banking.
- How's business?
- Pretty good.
I'm outside counsel for Mesa Verde.
Mesa Verde.
You know, I heard about a case.
I think you might be the right person for it.
Interested?
Of course.
I can't share all the details just yet,
but I can give you broad strokes.
There's a young woman...
into her early 20s,
pregnant with her first child...
nearing the end of term.
Healthy as a horse.
She develops a complication.
She goes to the hospital for delivery...
and there's a mistake
with the anesthesia.
She aspirates vomitus
into her oxygen mask.
Stops breathing.
The baby's delivered fine.
But the young mother
suffers serious brain damage.
She's left comatose on a respirator.
The family is naturally devastated.
And they're broke, so they have no way
to pay for the young lady's care.
And to make matters worse,
the hospital refuses to take responsibility.
And they've hired one of the most
expensive firms in the state.
This is the plot of The Verdict.
Yes. Of course it is.
Because movies are the only place where
those once-in-a-lifetime cases exist.
You know what I got coming up next?
A janitor who threw his pee on his boss.
The one after that, she stabbed her
boyfriend over a grilled-cheese sandwich.
This is the real world, Ms. Wexler,
and you won't find...
any save-the-broken-lawyer cases in it.
Don't think you're first
to rediscover their love of the law...
by trolling my court. You're not.
The best thing you can do
is stick to Mesa Verde.
Make lots of money.
Give some to charity.
Having said that,
we've got perpetual PD overload.
So beware.
Next time I see you lurking in my court,
I'm gonna put you to work.
Understood.
Good luck to you.
Thank you.
Your Honor.
All rise.
Good afternoon. Please be seated.
Case CR2003114882,
State v. Lester Downes.
You wanted to discuss
the conflict of interest.
Yeah, before we get started,
I'll address defense's motion...
to disqualify opposing counsel.
Well, I read your brief very carefully,
but I'm not...
- Sorry I'm late.
- Hey.
- Paper?
- Thank you.
Twenty-two across is Esmeralda.
Bell ringer's love interest.
- It's The Hunchback.
- Quasimodo. Look at you.
- Hey, Anita.
- Hey, Fran.
- The usual for you?
- Yup.
Thanks.
- Thank you, Fran.
- You're welcome.
You know, a girlfriend of mine
is playing piano with her band tonight...
at The Launchpad.
They're pretty good.
You wanna go?
Tonight's group.
We could ditch.
I'd better go.
I told Stacey I'd be there.
Sure.
Maybe I could stop by after.
That'd be great.
You know, speaking of group...
I've been thinking
about reaching out to Henry.
I think he needs a friend.
Every time I see him, he seems worse.
Henry's fine.
- You talked to him?
- Don't need to.
Then how do you know?
Because that dead wife
he's always talking about never existed.
What are you talking about?
It's an act.
Why would you even say that?
The guy's story changes
every time he tells it.
Really?
No, I don't think so.
The romantic night at the Cubs game,
their first kiss?
- Yeah?
- It never happened.
You can't know that.
Wrigley Field didn't get lights until '88.
There were no night games
before then.
None of his details add up.
Well, maybe he just got the year wrong.
Why would anyone
make up a story like that?
Okay.
Here you go.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
Thanks, Fran.
You know...
you have a very suspicious nature.
Watch him.
He's got a tell.
Like a bad poker player,
when he's lying...
he rubs his wrist.
Okay.
Wanna put your money
where your mouth is?
What, you gonna come
to group tonight?
Make it interesting.
All right.
Ten bucks says that
when he talks about Judy...
different story.
- All right. You're on.
- All right.
CC Mobile, this is Jimmy.
Hey-o. How's the first morning?
Good, Robbie.
But, yeah, actually, it's a little...
a little slow.
Yeah. That store's always been
a bit calmer. Just bring a book.
- So this is a normal weekday?
- Mostly.
But wait till inventory week.
There's a line out the door.
When's inventory week?
You just missed it.
Is there any chance...
you could move me to a store
with a little more traffic?
Let's see, the Gold Street store's
always hopping.
But looks like
the schedule's all full right now.
Let's give it a couple weeks,
then we'll see.
- Okay, no problem.
- If I can, I'll swing by later.
- Keep up the good work.
- See you then. Bye.
Yeah, that's it. I remember
the smoked windows.
That's the one that ran us off the road.
That place is like a fortress,
we're gonna need numbers.
I'll pull Domingo and Javier,
and their crews.
We'll round them up...
and hit them tonight.
Amigos.
Fucking Salamancas.
Give yourselves up, idiots!
It's the only way
you're coming out alive.
You're out of bullets, give up now!
We cleared out the Espinosas.
They're all done.
And the Salamanca brothers?
Marco took a hit...
but he'll pull through.
They went back south
until the heat dies down.
It's territory, isn't it?
The Salamancas wipe out
the Espinosas...
Espinosa territory is up for grabs.
Cartel can't give it to the Salamancas.
So I think they give it to you.
Get some rest.
You have more to do.
It's a service to the people.
It really is. It's a nonprofit.
And it's a perfect fit. I mean,
what with his degree in sociology and all.
I think he's really come a long way.
It...
He hasn't even talked about
getting a job until this week.
The place is called...
Sorry. I'm so sorry.
Willa, you hadn't quite finished.
It's called the North Fourth Art Center.
I hope he takes the job.
Well, thank you, Willa.
That all sounds really promising.
Anyone else?
Stacey.
Today I got up and I took a shower.
Kaylee woke up on her own,
and got herself ready for school.
It was just a regular morning.
I made french toast for breakfast...
and we talked about
the self-pasting toothbrush...
she's making for the science fair.
I took her to school and went to work.
And then I realized it.
I don't know why I noticed it
just then...
but I hadn't thought
about Matty all morning.
Not once.
When I was making french toast,
why didn't I remember that it's his favorite?
I think about Matty
every single time I make breakfast.
But not today.
And they weren't just minutes.
There were hours
that I didn't think about him.
And if I can go hours, then...
then why not a whole day?
Why not a whole week?
I mean, what if I lose
the sound of his voice?
What if I forget him completely?
I mean, I know I won't,
that's impossible, but...
I don't know. I just...
I don't know.
Thank you, Stacey.
You're not alone, truly.
I mean, it might be painful,
but if you ask me, I'd say it's progress.
I mean...
a lot of us in this room have felt
the same things you're talking about.
I know I have.
I keep trying to get there.
You know, to live in the here and now.
I know that's what Judy
would've wanted, but it's hard.
This guy at work,
I've been avoiding him...
for the last two weeks...
ever since he got back
from his vacation to Australia.
She always wanted to go to Sydney.
But money was tight.
Finally, we were gonna go
for our 25th.
And that's when
she got her test results.
God.
Mike, you have something
you wanna add?
You don't wanna hear
what I have to say.
- Well, we're ready if you are.
- Yeah?
This guy was never married.
- What are you talking about?
- Mike, you know the rules...
I know your rules.
He's been coming in here for months,
selling you a bill of goods...
getting you all misty-eyed
and loving every minute of it.
- Pop.
- Stop.
That's just not true.
Yeah? Okay.
So I'll go to the public library,
and I'll get the papers from 1997...
and I'll run a search on Judy DeVore,
beloved wife of Henry DeVore.
Tell me I'll find her obituary.
She wanted to go to Australia?
Last month, it was Cuba.
Come on, Henry.
Let's look at the papers.
See if the math works.
Come on. Mike.
She's not there, is she?
Go on, say it.
You have no shame.
Well.
He came to the right place,
didn't he?
He knew you wouldn't notice.
And you didn't.
All wrapped up in your sad, little stories,
feeding off each other's misery.
You wanted me to talk.
I talked.
Leave now.
I don't want you here.
Leave.
Answer me!
I don't want to play games.
I told you to get out of my house.
You must go. Now!
My God.
What have they done to you?
Papa.
Papa, no.
You need the hospital.
Papa. Please.
Don't call. Not anyone.
911, what's your emergency?
I won't be safe if you do.
Hello?
911, what's your emergency?
I'm okay.
Can I rest here a little?
This one?
- What about this one?
- No.
This one.
Sure thing. Hernandez and Sullivan,
they led the pack and load.
My top guys.
Okay.
What's that say?
It's not a guessing game.
Thirty-eight degrees.
It should be 35.
Must've come in set wrong.
Goes out set right.
The manifest doesn't say
anything about...
Yeah.
We'll fix that.
This okay with you?
- Are you talking about the strap?
- I am.
Might be a little frayed...
- but the rest of them are fine.
- And you know this how?
So we're pulling
all the E-track straps?
Is that a question?
- We'll pull them.
- Call for Ehrmantraut.
Ehrmantraut.
He wants to see you.
Yeah?
Tonight.
Hold on.
We're not done yet.
I'm a Fanta guy myself.
Yeah, well...
you can buy a truckload.
Here you go.
Hey, whoa, whoa.
This is more than we talked about.
Bavarian Boy made quite a splash
at the collectibles expo.
- Bidding war.
- Wow, great.
But we know
you could've kept most of this.
I would've never known the difference.
Yeah, well,
you could've left me high and dry.
I'm liking this Hummel thing.
Cash came fast and clean.
Got any more where that came from?
No, not really.
Oh, bummer.
We're gonna do this again.
- I'll find something.
- Sounds good.
When you do, call the vet.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. New job, new phone.
You never know who's listening.
You wanted to see me, here I am.
In order for our arrangement to continue,
there is a matter we need to discuss.
Okay.
Do you have something to tell me?
If you do...
you would be well-advised to do so.
Nacho Varga.
I wondered when
you were gonna get around to this.
You came to me.
You asked for a favor.
You looked me in the eye,
you shook my hand.
And all the while, you knew
Varga was moving against my interests.
I said I wouldn't kill Salamanca.
I never promised to be his bodyguard.
So...
what now?
If you're gonna make a move,
you better make it.
But they're not gonna, are they?
You brought me here
because you have an ask.
So why don't you stop running a game
on me and just tell me about the job?