[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[HEAVY BREATHING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER ON POLICE RADIO]
MAN 1: Stop moving, please. Stop moving.
MAN 2: In the back.
QUINLAN: What is all this?
GIBSON: Some costume night or something.
School fundraiser.
Victim's on the back terrace.
QUINLAN: Witnesses?
GIBSON: Got plenty,
though not a lot of clarity.
[HEAVY BREATHING CONTINUES]
QUINLAN: How compromised is the scene?
GIBSON: They did a pretty good job of it.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER ON POLICE RADIO]
GIBSON: Already dead when we arrived.
[HEAVY BREATHING CONTINUES]
Oh, my God.
It wasn't just the mothers.
It was the dads, too.
The thing about fundraisers…
Everybody wants to
prove who's the richest.
They're vicious.
Add alcohol to the mix and the
fact that women don't let things go…
They're like the Olympic
athletes of grudges.
It's sexist how the
women always get blamed.
It all goes back to that
incident on orientation day.
And at the root of it
was Madeline Mackenzie.
There's nothing to be nervous about. Your
sister loved going there, and so will you.
In fact, you should be excited.
Do you know why?
Because this is the very
first day of the rest of your life.
Okay, woman.
I am not 100% sure
about that tone, young lady.
And could you please turn it down, please?
Thank you.
[BRAKES SQUEALING]
-Mother…
-CHLOE: Fucker.
[SIGHS] Chloe Adeline Mackenzie.
-You were thinking it.
-Because I was scared.
Do you want to see how teenagers die?
This is how.
This young lady in front of me is
driving and texting at the same time.
[HORN HONKING]
MADELINE: You're going to…
This is just…
I'll be right back.
They're dead.
GIRL 1: Don't reply yet.
GIRL 2: Yes, I have to reply.
-That's not…
-Excuse me. You must stop.
-You're going to kill yourself or…
-Mom?
-What is your problem?
-Abigail, what are you doing?
You were supposed to be on the bus.
She picked me up, okay?
You know how I feel about
you driving with texters.
-Mom.
-It is worse than drinking and driving.
Get out of the car.
I'm not getting out of the car.
-We're three blocks from school, okay?
-Fine.
-ABIGAIL: You're being ridiculous.
-If I catch you driving and texting again,
-I will find your mother…
-ABIGAIL: Mom!
-…and I will throw this at her.
-ABIGAIL: Don't…
[GROANS]
It's possible that had she not
fallen, nobody would've gotten killed.
JANE: Ouch.
-ZIGGY: Did you hurt yourself?
-No, the lady just tripped.
[CONTINUES GROANING]
Shouldn't we make sure the lady's okay?
Yeah.
Damn it.
Stay here. Keep your seat belt on.
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
I think I rolled my ankle.
You should get some ice on it.
I would, but I have to
get my daughter to school.
It's orientation day, and this
school is terrible about tardiness.
-Oh. At Otter Bay?
-Yes.
That's where we're going.
My son, Ziggy, is about to start.
-Ziggy, like Ziggy Stardust?
-Yeah.
-That's a great name.
-Thanks.
This is my daughter, Chloe.
The one shrinking from
embarrassment over there.
Are you new to Monterey?
Yeah, we just moved here a few weeks ago.
Well, I'm Madeline Martha Mackenzie.
I always say the Martha,
but no one calls me that.
They call me Madeline.
I'm Jane, Jane no-middle-name Chapman.
Jane no-middle-name
Chapman, I like you already.
You're an intrinsically nice person, and
I have a nose for these sorts of things.
No. What Madeline had was a
nose for everybody else's business.
Oh, my God.
Believe me, I know.
Um…
Do you need a ride or something?
I'm a stay-at-home mom myself,
so I'm happy to welcome
another full-time mom to the ranks.
You know, sometimes I
think it's like us against them,
the career mommies.
Them and all their various board
meetings that are so important.
Google this, Yahoo that.
Please, I think they spend more
time on those board meetings
than they do actually parenting,
if you know what I mean.
My mom's an active talker.
I actually have a part-time job.
Yeah, so do I, but it
doesn't really count.
The over and under in
this town is about $150,000.
I work in community theater, 20 hours
a week, so I'm definitely an "under."
-What do you do?
-Just bookkeeping.
So most definitely an "under," too.
When I grow up, I'm
gonna run a massive label.
Do you have plans?
No.
He's a little nervous.
Relax. He's walking in with Chloe.
It's like walking in
with the golden ticket.
[CHUCKLES]
CHLOE: What kind of
music do you listen to?
Don't tell me. Bowie.
An autopsy is still being conducted
to ascertain the exact cause of death,
but at this point, we can confirm
that the victim suffered a broken pelvis
and a fracture at the base of the skull.
Come on, guys.
Would you put the guns down?
Come on, Josh. You've got to
get your jacket zipped. Let's go.
[CELESTE SIGHS]
Perry, help me out here.
What did we say about
shooting Mom before noon?
-Guys. Really?
-Put the guns down. We have to go.
I am not kidding, really.
[IMITATING GUN]
[GIGGLES]
-First one to the car gets $1.
-Me!
See? Just takes money.
You are so bad.
You love it when I'm bad.
-So bad.
-You are. So bad.
We are so bad.
There should be like a five-year limit
on how long couples get to be gooey.
He's a lot younger than her.
-I don't wanna go.
-Do you really have to?
Just two days.
She must be pretty, you know…
In the bedroom.
Come on.
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
-Thank you. Great. See you then.
-It's so pretty.
-I know, right? Isn't it gorgeous?
-Yeah.
-Madeline, hello.
-Can me and Ziggy go play?
Yes, of course. You guys go play.
-Hi.
-How are you? Pregnant again?
Of course, when am I not?
-You look fantastic.
-Thank you.
Did you…
No, but you're sweet to think I did.
-Well, you look fabulous.
-Thank you.
Hi, Jackie. Good to see you.
Okay, Gabby is such a gossip.
We don't like her.
Hey, Maddie, have you seen Justin at all?
I think he whooshed past here.
Are we doing the wine tasting
next week at your house?
Yes, I'll send you an email.
-I don't know where Ziggy went.
-He's with Chloe. He's fine.
-Renata. Hi. Hi.
-Hi, Madeline, so good to see you.
-You look adorable.
-Thank you so much.
This is Jane Chapman. She's new here.
-Hi.
-Welcome. Renata Klein.
-Thank you.
-This is Amabella.
-Hi.
-Hi. That's a beautiful dress.
-How was your summer?
-It was wonderful.
Very busy with the kids and camp.
-Just flew by.
-Same.
How was yours, yeah?
Well, joined the board at PayPal.
What was I thinking?
Adding one more thing to my life?
-[CELL PHONE RINGING]
-But, you know… Oh, hold on.
These are my Hamilton tix.
-Okay.
-I've seen it four times. Yes.
I'll see you in there.
Here, come meet my best friend.
Celeste!
-Madeline.
-When did you get to town?
-Late last night.
-You didn't call me.
-No, I'm sorry…
-And how did you get more beautiful?
Oh. Baby, look, Madeline's over there.
Yeah, we'll exchange numbers.
-You're wearing the dress I bought you.
-I know.
My new dress, my new shoes,
my new friend, Jane Chapman.
-Hi, I'm Celeste.
-Hi.
She came to my rescue when I
was trying to save young lives.
It's a whole story.
I'm going to kill Abigail.
That's her son Ziggy right there,
playing with Chloe and the boys.
Can you believe that
they're in first grade?
I know. Take a lot of pictures.
Hi, Maddie.
-Come on, boys. Come on.
-Nathan, hi. Bonnie.
-And this is Jane.
-Hi.
This is Bonnie, Nathan, Skye.
-I love this.
-Thank you, I made it in Peru.
Of course you did.
You know, we were saying we should get
Skye and Chloe together for a playdate.
I mean, they're half sisters, and
they pretty much never see each other.
It's ridiculous.
Are they? Am I missing the math?
HARPER: We were all concerned
about Bonnie and Madeline
having their girls in
first grade together.
You know, what that would
do to the classroom dynamic?
And Abby is Chloe's
half sister, so we just…
Right.
-Thought…
-Of course. Just have Nathan call me.
Yes, they have a common sister.
Can I have a word with you for a second?
Um. Yes. Just one.
-I just wanted to…
-What?
I just wanted to ask you if you were
okay with swapping the weekends,
if Abby can come with us this Friday?
We're going up to Bonnie's mom's house in
Camarillo, and Abby
doesn't want to miss it.
She and Bonnie's mom actually
have a special connection.
-Of course.
-Are you sure?
Do I not look sure?
Jane, we should go
because it gets very busy.
Yeah, yeah.
-Chloe!
-Nice meeting you.
-Nice to meet you, too.
-Ziggy, come on.
Come on, Zig.
Come on.
We're looking at all angles.
Nobody has been ruled out.
So we're like seriously
using the word "murder"?
MADELINE: I actually like Nathan.
Okay, I wouldn't go all the way to "like,"
but I accept and acknowledge
that he's a decent human being.
I was just legitimately
surprised to see him at orientation
because it's not like he was
ever there for Abigail's first day.
-And Bonnie is his new wife?
-Yeah, she's the very pretty one.
In fact, she's so pretty and
free spirited and Bohemian
and all loving that
sometimes I just want to…
Punch her in the face?
Hey.
You're gonna love this girl.
Oh. Good, they saved my spot.
-Hello, Tom.
-TOM: Madeline.
What's happened to you?
I've gravely injured myself.
I've twisted my ankle.
Come meet my new friend, Jane.
CELESTE: Here, sit down.
MADELINE: This is my
knight in shining armor.
She rescued me like a
wounded dog in the street.
-Hi.
-And you know what else? She's funny.
-It's nice to meet you, funny Jane.
-Nice to meet you.
I think she just moved to this
area for your delicious coffee.
So do you mind getting three…
-Would you like one?
-Yeah.
Three, please.
And will you throw in something
chocolate that won't make my ass look fat?
-You got it.
-Thank you.
Everybody moves here for the education.
Basically, it's private school
at a public school price.
Anyway, you're gonna to love it.
Do you surf?
Do you have a husband or…
I shouldn't assume. Boyfriend, girlfriend.
I'm open to all possibilities.
No. No husband or partner. Just me.
-What about Ziggy's dad?
-Easy, girl.
-Okay. I'm just wondering.
-It's fine.
He's not in the picture.
He was actually never in the picture.
We weren't together.
Really?
-Where'd you move here from?
-Just Santa Cruz.
I was up there with my parents.
You know, she does part-time
bookkeeping as well. Isn't that great?
You know, I work at the theater,
and whenever we go into production,
we hire freelance accountants, so I'll
ask them if they have anything for you.
You're so nice. Thank you.
This is Monterey.
We pound people with nice.
To death.
What?
What do I know of Jane Chapman?
Nothing, nothing. I'm fine.
MADELINE: You okay?
Nobody knows nothing about anybody.
You can write that down,
Detective, and underline it.
MADELINE: What is it, honey?
JANE: It's weird.
Sometimes, when I'm in a
new place, I get this sensation.
Like, "If only I were here."
-But you are here.
-I know.
It's like I'm on the
outside looking in, or like…
You know, like I see this life and
this moment, and it's so wonderful,
but it doesn't quite belong to me.
Does that make any sense?
Yeah.
-Are you following this?
-Yeah.
And, like, I look at you,
and you're so beautiful.
-MADELINE: That's true.
-Stop.
And I'm not saying that to
embarrass you at all, but it is true.
-You are, and so are you, and…
-I agree.
You guys are just right.
You're exactly right.
And for some reason, that
makes me feel wrong, I guess.
-It's crazy. I know I sound crazy.
-It's not crazy.
I mean, I have no idea
what you're talking about,
but if you were crazy, you'd fit in
perfectly in this town. Right, Tom?
MADELINE: We love crazy people here.
TOM: We love our crazy.
Here's your cupcake.
MADELINE: Delicious.
MADELINE: We love crazy people here.
We love crazy people here.
["BLOODY MOTHER FUCKING ASSHOLE" PLAYING]
I will not say I'm all right for you
[SIGHS]
BONNIE: Hold it. That's right.
You guys hold it.
Two, one, and let go.
Good job, you guys.
Sweetie, it's fine. Go back to work.
-I'll pick up Skye.
-No, it's not fine.
She can be hostile with me, but not you.
And I'm coming with you.
You think she should keep all
of her emotions bottled up inside?
-Who does that serve?
-"Am I missing the math?"
Bitch.
Can't she see that it has
nothing to do with you?
None of us really see things as they are.
We see things as we are.
Come on, Bonnie. Give me a break.
The kids are in the same class together.
Madeline's eventually gonna discover
how smart you are, and when she does,
shit's gonna hit the fan.
The shit is really gonna hit the fan
if I don't tell her about this petition.
No.
Everyone knew Nathan was a
little bit of a dick, but a likeable one.
I never liked him.
I liked his wife.
CHILDREN: ♪ Otter in the bay
won't you come out to school ♪
♪ Otter in the Bay ♪
♪ We'll teach you all
the rules, beautiful ♪
♪ We'll teach you history
and share a cup of tea ♪
-♪ Otter, we're so proud! ♪
-[SCHOOL BELL RINGING]
MADELINE: There he is.
Look at him. He's so happy.
Hi.
[LAUGHS]
-How was it?
-Fun.
-Yeah?
-I made friends.
You made friends?
You already made friends?
That is so exciting.
Hi, guys.
Hi.
Mm, I missed you. Oh!
MADELINE: Now, where is the Chloe?
Chloe. Of course, she's networking.
Hi.
Okay.
I just want to introduce you to Juliette.
This is my Amabella's nanny.
-Hello.
-Nice to meet you.
She's French.
It's good for them to learn
a language, you know?
I just thought it was nice for the
nannies to get to know each other,
-have your own little support system.
-Renata, Jane is not a nanny.
She's a mom, just young.
-Like you used to be.
-Oh. Like we used to be?
-Sorry, I…
-Maddie, hi.
BONNIE: I heard you're
working at the community theater.
I wanted to talk to
you about the petition.
About the play.
There's been some concern
about it being appropriate.
There's a petition to stop the play?
That play was kind of
like a lifeline for Madeline.
It tethered her to a purpose.
I signed it.
MS. BARNES: Excuse me!
-You signed it?
-I did.
I didn't know you were involved, though…
MS. BARNES: Excuse me, could I
have everyone's attention for a moment?
She grew up wanting to be Betty Grable.
MS. BARNES: All my first-grade kiddos…
Ended up Betty Crocker.
-Chloe, come on.
-…and their parents, please.
-I'm here.
-Hi, Chloe.
Wonderful.
Okay.
We have had such a wonderful morning.
But we need to have a little chat,
and it's a little bit serious, okay?
Someone hurt Anabella.
-Oh.
-MS. BARNES: Excuse me. Amabella.
And I would like whoever it
was to come over and apologize,
okay, because we don't hurt
our friends at school, do we?
-No.
-MS. BARNES: No, we don't.
And if we do, we always say…
-KIDS: Sorry.
-Sorry. That's right.
Because that's what big
first-grade children do, right?
Yeah. Yeah.
Baby, someone hurt you?
Amabella, do you think it
was an accident maybe?
An accident? Look at her neck
for God's sake. It has marks on it.
Amabella, sweetie, can you
tell me if it was a boy or a girl?
-It was a boy.
-It was a boy?
-What was his name?
-Maybe she doesn't want to say.
Mrs. Klein, my problem
is that the children
don't know one another's names yet,
so Amabella cannot tell me who…
-We're not gonna just let this go.
-Absolutely not.
Mrs. Klein, I'm so sorry.
Is she okay?
I don't know. They're gonna find out.
Just give her a second.
-Did you see what happened?
-No.
-RENATA: You're her teacher.
-MS. BARNES: You know what.
-You should be doing something.
-Um… Uh,
Amabella, sweetie, could you
maybe point to the boy who hurt you.
Come on, really?
-This boy?
-No.
Him.
-This boy?
-AMABELLA: Yes, he tried to choke me.
-What?
-ZIGGY: It wasn't me.
AMABELLA: Yes, it was.
MS. BARNES: Ziggy, sweetie,
we just need you to say sorry.
I didn't do anything.
[WHISPERS] I didn't.
Are you sure that it was
this little boy, sweetie?
Could she have got it wrong?
Can you say you're sorry to Amabella?
-She's hurt quite badly.
-ZIGGY: It wasn't me.
Ziggy, look at me.
-Promise.
-RENATA: We don't have to lie.
We just want to say we're sorry.
-Ziggy doesn't lie.
-Right.
I can assure you,
Amabella's telling the truth.
If my son says he
didn't do it, I believe him.
Of course.
You know what? I don't know if this
is the best way to deal with this, so…
I agree, but now we are,
so maybe the child needs to
take responsibility for his actions.
And he needs to see
there are consequences.
Little boys don't get to go
around anymore hurting little girls.
And none of us want to raise bullies, so…
We don't have to pretend we didn't do it.
It's okay. I believe you.
Jane, can you just
make your son apologize?
MADELINE: Renata.
Stay out of it.
I can't make him apologize for
something that I know he didn't do.
Of course you can't.
We will schedule a
meeting for another time.
-We can handle this later.
-RENATA: Okay.
This is unacceptable.
Let's go, baby. Let's go, sweet pea.
MS. BARNES: All right,
everyone, thank you.
I'm so sorry, honey.
Not that there's a right
little girl to strangle,
but he picked the wrong
little girl to strangle.
Ziggy.
Do you see her neck?
If you ever touch my little girl like that
again, you're gonna be in big trouble.
-Excuse me.
-Well…
Now you owe him an apology.
-Madeline!
-Renata!
The battle lines were drawn right there.
We've never had a Trivia
Night end in bloodshed before.
MADELINE: How dare she
speak to a child like that?
I mean, isn't there some
sort of students' bill of rights?
Celeste used to be a
lawyer, a very good lawyer.
I mean, isn't there due process
for a first grader? Am I wrong?
Well, he's not being punished, so…
Well, he's being stigmatized
as a bully, and that's worse.
I think we should not make
a big deal out of this. Just…
Madeline.
Harper Stimson, hi.
Jane just didn't fit here.
Kind of like a dirty old Prius
parked outside of Barneys.
It was a mistake to let people compete,
but that is not what got someone killed.
HARPER: Hi, Celeste. How's Perry?
Oh, uh. He's good. Thank you.
-HARPER: If it'll help…
-MADELINE: You didn't ask me how Ed was.
I'm sorry.
Listen, Renata happens
to be one of my best friends,
so if there's any way I can play the role
of peacemaker in all this, just please…
Thank you, Harper.
That's very sweet of you to offer.
And I'll make sure and let everybody
know that Renata is your best friend.
I'm only trying to help.
MADELINE: I'm sure you are.
This could get ugly.
We could just let it blow over.
Things never blow over
once Madeline gets involved.
They blow up.
Bitch.
[MUSIC BLARING ON STEREO]
There was a 4-by-3 stellate,
full-thickness scalp laceration
located on the superior
occipital portion of the scalp.
We also discovered a full
thickness scalp contusion,
and associated gall and
subgaleal hemorrhages,
and a putrefied and liquefied brain.
So it was a lot of blood?
Chloe?
MADELINE: Thank you.
The teacher couldn't
have handled it worse.
"Point out the suspect, Amabella."
Are you kidding me?
I take it this Jane is kind of damaged.
Why do you say that?
-You're drawn to damaged people.
-I am not.
Even Celeste, there's something
wounded about her, if you ask me.
I didn't ask, and I'm not
drawn to damaged people.
Do I like to help people in need? Yes.
Last time I checked,
that's not a character flaw.
-MADELINE: I see that look.
-Hmm.
I just think, to be accused
of something so horrible
on your very first day at a new school,
-can you imagine anything worse?
-ABIGAIL: Mmm…
Being choked, maybe?
Bruises heal. Stigmas can last a lifetime.
ABIGAIL: You don't think assault
victims bear lifetime emotional injuries?
I don't know.
Is there a recent study you'd
like to illuminate the
family about, Abigail?
-All right.
-"All right" what?
Nothing.
Well, it's not nothing. It's something.
You said, "All right."
Would you like to assign meaning
to that, or was it just a nervous tic?
CHLOE: Guys, Mom had a day.
And don't you start.
I'm on your side, woman.
-I'm gonna go with "nervous tic."
-ABIGAIL: Mm.
I think his "all right" meant,
"Let's not fight at the dinner table."
Were we fighting?
-I didn't realize we were fighting.
-We were about to.
You said I probably read some
study on women assault victims,
and I would've responded with,
"No, I learned it at my
self-defense and wellness class,"
which happens to be taught by Bonnie,
who, by the very mention of her
name, makes your eyes twitch,
so Ed said "all right" to head it off.
I see.
Well, speaking of Bonnie, do
you know what she did today?
She signed a petition to stop
our production of Avenue Q.
This is the play where the
puppets drop the f-bombs?
-Cool.
-It is not only not about that,
but it's actually a play
that you should see
because it deals with the
struggle of young adults being
-disillusioned with life…
-Hmm.
…feeling demoralized and defrauded
by the false promises of tomorrow.
I can get all that here.
What'd I say?
CELESTE: Look at me. Look into the camera.
It's okay. So helpful.
Big smile. Can you give me a big smile?
Smile.
Just look at me and smile.
One shot. Look at the camera.
Look at me. Look at me.
Yeah. But a big smile.
Can you guys… And just a
little bit closer together, guys.
-Hey, Mom, you wanna play Angry Beaver?
-In a minute.
I just need to get one more shot.
I think the angry beaver's
gonna get you, Mom.
-Is he? I hope not. That…
-[ROARS]
-The angry beaver is back!
-[SCREAMS] Oh, my gosh!
And he is hungry!
Hungry for mama's beaver.
[GIGGLING] Stop.
Oh, she is delicious.
Have a bite of this!
Mm.
Hi.
What happened? You're not going to Vienna?
No, I still have to go.
I'll get a flight out tomorrow instead.
-Really?
-Yes.
It's their first day of school tomorrow.
I can't miss that.
-Thank you.
-Of course.
[BOYS MAKE KISSING SOUND MOCKINGLY]
-JACKIE: I kind of agree with Thea.
-[PERRY IMITATES GUNSHOTS]
People over 40 shouldn't be gushy.
It's not cute.
I mean, last week she came home and
peeled potatoes at a homeless shelter,
and she couldn't stop talking about what a
beautiful experience it was to contribute.
I mean, she whines if I ask her to set the
table, but peel one
fucking potato with Bonnie…
Well, Bonnie is a positive influence.
What, you'd rather Abby be
out with her friends smoking pot?
I just feel like they're
both slipping away.
You should've seen Chloe today.
She just marched right into that
school like some sort of a woman-child.
She never turned around.
And it was like she was on her own.
"Bye, Mom. See you later."
I just feel like they're gonna grow
up, and they're gonna be gone,
and it'll just be you and I, and we're
gonna be on to another
chapter of our life,
and you have another chapter.
You have a business.
And I don't. I'm a mom.
This is my universe, and currently,
that universe is in meltdown
because my oldest daughter prefers
to hang out with her fucking step-thing.
Hey. You will never lose them.
And you know that.
I just thought one day
Nathan would get his due.
For some reason, Abigail
would love me more.
He hasn't paid in the
slightest, for any of it.
And now he's got Bonnie, and
she's younger and sexier and prettier,
and she probably gives
mint-flavored organic blow jobs.
And Abigail likes to hang
out with him and be buddies.
And he got it all. He won.
Okay.
Well, speaking as the consolation prize,
we're gonna have a pretty big
fight about what you just said,
-Oh, no, no, Ed.
-…but not tonight.
-Not tonight.
-I did not mean it like that.
You are the greatest thing
that ever happened to me,
and don't you for one
minute think anything else.
It's just entirely possible for me
to love you with all
my heart and still feel…
Hurt over your ex?
Come here.
[MUSIC PLAYING ON STEREO]
[GROANS]
You okay?
Fine.
I'm not liked.
What was that?
I said I'm not liked.
That simply isn't true, honey.
It's one thing to be demonized
for having the temerity of a career.
But look at this.
Look at our life.
What kind of person chooses to work?
Certainly not a mother, by
any acceptable standards.
[SIGHS]
You should have seen the
way they looked at me today.
[CHUCKLES] Oh, my God.
And on the one morning that
I chose not to go to the office…
Yep.
…and join my daughter for her orientation,
and then defend her when
she's physically assaulted.
And, yes, I reacted
humanly like any mom would.
And then I'm met with utter contempt.
Look, I'm sure there are those,
women especially, who would resent you.
I mean, look at you. Come on.
You're beautiful, hugely
successful, financially independent,
on the school committee,
the board of the aquarium.
Huh?
-Right?
-Yeah.
Hell yeah.
And to make matters even worse,
you're beyond sexy.
-Mm.
-[CHUCKLES]
Women.
You all want to be the
envy of your friends,
but God forbid you garner too much of it.
The mom was awful,
but the girl seemed fine.
JANE'S MOM: So what's going to happen?
Um…
I don't know. The teacher said that
we should just let it go, move forward.
So I guess that's what we're going to do.
I still don't understand why
you chose to move there
all alone.
I'm not. I have friends.
People here are actually very friendly.
People need family in
their lives, you know?
I really just think you
should come back here…
Do we have to get into this
every single time we talk?
I'm gonna go check on Ziggy.
Jesus.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
JANE'S MOM: Hello.
Hey, Mom. I'm sorry.
I love you.
I love…
[WATER DRIPPING]
[WHISPERING] Hi, baby.
Sorry I woke you up.
Am I in trouble?
No, of course not.
You trust me, right?
And I trust you.
Did you touch that little girl, baby?
It's okay if you did.
Ziggy?
No.
Okay.
I believe you.
Why did she say I did?
I don't know.
Maybe she was confused.
She probably just got it wrong.
Am I going to have any friends?
Of course you are, my love.
You're going to have so many friends.
Come here.
[KISSES]
-[SIGHS]
-[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Yeah?
Honey, I think we need
to talk about the SAT tutor.
Oh, Mom.
I know what you're going to say,
but your scores just aren't good
enough right now, honey, and I…
You know, the whole college
thing, it's kind of a racket.
Especially liberal arts.
People go off and study
Homer for four years,
and then you graduate with a
ton of debt and no job prospects.
Okay, let me be clear.
You're going to college.
Ed didn't go, and he's doing all right.
Yeah, but Ed studied computer engineering.
Do you want to be a computer engineer?
And Dad, he never went, and
he seems perfectly happy in life.
[SIGHS]
Career-wise.
Okay, well, let's just
finish that analogy.
Let's not leave Bonnie out of this.
Her little cup just runneth
over with happiness, doesn't it?
With no college degree at all.
I'm sorry that you hate
Bonnie and that I'm unable to.
I don't hate Bonnie.
And this isn't about
your dad or Bonnie or me.
This is about you,
Abigail, and your future.
And what I'm saying is,
the metric of success is not
always monetary or career-related.
It can be a much more holistic equation.
Okay, I'm not gonna pretend
to be the person in your life
who knows the most about
the holistic wonder of the world.
What I do know, and I
know this for sure, Abigail,
is that, when it all comes down to it,
you have to be independent,
and you have to be self-sufficient.
I was a very young mother when I had you.
All that it-takes-a-village crap
is only good to a certain extent
because even the best-laid plans
of your life go poof in your face,
and, in that case, you need to be strong
and independent and
educated and a strong woman.
You said "strong" twice.
You kind of remind me of a space
alien right now. You know that?
Good night.
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
No.
PERRY: "E is for Ernest,
who choked on a peach.
[BOYS CHUCKLE]
"F is for Fanny, sucked dry by a leech."
-[PERRY MAKES SUCTION SOUNDS]
-BOYS: Ew!
That's what you get if you go down
to the beach without me or your mom.
-MAX: But…
-Strictly forbidden.
There's too many leeches down there.
MAX: The last time we
went, there was no leeches.
PERRY: No, of course not 'cause I
was there, and they're scared of me.
What, you didn't notice?
Every time we go down there,
I just, like, scare them away.
JOSH: How?
PERRY: With my…
[BURPS] Burping superpower.
[BOYS GIGGLING]
PERRY: Do you want to know a secret?
JOSH: What?
My superpower, I actually get it from Mom.
-BOY: No.
-PERRY: You don't believe me?
What did we have for
dinner tonight with the steak?
-BOY: Mom's spinach salad?
-PERRY: Mom's spinach salad.
[PERRY IMITATING BURPING]
[BOYS LAUGHING]
PERRY: Top secret, okay?
[CONTINUES IMITATING BURPING]
"G is for George, smothered under a rug.
"H is for Hector, done in by a thug."
-[GASPS]
-[PERRY CHUCKLES]
-You startled me.
-I'm sorry.
-These are great.
-Mm-hmm…
Hmm.
The boys mentioned something
about a little girl getting hurt today.
Mm.
Renata Klein's daughter.
She wasn't really injured. She was just…
Oh, look at this. Could they be cuter?
PERRY: Oh.
I actually think this is my favorite.
-I love your finger there.
-Stop.
-Post it.
-All right.
People are gonna love it.
[CELESTE LAUGHS]
Well, so what happened?
With that girl.
A boy tried to choke her.
Are you serious?
[SIGHS]
Well, no one witnessed it,
but she was pretty distraught,
and she had marks on her neck.
Which boy?
Um, this new boy, Ziggy.
I mean, he seemed really sweet,
and I met his mom, and
she couldn't be nicer, so…
Yeah.
Well, to be safe, we should tell Josh
and Max to keep their distance from him.
-I don't think that's gonna be necessary.
-Honey.
-If the kid is violent, we don't…
-No, he's not violent.
Well, how do you know he's not violent?
What, because he seemed sweet?
-First off, he could be innocent.
-Or he could be guilty.
We don't want the boys to be
getting mixed up with the wrong crowd.
-They're six.
-They're not to associate with him.
You're being ridiculous.
[CELESTE SIGHS]
[CELESTE YELPS]
-The boys will stay away from that kid.
-Take your hand off me.
If I can't be here to look out for
them, I need to know that you do.
I asked you to remove your fucking hand.
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
[PLAYING PIANO]
ABIGAIL: Is that a song
from your puppet show?
Yes, but it's really more
than just a puppet show.
[RESUMES PLAYING]
[SOFTLY] ♪ Four years of college ♪
♪ And plenty of knowledge ♪
♪ Have earned me this useless degree ♪
The play means a lot to you, right?
I'll tell Bonnie to start a new petition
in favor.
Mom, are you okay?
You're not like dying
or anything, are you?
No, I'm not dying.
What would make you ask me that?
You seem a little wobbly.
Are you having one of
your massive periods?
No.
What people don't tell you
is that you lose your children.
As beautiful and wonderful as you are now,
the little girl whose curly
hair I used to detangle,
the one who had bad dreams
and would crawl into my bed,
she's gone.
Yeah.
And I guess that's why
I'm feeling a little bit…
Compounded by the fact that
your little sister's going to first grade.
I'm losing my babies,
which has been clinically
compared to a massive period, I think.
I'll always be your baby.
Bonnie's like a friend, you know?
Maybe even a best friend sometimes.
But I'm your daughter,
and you're my mother.
Mom, don't cry.
-Don't do that, okay?
-I'm sorry.
[ABIGAIL CHUCKLES]
I'm sorry. [SNIFFLES]
Your hair, though, get it
out of your beautiful face.
I can still call you babycakes, can't I?
-Not in public.
-Okay.
-[BOTH CHUCKLING]
-[DOOR OPENS]
Oh, no.
Not another one. You go back to bed.
[PLAYING PIANO]
[HUMS ALONG SOFTLY]
I love that song.
Do you want to play it together?
[INAUDIBLE]
We're treating the matter as a homicide.
We have no suspects as of yet.
I will say that we do believe we have
spoken to the person or persons involved.
Ziggy.
Baby.
What are we doing?
You were sleepwalking again, baby.
CELESTE: Where are we
going to do the interview?
QUINLAN: Right here.
CELESTE: I'll just put my purse down here.
NIPPAL: The first thing I
said, it wasn't just the mothers.
GABRIELLE: It was the dads, too.
STU: The thing about fundraisers…
MELISSA: They're vicious.
STU: It's not the male grizzlies
you've got to watch out for.
It's the sow.
GIBSON: Tell me about Celeste Wright.
GABRIELLE: [SCOFFS]
Something had to be wrong.
JACKIE: So elegant, so…
MADELINE: Volcanic.
Madeline Mackenzie?
Things never blow over…
Once Madeline gets involved.
They blow up.
Team Renata versus Team Madeline.
BERNARD: The battle
lines were drawn right there.
So we're like seriously
using the word "murder"?
[MUSIC PLAYING]