Alright, let's do an exercise.
You can build anything in the
world you want with your compression.
What's it going to be? Three, two, one, go!
- A new Internet.
- What? Why?
(DYNAMIC INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC)
I am your lead investor;
- You will respect me as such.
- I do not respect you because
you are fat and poor.
So you're telling me that the
perfect application of my
algorithm belongs to Gavin
Fucking Belson. (CLANGING)
(CLATTERING)
We need his patent and his funding.
Eventually this will render
- every server obsolete.
- Holy shit.
Welcome to the future, Gavin.
Whoa. Hold it.
- Oh no!
- Son of a bitch!
I have spoken to our top
LPs to start a new firm.
Would you care to jump ship with me?
You are, after all, my best friend.
What?
♪
(SHATTERING) Gavin just fucked off to go
- find himself who knows where.
- What is it?
It's the patent. He just signed
over full ownership to me.
There is a loud man here to see you.
Kendo in the house.
- (LAUGHING)
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- (SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
- _
_
♪
Welcome home, and congratulations
on getting your business back.
Thank you, and I should congratulate
you on your breakthrough.
I can help you get where you want to go.
I'm pretty sure I know where I
want to go and how to get there.
I shall look forward to the fight.
♪
(SILENCE)
Jesus! What the hell did he order?
(SINGING IN SPANISH)
No, no! No, no, no! Stop! Stop it! Stop it!
(DYNAMIC INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC)
_
♪
Oh my God. (CHUCKLES)
These are our new offices?
RICHARD: Yeah. Well,
this is just the lobby.
We're up there on the
second floor, but yup.
These are so nice.
(GASPS) There's a fireplace.
Oh! I am a sucker for an
intuitive kitchen layout.
Follow me, right up here.
Trust me, you're gonna love it.
GILFOYLE: It's hard to believe
your pathological inability
- to make a decision finally paid off.
- (LAUGHS)
- (DINESH LAUGHS)
- JARED: Wow. Richard, well done.
Dude! Look at this place, huh?
- JARED: Oh, I love it.
- (DINESH LAUGHS)
So, when do these guys move out?
Oh, no, this isn't our space.
Our sublease is straight through here.
(DINESH LAUGHS) Okay.
I welcome you
to Pied Piper's new home.
- Huh? (LAUGHS)
- (LIGHTS HUMMING)
Hoo-hoo-hoo!
It's... it's very white.
Yeah, it's minimalist, you know?
Sharp, clean lines.
I was thinking about maybe putting
my desk here in this corner.
Jared, you over here, right?
Dinesh, Gilfoyle, maybe up
against this wall or over there.
You know, just take a
minute, walk around the space,
see where the mojo takes you.
I mean, we've got some
good feng shui in here.
Really good. (MIMICS FISTS WHOOSHING)
Richard, the plan was to hire 15 coders
and some assistants and... and other staff.
Where exactly would we put them?
Easy. Right around here.
Look, guys... (CHUCKLES) the price
(EMPHATICALLY) is unbelievable.
I'm just happy that we got to it
when we did before anyone else.
I... I emphatically
vote that we move on this
now, if we all agree.
I mean, we do agree, right?
I cannot put this delicately, so...
(SHOUTING) Are you
fucking kidding me, dude?
You want us to work in here?
This is a fucking black site, Richard!
A black site would actually be better,
because at least we'd be
protected by the Geneva Convention.
This is fucking with my
eyes. Can I get outta here?
Okay, ha... hang on.
Richard, can I talk to you
- for one second, please, privately?
- RICHARD: Sure.
- Ah!
- See? Plenty of outlets.
(WHISPERING) Richard... what are you doing?
We can easily afford a
place with windows and... air
where you can maintain a
connection to time and space.
(WHISPERING) If... if we spend
all that money, it's gone.
Okay, don't you remember Jack Barker
squandering all our runway
for those fancy offices
or Russ Hanneman spending nearly
every cent we had on fucking swag?
I'm sorry, man, we do
not get another chance.
This is it.
GILFOYLE: There is no point whispering.
We can hear every fucking
word you say in this sweatbox.
I can hear you gulping, Richard.
No, you can't. (GULPS)
(GROANS)
Richard, it is my firm opinion
that if we were to take this space,
our new hires wouldn't be coding,
they would be having panic attacks.
No, come on. I'm doing a
really good job of hiding it,
but I'm having one right now.
(BREATHING RASPINGLY)
I gotta get the fuck outta here.
- Jared, you okay?
- I will not be back.
Wait, guys, hold on. Jared, I'm
gonna get you some water, okay?
(JARED GASPING)
(THEME MUSIC PLAYS)
Synced and corrected by louvette
www.addic7ed.com
♪
RICHARD: Okay, what about
this guy, Chris Berger?
He's a very skilled engineer.
He was very funny when we met
with him. I think he'd be great.
He was oddly tall, don't you think?
GILFOYLE: Yeah, pass.
Alright, what about Blake Kang?
His beard hair looked like head hair.
And his head hair looked like beard hair.
Come on! It's been a fucking month.
I got us these expensive-ass offices
because you wanted them, and now
they're just sitting here, empty,
because you guys won't agree on anyone.
Look, I'm going to be seeing Laurie Bream
at this stupid Innovation
Hall of Fame event tonight,
and she's gonna ask how hiring is going.
She's 11 months pregnant
and highly irritable.
What am I going to tell her?
That we've just been dicking
around the whole time?
- We're not dicking around.
- Really?
What about this?
GILFOYLE: Touché.
He sent in a professional
headshot. We had no choice.
Plus his face looks like a taint.
Okay, yeah, fair.
But look, I sent you
63 good people.
I spared you kilt guy,
openly alt-right guy,
obviously closeted alt-right guy,
and the guy with the
stupid fucking pizza app.
It was so lame, it would
somehow make you hate pizza.
- You have to choose.
- Dude, it's easy for you to say.
You're gonna be off CEO'ing,
going to fancy galas.
We're the ones who have to like be
in the engine room with these clowns.
GILFOYLE: They have to
meet our rigorous standards.
I mean, look at the
three we've already hired.
- Just look at them.
- There they are.
♪
Stallions.
GILFOYLE: Each one more
magnificent than the last.
DINESH: Perfect.
Yeah, they're glorious, obviously,
but that's only three of them,
and they're luxuriating here
in this huge fucking palace
that is costing us a fortune, so
hurry up and pick these fucking coders,
and stop acting like a couple
of spoiled millionaires.
Alright, Richard,
your tuxedo is pressed
and ready for the gala.
I put a touch of mint in the steamer.
You're gonna look like Richard
Gere from "Pretty Woman."
Maybe tonight you'll fall
for a radiant sex worker.
♪
During my sabbatical from Hooli,
I toured the wonders of the
world, seeking inspiration
from mankind's greatest achievements...
The Parthenon, Angkor Wat,
the Great Pyramid of Giza.
But it wasn't until my flight home
that I had my epiphany.
Yes, those wonders
are visited by thousands
of people every year,
but 2.4 million people
visit HooliSearch every minute.
(MUTTERS) God, what a fucking douchebag.
- (PEOPLE SHUSH)
- GAVIN: And then it occurred to me.
What I have built is a
far greater achievement,
than any of the ancient world.
And the ideal version of myself
was the man I already was.
- (APPLAUSE)
- (CLASSICAL SCORE PLAYS)
Thank you.
Richard? Richard Hendricks.
- Oh. Huh? Okay. Yeah, hi, Duncan.
- Yeah.
Me and my guys were just talking
about you and your pizza app.
(CHUCKLES) Oh yeah. I bet.
Our algorithm finds you
the cheapest, fastest pizza,
and it's... it's awesome.
- Yeah. Definitely.
- It's actually so awesome...
That... oh man, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna have to pull my resume.
Oh, you're pulling your...
(CLICKS TONGUE) Oh no.
Yeah, I just don't feel as psyched about it
- as I do about Sliceline.
- Sliceline?
That's the name of your app?
- Yeah.
- Oh God. (CHUCKLES)
- Great.
- Yeah, it's a pun.
- Is it?
- Yeah. It rhymes with Priceline.
- Okay. Just... so, it rhymes? Okay.
- Yeah. It's a rhyming pun.
Anyway, there might be some major
VCs around here, so I gotta go mingle.
Okay.
It's the... it's the worst
part of this job. Am I right?
(LAUGHS) I'm kidding. It's
the best part of the job.
Okay.
(MUTTERS) What an asshole.
- Richard.
- Gavin, hello.
Don't you look cute in your Sunday best?
How's that little bunny Internet going?
Mmm. New Internet. New.
Unlike your old Internet.
(CHUCKLES) You know, I'm
glad I ran into you, Richard.
I was actually starting to
feel bad about what I did today.
Oh? And what was that?
Invent the MOSFET transistor? (CHUCKLES)
It's old technology.
It's very old, like you.
No. I've heard that
you're trying to staff up.
Over the past few months,
you've met with just
about every distributed
systems developer in the Valley.
Okay, well, not everyone.
63 of them, and as of
4:30 p.m. this afternoon,
I hired them, all 63 of them.
Yeah, I had to pay through
the nose, but you know what?
- ♪
- That look right there on your face?
It makes it worth every penny.
You know what? Enjoy
the reception, Richard.
You too.
♪
JARED: Yeah, he wasn't bluffing.
He hired all of them.
Even my boy Blake Kang?
He was a good one.
I'm sorry, uh, your boy?
I thought his hair was backwards?
You guys were lukewarm on him and everybody
else for all kinds of stupid reasons.
Well, now that they're unavailable,
their strengths are more readily apparent.
And I don't want to point
fingers, but we wouldn't be here
if you hadn't let Gilfoyle and
me waste so much time being picky.
What? I was dying to move faster.
I was just respecting your process.
Our process sucks.
Your inability to stop us from sucking
is a failure of leadership.
At least we still have the stallions.
Ah. Those stallions.
Look at 'em. Magnificent.
Sit back down. Just sit in your chairs.
Jared, um...
call alt-right guy and cologne boy
and all the other rejects,
and... set meetings.
Well, I did a little
digging on the alt-right guy,
and he's pretty involved in a
campaign to eliminate black emojis,
but there might be another option.
Do you remember Kira Pickford?
Yes, actually. Yeah, good coder,
but she had her own company.
Well, that's true, except
that her company, Optimoji,
just lost their second round of funding,
so they're basically on life support.
So?
So, what if, instead of
building a team, we acquired one?
DINESH: But Optimoji has
30 people. We only need 12.
Well, we'll just insist
that she let the other 18 go.
We have a lot of leverage.
Richard is a shrewd negotiator,
and I'm, you know, spirited.
♪
Look, Kira, this is a fair offer.
But... I've got 30 great guys.
We're like family,
and you only wanna bring along 12?
I have to do what's right by my guys.
Look, I know what it's like to only be able
to rescue half your family,
- and it's awful, but what can you do?
- Shh, shh.
- Sometimes there's only one...
- Jared, okay, stop.
Um, look, Kira, you're not gonna
find a better deal than that.
Your company is close to bankruptcy
and we all know that there are a lotta
coders out there in this old town,
and we could go to any of 'em,
but we wanna go to you, so...
kinda feels like we've got
all the cards here, huh?
Richard. You keep following me,
I'm gonna call the cops.
- (CHUCKLES) I'm just kidding.
- Oh.
- Hey, I'm Duncan.
- Hey. Kira.
Hey, guess what company just got
his Series "A" Term Sheet? Huh?
Oh, the Sliceline. (LAUGHS)
Congrats, yeah.
DUNCAN: Yeah, we're staffing up like crazy.
Speaking of staffing, how about
all those coders you lost, man?
I'm sorry. That must've been a real blow.
What coders?
Um, I'm sorry, I don't mean
to be rude, but this is boring.
Thank God I didn't accept your offer.
I'd be the only guy working for you
now that Gavin Belson swooped in
and tactically mass-hired every single
distributed systems
engineer you were looking at.
Gavin hired all of Richard's coders?
Not everyone. Not everyone.
Yup. The guy is savage,
and so are my guys if they
don't get their caffeine,
so nice meeting you,
Kira. Cool. Cool, cool.
What were you saying about
holding all the cards?
All of my coders or none of them.
Take it or leave it.
♪
DINESH: What?
GILFOYLE: What the fuck?
- Do you have...
- Do you...
DINESH: Jian-Yang!
Jian-Yang... would you please explain
why we each found some random
Chinese guy asleep in our beds?
Yes, you work all day.
Your rooms are always empty, so they use.
- The fuck they do.
- Yes, it's not your house.
This is not your house either, Jian-Yang.
This is Erlich's house.
Do you think Erlich
would want your guys here?
No. That's why I invite
them, because I hate Errich.
We are not Erlich.
You are from Errich's administration.
No, we are not. Nobody has
heard from Erlich in months.
This isn't working. I'm gonna drag
your cousin the fuck outta my lair.
JIAN-YANG: No, this is my cousin.
♪
Engineers, welcome.
You are 63 of the top distributed
systems developers in the Valley,
and we're looking forward
to working with you.
Hooli is the future, and your future is...
♪
the Box Two.
So, are there any questions?
Yes?
I'm sorry, but what if we
don't wanna work on that?
Weird. This is our flagship product,
but I'm sure we'd all like to hear
what you would like to work on.
A decentralized Internet, like we were
going to build with Richard Hendricks.
Actually, that's the one thing
we can't do here at Hooli.
Yes?
Sorry. You only hired us because
Pied Piper wanted us, right?
Untrue. Go on.
And Pied Piper only wanted us
because of our ability to help
build a decentralized Internet.
Can't speak to that. Continue.
And you're telling us
that even if we want to,
we can't build a
decentralized Internet here.
May I ask why not?
Because Richard owns the patent for it.
Yes, third row, red hoodie.
- How did he get it?
- I gave it to him.
- You in the back?
- Why did you do that?
It was a Buddhist act of selflessness.
Well, I'm also a Buddhist, and I
would never give him the patent.
I mean, once he builds that Internet,
he's gonna render Hooli's entire web-based
ecosystem completely obsolete.
I mean, everything you're
doing here is antiquated.
That's not a question. That's a statement.
You know what?
Fuck you guys. I don't
want you working on my box.
It's too good for you. "Antiquated"?
Why did you all take my money
then, you entitled little pricks?
You all think you're John Lennon
until someone waves a dollar in your face!
You know what? Get outta here!
Go on, just wander the campus
for four years until you vest.
See what I care.
I'm serious! Go! Goodbye!
Thank you very much!
(MURMURING)
Assholes. "Antiquated"?
Fuck do they think they are?
I'm in the Innovation
Hall of Fame. Are they?
Speaking of, they sent over
the official inductees portrait.
You and your peers. Handsome bunch.
Fuck.
Fuck!
♪
- So, Mr. Yang...
- It's Mr. Jian.
In China, last name comes first.
Okay. Mr. Jian, you say that Erlich
Bachman wrote this letter...
- to you?
- Yes.
"This is Erlich. Hello.
"I am gone, but Jian-Yang
is a very good friend and very smart.
"I want him to be the leader of the house
"and control all of the friends.
Goodbye. Bachman Erlich."
Yes. I want his house.
Thank you.
Okay, I don't technically
represent Mr. Bachman.
I'm Pied Piper's corporate counsel,
so my exposure to Bachman pertains only
to his 10% ownership of the business.
Errich owns 10% of Pied Piper?
This was not a lie?
Sadly, no, that's very, very real.
That's worth a lot of money.
It's promising tech. One day
it could be worth a shit-ton.
Shit-ton. Yes.
Mr. Jian, you seem like a good guy.
Um, this letter is not a legal document.
I mean, maybe a skilled
attorney could make a case
that in the absence of an existing will,
this would serve as one in
the case of Bachman's death,
but as far as I can tell, the guy is not...
Dead.
Yes. Errich is dead.
Do you happen to have...
a death certificate
- or any... any form of proof of...
- Yes.
I can get it now.
♪
RICHARD: Our deal with Kira
is for 30 fucking coders.
Where in the hell are we gonna put them?
Well, I suppose we could put
three more workstations here,
and then two more over there.
It'd be crowded but cozy.
They'll be all holed up together
like the Branch Davidians.
Yeah, but, I mean, are we sure
this is the right thing to do?
I mean, I don't want
to crowd the stallions.
Are we sure taking on all 30 of
Kira's guys is the right move?
We can get up and running.
They all know each other,
so we won't have to play the name game.
- Yeah.
- (PHONE RINGS)
- Ron, hello.
- Hey, buddy. Hang on just a second.
No, the... the exit is...
The exit is the other way.
God damn it.
Um, Richie, you know
a guy named "Jee-Ann"?
Jan? Uh, no.
Well, I know a "Jan the
Man," but she's a woman.
Look, did you... did you talk
to the Optimoji board yet?
Uh, did we close the deal?
Uh, well, a deal closed.
Another bidder came in with a better offer,
- so they went with them.
- RICHARD: (ON PHONE) What?
Was it Gavin fucking Belson again?
RON: (ON PHONE) No, it was a new company.
Real smart, clever name.
Sort of a pun that rhymes.
- ♪
- (DOOR OPENS)
Oh, hello, dickheads.
I hope I'm not interrupting your plotting,
- (KEYBOARDS CLACKING)
- you sneaky little dinks.
Kira, you and I had a deal, okay?
So fuck you, fuck you, and fuck you!
- (CLACKING STOPS)
- MAN: What did he say?
Not you. Just e... everyone.
I meant fuck all of you. No one specific.
- Richard, you low-balled me.
- Mmm?
Remember? Well, Duncan here said
he wanted to grow fast as balls.
- He said he was psyched.
- Yeah, I am psyched.
I'd hire a million people if I could.
See, if I have to sell my
company, I might as well sell it
to the CEO who actually wants all of us.
It's pizza, Kira.
Richard, we're just three CEOs
trying to do right by our companies.
Okay, you know what? I'm
glad you turned us down,
because I don't want to work with anyone
who wants to work with this... meathead.
I'm taking these. I'm taking all of them.
♪
Maybe just take one. You
have like four employees.
RICHARD: Ha!
Ah, shit.
GAVIN: Throw it away.
Patrice, I'd like to welcome
you back to the Hooli family.
It's wonderful to be back, Gavin.
Sadly, the timing couldn't be worse.
Those code-monkeys I just hired
were right about one thing:
Making Jack's box the flagship
product of this company
will send us down a path
to technological irrelevance
from which we will never return.
But in light of the time and resources
we've invested in this product,
convincing the board and our shareholders
to simply scrap it will
be nearly impossible.
Our company is too big to
turn around that quickly.
Gavin, what if you launched a new
product to help us correct course?
Absolutely. Look at all the products
you've brought to market over the years.
GAVIN: Hmm. True.
I did invent the HooliPod and the HooliPad
and the HooliPad Pro,
but a man only has so many
game-changing inventions in him.
And technically, all the products
he just named were money-losers.
I mean, you could argue
we'd have been better off
if he'd never invented any of that stuff.
- Hoover.
- HOOVER: Sir.
(WHISPERS)
Patrice, can I talk to
you outside for a second?
Anyway, if Jack Barker's insidious
box is allowed to go to market,
we may all lose our jobs.
We may all go the way of Patrice.
But we must fight it. We cannot sacrifice
our long-term wellbeing in the interest
of paltry, short-term profits.
Well, they're not paltry, exactly.
Did you not see the preorder
figures for the Box Two?
They came in this morning.
Holy shit.
Are these right? How many quarters is this?
Just one. The Box Two will be by far
the most lucrative new
product we've ever released.
Fucking Sliceline.
Plus his fancy, hi-tech pizza
tastes just like Domino's.
There's a reason for
that. Check out the liner.
JARED: Oh yeah. I guess that's Domino's.
We never had pizza 'cause my step-mom said
Italians aren't real white people.
Hold on. Duncan doesn't
even make his own pizza?
He just orders it from Domino's
and switches the boxes?
(SCOFFS) He really is sneaky.
It's not sneaky. It's stupid.
Switching boxes costs a lot of money.
Okay. How do you know?
I need to prove Errich's dead,
so I want to ship a dead body from China,
but it's hard to find
a white body in China,
especially fat like Errich,
so I buy a fat, white cadaver
from Cincinnati medical school.
But to ship to China, then switch box,
then ship back, it's way too much money.
Say that again.
Like, not one word of that made sense.
Hold on. Just... ju... What... uh...
does anyone... does anyone know
the price of a Domino's pizza?
A large, 10 bucks.
Okay, well, Sliceline
sells theirs for nine.
- So?
- (EMPHATICALLY) So, we're not fucked yet.
♪
That was kinda crazy, Richard. That was...
(LAUGHS) I mean, you
threw a full-on tantrum.
I know, I know. I am so sorry.
It's just... I guess I'm just a CEO
trying to do right by my company.
- Like you guys.
- (PHONE BEEPS)
Speaking of business, wow,
we're having a hell of a night.
Yeah, well, I would know.
About 500 of those orders tonight are me.
Oh. Richard, you really
didn't have to do that.
But the peace offering
is super appreciated.
Yeah, well, I wouldn't really
call it a peace offering.
You see, Duncan, you took
eight mil in funding, right?
And then you matched my offer to acquire
Optimoji here from Kira,
but the thing is, you
can't sell your pizzas
for nine bucks a pop without
taking a bath, can you?
The reboxing, the double delivery, ugh.
You lose, what, four bucks an order?
(CHUCKLES) Five, actually.
- We're losing five bucks a pizza?
- Yeah.
Only temporarily. So,
her team is gonna optimize
our order routing and allocation,
and then we'll be cash-flow positive.
We can easily turn it around
- before we run out of money.
- Right.
- Yeah.
- Unless a lot of people
buy your pizza very quickly.
(PHONE BEEPS, WHOOSHES)
What are... What are you doing?
Well, Duncan, I can be a dickhead too.
You see, I have $13
million in my bank account
and a very low payroll, which affords me
to buy a lot of tasty 'za
before you can turn it around.
You're trying to bankrupt us?
No, Kira. I'm simply trying
to devalue your company,
so that I can make a
low-ball acquisition offer
which you cannot refuse.
Richard, I'm just gonna
delete your account.
You see, my engineers
already thought of that,
and they worked up a little botnet program.
Thousands of fake users
indistinguishable from real ones
geolocated perfectly to maximize drive time
and bleed your little
greasebag operation dry.
You know, I may not have that many coders,
but the ones I do are stallions,
each one more magnificent than the last.
♪
MONICA: You spent $19,000 on pizza?
No, $19,000 on vengeance.
You're acquiring Sliceline
who already acquired Optimoji?
Richard, you're talking
about absorbing a staff of 50.
How are you gonna spin this to Laurie?
Well, you said you'd
protect me from Laurie.
I mean, she's your partner.
Are you afraid of her?
Of course I'm afraid of her.
The woman got pregnant just to prove to me
that she could do it without
missing a day of work.
Okay, fair enough, but maybe this
one time you could take my side.
I cannot take your side.
You're asking for 50 employees.
- Think of the...
- Sorry I am late.
Hey, Laurie. Did you, uh...
Induce? Yes, this morning...
and here I am.
So, Richard,
I received your email.
I understand you wish to
acquire a company called...
Sliceline,
which themselves recently
acquired a company called Optimoji.
Yes, and I will be firing
both companies' CEOs
and taking on a total
engineering team of about,
uh, 50.
Fifty?
Monica, you are okay with this?
Well, it shortens their
runway significantly,
but you did say that you
want them to grow, Laurie.
Yes, but in this case it seems...
(SIGHS) reckless.
However, if you are on top of it,
Monica, then...
(PEN SCRATCHES)
...approved.
Congratulations.
Great. Thanks. And
congratulations to you too.
On?
On the... on your... On your baby.
Oh.
♪
_
This is awesome. Gavin is
essentially doubling-down
on the very thing we are destroying.
It's like he's giving up.
Maybe I should've ordered the nicer Tesla.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
DINESH: Ah.
Oh gosh. Everyone's here.
JARED: Richard. So many people.
Richard.
Hey. Hey.
I thought you'd want to
give some opening remarks,
you know, it being the first day and all,
just to set the tone.
Ladies and gentlemen, Richard Hendricks!
(APPLAUSE)
(PANICKED BREATHING)
(GULPS) Um...
(STAMMERS) Well, it's
great to have everybody
and... so many... f... faces.
We've got a lot of...
men and women here.
And...
(GULPING)
we should remember that.
So, let's keep it clean.
(GULPS) Um...
it's always a challenge...
(GULPS) to get it...
I've got... I should probably...
more to say in a minute.
I just have to go, one...
One second, in my office...
(GULPS) and then we'll conclude.
Uh, he just needs a second in his
office, then he's gonna come back.
Oh God.
Don't tell anyone, okay? (SPITS)
Um, Richard, I know...
I know money's tight,
but I think I might invest in
a modesty panel for your desk.
RICHARD: What?
("THE MONKEY" PLAYS)
(GAGS, RETCHES)
Synced and corrected by louvette
www.addic7ed.com
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ The monkey speaks his mind ♪
♪ Now, three monkeys
sat in a coconut tree ♪
♪ Discussing things as
they are said to be ♪
♪ Said one to other,
Now listen, you two ♪
♪ There's a certain
rumor that can't be true ♪
♪ That man descended our noble race ♪
♪ Why, the very idea ♪
♪ Is a big disgrace ♪
♪ And here's another thing ♪
♪ You will never see ♪
♪ A monkey building a fence ♪
♪ Around a coconut tree ♪
♪ And let the coconuts ♪
♪ Go to waste ♪
♪ Forbidding all the monkeys ♪
♪ To come and taste ♪