Richard...
Do you think if I asked
they would let me visit her?
Jared, she's going to be okay.
I promise.
_
The brilliant little idiot.
He found a way around the patent.
It's Hendricks' Internet, but
it's not Hendricks' Internet.
I will no longer be able
to manufacture your boxes.
You see, my company will be
manufacturing a new device
that will quickly render yours obsolete.
Did you speak to Laurie about our series B?
Sort of.
Nothing is personal with Laurie, alright?
It's what makes her such a great VC.
A term sheet for your series B.
Congratulations, Richard.
Thank you.
Wow. That is one expensive bottle.
You guys deserve the best
bottle of champagne they have.
Yeah, all champagne
tastes the same to me, so.
I agree, I mean, what's the difference
between good champagne and bad champagne?
About $500.
Guys, come on. Enjoy it.
You're about to close
a $30 million series B.
And you don't have to sell any ads
or harvest user data,
which for any other VC in town
would've been a non-starter.
Frankly, I'm surprised
that Laurie went for it.
Well, I'm not wild about the idea
of her having two more board seats.
I mean, she did kill
Fiona right in front of us.
Listen, don't worry about Laurie, okay?
I'm gonna be your point person on this.
She's got her plate full.
She's raising money to recover
from the whole Eklow debacle.
Okay.
So... to you guys.
All right.
- Cheers.
Yup, thanks.
All right. I have a dinner meeting
and I kind of feel like a fifth wheel,
so I'm gonna pick up the
check, leave you to celebrate.
- Congrats again, guys.
- Okay.
Bye.
Well, the only person we don't spend
20 hours a day with just left.
So.
What's new with you guys?
Well, I'm thinking of buying
some new bookkeeping software.
All right. I think the
only actual way to celebrate
is to spend one waking minute apart, so.
I'm gonna go.
Are you going home?
Let's... let's share an Uber.
Oh, well, if you're going that direction,
I'm... I'm driving, so I could drop you.
Hey, Gilfoyle. Wanna play Fortnite?
Oh, hold on, I didn't know
we were playing Fortnite.
Yeah, I'll come along.
Synced and corrected by louvette
www.addic7ed.com
I would've taken that
plate to the sink for you.
Uh, it's okay. I just finished, so.
How was the sandwich I
made you? Was it good?
Good condiment blend?
Yeah. It was perfect, thanks.
Richard.
This might be out of line, but...
would you mind telling Jared how
much you enjoyed the sandwich?
I'm finding him a little intimidating.
Sure, yeah. Look, I know he
can be a little eccentric.
I tend to hold my breath around him.
It's exacerbating my asthma.
Ooh, okay...
Richard, do you have a moment?
You know what?
Holden just made me a really good sandwich.
Oh, well, that's nice.
Yeah. Yep.
Did he ask you to mention that to me?
What? No.
- Okay.
- No, he's... he's just great.
Well, "In doing what we
ought, we deserve no praise"
because it is our duty."
St. Augustine.
So, um...
I've been keeping track
of the compute credits
that you gave to Laurie.
And she sold them to Gigglybots
and then Gigglybots sold them to SmashHub.
And they traded hands a few more times,
the price increasing
each time until they were
bought by a venture fund in Mountain View.
Okay, uh, so if we wanted to buy them back,
how much would it cost us?
It's $1.6 million.
- What?
- The fuck?
- More like that?
- Yeah.
So Dinesh, is it true?
Is series B happening?
We all heard it's happening.
Oh, guys, please, you
know I can't talk to you
about upper level management stuff.
It's totally happening. Look at his face.
He has the worst poker face.
No. Don't... Don't look at my face.
This is great news. We're
all getting big, fat bonuses.
I was a little worried I made
a mistake ordering that Tesla.
Sorry, Tesla? What Tesla?
Model S. Same as yours.
I mean, not exactly the
same. I ordered the P100D.
Newer model.
It's got longer battery life...
You know what? This is a workplace.
This is not a fucking slumber
party, gabbing, gabbing.
And series B is not a done deal.
Despite what my face says, okay?
Don't trust this face.
No one should ever trust this face.
Congrats on the Tesla, Danny.
So excited for you.
Series B, baby!
Fuck Danny.
I mean, I love my Tesla.
It has Insane Mode,
which means it goes zero
to 60 in 3.2 seconds,
which is literally insane.
But the Tesla that Danny
ordered has Ludicrous Mode,
which means it goes zero
to 60 in 2.8 seconds.
So it's gonna take me an entire
0.4 seconds longer to get to 60.
I mean, how would you feel
if one of your neighbors
got a tiki head bigger than yours?
Oh, well, when we bought it,
we made sure it was the
biggest one they made, so.
You're the biggest tiki
head guy in the neighborhood.
I used to be the Tesla guy in the office.
I maxed out my credit cards to
be able to afford that thing.
And now that we're getting series B,
any one of these bourgeois
new money millennial fucks
can just go out and buy one.
I don't wanna sound selfish,
but sometimes I wish only
I made money. You know?
What are we talking about, here?
You want us to launch a cryptocurrency?
I do.
The fact that people are willing
to pay many multiples more
for our compute credits than they're worth,
we have an opportunity here.
Worth is relative, Richard.
What do you mean?
Why do people covet
the silly pieces of green
cotton paper in their wallets?
It's because we are all sheep.
And we've mutually agreed
to endow certain things
with value.
And right now, for some reason,
the market values our
credits more than we did.
Gilfoyle, we're not gonna suddenly pivot
and become a digital currency company.
I'm not proposing a pivot.
I'm proposing that we sell digital currency
as a way to finance our
new Internet company.
You wanted an alternative to Laurie Bream.
Well, it's right here in front of you.
PiedPiperCoin.
Okay, look, I...
I'm not gonna bet the entire future
of my new Internet and
everything I've worked for
on becoming the next Bitcoin.
You really expect me to do that?
There are very few things
that I will defend with true passion:
medical marijuana,
the biblical Satan as a metaphor
for rebellion against tyranny,
and mother fucking Goddamn cryptocurrency.
Mmm.
I have a PowerPoint that I've been
wanting to show you for some time.
Walk me through this.
We can't make our boxes in China
because Yao has threatened
every manufacturer in the country.
- That's right.
- We can't afford Bangladesh,
because the workers have unionized.
Sadly, correct.
And we can't use our place in Laos,
because one person gets
her scalp ripped off
and suddenly, everyone's
screaming regulations.
Yes.
You know, you hear a lot of chatter
about the growth of the global economy,
but no one wants to
talk about the downside.
Gavin, there is one other
manufacturing option we
haven't discussed yet,
which considering the
current circumstances,
might be worth consideration.
I'm open to anything.
America.
Fuck you.
I feel the same way.
But we were recently contacted
by the mayor of Goldbriar, North Carolina.
They had a DVR manufacturing
plant that closed.
The retooling would be minimal.
They've got a skilled labor pool
just sitting idle and they sound desperate.
Really?
How desperate?
It was pitiful.
Really?
In 350 BCE,
Aristotle defined sound money as being
durable, transferable,
divisible, scarce, recognizable....
- Gilfoyle?
- And fungible.
What?
Can we skip ahead 2,400 years?
I mean, I know what cryptocurrency is.
Richard, a lot of work
went into this presentation.
- Okay.
- Fine.
But you're missing out
on a lot of wisdom, here.
Why don't you tell me what you know
about Bitcoin as a jumping-off point?
Okay, sure.
Uh, well, I'm pretty sure it
was founded by a Japanese guy...
Or guys, or girls,
going by the name Satoshi Nakamoto in 2008.
True identity still unknown.
Okay, look, every day I read an article
about how we're in a Bitcoin bubble.
And who is writing those articles?
I don't wanna say the establishment.
But is it possible that Warren Buffett
called Bitcoin a pyramid scheme
because he has 92 billion
conventional dollars to protect?
Let's say he's right.
Let's say Bitcoin dies.
So what? MySpace,
Friendster, they both died.
But they paved the way for
other social media tripe
like Facebook and Twitter
to completely overrun the planet.
Crypto is out there.
And it's not going away.
It just feels sketchy.
In the same way that a new Internet
is sketchy, Richard?
- Well...
- What is crypto?
If not decentralized, anonymous, secure,
and an existential threat
to the powers that be?
I would think that you'd be
all-in on something like that.
Yeah. But do you really
think we can create a currency
worth $30 million?
Because that's what we'd be giving up.
Maybe. Probably even more.
But even if it's less,
we would still gain control, autonomy,
board seats and shares,
and you wouldn't have to rely
on a VC who once fired you
from your own company.
So, there is a mode
above Ludicrous Mode. Am I correct?
Yes. It's called Plaid.
And it comes standard on
the new Tesla Roadster.
How do I get into one of these babies?
Simple. You put down a
$50,000 deposit today.
Okay.
And you'll be behind the wheel
as soon as they become available.
And how quickly will that be, Stephanie?
Soon. We're thinking a few years,
which goes by fast.
My daughter was a teenager in high school.
- Next thing I knew...
- I'm gonna stop you right there.
Your oily salesmanship is
starting to really irritate me.
Okay?
I need to maintain my Tesla superiority,
and I need to do it now.
Okay, I'm looking at a
new set of wheels here.
The 21-inch Arachnids.
Very nice. But they're not for sale.
You can only get them through
our referral awards program.
You refer three other customers to us,
they buy a vehicle and,
zoop-zoop, you get the wheels.
So, if I get more people to buy Teslas,
then I will have the wheels
and no one else can get them?
Not even Danny?
I'm sorry, who's Danny?
He's the guy with the shitty wheels.
And now, the CEO of Hooli,
Mr. Gavin Belson.
_
Thank you, Mayor Wilkins.
Thank you, Goldbriar, for
this warm, wonderful welcome.
You know, being in North Carolina
always feels like a bit
of a homecoming for me.
I own a vacation property
just off the coast in Bermuda.
Technically, it is my
primary legal residence.
_
Good people of Goldbriar,
for too long, foreign interests
have used unfair trade and labor practices
to plunder American wealth
and steal American jobs.
But I don't blame them for that.
No. I blame weak, spineless
American politicians.
But if your mayor does his job,
your jobs will come back,
and soon, you will proudly be building
the Gavin Belson Signature Box Three.
But if for some reason
he can't make my very
reasonable proposal work,
you know who to blame.
I'm excited to get started.
What about y'all?
- Hi, Holden.
- Oh.
Jared. Hi.
Hi.
Can I ask you a question?
Of course.
Did you ask Richard to tell me
that he liked the sandwich
that you made for him?
No.
Is that the truth?
Yes.
Okay.
Good job with that plate.
Thanks.
Now, I can see the looks on your faces.
I know what you're thinking.
Why does Dinesh care so
much if I buy a Tesla?
I'll tell you why.
Because Teslas are good for the world.
Surprisingly pedestrian
wheels, but you get over that.
So, come on.
Series B, right? Cha-ching.
I was gonna use that to
pay off my student loans.
That's boring.
And don't take this the wrong way,
but it seems like it's very important
for you to be the Tesla guy in the office.
Like, weirdly important.
I'm not weird, you're weird.
You guys are being so weird.
Come on. What's it gonna take
to get you into a Tesla today?
Here. I've printed out hundreds of these.
There you go. There you go, pass these on.
Dave? Dave?
All right, what's this interesting idea?
Gilfoyle and I were talking.
And this may seem a little
out there at first, but...
Instead of funding our
launch with a series B,
what about...
an ICO?
An initial coin offering?
It's basically a...
Are you a fucking moron?
Maybe I don't need to be here for this.
Sit the fuck down.
Okay.
Richard, what are you doing?
Just exploring our options.
Why? You don't think I have your back?
Look, I get that you're giving up
board seats and shares,
but look what you're getting in return.
As if the $30 million you were
getting wasn't good enough,
we provide you with marketing,
networking, staffing.
We help you negotiate partnerships
and navigate regulations.
All these things that are
changing by the minute.
Gilfoyle, can you help with any of that?
I'd rather just listen if
it's all the same to you.
Look, if you do an ICO,
you're not only saying fuck you to us,
you're saying fuck you to all VCs.
Jesus, Richard. Why would you even
think it would be okay
to talk to me about this?
Like would you ask your wife
who you should cheat with?
No.
Well, maybe.
I don't know, I...
I guess I was just looking
for advice from a friend.
Oh, are we friends, Richard?
- Yes, of course.
- Really?
Have we spoken once in the past year
about anything other than business?
Yes.
Wait. No.
- When's my birthday?
- Come on.
Do I live in a house or an apartment?
Did you even know that I was married?
- You are?
- I was, I...
had it annulled after three months.
Did he ask you who he should cheat with?
Look, you came for advice, fine.
Forget an ICO.
Okay? I'm sure Gilfoyle
told you that he can handle
all the technical stuff.
But this is not just a math problem.
They're my direct competition.
I've done my homework on this.
So before you walk away from stability
and gamble your entire company on crypto,
there's another "friend" of yours
I think you should talk to.
I was such a fucking pussy
when Bitcoin broke, Richard.
If I had the balls,
I'd have put every penny
I had into that shit
five years ago,
watched it go up, up, up, up, up
and then pulled out right before
it all came crashing down again.
I mean, Jesus, why didn't I do that?
Fuck me! But then, it occurred to me...
I own 36 fucking companies, Richard.
If I make them all ICO,
that's 36 bites at the apple.
So I did it.
- You... you did 36 ICOs?
- Yup.
- Did they work?
- You know, one of the things
being in the three comma
club has taught me, Richard,
is it's not always about money.
Sometimes, it's about wisdom.
And did I lose a B? Close to it. Fuck!
But I bet I gained two B in wisdom.
So you lost it all?
Ha, ha, Richard, if I didn't
love this crazy guy so much,
I'd knock his fucking teeth out.
Nah, nah, I didn't lose it all.
I mean, one of them got
shut down by the SEC.
On a few, we got scammed.
But some of them worked.
One of them worked.
One? One out of 36?
Yeah. Listen,
all the coin I had from the ICO that worked
was on a USB thumb drive.
And my dumb fucking housekeeper
threw out my jeans,
'cause they were ripped.
Even though I paid more
for the ripped ones.
And the thumb drive was in the pocket, so.
$300 million in crypto is
buried out here, somewhere.
But my boys will find it.
If they wanna get paid, right?
And when they do,
that coin could cover all the losers.
I mean, it's up 3,000%
in the last two weeks.
If it keeps going like this
over the next three, four months,
we could be talking the four comma club!
That's a T, not a B, Richard.
- Mr. Hanneman!
- Shit, you found it?
Jose! Yes! No!
I said a thumb drive.
In the... that's an actual thumb.
That's a human... Just
fucking put that back!
Again, Richard...
the math is sound.
Well, Mayor, I sure have
enjoyed our time together.
Let me know when you get this done.
Uh, Mr. Belson, I'm sorry,
but this list of demands
is not remotely workable
for a community of our size.
A mayor's job is never easy.
But you'll find a way,
if you care about your constituents.
Mr. Belson, I grew up in this town.
I've lived here my entire life.
- I'd do anything to...
- Wait, wait, wait, wait.
- Your entire life?
- Mm-hmm.
- How old are you?
- Forty-seven.
That's a little weird, isn't it?
The point is, I'd do anything
to help the people of this area.
But giving you public money on this
scale would decimate our budget.
I could have the local high
school renamed after you.
Rosa Parks has never
even been to Goldbriar.
I don't want a fucking high school.
I wanna manufacture boxes
at an 80% profit margin.
I don't understand.
All my asshole friends keep getting
NFL stadiums and corporate headquarters,
all fully paid for.
And you can't make one
fucking factory happen?
I mean, the only things I have
left to cut are essential services.
There you go. Do that.
You could have a volunteer fire department.
Because I can't afford
a penny more than this.
Everybody ready?
Two, three!
- ♪ Oh Carolina prowl off ♪
- ♪ Do-do-do-do ♪
♪ Jump an prance, oh Carolina ♪
- ♪ Prowl off jump an prance ♪
- ♪ Do-do-do-do ♪
♪ Oh Carolina gal prowl off ♪
- ♪ Gal Yuh fi jump an prance ♪
- _
- ♪ Prowl off ♪
- ♪ Do-do-do-do ♪
♪ Jump and prance ♪
♪ Carolina come bubble 'pon me ♪
♪ Oh, watch how she groove ♪
So, pretty sweet, right?
Yeah, it's nice.
Sorry we couldn't find a
safe spot to try Insane Mode.
It feels like your kidneys
are gonna get, like,
ripped right through the back of your body.
- It's like...
- Yeah, I don't think I'd wanna do that.
Well you don't need to do it.
But you wanna be able to tell
people that you can do it.
Right? It's like having a gun.
So, Charlie and Nadia
have already said yes.
You'll finally have something
to talk to them about.
Oh, let me think about it.
Fine. Okay, just pull
into the designated EV...
...2.8 seconds.
Oh, fuck.
Danny already got his car.
I'll pay your down payment and first
three months. Do we have a deal?
Wow, really?
Make it six months.
Fine! Okay, just go.
Hide before Danny sees
us in this shitty car.
- Go, go, go. Go.
- Wow, uh...
Hello?
Hey, guess what?
My boss just bought me a car!
What? No! Ew. Ugh!
Richard? Ron LaFlamme's office just called.
And the series B paperwork
is ready for you to sign.
Okay.
Uh, well, then I guess I'll
just go over there and sign it.
Richard, I know you were
pinning your hopes on the ICO,
but I... I think series
B is the right call.
Yeah, no, I... I hope so.
We're gonna get the
money we need to launch,
and everyone out there is
gonna get a great bonus.
And then, you're gonna
have an army of happy
and highly motivated workers...
Jared?
Everything okay with Holden?
You mean, like, mentally?
I was wondering that, too.
No. No, no. Just, like...
like, with you and him.
Just seems like you're
being really hard on him.
Do you like him?
Yeah. I mean, sure.
Okay. It's okay if you like him.
That's all that matters, right?
Yeah.
Okay. Well, I'll see you when, uh...
I'll see you when you
get back from LaFlamme's.
Every institutional investor
to whom I reached out
agreed to participate in our second fund.
The capital issues we
faced due to Eklow's failure
have been remedied.
Laurie, you are a badass.
Ah, yes. A compliment.
Well, I think the numbers
in our new prospectus
speak for themselves.
Sorry, you're projecting
that 70% of Pied Piper's
operating income is gonna
come from ad sales, but...
Pied Piper's not gonna sell ads.
Yes. I understand that
is their current position.
No, Laurie, when we
offered them their series B,
I promised Richard that
we would never make them
harvest data or sell ads.
However, that language is
not part of their term sheet.
I am not saying that we will
force their hand on this issue.
But neither am I saying
definitively that we will not.
Okay, but you and I,
we are partners, right?
Of course.
Any decision we make, we
will certainly make together.
Good. As long as that's clear.
And again, great job closing our funding.
Ah, yes. Huzzah. Onward.
Laurie, did you have
the big, hairy question
put back on my wall?
Yes. I like it there.
But I don't.
And yet...
All right. One more, right there.
And done-zo.
Series Ba-bam.
Richard, don't sign it.
Look, I can't protect you.
At some point, Laurie's gonna fuck you over
- and make you sell ads.
- What?
And I don't think there's
anything I can do about it.
Don't sign the deal. I just did. It's done.
Jesus Christ.
Laurie's gonna sell ads.
Isn't that what I told you?
What the fuck am I supposed to do now?
God!
You know I can just tear these up, right?
No, I know. Good.
- I like it.
- _
But can we adjust the proportions?
Make the logo bigger?
And... and make the flag bigger?
And... and make the box bigger, too.
It all just needs to be bigger.
Okay.
- Bigger.
- Yeah.
- Sir.
- Ah, Hoover.
How's the factory coming?
We almost online?
Not exactly, sir.
It's gone.
What do you mean?
Did that dipshit mayor renege on our deal?
No, he made every effort,
including having the factory repainted.
Okay. So what's the problem?
Well, apparently, the painters left
some oily rags in a garbage can.
Mm-hmm.
But because of cuts to
the sanitation service,
the trash was not collected
and the rags smoldered and caught fire.
And because of cuts to the fire department,
the blaze spread.
A number of concerned citizens
volunteered to help fight the fire,
but because the water was
cut off, they could not.
Okay, so what happened?
Well, the vast majority of our
expensive, rare earth materials
survived the fire.
Well, that's something.
Until the flames abated,
when because of mass layoffs of police,
the locals that were
there to fight the fire
decided instead to loot
the burned-out factory.
The National Guard attempted
to reach the factory
to help stop this, but...
- The roads.
- The roads, sir, yes.
Okay.
So, we lost it all?
- Everything?
- Yes.
Also, the IRS called.
Somehow, they found out about Bermuda.
Look, when you take it all into account,
turning down our series B
and doing an ICO to fund your launch,
may actually give you the best odds.
You said ICOs are suicide.
Well, I'm a VC
and some of that might have
been self-preservational.
Okay.
Well, even if you were
exaggerating, you're still right.
I mean, Russ Hanneman had 36
chances to make an ICO work
and he basically failed.
I only have one.
Look, Gilfoyle can handle
all the technical stuff.
You just need to hire someone
who can handle the business side.
- Like who?
- I don't know.
I'm sorry, but I gotta
Uber back to the office
before Laurie realizes I'm gone.
No, no, wait. Who do I hire?
Someone who understands securities, right?
Not necessarily.
I mean, your coin doesn't
have to be a security.
You could do a utility token instead,
since you provide an
actual unit of compute.
Although, you'd have to convince the SEC.
Damn it. Surge pricing.
- Monica.
- You might not even need to bother
with a moving average pricing
strategy when you launch.
But you will need to keep a close eye on
statements from the federal government,
South Korea, and China.
So, whoever you do hire
should definitely know how to do all that.
Okay, six minutes.
- Monica.
- What?
It's you.
You're the right person.
No.
No. No, no, no, no, no.
Come on. Give me one good reason.
I... love my job.
You hate working for Laurie.
With Laurie, okay? We
are both equal partners.
Okay.
Look, Monica. I will do the ICO.
But only if you do it with me.
Come on.
Wait, what's happening?
Canceling my Uber.
- So, you're in?
- Fuck it.
I'm in.
Fuck series B.
PiedPiperCoin is totally gonna work.
Yes. It is. It totally is.
So, just to confirm,
in order for this coin to be worth
what series B was worth to all of us,
it has to sell for how much?
$68.
I see.
And seven cents is less than that.
Yup.
Whose idea was this again?
I believe the initial idea was Gilfoyle's.
To be fair, it was Monica
who really pushed it over the goal line.
Well, I'm gonna head
down to the Tesla dealer
and beg them to take my car back.
Well, that's something.
And my two referrals fell through.
And I had to return mine.
So now the only Tesla in
the office is Priyanka's
and I'm paying for that.
So, that's cool.
Richard, adversity is a great teacher.
Just like cigarette burns.
Laurie, hi.
Monica.
Congratulations on the ICO.
Yeah, yeah. Not quite the
numbers we were hoping for.
I'm sure you're happy about that.
On the contrary.
Monica, you have certain values.
And I see no reason you should not
work with companies that share them.
Similarly, I should work with
companies that share my values.
So, no hard feelings?
No feelings at all, Monica.
We are friends
and we should not let business
get in the way of that.
Speaking of, I am stepping into a meeting.
Right, well, I'm surprised
you're taking this so well,
I really appreciate it, Laurie.
Let us talk soon.
Have you received my proposal?
Very promising.
Synced and corrected by louvette
www.addic7ed.com