They won't...
She won't stop, you know?
Day after...
I was a maker.
I'm gonna do it tonight...
when she's sleeping.
But I'm scared--
She said that
I gotta make a meatloaf.
I said we'd bring
Jell-O salad,
but Kitty said
meatloaf, so...
Hon?
So... What's that, hon?
I said it's Gordo's
birthday tonight.
We're supposed to be at your brother's
at 4:00 with meatloaf.
It sounds different today,
don't you think?
Like, angry?
I'm washing towels.
It's a towel sound.
Oh.
Kitty said they just got one of
those fancy European all-in-ones.
Says it washes and dries.
One machine.
Can you believe that?
Bet that set
them back a penny.
He can afford it,
your brother.
Kitty said he just
got a big promotion
after only working
there a year.
Kitty said they also got
one of those fancy new
surround sound systems.
Guess I married
the wrong Nygaard.
Oh.
That's what I said.
We had a good laugh.
Well, it's just
slow now at the shop.
Hon... that's what
you always say. "Slow."
Well...
better get back to it.
You make your own wins.
That's what Kitty
said Chaz told her.
Salesmen make
their own wins.
You gotta try harder, hon.
Smile, for Pete's sake.
Maybe wear a nicer tie.
You gave me this tie.
Well, if you were
a better salesman,
I'd have bought
you a nicer tie.
At least take a look.
I keep thinking
maybe it's the settings.
Kitty says Chaz
fixes things around
the house all the time.
Says he took the toaster
apart over the weekend.
Now it's good as new.
Browns to beat the band.
So that's...
Like I said, there's two kinds of policies
you should be thinking about.
You got your Whole Life
and your Whole Life Plus which covers
the same benefits of Whole Life
plus a heck of a lot more.
Well, we just came in to get Charlene
on my health care.
On account I'm having a baby.
Yeah.
A boy, we're hoping.
Or a little girl.
I'd just about hug the pants
off a little girl.
Yeah? Well, uh...
Even more... Yeah.
All the more reason to...
Because what happens...
what happens
if you have an accident
at your job?
I work at the library.
Okay.
What happens if you have a car crash
and go out the windshield...
or... or... or say you're
up a ladder cleaning out the gutters
and you fall off the darn thing
and break your neck?
These things happen
every day.
And people fall
asleep smoking in bed.
They burn to death.
What... what I'm saying is
the morgue is full of guys thought
they didn't need life insurance.
For peace of mind, I'm saying,
to know that your little boy...
Or girl.
Right....or little
girl is taken care of.
We're supposed to be
at my mom's by 4:00.
Yeah, so we're gonna...
Oh, okay.
Well, at least let me give you a
brochure or I got these pens.
I got these nifty pens...
Look at that, huh?
...with most of the colors.
Okay, well, if you change your mind,
then give me a...
Oh, heck.
Will you look at that?
What is it, Dad?
Yeah, Dad. What is it?
Hey, Sam.
That there, boys, is a black man.
He don't...
he don't look black, Dad.
Yeah, Dad, he don't look black.
More like a big pumpkin.
Yeah! Yeah, like a big,
stupid pumpkin.
Lester Niggered.
Now, come on, Sam, it's Nygaard...
just like in high school.
You went to high school
with a black man, Dad?
Yeah, Dad, did you?
Shut up.
How you been, Lester?
Yeah, real good.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Me, too. Yeah, trucking
company's doing super.
Got rigs all over
the Great Lakes.
Just bought a summer
house up Bear Island.
It's pretty sweet.
Hey... you remember
the story I told you
of the boy I put in the oil drum
and rolled onto the highway?
Is that him, Dad?
Yeah, Dad, is that him?
Oh, you betcha.
Betcha.
Good old Lester
pencil dick.
Hey, say, Lester...
what was the name of that girl
you went with in high school?
You know, the curvy one.
That's Pearl. Yeah.
Yeah, Pearl.
What a rack on that girl, huh?
Dad's saying she had big titties.
Yeah, I know what "rack"
means, you fairy-- Ow!
Yeah, Dad, ow...
You know, she gave me a tug once.
Homecoming senior year.
Had the nice fat hands.
Real soft.
We're married now.
Going on 18 years.
Oh, Dad,
that's embarrassing.
Yeah, Dad,
super embarrassing.
Eighteen years, huh?
Yeah.
That's something.
Never knew what she
saw in you, really.
Well, I...
No, I mean, help me out.
Is it your stupid pencil dick or your
little rat face?
Yeah, well, uh...
I should get back to it.
Come on.
Did I ever tell you
how I used to beat
this little guy up
in high school?
I'd write my name on my fist in
Sharpie before I'd punch him
so everyone else
would know who did it.
That's a good one, Dad.
Yeah, Dad, real good one.
Remember?
Yeah, I... It's...
it's a long time ago, but...
What a day.
Mmm.
Excuse me, miss?
Do you think...
Will it be much longer?
This thing hurts like the dickens.
We'll call your name.
Yeah, but I've been
here an hour already.
We'll call your name.
Could I have a sip?
Oh.
Heck, take the whole can.
I can't drink the darn
thing without a straw.
Obliged.
Mmm.
What happened
to your nose?
It was...
it was just
a misunderstanding.
Now was this you misunderstanding
the other fella
or him misunderstanding you?
Pardon?
Who misunderstood whom?
No, what I'm saying...
It's...
it's not good to dwell
on these things.
Why?
Pardon?
Why is it not good to
dwell on these things,
especially things that
put you in a hospital?
Well, I was... I was outnumbered,
if you want to know the truth.
Three to one.
Big... big guys, too.
Well, one of them.
Other two were just
kids but big for their age, you know?
If I was any kind of man,
I'd have shown that Sam what's what.
Sam?
Hess.
The bully in high school
and he's a bully now.
So why didn't you...
show him what's what?
Well, his...
He had his sons with him and...
You let a man beat you
in front of his children
to send them a message?
No, that's not...
Heck.
Just... heck.
In my experience, if you let a man
break your nose,
the next time, he tries to break
your spine.
Sam? No way.
I mean, I don't think.
It just... I guess I embarrassed him
in front of his boys.
You embarrassed him?
Yeah, by...
He was telling me about a time where he
and my wife, they were...
But he didn't know she was my wife
is the thing and when I told him...
This man slept with your wife and
you're worried about embarrassing him?
Not slept. No, they didn't...
He said it was just...
She has soft hands,
see, and I guess...
No, mister, we're not friends.
I mean maybe we will be someday.
But I gotta say, if that were me
in your position...
I would have killed that man.
Well, now...
Come on.
You said he bullied you
in high school, right?
Four years.
Gave me an ulcer.
You know what, one time,
he put me in an oil barrel
and rolled me in the road.
Seriously?
And now he tells you that he had
relations with your wife.
He bullies you again
in front of his children.
This is a man who doesn't
deserve to draw breath.
Yeah, okay, but...
Here's the thing...
No, that is the thing.
Well, heck!
I mean, okay... okay,
but... what am I
supposed to do?
Heck, you're so sure about it.
Maybe you should just kill him for me.
You're asking me to kill this man.
No, that was... I was joking.
Mr. Nygaard?
Yeah, that's me. Just one second.
We... we... we... we...
We're just two fellas talking, right?
We're just blowing off steam?
Sir, it's real busy.
Like I said, one second.
Sam Hess.
No, just... just one second.
That is not--
Sir!
Just one word.
Yes or no.
Sir, I'm going to give your spot--
Yeah!
Yeah, I'm coming, for Pete's sake.
Cold enough for you, Chief?
Supposed to get down to negative 10 later.
Yeah, heard that.
Don't much like the sound of negative.
Thought I'd strip down to my shorts,
work on my tan.
So what's this here then?
Chief, I arrived on the
scene at 1300 hours,
found this '93 New Yorker.
Looks like she fled the road
and crashed the fence.
I found a set of footprints
leading away from the car.
Thought, possibly,
our driver, injured,
you know, got confused,
wandered into the woods.
I was just about to investigate.
There's blood here.
Hair, too.
Yeah, saw that.
I was thinking maybe a deer,
but couldn't find the evidence, so...
Here it is.
Son of a gun.
Blood on the steering wheel.
Driver could have hit his head.
Or her head.
You check the trunk?
No, sir.
Huh.
So you want to take a look
at those footprints then?
Sounds good.
How's Ida?
Any day now.
You got a name picked out?
Can't get that woman to decide what
color to paint the nursery.
Can't believe I missed that
deer in the trunk.
Don't take it hard.
Been doing this a long time.
Never checked for a deer in the trunk
or any wildlife.
Chief.
Hiya, hon.
In the kitchen.
Something smells good.
Your boy wanted a hamburger.
Sounds like my boy.
Molly found a wreck out on 71.
How's she doing?
Molly? Yeah, good.
I always liked her.
Yeah, she's a peach.
Anyhoo, looks like the driver tried
to head out on foot.
He got lost and froze
to death in the woods.
Oh, my.
Yeah.
Funny thing is, the fellow was just
wearing underpants.
That so?
Yeah.
No ID, nothing.
Hmm.
Couldn't find his clothes anywhere.
Maybe he ate 'em.
Hmm.
I was thinking maybe
blue for the nursery.
Yeah?
Hmm.
Earlier, I was thinking maybe blue.
Then I changed my mind.
Blue's nice.
Maybe green.
Well... I'm ready to get painting.
Soon as you decide.
You're a good man, Vern Thurman.
My sister was crazy telling me
not to marry you.
Your sister is crazy.
Hmm.
Dad said we could take turns.
Yeah?
Dad said that he also thinks
you've got a potato brain.
So-- Hey!
You're doing it wrong.
You need to press your forearm into
the back of his neck,
grab your elbow with the other hand
to choke him right out.
What do you want, mister?
Yeah, mister, what do you want?
Sign outside says Hess & Sons.
Which one's the older boy?
Me.
Mickey.
So... that leaves me in
charge when Dad is gone.
Are not! Mom said...
Mom has nothing
to do with it, sister!
Hey!
Help you with something?
Sam Hess?
Who wants to know?
Me.
Only two reasons to
come to my shop, friend.
Either you need a truck
or you drive a truck, huh?
You a truck driver?
I was just talking
to your boys.
I think the younger
one's a little dim.
What did you say?
His IQ seems low, I'm saying.
Have you had him tested?
Hit him, Dad.
Yeah, Dad, hit him.
I'm gonna restrain myself.
You know, on account of you got
an obvious head injury
and not beat you to death
with a tire iron.
But I'm gonna ask you again.
What the heck do you want?
I just wanted to
have a look at you.
Okay, that'll do it.
How does a grown man
fall over his own feet?
It was ice.
I slipped on ice.
We should have canceled.
Oh, don't be a baby.
Hi!
Hey, we're here.
We're here.
Hi.
Come on in.
Chaz is working the ham.
Took the whole team
down to Duluth Tuesday.
Big spread at the Marriot.
I've always
wanted to stay there.
Yeah, it's real sweet.
King-sized bed, view of the lake,
you name it.
Boss took me out for dinner.
Just the two of them.
Steak big as a catcher's mitt.
Said, "Chaz, you're going
places in this world."
Gave him a raise
and a corner office.
Yeah.
Hear that, Lester?
A corner office.
Yeah, real good.
And him, your younger brother.
Yeah, I said I heard.
Vice-president,
sales, Midwest region.
Bought the surround
sound to celebrate.
I mean, it's pretty sweet, huh?
You're gonna have
to marry that ham,
you get any more familiar with it.
Saw it on Rachael Ray.
She said that massaging
breaks the muscle down,
makes the meat juicier.
Lester never wants
to try new things.
Now, hold on.
That's not true.
We make Gordo try
stuff all the time.
Chaz says we have
to open his horizons.
Broaden his horizons.
It's a big world,
you know.
There is more to life
than just Minnesota.
Took a real tumble, huh?
There's a spot over
by the fire station.
It's always icy.
Don't know what
the heck I was thinking.
Lester...
come out to the garage.
Help me get some more beer.
Took Gordo to a specialist last month.
Think he might
have the autism.
Yeah?
Won't stop drawing on the walls,
and Kitty, she said she found a
Mason jar in his closet.
I guess that he
pees in it at night.
What's that about?
Hey... you want to see
something cool?
All right.
Sweet!
Yeah, not those.
Gee. What... what is that?
That there... is your M249 SAW
light machine gun,
sometimes referred to as "The Piglet."
Are you allowed...
Can you even have that?
Is it legal?
Technically, no way,
but I got a buddy who works supply
over at Camp Ripley.
And, heck, I'm an American.
I pay my taxes.
You want to take a look?
It's gas-operated, air-cooled,
shoots 725 rounds per minute.
Okay.
Jeez.
You should have told
me it was so heavy.
Is it okay?
No, Lester, it's not okay! You...
Here.
You broke the darn...
Why are you such a GD screw-up?
Hey, now.
Ever since you were...
And now Kitty.
She said she talked to Pearl last week
and she's had it...
your wife.
Said you'd been acting plain weird,
just moping around.
Said she caught you
standing in the bathroom
with your toothbrush
in your hand just looking in the mirror.
Said foam was coming
out of your mouth like a rabid dog.
Come on. That's... not how
I may or may not be feeling.
And for your information,
I hadn't had a lot of sleep
the night before.
So... so... so, the toothpaste,
that was just nothing...
Did you really trip
on the ice and break your nose?
Yeah. Yes.
I... I told you,
outside the fire station.
You know they run the hoses
and wash the trucks,
and it gets all
slippery and wet.
You know, guys at work,
they talk about how they look
up to their brothers...
their older brothers.
Sometimes I tell
people you're dead.
I mean, heck, Lester,
you're 40 years old.
When are you gonna
get your act together?
Your own brother?
You didn't have to hit him.
I mean, seriously, what is the
matter with you?
Your own brother!
Yeah, it's one more...
Yes, one more time.
Before the 17th?
Do you need this
to look like an accident?
Figure it out
and call me back.
Realty.
It's me.
St. Paul, your call was
expected yesterday.
I got delayed.
Problems?
Car trouble. It's fixed now.
But you finished the assignment?
Of course.
And when can they
expect you in Duluth?
The new client
is anxious to begin.
Soon. I took a detour.
And the nature of this detour?
It's personal.
Shouldn't be more than a day or two.
I'll let Duluth know.
All right.
Yeah. Oh, yeah,
big fella.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah... that's good.
Yeah? Yup?
Mmm.
Yeah?
Jeez. Where?
Okay.
Pick me up, huh?
Gotta go?
Mmm.
Homicide.
Molly's coming to get me.
Go back to sleep, hon.
Love you.
Love you, too.
Thanks.
Ida sleeping?
Yep.
What do you want me
to write for cause of death?
Put "self-explanatory."
You okay there, Bill?
Oh, yeah.
Threw up a bit ago.
Not in here, I hope.
Oh, no...
went out to the parking lot.
Wife made spaghetti for dinner.
Seemed a shame to barf it up.
I'm okay now...
so long as I don't look.
Heck.
That's Sam Hess.
Hess that owns
the trucking company?
Yeah, with the two boys.
Both dumb as a dog's foot.
Hold on.
Isn't Hess tied to
that syndicate of fellas out of Fargo...
gunrunners and such?
So they say.
Never seen the proof.
Well, jeez, you...
I mean, you think this could be,
like, an organized crime thing?
You know, a hit or the like?
I don't know what I think yet...
except I was warm in
bed half an hour ago.
How many times
I got to tell you?
You can't just
take the sheets off of one bed
and stick 'em on another.
It's unsanitary.
I shake 'em out first.
You don't have the sense
God gave a clam, do you?
Go shovel the walk.
I need a room.
Just you?
Pardon?
Is it just for you, the room?
What difference does that make?
It's a different
rate for two.
And if you got pets,
dog, cat, it's an extra 10 bucks.
What if I got a fish?
Excuse me?
Would a fish cost me $10?
Or what if I kept
spiders or mice?
What if I had bacteria?
Sir, bacteria are not pets.
Could be.
Sir, perhaps you'd
be happier in a different motel?
I just want to know the policy.
You see, I'm a student
of institutions.
Sir, do you have
a pet or not?
No, it's just me.
Why do you let her
talk to you like that?
She's not that bad.
Son, she compared
you to a clam.
Well, what should I do?
A guy insulted me once.
I pissed in his gas tank.
Car never drove straight again.
Leroy's Motor Inn.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm looking out my window,
and there's a young fellow
urinating in the gas
tank of a red Cavalier.
Son of a--
Hey!
You little...
Warm you up, hon?
Yeah, thanks, Dad.
Looking at?
Murder file.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Sam Hess got himself killed
last night over at the Lucky Penny.
You don't say.
Knife in the head.
You didn't hear that from me.
Hey there, Molly. Lou.
Coffee?
Sure.
Eggs over medium?
Won't say no.
How's the leg?
Goes from my ass to
the ground just like the other.
Thinking of doing some
ice fishing this weekend.
Sorry to hear it.
Interested?
No, sir.
The only thing I ever
caught fishing in winter was a cold.
Say, Chief, listen,
I been thinking
about that fella
in the snow with the underpants.
Mmm-hmm.
Something odd about that.
You're saying other than the fact
he was just wearing panties?
Yeah. See, we know from the wreck
that whoever was driving
cracked their head on the
steering wheel, right?
But the fella in the snow...
No head injury.
Yeah, so you see--
That's some good police work there,
Deputy.
Oh. Thanks.
But if he's not the driver,
I guess we gotta ask...
who is he?
Ran his prints, nothing.
Plus, it turns out
the car was stolen.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Yeah,
over in Grand Forks.
I called the local PD.
I'm just waiting on a callback.
Any thoughts
there on Hess?
No, not as such.
The, um...
lady that Hess was with
didn't get a good look
at the fella who killed him
on account of all the blood in
her eyes, but...
you know, we're checking
the knife for prints.
Also, Bill's going
around to local stores
to see if maybe the knife
was bought here in Bemidji.
You'll make
a good chief one day.
Me?
What about Bill?
He's got seniority.
Bill cleans his gun
with bubble bath.
No, it'll be you...
if you want.
When you talk to the
police, just keep it simple.
Thanks but no thanks,
in other words.
I've already
talked to Fargo,
and they want to
deal with this themselves.
They're sending guys.
Deal with what?
He was in a whorehouse.
I'm glad he's dead.
Ma, don't talk like that.
Yeah,
Makes me live in the North Pole,
and then he's got the nerve to...
I'm not kidding.
I'm gonna sing at his funeral.
Mmm-hmm.
Mr. Mickey,
you have a phone call.
She said me, you doofus.
Can I come?
No.
Jeez! Just stay
here with Ma.
Hello.
Mickey?
Louis Grossman,
your dad's estate attorney.
First of all...
I'd like to say
how sorry I am for your loss.
Okay.
Next thing is...
I'm responsible for
overseeing the dispersal
of your dad's vast estate.
You mean the money?
Right.
Money, real estate, holdings,
automobiles and...
Well, there's no delicate
way to put this.
The will was very clear.
Your dad decided to give everything
to your younger brother Moe.
Are you kidding?
I know it's hard to hear...
but the will was very specific.
Quote, I leave the entirety of
my vast estate
to my second-born
and favorite son Moe.
That's sweet.
He must have
really loved that boy.
Anyway, that's it.
Once again,
I'm sorry for your loss.
If you have any questions,
please don't hesitate to call me.
Well, like I said, Mrs. Hess,
we're checking some things on our end,
but if there's anything
you could tell us
about your husband's business...
I appreciate the visit, Chief,
but Mrs. Hess had no kind of
involvement with Sam's business.
Frankly, she's mystified.
Her husband being a pillar of
the community and all.
I mean, heck,
voted Bemidji Businessman of the Year,
1996 and '98.
Who... who was it?
I'll tell you there.
Yeah.
Like I said, it's a puzzler.
'Course, we both
know some of your boys
have had run-ins with
the law in the past.
Stolen merchandise
charges and the like.
And, you know,
the Staties had that case
as to maybe your
outfit's got ties
to that crime
syndicate out of Fargo.
You're gonna stand here...
Let me get this straight.
You're gonna stand here
and call the victim a criminal in
front of his wife, his kids?
Well, now, no one's calling
anyone a criminal.
Just trying to figure
out what happened.
Chief! 217! 217!
What the heck?
Heya, Lester.
Hiya, Bo.
Jeez, what happened
to your face there?
You know that spot
near the fire station?
Where they wash the trucks?
Yep.
Slipped on the ice.
Say, Lester, I need you to
pull the file on Sam Hess.
On who now?
Sam Hess. You know, owns the truck
depot over on Winslow.
You know, big fella.
Yeah, well, he's dead.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Shame. It's a big policy.
Murder, they're saying.
Stabbed to death is what I heard.
You okay there, Lester?
Sure.
Sure... You know
I went to high school with him?
You don't say.
Well, anyway, I need you
to pull the policy on that.
I have to get on the phone
with his wife later.
Uh...
Did you...
Jeez.
Did you really kill him? Sam?
Oh, my God.
Is Sam dead?
How do you feel about that?
Well, I mean...
of course, it's...
you know, a tragedy.
Well, why'd you kill him then?
Now hold on a second!
I never--
Well, actually, you did.
Remember, yes or no?
I never said yes.
Didn't say no.
No, that won't-- Come on.
That...
In a court of law--
Who said anything
about a court of law?
Look, I just mean...
I... Jeez.
And he had a wife,
you know, and those boys.
Lester, he put you in a
barrel and rolled you on the road.
Your problem is you spent your
whole life thinking there are rules.
There aren't.
We used to be gorillas.
All we had is what
we could take and defend.
The truth is you're more of a man
today than you were yesterday.
How do you figure?
It's a red tide, Lester,
this life of ours.
The shit they make us eat...
day after day,
the boss, the wife,
et cetera, wearing us down.
If you don't stand up to it,
let 'em know you're still an
ape deep down, where it counts.
You're just gonna
get washed away.
Phone call, Chief.
It's the wife.
Hey, hon.
White.
White, what?
I decided we're gonna
paint the nursery white.
It's already white.
Well...
I want to paint it again.
The baby's room should have a new coat,
don't you think?
I do.
Any particular shade?
What do you mean?
Well, you got your
bright white, your snow white...
Eggshell.
Right, there's eggshell.
Oh. I hadn't thought of that.
I'll tell you what.
Why don't I stop
by the hardware
and pick up some
different shades
and we'll figure
it out tonight?
We're having a baby, Vern.
That's true.
No, I mean it's
finally sinking in.
We're gonna have a baby.
I can't wait.
I'll see you soon.
Is there anything else
you need there?
Nope, I'm good.
Come in, Chief.
This is Vern. Go ahead.
Chief,
I'm over at the hospital.
I was checking on
the Hess boy and--
How is he?
You know, broken collarbone.
Got his bell rung pretty good.
That's a shame.
Yeah.
Hey, so I got to
talking to Sue Roundtree
and I asked her if they
had any head injuries lately,
you know, my theory about
the driver and the wreck,
and she says they did...
yesterday.
Real peculiar fella, she says.
Real intense.
And here's where
it gets interesting.
'Cause she says the fella with
the head injury
was talking to another fella
about Sam Hess.
Yeah?
Yes, sir.
Says the two was
thick as thieves.
So suddenly I'm thinking
maybe these two cases,
maybe they're connected, huh?
Could be.
She say who
the other fella was?
Lester Nygaard.
Really?
You know him?
Sure, I know Lester.
Sells insurance
over at Bo's shop.
Yeah, yeah, I called over
and they're closed,
so I was gonna go
by Lester's place.
No, I know Lester.
I'll do it.
You call it a day.
Good work.
Lester?
In the basement.
Whatcha doing, hon?
I'm... trying to
fix the darn thing.
It looks like
the motor mount broke.
You sure you know
what you're doing?
It seems pretty
straightforward.
So, you want to
give her a try?
There's nothing in it.
For a test, I'm saying.
Turn it off.
Turn it off!
You killed it.
You killed my washing machine.
No, I was--
It was the...
the tide, you know?
I was standing up to the--
I was...
I was being a man.
But you're not
a man, Lester.
You're not even half a man.
Honestly, I don't know what
got into me marrying you.
My mom said,
"Don't do it, Pearl."
She said, "He's the kind of boy
that loses all the time.
"And you know what those boys
grow up to be, don't you? Losers."
Take that back.
Or what?
What are you gonna do?
You can't even face me
when we're having sex.
Now, hold on!
That is you not facing me!
That's so I can
picture a real man.
Oh!
You take that back.
Or what?
What are you gonna do?
Oh.
You gonna hit me?
That's a--
Oh.
Oh, jeez.
Oh, jeez. Oh, jeez.
Oh, God, I'm sorry.
Oh, God.
Yeah, it's me.
You gotta help me out.
I've done something bad.
Leroy's Motor Inn.
Hi. Can...
can I have Room 23 please?
Yeah?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's... it's...
it's me. It's Lester.
She's... My wife...
my wife, she's...
Oh, hell!
Look, I think I...
She's in the basement
dead and...
Look, I'm freaking out here.
I don't know what to do.
Lester, have you
been a bad boy?
Jeez.
Yeah, I took the hammer and...
Look, can you come over?
I'm on Willow Creek Drive, number 613.
Please! Please?
Sure, Lester.
I'll be right there.
Thank you. Thank you!
Here we go.
What did you do?
You killed her!
You killed her.
Evening, Lester.
It's supposed to get down to
negative 10 tonight, I hear.
Is Pearl home?
No.
No, she's at my brother's.
Okay, then.
How's the nose?
This...
It hurts.
How'd it happen, anyway?
Slipped, over by
the fire station.
You go to the hospital?
Yeah, they set it.
You talk to anyone
while you were there?
What do you mean?
Well, the reason I'm here...
I'm not sure you heard.
Sam Hess got killed
last night at the Lucky Penny.
Nasty business.
Yeah.
And, well...
I heard you were talking to another
fella about Hess before he died...
over at the hospital.
No, I don't think so.
What was his name again...
the other fella?
You okay, Lester?
You seem a bit... seem a bit jumpy.
Yeah, yeah,
yeah, it's just, you know...
Pearl is gonna be
home soon and...
Lester, listen to
me very carefully.
I need you to get
down on the ground.
Wait just a second.
Lester, on the ground!
This is not
what it looks like.
Now, hold on. Hold on.
Don't...
don't go down there.
There's nothing down--
That's not-- I didn't do nothing.
I didn't... I just got home.
I just got home and...
There's nothing down there.
That's not-- I
didn't do nothing.
I didn't do nothing!
I just came home.
This is Chief Thurman.
I'm at 613 Willow Creek Drive.
Requesting back up.
613 Willow Creek--
Chief?
Any more?
Lester, are there
any more cops?
Mmm-mmm.
What did you tell him?
Nothing.
He... he asked about Sam.
You got any more shells for this thing?
No.
Is that the basement?
Mmm.
Jeez.
The police are here.
I said the police are here!
What do we do?
Officer down.
613 Willow Creek Drive.
Roger that.
Confirming code 3.
Bemidji Police!
Oh, my God.
All units,
officer in need of immediate
assistance at 613 Willow Creek Drive.
Bemidji Police!
If there's someone in the house,
come out with your hands up.
Molly!
Down here!
Husband's alive.
Oh, jeez!
Dad, come in, Dad. Over.
Yeah, Dad here.
Come back.
Vikings up by 13. Over.
What happened? Over.
Kicked in another
field goal. Over.
Sweet.
You brush your teeth? Over.
Yeah. Over.
Homework? Over.
Did my math and science. I still have
to do English. Over.
Okay. Well, as soon
as the game's over.
Over.
Evening, Officer.
Evening.
License and registration,
please.
We could do it that way.
You ask me for my papers,
I tell you it's not my car,
that I borrowed it,
see where things
go from there.
We could do that...
or you could go get in your car
and drive away.
Now, why would I do that?
Because some roads
you shouldn't go down.
Because maps used to say,
"There be dragons here."
Now they don't.
But that don't mean
the dragons aren't there.
Dad, come in, Dad. Over.
You step out of the car,
please, sir?
How old's your kid?
I said, step out of the car.
Dad, come in, Dad. Over.
Let me tell you what's going to happen,
Officer Grimly.
I'm going to roll my window up.
Then I'm gonna drive away
and you're gonna go home to your daughter,
and every few years,
you're gonna look at
her face and know that you're alive
because you chose not to go
down a certain road on a certain night,
that you chose to walk into the
light instead of into the darkness.
Do you understand me?
Sir.
I'm rolling up my window.
Dad, come in, Dad. Over.
Dad...
are you there? Over.
So, I got two kinds of sandwiches.
Tuna and turkey.
Tuna's for the fish...
unless you think
they'd think that's cannibalism.
You know, I've been looking for
more help in the restaurant.
You know, someone to seat customers
and answer the phone.
A hostess?
Is that what they call it?
Yeah.
Anyway...
not sure if that's something
you might be interested in.
I'm a police officer, Dad.
Well, sure, I know that.
I also know that
people in this world
are... less inclined
to shoot a hostess
than, say,
an officer of the law.
That's true.
So, that mean you're gonna help
your old man out?
Nope.
But maybe you could
put that in the ad.
Listen, on second thought,
I think I'm gonna head into work.
Rain check on the fishing?
Sounds good.
Love you, Dad.
Love you too, hon.