Precedently on Fargo...
Who?
Fargo!
Freeze!
Police officer!
Halt!
That cop, the female,
says you are a suspect.
Suspect of what?
For Pearl,
the Chief...
even Sam Hess.
If you want this to go away,
you gotta give 'em someone.
It's good waffles,
hon.
It's a mix.
Who's ready for seconds?
- Gordo?
- Yeah.
- Watcha doing there?
- Reading a comic.
It's breakfast time,
though. It's supposed to
be family time.
Yeah, put your
comic away, huh?
- One more page.
- That's not...
It's breakfast, mister,
family time.
You heard your mother.
700 to 1,000
people are without power...
Your mom needs
help after school.
Got hockey.
After hockey, then.
I'm supposed to
play with Kevin.
Well, you can play
with Kevin tomorrow.
It's time you learned
some responsibility.
...thousands of fish
fell from the sky.
Oh, hon, listen to this.
Meteorologists are saying
the incident was probably
caused by a tornado,
which sucked up water
and fish from a lake and
dropped them off miles away.
And we'll have more
on this developing news
story a little later tonight,
along with our
meteorologist's take on
exactly what happened...
The darndest thing.
Come on, bud,
get your boots on.
You don't wanna be
late for the bus.
Kiss, kiss.
Kiss, kiss, kiss.
...crews are out in force
this morning, and will be
working around the clock
to keep roads as
clear as possible.
Love you.
- And me?
- Dad.
...as cleanup continues
on what reporters are calling
the storm of the century.
Plow drivers have
been working
for 24 hours straight
without rest and
feel exhausted.
We spoke to
one earlier today...
No funny stuff today.
So then, Neo's like,
"I'm the One,"
and Agent
What's-his-name is like...
"The sound
of inevitability."
Yeah.
And he's got him, right?
Around the neck.
You're hurting me a little.
Don't be such a baby.
Guys.
So they're on the
tracks, right?
And the train's coming.
And Neo says,
"No way." And he...
Uh...
So we're in the room
with the stripper, yeah?
And Blackman
wants to know
how much for a blumkin.
Which, I'm like...
"What the heck is that?"
Blackman.
Yeah.
So he says, you know,
"Why not stick around
and find out?"
And I'm like...
Mr. Nygaard,
your wife is on one.
Yeah,
I'll call her back.
Oh, no,
she said it's urgent.
Yeah, hon.
Chaz,
the cops are here.
Gordo's been arrested
and the cops are here.
Whoa, whoa, slow down.
What do you mean
the cops are there?
In the house.
They think that
Gordo brought
a gun to school.
And they're tearing up
the house.
They say they got
a search warrant.
Don't... Don't let them.
I... I'll be right there.
Just...
I'll be right there!
Chaz, what have you done?
I'm coming! I'm on my way!
Chaz?
Now...
Wait, hold on!
Hold on a minute What?
You son of a bitch!
He's my baby!
No, I got...
I got permits for those.
You son of a bitch!
Now, Bill Oswalt,
hold on...
Son of a bitch!
I can explain that. I...
What have you done?
You son of a bitch!
I hate you.
Hey. Bill...
Busy morning, huh?
Is there...
some kind of development
with the case?
Is that why I'm...
Where's the female deputy?
She got shot, Lester.
She got...
In Duluth.
I should be up
there right now,
but then there's
this mess.
I don't even know
where to start.
It's like... When you see
on the news...
A boat sinks in India
and 300 people drown.
And you ask yourself,
"Do I know 300 people?"
Or one of those
African massacres with
12 year-olds with machetes.
And they kill,
You can't even...
you can't even
count that high.
We lost 16 people in
1920 to the flu.
I looked it up.
In '78, six people died
in a pharmacy fire.
But nothing
like this, ever.
Three people murdered
in two days,
including the
Chief of Police...
Lenny Potts missing...
and a cop shot.
And now a kid brings
a gun to school.
A kid?
It was Gordo, Lester.
Gordo? My Gordo?
He had a handgun
in his backpack.
Unloaded, thank gosh.
But still, you can't
Not with the
current climate.
Is he in trouble?
Is he... He brought
a gun to school!
And still,
Gordo's the least of this.
We searched the house.
And, Lester,
I gotta tell ya,
I don't know whether to...
After all these years,
I'd like to think
that you could've...
come to me.
You could've trusted me
as a friend with...
We know you were
in the room when
Vern was shot.
You had a shotgun pellet
in your hand,
same as killed Vern.
Was your wife
having an affair?
With Chaz?
Mmm-hmm.
We found a photo...
photos...
at his place...
suggestive...
I don't wanna
talk about...
...boudoir photos
and a pair of...
Bill...
Yeah. And I know...
I know how much
you loved her.
I remember.
Ninth grade science class,
Mrs. Nagutuck...
Pearl walks in the
first day of class
and sits down
and you look at me...
"I'm gonna marry
that girl one day."
But she was always...
I know this is
out of line, but...
we all heard the stories.
But to sleep with
your own brother?
I know.
God! Your own brother!
And what then?
She tells him
it's over and he...
We all know your
brother had a temper.
He broke a guy's
nose once just
for cracking wise
at the state fair.
Yeah! I remember.
He had to do
community service.
So what?
She cuts it off,
the affair, and then he...
All I know is that I
came home from work
and they were arguing
in the basement.
I heard the voices.
I thought, "Is that Chaz?"
And so I went
over to the top
of the stairs to hear,
you know.
And she says...
Uh...
"Love? Is that what
you think this is?"
Or something like that.
And she laughs.
And then she says,
"You know,
you're not half the
man your brother is."
Then I hear
this sound. This...
I'll never forget it.
So... Um...
...I run downstairs and...
...there's Chaz.
And he's got the hammer...
And he looks up
at me and says,
"Oh, geez, Lester.
"What did I..."
I'm upset.
I try to get to Pearl,
you know,
to check if she's...
And Chaz says to me,
"Lester, this was
an accident."
And I'm... "An accident?"
He hit her with a hammer.
And... he raises up
the hammer again.
He's still looking at me.
I don't know if
he's gonna... or what.
So I say, something like,
"Chaz, what the heck..."
And the doorbell rings.
Vern?
Mmm-hmm.
I wanted to say
something, Bill.
I swear.
But Chaz,
you know, he's...
You were afraid?
Oh, I was afraid.
And Chaz is my
only brother.
So then what happens?
So then we go upstairs...
and Chaz says,
"Take care of it."
And he goes in the back.
Where you
kept the shotgun.
Where I kept the shotgun.
I should have thought
about the shotgun.
I know, I know.
But I... I was in shock.
So I let Vern in,
and right away,
I think to tell him,
to say what's happened.
Because Pearl
could still be
alive downstairs,
there might still be
time to...
And then Chaz comes
in with the shotgun.
I should've stopped him.
I should've said
right away...
"Chaz is in the
house and he's..."
But I was afraid,
like you said.
And now...
And now, it's...
Bill, if you think that
makes me guilty
of something, then...
Oh, I want you to throw
the book at me.
Put me in jail.
'Cause I loved her,
you know, Pearl.
Despite all...
She was...
She was my wife.
Lester? Lester!
Lester, what did you do?
Lester!
Freeze!
Police officer!
Halt!
She's awake.
Hey.
What happened?
Um, you got shot.
Just go outside
now, okay?
Why?
Just do it.
Did we get him?
Who?
Malvo.
I had him and...
Till this other
fella popped up.
Um...
Look now,
I gotta tell you
something.
Do you know what
happened to
the fella I shot?
Is he...
He's... They got him
upstairs...
in Intensive.
I shot him twice.
Just like they
teach you...
center mass.
And him with
a bazooka.
How the heck
did I do that?
'Cause you're you.
Look, here's the...
Uh...
I shot you.
Well, that don't
make sense.
You... you ran off.
And I couldn't see
anything, you know?
I mean...
not that that's any...
There's... there's no
excuse for it,
for what I did.
You were out there...
alone, needing
back up and I...
What'd I lose?
A spleen.
Oh...
I'll get you a new one,
I swear.
Yeah, you better.
There's gonna
be an inquiry.
I... I was too shook up
at the scene to...
but... I'll...
I'll confess.
They'll probably
take my badge,
but with all
that's happened,
that's likely best.
So...
Come on now.
You said yourself it was...
a blizzard and
whiteout conditions.
And I...
I could have shot you
just as easy.
I... I've just been
messing things up
from the go.
Hey, now.
That's enough of that.
You want some pop
or something...
No, but I want a new spleen,
that's... what I want.
So... you know...
you better get
cracking, mister.
Dad... who's watching
the restaurant?
Screw the
damn restaurant.
I guess we both got
bullet holes now, huh?
You got premium channels?
I'm not sure.
I just woke up.
...this work that
is extremely difficult.
The bark beetle carries
the worm to its nest.
He shoots,
he scores!
Gophers are playing.
If that's what you
wanna watch.
Ben Schmidt says
you put down a guy
with an assault rifle.
Well, he was
pointing it at me.
Yeah.
Proud of you.
Hmm...
All right.
Cleaners?
Hi. Yeah, I got...
How you doin' there then?
I'm real good now.
How are you?
You know, can't complain.
Wife's got a bit of a cold,
but that's life, right?
Sure.
Well, my house needs...
It's... I'm not gonna lie.
It's a real mess.
That's our
bread and butter.
Well, do you fellas
do crime scenes?
Had a breakin, huh?
Yeah, it's a little worse
than a breakin.
A lot of broken glass or...
I'd rather not get...
Sometimes they
defecate in your...
Oh, let's just say
there's a lot of blood.
Hello?
Good!
And twist!
And front!
And side!
And two...
and three and good!
Left arm.
And bend... bend...
bend.
Good!
- It's one story.
- One story...
So I notice you got
a pin on your map in
every state but Georgia.
What the hell do you got
against Georgia?
My first wife.
She was Korean.
She used to spit at me
when we had sex.
Can I sit?
Or... did you wanna
kill me standing?
Two hombres took
a run at me in Duluth.
Mexicans?
That's the wrong
part of the sentence
to be focusing on.
The point is,
they said Fargo
sent them.
So I have two questions.
First...
did you tell these boys
where to find me?
Second...
who do I see
about this in Fargo?
Look...
you know I can't...
Did you put them on me?
No. Of course not.
But you gotta
understand...
this is a business
of relationships.
I can't just...
Of relationships?
Right.
And... well...
it's not my position
professionally to get
involved in squabbles.
Especially not of
a private nature.
How do you
know it's private?
If people are unhappy
with our services...
they call.
A guy screws up,
arrangements are made...
a cash settlement.
If that's not enough,
he'd break a leg
or an arm.
But no calls...
not about you.
So whatever it is...
it's gotta be personal.
It doesn't matter.
It's the principle.
This one calls an ambulance.
That one calls a hearse.
I'm gonna ask you again.
And depending
on the answer...
I pick up this or that.
Who do I talk to in Fargo?
You remember me?
Um...
Dead.
Can...
Can you talk?
Speak, I mean.
Right.
But you...
you read lips?
Okay.
You know I'm the one
who shot you, yeah?
Do you remember me
from before?
In Bemidji?
The insurance office.
You were talking to
Lester Nygaard.
It just hit me,
lying in bed thinking
about that...
what happened, you know.
Hold the phone,
I know that fella.
Did you come here
looking for Malvo?
For...
Lorne...
Malvo. Lorne Malvo?
Did Lester tell you
where to find him?
It hurts.
Yeah... mine, too.
You know, it's crazy.
I never shot anyone before.
I'm gathering this wasn't
your first time, though.
Look at us.
And you got a dad
somewhere I bet,
just like me.
And I mean,
what's the point,
you know?
Because here you are and...
your friend is dead.
And you're gonna spend
the rest of your life
in jail.
And for what?
Okay.
Okay, Mr. Nygaard.
I gotta ask you to stand
and put your back
to the bars.
Listen, Officer,
this is a huge mistake.
This is a setup.
Sir.
Do you understand?
Evidence has been
planted...
Sir, turn and back
towards me...
It's been falsified
and if I...
...or I'm gonna have
to tase you!
...could just talk to
my brother...
This is a nightmare.
You...
You gotta believe me.
I didn't do these things.
Not for me to say, sir.
Where are you...
Transfer to county.
You'll be there
until the trial...
or until you make bail.
Jeez, Lester.
Oh, hey.
I heard
you got arrested.
Well, you know how it is.
Had a few too many,
slept it off at
the station.
Who can blame you really...
after what you've
been through.
Yeah.
They were real
sweet to me.
I'm the victim here,
you know.
Of course.
So...
what's on the
agenda for today?
I'm ready to go...
you know... start fresh.
I... I can work
late even.
There's nothing at home
but an empty house. So...
Right. Well...
I was just about to
call the widow Hess.
Yeah, her claim's
been denied.
You don't say.
Yeah.
It seems Sam stopped
paying the premium.
A shame, really.
I mean, good for us.
That was a big policy.
Well, she's not gonna be
happy about that.
No, she's not.
Why don't I take that
off your plate?
Really?
I mean, I don't know.
Are you sure
you're ready for...
Look, she can't
shout at me, right?
Not after...
I mean,
we're in the same boat.
So I figure I tell her,
she has a good cry,
and that's that.
Otherwise she's gonna
be all claws out.
That makes sense.
Yeah. Then it's settled.
I'll head over.
You don't wanna just call?
No, in person is better,
I think.
Give her a shoulder,
you know?
Come in.
I... brought you
some flowers.
Oh, thanks,
just put 'em...
What are you...
Oh.
It's making my
head hurt.
This whole case...
all the moving pieces.
I thought I'd put it up,
you know, graphically...
see if things made
much more sense.
I called back to Bemidji
to talk to Bill,
but he's...
I don't know.
Some kid brought a gun
to school or something.
So everyone's kind of
running around.
And to be honest,
everything they said didn't
make much sense anyway.
Who's the
deaf fella then?
Fella upstairs,
tried to murder me
with a bazooka.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Turns out he can't hear.
And the other fella
with his throat cut,
I'm guessing he translated.
And they're who now?
Well...
that's the thing.
All I can think is...
and maybe this is a stretch,
but heck if I know
any other way to
think about it.
Sam Hess, right?
So... he owns
a trucking company.
And we always thought
he had maybe alleged
ties to organized crime,
this operation
out of Fargo.
So... when Hess
gets killed,
I'm thinking maybe Fargo
sends these two boys
to figure out
what happened.
And how do they
end up here?
Well... follow me.
If we think...
which we do...
...that Lester...
on the day
of the murder...
got bullied by Hess...
and then met Malvo
at the hospital.
Right... and hired Malvo
to kill Hess.
Which he did.
And then...
these two boys come in
from out of town
asking questions.
Get to finding Lester.
And he sends 'em here.
So Lester knew
that Malvo was here...
in Duluth.
It would appear
that way, yeah.
Well, that's...
that's ammunition, right?
I mean,
to go back to Lester.
Oh, yeah. You betcha.
Took forever,
but I got 'em to sign off
on taking you home.
Oh, so you're...
Yeah. Sure that...
Recover at home,
you know, it...
makes sense, sure.
Thanks, Dad.
Well, okay.
I guess I'll see
you later.
Dad, my flowers.
Oh, yeah.
Thanks for these.
He bought me flowers.
You don't say.
Glad you like them.
I'm gonna put them in water
as soon as I get home.
You keep your chin up,
Gus Grimly.
We're winning this thing.
Don't you forget.
Say bye to
Greta for me.
So he's got the stick
in his mouth, right?
Biting down.
And I grab the arrow...
and Craig is in the
car having a giggle.
Thinks the whole
thing's hilarious, which...
That's my cousin
out there, right?
So I slip the knife
out of me boot.
Give him the
old what for.
Held the knife to
his bloody face.
And lunch is over.
I don't know how
they eat that crap
every day.
Speaking of...
What? It's fresh.
Do you know the
conditions of a modern
fast food restaurant?
I'm not just talking
about hygiene.
Get bent.
They did an
experiment once.
Scientist took two
glasses of water...
and he starts
cursing at one,
calling it all
kinds of names.
You're making this up.
I swear to God.
Mmm-mmm.
He yells at one glass
and then whispers sweet
nothings to the other glass.
Okay? And in one week...
Just stop it.
But, listen,
a week later...
Can I help you, sir?
Gun!
Is that shots?
Oh, my God! My God!
Drop it!
Call 911!
- Where's the top dog?
- The what?
The boss man.
Third floor.
Private elevator.
Oh, no! No!
He's got a gun!
Freeze, shit bird!
Shit! Ah...
What's the code
for the elevator?
Nine-thirty-three.
He's gotta be in there.
Son of a...
God damn it!
Get him!
Get him! Quick!
Come on, get back!
Get him!
Jesus!
What the... What?
Was that...
Call it in.
Oh. Okay.
Call it in, man.
Your pop is in the way.
Where are you...
Hold on.
Got me all...
Maybe we should get
in the car and then
back up a few feet
and then pull back in
like we just arrived.
Can we just
focus on the...
You need to have
fewer ideas.
Shitballs.
We're in so much...
Okay, let me
do the talking.
Why? I can do the talking.
Because
when you talk...
Back!
...bad shit happens.
Get back!
FBI! We're FBI!
Back! Get back!
Get back, please.
Police on the scene.
What have you guys got?
Really?
No... Well,
he doesn't know...
It's a body. Lock it down.
Multiple gunshots.
The shooter's still
inside the building.
You're gonna need
more patrolmen than this.
Okay, okay.
Okay, we're good.
We're going in. Back us up.
James, you follow us,
come on.
Yes, sir.
It's about time.
I've been calling.
Sorry about the delay.
You know the red tape
on these things.
Mmm-mmm.
Come on in.
Thanks.
You look
real nice today.
Thanks.
You're sweet.
The boys home?
No, thank God.
They have a game.
Good.
You don't go
then, no?
Are you kidding?
I just stay here trying
to drink enough
so I'm numb by
the time they get home.
Got one of those for me?
Why, Lester...
Hmm?
Sure.
Cheers.
To fresh beginnings.
Yeah.
So it's all set, right?
I'm getting paid?
Um...
Well, they should.
What do you mean
"should"?
When do I get
the money?
Like I said,
there's a few more hoops
on these homicide cases.
We're not just
talking about filing
a death certificate.
I don't think
I'm telling you anything
you don't know
when I say these
insurance companies,
they don't like
writing checks.
But I'm gonna
get it, right?
Well... that is
where a skilled
middleman such as
myself comes in.
You see,
it's all about
knowing who to call.
It's all about
knowing which...
palms to grease...
if you get my meaning.
I...
know a little something...
about greasy palms.
Well, why don't you
and me have another drink?
You can show me that.
Oh, Lester!
Lester.
Slow down, tiger.
You're hurting me.
I'm sorry.
God. Oh, God. Oh, God.
Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God.
I should take you home
and put you to bed.
It'll just be a second.
I promise.
Hey.
Oh, my gosh. Are you...
They said you were still...
Oh, the bullet went
clean through.
Doc says take
a few days, rest up.
Otherwise, fine.
Where is everyone?
Celebrating.
We got him...
who killed the Chief.
Lester?
You arrested Lester?
No.
Didn't you hear?
It was his brother...
Chaz... the whole time.
He was having an affair
with the wife.
She broke it off.
What?
Yeah.
Beat her with the hammer,
then shot the Chief.
Lester covered for him.
Bill thinks 'cause of
Chaz's temper...
you know...
the fear factor.
Where...
That's not...
I gotta talk to Bill.
Where's Bill?
Yeah, with the rest...
over at Bernard's.
I'm supposed to go over
after my shift.
Okay, I gotta...
Shouldn't you go home?
You okay, hon?