We're here about Hess.
Oh, yeah,
you want Gold...
Uh, Max Gold.
He's on his way.
You Gold?
Yeah.
And you're...
We're from Fargo.
Good. They, uh,
said they were
sending someone.
They were right.
There's no library
in this town.
Why is there no
library in this town?
Uh, cutbacks?
He thinks every town
should have a library.
I agree.
Tell him I agree.
Fargo sent us to find out
what happened to Hess.
He got stabbed in
the back of the head
at a strip club is
what happened to him.
Okay.
Okay. Okay,
all right.
Do you believe
this was connected
to the business?
I...
Things have been quiet.
No labor BS,
no skirmishes with
other trucking concerns.
So?
There was a guy.
I told this to Fargo.
He came by the garage
the day it happened.
Brown hair,
just under 6 feet,
not young, not old,
had a cut on
his forehead here.
Said he just wanted
to take a look at Sam,
which he did, then he left.
Look...
Hold on a second.
He was my
friend, okay?
Sam.
Sure, he was a jerk,
but deep down...
All I'm saying is,
you're gonna
find him, right?
The guy who did it.
We'll find him.
How's your
head, then?
Oh, yeah, it's okay.
Aches still, but...
You try that
hot dish?
Oh, yeah.
Real good.
Yeah.
So, you know...
Kitty and I were talking
and we think you should
move in here for a while.
Just stay with us,
you know,
until you get the house
cleaned up or sold.
Why the heck
would I sell the house?
Oh.
Not saying you
have to go that way.
Just, you know,
stay a few days,
until we get
it cleaned up.
Cops left a real mess.
Oh, yeah? Mmm-hmm.
Yeah, the crime
scene and all.
Really turned
the place upside down.
Looking for clues,
I suppose.
How you doing?
You all right? Okay.
You don't have
to do that.
They were piling up.
Vern told me
this story once.
When he was a rookie,
he had a boss who
couldn't tell his shoe
from his foot.
Got killed by
a hail stone.
Just standing
in the parking lot
at the Dairy Queen,
having a milkshake.
Hail stone comes down,
size of a softball,
crushes his skull.
What flavor?
Strawberry, I think.
I was thinking about
when my dad got shot.
Traffic stop, yeah?
Mmm.
Yeah.
He pulled over
the fellas
that robbed Callahan's
and stole the snow plow.
They came to
tell me at school.
I was in algebra.
And he's okay,
you know?
Got the limp, of course,
but, uh, they caught
the guys, so...
The little one
he even got probation.
Convinced the jury
it was a Stockholm
syndrome deal.
Okay, we got now
a list of who will come
by when and do what.
This is on
the due date,
you know?
Get you to the hospital,
bring you home, so,
you're covered.
Say, Bill,
I was thinking.
We should talk
to Lester Nygaard
first thing.
Lester? Ugh.
He already made
a statement back
at the hospital.
Yeah, I know.
I read it.
But, see, thing is,
Vern was on his way
to Lester's house
to talk to him
about Hess' murder,
you know, how possibly
Lester was involved.
Lester?
Ah.
Went to high school
with Lester. Uh...
Had to dissect a mouse
in Mrs. Knutson's class
and poor Lester fainted.
Well, yeah,
okay, but...
Girl had her monthly
once in gym class.
There goes Lester
fainting again.
Right, so he...
he doesn't like blood,
but still...
Plus,
this Hess murder,
got to believe that's
about the cutthroat world
of regional trucking.
Yeah.
So it's, uh,
just coincidence,
you're saying?
Hess gets killed
and then,
the massacre at Lester's
house the next day.
Exactly.
See, I'm thinking
this is home invasion.
You know,
it's a drifter
or some such.
Drug related, maybe,
but not, you know,
Lester Nygaard.
Am I right, Ida?
You're not not right.
But, on these
high-profile deals, Bill,
it never hurts
to talk to the
eyewitnesses yourself.
"Take control
of the facts."
That's what Vern
always used to say.
Okay. Okay, good.
We go see Lester,
but, I do the talking.
Heya, Lester.
Bill.
Mr. Nygaard, uh,
we got some questions
we'd like...
This is Molly.
Deputy Solverson.
Sure. Nice to meet you.
Like I was saying, uh,
we got some questions,
so...
How you
holding up, Lester?
How's the head?
Oh. Yeah.
Yeah, it hurts.
Uh, I got a little,
double vision still.
Jeez, well, you know,
if now's not a good time...
No, no,
I was just about to...
I want to help, you know?
It's just there's
so much work to do.
Yeah, sure.
It'll only take
a second.
Oh.
All I got is grape juice.
Hope that's okay. Ugh.
Pearl says it reminds her
of being a kid.
Said.
Uh, remember that gum.
That grape gum
that they had
when we were kids?
Heck, what was
that called?
Uh, so we got
your statement
from the hospital.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I...
I was real thorough
with those fellas.
I... I mean,
what I could remember.
Doctor says
I got a concussion.
Says if I was hit
any harder,
my brain could've swoll up
and leaked right out my ears.
Oh!
Thank gosh
that didn't happen.
Uh, in your statement,
you said that, um,
you came home
and found your wife,
that...
that she was
already dead.
Uh, downstairs, yeah.
I heard the washer going...
spin cycle...
and I...
Well, you know, she...
she was on the floor,
you know,
and there was
a lot of...
I never even
heard the guy.
Uh, just one minute
I'm, uh,
looking at her...
and the next...
So, uh, you don't
remember Chief Thurman
coming to the house then?
Oh, no, no.
I feel sick
about that, really.
I guess he saw
the guy breaking in.
Uh, no, Mr. Nygaard.
Uh...
Chief Thurman
came to talk to you
about a man you may
have met in the emergency
room the day previous.
Hmm, you don't say.
Look, Lester,
if this is too
hard for you,
you can just give us
the bare bones...
We got a witness
says that, uh...
she saw you and
this other fella arguing
about Sam Hess.
Who?
Sam Hess.
You remember Sam.
He used to beat you
up in high school.
What?
Oh, yeah, Sam had a thing
for ol' Lester here.
Used to chase him
around the schoolyard
till one or the other
ran out of gas.
You remember...
big kid. Uh...
What was that
name he called you?
Lester Nig...
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, Sam.
Yeah.
That... that was
a long time ago.
Oh...
But,
you were talking about him
in the emergency room,
so what's the story there?
Well, I, uh...
Hmm, it's real fuzzy,
but I might have said,
uh,
"My face is a mess."
Mess sounds like Hess,
so probably your, uh,
the witness just misheard.
Yeah, that's possible.
Can you describe
the fella?
Height, eye color,
that kind of thing?
You know,
the last few days,
they're real fuzzy.
Reason we asks is,
we got an operating
theory, okay?
This being the work
of a drifter...
or drifters...
possibly drug-related.
See...
I'm thinking this fella
you met at the hospital...
maybe he followed
you home...
That's not...
We don't both...
share that theory. So...
No, but... Yeah.
I... I'm a little scrambled
right now.
Uh, I... I got a concussion.
I'm not sure if I said that.
So, uh,
yeah, things...
things are
kind of fuzzy.
Well,
you know what?
I'm satisfied.
I've actually...
I got a few
more questions...
Yeah. Thanks for
the grape juice, Lester.
Uh...
Takes me back,
I tell you.
And, uh,
I'm gonna
look up the name
of that gum
when I get home.
Hubba Bubba.
Hubba Bubba, yeah,
yeah, Hubba Bubba.
We used to
crack up about that.
Do you remember
Hubba Bubba?
No.
If you need
anything, Lester,
you give us a call.
'Cause I'll tell you what,
this is a tragedy.
Straight-up,
dyed-in-the-wool
tragedy.
She was a good woman,
you know.
Good wife.
I...
I just keep
asking myself...
"Who could've done
a thing like this?"
Good morning,
young fella.
You have a package
for me?
All righty,
what's your name?
Why?
So I can find
the package.
Duluth.
I'm sorry?
The package is
addressed to "Duluth."
Eh, that's a city.
I need your name.
I told you my name.
Your name's Duluth?
Well, I'll need
to see some ID.
No.
What?
You heard me.
Well, I can't
give you your mail
if you don't show ID.
Sure you can.
All you gotta do
is look through those
packages over there,
find the one
addressed to "Duluth"
and then hand it to me.
Look, son,
we're in Duluth,
so technically,
all the mail is
addressed to "Duluth."
Am I gonna need
to come back there
and find it myself?
Sir?
Okay.
This is highly irregular.
No, highly irregular
is the time
I found a human foot
in a toaster oven.
This is just odd.
Uh.
I'm a minister, apparently.
Sir?
You have
a blessed day.
Mmm.
Missed a spot.
You're looking at the
Supermarket King of Minnesota,
La Mercado Rey.
Twenty-nine markets
in 15 counties...
and it all
started right here,
in this office.
Next quarter, we're
expanding into Wisconsin
and the Dakotas.
By this time
next year,
I'll rule the whole
goddamn Midwest.
You see my mangoes?
Straight from Ecuador.
Kiwis, too.
That's what makes my stores
so goddamn superior.
I got mangoes in
goddamn January...
and the back of
a 90-year-old woman.
God damn it.
Who's the fire hydrant?
Semenko,
head of security.
You an Oilers fan?
Wally here is 1992
Farm League MVP.
Knocked 138 heads
career-wise.
Ain't that right, Wally?
Our mutual friend
said something about
a blackmail letter?
Found this on my
windshield last week.
What does this mean,
"I know about the money"?
What it means
don't matter.
It's blackmail.
I didn't bring you here
for what it means.
I brought you here
to make it stop.
Semenko said, "Don't do it."
He said...
he said, "Let me handle it."
But you don't get
to be La Mercado Rey
without knowing
when to delegate.
That's a pretty
specific number,
$43,613.
Hell, maybe
he wants to pay off
his student loans.
I don't know.
What matters is,
can you find the guy?
Hey, Dad,
got a good one
for you.
Oh, sorry.
Don't you know
closed door means
"keep out," boy,
or at least knock,
for shit's sake?
You'll like this.
What's a karate expert's
favorite beverage?
Kara-tea.
Get it?
It's... it's tea.
Son, get the hell out.
Nice to meet you.
Look, I can find the guy.
The question is,
what do you
want done with him
once he's found?
Send him packing.
Isn't that what they say?
Who says that?
In the movies.
I don't watch movies.
You don't watch movies?
Look...
this ain't complicated.
You don't get to be
the Supermarket
King of Minnesota
without making
a few enemies,
all right?
Start with my damn wife.
You think your wife's
blackmailing you?
You ever nail
a Greek woman?
After 40,
their pussies grow teeth.
And she ain't my wife.
She's my
soon-to-be ex-wife,
and she is suing
me for 50%.
Except now,
I'm starting to think
maybe 50% ain't
enough for her.
This is kind
of embarrassing,
but, uh,
would you sign
a copy of my book?
I'd be delighted.
You, uh, you want
something personal?
Yeah, could you put,
"To Frank Peterson,
"thanks for nailing
my blackmailer."
I'm just kidding.
Anything you want.
You're the writer.
In addition to the victims
in the basement,
that's Nygaard,
Mr. and Mrs.,
we're hearing
the chief of police
was shot-gunned
in the foyer.
That means entryway.
No description
yet of the suspect
or suspects,
but I told the new chief
over in Bemidji
we'd be on high alert
for anything that connects.
That means
suspicious persons
or jailhouse snitches
saying they know a thing.
Okay, let's get to it.
Grimly.
Animal Control guy called in sick again.
You're on duty.
Yes, sir.
I got "aurora borealis."
What about you? Over.
I just put "northern lights." Over.
Um, my dad's home
with dinner. Over.
What's it tonight? Over.
It looks like
burgers. Over.
And chicken nuggets.
Over and out.
You get
the dipping sauces?
Extra, even.
Oh.
Good day?
Yeah.
We, um,
we had an assembly...
and the principal
talked about bullying
and how bullying was wrong
and if we saw
somebody getting bullied,
we should
say something
or stop it.
And I raised my hand,
and I asked
what you're supposed
to do
if the bully is, like,
a lot bigger than you
or has a knife
or something.
And what did he say?
He said if the bully
has a knife, then,
you should tell
a grown-up.
Well, that's good advice.
Yeah, but,
what if there's no time?
I mean,
you're the police.
If you saw somebody
doing something,
you'd stop 'em, right?
Well, you know,
sometimes there's more
than one right thing.
What does that mean?
It means,
I got you, and I am
responsible for you...
and sometimes,
I might be in
a situation where,
and this hasn't happened
and it won't,
but a situation where...
if I try to stop a guy
from doing a bad thing,
I could get hurt,
or worse.
And then, who would
take care of you?
But it's your job.
Well, I got two jobs,
and the first,
the most important,
is being your dad.
Well,
if I saw somebody
doing something...
I would stop 'em.
I believe you would.
Every cooperation,
obviously.
If you want the girl,
if you want drug,
just ask.
You know who we are.
I told the police,
I couldn't see the guy
on account of the blood
being in my eyes.
We got a description
of a man.
5'10", brown hair,
big bruise on
the forehead.
Does it ring
a bell at all?
Could be Lenny.
Who's Lenny?
Comes in here a lot.
Drinks pretty heavy.
I heard him say
a few things over the years
about guys like Hess.
Money in the pocket,
think they're tough shit.
That's him at the bar
with the Band-Aid
on his head.
Well, the Russians,
they used to send
dogs up into space
which is stupid
because what's a dog
gonna do in space?
At least with a monkey,
they can operate
the, uh,
the equipment
and something.
Hey, my friend would
like an orange soda
and I'll have, uh,
just a cup of hot
water with lemon.
What are you
supposed to be, some
kind of, uh, circus act?
Oh, my friend was
wondering, how'd you, uh,
hurt your head?
Oh, is your friend
looking for a date?
'Cause you know
this is a place for dicks
who like pussies,
not pussies
who like dick.
No, seriously,
how'd you hurt
your head?
Screw.
I ain't afraid of
a dink and a lepton.
You like playing
with knives?
Oh, you keep
talking, big boy,
you're gonna find out.
That the guy?
Can you take off
the tape maybe?
God damn
you little bastards!
I'll kill the lot of you!
Hey, now,
look, okay?
I'm sorry for what
I said to you before
about the dink
and the lepton.
I don't think
it's him.
Delicious.
Just a few more.
What'd you say
your name was again,
handsome?
Frank Peterson, ma'am.
I work for Mike,
your divorce attorney.
Ah, charmed,
I'm sure.
Oh, sorry,
I just bronzed.
He's a pig.
You smelled his hands?
Have I smelled
your husband's hands?
They smell like feet.
Your ass looks
amazing, darling.
Keep it up.
So anyway, uh,
I've been tasked
to put together
a complete record
of your husband's assets.
We want to get you
the biggest divorce
settlement possible.
Now, I've got your
husband's net worth
estimated at $10 million?
More.
Fifteen?
Okay, sweetie, uh,
let's do a cool down,
yeah? Five minutes.
There you go.
Ma'am, can you
confirm that
your husband started
his first grocery with
a loan from his uncle
like it says
in the book?
That's the story.
But you don't believe it?
Stavros
had two uncles.
One was a drunk
who lived in a barn...
and the other died
in a fishing accident
when he was 10.
So where did
the money come from?
Hey, Ma.
Frank Peterson.
Oh, yeah,
from the store.
Hey, I got one
for you.
What kind of bone
will a dog never eat?
Huh.
Chicken?
A trombone.
Oh, yeah.
That's a good one.
A trombone.
Oh, my dad'll
like that one.
Your dad,
your dad.
Your dad's
screwing us, mister.
Mommy.
What? I'm just
being honest.
He's a hard-on,
your father,
and you're too trusting.
But he's my dad
and you're my mom
and everything's
gonna work out, okay?
Mmm.
Oh.
Aren't they just
the sweetest pair?
Mmm?
Yeah, it's... it's... it's me.
It's Lester.
Uh, she's, um... My wife...
my wife, she's, uh...
Oh, hell!
Um...
I think I, uh...
She's in the basement
dead and, uh...
Look, I'm freaking out here.
I don't know what to do.
Yeah, it's... it's...
it's me. It's Lester.
Uh, she's, um... My wife...
my wife, she's, uh...
Oh, hell!
Um...
I think I, uh...
She's in the basement
dead and, uh...
Look, I'm freaking out here.
I don't know what to do.
Lester, have you
been a bad boy?
Jeez. Yeah...
Oh, sorry,
I just bronzed.
...I took the hammer
and, uh...
Look, can you come over?
I'm on Willow Creek Drive, number 613.
Please! Please?
Sure, Lester.
I'll be right there.
This place is a shithole.
Okay, nutsack, here's the drill.
You're gonna pack up
your shit and blow.
I'll tell Stavros you
couldn't find the guy,
and in return,
I won't bust your head.
You hearing me, asswipe?
I did some digging on you, made
some calls, you get me?
And we don't need you and your
big city connections
coming here and showing us
what time it is.
I'm the guy.
You understand? Me.
Twenty years I work
for the King.
You know what that makes me?
The goddamn
prime minister.
So give me the letter,
pack up your shit and...
What the hell you doing?
That's disgusting.
Okay, slick.
I got your number.
I'm on to you.
Just remember,
you were warned.
Semenko warned you.
Uh, hey, Molly?
Yeah, Chief?
So, just want to make sure
we're on the same page
about everything.
I want you to center it.
Same page
about what?
Just about Lester
and the case, you know.
Just want to make sure
you know to focus on
the break-in angle.
Maybe call some other
towns, see if they had
a similar problem.
No, higher.
Similar to three murders,
including the police chief?
Not, you know,
literally.
Just ruffians
and the like.
Right there. Perfect.
Look, Chief, I know
you don't think Lester...
Maybe call the Staties,
you know?
See if they effected
any car stops,
suspicious types...
where the driver
had a head wound
and the like.
Yeah.
Yeah, but I think, uh,
Just...
leave poor Lester
alone, will you?
You'll be
in Gordo's room.
He's on the sofa
which is... Ha!
Don't worry.
His dad built him a fort.
He loves it.
Ugh.
Baby, it's cold outside! Brr.
But here at Phoenix Farms,
it's always summer.
Real good peas, hon.
Yeah, Mom, real good.
How's your dinner
there, Lester?
Oh, yeah. Real good.
I was thinking of going hunting
this weekend.
Mmm-hmm.
Told Gordo I would
take him shooting.
You interested?
Ah...
Now, hon,
I don't think
your brother wants
to be around all
that guns and violence,
not... not after
what happened.
Oh, shoot, I'm sorry.
No, no, it's fine.
I can be a real
ass sometimes.
Language.
No, no, no, I...
It sounds, um...
You know, you know,
bag a deer or something.
So, I... I've been thinking,
maybe I should sell
the place, you know?
Get a...
What do you call it,
a fresh start?
Yeah? That's
great. Mmm.
I'll call Jimmy.
It's a fine market
right now he says.
Real good.
It is the right choice,
sweetie.
Too many bad memories
in that old house.
Mmm-hmm.
Both Chaz
and me think so.
Oh!
Oh, jeez!
Mmm.
Oh, I am...
I am so sorry.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Hi.
What can I
do for you, son?
Well, uh, I got a...
I need something for
a wound,
I guess you'd call it.
Are we talking pain pill
or something more topical?
Well, it's...
I guess, um,
something to keep it
from getting infected.
Okay, that'd be
an anti-bacterial.
All right.
I got some in the back.
Mr. Nygaard?
Yeah? Ooh!
Hiya.
Hi.
Deputy Solverson again.
I just have
a few more questions.
Is now a good time?
Not really.
I'm kind of in
the middle of...
Sure. Yeah, no,
I understand.
Yeah, it won't
take a second.
Um, so listen,
going back to
the emergency room,
that... that first visit,
that was for a broken
nose, is that right?
Shoot, I...
I just remembered.
Um, sir...
You know, I...
I got to be honest.
I'm starting to feel
a little harassed here.
Now, that's not...
Sir, your unguent!
Sir!
I think he means you.
You know,
you're asking
about a fella,
that I might've talked
to at the hospital,
when you should
be out there
looking for the animal
that killed my wife.
With all respect, sir,
your wife's not
the only victim here.
A friend of mine
was killed,
plus, you know,
Sam Hess.
Yeah, I told you,
I haven't seen Sam
since high school.
I'm not sure
this is your car,
Mr. Nygaard.
What? Oh, no, it's...
It's my wife's.
Mine's in the shop.
Well, sir, it's just...
it's hard to believe
is all, you know?
I mean, you're saying
this is all some...
some big coincidence,
you know,
you knowing Sam and all.
And it's a quiet town
and suddenly we got
four victims in 24 hours,
yourself included.
And then there's
this witness
saying that you were
talking about Sam Hess
the day he died
and, you know,
then it turns out
you and he
had differences
in the past, so...
You know,
all I'm saying is,
just...
help me understand
what happened.
Look,
I answered all your...
Just ask Bill, huh?
Your boss, he said
he was satisfied.
And I... I got...
Look at me.
My wife
is dead,
and you're harassing me.
I'm not harassing
you, sir. I...
Talk to Bill!
He'll tell you this...
this was a break-in.
You're wasting time
talking to me.
I'm...
I can't help you.
Watch your feet now.
So, how's it going?
Uh, well, it turns out
Lester and Hess went
to high school together
and Hess used
to beat him up.
A learned detective
might consider that a clue.
Yeah, that's what
I said.
But Bill's a big believer
in coincidence, apparently.
Well, what he lacks
in common sense
he makes up in self-esteem.
Yeah.
Bill have a theory?
Oh, yeah, he says
that it was a spree,
you know?
A drifter or, quote,
gang of drifters.
You know, like it's 1942.
Like, uh, drifters
are a national threat.
Hobos.
Well, he's chief now,
so he sets the agenda,
same as always.
Yeah, I know.
It's just...
I mean, you know,
here we get
this car crash
with this dead man
in frozen panties nearby,
and the driver
has a head injury
and maybe went to
the emergency room
where he talked to Lester
about Sam Hess,
and then within 24 hours,
Hess is dead
and then there's
the fracas with, you know,
Lester's wife and Vern.
Not sure
if you remember,
but when you were five,
they had to put
you under anesthesia
to fix your teeth.
Gave you that mask
and gas that smelled
like tutti-frutti.
Yeah.
My soft, little girl
in a hard world of
drills and needles.
I'm 31, Dad.
I carry a gun.
I know,
but it's relative,
you know?
There's the kind of things
a school teacher
gets exposed to,
truancy and the like,
and then there's
the stuff a cop sees,
murder and violence,
and general scofflawery,
and then there's
the kind of deal
you're looking at now.
Which is?
Which is
if I'm right...
savagery, pure and simple.
Slaughter, hatred,
devils with dead eyes
and shark smiles.
One day, you're gonna
get married and have kids...
and when you
look at them,
their faces,
you need to see
what's good in the world.
'Cause if you don't,
how you gonna live?
You talk a lot,
you know that?
It's always been
a problem.
Lou.
Chief.
Molly,
could I have a word?
Yeah, sure.
Pull up a chair.
You want some coffee or...
Yeah, no, uh...
Lester Nygaard
called me, yeah,
and he's super upset.
Well, yeah, you know,
I thought
he might do that.
Yeah, we talked
about this and all...
and I thought we were...
I thought I was clear
that we were gonna focus
on the drifter angle
and not, you know,
harass the victim.
Well, I'm not,
you know...
I didn't harass him.
I just... I got questions,
you know.
Yeah, well,
I'm the chief now,
and I got to...
Everyone's gotta
line up behind me,
you know, toe the line.
Sure, yeah,
yeah, I know...
Yeah, we talked about this,
and now I gotta
take you off the case.
Well, we all know
how you felt about Vern.
I mean, heck,
who didn't?
But, uh, maybe
it's best if you just...
And this could
be good for you,
career-wise, because, uh...
I'm gonna make
you head of inquiry
on that, uh, frozen fella,
the naked one, yeah.
I'll make you
lead on that.
Bill, listen, I...
Yeah, so
that's my decision.
Take care.
What...
Well, okay, then.
See you for dinner.
Yep.
Drills and needles.
To live in an old shack
by the sea
To live with the dawn
and the dusk
The new moon
and the full moon
The tides
the wind and the rain
To surf
and comb the beach
And gather sea shells
and driftwood
And know the thrill
of loneliness
And lose all sense of time
And be free
To hike over the island
to the village
And visit the market place
And enjoy the music
and the food
and the people
And do a little trading
And see the great ships
come and go
No, wait.
And man, have me a ball
And in the evening
when the sky is on fire
Heaven and earth
become my great
open cathedral
Where all men are brothers
Where all things
are bound by law
And crowned with love