Erstwhile on Fargo...
The blackmail,
I'm gonna pay it.
Blood and locusts...
The Book of Exodus.
God is watching
and He knows.
Knows what?
Pick me up in an hour.
We'll get the money.
He's gonna pay?
A million dollars?
Did you mean to
lock me in here?
We got a big day tomorrow.
Get some rest.
That's Sam Hess.
I mean,
you think this could be,
like, an organized
crime thing?
We're from Fargo.
You're gonna find him, right?
The guy who did it.
I need a name.
Malvo. Malvo.
Lorne Malvo?
He killed him.
He killed Hess.
So, anyway,
this freakin' guy...
The women are
in the box, yeah?
Customs seal on.
Eighteen cubic tons metric
at $110 an ounce...
And he decides--
Oi!
...stepped twice.
Soy sauce...
and another Mai Tai.
Mai Tai? Mai Tai?
...minus labor,
minus packaging,
minus extra-governmental
operating costs.
Anyhoo, he decides
he's in love
with one of 'em.
...yield so far,
9,000 unique
credit card numbers,
with a credit limit of
approximately $1.1 million,
minus real estate,
minus labor, minus R&D.
Sam Hess.
Assets deployed,
Mr. Wrench and Mr. Numbers.
Three days plus
lodging plus mileage.
You want the...
Bottom line,
they don't think...
Our guys, they said...
doesn't look related
to the business.
Could be extra-marital...
on the wife's side.
So... now, they're en route
to a second location
to apprehend who we...
think is responsible.
Dead.
What's that?
Not apprehend, dead.
Don't care extra-marital.
Don't care not related.
Kill and be killed.
Head in a bag.
There's the message.
Of course, boss. Yeah.
Nineteen-hundred
units shipped by rail
at a cost of $600 per
plus customs
plus extra
government expenses.
Good evening,
ladies. Good...
Welcome, ladies,
to Turkish Delight...
where your wish...
your wish is our command.
Time to make the call.
No, I mean... you know...
Maybe I don't
wanna now, you know.
'Cause... That's...
maybe... maybe
something got broken
there in the night,
you know... something...
something
important like trust.
You know, maybe...
we need to revisit
who gets how much here.
What's in the bags?
Look... okay, here's
what I'm thinking. I'm
thinking 60-40, all right?
You know,
with me getting, you know...
Because, you know,
am I or am I not
doing all the...
What about
the voice thingy there?
"Luke... I am your father--"
Ow!
Stop screwing around.
What...
"Luke."
I think you broke it.
So about that
60-40 split there,
you know, I'm...
Hey, why is there
paper on the windows?
Word for word.
You really want me
to say all this?
Yeah.
"Once upon a time,
there was a little boy.
He was born in a field
and raised in the woods...
and he had nothing.
In the winter,
the boy would freeze...
and in the summer,
he would boil.
He knew the name
of every stinging insect.
At night, he would
look at the lights
in the houses
and he would want.
Why was he outside
and they in?
Why was he so hungry
and they fed?
'It should be me, ' he said.
And out of the darkness,
the wolves came, whispering.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?"
Yeah.
"Gustafson Parking Garage,
high noon."
Well... did it sound like
he was gonna pay?
I don't know what
that sounds like.
So is the Greek the boy or...
Give me that duffel over
there and I'll tell you.
Hey...
what's with
all the duct tape?
Tellin' you, folks, things
are shaping up to make this
one of the worst blizzards
in Minnesota history.
A perfect storm
or what have you.
This is definitely
one for the record books.
That's right, Norm.
And expect white outs
and blizzard-like conditions
as this system moves
quickly down from Canada.
Also,
expect poor road conditions
and even closures.
So, folks,
please avoid driving today
unless you absolutely have to.
Gosh, I...
avoid going out...
Starting to come
down out there.
"Storm of the century,"
they're sayin'.
Is Greta here?
No, she's at a friend's.
Thought it would be safer.
Um...
You didn't have to come.
I was coming anyway.
Told you last night.
Just left
a little earlier is all.
So... you really think
this Malvo fella
was at your apartment?
Not at the apartment,
outside.
My neighbor,
he does the watch.
He said he saw this fella
sitting in his car
outside the apartment.
May even have
followed me here,
I'm thinking.
So the neighbor, Jewish fella,
he gives the guy a warning,
you know,
a kind of, "Move along."
Said the fella was
real menacing in return.
Had a police scanner, he said.
Talked about how
maybe he was gonna...
come back and kill
the neighbor and his family.
Oh, jeez.
Did you call it in?
Well, see... I don't think
they'd believe me
is the thing.
I mean, not after, you know,
I arrest the wrong fella,
being what they think.
So there's that.
He get a plate number,
your neighbor?
Yeah, yeah. He...
I called it in.
SUV of some type...
company car.
Which company?
The grocery chain, you know,
"July in January."
Phoenix Farms.
Right.
Which...
This Malvo fella
saying he's a pastor...
so not sure
the connection there.
Well, maybe
we should drive over,
see what they say.
Yeah. Let me get changed.
Morning, Mr. Creech.
And how're
we feeling there,
Mr. Nygaard?
Oh, yeah.
Real good.
Ready to go home.
Well, now,
that's up to him, I suppose.
So how's your pain level
on a scale of one to 10?
Yeah, not bad.
So maybe a three?
Hmm?
What... What's with...
Why's there
a police officer outside?
Not for me to say, is it?
Okay, Mr. Creech, I'll be
back to take you to
Radiology in 10 minutes.
I'm... I'm his brother Chaz.
Chaz Nygaard.
Lester... it's me.
Hey.
What did you do?
When?
Come on, Lester.
There's a deputy
outside the door,
for Pete's sake.
I just... cut my hand
on a... some rusty nail.
Not sure how that involves
local law enforcement.
They said you were there
when the Police Chief
got murdered.
Well, heck.
I think I'd remember that.
Unless... I don't know,
with the head injury,
maybe...
'Cause lying...
You're lying.
Says who?
That cop, the female,
says you are a suspect.
Suspect of what?
Murder...
for Pearl, the Chief...
even Sam Hess.
That is crazy
is what that is.
I'm the victim! Me!
He came to my house. They...
I almost died.
Did you tell her that?
Don't lie to me!
I took you in. My house...
This is...
Around my kid...
Oh, boy.
Oh, boy. Classic.
Cops can't
figure out who did it,
so they start
throwing blame around.
You said
you were kidnapped.
You called me in a meeting,
said you were
mixed up in something.
That was-- I told you
I was just pranking you.
No, you said you were
in the trunk of a car.
Said a couple of
fellas grabbed you.
What are you
mixed up in, Lester?
What the heck is goin' on?
Chaz, I swear to you,
this is all just a...
Heck, you're my brother.
You should be on my side.
People are dead, Lester.
Your own wife.
A... a conspiracy,
they're sayin'.
Like... like... like... maybe
you hired a fella to... to...
To...
what?
Come on.
Chaz, I swear to God...
I did not do this... anything.
Well, they think you did...
or know who did,
so... so... you gotta
give 'em something...
someone.
If you want this to go away,
you gotta give 'em someone.
Chaz... buddy, come on.
This is...
You have got to
stand by me here.
You've been a burden
my whole life.
I'm done.
There's something
wrong with you, Lester.
There's something missing.
You're not right
in the world.
Chaz.
Okay, here's
Mr. Creech's charts.
Are we ready, Mr. Creech?
Okay, Mr. Creech,
someone will be out
for you in a minute.
So he had a shotgun pellet
in his hand this whole time?
Lester? Yeah.
Which means he wasn't
knocked out in the basement
like he said he was.
So maybe...
maybe he and Malvo
weren't foes there
at the end.
Maybe... they colluded
on this whole thing.
Hmm.
Welcome to Phoenix Farms!
Hiya. We're
police officers.
You sure are.
This about the bugs?
Sorry?
The bugs. The...
What do you...
Locust?
Or wait. Maybe we're not
supposed to tell people.
Dave, are we telling people
about the bugs?
Is there a manager
or someone we can talk to?
Not sure anybody's in yet.
Dave, anybody in
the offices yet?
Let me check.
Mr. Cosmopolis to
Customer Service.
Okay, then...
I'm gonna leave my card.
Deputy Solverson.
We're here
about a company car,
who's driving it.
The license number
there on the back.
When a manager gets in,
just have him call.
Okay, sure. Thanks
for stopping by.
Thanks.
So what do
we do now then?
I could use
another cup of coffee.
Please take your ticket.
Oh, God.
Oh, God, my God.
What?
Kid's
getting restless.
How's he doing?
He's baffled...
just like me.
Did you make the drop?
No.
It's not too late
to get off the pot.
It's a lot of damn money.
It's not about the money.
It's bigger than the...
Thank you, God.
Than what?
I know what I gotta do now.
Give me an hour
and head back.
Tell the damn kid...
I love him.
Yeah, I'm...
I'm not gonna say that.
Pack your shit.
We're heading home.
Was that my dad?
Ticket, please.
I changed my mind.
I decided...
God, He told me.
He has different plans.
God told you not to park here?
No, no, no.
I know what I have to
do now. I didn't before.
Well, sir, I gotta...
It's $2 for
the first 30 minutes, so...
Son, do you go to church?
Yes, sir.
Then open the goddamn gate.
Your Lord demands it.
Two-faced.
What's that?
Oh...
When someone's a liar,
that's what you... you say.
"He's two-faced."
Like, he's got one face
for telling the truth
and another for...
I guess that's what...
bothers me the most,
you know.
Not the violence and
the murders and all?
Well... of course that...
but, I mean...
When a dog goes rabid,
right, there's no mistaking
it for a normal dog.
And here we are.
We're supposed to be...
you know, us people...
we're supposed
to know better...
to be better, you know?
It must be hard to
live in this world
if you believe that.
You have no idea.
620, be aware. Possible
313 in progress,
Bishop and Main.
Roger from
Dispatch. We're sitting
around Willow Creek...
8434, base.
I'm gonna go ahead
and cancel this thing.
Thought about it.
The 60-40 thing
doesn't work for me.
All right,
I'm gonna take it to north,
in case he shows up
down the block.
Dispatch
to 121 1 Mint.
121 1 Mint. Roger.
A 172. Tenth
and Market to code four.
Can I get a case number?
Hey. Hey!
In case Stavros
does call the cops...
we wanna make sure
they're too busy to respond.
That's part one.
Mmm-mmm.
Part two is...
have you ever had
Turkish Delight?
It's disgusting.
That's okay.
I'd be insulted
if you didn't try.
Roger that.
One citation, one...
A 172. Tenth
and Market to code four.
Can I get a case number?
No!
All units,
shots fired. Beacon near
Bundy. I repeat, shots fired.
Car 1-7 in the area.
Responding.
Ow!
Mr. Creech?
Hello?
Anyone there?
No TV until
you do your homework.
Just don't go there.
You know that.
Wash your hands first.
Did.
Yeah? When?
Between the car
and the house?
So this fella gives away
all his money and a kidney
and then he kills himself?
That's what he said,
my neighbor.
Why didn't the fella
just go work for a charity?
Got me.
Probably close the roads
soon, if you're
gonna head back.
Still gotta take
a look at Lester's car.
Maybe take another run
at Phoenix Farms,
I'm thinking.
Try to get an ID
on that company car.
Don't much like this fella
threatening people.
Never wanted to
be a cop, you know.
I mean...
some kids grow up
thinking about it,
but not me.
And your dream was what then?
You're gonna think
it's funny, but...
I always wanted to
work for the Post Office...
and be a mailman.
I like that you get to see
the same people every day...
bring 'em that check
they've been waiting for...
and presents for Christmas...
be part of the community.
But... when I applied,
they were on
a hiring freeze.
Then this pal from
high school tells me
the local PD is hiring,
so I took the bus downtown.
Never thought they'd,
you know... they'd take me.
So why try?
Well, you know...
Greta's mom passed
and she was the one
with the paycheck, so...
Oh, jeez.
I wonder what that's about.
All Tac units arrived after
me. Repeat, Tac team...
I don't want to
die in this way.
How bad?
Sir, multiple shots fired,
property damage.
No injury reports
at this time...
and perps are still
thought to be inside.
Multiple?
Unclear at this time.
To the individual
or individuals
inside the house.
This is Lieutenant Schmidt,
Duluth Police Department.
I'm ordering you to
throw out your weapon
and come out with
your hands up...
or we'll start blasting.
Move!
Roger that.
Tac team 2 is on the move.
On the move.
Divide and conquer on three.
Over.
No!
Shots fired!
Go, go, go!
They're shooting!
Shot's fired!
Shots fired!
Engage! Engage!
No!
Shots fired.
Repeat, shots fired.
Cease fire!
Cease fire, damn it!
I think we got him.
Based on what? ESP?
Breach!
Wait!
Gun!
Suspect is down.
Repeat, suspect is down.
Oddest suicide
by cop I ever...
They're shooting up
the block. It's goddamn
World War III.
Call 911.
No, wait!
This is Grimly.
Shots fired,
Fourth and Hunter.
Requesting backup.
What do you think?
Accident, I guess.
Words exchanged,
differences.
Heck of a lot of bullets
for a fender bender.
No, wait!
We should wait for...
Who?
God!
Damn it!
Fargo!
Here!
One down!
He's dead, I think!
Freeze! Police officer!
Halt!
Just
a horrible time to be
on the roads, guys.
And I don't
recall any time, Kim...
Unless you get
a serious blizzard
like '96 or even into '93.
...where we have had so many
interstates shut down...
Let there be light, huh?
What the heck was that?
What... Jeez.
God! Fish!
Jeez!
Buddy?
Dmitri?
I gave it back.
I gave it back!
Mr. Creech.
Oh, thank gosh.
There you are, Mr. Creech.
Thought we'd lost you.