Erstwhile on Fargo...
Mom home?
Yeah.
Let's eat.
I'm starving.
FBI.
I called a couple
times now about
the Fargo
Syndicate massacre...
Now I might know
the fella responsible...
Jesus!
This is where you work now.
I have a commendation.
I give you...
Insurance
Salesman of the Year,
Lester Nygaard!
So proud of ya, Lester.
Oh, Miss? Can we have
some more sparkling water?
And this is any animal.
Pig, gopher, chicken...
They go long enough
without sleep,
you start to see
abnormalities
behavior-wise.
First there's
the inability
to concentrate
and perform certain
fine motor skills.
Then you start to see...
And the army did studies
on this in the '50s.
The effects of
sleep deprivation
on the human brain.
I know 'cause
a buddy of my dad's
was a subject back during
the Korean conflict.
I mean, shit, Ray,
what's the longest
you've ever
gone without sleep?
Five days for me.
This was back
in dental school.
Marty Perlmutter
stole a prescription pad,
wrote us all
a scrip for amphetamines,
so we could cram for finals.
And boy howdy, I tell ya...
After three days
of no sleeping,
I was an animal.
All right, mi amigo.
That ought to do it.
I'm still a little worried
about the 203 and the 204.
So we should
make an appointment
to get together again
in about six months.
Appreciate it, Doc.
Really.
This black fella rolled over
my foot with a steam cleaner.
And I tell ya, this hurt worse
than that did by a long shot.
Yeah, nerve pain,
that's a bear.
Oh, you wanna
avoid nut brittles
for a few days,
and any kind
of fruit with pits.
Jemma's got a pamphlet.
All right.
Okay.
Yo, Mick Mike...
We still on for
golf next week?
Of course, we are,
Burty Burt.
But more importantly,
are you and Louise
still gonna make it on Sunday?
Uh, do dogs smell
each other's butts?
I think I might have
observed that type of
behavior on occasion.
Well, we'll be there.
Weezy's making her
famous five bean dip.
Aces.
Oh, thanks, babe.
Mick Mike.
I just keep
pinching myself.
Honey, you've earned it.
It's like my mom always said,
"Boys, if you like the milk,
buy the freakin' cow."
Aw, that's so sweet.
I am gonna
stick my whole thumb
up your ass later.
Aces.
Yello.
Hey, hey.
Darling,
is this guy bothering
you or what?
You!
We're gonna tie one
on tonight, friend-o.
I'm telling you.
No time like the present.
That's what I always say.
Bean dip?
You betcha.
Oh.
You look great.
You too.
Ice wine.
Buddy of mine says
they swear by this
stuff in Finland.
Well, they're all a bunch
of sex-crazed alcoholics.
So they should
know, right?
Sweet.
Hmm.
Weezy says you
popped the question.
Gonna make
Jemma an honest woman.
Oh, yeah, I cried like a baby.
I'm not afraid to admit it.
Well, she's
something else,
that Jemma.
Just between us girls
that body, is it...
I mean...
What's she like in the sack?
Hellcat.
That's the only word for it.
Shit.
Weezy's basically
a Jew in the bedroom.
Oh, you mean
she wears a wig
and makes you
do it through a hole
in the sheet? Yeah.
No. No.
She stopped
putting it in her mouth
as soon as the ring
went on her finger.
That's a national tragedy,
Burt.
Amen.
Gotta tell ya,
Mick Mike, I sure do like
having you around.
Likewise, Burty Burt.
The office was dead dull
until you showed up.
Positively geriatric.
I'm a rascal.
There's no two
ways about it.
Yessiree, Bob.
Like I told you before,
you and my brother
would get along
like gangbusters.
Well, I'd like to meet him.
Yeah.
Like I said, it's tricky.
He's in witness protection.
Say what?
I said, he's in
witness protection.
Turned state's
evidence against
these mob guys outta Chicago.
Told him not to.
Now, I haven't seen
him in over a year.
He still calls though.
Not supposed to.
You can't break
up the Canton boys.
I'll betcha.
Oh, screw it.
What are you
doing next weekend?
You tell me.
Oh, I like that,
"You tell me."
Well...
Weezy and me,
we're headed
for Vegas to
a little family reunion.
Why don't you and
Jemma tag along?
Aces.
You did this to me.
I had a wife, family.
I was happy.
And then you started...
Started what?
All we did was talk.
No, that's not...
No, you said things...
Jumbled me up.
You told me I needed...
Now, they're dead.
Why'd I listen to you? Why?
Tell my wife I love her.
Oh, honey, can we get
some more sparkling water?
Thank you.
I put my mask on.
Tawny hands me
the number two needle.
I start to give
the guy a novocaine shot.
Well, I stick
the needle in
my own finger.
And... Yeah.
And it hurt,
but I don't want
to look dumb,
so I try it again.
The next time,
I stick it in my thumb.
Now I'm so flustered
that I go to take my mask off,
while I'm still
holding the needle,
jab it right in my face.
And the patient is like...
"Doc, what's wrong?"
And I'm like...
I can't even move my arm.
I mean, it was insane.
You're a riot.
He's a riot.
You have no idea.
So,
we are all set for tomorrow,
to go see
you-know-who.
Should be fun.
Real clandestine stuff,
change cars twice, no phones.
Geez, who did you say
is after this guy again?
Well,
what are the odds?
Sorry?
It's me, Lester.
I'm sorry, sir.
You must have me
confused with someone else.
No. Minnesota,
last year?
The emergency room?
I didn't recognize
you at first either,
'cause you got a whole new...
But hey, so have I.
What do you think
of the suit?
Bill Blass.
Check this out.
Salesman of the Year.
They gave it to me
on a stage and everything.
Uh, Mick Mike.
You gonna introduce us
to your friend there?
You know,
I'd love to, Burt.
But unfortunately,
I've never met this
man before in my life.
What?
Right, we don't know
each other.
Okay, honey, let's go.
We're never
gonna make the show
if we don't get out of here.
Walk away.
Sorry, I must have...
Congratulations
on your award.
Thank you.
Burt, did I ever
tell you about the time
I made a night guard
for Britney Spears?
I swear.
Come on.
He was a piece of work, huh?
Who's that?
That guy in the bar.
You sure you don't know him?
People nab me all the time.
Just one of
those faces, I guess.
No.
You don't get to...
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but it's not right.
And when
something's
not right,
well, the old Lester,
now, he would have
just let it slide.
But not this guy.
I've worked too hard.
I've come too far...
Lester, stop.
So now you do know me.
Honey?
Is this what you want?
Ah.
Hey, Mick Mike,
lighten up, huh?
Lester, is this
what you want?
Yes or no?
Yes.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my...
That's on you.
I worked this guy
for six months, Lester,
six months.
Can you imagine the number
of sewer mouths
I put my hands in?
The gallons of human spit?
Plus, the $100,000 bounty
down the toilet, but...
Still, the look on his face
when I pulled the gun.
Classic, huh?
Grab the fat guy's feet.
We'll throw him in a dumpster.
Shit, Lester.
See you later, Lester.
See you soon.
Shit.
All right.
Okay. Get dressed.
We gotta...
Lester, are you okay?
Get dressed!
Come on.
Okay. Go, go.
All right. Let's go.
Keep up, hon.
Keep up.
Lester, you're
hurting my hand.
Sorry. Sorry.
Okay, okay. Come on.
A man has a fox,
a rabbit and a cabbage.
What man?
Any man. A man.
Colonel Sanders?
Could be, could be
George W. Bush.
Why would George W. Bush
have a fox and
a rabbit and a cabbage?
Just listen. A man
has a fox, a rabbit
and a cabbage
and he wants to
get across the river,
but his boat
can only carry one
of them at a time.
Get a bigger boat.
No, no. That's
not an option.
And here's the problem...
If the man leaves
the fox and the rabbit
alone,
the fox is gonna
eat the rabbit.
And the same
for the rabbit
and the cabbage.
So how does the man
get all three of his
items across the river
without losing
any of them?
A turducken.
A... What's that now?
He stuffs
the cabbage in the rabbit
and the rabbit in the fox,
and he eats all of them.
That's not the answer.
It's an answer.
Hello?
Incoming or outgoing?
I need you to pull
the Syndicate file.
Why?
Is it like
a clown car
back there?
Why do you need
the Syndicate file?
Yeah. Did something
happen with the case?
A break?
No. Just a phone
call I've gotta log.
Phone call from who?
Yeah, who called?
That's really
not your business.
Hey.
Deputy Solverson.
Solverson. What does he say?
Says he knows who did it.
Okay.
Where's Bemidji?
Thanks, Dad.
I think I'd look
cool with a limp.
Saw the profile of
Bill in the paper.
Yup.
For the record,
I advised against
wearing a sword
in that picture.
Honey, pass the syrup.
Yeah.
Anyway, I'm in charge
today on account of...
Bill's on his way
to St. Paul now for a...
What do you call it?
Law enforcement conference.
So, watch your butts.
How's the route?
Can't complain.
Takes me out by the lake.
It's a nice drive.
Dated the girl
who delivered
my mail once...
After her mother.
Convenient at first.
Awkward after,
once we broke up.
Seeing her every day.
Ended up moving to
a different neighborhood.
So that's why we moved.
You know you could
have just had
your mail sent to work.
I never thought of that.
So when's your last day?
About a month.
She's nesting.
Uh, geez. You know,
you buy one
throw pillow...
We better...
Bye.
Bye, kids.
Hey, and go fishing later?
You're the granddaughter
I always wanted,
but was afraid to buy online.
Bye.
You did good, hon.
Yeah, and you
by proximity, huh?
Solverson.
Bill? Yeah. No.
He's in the
Twin Cities for...
Oh, geez.
Three people, uh.
Killed how?
In an elevator, huh?
You say one's a dentist?
Yeah, I'm...
What do Las Vegas
police want me to...
Oh, sure. Yeah.
Yeah. No,
I can go see their witness,
get a statement.
What's... What's
the witness' name then?
Will you slow down?
You'd think we were
being chased.
Sorry.
Was it me?
Did I do something?
What?
No, I told you.
I made a lot
of new contacts
at the awards.
Big fish.
You have to strike
while the iron's hot.
I know, but you woke me up
in the middle of the night.
Oh, I'll make it up to you.
How's that?
We can take a trip.
Anywhere you wanna go.
Natalie says in
Acapulco you get
to drink rum right
out of the coconut.
Acapulco it is.
In fact, uh, why don't...
We should leave tonight.
Really?
Sure. Yeah.
I mean, why not?
A little fun in the sun,
drink from a coconut.
We deserve it, huh?
What about work?
Your big fish?
Well, you only
live once, right?
Let's just...
We'll go home,
pack some stuff
then head back
to the airport.
Have our toes in
the sand by dawn,
a real adventure.
Oh, Lester.
Okay.
Now, here is
what you're gonna do.
You're gonna go inside
and pack your best bikini.
I'm gonna get changed
and head to the office.
And I'm gonna buy the tickets,
get the passports...
And then we are
gonna run away together.
Heck, we might
never come back.
Thanks, hon.
There we go.
Trust the circles,
whenever you go around,
just keep going, even though
you think you'll fail.
So I checked and there's
an 11:00 out of Minneapolis.
So we should be on
the road by 6:00.
Okay. I'll defrost
that pea soup.
We can have
that before we go.
Oh, yeah, sounds good.
Love you, hon.
Love you, too.
Oh.
Scared me there.
Startled me.
Mr. Nygaard,
Deputy Solverson.
Maybe you remember?
Yeah, sure.
I'm sorry to bother you,
but we got a call
from Las Vegas PD.
What?
Las Vegas police?
And they said you were, um...
That you might be
a witness to a murder.
Uh, three murders, actually.
Lester?
It's fine.
Go back to your show.
Is everything okay?
Yes, ma'am,
just a routine inquiry.
Is now a good time
to ask you a few questions?
No.
Oh.
I've got an appointment.
I gotta get to work
and Linda's got shopping.
Now, Lester. Don't be rude.
We just got back
from Las Vegas.
Can you tell me
what this is about,
or is that classified?
Oh, well, yeah, actually...
I could come to the station
this afternoon and
give a statement?
Not that I,
you know,
saw anything.
Honestly, Lester, stay or go,
but I got a bladder
the size of a penny.
Oh, you poor thing.
Please, come in.
Thank you.
Hey, guys.
Is your dad around?
Yeah. Daddy!
Dad!
Help ya?
I'm not sure.
I'm looking for
Lester Nygaard.
Oh, yeah. We bought the place
from him in the fall.
Nice guy.
Yeah, that's Lester,
all right, nicest guy
you'll ever meet.
You got any idea
how I can find him?
Uh, I don't have
a forwarding address.
He's got the shop
over on Third, though.
Is that Bo Munk?
No. Got his own
place now,
with his name on it.
Oh, nice.
Like I said, over on Third.
You can't miss it.
Okay. Thanks.
Oh, uh...
One more thing.
You do know
people were murdered
in this house, right?
Hell of a thing.
Man in
the living room, shotgun,
woman in the basement.
I think it was
a hammering.
Afterwards Lester told me
he used to hear noises coming
from the basement at night.
Footsteps on the stairs,
a woman moaning.
That kind of thing.
But I'm sure it
was in his head.
You have a nice day.
Have fun, kids.
I don't like him.
So you won an award.
Uh, that's right.
Salesman of the Year.
Oh, hun...
Yeah, I...
It was
a national competition, so...
Uh, then it was
dinner with Buck Young,
who's the head
of the whole deal
that gives the award.
That was some spread.
I think we closed that
place down drinking.
Uh, and I said,
"I'm still up for some fun."
And Linda said she
wanted to go to bed.
I'm a morning person.
Yeah, but then
I thought, "Heck...
How often does something
like this happen.
Winning an award?"
So, yeah, a nightcap,
just to celebrate.
I told him to go.
Yeah.
So, sure.
So I went to the bar.
And this is the bar
at the hotel?
Yes, sir.
Yes, ma'am.
Excuse me.
Uh. The Royale,
I guess it's called.
I ordered a drink,
I had a chat with
the bartender for a bit.
Uh, male or female?
Female. A woman.
Uh, but, you know,
one drink and I'm back
upstairs to bed.
And what happened
on the elevator?
Nothing.
I mean, it went up.
So everyone on the elevator
was alive when you got off.
Oh, yeah, they sure were.
Uh, they were laughing
about something.
Friday night in Vegas.
That is some place,
I tell ya.
Linda and me,
we'd never been before.
What I love most
are the fountains.
Also, you can
gamble at the airport.
Right.
Well, I checked
and it looks like you
changed your flight
at the last minute
to come back on
the first flight.
So, what was
the reason there?
That was me...
My idea.
I just...
I got homesick.
Woke Lester up in
the middle of the night
and told him did
we have to
stay another day,
'cause I was ready
to go home.
Yeah.
That's right.
That is right.
Uh, remember? I said, "Babe,
the room is paid for
through till Sunday."
But she was adamant.
I tend to get my way.
Oh, boy, does she?
Okay then. Well, uh,
thank you for your time,
Mr. Nygaard. Missus.
When's the due date?
Oh, I've got
a few weeks still.
Uh, listen. Vegas PD
is gonna send over
some pictures from
the hotel security camera.
So don't leave
town for a while.
I may have some
more questions for you.
Oh, shoot.
We were gonna...
No, absolutely,
absolutely.
We'll be right here
if you need us.
Car four, come back.
I'm coming.
Yeah, this is four.
Hey, Molly,
a couple of FBI fellows
came by the station
looking for you.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Couldn't reach
you on the radio.
Thought you'd
be at your dad's,
so I sent them there.
To the diner?
Yeah.
So you should
probably check in
on them.
They seem real
eager to talk to you.
Okay then, will do.
Coffee?
Yeah. Decaf,
if you got it.
And a piece of pie.
I got apple and cherry.
No good ever came
from a piece of cherry pie.
Thanks, friend.
Local PD?
State cop, 18 years.
You got the look.
I spent some time
with the Tampa DA.
Lawyer?
Yeah, something like that.
Say, you may be
able to help me.
I will if I can.
Uh, I'm in town for
not too much time,
just passing through, really.
But I wanted to look up
my old pal, Lester Nygaard.
Oh, sure,
I know Lester.
Did you go by his shop?
Oh, first thing.
But wouldn't you know it?
They're closed.
Went by the house, too,
except it turns
out he's moved.
No kidding.
Hmm.
So you can see
my predicament.
You tried calling him?
Yeah, I could do that,
but I was hoping
to surprise him.
That's a pickle.
Yup.
That your boy?
In a way.
My daughter's
husband.
They look happy.
'Course, no one hangs
the sad pictures,
am I right?
Mom crying and
dad looking angry.
The kid with the black eye.
How long did you
say you worked
for the Tampa DA?
Oh, I didn't say
I worked there.
Spent some time, that's all.
But that's just me.
I'm a traveler.
Big cities,
the small towns...
Open road.
Which is why I thought,
"Here we are in a..."
What do you call it,
"A tight-knit community."
So, uh...
Thought I'll just ask.
So here I am,
asking you if you know
where I can find old Lester.
Had a case once.
Back in '79.
I'd tell you the details,
but it'd sound
like I made 'em up...
Madness really.
Bodies?
Yes, sir...
One after another.
Probably,
if you stacked 'em high
you could have climbed
to the second floor.
Yeah, I saw
something that year...
I ain't never seen
before or since.
I'd call it animal.
Except animals
only kill for food.
This was...
Sioux Falls.
You ever been?
Went to Sioux City once.
Back in my scandalous days.
But anyway,
you didn't answer
my question there.
Well, I tell ya what?
You leave me your number,
I'll make sure Lester gets it
next time he comes in.
That's a solid offer, friend.
But like I said,
I'm just passing through.
Thanks for
the pie and the coffee.
I haven't had
a piece of pie like that
since the Garden of Eden.
Hey, Dad.
Hey, hon.
Everything okay?
Oh, yeah.
Sometimes you
just get a weird one.
Well, I'm supposed
to meet a couple of
fellows from the...
Never mind.
I see 'em.
Hey there, I'm...
Deputy Solverson?
That's right.
I'm Agent Budge and
this is Agent Pepper,
FBI from Fargo.
We went by the station.
They told us you'd be here.
Am now.
Should we grab a table?
Yeah.
You made a phone
call to the field office
yesterday about
the massacre last year.
Said you know who shot up
the Syndicate building?
Called seven times,
according to the file.
Wouldn't take
no for an answer.
I'm not clear on...
The FBI sent
a fella already.
He looked at my evidence
and said it was
circumstantial.
A worker bee...
Or what do
the ants call them?
A drone.
We're invested.
Got a personal stake,
is what my partner...
See, we were there
on the day at the Syndicate.
Surveillance.
Day 156, just logging
the comings and goings.
Six months and
nothing happens.
Going crazy with...
And then...
So, you see,
we're invested
personally, like I said.
And when
we heard you called...
That you have
an answer.
So please,
we have to know.
Who is he?
Um, Dad, I think
we're gonna need
some coffees to go.
My God.
You put all this
together yourself?
Oh, no.
Gus helped me...
My husband.
He used to be Duluth PD.
He's a mailman now.
But you can see
why I think this is your guy.
Okay, I'm here.
Hey, Chief.
These fellas...
Bill Oswalt.
I'm the chief here.
Sorry I wasn't around to...
I was at a conference.
And then Cindy called
and said there were
two agents from the FBI here.
Oh, no.
Now, Chief,
listen, before...
No, no, no.
I am so sorry.
Molly, these guys
aren't interested in...
Let's meet in
my office.
Have you seen this?
Have I seen this?
Son, this thing's been
giving me nightmares.
Come on, now.
That's not fair.
She did tell you
that we caught the guy
responsible for
killing the wife?
Didn't she?
Uh, the brother Nygaard
and he had
the bloody hammer...
So you don't care
about the fact
that this Malvo character
was seen with Lester
at the hospital?
Or that he ended up in Duluth
in direct conflict
with these other two?
No, because that, uh...
What happened in Duluth...
I'm gonna call HQ
and let them know
we'll be staying the night.
We can take another run
at Lester tomorrow.
Is there a motel?
Um, yeah, sure. I can...
I'll get you directions.
This is tremendous work,
Deputy. Impressive.
Yeah, I better just...
Come on.
Okay.
All set. Ready to go?
What? I thought
we weren't gonna go.
Acapulco,
here we come.
Oh, my God.
You betcha.
I talked to the deputy.
She said, "Sure, go."
So now, we just gotta swing
by the office and
pick up the passports.
What about my coat?
Oh, you're not gonna
need a winter coat
where we're going.
You know I had
a crush on you
right from when we met.
Hmm.
Oh, yeah?
Swear to God.
Used to sit at my desk
and dream about
you leaving your wife
or somehow getting
her out of the picture.
Not that I wanted...
No, of course not.
Nothing wrong
with dreaming.
Oh, I agree...
Like Cinderella.
Yeah?
I remember when
I was three.
And I told you
how we came
over to America,
settled in Minnesota,
my folks bought the motel?
Yeah?
Well, they put me
right to work.
Just...
Laundry at first...
Then making the beds
and cleaning the rooms.
You don't even
wanna know the disarray
people leave behind.
I bet.
One time...
I'll never forget this.
I was changing the sheets
on a king size, and I'm...
Suddenly, I'm like,
"What's that smell?"
Well, the guest had...
He made a BM between
the mattress and
the box spring.
What?
I guess he took
the mattress off
and did it,
and then made
the bed back up,
which...
It's a lot simpler
just to go to the toilet.
My point being...
That while I was cleaning up
I had this dream that someone,
a man... Would come
along and take me
away from all this.
And then I met you.
And here we are.
And we're going
to Acapulco.
I thought we were
going to the shop?
We are.
You know how icy it
gets right out front.
Lester?
You know I hate
to do this, but...
I kind of
tweaked my back before,
getting the luggage
out of the car.
Oh, you poor baby.
So do you think
you could run in?
The passports are
in the safe. There's
some cash in there too.
Can you...
Will you do that for me?
Of course, hon.
Thanks.
Linda?
Hmm.
It's cold out there.
You're sweet.
Oh, uh.
Put your hood up, huh?
I'd hate for your
pretty face to freeze.