- Good morning, Mr. Draper.
- Morning.
It's Beverly, isn't it?
He's on 19.
Thank you.
Good morning.
You don't have to do this
every day.
I won't have you lost again.
I wasn't lost, I was late.
I was fibbing.
Well, you can't do that.
It throws off a very busy schedule.
And not to mention everything,
et cetera.
Can you call housekeeping and ask them
not to make up my bed while I'm still in it?
Well, you won't have to
endure the hardships
of the Plaza much longer.
The floors of your apartment
will be done Monday.
If you pick paint,
you could move in next week.
That's great.
Honey, you can just have this
waiting on my desk.
Does it smell any better
in here?
If you like Air Wick and fruit.
When I was packing,
well, I think these were best
kept from the movers.
Have you thought about new furniture?
I think it looks great in here.
No, for your apartment.
You only have a bed.
I made dinner reservations
in Farmington tomorrow.
You're taking Sally
back to school.
Thank you.
Jim Hobart's back from vacation.
No napping.
You and the computer are
gonna share an office over there?
No, the old girl
served her purpose.
McCann is mission control.
Statisticians, programmers,
5 men and 10 women
just handling data.
Maybe they can keep track of your hat size.
Seems to be growing.
Why are you still here?
Somebody's got to hand over
the keys.
Well, I'm on 24 and you're on 26,
but I'll be up there
all the time.
There's an
executive dining room.
You know, I once rode on a bus to camp
sitting next to a guy like you.
We're not gonna be bunkmates, Crane.
I'll make them build
another floor if I have to.
I'm not going to let you spoil
the moment. My moment.
See you in the funny papers.
I don't know what's keeping
the building representatives,
but I feel perfectly comfortable...
Forging my signature?
No, that's okay. You can go.
Well, this is my last day
and I wanted to thank you.
Bullshit. They can't fire you.
Actually, I took another job.
Travelers Insurance.
My cousin works there.
Look, I hate Caroline, too.
No, it's...
- Did I do something?
- No.
It's just I kept thinking
about walking into a new office.
Yeah. I'm doing it, too.
And now there's gonna be
one less person I know.
Mr. Sterling, it's not you.
Advertising is not a very
comfortable place for everyone.
That in mind,
I have to say thank you.
You're very amusing.
Fat lot of good it did me.
Hello, neighbor.
We're the welcome wagon.
We heard you had a window.
Aren't you sweet to come by?
This is Beverly.
- And who are you?
- I'm Libby Blum.
Karen Schmidt.
Can we have a minute?
We're copywriters.
I recognized the names.
I was just going over Tampax.
We also did the pill
for Ortho...
If it's in it, near it or makes
you think about it, we're on it.
So, Topaz Pantyhose and Butler
Shoes set off an alarm.
But we really love Avon.
This is incredible.
So you just came in here
to get on my business.
And to say hello.
Well, I'm flattered by both.
If you want us,
just ask Frank in the studio.
He'll ask Bobby in traffic,
and he'll tell Carl,
the associate creative director.
You can put a request in however you want.
We'll let the Soviets
deal with it.
You're aware that Peggy Olson
handles all of those accounts?
See, I told you.
Well, we'd love to share
the crumbs with her.
Thank you so much for the plant.
We're going to
the Oyster Bar tonight.
We have an informal
ladies' club.
It's not women's lib,
just a bitch session.
We are strictly
consciousness lowering.
When I get settled in.
Incredible.
Did you come to get your furniture?
There was a mix-up.
My office isn't ready.
Why are you still here?
Well, I'm not going to McCann.
And so far I'm not going anywhere.
And I'm being paid
through the end of the week,
so I thought I'd make
some long-distance phone calls.
We lost Dow.
We still owe them work.
Could you get Mr. Kreutzer
at Sugarberry Ham for me?
Why would I do that?
Because Marsha's
sorting things out over there
and I'm not calling myself.
I'm giving you
a standing ovation.
How was the Bahamas?
It's everything
we say it is in print.
I hope you're finding
everything satisfactory.
Ferg's been
an excellent tour guide.
He's just following you around
because he's our resident impressionist.
Do an imitation of Don yet?
"I'm, um, working very diligently
"on the, um, matter at hand."
Well, you better not make a joke
of this man.
We've lined up coffee
and baloney with Nabisco,
National Cash Register,
and your old friend
Conrad Hilton.
He bought you a gift.
That's never good.
And we just bought an entire agency
in Milwaukee to get Miller Beer.
For me?
When I want something, I get it.
And I've been trying to get you
for 10 years.
You're my white whale, Don.
Well, maybe you should send me
to the Bahamas.
In due time.
The important thing is
we're expecting you
to bring things up a notch
around here.
Jim, I don't know what to tell ya.
I'll do my best.
And, Don, this is a shirtsleeves
operation. We want you relaxed.
And should you ever
need anything in this city,
dinner reservations,
parking tickets...
Just drop our name into yours.
I will.
Miller Beer is coming in tomorrow
for handshakes
on their new idea.
Diet beer.
For ladies?
For men
watching their waistlines.
Why don't we call it "Tub"?
Have you said it yet?
What?
Have you introduced yourself?
I'm Don Draper
from McCann Erickson.
I appreciate the call.
Mostly because it's hard
for me to walk around here
acting like nothing's changed.
Only some things have changed.
Avon will be serviced
by the exact same personnel.
Creative handled by
Ted Chaough and Peggy Olson.
Forget about personnel.
Every dollar you spend
will now get you five times
the audience.
And once we get you on TV...
Well, we already are on TV.
We know that.
What Dennis is saying is...
You know, I'm in Atlanta all the time.
How about a trip to Augusta,
play a few holes?
You any good?
No.
No, I'm not.
Listen, my girl is telling me that
it's time for our staff meeting.
- Thanks again for the call.
- Of course.
Such a pleasure, Barry.
Bye.
Who's next?
I don't know what to say
except Barry is in a wheelchair.
What?
I told you that...
and I wrote it down.
I thought
that was Charlie Butler...
from the shoes.
No, it's not.
And it's Charles Butler
and it's footwear.
I can't believe you.
It's an honest mistake.
You heard him say he was
"walking around the office."
It's an expression.
Which he shouldn't be
able to use.
I stayed up all night
preparing those briefs.
Mr. Donnelly said you'd be on
the call to help with the transition,
but you seem like you don't even care
about keeping these accounts.
I'm sorry. Who told you
you got to get pissed off?
All I ask is that
you please read the brief
before our next call.
You know what?
Do it yourself.
I thought you were gonna be fun.
I'm sorry to drop by.
Marsha. That's so sweet of you.
You didn't have to come up here.
It's not your fault.
Those are actually from McCann.
An apology. That's classy.
How do I explain this?
All the SC&P girls got flowers.
It's still classy.
Well, all the new secretaries.
They thought I was a secretary?
Did you tell Don what happened?
- Do you want me to?
- No.
- Maybe I should call Joan.
- That's not her job there.
- I know that, Marsha.
- I am taking care of it.
As well as your mail and memos
regarding Peter Pan
Peanut Butter and Tampax.
What happened to all my things?
They're putting your boxes in storage.
You will have an office any minute.
In the meantime,
you can work in the pool.
I am a copy supervisor.
I am not setting foot in there
until I have an office.
If they want me,
they can reach me here.
At home?
No. No. I'll be at SC&P.
Hell, that's where my furniture is.
I will let them know.
Could you hold that?
Good morning.
How are you, stranger?
Homesick.
- Well, takes some time to settle in.
- I know.
You should come by for a drink.
When am I going to do that?
Put me on your calendar.
We don't share any accounts.
You're too important.
Not for you.
Believe me,
I'd involve you if I could.
It's been a little bumpy.
I can still interfere.
No, I'll figure it out.
Of that I am certain.
- Let's make a date for lunch.
- Soon.
Tell me if you like the
general idea so I can take a few risks.
Where'd you learn to do this?
I'm an army brat, remember?
New base every year.
I want to live here.
You're my decorator.
I'll pay you in cash.
Nonsense. I love it.
Lunch in the executive boardroom
with Miller Beer.
They asked if roast beef
was okay.
Perfect.
Joan, nice to see you up here.
Are you coming to the Sears briefing?
That's a good idea.
No, I was actually
looking for Mr. Donnelly,
but if now is a bad time...
Ferg.
Pete, it's your meeting.
You can start without me.
I'm gonna put in a request
to get you involved with this.
Thank you.
That's thoughtful.
So, what can I do for you?
It's just...
Regarding the Avon transition,
I thought maybe
Pete could be an asset.
Pete's a vice president.
What's wrong with Dennis?
I like Dennis personally.
I'm not sure
the client responded to him.
Say no more.
I'll take care of it.
Hello?
Are those my boxes?
I gotta go.
I gotta go!
Yeah, I signed for them,
but I was wondering
what happened.
You've got to be kidding me.
You know
we're the only ones here.
Have you been on the phone all morning?
Stan called.
He doesn't have a phone yet.
He's on the 14th floor.
Come by and say hi.
And
I prepared this
for your approval.
What is this?
Do you think "quagmire"
should be plural?
We can't do this.
They're never going to
look at it.
Ed, you could easily end up
working for Dow again
or Ken Cosgrove.
You could even end up working for me.
That's not very subtle.
I asked you to do one damn thing
and you didn't even do it.
Fine. I quit.
Well, thanks for everything.
When you get settled in over there,
which will happen,
give me a call.
I promise.
I'm sorry. It's Bob, right?
Yes. Don, good to see you.
We've got the best box lunch around.
It should have your name on it.
Is this the Miller Beer meeting?
It certainly is.
Bill Phillips, Conley Research.
Don Draper and Ted Chaough.
- A pleasure.
- Shall we?
Is this every creative director
in the agency?
It's only half of us.
So, are you here
to "bring us up a notch," too?
So they tell me.
Good morning, gentlemen.
As you know, this is Bill Phillips,
senior director at Conley Research.
Bill, why don't you tell us a little bit
about this exciting new beverage.
Despite that pile of facts
and figures in front of you,
I don't look at this
as a presentation of research.
To me, this is an opportunity
to stimulate
some of our industry's
finest imaginations.
I'm going to describe a man to
you of very specific qualities.
He lives in Wisconsin,
Michigan, Ohio.
Some call it "the Heartland."
Some call it "the beer belt."
He has some college.
Makes a good living,
but it doesn't feel like it
because he works long hours.
He has a lawn mower.
Wants a hammock.
Bunch of power tools in
the garage that he never uses.
He loves sports
because he used to play them.
And he loves dogs
because they don't talk.
We all know this man
because there are
millions of him
and he drinks beer.
Not just any beer.
No, it has to be his brand.
And what is his brand?
The one he drank in college?
The one his dad drank?
The one that comes
in the best bottle, can, tap?
It doesn't matter
because that's it,
and it's not open
for discussion.
Now, you all know
that that's not true...
but how do you get him
to open his mind?
Better have something more,
or in this case...
less.
And that's tricky.
When we talk about
a low-calorie beer...
we immediately become feminine.
It's the word "calorie."
It makes you think
of a reducing plan.
A note on the fridge
to remind her about her diet.
Your girl still at lunch?
Beverly always takes
the whole hour. I insist.
I have a little news for you.
I hope
I didn't cause any trouble.
Too early for you?
No, of course not.
So, I spoke with Dennis.
I hope I didn't
ruffle any feathers.
Well, here's how it looks.
Like some junior account man
came in
and started swinging her elbows.
He didn't read the brief...
and I'm not Dennis' junior.
Joan, see it from his side.
He has a wife and three children.
He's not going to work for a girl.
What's he gonna say to a client?
"She's my boss"?
It happens all the time now.
Peggy Olson was our copy chief.
It's different with a bunch of
writers fresh out of Columbia.
And honestly, I doubt that's
gonna continue here anyway.
I see.
Joan, I didn't come down here
to upset you.
I agree that the best way
to keep the business
is to keep your status
on your accounts.
And you'll certainly get
the respect you desire
now it's just you and me.
You don't have to do that,
but I accept.
Good.
Now, first thing we have to do
is pay this guy a visit.
- Who?
- Barry from Avon.
We owe him an apology.
And let's face it, it would
be good to get out of town,
even if it's to Atlanta.
I appreciate that,
but I don't want to put you out.
Look, I know a good job
when I see one.
No, it's just that
might be too much.
He'll be in New York soon
and Avon corporate
is blocks away.
Hey, I'm easy.
I'm not expecting anything more
than a good time.
Excuse me?
I mean, I want to get
to know you, of course.
Of course.
Good.
My first act of benevolence,
you can call Charles Butler on your own.
We'll take him to lunch
next week.
Thank you.
From now on, no one comes
between me and your business.
I appreciate that.
We can't lose those accounts.
What would you do around here?
Loretta!
Here she is.
Sally left?
Yes. She got a ride
with her friend.
And no one thought to call me, I guess.
- Do you want something to drink?
- No.
They left after lunch.
I told her to call your office.
Your secretary is a moron.
I was out of the office.
I wanted to get the car washed.
She comes and goes
as she pleases.
And we can't get mad at her
for being independent.
It's normal.
Is that what Freud says?
So far I haven't come across
anyone normal.
You okay?
I carried $100 worth
of textbooks yesterday
during registration.
Maybe you're getting old.
I'm younger than you.
Always have been,
always will be.
Maybe you could find some nice
freshman to carry your books.
That's fine.
When do the boys get home?
Gene's at Cub Scouts
and Bobby's got baseball.
They won't be back until 6:30.
I'll let you get back
to your studies.
I've always wanted to do this.
Knock 'em dead, Birdie.
Bye.
Shit.
Your stomach is grumbling.
You never let me eat.
I can make fried chicken.
I don't mind playing the house,
but as long as your mother
and Kevin are away,
why don't you call in sick?
Let me take you to Bermuda.
No.
Cape Cod?
I don't wanna go anywhere
I don't want to go.
Don't make plans for me.
All right. All right.
I have a lot of work.
Look, I know I told you
not to complain,
but that doesn't mean
I don't want to hear about it.
But you really don't.
What happened?
It's a big place, and I asked
the wrong person for help.
And I don't think
I can get out of it.
Well, if you don't like that job,
you don't have to do it.
You got enough, and you got me.
They still owe me
over half a million dollars.
I'm not walking away from that.
So, this is a business problem.
Now, I can help.
You're already helping.
There's two ways
I deal with disagreeable people.
One, you can call a lawyer,
throw a bunch of paper at them,
tie them up in court,
cost them some money.
Nobody wins,
but it loosens the earth.
What's the second?
You can call a guy.
"A guy"?
I'm a developer.
Men get stubborn.
What does "a guy" do?
You get the right guy,
all they have to do is show up.
You've really done that?
You seem to like it,
so I'm gonna say yes.
You're disturbed.
Doesn't seem like
such a big problem now, does it?
I don't want to say goodbye for the summer
Beautiful night out there tonight.
In downtown Cleveland,
we have a high of 75, low of 62.
Not too sticky,
and it should stay
that way through the weekend.
I don't know about you,
but I am not ready
to say goodbye to the summer.
But not true of the folks
at Higbee's Department Store
where they're ready to provide
all the back-to-school fashions.
I'm really tired, aren't I?
You've been driving for seven
hours in the wrong direction.
Where are you going?
Racine, Wisconsin.
Ever been there?
No. What's in Racine?
Maybe some waitress
who doesn't care about you?
You shouldn't do that.
That's not gonna stop me.
You like to play the stranger.
Remember On the Road?
I've never read that book,
you know that.
I'm riding the rails.
"Whither goest thou, America,
"in thy shiny car in the night?"
Yes, it's gonna be a cold, lonely summer
But I'll feel the emptiness
- Hello?
- Peggy?
Yes. Who is this?
It's Marsha.
I thought I would try this
before I ran over.
Your phone's dead.
What do you want?
Well, on behalf of McCann Erickson,
I want to welcome you
to your new office.
When can you come over?
- Well, I guess right now.
- Wonderful.
Can you work at a drafting table
till they bring your things over
tomorrow?
Yes. Thank you.
Hello?
Is someone there?
- Roger.
- Oh, Christ!
I have a heart condition, you know.
Believe it or not, I'm not scary.
Organ music is scary.
What are you doing here?
I told Caroline I wanted
to pack my personal things,
which I will eventually do
as soon as I figure out why she
thought my bar wasn't personal.
Did you try Don's office?
All I found was lighter fluid.
I'm not there yet.
Mine's gone.
I don't want to go to a bar.
I did that yesterday.
Listen, sweetheart, if you don't mind...
I'm not running an errand.
I have to go to McCann.
Three days ago.
They screwed up my office, it...
It doesn't matter.
They're finally ready.
I'd do it for you.
Would you drink vermouth?
Yes, I'm afraid I would.
I'll be along in a minute.
Mr. Hobart. Can I help you?
You're sitting in his chair.
You're obviously not expecting him.
I told Daphne I don't know
when he'll be in.
Can I take a message?
Sure.
Tell him he missed Nabisco
and National Cash Register
just left,
so he might as well
take the rest of the day off.
Thank you. I'll let him know.
Is he on a bender, sweetheart?
I haven't heard from him,
but he went to take his daughter
to school.
I'm not concerned.
Look at this.
"Christmas Day, 1951 ."
Who's Roberta?
I don't know.
Roberta.
We had our drink.
You clearly don't need help.
You need an audience.
McCann made you wait.
You can make them wait.
I'm not enjoying this.
Oh, my God. What is this?
It's an octopus
pleasuring a lady.
It was Cooper's.
Was in his office forever.
You can have it.
You can put it in your office.
No. They won't take me
seriously.
That's pretty serious.
It's 150 years old.
You know I need to
make men feel at ease.
Who told you that?
So now I gave you something,
you can sit tight and keep me company.
You think you're gonna
have fun like this over there?
This is more attention
than I've ever gotten from you.
You should see the floor I'm on.
It's a nursing home.
What the hell happened?
You're acting like
you had nothing to do with this.
I'll have you know,
I held this place together.
I know you think that,
but you actually sold it.
You were supposed to
watch out for us.
This business
doesn't have feelings.
You get bought, you get sold,
you get fired.
If the account moves, you move.
Even if your name's on the damn door,
you should know better than to
get attached to some walls.
Well, hopefully I'll have
that problem someday.
Okay, hot stuff.
It's exciting.
I mean, I know
it's going to be challenging...
but I needed that.
So do you.
In the summer of '44,
it was over 100 degrees
every day in the Pacific,
so we dropped anchor in the
Ulithi Lagoon to go for a swim.
And you can imagine the men.
It was bedlam.
But I couldn't do it.
Can't you swim?
Did I mention I was in the Navy?
No, the real problem was
it was a two-story drop
off our cruiser.
We all have regrets.
No, I did it.
I just needed a push.
This was a hell of a boat, you know.
Come on.
It just looks good now,
but it was miserable
when you were in it.
Trust me.
Is that really how you're
gonna remember this place?
No.
Good.
This is the one for the road,
okay?
You gonna show up drunk
at 4:00 on your first day?
You know any Freemasons?
Yes? Can I help you?
I'm looking for Mrs. Baur.
I'm Mrs. Baur.
Good evening. I hope
I'm not disturbing your dinner.
Not yet. My husband
will be home any minute.
Well, I really just need
to talk to you.
I'm Bill Phillips
from Conley Research.
We represent an array
of American companies,
including Miller Beer,
and out of over 900 entries,
you, Diana Baur,
were chosen to win a brand-new
Westinghouse refrigerator
full of Miller Beer.
Now, you have your choice,
white or harvest gold.
That's the fridge, not the beer,
of course.
Well, that sounds wonderful...
but I'm not Diana, I'm Laura.
Can I still accept it?
I don't know.
I'm supposed to speak to Diana.
Is your mother home?
You really should
speak to my husband.
She's his ex-wife.
I guess if he knows where
she is, I could come back...
or wait in the car.
My neighbors have seen you
on the porch long enough.
Come on inside.
Have a seat.
Would you like some iced tea?
- I don't wanna be a bother.
- It's no bother.
I have to check on the chicken.
Are you looking for my mother?
Diana is your mother?
If she won something,
I should get it.
Yes, that makes sense.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It was no problem at all.
I hope you're finding
everything satisfactory.
Well, I'm here
because I need your help.
I'm at your disposal.
I don't know how to put this,
but I don't feel that
my accounts
are getting
the right kind of attention.
Our accounts.
Well, that's just it.
I fully expect
to service clients
with the help of your personnel.
But as a partner at SC&P,
I had a certain amount
of status.
You know, more independence.
What's the problem?
You can speak freely.
Well, I don't think that
Ferg Donnelly is a good match.
Ferg's very important
around here.
Frankly, you're lucky he's taken
an interest in your business.
I understand that,
but it's not necessary.
I don't mean to brag, but I've been
handling this account on my own
since I brought it in
I'm sure that's true,
but you're gonna have to
get used to
doing things the way we do them.
Well, I don't know how to say this,
but I can't work with him.
Joan, it may not have sunk in,
but your status has changed.
Avon, Butler Footwear,
Topaz Pantyhose,
I guess you don't need
those accounts.
I've tried to be patient...
but I don't care about
your SC&P partnership.
I don't know if somebody
left it to you in their will,
but your little stake
doesn't mean anything here.
Is that what you want?
Because I'm perfectly happy to take
my half a million dollars
and be on my way.
I'll bet people always say
you're the kind of gal
who doesn't take no
for an answer.
But no...
you're not telling me
how to run my business.
Now, find a way to get along...
or you can expect a letter
from our lawyer.
I wonder how many women
around here
would like to speak to a lawyer.
I think the Equal Employment
Opportunity Commission has one.
Women love it here.
You want to threaten us?
You'll be all alone.
No.
I think the second I file a complaint,
I'll have the ACLU in my office
and Betty Friedan in the lobby
with half the women
who marched down Fifth Avenue.
I guess you didn't see
the headlines
about what happened
at Ladies' Home Journal.
Or Newsweek.
Do you have any idea
how much space McCann buys
in The New York Times
every year?
We could get them to print
Mein Kampf on the front page.
Yes, I'm sure I'll find it difficult
to find a reporter
who wants to embarrass you
this deeply.
Look,
you're unhappy,
and now I'm unhappy.
So, how about this?
I'm willing to give you
50 cents on the dollar...
to never see your face again.
I guess I wasn't clear.
I'm not negotiating.
Then you should get
out of my office immediately.
Go ahead.
I'd rather give it to a lawyer.
So you get to drive all over
America giving people prizes?
That sounds like fun.
Well, I also give
a lot of boring presentations.
- Hello.
- Hello, honey.
This is Bill Phillips.
He says Diana
won some kind of prize.
A refrigerator
full of Miller Beer.
Really?
Well, there's been some confusion
because a Mrs. Diana Baur
entered our contest,
and, well,
she's nowhere to be found.
Diana never entered any contest.
Well, I guess it's a mistake.
Yeah...
letting you in our house.
And my wife, she doesn't know any better,
but I guess you knew that.
- Cliff, please.
- Let him answer.
Who the heck are you?
Or do I have to call the police?
You're right.
I'm deeply sorry
for the ruse, ma'am,
but I work for
a collection agency.
Clearly you're not responsible
for Mrs. Baur anymore,
but I need to know
her whereabouts.
Last I heard,
she was in New York.
- Do you have an address?
- No.
That's all I got.
I apologize for the intrusion.
Guess we're not as dumb
as you think we are.
I'm leaving.
The clothes, the shoes,
the Caddy?
You're no collection agent.
I am.
You think you're the first one
that came looking for her?
She's a tornado...
just leaving a trail of broken
bodies behind her.
I didn't mean to disturb you.
Yeah, but you did.
I'm just starting
to get back on my feet.
Just starting to get back to even
part of the way to where I was.
Look, I'm sorry.
I was worried about her.
She seemed so lost.
I lost my daughter to God
and my wife to the devil.
I lost everything.
Is that what you wanted to know?
No.
You can't save her.
Only Jesus can.
He'll help you, too.
Ask Him.
- Look, I...
- And don't come back.
Come on, once more from the top!
Where the hell have you been?
I had a lot of stuff to move.
Are any of you planning
to work here,
or is this
the con of the century?
Look, calm down.
We're all just settling in.
Calm down? Where the hell is Don?
He walked out of a meeting
Wednesday
and hasn't come back.
He does that.
Well, you may have sold me
a rotten apple,
but it's not too late
to let the ax fly.
Starting with that redhead.
Joan?
I don't want to hear
her name again.
Good morning. You made it.
You just come to work
like nothing happened?
I'm here and I'm doing my job.
Get the door.
Jim Hobart's not afraid of you.
Then why'd he send you?
To tell you I can't help you.
Well, thank you very much.
Listen to me.
You're not going to do better
than 50 cents on the dollar.
It's not about the money.
It's only about the money.
Don't hide behind politics.
Take the money
and be done with them.
Take half my money?
I know it's all my fault.
And I'm trying to take care of it.
You've started something that
could leave you with nothing.
It's plenty.
I made sure he's good for it.
Tell him he has a deal.
Where you headed?
St. Paul.
I can go that way.
Great.
I don't want to take you
out of your way, man.
It's not a problem.