Betty.
What are you doing?
I don't want you to ever see
him again. You can't have him.
It's been over for a long time.
Okay, I'm not seeing
him. I don't want him.
Well, don't see him again.
I'm telling you.
I won't.
Well, I think under the circumstances
that I should just bring Alisa home
and drop her off
after Bible school.
No.
No, I don't wanna
see you anymore.
Just keep Alisa.
Take her to the movie.
Because I don't wanna
look at you again.
You can bring her home tomorrow.
Sure.
Alisa's suit is on the washer.
I'll go get a towel
from the bathroom to...
to wrap it in.
Thank you.
Don't forget
Alisa's peppermints.
That's okay. I'm sure that
we have peppermints at home
- that I could give her.
- She likes ours.
I'll give you these.
Betty.
I am so sorry.
You can't have him.
Betty.
I'm gonna have another baby.
You can't have him.
You can't have him!
- You can't have him!
- Betty! What are you doing?
What are you doing?
I've gotta kill you.
Target.
I don't want him!
Don't want him!
Sorry. I'm sorry.
No. No. No.
Please, please,
please, please, please.
Nothing's changed.
Candy!
Oh, Barbara.
I went to Betty's and
we just got to talkin'
and I looked at my watch and
thought I had enough time
to go to Target to get Father's Day
cards, so I drove all the way to Plano.
But when I got to
the parking lot,
I realized my watch had
stopped, and so I was late.
I didn't even go
in. I'm so upset.
I wanted to see the
kids' puppet show.
And Jenny was just
asking about you.
Well, I'm just gonna have
to make it up to them.
- Candy, where have you been?
- I'm so upset.
I went to Betty's and,
well, we just got to talkin'
and I thought I had enough time
to go get Father's Day cards
at Target. But when I got there,
I realized my watch had
stopped and that I was late.
I had to get Alisa's
swimsuit from Betty's,
or I wouldn't have been
late. My watch stopped.
We're taking Alisa with us tonight
to see "The Empire Strikes Back."
- That's nice.
- Yeah.
Well, that reminds me, I
have to go check on the kids.
- Alright.
- Bye.
Hi, Mom!
Hi, Mom.
Mom, I like this one. "Hats off
for a wonderful Father's Day."
That sounds great, honey.
"To wish you a
happy Father's Day,
"and then to tell you, too,
there's always lots of love
and pride in every
thought of you."
Great.
- Come on, come on! Let's go!
- Wait!
- Come on, Ms. Candy!
- Come on, Mommy!
Girls, can you get your suits on? We
don't wanna be late for Alisa's lesson.
- Hello?
- Pat, hi.
We just got back
from Bible school.
I need you to make sure you
get enough money at the bank
because Alisa is going
to the movies with us.
- You checked with Betty?
- I went to Betty's
to get Alisa's suit,
but we just got to talkin'
and I lost track of time.
And then, I got to the Target,
and I noticed my watch
stopped. And so, I just...
I missed the whole
Bible school program.
So, we'll just meet you at
the parking lot at 15 to 5!
Somebody's here, honey,
so we'll meet you there.
- Okay!
- Okay.
Bye.
- Hey!
- Hi. I'm so sorry.
The day just got away from me.
No worries.
Can I grab it?
What?
- The card table.
- Oh, yes! Yes, of course.
I swear, I don't know
where my head is at.
I got so busy that I even
missed the puppet show.
What's wrong?
Nothing. Nothin'.
I'm just, you know,
going in too many different
directions at once is all.
It's here.
Thanks for the card table!
- Talk to you later, baby.
- Bye!
Welcome to Dallas
International Airport...
Directory assistance,
please, in Wylie, Texas.
- Hello.
- Richard, hi. This is Allan Gore.
- Hey, Allan.
- I'm sorry to bother you.
I'm out of town
and I've been trying
to catch Betty all day.
I think the phones must be
out of order or something.
But would you mind knocking
on the door over there
just to make sure she's home?
Sure I can run over.
Yeah. Hold on a
minute. I'll go check.
Okay, great.
Thank you so much.
No answer, Allan.
She must be out.
Okay.
- Thank you for checking.
- No problem.
I really like your
mom's lasagna.
Thanks! I'll tell her.
- Remember that cute turtle I made?
- Yeah.
- Out of pipe cleaners?
Hello?
Candy, this is Allan.
Have you seen Betty?
Allan!
- Hi, where are ya?
- I'm in Minnesota on a business trip
but I've been trying to
get ahold of Betty all day
and she's not answering.
And I thought maybe you
talked to her today.
Yes, I saw her this morning when
I went to get Alisa's swimsuit.
Do you happen to know
if she had any plans?
No.
No, but I still have Alisa
'cause there was a change
of plans this morning.
Jenny wanted Alisa to
stay over another night
so they could go to the movies.
Did she seem alright to you?
Yeah! Yeah, she was fine.
You know, I'd be happy to go to the
house and check on them for you.
No, that's okay. I'll
call the neighbors again.
Okay.
Okay, well, just let me know
if there's anything I can do.
- Okay. Thank you. Bye.
- Okay. Bye.
What's going on?
Allan's out of town.
He can't get ahold of Betty,
so he's a bit worried.
I'm sure she's okay.
She could be out with friends.
I'm gonna go call her
again, if you'll excuse me.
Richard, I'm really
sorry about this.
Could you run out back
and look in the garage
to see if her car is there?
- Yeah. Yeah, just a sec.
- Okay. Thanks.
She never leaves that
garage door open.
Can you please go back over there,
check all the doors and the garage again
and I want you to get in the
house any way that you can.
- Allan just called.
- Yeah, I guess he's calling everybody.
- Yeah, he called me, too.
- He sounded pretty upset.
Said we should get in
the house any way we can.
Got my realtor keys. We can
try 'em on all the doors.
Oh shit. Hey!
- Yeah?
- It's not locked.
What? Lester!
Betty?
Oh, my God.
- Oh, my God.
Hello?
There's nothing here.
The baby.
- Hey! Hey!
- Let's...
- let's get her outta here.
- It's okay. Yes.
I'll take her to my house.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. I got you.
I got you. I got you.
It's okay.
Oh God!
Don't go in there.
She's dead.
- What? What!
- She's dead.
What.
- Hello?
- This is Allan.
Oh God. I have to
make a decision.
What? What decision?
What's wrong?
- I don't know...
- It's okay.
Allan? Yeah, it's Jerry.
- What did you find?
- Oh, gosh, it's not good, Allan.
The little one's okay.
- The baby?
- Yeah, she's okay.
What about Betty?
- What about Betty?
- I'm so sorry, Allan.
What? What happened?
I don't know for sure,
but it... Oh God.
It looks like she's been shot.
I'm so sorry, Allan.
I wish there was a better
way to tell you. I do.
Stop. Stop.
- You kidding me?
- Hello?
Candy,
I have some bad news.
Betty's dead.
What?
What happened?
It looks like she's
been shot, apparently.
The neighbors found her.
Oh, my God.
What about Bethany?
We don't even own a gun.
I don't even own a gun.
I don't know what to say.
Could you please keep
Alisa for a while
and don't tell her what
happened? I wanna tell her.
Are you gonna be okay?
Yeah.
Thanks. I've gotta go.
This way, Chief.
Look there.
Looks like one of
them cult deals.
Call the sheriff.
We gotta have backup.
Then call Collin County.
In fact, call everybody.
Whoever did this could be crazy enough
to still be in the neighborhood.
This is Chief Abbott.
This is Allan Gore.
Mr. Gore. I'm Chief
Abbott of the Wylie PD.
Can you tell me what you know
about what happened here?
I understand that
Betty's been shot.
That's correct.
I've been trying to
reach her all day.
I left for Saint Paul
on business at about
4:30. I tried to call her before
I left. She didn't answer.
I kept trying her
right up until the
point that they told me.
I understand. And do
you know anybody else
that could have been
around the house today?
Well, Candy Montgomery.
She's a friend of ours.
She said she came by to pick
up a swimsuit this morning.
Serious?
The goal to contaminate as
much evidence as possible?
Start with the utility room.
Then the bathroom.
It's covered in blood.
Hello?
It's Allan.
My flight doesn't land
till about 10:00 or so.
I'm going to go home first. Can
you keep Alisa till 3:00 or so?
Of course.
- And she still doesn't know?
- No. No, we've...
we've kept her away from the
radio or anything like that.
Okay.
I talked to the
police last night
and I mentioned you were over there,
so they'll probably be calling you.
- That's fine.
- Okay. I'll call you later. Bye.
Okay.
- Hello?
- Have you heard?
Betty Gore's been shot.
She's dead!
Yes, we heard. Yes.
It's all over the news.
Honey, I have Alisa with
us. I should get off.
Listen, when I get all these
relations out of my house,
I'm gonna come over, and we're
gonna drink a pot of coffee
- and talk.
- That is just what I need.
Thank you, honey. I'll
ring if I hear more.
Jesus.
Hello?
It's me, Jo Ann. You
heard Betty's dead?
We heard last night,
yeah. It's so awful.
The police just left.
They say she was
murdered with an axe.
- An axe?
- Yeah.
Must have been some
very sick person.
It looks like from
the pinky finger.
Probably the victim's.
How we doin'?
It was not premeditated.
The weapon's too strange,
signs of a struggle everywhere.
It was a crime of circumstance.
Or sex crime, maybe.
That I can't tell you. The coroner
will have to make that call.
But those footprints in the utility
room do not belong to a man.
They're too small.
Think a woman did
this. A woman or a kid.
He's about to step out
of the cab right now
and this would be the first time
that he has been here after...
How'd it happen, Dick?
What all do you know?
Just that she was shot.
Well, that's wrong.
- What happened?
- The weapon was an axe.
And it was very brutal.
Crime lab was here
until 8:00 this morning.
It was all hell to clean up.
I wish there was another
way to say it, to tell you.
- I wasn't here.
- What?
I wasn't here.
Betty
was always afraid when I go
something would happen.
She always said I should
be here. A husband
should be home.
And I wasn't here.
Come on, sweetie.
Daddy!
Hi, sweetie.
Oh, Allan.
Allan. Oh, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Princess! Cheeto!
Is there anything that
we can do for you?
Just please don't leave yet.
I'd like for you to be here
when I tell her. I
think that'd help.
Of course.
Sweetie, can I talk
to you for a minute?
Last night,
somebody very bad
came into the house
and
cut up Mommy very bad and
Mommy's not coming back.
Understand?
She was damn near dismembered
from what I'm told.
Can you imagine?
That's why I always
say, use the deadbolt.
Like she'd been put
through a Veg-O-Matic.
I'd just finished
seeing "The Shining"
when I got the news, if
you can believe that.
Talk about bad dreams.
Well, it had to be a drifter.
A weapon like that
during the day in Wylie?
Now, my bet is probably
either sex criminal
or a burglar caught in the
act. And whoever it is,
likely a thousand
miles away by now.
Honey, I'm gonna go speak
to Don for a second.
Okay.
It happened Friday,
today's Sunday.
After 48 hours, the odds flop.
- Hey, Don. Hi, y'all.
- Hi, Candy.
We're just talking
about it. Awful.
Oh, yes. It is.
Can I speak to you in
private for a second?
- Sure.
- If that's alright. Okay. Thanks.
Well, I guess you know that
I was there that mornin'.
I was probably the last
one to see her alive.
Well, I doubt the last.
Maybe second to last.
Well, yeah, you
know what I mean.
Anyway, I'm supposed to speak
to the police this afternoon,
and is there any reason
that I should be worried?
- What do you mean?
- I don't know.
I was the last one seen at the
scene of the crime and everything
and those are always the people
they arrest on the TV shows.
Candy, they talk to everybody
in a case like this.
And the way she was chopped up.
Whoever did this had
to be a very big man.
Yeah. Yeah. You're right.
- Thanks, Don.
- Sure.
Family and friends of the
Gores continue to gather...
My deepest sympathies.
I appreciate that.
Bob's got Bethany
in the bedroom.
I think they both need a
moment away from all this.
What about this Marriage
Encounter thing?
You and Betty went to that?
We did, yes.
Could it be someone from there?
- I'm hearing it's like a cult.
- I don't...
It wasn't anyone from Marriage
Encounter. It's not a cult.
Why did you two go there?
They're evidently
doing two services.
One here tomorrow and the
other in Norwich on Wednesday.
And get this. Ron will be
performing the ceremony tomorrow.
Ron Adams?
Betty hated him.
I know, but they hadn't
officially rejoined
the Wylie Church so, technically,
Ron is still her pastor.
- Oh, my God.
- Candy? Candy.
Some of this food needs to
be put into the freezer.
I'm afraid I can't get
myself to go into that room.
Would you mind taking
it in there for me?
- Yeah, okay.
- Thank you.
Hey! Hey! Stop!
I'm sorry about those dogs.
Anytime anyone comes in this
room, they bark like that.
I'm Bertha. I'm
Betty's mother.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
"Happy Father's Day, honey.
"It really means a lot to
have a husband like you.
"A lot of time, a
lot of frustration.
"A lot of headaches,
a lot of worry,
a lot of fun."
That's so great. Thank you.
You're welcome.
Wow. Look at you.
Oh, well, I'm not sure what one
wears to the police station,
so I figured I might
as well look nice.
You sure you don't
want me to go with you?
Oh, yeah. I'll drive myself.
They said it shouldn't take long.
- You sure?
- Yeah. I'll be fine.
Well, let's just start
from the beginning.
The beginning would have
been vacation Bible school.
And that would have started
about 9:00 in the morning
with a service ceremony sort of thing,
where I told one of my parables.
"The Three Trees."
Would you like to hear that?
Oh, no. That's okay.
After the ceremony?
After the ceremony,
I left the church
around 9:45, and got to
Betty's around 10:00.
What was she doin'?
She'd just put the baby down,
and she was drinking
a cup of coffee and
sewing something out
of yellow material.
And she was about to
watch "Phil Donahue."
So, after you got there?
Yes. We got to chattin' about
what to do with the children.
And then, we went and played with the
dogs 'cause they just got a new puppy.
And then, I told her
about this new business
that I've started with Sherry Cleckler,
a wallpapering and painting thing.
And then I showed her one of my
cards and she thought that was cute.
And maybe I can leave
some for you all.
After you showed her
your business card?
I went into the utility
room to get Alisa's suit
and Betty went to grab
a towel to wrap it in.
And then she handed me
some peppermint candies
because Alisa doesn't like to
put her head under the water.
And so, she sort of just
bribes her with the candies.
What did you have
on, clothes-wise?
I was wearing a burgundy
blouse and blue jeans.
What about shoes?
We picked up some
footprints in the hallway
and we need to screen the
prints for people we know
who were in the house.
I was wearing my
blue tennis shoes.
- Rubber soles?
- Yes.
Do you have those shoes?
Not with me but I
could get them for you.
How long do you think you
were in there, in total?
About 15 minutes.
And after?
After, I went to Target in
Plano to get Father's Day cards
but I noticed my watch stopped.
It still said 10:15.
And so, I asked someone what time
it was, and they said it was 11:10,
meaning I was already
late for the puppet show.
And so, I drove
straight to the church
and got there around
11:30 for the luncheon.
And I didn't know that anything
was wrong until about 8:30
when Allan called me to tell me
that he was having a hard
time getting ahold of Betty.
I'm not saying cancel it altogether.
Just, you know, postpone it some.
Yes, I realize that they
wanna go and we will.
It's just under
the circumstances,
it's not the best time to
go to Six Flags, that's all.
Not just that she was a
popular school teacher,
but, bear in mind, this
is the first murder
of any kind in
Wylie in 25 years.
That it was committed with an
axe against an innocent woman
in her own home in
a nice neighborhood,
you can understand why this
whole community is on edge.
She was a loving mother, a loyal
wife, a committed person of faith.
How can a thing like this happen
to a person who is so
needed by her family?
A mother so needed
by her children.
A daughter so loved
by her parents.
Perhaps there will be
those who look to God
and say that He has some
eternal purpose in all of this.
I cannot accept that.
The notion that God would will
something like this upon anyone.
This was not God's will.
His will has been thwarted by the
actions and behavior of humanity.
Humanity seems too kind a word.
A monster.
When things like this happen,
God's will and purposes then
change to His ultimate will.
This act was unnatural.
It was evil.
I'm sorry, but I feel
like we've been over this.
Well, with me, you have, but I
want these boys to hear it as well.
But we're trying to be as
painstaking as possible.
I appreciate that.
How were things
with your marriage?
- They were good.
- Yeah? She was secure in it?
There was a time
when she wasn't.
You know, we've
we had our issues,
specifically over the travel.
She battled postpartum
depression, which was a strain,
but things were
improving of late.
We'd gone to a church program
called Marriage Encounter
and things were improving.
So you can't think of anybody
that'd wanna hurt your wife?
No. She didn't have any enemies,
or...
She wasn't too popular at
her school with her students.
One time, our house was
vandalized, but I can't imagine
that.
If I could go back a second.
You said that on Friday evening,
and then again on Saturday,
you had several conversations
with Candy Montgomery?
Yes.
- She told you she was at the house?
- Yes.
What else she tell you?
That Betty seemed fine.
Now, I apologize for having to ask
this, but can you think of a time
where Betty might have had
an affair with another man?
Yes, in 1971.
We were living in Las Cruces.
It was a time when
I was traveling.
She had a one-night stand
with a college student there
at New Mexico State.
I don't believe she
ever had another affair
with any other man since then.
Pretty sure about that?
Yes.
You ever had an affair yourself?
No.
Have anything else you wanna tell us
that could help us in the investigation?
I can't think of anything
at this time. No.
Hello?
Chief Abbott? It is
Allan Gore calling.
I'm sorry to disturb you.
I was just calling
to let you know that there was one
thing I was not truthful about.
What's that, Allan?
I did have an affair.
With Candy Montgomery.