Okay, well...
I did not get the
job in New York.
But I got the real prize--
domestic bliss.
Jan made me breakfast
this morning.
Well, she bought the milk.
It's soy.
This is why I do it.
That's what I have
to come home to.
She probably won't be
up for a few hours.
This is going to be
a very good year.
Very good.
Jan is at home.
Jim is back.
My protégé Ryan is at corporate.
Good stuff.
Andy and Dwight are
rocking the sales team.
I feel very blessed.
D'oh!
*
You know, generally
it's not a good idea
to click on any Internet offers
that you haven't requested.
What was the exact offer?
It was for a...Video.
Yeah, well, what kind of video?
A celebrity sex tape.
Really?
What kind of celebrity?
Not relevant.
How much you pay for it?
Not relevant. You pa for it?
It all happened so fast.
I broke up with Karen
after the job interview.
And, uh...
It was a little awkward
when she came back
from the city.
She told me very clearly
that just because
we were broken up
didn't mean that she
was going anywhere,
because she had worked
really hard for her career.
But the next day,
her desk was empty.
And as for me and my
current romantic life...
I, uh...
I'm single now and looking.
So if you know anybody...
Jim and I went to
dinner a few times
when he got back from New York.
I talked him
through his breakup.
It's really nice to
be good friends again.
Are you kidding me?
Pam and Jim are
totally hooking up.
All they do is smile.
They're just
keeping it a secret.
Right?
I don't know.
There is no evidence
of intimacy.
They've been in
remarkably good moods.
Could be other things.
Are you kidding me?
And Sunday,
I'm thinking of going to that
flea market at the drive-in.
Oh, that sounds fun.
I'm mountain biking
on Sunday in, uh...
Montage mountain.
Cool. Yeah.
Well, have fun with that.
Ladies and gentlemen.
I have some bad news.
Meredith was hit by a car.
What? Where?
It happened this morning
in the parking lot.
I took her to the hospital.
And the doctors tried
to save her life.
They did the best
that they could.
And she is going to be okay.
What is wrong with you?
Why did you have to
phrase it like that?
So she's really
going to be fine?
Yes.
She has a slight...
Pelvical fracture.
But, uh, people have
survived far worse.
Thank god you were there.
Yeah.
Did you see who did it?
Oh, no need.
We can just check
the security tapes.
Yeah, kind of a good
news/bad news there.
I was able to be on
the scene so quickly,
because I was in the
car that hit her.
Who was driving?
Oh, Michael.
One day Michael came in
complaining about a speed bump
on the highway.
I wonder who he ran over then.
It's only Meredith.
Yeah, it's only Meredith.
Thank god.
But did you see the
way they looked at me?
Like I was a murderer
or something.
Hey.
Why did you do it?
It was an accident.
Was she talking back? No.
Just got sick of that face?
Did she owe you money? Uh-oh.
Is this downsizing?
Did she spurn your advances?
Hey, guys.
We're all gonna visit
Meredith at lunch.
And we're kicking
in $5 for flowers.
Who's we? You and Jim?
No, me and Stanley
and Phyllis so far.
Oh. I bet Jim goes too.
Yeah, I haven't asked him yet.
Oh. I bet you ask.
I was planning on it.
I bet you were.
Angela? Subtle.
What? Are you coming?
I can't. Sprinkles is sick.
She's been sick for some time.
Thank you for asking.
No one asks about sprinkles.
I have to give her her meds,
I have to pet her.
And who will she eat lunch with?
Can't your other cats
keep her company?
There's bad blood.
Jealousies, cliques.
Angela,
you're the chairman
of the party planning committee.
I shouldn't even
be planning this.
It's your job.
All right!
My lord, my liege.
Yes, Michael?
So Ryan got promoted
to corporate
where he is a little
fish in a big pond.
Whereas back here in Scranton,
I am still top dog
in a fairly large pond.
So who is the real boss?
The dog or a fish?
So I need a little
treat for the gang.
Something to win
their affections back.
Back?
Why is that, Michael?
Well, I ran down
Meredith in my car.
Oh!
Did you do this on purpose?
No, I was being negligent.
But she's in the
hospital, she's fine,
recovering nicely.
Tiny little crack in her pelvis.
But she will be--
did this happen on
company property?
Yes.
It was on company property
with company property.
So double jeopardy. We are fine.
Mm, I don't-- I don't
think you understand
how jeopardy works.
Oh, right, I'm sorry.
What is "we're fine"?
People keep calling
me a "wunderkind."
I don't even know
what that means.
I mean, I know what it means.
It means very
successful for your age.
So I guess it
makes sense, but...
It's a weird word.
Hey, d.
Hey monkey, what's up?
Can you do me a little favor?
Go to my place at lunch and
give sprinkles her medicine?
Sure.
I have to visit the alkie.
Check to see if she's faking.
If a car hit me, it
wouldn't crack my pelvis.
You know what?
I bet she cracked it at home.
Jumped in front of the car
to get some worker's comp.
I wouldn't put it past her.
So what do you need me to do?
I wrote it out. Mm-hmm.
There's a diabetes shot.
Roll the Insulin in your hands,
don't shake it.
She gets an Ace
inhibitor with her meal.
But you have to put her
right in front of the dish,
or she won't see it
because of the cataracts.
Mix one capsule of
omega fatty acid
in with her kidney medicine.
Um, and you wanna
give that to her
15 minutes after she's eaten.
And, oh--there's a fungal cream,
because she has this
infection under her tail.
So you're gonna have
to lift her tail
and put the cream right
at the base of her tail.
Okay, I have an announcement.
You pushed Darryl out the window?
No.
You shot Dwight? No.
No, that is not funny.
I love my employees.
Even though I hit one
of you with my car.
For which I take
full responsibility.
Look, I am just trying
to take everybody's mind
off of this unavoidable
tragedy and on to
more positive things.
So I thought we
should plant a tree.
Oh, good. That means
we don't have to work.
Okay, we're leaving for
the hospital at 1:00.
So, like, a freedom tree.
I can take three people.
I can also take three people.
- Separate cars.
- Pam?
All right, we'll get a
card at the hospital,
and we'll sign it outside her room.
Pam.
Sales people can go
later in the day.
Hourly workers can go at lunch.
Okay, good, good.
So we'll just all go down
there together at lunch.
Excellent. I-I was
thinking that--
good work, Pam.
But if you--
yaaaay, Pam!
All right, since I am
the boss, I will drive
as well.
Who wants shotgun?
You can't be serious.
You ran a woman
over this morning.
Everybody inside the
car was fine, Stanley!
Guess what? I have flaws.
What are they?
Oh, I don't know.
I sing in the shower.
Sometimes I spend too
much time volunteering.
Occasionally, I'll hit
somebody with my car.
So sue me.
No, don't sue me.
That's the opposite of the
point that I am trying to make.
Ew.
I hate hospitals.
In my mind, they are
associated with sickness.
Oh...
She looks like an angel.
She looks awful.
No--okay.
She always looks like that.
It was not my fault.
I think she's awake.
No.
She's in a coma.
Okay.
* Meredith
Ooh!
I brought all your friends
from the office, dear.
At the same time. Yep.
Hello, Meredith.
This is weird.
Brought you some balloons.
Why don't we-- here you go.
Tie these up, cheer
up your tubes.
Oh, shh--
oh, for god's sake.
Whoa. Nurse!
No, don't bother the nurse.
Just put it back in.
I am going to be sick.
I am going to puke. I wouldn't--
I wouldn't worry about it.
Don't touch it.
What are you doing?
Just gimme that.
Thanks.
Does it hurt terribly?
No, it's not too bad.
They have me on a
lot of painkillers.
Oh, really? What kind? Codeine?
Vicodin? Percocet?
Fentanyl? Oxycontin?
Palladone? What?
I have no idea.
Oh.
Well, it was really great
of all of you to come and
visit me at the same time.
I'll see you guys at the office.
Okay, wait up, wait up, guys.
Guys, guys, hold on a sec.
You know what I was thinking
might be sort of fun?
Is if you forgave me...
In front of everybody.
Michael, I'm not gonna do that.
'Cause you know what they say
in the Bible about forgiveness?
Forgiveness... Is
next to godliness.
No, that's not.
That's cleanliness.
Well, just shh. Just--just--
you cracked my pelvis.
Look, I just-- I
don't understand
what is preventing you
from laughing this off
and giving me a big hug.
You're not forgiven.
Come on.
Michael!
Michael! Ahh!
Do I need to be liked?
Absolutely not.
I like to be liked.
I enjoy being liked.
I have to be liked.
But it's not, like,
this compulsive need
to be liked.
Like my need to be praised.
Hey. Hey, monkey.
Any problems?
Well, you left the TV on.
And your cat is dead.
What?!
Sparkles, the
white one, is dead.
Sprinkles.
That was the sick one, right?
Uh-huh.
But I thought she had more time.
No.
Did she look--
when you saw her,
how was she looking?
Really dead.
Like a, just a dead cat.
So... Hey, come on.
Don't be sad. Just...
Okay? Just...
She's in a better place.
All right.
Actually, the place that
she's in is the freezer.
Because of the odor.
It's gonna be okay.
Okay, you know what?
Everybody, let's just get
over the whole Meredith thing.
She cracked her pelvis.
A tiny, little crack.
And she's gonna be fine.
So let's just--
Michael, Angela's cat died.
Sprinkles?
Oh, sh...
I'm sorry, Angela.
Man, what a day, huh?
How could it get any worse?
Her computer crashes
with the porn,
and then Meredith
with the accident,
and then...
Sprinkles!
God!
That's three things.
I'll tell you what's going on.
This office is cursed.
And we need to do
something about it.
I am taking responsibility.
And it is up to me to
get rid of the curse
that hit Meredith with my car.
I'm not superstitious, but...
I'm--i am a little stitious.
Did anyone do anything
involving an Indian
burial ground?
Like what?
Like park on it.
Or dig up a body.
Toby?
Do you have anything
you wanna tell us?
No, I did not violate
an Indian burial ground.
In fact, I had some
good luck recently.
Alfredo's pizza picked
my business card
out of the basket, so I
get a week of free pies.
That's cool. Yeah.
Perfect.
So our tragedy is
your good luck.
Satan.
Sprinkles never hurt a soul.
God, in your infinite
wisdom, how can you do this?
She wasn't ready.
She had so much
left to accomplish.
It is only a cat.
You never...
You don't like them.
Cats do not provide
milk or wool or meat.
Dwight, please.
Dwight, you haven't seen
Meredith yet, have you?
No, I have not.
Well, I think you should
go to the hospital
and pay your respects.
I do not respect her.
But I will go.
All right.
I would now like to talk about
each of your individual
religious beliefs.
Oh, Michael, you can't ask
about religious beliefs.
Satan is a master of lies.
Everything he says
is the opposite.
All right, well, then you can
ask about religious beliefs.
Thank you for the permission.
Psych!
All right, let's just
go around the room,
and--and tell me
what you believe in.
- Um, catholic.
- Okay.
Presbyterian.
Oh, me too.
For real? Same religion.
All right. Cool.
Uh, I'm a lutheran,
and Bob is a unitarian.
It keeps things spicy.
That's why we're cursed.
I've been involved
in a number of cults,
both as a leader and a follower.
You have more fun as a follower.
But you make more
money as a leader.
Kelly, you are hindu.
So you believe in Buddha.
That's Buddhists.
Are you sure?
No.
What are you?
Uh, well, if you're gonna reduce
my identity to my religion,
then I'm sikh.
But I also like hip-hop and npr.
And I'm restoring a 1967
corvette in my spare time.
Okay.
So one sikh,
and...
As a farmer,
I know that when
an animal is sick,
sometimes the right thing to do
is to put it out of its misery.
With the electricity we're
using to keep Meredith alive,
we could power a small
fan for two days.
You tell me what's unethical.
Blink once if you want
me to pull the plug.
Don't pull any plugs.
How are you doing, miss Palmer?
Better. Excellent.
Are you a doctor
or a male nurse?
Um, I'm an intern,
which makes me a doctor.
Psh.
Her chart doesn't indicate
that she had a hysterectomy,
but she did, or at least,
she got time off for one.
Ah, so that is where
her uterus went.
Um, miss Palmer, your
last tetanus shot was
when you were bitten by
a bat a few months ago?
Yes.
Dwight here trapped it in a bag
against my head.
Just doing my job.
It also says you were
recently bitten by a raccoon?
And a rat.
Separate occasions.
Spend your whole life trying
to get people to like you,
and then you run over one person
with your car.
And it's not even one
of the popular ones.
Everybody gets on your case.
Doesn't make any sense.
God is dead.
If there was a god, then Ryan
and I would be married by now.
Maybe believing in
god was a mistake.
What did people believe in
before?
The sun?
Maybe there's some
sort of animal that we
could make a sacrifice to.
Like...a giant buffalo.
Or some sort of
monster, like something
with the body of a walrus
with the head of a sea lion.
Or something with the body
of an egret
with the head of a meerkat.
Or just...
The head of a monkey with...
The antlers of a reindeer.
With the body of...
Uh...
A porcupine.
I will do some research.
Okay.
I can help you with that.
So just to be safe,
they are giving her
the rabies vaccine.
Ohh! God, rabies?
Mm-hmm.
I was in the hospital
room with her.
How contagious is that?
Is that like an std?
No, no. You gotta be
bitten by something.
This place is so cursed.
Actually, the doctor said
it was lucky she came
into the hospital,
'cause the only
way to beat rabies,
is to start treatment
before the symptoms set in.
Lockjaw.
I know a lot of you
are very upset with me
for endangering Meredith's
life by hitting her
with my car.
But it may make you
feel a little bit better
to know that before
that happened,
Dwight endangered her life
by putting a garbage
bag over her head
and it had a bat in it.
Six of one, really.
Turns out, Meredith has
been exposed to rabies.
Which is, like, ten times
worse than a little
crack in your pelvis.
Thanks to me, she
went to the hospital,
and that saved her life.
Curse is broken.
Curse is broken, people!
Oh, there is a god!
And he has a plan
for us after all.
So go home,
get some rest.
Very, very good work today.
Got a lot accomplished.
Is there a god?
If not, what are all
these churches for?
And who is Jesus' dad?
Oh, well.
If they aren't together now,
then they probably
never will be.
I thought they'd
be good together.
Like pb & j.
Pam beesly and Jim.
What a waste.
I told you I'm
not dating anyone.
And even if I was,
I don't think it's
anyone's business.
I mean, when I do fall in love,
like, when it's for real,
the last person I'm
gonna talk about it to
is a camera crew
or my coworkers.
Almost marrying Roy Anderson
was as close to Pamela Anderson
as I ever wanna be.
Trust me, when I fall
in love, you'll know.
Michael Scott's dunder
Mifflin Scranton
Meredith Palmer memorial
celebrity rabies awareness
fun run race for the cure,
this is Pam.
Pro-am.
Pro-am race for the--
They hung up. Okay.
A woman shouldn't have
to be hit by a car
to learn that she
may have rabies.
But that is where
we are in America.
And that does not
sit right with me.
And that is why I
am hosting a fun run
race for the cure for rabies--
to raise awareness of the fact
that there is a cure for rabies.
A disease that has been
largely eradicated in the U.S.
But not very many
people know that.
No, rabies.
Babies would be a good idea.
Can I put you down for a dime?
Hi, stankley, how
many sponsors so far?
Zero.
Come on, man.
You gotta step it up.
It's for a good cause.
Jan called this morning
and pledged $500.
Isn't that your money?
That is for a good cause.
Phyllis, how is the
rabies quilt coming?
Oh, it's coming.
Oh, look at that!
Three. Way to honor
Meredith, Phyllis.
Michael? Yes?
You cannot make me run. Okay.
It is not a real charity.
It's stupid, Michael.
And I'm not gonna do it.
All right.
You didn't run for me
when I thought I
had skin cancer.
I know that you're
probably scared
of people seeing your
fat legs in shorts.
No.
Okay.
Well, back in olden times,
a large, fat person like this
was a person of power.
A person who had money,
who could buy food.
A person of respect, like the
regional manager of the day.
Whereas someone athletic
and trim like myself
was somebody who
worked in the fields,
and I was a peasant.
I just don't wanna run.
I didn't bring my
sneakers or my clothes.
Well, you're going
to have to run
or you're gonna be
in a lot of trouble.
It is not olden times anymore.
I'm petrified of nipple chafing.
Once it starts, it
is a vicious circle.
You have sensitive
nipples, they chafe.
So they become more sensitive.
So they chafe more.
So...
I take precautions.
Hey, Angela.
Hey, um...
I'm sorry about your cat.
This is sprinkles.
She was my best friend.
I kept her going through
countless ailments.
I asked Dwight schrute
to feed her once,
and she is now deceased.
This is Halloween last year.
Just a couple of kittens.
Out on the town.
Psst!
I'm having
relationship problems.
And since you're always
having relationship problems,
I thought you'd be able
to give me some advice.
What's wrong?
I have this crazy thought
that I know is crazy.
That maybe Dwight killed my cat.
Hmm.
When I got home,
sprinkles' body
was in the freezer
where Dwight said he left her.
But all my bags of
frozen French fries
had been clawed to shreds!
Oh.
Something's not right.
The vet's doing an autopsy.
Angela, I'm sorry.
Did Roy ever kill
one of your cats?
I'm more of a dog person.
So what's your
strategy for this race?
Well, I'm gonna start fast.
Mm-hmm.
Then I'm gonna run
fast in the middle.
What? Then I'm gonna end fast.
Why won't more people do that?
'Cause they're stupid.
What?
Oh, um, no, that's not--
I mean, that wasn't--
yeah, that was, um...
I mean, I can see how
it would seem a bit
like we, uh...
How it looks like, um...
But, I mean, nowadays, you
can edit anything, right?
I mean, you can
edit anything to...
Look like, um, anything.
So. Yeah, I gave
him a ride home.
Because... Right.
We're dating.
Wow.
There it is.
Uh, yeah.
We haven't told anybody.
But it's going really great.
Right?
It is going really great.
Ow!
Shut up.
You're taking this out on me,
but I was only the messenger.
Oh, really?
You'll feel better after the 5k.
Exercise is good for depression.
I am not depressed.
I'm in grief!
We have raised almost $700,
most of it from me and jan.
Um...when do they put
that on the giant check?
Or is that something
that we write in later?
Well, a giant check costs
about $200 to make up.
I have a print shop
standing by, but--
what do you think, Michael?
That's over 25% of our funds.
Mm.
It's...a tough decision.
Um...
I always imagined it
with a giant check.
Yeah, I mean, I personally
am definitely on board
for the giant check.
Giant check it is.
Well, I don't know.
On the other hand, it
does leave less money
for bat birth control.
Bat birth control.
Wait, this money is going
to bat birth control,
right, Michael?
That's what you told
me when I contributed.
You didn't contribute very much.
I was also hoping to hand
the giant check to
a rabies doctor.
How's that going?
Not well.
A doctor won't come out
to collect a check for $700.
Or $500 if we go
with the giant check.
Which we are.
And also...
There is no such thing
as a rabies doctor.
How about a rabies nurse?
I don't think so. You
know what, though?
I've actually seen ads
for nurses that you
can hire by the hour.
For, uh, parties
and bachelor events.
That's possible. Look into that.
Great. It's gonna cost
a couple hundred bucks.
And, uh-- oh, actually, more...
With tips.
Maybe we should
skip the ceremony
and just set up a college
fund for Meredith's son.
Have you met that kid?
Not going to college.
Michael.
5k means five kilometers,
not 5,000 miles.
Come in!
Hey. Hey, hey!
Oh, my god! What are you doing?
What are you doing?!
You said, "come in!" No, I didn't.
Just--
oh, my god.
Please, get out.
So I closed the door,
but the image of his--
baguette.
Dangling participle. Ooh.
Still burned in my eyes.
I can imagine.
Come in.
May I enter the room?
Yes. Or "come in."
See how I did that?
That's the way you
should enter a room.
You knock and then you
wait for the all clear.
You couldn't have taken
off all your clothes
in the men's room? Yes.
But I have an office,
so why would I do that?
On average, how many hours a day
do you spend naked
in your office?
Just ballpark.
European offices are
naked all the time.
They're so not.
Besides, my shirttail
covered most of it, so--
I didn't see where it started,
but I saw where it ended.
Phew, gross.
That's not gross! It
is the human body.
What is your problem?
Pam, you're an artist, right?
Think of me as one
of your models.
Okay, you know what?
I don't want this to detract
from what we really need
to be thinking about today.
It's not fair to
people with rabies.
And that's the point. Right?
Okay.
Let's go have some fun.
All right.
They say if you're
nervous around someone,
you should picture them naked.
I do not recommend
this strategy.
Try picturing them
with more clothes on.
Or a funny coat.
Oh, I'm sorry, is
this a working office?
And not a French beach?
Okay, name, please?
Creed Bratton, 75+ division.
You're over 75 years old?
82 November 1st.
How much is the prize money?
There's no prize money.
Well, is any of this real?
Check that out.
Look at me, I'm Toby!
I'm stretching.
I know what I'm doing.
Why is he even here?
So I heard that you
were peeping on Michael.
What? No, it was not--
look, I don't know
what your deal is,
but he's mine, okay?
So hands off.
Okay, everybody, listen up!
Thank you for coming.
Before we get started,
I wanted to say
a few words about
this deadly disease
called rabies.
And I'd like you to take a look
into the face of rabies.
That should scare you.
It scares me.
You people need to
educate yourselves.
Myth: Three Americans
every year die from rabies.
Fact: Four Americans every
year die from rabies.
How many of you
know someone who
has been afflicted
or affected by rabies?
Show of hands.
One, two, three--
too many to count.
It is truly the silent killer.
No, it is the foaming,
barking killer.
And it is something
that-- Darryl!
What are you doing?
I'm giving him a peanut.
No, don't give him--
did you hear anything I said?
Look how happy he is.
He's happy because he's insane.
You know what?
That's a perfect example
of the kind of awareness
we need to generate.
Where's the nurse?
This is the reason we're here.
Hello, Michael.
Oh, hey, I know you.
Elizabeth, right? Yeah.
Wow.
Very cool you went back
and got your degree.
I would like you to
accept this check
for $340
made out to science.
Make sure that that gets
into the right hands.
Right.
You got it?
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Fettuccine Alfredo.
Time to carbo load.
Mmm.
Just remember, folks,
it's not about winning.
It is about finishing.
On your marks!
Get set!
Down!
On your left!
Wow, you're fast.
You're doing great, Michael.
Look at you go!
That's my boss!
Yeah, baby!
I'm fast. I'm very fast.
I'm like Forrest Gump,
except I am not an idiot.
Oh, yes, I will work out today.
I will work out a way
to avoid running
for a stupid cause.
I've walked two marathons.
Pretty sure I can handle a 5k.
The key is drafting
to eliminate wind resistance.
Yeah.
Oh, we're in last place.
Oh, would you look at that?
Darn it.
Water!
Water.
Oh! Water, babe?
No, no water for me.
Not while rabies
causes fear of water.
Solidarity!
Michael, that's irrational!
Rabies victims...
Have to live with an
irrational hatred of water
their entire lives.
So...least I could do.
Oh, god. My nipples.
It's starting.
Can we get another round?
Okay. Thanks.
So we've got what?
Another 20 minutes?
More or less. Mmm.
That fettuccini...
Is hitting my
stomach like a rock.
You got nothing to worry about.
I put imodium in Toby's
coffee before the race.
Excellent!
Simpsons!
Wait, imodium or ex-lax?
I'm making great time.
Usually I have to
take a bathroom break
halfway through
a race like this.
But...not today.
Ooh, an estate sale.
Want to go in?
I don't know, I'm really
committed to winning.
Okay, but what if I told you
that all the money
you spend here
goes to preventing a disease
that's already been cured.
Mmm, yes.
That's what I thought.
Yeah. Right?
Let's do some good.
You have reached the offices
of dunder Mifflin Scranton.
Currently the entire
staff is out doing
the Michael Scott d.M.S.M.P.M.C.
Rabies awarness pro
am fun run race...
For the cure.
Leave a message.
Oh, god.
Oh, Alfredo sauce.
I'm getting a stitch. Ahh!
Ow! God!
Watch the nipples, Kevin!
Back off me.
How you feeling? Better?
No.
Well, you look cute as button.
You've worked up quite a sweat.
The vet is removing
all of sprinkles organs
right now and sending
them to the lab.
I am a farmer, Angela.
What does that mean?
Okay, when a farmer sees
an animal that is in pain,
that has no quality of life,
that has no utility,
a farmer does what city folk
don't have the stomach to do.
You did kill her!
I-I sang her her favorite songs.
You put her in my freezer!
It was beautiful and
gentle and respectful.
I fed her antihistamines and
she gradually fell asleep.
Well, then she barfed
them up in the freezer
and tried to get out.
Well, I'm not responsible
for that--hey!
Ow! It's okay!
It's nothing! I'm robbing her!
It's nothing! It's fine!
How could you do that
without telling me?
I thought I was helping you.
I expected a hug.
I took care of that cat
the best way I knew how.
Cat heaven is a beautiful place.
But you don't get there
if you're euthanized.
I know a great taxidermist.
I'll pay to have her stuff.
Well, he's not great,
but he's pretty good.
You don't understand.
Take bat bites seriously.
Don't get bit.
Or we can have her buried out
at the east field by mother.
Huh, Angela?
Don't touch me, Dwight.
You like it?
It's kind of designy and cool.
It was $8.
Oh, and I get to carry it.
And the winner is
Toby Flenderson!
Have a seat. I'll write it down.
Where are we?
I don't know.
Like five kilometers
from the office.
He couldn't have
made it a circle?
I am not going to finish.
I can't beat rabies.
Nobody can beat rabies.
Rabies has been around
for a thousand years.
I was fool to think
that I could beat it.
Pictures of the dog all around.
Yeah, probably-- hey.
Michael?
What are you doing here?
Did you come back for us of--
I can't finish.
I feel so weak. I just--
well, you're
probably dehydrated.
What do you want me to do, Jim?
A glass of water
would be a start.
No, there are people...
All over the world with
all sorts of problems
and afflictions and diseases.
They're deformed
and they're abnormal.
And...they're
illiterate and ugly.
Symphonies don't have any money.
Public TV is bust.
I can't do anything about it.
I can't, you know--
there's just one of me,
and there's thousand of them.
And rabies wins.
Wow, you are a downer.
We were having a
pretty nice day.
I'm still having a nice day.
You are? Yeah.
Hey, Michael, look at this lamp.
$8.
That's a good deal.
And Michael, you
don't have rabies.
And chances are you're not
gonna get it anytime soon.
So you don't really have
to think about it too much.
Pam, if everybody felt that way,
nothing would get done.
Yeah, but there's
other better people
out there who are helping.
You just don't
think I am capable
of making a difference.
I know you, Michael.
I saw you naked.
You don't--
you don't know me.
You've just seen my penis.
I can make a difference.
Remember, I'm the one
who started this whole thing off
by hitting Meredith with my car.
And I owe it to her
to finish this g.D. 5k.
Oh!
No, no!
Finishing that 5k
was the hardest thing
I have ever had to do.
I ate more fettuccine Alfredo
and drank less water than
I have in my entire life.
People always talk about
triumphs of the human spirit.
Well, today I had a
triumph of the human body.
That's why everybody was
applauding for me at the end.
My guts and my heart.
And while I eventually
puked my guts out,
I never puked my heart out.
And I'm very, very
proud of that.
Hey, Michael. Hey, mer.
How you doing?
Better.
It's ironic, isn't it?
I mean, I'm in the hospital
for not getting enough water.
And you're in it for a disease
that causes a fear of water.
I'm in because you
hit me with your car.
Oh. But I want to say...
I heard you were
trying really hard,
so...I'm not mad at you anymore.
Thanks.
I'm not mad at you anymore.
Want to share?
Sure.
I'm not really sick.
I'm good.