What's wrong, Michael?
I got gum in my hair.
You do.
This just stinks.
Don't touch it.
Please, don't touch it!
You've got a ton of dandruff.
Okay, let me be.
How'd you get gum in your hair?
I was walking in and I noticed
something shiny under Stanley's car,
and I'd gotten under to see what
it was, and I messed up my hair.
All for a stupid
piece of tin foil.
But, best-case scenario, you
thought it was a quarter.
Kill me, right now.
We have peanut butter
in the kitchen.
I don't feel like peanut butter.
Get me an ice cream sandwich.
Nope, not for you, it's for your hair.
And it is 9:00 a.m.
No, Dwight, not the good peanut butter.
People are gonna get mad.
Hey, hey, hey. This is my
hair we're talking about.
Smells good.
Tastes good, too.
Oh, don't, that's disgusting.
Wow, a lot of calories.
Well, just don't
leave it on too long.
Keep massaging, please.
Oh, yeah, that's nice.
Hey, Michael, how was
your date last night?
I will be honest. The dating
has not been going well.
Look, men are visual creatures.
We crave beauty. Like
a piece of fine art by
any number of renowned artists.
Or an arty photograph
of Cindy Crawford nude.
That, but the women I'm
getting fixed up with are...
Not that they aren't nice
or have great personalities,
they just, they just lack
a certain Crawfordness.
I am livid. Absolutely livid.
It's ridiculous.
Yes, I'm having the Scranton
branch come in on one Saturday,
so they can re-enter sales
that they made on the phone
as sales made by the website, which
they should've done in the first place,
My favorite branch.
How's everybody doing?
Hey, man, do you mind if
I run something by you?
Love it! Go.
Well, I kind of feel like what we have
going for us is our customer service.
And no matter how much
we change this up,
I don't know that a website's
gonna be able to replace that.
I can tell you've thought about this a lot.
I appreciate that.
Thanks.
David Wallace does, too.
You told him all about this
at the Christmas party, right?
Did I?
You did, yeah.
Hmm.
Watch your back, Jim.
I'm just kidding.
Ladies and gentlemen, may I
have your attention, please?
I know that a lot of you
are very angry with Ryan,
because he is the reason we
all have to come in tomorrow.
However, I swear to God, if
any of you hurts him in any way
emotionally, or taunts him,
or makes fun of his height
or his half-beard...
Okay. Thanks, Michael.
He... Yeah.
I'm here today
to do some creative problem solving
about Dunder Mifflin Infinity
and field your questions.
Question.
Dwight.
Why am I being forced
to come in tomorrow
and pretend that a website
made sales that I made?
This is a temporary measure to
increase the legitimacy of the site.
I don't like when my clients call
me to help them use the website.
I'm not seeing
commissions on that.
I hear you, Stanley. That
is a great observation.
Problems like that will not happen when
we launch Dunder Mifflin Infinity 2.0.
When will that be? TBD.
Phyllis.
Did the police solve
the problem with...
Yes, yes, they did.
Yes, they did.
Yes, the social networking feature of
the Dunder Mifflin Infinity website
was infiltrated by
sexual predators.
I don't understand why our website
needs to have social networking at all.
Yeah, actually I have to
agree with Dwight on that one.
It's all about creating a
one-stop consumer experience.
All right? You're chatting
with your friends,
you're talking about
the latest music.
About the election.
All of it is happening in
our virtual paper store.
And then an older gentleman
asks you, "Boxers or briefs?"
I don't get the big fuss, here.
I like the site.
If I had created a website with
this many problems, I'd kill myself.
Do you have a question, Kelly?
Yeah, I have a lot of questions.
Number one. How dare you?
Ryan has done a very good job, and
I am not applauding sarcastically.
Think about it. A month ago,
nobody would go on this
site, because we were worried
about getting molested or losing
our identity, having it stolen.
But now, at a time TDB, all of
these problems will be in the past.
You done good, kid.
You done good.
Well, it has been nice
seeing you again, my friend.
You, too.
Oh, Ryan, I need a
girlfriend so bad.
Michael, let me go.
Let me go, Michael.
All right.
Do you know any girls in New York
you might want to hook me up with,
that might be interested
in a guy like me?
Nah. Nah.
Sorry, man. Well, you tried.
But, seriously...
You should see the girls I
meet at clubs in the city.
Unreal.
They sound great.
Bye, everyone! Stay real,
Scranton, all right? Peace!
Would you have
sex with Meredith?
What?
Do you think she'd
keep it quiet?
I'm gonna go to my desk.
Jim, it's not the horniness, okay?
It's the loneliness. That's...
I know.
Let's go to New York. We'll
go clubbing with Ryan.
I can't. Yes, you can.
You're single, I'm single.
It'll be awesome.
I'm not single.
Who are you dating?
Pam.
That's still going on?
Okay, Dwight, grab your stuff.
We're going to New York to party
with Ryan and to meet girls.
- Yeah!
- Oh, yes.
Count me in, dudes. I am in
serious need of some bro time.
Old ball and chain's been a lot
more chain than ball lately,
if you know what I'm saying.
I'm right here.
No, singles only. Singles only.
Also, three is unlucky.
Curse of three. Sorry, Andy.
Cannot take any chances on curses.
Not tonight.
Let's go. Everybody, I will see
you tomorrow, Saturday morning,
probably wearing the same clothes
that I'm wearing right now,
if you catch my drift.
We get it.
I am going
to go get laid.
Goodbye!
With sex!
You know what? If we all stayed
a couple hours late tonight
without Michael distracting us, we
wouldn't have to come in at all tomorrow.
So I caught everyone before they
left, and I told them my idea.
And they loved it.
Because this is a group
that respects good ideas.
The one time a
year they hear one.
Ryan's assistant told us
that he would be at
this club this evening.
It is called Prerogative.
This place is packed!
Fire hazard.
Packed with
"beautiful babies."
Swingers, classic.
Jon Favreau, tall
guy from Dodgeball.
These women look
like white slaves.
No, they're just hot. Hotties.
I don't know. When you think about
it, Cabo is really the Third World.
I don't go to a place like that
to see more poverty, you know?
You go there to get
some glamour, and...
Hey.
Michael?
What are you doing here?
Well, you know,
just taking you up on
your offer to party, so...
Ta-da!
That is so awesome, man!
All right!
And you brought this guy!
Yeah!
Oh!
Ryan, it's Michael and Dwight.
I know it's you guys! Okay.
I'm so psyched you're here.
Well...
All right!
Let's get a drink!
Let's do it!
Thanks a lot, guys! Good job!
Later.
Nice job, everybody.
Great work.
Did you not tell the security
guard we were working late?
Nope. I didn't.
But let's go inside and
I can call him right now.
We can't. I locked the office
from the inside when we left.
Perfect. You guys worked
together on this one.
If I'm not in my bath with a glass of
red wine in one hour, you're both dead.
There is a master key and
a spare key for the office.
Dwight has them both.
When I asked, "What if you die, Dwight?
How will we get into the office?"
He said, "If I'm dead, you
guys have been dead for weeks."
Guys, I want you to meet a really
good friend of mine. This is Troy.
Hey, nice to meet you.
How're you doing?
Hi. Dwight.
You resemble the
Tolkien character.
He basically is, man. He's
a regular banking wizard.
No, no, no, not a wizard.
A hobbit.
Bottle service, y'all?
Oh, okay. All I know is,
I would like some chicken
fingers and a Midori Sour.
We don't serve food here.
Oh, okay. Then just
bring me two cups,
one with olives, and another one
filled with maraschino cherries.
Do you live in a
regular-sized house?
Yeah, he's a normal guy.
He's cool.
You really don't have
his phone number?
I told you, I have the
number that rings here.
Do you want that number?
I might have it in here.
Wow, that's great, Toby.
It's so random that I have it.
Toby, you're the best!
When I put it in, I thought it might be a
waste of time, but I guess it was worth it.
Great. It's under here
as "security guard home."
Did you not get his name, or...
No.
It's ringing... Does anybody
have his name, quick?
Yes, it's Eddie.
It's not... It's not Eddie.
It's Evan or...
Hank. His name is Hank.
No, guys, his name's not Hank, it's...
Is it Edgar?
Elliot. Elliot.
Is it... Hey, chief.
This is Jim Halpert from
where you work.
You are the guy who sits behind the desk.
You're the...
The African-American guy.
I mean, you're...
Who have I got here?
Dwight Schrute, man.
How's Schrute Farms?
Good.
This guy owns his own beet farm.
Insane!
Well, it's weevil season,
but we were prepared.
"Weevils." What a
crazy word, man.
I don't even know what that means.
What does that mean?
They lay their eggs inside
the unripe beetroot,
then, come springtime, the
babies eat their way out.
Crazy! Sick!
That's too much for me, man.
I'm gonna hit the bathroom.
You've already
been several times.
Yeah?
Maybe you have some kind
of bladder infection.
I don't know. Maybe.
I'll order you some
cranberry juice.
With vodka. You're the best!
Do you have powers?
Oh, thank you, Hank.
You are a lifesaver, Hank.
Appreciate it.
All right, so Hank is going to come
down here. He's gonna let us all out.
He said it should be
just under an hour, so...
Oh!
We did it.
We should all make sure to give
him a big tip this Christmas.
Sorry, guys, but I don't think
I chipped in for last year's.
Neither did I.
Jim was supposed to collect it.
Way to go, man.
Now he's never gonna come.
By a show of hands, who thinks we're
a better couple than Jim and Pam?
Phyllis!
I thought about getting a tattoo
on my back, as well, at one point.
I was thinking about
getting Back to the Future.
"Back" because it's on my back,
and "Future" because I'm the kind of guy
who likes to look ahead into the future.
I just think a tattoo should
mean something, you know?
And it's my
second-favorite movie.
I've never heard of that movie.
Back to the Future? Oh, wow!
Well, you should take a
film education course.
How old are you?
40... I'm in my 40s.
Wow, that's so cool.
Yeah.
Well, I'm gonna go
back to my group now.
Oh, okay.
Thanks for the drink.
You are welcome.
This place is like a...
Like a sexy preschool.
Did you want a place where
we can meet older women?
I would love a place where
we can meet older girls.
Hell, yeah!
I'll hook it up!
Wow, that's dangerous.
Excuse me.
Yeah?
How did you all find each other?
We're the Jersey State varsity basketball
team. Northeast Regional Champs.
Amazons!
It's off. It's not
the dude I know.
It's some other loser who
won't let us in without chicks.
- You're kidding.
- Let's bail.
Wait, wait, wait. You two,
Jersey State girls, let's go.
We're not going
unless we can all go.
Okay, you know what? Fine.
Let's go, two girls to a guy.
Come on, let's do it.
Come on, Ryan. Move out!
Hey, three or four with him.
Let's go, come on. Here we go.
Don't step on him.
Really?
Hey, look what I
found in the back.
Want to play? I can
teach you to throw.
I know how to throw a football.
Of course you do.
Yeah, Pam! Hit me up!
Go long!
There you go.
Wait a minute. What is this?
I didn't order this.
It's for you. From them.
What are you doing, man?
It's not safe. Anything
could have been in there.
Nice try!
I've never met
anybody who does that.
You wash dogs. Very cool.
That's one aspect of small pet grooming.
What do you do?
I am a bank teller.
Ryan told me to always tell
women you work in finance.
Cool. Yeah.
I think so. Yeah, I have fun.
I'm just gonna use
the powder room.
All right. So,
I'll see you soon.
Very perfect.
This needs to be shared.
She washes dogs.
You're doing it, man I know!
I don't want to get
ahead of myself, but...
I think I want her
to meet my mom.
Hey, man,
do you ever think there's gonna
be this massive nuclear holocaust?
And after all the major
nations are destroyed,
there'll just be tribes in the
jungles that rise up and survive?
That jungle warfare is
gonna rule the world?
Yeah, maybe.
It's inevitable, right?
Mmm-hmm.
Please don't pick up.
Hello.
Hank.
Is that you? Yeah.
Still haven't left
the house yet, huh?
I was getting ready to leave.
Good. Please hurry.
Stop calling me, so I
can put on my damn socks.
Will do. I'll stop calling.
I am.
I am getting out there.
Well, no, I've asked a lot
of girls to dance, Mom.
They're just... It's not...
Listen to me for a second.
Yes, I shaved the
back of my neck.
Oh, my God. Mom, I gotta go.
One of my friends is getting
beaten up by some girls!
Actually, it's kind of too bad
we're not coming into work tomorrow.
Why?
I bet Michael had some elaborate
theme party planned, like
"Scrambled Egg Saturday."
More like, "Hey, everyone, let's
get your boss laid" Saturday.
I have an announcement to make.
I am moving to Costa Rica.
I've thought about it
for a long time, now,
and I'm finally gonna do it.
So...
I'm just gonna hop the
fence and jog home, then.
Those girls really
whaled on you bad.
Why wouldn't they let me dance?
Okay, I gotta go.
Do not take him to a hospital.
Pretty weird.
Do you have to go with them?
I do, I have to go.
Stay. Just stay, please.
Okay, no. I have to go.
Good luck against Conn
College, all right?
Call me.
Uh-huh.
I'm not gonna call her.
I don't want to go back in.
I know. Here we go.
Cleaning people. Oscar?
Okay, so all you need to do is
explain to them what happened,
'cause I think they can help us.
Why are you assuming
they only speak Spanish?
If they speak Spanish.
Good evening.
We locked ourselves in.
They happen to speak Spanish.
Lucky us.
This is a one-time thing.
You know that, right?
Wow. All right!
This is it.
This is where the magic happens.
Nice! Very nice.
One of you can have the sofa, and
one of you can have the floor.
- I got the sofa.
- I got sofa.
Dwight, I got the
sofa, I'm the boss.
Come on. I got floor!
In case anybody needs
to go to the bathroom
in the middle of the night, I don't
want to get my head stepped on.
Do you want me to sing you a
song my mother used to sing me
when we were sick? No.
Okay, Dwight. Dwight.
Leave him alone. It's a lullaby.
Ryan? Ryan, we're gonna
take your clothes off.
No!
Guys...
I think my friend Troy
might have a drug problem.
What do I do?
I think his species might have
a higher tolerance than ours.
Just stop.
Here's what you do.
You tell him that you're his friend
and that you're going to help him,
and that everything's
gonna be all right.
And then you put a wire on him,
and you find out who's
selling him drugs.
And then you get that
guy and you flip him.
You turn him into a snitch.
You follow that guy
to the people who're
really, really bad.
I've been watching The Wire recently.
I don't understand a word of it.
Guys, I'm going to sleep.
You can leave the light on if you
want, but please stop talking, okay?
Okay. Good night, Ryan.
Good night, Ryan.
Best night ever.
Like I said,
it's not about the horniness.
It's about the loneliness.
And how can I be
lonely with my boys?
Like a famous person once said,
Boys on the Side.
But I don't... I disagree.
I say, Let's Hear
It for the Boys.
Son of a bitch.