Richard, you
vastly overspent,
and it's not unreasonable
that we would be upset.
- It'll work.
- I promise you.
The FDA created
a special label
to say that
it's less addictive.
I would never prescribe
a narcotic for moderate pain.
That fucking label
caused everything.
This drug has only been
on the market for three years,
and there's already
been a spike in overdoses.
Our community is ground zero
for a growing
national catastrophe.
We're gonna do
everything we can
to hold someone accountable.
But you got all these people.
They almost never mention
OxyContin by name
in the video
promoting OxyContin.
And this video is
the first major introduction
of OxyContin.
Prove they're lying
about the dangers of the drug
and that they're
selling it anyway.
I can't lose my job.
I gotta make enough money
to get out of here.
- There's a new drug.
- The FDA said it's safe.
♪ ♪
Do you solemnly swear that
you will correctly transcribe
to the best of your ability
all of the testimony
given by each and every witness
testifying in the matter
now pending
before this grand jury
and that you will keep secret
and divulge to no one
any of the proceedings of this
grand jury, so help you God?
I do.
♪ ♪
It takes
10 to 15 years for a new drug
to complete the journey from
inception to the marketplace.
♪ ♪
If OxyContin had failed
when it launched in 1996,
what would have been
the consequences?
Purdue Pharma
would have lost $40 million
with no significant product
in the pipeline.
Big day, right?
First sets of numbers
coming in?
I'm sure they'll be fine.
♪ ♪
And how much damage
would that have inflicted
on Purdue Pharma?
It likely would have
sunk the entire company.
They're not bad.
We can do better.
How's our video
testimonial coming?
A bit slow.
The drug is so new,
there's not a lot of people
who can testify to it
at this point.
- Then find some.
- Yes, sir.
Physicians need to know
it can take its place
next to penicillin
as one of the most important
in the history of medicine.
Let's hold
more weekend seminars
to explain to physicians
how truly revolutionary
this drug is.
It's your favorite
pharma rep.
If he's gonna bribe you
for access,
you should get
more than flowers.
How about a mani-pedi
next time?
Yes, please.
And your present, Doc,
is a pen
with a titration chart in it.
- Oh.
- There you go.
Thanks.
Think I'd rather have flowers.
So now that you bought
your way into my office,
what do you need?
- Can we sit for a minute?
- Sure.
I wanted to extend an
exciting invitation your way.
Purdue want to invite you
to an all-expenses paid trip
to Scottsdale, Arizona,
at a five-star resort
to hear pain experts
discuss new treatments.
- Even allowed to do that?
- Isn't it illegal or something?
- Oh, you kidding me?
- No, it absolutely is.
All the pharmas do it,
and, you know, these seminars,
they're a lot of fun,
and they're very informative.
- Mm.
- I can't.
I've got--I've got
a full practice,
even on weekends.
- Too many folks.
- Right.
But the seminar
would be an extension
of your work here.
There'll be a lot
of pain experts,
and you'll walk away
with some great tips.
Take your wife, you know?
Two of you could have
a relaxing spa weekend.
My wife passed away
from ovarian cancer, so...
- Oh, my God.
- Yeah.
- I'm sorry.
It's all right.
Well, um, I'll keep
checking in with you.
And, uh...
think about Scottsdale.
Sure.
It'll be fun, Doc.
♪ ♪
Hey, Logan.
I've been wanting
to check on you.
Wanna take a look
at that shoulder.
Doing the same.
Still can't lift it more--
much more than that.
Pains the shoulder
something awful.
Yeah.
Been more than six years, Doc.
- Yeah, I know.
- I know.
Hey, there's a new medication
I might want you to try.
What kind
of medication's that?
When a patient
first takes OxyContin,
it can be very effective.
The patient often feels like
their life has been
instantly transformed.
Unfortunately, the drug didn't
always work as Purdue claimed.
Oh, how so?
♪ ♪
So we've been getting some
complaints from patients
and doctors that the drug
isn't lasting 12 hours.
People are waking up
in the middle of the night
in pain.
Our entire FDA approval
is based on the fact
that it's a 12-hour drug.
Insurance companies
and hospitals won't cover it
if it doesn't last
the full 12 hours.
How did this happen?
Well, we always knew
it was a possibility
that the drug
wouldn't last 12 hours.
The Puerto Rico testing
only hit at 50%--
The FDA only requires
a 50% threshold.
Thank you.
That will be all.
♪ ♪
Don't worry.
We'll figure this out.
It's an excellent drug.
♪ ♪
You've got
your mother worried sick
about you, Richie.
Well, our patent expired.
Dad would be dead
without a replacement.
Because ear wax just isn't
good enough for you.
Forgive me for trying to...
make us more
than the Betadine family.
I know, I know,
you've got grand ambitions,
but I am concerned
you're going to become Icarus.
♪ ♪
If OxyContin does
what I think it can,
then it's gonna be bigger
than anything Uncle Arthur
ever dreamed.
Richie...
Arthur is dead.
♪ ♪
When Roche hired Arthur
Sackler to market value,
he needed to find a way
to separate it from Librium.
So Arthur devised
a specific medical condition
called psychic tension.
Where Librium
was taken for anxiety,
you would need
a much stronger medication
for psychic tension.
And thus, Valium became
the number one tranquilizer
on the market
by creating the condition
known as psychic tension.
Now, we have created
the greatest painkiller
in the history
of human civilization...
and all we have to do
to ensure the world gets it
is to figure out
a medical condition
that would require
an OxyContin patient...
to double their dose.
♪ ♪
Today we're gonna talk
about a medical condition
known as breakthrough pain.
Neither common nor rare,
breakthrough pain
is a specific type of pain
that breaks through
the 12-hour cycle.
Yeah, I've had
several complaints--
or should I say questions--
about the drug
not lasting 12 hours.
All right,
what you need to do
is tell your doctors
that their patients
are experiencing
breakthrough pain.
But we have
an effective solution
that will allow their patients
to get a full night's sleep
on OxyContin.
All they have to do
is double the dose.
So if they are
on 10 milligrams,
they double the dose to 20.
If they're already on 20,
they double to 40.
♪ ♪
Hey, if this drug
isn't working
like we say it is,
doctors are gonna stop
prescribing it.
Then maybe you should start
selling Viagra.
Thanks for the help.
Look, the 20
and 40 milligrams
are two and four times
more expensive than the 10.
So if we can convince doctors
to double their doses,
we will be doubling
our paychecks.
Yeah, I get that, but...
what if it doesn't work?
No drug is going to work
perfectly for every patient,
and that's not our problem.
Our job is to sell.
Then I guess
we double the dose.
Yeah.
Doc, I was able
to get some information
on the 12-hour issue,
and, uh, it's not uncommon.
What your patient's
experiencing
is breakthrough pain,
and it can happen
hours nine and ten,
especially if the pain
is uniquely acute.
Breakthrough pain.
I've never heard
of breakthrough pain.
You really haven't?
Well, it's a--it's a term used
primarily by, uh--
by pain specialists, you know?
And the solution is--is simple.
You, uh--you
just double the dose.
So if they're on 10 milligrams,
you know,
you bump them up to 20.
Oh, no, no, no.
No, that's--that's too strong
for a narcotic.
I'll just switch her
to Percocet
or low-dose morphine pills.
Doc, I wouldn't do that.
Tho--those drugs,
you know, they're not--
they're not non-addictive
in the way that--that OC is.
And it's perfectly safe
to--to double the dose.
You're telling me
that your drug
is the only drug in the world
that can help my patients?
Well, ye--I mean,
I'm saying--
I'm saying it's
your best option, you know?
Have you had
a number of patients
with--with breakthrough
pain issues?
Well, I guess I just got one.
I don't know, I've only got
four people on it, Billy.
Right, but they're all
doing great, right?
Yeah, it's been
very effective, actually.
See?
There you go.
I--I'd stay away
from morphine, Doc.
You know, it's not, uh,
it's not 1894 anymore.
Teddy Roosevelt
isn't president.
Well, Teddy Roosevelt
wasn't president then either,
but I get your point.
Uh, okay.
Yeah, I guess morphine
would probably be too strong
for her back injury anyway.
♪ ♪
Hello?
Uh, so--sorry, Doc.
I think you cut out there.
I think doubling her up
to 20 milligrams
will do the trick.
Just--just give it a try.
All right, I'll let you go.
Bye.
So, um,
there's a new issue.
A number of doctors
have the misconception
OxyContin is less powerful
than morphine,
when, as you know, it's
much more powerful, and, uh,
the confusion has started
to come up more frequently.
What are some
of the side effects
associated with morphine?
Difficulty breathing,
sedation, coma, and death.
And is OxyContin
more potent than morphine?
Yes.
Its active ingredient,
oxycodone,
is twice as potent.
And thus twice as dangerous.
I think it would
be extremely dangerous
at this early stage
in the life of this product
to, um, clarify for physicians
that our drug
is stronger than morphine.
So we do not plan
to do anything about that.
And I agree with you.
Well, you'll
be happy to know
you're not the first person
who can't sleep
through the night.
That's not uncommon.
So we've got two options.
We can, uh, switch you
to a different medication.
No, I-I don't wanna switch.
This works better than anything
I've ever used before.
Okay, well, option two
is I can double your dose
to 20 milligrams.
But if that doesn't work,
we'll switch to something else.
And if you're still having
a hard time
sleeping through the night,
you call me.
And if you don't call me,
girl...
Then you'll call me.
That's correct.
So how's those moving plans
of yours coming along?
Uh, I don't know.
Maybe I just keep my head down
and figure it out
in a year or so.
You know,
when Shelly told me,
"I want to move
to Finch Creek,"
I thought, "Finch Creek?
Are you nuts?
Finch Creek?"
I mean,
I'm from this little town
in southwest Pennsylvania.
That's like New York City
compared to Finch Creek.
I loved it
the minute I got here.
Best decision I ever made.
So if you wanna move
to Eureka Springs,
you just go ahead
and dive in the deep end
and do it.
All right?
You can always come back.
Can I always move back?
♪ ♪
Thanks, Doc.
Bye.
♪ ♪
Can you just confirm
that you're the ad agency
that made the I Got My Life
Back promotional video?
Yes, that was ours.
After reviewing it,
we were curious
as to why nobody says
"OxyContin"
in a video designed
to promote OxyContin.
- They don't?
- No.
There's maybe one mention,
40 minutes.
Everyone just says either, uh,
"the pain medication"
or "the pain medicine."
You got people
tying themselves up
not to say OxyContin.
Now, why is that?
I don't remember,
and that shoot was years ago.
Uh-huh.
And it's important
our clients know
we won't disclose
internal communication.
And it's important
that you know
that we have subpoena power.
So you can either
answer our questions here,
or you can answer 'em
under oath
in front of a grand jury
in Roanoke, Virginia.
Which is beautiful
this time of year.
You see, guys, right now,
we view y'all as witnesses,
but that can quickly change
to suspects.
Look, this was all
a long time ago, okay?
But we might've been
given instructions
that they didn't want
the participants
to say the name
of the medication.
Why not?
If I recall,
the original concept
wasn't to promote OxyContin.
They just wanted us to do
a public service announcement
for pain relief.
That might've been why
Purdue didn't want anyone
to name a specific drug.
But there are titles
at the end
that say OxyContin.
And it's written
at the bottom of the screen
the exact milligrams
each patient's on.
You need to clarify
this issue.
We were given instructions
to add the OxyContin graphics
after the shoot while
we were editing the video.
So it started out as a PSA,
and then somewhere
in the post-production process,
it became a promotional video
for OxyContin?
Is that what happened?
We just did what they wanted.
They said, "Make a PSA,"
so that's what we shot.
Then in post, they said
"Add the OxyContin titles,"
so we did.
So who at Purdue Pharma
gave you
these specific instructions?
♪ ♪
Oh, let me guess.
They had no names of any
upper-level Purdue executives
- tied to the video.
- No, sir.
Purdue went to great lengths
to make sure there were
no executives' fingerprints
on anything.
Like I said,
that's where it gets murky,
but we'll keep digging.
Won't be our entire case,
but it could be great
in terms of proving fraud.
Or at least get a judge
to grant us access
to all Purdue's internal files.
Well, you better
find something big, and fast,
because we've got a situation
that might shut
this whole thing down.
I just got a call
from Main Justice.
The Deputy Attorney General
wants us to go to DC
to discuss this case with him.
That's--that's unusual
this early in the case.
I know.
If I'm getting calls,
it must mean that someone
with a lot of influence really
doesn't like what we're doing.
When does he wanna
meet with us?
In two weeks.
You ever met James Comey
in person?
- No.
- What's he like?
He's very tall.
I'm gonna need more
on this video
if we're gonna keep
this case open, you got it?
Find me something good.
♪ ♪
Thanks, all, for coming out
to North Carolina
for this operation.
Everyone on this list
participated in a video
entitled I Got My Life Back.
This video could be
a key piece of evidence
in proving Purdue
committed fraud
in the promotion of OxyContin.
To better ascertain
the details of the video,
we'll interview
each of them simultaneously.
Give them less of a chance
to coordinate their stories.
♪ ♪
What do you want?
I'm Rick Mountcastle
with the federal government.
- Can I help you?
- Yes, ma'am.
My name's Randy Ramseyer.
I work for the government.
- Why?
- What's wrong?
So in the video you shot
where you're taking
the medication OxyContin...
Yeah, I--I was taking it
for a--a injury.
And I noticed you--you didn't
actually call it OxyContin.
I was told it was
a public service thing
for chronic pain sufferers
to be more comfortable
taking pain medication.
Every now and then,
I would slip up,
- and I would say OxyContin.
- Well, yeah.
And they would say,
"Don't say that.
Say 'the pain medicine.'"
Did the producer
ask you not to say
- the--the name OxyContin?
- That's right.
He--he didn't want me to say
"opioid" or "opiates" either.
- What'd he ask you to say?
- Uh, "medication."
"Pain--pain medication."
- Pain medication?
- Yeah.
But they told me
when I was done
that I was real natural.
I can't imagine how hard
that would be,
sitting in front of a camera
trying to be normal.
- Oh, no.
- He died a few years ago.
Oh, I hate this gravel.
And was it drug-related?
Oh, yeah, he was oxy-cuted.
Who asked you to participate
in the video
in the first place?
My doctor did,
Dr. Alan Spanos.
Oh, Alan Spanos.
- Dr. Spanos.
He--he prescribed
OxyContin and...
♪ ♪
Yeah, he...
- You all right?
- Uh-huh.
Yeah, yeah.
Uh...
♪ ♪
And who reached out
to you initially?
It was an ad agency
from New York.
And when you were
approached,
was it for a video
to promote OxyContin?
No, they said it was
a public service announcement
for pain management
and general opioid use.
Were you surprised that
a public service announcement
that you asked your patients
to participate in
ended up
being a bait and switch
to promote OxyContin?
I thought the video
was still very useful.
Well, we've been
interviewing your patients,
and some of them
are clearly addicted to drugs.
As you may know, one of them
died of an overdose.
Another one appears
to be well on his way.
15,000 doctors
were sent a video
with you promoting OxyContin.
And it now appears
that these pills
are a lot more dangerous
than that video claims.
Does that bother you?
What I'm here to do
is to cure pain,
and I shall use everything
in my arsenal to do just that.
Pain has been wildly
undertreated in this country,
and opioids have been
unfairly maligned for years.
OxyContin has worked miracles
for my patients
who have suffered for years
and who are now
getting their lives back.
Okay, okay.
So we got a fraudulent
video of people being told
not to discuss the exact drug
that they're in the video
to promote.
Mm-hmm,
should definitely be enough
for Comey to let us keep going.
Unless he's already
made up his mind.
Would you resign
if he shut us down?
- No.
- You?
No.
I'd be pissed, though.
You got another ketchup?
- Yeah.
- Hold on quick.
Hello.
This is Randy Ramseyer.
Uh, hi,
this is Regina Carter.
You--you left a note
at my apartment.
Yes, that was me.
Uh, I'm an assistant
U. S. attorney,
and I was hoping
that I could interview you
regarding a video that you
were in about five years ago.
Okay.
Uh, when--when could we
come see you?
Well, we were hoping
as soon as possible.
We could come by tonight.
- Tonight?
- Yep.
We're just wrapping up
a dinner.
Rick, could you get the check?
And we will, uh--
we'll head on over there.
We'll be over there
in about the next 15, 20.
Listen,
what happened with me
was the pill stopped working
'cause my tolerance grew,
and doctors just kept
doubling my dosage.
I was eventually taking
160 milligrams a day.
Started falling asleep at work,
lost my job,
my car,
then my house.
I had to declare bankruptcy.
I am so sorry to hear that.
How did you--how'd you stop
taking the drug?
I weaned myself off.
Hardest thing I ever did.
But I thought, "If I don't
get off this medicine,
I'll end up dead."
And when you realized
you were addicted,
did you go back to Dr. Spanos
to discuss--
Hell no, I never spoke
to that man ever again.
They used us in that video.
I helped a company
make billions selling drugs.
I mean, we were all pawns,
making people think
the drug was non-addictive.
And I can't help
but feel guilty about that.
Ma'am, you are
not responsible for this.
You are a victim; they lied
to you, they lied to you.
Companies like this, they buy
their way out of trouble.
Black kids selling weed
go to jail for decades.
Well, that's why we're here.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
Is there a restroom
in the lobby?
Yeah.
♪ ♪
Here you go.
Thanks, Peter.
Sure.
♪ ♪
God, it's so cool
that you're a DEA agent.
I still can't believe it.
So, um, you have
your gun on you?
- Mm-hmm.
- Pretty much always.
Where do you keep it?
♪ ♪
I never thought feeling a gun
pressed against my leg
would turned me on.
Most guys are weirded out
by my firearms.
Oh?
They don't wanna date
someone with a "masculine" job.
I research
Senegalese mineral rights
for the state department.
Everybody's job
is more masculine.
I bet you were the hottest
mineralogist in high school.
That's a good use
of mineralogist.
Why did you ask me out?
I think you might be one
of the most strikingly
beautiful women
I have ever seen.
♪ ♪
Good morning.
I don't want to be
too aggressive, but, um,
wanna grab dinner
tomorrow night?
Oh, well, yeah,
I'd--I'd love to, as well,
but I'm--I'm gonna be
leaving town for a few days.
- Oh.
- Okay.
How about
right when I get back?
Yeah, great.
- Coffee?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
Initial consultation's 500.
Then you come in
every 28 days for your refill
for 125.
Do I meet with a doctor
for my refill appointment?
Only if you want to,
or you can just pick up
your prescription.
Um, the doctor is booked
till next Thursday,
so you can fill those at home
if you like.
Is there any way that I can
meet with a doctor today?
I have really bad
shoulder pain.
So does everyone else.
Have a good day.
Hey!
- Hey!
- You piece of shit!
Hey!
Come on!
Don't you fucking move.
Come on.
Have you ever heard
of the crack epidemic?
It was big
in poor neighborhoods
in the 1980s.
Huge portions
of the Black population
were hooked on crack.
I grew up in D. C.
During this time,
and there was this convenience
store across the street
from my grandma's apartment.
And the parking lot
was a warzone.
People selling drugs,
killing each other.
My grandma got mugged
three times.
This was how I grew up, Lucas.
Watching my friends die
from drugs.
If you continue on this path,
you're going to end up
just like them.
Is your grandma okay now?
She's fine.
Thanks for asking.
- I didn't want her money.
- I was...
I was trying to steal
her prescription.
How do you know she had one?
She came out
of the pain clinic.
That's where everyone gets
their Oxy prescriptions.
And what would you
do with it?
There's a girl in my class,
eighth grade.
And she's got this older
brother that makes fake IDs,
so we use it to get
the prescription filled.
Take half
and sell the other half.
How many kids in your school
are on OxyContin?
I don't know.
Maybe half.
♪ ♪
- Now how about here?
- Any pain?
Nope.
If I lift higher,
does that hurt?
Don't feel a thing.
And you--and you feel like
you have full range of motion?
- Yeah.
- Just like before.
You think the drug
lasted 12 hours?
- Well, I didn't time it.
- How about sleep?
Any problems sleeping
through the night?
No, it worked like a charm.
I actually went bowling
last week.
I didn't think I'd ever get
to go bowling again.
I appreciate it, Doc,
Sure about this, Doc?
I'll take you to any steakhouse
in the state.
Uh-uh, I'm sure as can be.
Mmm, look at that pie.
You can't beat the chicken
here at Nancy's.
- What can I get you, Doc?
- Hey, Bo.
You know what I like.
- For you?
- Uh, I'll have the same.
You and your dad close?
Um, not really.
He's a writer and a professor.
Brother writes short stories,
so they're close.
- Mom's a poet.
- Really?
Yeah.
I'm sort of the, uh,
Roger Clinton of the family.
Huh.
Well...
I'm sure they're
very proud of you.
Yeah.
So, um, you ever think
about dating again, or...
- Nah.
- No interest.
Well, you should come to our
weekend seminar in Scottsdale.
Mm.
They're a ton of fun,
and it's all expenses paid,
and a ton of
interesting women there.
Mm-hmm.
Doctors, nurses,
pain specialists.
Russell Portenoy
is gonna speak.
- He is?
- Yeah, he's the main speaker.
You know, when Shelly
was in the hospital,
I read some of his articles,
and, uh,
they really helped.
Gotta say.
Do me a favor
if you think of it.
Uh, mention to him
that, uh, I'm really grateful.
So thank you.
Come to the seminar
in Scottsdale
and tell him yourself.
♪ ♪
Hey, Mom?
Yes, dear?
I think there's something
we should talk about.
Okay.
Uh...
This may be hard
for you to hear, but...
I like girls.
I always have.
Not just as friends.
And I know--I know Dad
is gonna be real upset,
but maybe you could talk to him
and tell him that nothing's
gonna be different.
I'm--I'm still the same person.
I promise I am.
I just...
I can't live like this anymore.
I just wanna be myself.
I'm sorry, dear.
Did you say something to me?
No.
♪ ♪
How much those run you?
I'm ready.
For what?
I want to do it.
I want to move
to Eureka Springs.
♪ Blue, blue,
blue Christmas ♪
Are you kidding me?
I've been feeling
a lot better this past week.
And I realized you were right.
Coal's a job.
It's--it's not a life.
I want my life with you.
♪ You'll be doing
all right... ♪
Your face is so pretty, Bets.
It should never be
covered in soot.
♪ But I'll have a blue,
blue, blue, blue Christmas ♪
♪ ♪
♪ She rides to the sun too ♪
♪ Lights fade
as she casts her spell ♪
♪ ♪
Hey, Bridget.
We heard this was your spot.
Oh, what the fuck?
- Hey, Bridget.
- Great to see you again.
How's your divorce coming?
- It's finalized.
- Want a drink?
Uh, neither of us drink.
Not surprised.
You don't have
to be like this.
We're on the same side.
I'm helping you.
I'm saving you
from wasting your time.
The FDA, Justice, the doctors,
they all want their drugs.
And big pharma will
spend everything they can
to make sure
that they get them.
And this is just gonna
keep going and going
till we're all just one big
pill-popping zombie nation.
Have you seen Purdue's
I Got My Life Back video?
- Sure.
- It's a fraud.
They were told it was a PSA
when they shot it.
And several of those
participants became addicted.
Few of them are dead
or close to it.
You know who'd be
interested in that?
Sarah Miller and Judy Cohen.
Sarah Miller, Judy Cohen.
At the DOJ's office
of consumer litigation.
Well, I thought
they were all conspirators
in the upcoming
zombie apocalypse.
Not everybody.
Now, that was my tip
for the day, boys,
so if you can both
kindly fuck off,
I'd certainly
be better off for it.
Thank you, Bridget.
I'm sorry about your divorce.
I'm at a loss for words.
It--it--it--it almost makes me
want to tear up a little bit,
but I--it--it's just changed
my life for the better.
I'm coming home
with energy to spare.
Just to have the evening
to do things with
was unheard of.
We've been having problems
with Purdue from the get-go.
- Like the label?
- Like the label.
So when Curtis Wright
approved
the original FDA label,
was there internal pushback?
Oh, yeah.
Diane Schnitzler
emailed him that
Purdue's "less addictive"
claims sounded like bullshit.
What was Mr. Wright's response?
He said, "Actually, Diane,
this is literally true."
So Curtis Wright is
the FDA medical review officer
who approves an unprecedented
label for Purdue.
And then he goes
and he works for Purdue.
So do you think there's
quid pro quo with Purdue
to grant such generous wording?
Yeah, well, I get that
it has the appearance
of corruption,
but it's possible there wasn't.
What Curtis Wright did
is the way the industry works.
It's a revolving door
where as soon as people
leave the government,
they go and work for the exact
people they were regulating
for five times the money,
and it's all legal.
What appears to be corruption
is simply how the system works.
Here's an ad, says patient
only needs two pills a day,
but the drug often
didn't last 12 hours.
So how does an ad like this
get through the FDA
approval process?
You'll have to ask
Ronald Reagan.
Does he work
for Purdue now too?
No, but when
he gutted the FDA,
they went from policing
big pharma
to being at their mercy.
39 employees are responsible
for 35,000 promotional items.
How do they grant
proper oversight?
Just give me five minutes.
It works as an honor system.
Drug companies
are supposed to be honest.
I know.
So if a company was being
criminally dishonest
in its promotional marketing,
what would you charge them with
if--if fraud
was too high a bar?
Sarah?
Can you all give us a moment?
If it were me, I'd charge them
with criminal misbranding.
Never heard of that before.
Most people haven't.
It's perfect for this because
you don't have to prove
the misbranding
caused the overdoses
or pin it on an individual,
just that the company
misbranded the drug.
♪ ♪
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I want more hot water.
- More hot water?
- You're already boiling.
I think that's enough.
All right, sweetheart?
You stick your tongue out
at me?
Let me take that.
Oh, I got it.
I got your tongue.
It's pretty good.
Okay.
Shh, shh, shh.
What do you got?
Nothing good.
Main Justice
doesn't like the pharma case.
But wait--wait--
wait a minute, wait a minute.
Do you know why?
Seems pretty early
to pull the plug on me.
I don't have details.
Just that Comey
doesn't like the case.
- All right, got it.
- Thanks.
What's wrong?
DAG wants to shut
my pharma case down.
Isn't that a little fast?
I always knew
there was a chance
we might get shut down
by Main Justice.
It's pretty crappy
if you ask me.
I wouldn't say "crappy"
when we go to Comey.
He doesn't like
that kind of language.
No, that's Ashcroft.
I heard he dressed Comey down
one time for saying "turd."
Comey tells us the case is off,
I'm gonna say,
"Well, that's one big
turd burger, sir."
So, uh, listen,
day after we get back,
I gotta have surgery.
I'm gonna be out for a week.
You okay?
I have prostate cancer.
It took 'em a minute
to find it, but it's fine.
They don't think it spread.
Just, uh--just need a week.
I'm so sorry, Randy.
Just take two weeks off,
or three, as long as you need.
No, I just need a week.
Is it okay if I pray for you?
- Right now?
- I could.
- Oh, no.
- No, it's all right.
It's not really my thing.
Thank you, though.
I just want to see
if I can find some napkins.
Okay, so just
let me handle this.
Even if Comey says we're dead,
it doesn't mean we're dead.
Then what does it mean?
It means we're dead.
Getting some complaints
about your investigation.
That it's out of control.
Well, that's just
not true, sir.
We--we've been doing
this whole thing by the book.
These guys are behaving
like pros.
And this is a very serious
issue that warrants
all the attention
we've been giving it.
Serious?
Well, how serious
does chicken get?
- Chicken?
- Chicken, sir?
Yes, chicken.
What do you--what
do you mean by chicken?
Do you mean, like,
chicken the food
or chicken you're scared?
Like you--you're a chicken?
Chicken, the food.
Why are you investigating
the chicken guy?
Colonel Sanders?
No, Frank Perdue.
- Oh, no, sir.
- No, no, no, no.
Uh, we are not investigating
Perdue Farms.
We are investigating
Purdue Pharma.
It's--it's spelled
differently, I think.
Yeah, it's spelled with a
"U" instead of an "E."
Yeah, Purdue Pharma.
No, it's the company
that manufactures OxyContin.
It's not the--the, um--
it's not the chicken people.
Well, my staff must have
been misinformed.
Well, perhaps whoever's
complaining about us
is trying to get you
off our track, sir.
And for good reason.
It's early days.
We already have
substantial leads.
Manipulative advertising,
false claims about addiction,
overdoses are skyrocketing
while Purdue continues to lie
about the drug's safety
to doctors,
to patients, and the FDA.
We have a major case here.
♪ ♪
Well, then go
make your case.
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Can you feel it, baby? ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ I can too ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ I'm gonna swing,
come on, swing ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Come on, swing,
c-come on, swing ♪
Hey, can I offer you
a complementary OxyContin
bucket hat?
Uh, no.
Maybe one of
our compact discs?
- No, thanks.
- All right.
- Hey, well, enjoy your day.
- Okay, thanks.
Dr. Finnix, so glad
you could make it.
- Thanks.
- Hell of a spread, right?
Oh, you bet.
I wasn't lying to you.
No, you weren't.
Um, I wanted to introduce you
to Dr. Russell Portenoy.
- Pleasure to meet you.
- Oh, no.
The honor's all mine.
Believe me.
You're very kind.
Uh...
I feel a little silly,
to be honest with you,
but I actually brought
your book down
and I wonder
if you'd sign it for me
over the weekend
if you have a chance.
- Are you kidding?
- It'd be my honor.
- All right, great.
- Great.
Well, look, don't let us get
between you and the food.
- Don't miss out on that lobster.
- All right, Billy.
And, uh,
we'll see you shortly.
- We're just over here.
- All right.
All right, Doc.
We're honored
that you'd take a break
from your busy schedules
to spend the weekend with us,
and--as well as--
the country's leading
independent pain organizations.
We have representatives from
the American Pain Foundation,
the National Foundation
for the Treatment of Pain,
American Chronic
Pain Association,
the American Pain Society,
and the American Academy
of Pain Medicine.
But to start us off,
we wanna begin
with the foremost
pain specialist in the country.
He is co-chief of the Pain
and Palliative care Service
at Sloan-Kettering,
Dr. Russell Portenoy.
This is truly
a special moment
in the history of pain care.
Hospitals, doctors,
think tanks, and even the FDA
are rethinking the very nature
of pain treatment.
And what we've learned is
that opioids, certain kinds,
are not nearly as addictive
as they have been perceived.
Narcotics can be abused
and are not appropriate
in all instances.
But when properly
prescribed by doctors,
they almost never lead
to addiction.
In most immediate-release
opioids,
blood plasma levels spike
between euphoria and pain.
But OxyContin's
time-release system
causes blood plasma levels
to have
fewer peaks and valleys,
creating a plateau effect,
which results in less euphoria
and less potential for abuse.
And did--did doctors attend
these weekend seminars?
Yes, many of them did.
This is Dr. Samuel Finnix.
Runs a patient care practice
in Appalachia.
And, Drea here, we stole
from Johnson and Johnson
and she, uh,
she runs the South.
Covers multiple
Southern territories for us.
It's an honor to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
I'm from a small town
in Alabama,
so I know how important
the local doctor is.
Yeah.
Have you been prescribing
OxyContin to your miners?
To a few, yeah.
Yeah, it's been--
it's been effective.
And what occurred
at these events?
Doctors were often co-opted
by Purdue Pharma.
You should do a talk
with Dr. Finnix.
I bet people would love
to hear about his patients.
Great idea.
Yeah, well, what do you think?
No, I-I can't really
get up and speak
in front of people.
Oh, please.
You're far more impressive.
You're on the front lines.
Just think how incredible
it would be
if the story of a coal town
could help change lives
all over the country.
- Absolutely.
- And I mean, it'd be easy.
You know, I'd be asking you
the questions
so you don't have
to embellish anything.
Just, uh, tell people
what you're seeing.
It'd be wonderful
for these city boys
to see how us country folks
get things done.
- Yeah.
- Well, uh, sure.
Okay, I guess.
You're gonna ask me
the questions?
- Absolutely.
- I'll be right with you.
- All right, well.
- See how that goes.
So, uh, Dr. Samuel Finnix,
tell us, what kind of ailments
do your patients
typically have?
Many of my patients
are miners,
so I see back injuries,
shoulder lacerations,
broken hands, things like that.
And you would say,
in your experience,
pain is part of everyday life
in the mines?
- Yes, it is.
- Yes.
I-I have, um, uh,
firsthand experience of pain.
My father was diagnosed
with a rare form of cancer.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Which he survived,
but watching him
suffer through that
was one of the--the hardest
things that I've been through.
You also have
firsthand experience
with that kind of pain, right?
I do, yeah.
Uh, my wife had cancer, um,
and, uh, well, she passed away;
she didn't make it.
I'm so sorry.
Purdue's drug, MS Contin,
was very helpful to her
in her final days, wasn't it?
- It was.
- It was--it was helpful.
That's why I wanted
to try OxyContin
on my patients because, uh,
I don't want them to suffer.
If there's a drug out there
that can help them,
well, then I-I want to try.
And the patients are wanting
to try it, too, right?
Heck yeah, they are.
I know most people don't,
you know,
they don't think about us
up there in the mountains.
Uh, but these people,
you know,
when this country needed
to build airplanes,
uh, during World War II
overnight,
where--where do you think
that steel came from?
The bridges we drive across,
the high rises you live in,
stadiums
where we all watch football,
that's all--that's steel.
And steel comes from coal.
Um, I'm probably
talking too much.
Am I talking too much?
No, please, please.
And who do you think digs
that coal out of the--
out of the mountains
in the hollows?
My patients do.
It's dangerous work, and...
they risk their lives every day
to keeps the lights on
in places like this.
To keep the lights on
in the big cities.
Keep the lights on
in your fine homes.
And, uh, they carry the burden
of building this nation
on their backs,
and they deserve to do it
without pain.
So if this drug can help
these good folks
have a better life
and feed their families,
well, then Purdue Pharma
is doing these people,
my people, a great service,
so...
God bless them for it.
- Were you nervous?
- Yeah.
Oh, well,
you didn't look nervous.
- You were incredible.
- Would you excuse me?
You were
absolutely incredible.
I've been to hundreds
of these, and seriously,
I've never been so moved.
- Oh, thank you.
- Really appreciate it.
- Hey, Daniel.
- Do you mind if I steal
the star of the weekend
for just a few minutes?
- Of course not--thank you.
- Nice talking to you.
Nice talking to you.
I have to tell you,
you spoke for the people
that don't often
get a voice in this country.
Well, look, thanks
for getting me up there.
Oh, it was beautiful.
You know, Purdue
has a speaker's bureau.
They'd be lucky to have you.
Is this okay?
Yeah.
What's that?
Oh, we pay speakers
to go to events
like this around the country.
They get $500 to $3,000
for a speech.
Those speakers get paid?
- Oh, yeah.
- It's not a secret.
You should think about it.
You were great up there.
That guy's amazing.
- Mm.
- Yeah.
He's, uh--he's really special.
And I'm sorry about your dad.
Is he okay now?
Yeah, I, uh...
I made that up.
My, uh--my dad
never had cancer.
Wow.
This is the first time
that I've ever wanted
to fuck you.
Huh.
You, uh--you want to do
something about that?
Oh, oh, William,
I don't think so.
But just because
this is the first time
doesn't mean
that it's the last.
♪ ♪
Once a month, you could have
a fun weekend for yourself
and you'd get to see
my big smile
if it wouldn't
bother you too much.
Oh, I don't think
seeing your smile
would bother anyone.
I thought you said
it was working.
It was.
I'll be right back.
There are many cases
where a higher dose
loses its effectiveness
fairly quickly
because the patient
develops a tolerance.
♪ ♪
This makes the user
increase their dose again
at a fast rate.
And is that dangerous?
Absolutely.
It's one of the reasons
why overdose rates
are so much higher
on OxyContin.
These are
the new numbers,
and you'll see
a significant difference
from the initial
rollout figures.
Better.
Really great job, Richie.
That's really great.
Yes, yes, there's
been a definite improvement
in the sales figures.
We also found doctors who
attended the weekend seminars
have been writing
twice as many prescriptions
as doctors who don't.
Then we should throw
more weekend seminars.
But, um, more significantly,
doubling the dose
not only solved
the breakthrough pain issue,
it increased our bottom line,
since manufacturing
a 20 milligram or 40 milligram
is almost the same cost
as a 10 milligram.
This is bringing in revenue
at a much faster rate
than projected.
There's a scenario
I've been concerned about.
And what is that,
my dear cousin?
Well, what happens if
someone has breakthrough pain
and they're already
at 40 milligrams?
The sales reports from last
quarter were terrific,
so much so that I am
pleased to announce
that we will be launching
a brand-new product.
Ladies and gentlemen, it is
time to double the dose again
as I present to you
the 80-milligram pill.
Whoo!
♪ ♪
♪ She's my baby ♪
♪ She belongs to me ♪
♪ But yesterday
she walked home all alone ♪
♪ Everybody else
looks at my baby ♪
♪ Then they wander over to me ♪
♪ But baby's
feelin' bad today ♪
♪ She said she's thinkin'
of goin' away ♪
♪ And I'm cryin' ♪
♪ And my body's flyin' ♪
♪ But I remember you ♪
♪ She's my baby ♪
♪ Ain't that something? ♪
♪ But I know ♪
♪ She belong--
she belongs to you ♪
♪ ♪