Good morning, sweetheart.
Good night. I love you.
Mary?
Mary, please look at me.
I don't get...
I can't understand
why you came back and went away again.
Why would you?
I'm doing it all exactly
the same way it was that day.
The same song, the same places,
the church, the supermarket,
the same fruit in your shake,
the same burrito,
but it isn't working.
I know it was this place.
It was the first night we were here
and I know it was this place
because you woke up, Mary.
We spoke.
And we laughed.
And we...
For three hours you were awake,
and I don't know why
you went back to sleep.
Is it a test?
Can you look at me?
Just give a small sign that you're here?
Oh, this isn't fair.
You can't give that to me
and take it away again.
So you...
You need to look at me now, Mary, okay?
Look at me.
Look at me!
Please pull over
to the waiting area.
Visitors coming through.
We'll let you all through in five minutes.
Please pull over to the waiting area.
Excuse me, sir.
My wife has an appointment. We need to--
We'll let you go as soon as we can, sir.
Let's go!
Please pull over.
Visitors coming through.
Please pull over. Visitors coming through.
Think they could invest
in a bigger bridge, huh?
- Come on in.
- Visitors coming through.
That's true, Matt,
but then the town
would lose its authenticity.
- What's happening?
- Get back in your car, sir.
- Can I--
- We have runners. We have runners.
Go, baby, go!
Hey!
TECH". Any allergies?
No allergies, but she has
an adverse reaction to amoxicillin.
TECH". And the reason for the scan?
I was hoping to find out if there's been
any improvement in brain function.
Anything in her behavior
to suggest a change?
I'd just like to compare her results
to her last scan, please.
You can send them
to our doctor in New York.
You got it.
Can you tell me how much the co-pay is?
You'd have to talk to billing.
Will she feel it?
I don't know.
Sir, personnel only once the scan starts.
Someone will come get you
when she's through.
Yeah, okay.
Oh, oh!
Shit! Shit!
Fuck!
Mr. Jamison!
Would you mind coming back inside?
- Why?
- We'd like to discuss the results.
I told you to send
the results to our doctor.
I'm not paying for any more--
There's no charge, sir.
But if you could please
just come on back in.
It's important.
Mr. Jamison.
Charlie Simpson. How are y'all today?
I'm good, thanks.
Sorry, are you a doctor?
Uh, no, sir, lam not.
If you wouldn't mind taking a look at this
and signing it, y'all can be on your way.
Waiver of liability? I don't...
Sorry, I don't...
They said this was about Mary's results.
- Is there a problem?
- Yes, sir, there is.
You failed to disclose
your wife's condition.
If you had, we would have
never administered the contrast dye.
I told you about her condition.
I answered all the nurse's questions.
You told us she was
in a persistent vegetative state.
You did not tell us that she was pregnant.
Our blood draw showed
HCG levels well over 1,000.
We couldn't have children.
I never thought...
You're pregnant?
Well, congratulations.
Now if you'll please
just sign the release.
What is this?
It indemnifies the imaging center
in the event that the pregnancy
is no longer viable.
Why wouldn't it be viable?
Because your wife is a 40-year-old woman
in what amounts to a coma.
You're looking at close to a 90% chance
of her miscarrying.
That's why we ask for consent
before we administer an MRI.
But our tech did not ask
for it in this case, sir,
because your wife
is not capable of giving consent.
And if she's not capable
of giving her consent for a test,
she cannot give her consent for anything.
You take my meaning?
No.
She was awake.
She was awake when we...
I would never do that.
Of course you wouldn't.
Just like you wouldn't want to
have to say that under oath
if you didn't have to.
Now please sign the release.
I want my co-pay back.
I knew it!
Ten years we tried. Ten years and nothing.
And in one night... One night!
It's that place.
That's why you woke up, isn't it?
So this could happen.
Don't you worry about that 90% business.
Once we're back across that bridge,
you'll be fine.
You and the baby.
Oh, poor guy-
Hey there. You okay?
I've been better.
Anything I can do to help?
Yeah. Just conked out on me.
I think it might be the radiator.
Yeah. I tried to call for a tow,
but there's no reception out here.
Well, let me try.
Dropped it in the toilet.
Ah, I've lost two that way.
Well, we're just
a couple of miles out of town.
I can give you a ride.
Is that your wristband?
You live there? In Miracle?
Yes.
Me and my wife, Mary.
She okay?
Getting better all the time.
Oh, hey.
What's your name?
Is that your son?
I'm sorry.
We, we have to get in.
Get his wristband, son.
Careful, don't rip it.
I can't get it off.
Stand over here, God damn it.
We have to get in.
All right, come on. Door, get in.
Matt.
Matt, we have to hurry.
You have to get us back in.
Mary?
He won't last out here.
I'm gonna lose the baby, Matt.
Please, honey.
Get us back in.
I will.
Mary?
It's okay, honey.
I heard you.
We'll go right now.
No.
No!
Hey!
God damn it!
Don't worry, sweetheart. I heard you.
We're almost home. Almost home.
Hey!
Friend.
Where are you coming in from?
Shit, are you hurt?
Do you want to get in?
I know all the ways.
Back door, my friend.
- How much money you got?
- We live here.
Oh...
Well, a thousand pardons, sir.
Almost home, sweetheart.
"Now climbeth Tamora Olympus' top,
"safe out of fortune's shot."
Hello. Excuse me.
This access is for park personnel only.
I'm afraid I'm gonna have to ask you
to return to camp.
We live in the park.
We were attacked, me and my wife.
A man and his son, they were in a red car.
Would you like to report this
to the local sheriff's office, sir?
I'd like to report it to you.
Sorry, but we got no jurisdiction
if you're not in the park.
We live in the park. Please just let us in
so I can get my wife home.
- The longer she's--
- I cannot let you cross
without a valid ID, reservation,
or a wristband.
They stole our wristbands.
We live on Scarborough Street.
I work at the Sacred Mission
with Reverend Massey.
We shop at the Safeway on Amarillo.
We attend the Jarden community pool
every Sunday and Wednesday.
My sister just moved here,
but I haven't memorized her number
and my phone fell in a toilet.
Please.
We live here.
Y'all need to go to the visitors' center,
get yourselves
some replacement bands, okay?
Yes, sir.
Yeah, thank you.
- God bless you.
- He does every day.
The visitor wristband
is your ticket into Miracle.
Visitors must wear their wristband
at all times.
Spell your name again for me.
J-A-M-I-S-O-N.
Is this gonna take much longer?
We got a wedding in town.
You said it was a sanctuary pass?
Yes, Reverend Massey sponsored us,
of Sacred Mission.
My sister just moved here.
Um, could she sponsor us?
What's her name?
- Nora Durst.
- Durst.
Excuse me. Can you help us?
Could you just wait a minute?
May I?
- Hello?
- Kevin?
Oh, thank God. Um, Mary and I...
They won't let us back into town.
We're at the visitors' center.
- Our wristbands were stolen--
- Jesus Christ, man.
- Step aside.
- And now they won't give us any new ones.
- I'm on the phone.
- I don't care.
Sir, unless they've been here
for six months, I can't help you.
Now, you hear that? She can't help you.
Now step aside, man.
Please, will you mind your own business?
No, I did my business.
I've got my documents and you don't.
So why don't you just
roll her on out of here
'cause she doesn't look like
she's in a rush to get anywhere.
- You've got your documents?
- That's right.
- You've got your documents.
- Yes.
Let's see them, huh?
Welcome to Miracle National Park...
She pretending?
No, she's not pretending.
He will die.
What?
She says if you don't get her back inside,
he will die.
Who?
RANGER". Matt and Mary Jamison.
Jesus, Matt. Are you okay?
Yeah.
Thank you.
You zip-tied him?
Man got a busted hand.
Works at the church.
What, you scared
he gonna baptize you or something?
Give me the clippers.
This is John.
He's gonna help you and Mary.
Yes, we met.
Mmm-hmm.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You should get it looked at
in case it needs to be set.
Erika will take care of him
once we get back into town.
My wife's a doctor.
I'll be fine. Thank you.
I'm sorry about your daughter.
I've been handing out
fliers at the church.
Appreciate it.
Try to keep it elevated.
I always do.
I wish I could say this never happens,
but every man for himself out there.
It can get rough.
What were y'all doing in Austin?
Just getting a test, a scan for Mary.
- Everything okay?
- Yes, thank you.
We do it every six months or so
to see if there's been
any change in her condition.
- Was there?
- Sorry?
Any change in her condition.
No.
Except for the pregnant part.
The what?
You... You went through Mary's bag?
It fell out.
One of the rangers picked it up.
- Matt, what's he talking about?
- Please, this is very complicated.
JOHN". It is complicated.
Yes, and we, you know...
They said the pregnancy is high risk,
so the longer we're out here...
I need to get Mary back into town now.
Why?
What?
Why do you need to get
Mary back into town now?
John, he's been attacked.
Yes, and I'm trying to help,
but I'm not getting the whole story.
Did she wake up?
You brought her here,
all the way to Miracle, Texas,
and she woke up, right?
And while she was awake, you made love.
And then, shit,
she went right back to this.
That the story you gonna tell?
The only story you can tell?
'Cause it's not true.
Because that doesn't happen here.
People don't get healed.
My wife lost her hearing a long time ago,
and it's still lost.
So, what, God likes your wife
better than mine?
Your friend Kevin here
asked me to help you out.
I owe him, so I will.
But you got to tell me the truth.
The truth?
In about five months,
when your wife starts to show,
and everybody knows she's pregnant,
you need to say that you were sad
and lonely and confused.
And that you are very sorry
for what you did
because you knew it was wrong.
- Jesus, John--
- That's the truth.
Right?
Yes.
She never woke up.
Okay.
Well, let's get you home.
What happened to you?
Excuse me?
I know your daughter is missing
and that's terrible, I'm sorry,
but you were like this before that.
You're angry at this place.
What happened to you?
You know what?
I don't think I'm gonna be able
to get those wristbands after all.
- Hey, come on. Hey, John. Hey!
What the fuck was that, Matt?
How much money do you have?
- What?
- I'm gonna need money.
How much do you have?
Me and Nora
are gonna talk to the officers.
- Now, Kevin. I need to get her back now.
- Okay, okay.
I got that. Thank you.
- Get her on the bridge.
- I've got her.
- Coming through.
- We'll be fine, Kevin.
I'll get us back in.
You'll be fine.
You and the baby.
Excuse me, um...
Excuse me.
Excuse me, um, ladies.
I'm looking for a tall man
with a samurai bun.
Excuse me, gentlemen, um...
Look at him.
You beat that little grubworm
of yours?
- Hey, what you looking at?
- Suck on that!
Punk!
You want to free him?
What?
Do you want to free him?
Look over here!
Yes, of course.
Then take his place.
Yeah! Go!
- Get up there.
- Yeah!
Yeah, I didn't think so.
Yeah, get up there.
Hey!
Y'all okay?
Yes, thanks.
I'm looking for a tall man
with a samurai bun on his head.
Swedish guy?
Yes, I think so.
Name's Elmer or something.
Trailer, big green stripe.
- Thank you, sir.
- Yep.
Elmer?
- Not Elmer, Almer.
- What?
Almer. Fucking Almer!
I need your help to get in.
Hey-
Friend, how much money you got?
How much does it cost for me and my wife?
Can she get out of the chair?
No.
Uh...
$1,000.
Okay, I have about just over 400 here.
- I'll get you the rest when we're in town.
- Come on, friend.
You want fair deal, $1,000.
No, I live there.
I can pay you back, I promise.
Friend, I'm not going anywhere.
Come find me when you have the money.
No, it has to be now. We have to go now.
My wife is pregnant.
- She needs care.
- She's pregnant?
Can you help me? Almer, please.
Yes.
For $1,000.
It's all right.
I'll find a way.
He'll show us a way.
Please.
MATT". Excuse me, ma'am.
Is this your cross?
Yes, sir.
I'm Reverend Matthew Jamison.
This is my wife, Mary.
Sandy.
Sandy. I'm sorry to bother you.
May I have a moment of your time?
I have a friend I met
doing some missionary work years ago.
He preaches at a small church
across the bridge there.
And he's been trying for years
to get me to come out and visit him,
so I decided to take my friend up
on his offer and come here to Jarden.
The plan was to stay for about a week.
We've been here for three months now.
How?
Um, religious exemption.
They gave Mary and I wristbands
that said "Sanctuary" on them.
This morning, a man attacked us
and took those wristbands.
And now they will not let us back in.
Sandy, I'm asking for your help.
I'm calling upon your sense
of community and charity.
Mary and I need some money so that I can--
How much?
$500.
I know that's an extraordinary
amount of money,
but I give you my word as a Christian,
I will pay you back.
What denomination?
20s. It's whatever you can--
No, no, you're a reverend.
What denomination?
Episcopalian.
- Why?
My father was a reverend,
I was raised in the faith,
but I welcome all beliefs into my church.
Where'd you go to seminary?
Berkeley Divinity.
- Where's that?
- Connecticut.
What's your favorite book?
Of the Bible. You got a favorite book?
Job.
What's his wife's name?
She isn't named.
And she speaks only once.
"Does thou still retain thine integrity?
Curse God and die."
Wait right here.
Good thing I didn't say Lutheran.
This is Reggie.
Hello.
I'm Matt Jamison. This is my wife, Mary.
- You'll do it?
- I haven't asked him yet.
Do what?
You want $500?
- Yes.
- Okay.
You got to hit him just once,
but as hard as you can, with this.
And he has to say it.
Yeah, when you hit him,
you got to say, "Brian."
Who's Brian?
What the fuck do you care?
I don't understand
why you want me to do this.
Look, you're a bona fide man of God.
If you do this, it counts.
You're a man of God, right?
Yes.
Well, you want your fucking money or not?
Go on, shoo! You sick fucks. Go on.
- Come on, hit him hard.
- And say "Brian."
I want my money first.
You get paid when you do your job.
Hit him. Hard.
- Hit him! Hit him!
- Go on.
- Go on, 'mt mm. Come on.
- Hit him!
Hit him! Hit him!
- Hit him like you mean it.
- Hit him!
- Come on, no.
- What?
- No. Hit him hard.
- That's as hard as I can.
- Come on, you're holding back.
- You didn't say it.
- I can't, my thumb.
- You're holding back.
- I did not.
- Bullshit.
- No.
- Why won't he say it?
- Come on, hit him harder.
- What? I hit him.
- No, not hard... Not hard enough.
- We had an agreement.
We had an agreement that
you'd hit as hard as you could.
- He's not gonna do it.
- Honey, you want a shot at it?
I bet you can hit harder.
Want to get out here and swing? Come on.
Go, hard.
Why won't he say it?
He's not gonna do it.
Brian!
Was that hard enough
or do I need another oar?
You are short $60.
Okay, my friend.
We are good to go.
Are you claustrophobic?
Am I what?
How far?
Just a couple minutes.
There's a gate on the other end.
Sometimes they lock with chain.
Here.
You're not coming?
You pay for me to show you,
not to hold your hand, friend.
Come find me
when they throw you out again.
What do you think, Mary?
Lighten our darkness,
we beseech thee, O Lord,
and by thy great mercy
defend us from all perils
and dangers of this night.
For the love of thy only son,
our savior, Jesus Christ.
Amen.
Well, at least we're out of the rain.
All that money for pointing us to a drain
and a pair of bolt cutters.
I could... I need to...
Okay, I got it.
I got it.
Yes!
Oh, don't worry, Mary. I've cut it.
I just had to...
Yes!
God!
No, no, no!
No!
MEW-
You're okay.
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
We'll leave when it stops raining.
Get the fuck out!
Now!
Matt!
Matt Jamison!
Nora?
Hey.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Where's her chair?
- We lost it.
Thanks for coming.
We pushed out the back seat
a little for air.
- Get in.
- They're searching trunks.
They won't search ours.
What's happening?
There was an anonymous tip
that those missing girls
were spotted out here in the encampment.
You'?
It was anonymous, Matt.
Now get in the trunk.
There.
- You good'?
- Let them through. Here comes the truck.
All right, let's go. Forget it.
Move it.
Remember that train in Frankfurt?
You and me crammed
into a single sleeper berth.
I had to hold you
so you wouldn't fall out.
You thought it was romantic.
"Do Yeats," you said.
And I said, "I only did Yeats
to get you to fall in love with me.
"I don't need poetry anymore."
And you said, "You still need it."
"Though I am old with wandering
Through hollow lands and hilly lands,
"I will find out where she has gone
"And kiss her lips and take her hands
"And walk among long, dappled grass
"And pluck till time and times are done
"The silver apples of the moon
The golden apples of the sun"
Sir?
There's an accident.
Goddamn goats.
He's dead.
We have to go. Help me.
It's mine.
What are you doing?
Will you take care of her?
What are you talking about?
- We have to get back in the car.
- I shouldn't have to hide, Nora.
Will you take care of her
just for a little while?
God damn it, Matt. Seriously?
Please?
What's going on?
Where are you gonna be?
Not far.
I love you. Good night.
What happened?
He's not coming with us.
Get in the car.
Who the fuck is that?
My wife woke up
the first night we arrived in your town.
It's the only time in over three years
she's talked to me.
And there may be no way to prove it,
but it happened,
and I will never say it didn't.
I don't want your wristband.
Mary found hers,
so she's back where she belongs,
and I have no doubt
that she'll wake up again soon.
And when she does, I'm going to come back
and you and I will have a talk.
This boy needs help.
His father's dead.
Okay.
Okay what?
I want to free him.
Why?
'Cause it's my turn.
English - SDH