Go on, have another one.
Thanks, Mrs. Bell.
Although, you…
you and your bikie mates,
you're… you're not exactly
law-abiding citizens.
Mate, the Rebels
have heaps of laws.
And I know, because I enforce them.
It's a fine couple of boys
you've raised here.
Yeah, we've done our best
for them.
You know, Eli's letters,
they were the best thing about my lag.
Didn't care about my bad reputation,
didn't judge.
Anyway, mate, that's why I was droppin' by
to give you this.
- Really?
- Yeah, go on.
Apologies
for the wrappin', mate.
Us bikies aren't known
for our gift wrappin'.
You always said in your letters
that you wanted to be a writer,
so this is for your journalizing.
Well, go on, mate,
open it up, give it a crack.
Say something into it.
Testing, testing, one, two, three.
Yeah.
There you go, mate.
You'll be a journo in no time.
Well, that's his dream.
It's not really easy.
I mean, you gotta get a cadetship
or write a story
no one's even heard of before.
You know what, mate,
I've got stacks of those.
I've already done my time,
they can't lock me up for that shit again.
What do you wanna know?
♪ Ha, ha, ha… ♪
The problem
with being a notorious criminal
is that no one will leave you alone.
The cops are keen to look for themselves,
but generally they prefer…
…a pub on the Condamine River
outside Warwick.
So we get there,
it's chockers with Bandidos outta Sydney
actin' like they own the place.
♪ Here come the woman ♪
♪ With the look in her eye… ♪
Here you go, sweetheart, that's for you.
♪ Raised on leather ♪
♪ With flesh on the mind ♪
♪ Words are weapons ♪
♪ Sharper than knives ♪
♪ Makes you wonder
How the other half die ♪
♪ Other half die… ♪
It's always some mob
from over the border that brings it on…
I wake up on the deck
covered in blood and broken furniture,
tryin' to get back on my feet
when a big fat bloke comes flyin' out…
…one of ours. So I grab 'im by the neck
and say, "Whose side are you on?"
♪ Here come the man ♪
♪ With the look in his eye ♪
♪ Fed on nothin' ♪
♪ But full of pride ♪
♪ Look at them go, look at them kick ♪
♪ Makes you wonder
How the other half live… ♪
He says, "I'm not on anyone's side.
I own the fuckin' pub
and you're all banned for life."
♪ Devil inside ♪
♪ The devil inside ♪
♪ Every single one of us
The devil inside ♪
♪ Devil inside ♪
♪ Every single one of us
The devil inside ♪
♪ Oh yeah ♪
What?
Mm, is that Alex Bermuda?
Who wants to know?
This is Brian Robertson
from The Courier-Mail.
I've got this kid
sitting opposite me, Eli Bell.
Says you told 'im your life story.
Yeah, that sounds like somethin' I'd do.
So you better print
every fuckin' word of it.
Have you seen how long it is?
This kid thinks
he's Brisbane's answer to Leo Tolstoy.
And how the fuck do you know
that he's not?
So what do you think Mr. Bermuda's plans
are now that he's outta prison?
Well, um, my brother Gus, he wants 'im
to try and get into some charity work.
Alex says he's got some experience
collecting cash.
I have no doubt he does.
So, how much do you want for this?
I dunno. What do you usually pay?
I mean, 'cause-- 'cause
what I really want is a job.
Doing what?
Assistant crime reporter.
Dream on, mate.
Are you even outta school?
That's never gonna happen.
But I could use you to write color pieces.
What are color pieces?
Oh, it's basically the descriptive stuff
we print up to, uh, make up the space.
Real estate blurbs, Toowoomba flower show,
best grandma competition.
Not everyone can do it, but trust me…
…you're a natural.
Okay.
All right, I will tell Shirley
to put you on a starting wage.
All right.
- Welcome to the team.
- Thanks.
Everybody, this is Eli Bell.
He wants your job.
Fuck off.
…which makes 223,000 raised so far,
but that's still below our target.
Thank you all so much for your time.
Hi. Thank you so much.
Very nice to meet you.
Oh, fuck.
- Ow!
- You all right?
Yep, I'm okay.
Oh!
All right.
Try that.
Uh, yeah, good. Fuck!
Put it-- Put it in neutral, eh?
Fuckin' 'ell.
Try it now.
Hey!
- Oi, guess what?
- What?
- I got the job.
- How good's that?
- What did I tell you?
Oh, I'm a proper journalist now.
Wow. Oh, Eli, I'm so proud of you, mate.
That's incredible.
- Oi, guess what?
- What?
Got the bloody job.
- Really? Good job!
- Thanks.
He's a journalist. Eh?
Now, we can talk
about that 50 bucks you owe me.
- How about you start workin'?
- I'm fixin' the car, mate.
-Did you get it goin'?
-She's hummin' like a tuna patty.
It's so clean now.
Smooth ride. That's my fella.
- I gotta go.
- All right.
-You're a champion, mate.
-Thanks, Dad.
Whoa. Whoa.
- Congratulations.
- G'day, mate.
My son got a job as a journalist.
Here we go.
Oh.
Our Man in Havana. Have you read this?
Yeah, yeah, sad to see that one go.
It's my favorite Graham Greene.
-Ah, Jane Austen.
-Yeah.
-She's comin' back into fashion.
-Mm. Yeah.
"The gentleman
that takes no pleasure from a good novel
must be intolerably stupid."
I'll take all these. Uh…
Eh?
Twenty bucks for the lot?
Thanks, boys. Thank you, yep.
Wow.
You look happy.
Yeah, well, he's gonna take a dozen boxes,
and he wants to pay me money
to look after the shop
three days a week. Me!
-Wow.
-Yeah.
What about your agoraphobia?
You know, with all those customers.
Oh ho.
Frankie, it's a bookshop in Darra.
I don't think
I'll be fightin' off the crowds.
But yeah, I'll be bringin' in some money
and, uh, ya know,
either way, I… I reckon I owe you,
Frankie.
I owe you too.
You did a pretty good job with those boys
all that time I was inside.
Not really, but, uh, thanks.
And I appreciate you keeping
off the bottle since I moved in.
I know you're making an effort.
You know, the truth is, I…
I don't really miss it that much.
But, uh, I think havin'
the boys and… and you here just…
just calms me down a bit.
But don't worry…
…I'll manage without youse.
I-- I'm not developing a dependency
or anything, just…
It just feels nice.
Bloody good day, though, eh? What a day!
Cracker.
Good work
with that bank info from Vanuatu.
But keep the rest of it under your hat,
these walls have ears.
Caitlyn.
Eli? What the hell?
I did as you said, gave Brian Robertson
an, uh, article he couldn't refuse.
Oh my God, high five.
-What was the article?
-Um, "Alex Bermuda, My Life in Crime."
-That was you?
-Yeah.
Well, I mean, Dave Cullen rewrote it,
but it was based
off of my initial interview.
Yeah, typical. Well, I hope
they're at least paying you properly.
Um, they got me on a starter salary.
How much is that?
I dunno. Didn't ask.
Well, if it's less than 200 a week,
ask for a pay raise.
Okay. How was Vanuatu?
Who said I was in Vanuatu?
Uh, I overheard Brian.
Yeah, it was fine.
Good place for a holiday.
Well, I'll see you around, eh?
Uh…
What on earth are you doin'?
Just tryin' to
get into some shape, ya know?
Mm…
- Are you doin' this for Mum?
- Mm. No. No.
Well, I dunno, maybe.
Lyle was, uh,
pretty muscular, yeah?
Yeah, he was a boxer once.
Yeah, women love muscular arms.
I dunno why. I--
I don't have much in the arms department.
Yeah, look, I don't think Mum
left you just because of the arms.
Just sayin'.
No, you're right.
Plenty of other stuff to…
…make up for.
You stood up to Teddy, so that's a plus.
- Well, not really.
- You were good, Dad.
I mean, you didn't freak out
like you normally do.
I like it when you call me Dad.
You reckon she still thinks Lyle's alive?
No, she knows Lyle's
not comin' back, Dad.
Nice day. Yeah.
Yeah. Ah, it's pretty good.
Wha!
- If you love someone, right…
- Yeah.
…I think you've just gotta do things
that you normally wouldn't do.
-Like what?
-I dunno, stuff that terrifies you.
Like goin' to the supermarket or…
-Yeah.
-…something.
You've obviously given this some thought.
You got your eye on someone at work, mate?
There's this one person.
But, um, nah, she's outta my league.
Yeah, well, you know, I thought
that at the start with me and your mum,
but, ya know,
you never know until you ask.
And now to a story
of local champions.
Listeners may remember
a young lady named Shelly Huffman,
whose life was changed
by an anonymous gift of $50,000.
There seems to be no stopping
this young lady…
Eli? Robert? Shelly's on the radio.
…who have so far raised
more than $200,000
for disabled schoolchildren statewide.
The pair have now been included
in this year's list
of Queensland Champions.
-In recognition of exceptional service.
-Oh my God.
Philanthropist and owner…
- Oh my God.
- …of Atlas Prosthetics, Tytus Broz, says…
Oh my God, Gus is gonna be
a Queensland Champion!
-The award ceremony…
-Shush! Shush. Everyone shush.
…will be held
in Brisbane City Hall's concert hall.
What? There's a ceremony?
…Prime Minister Bob Hawke
is facing ongoing scrutiny days after…
Okay, that's it.
No arguments, we're going.
Oh yeah, look, I… I d-- I don't need to go
if there's not enough tickets.
-Uh, you're coming, Robert.
-Okay.
- And what are you grinning at?
- Nothin'.
How did I not know about this?
This is, uh, front-page news.
Aren't you supposed to be a news reporter?
All right, Dave Cullen,
I want you to follow up
on the legless corpse
they found at Indooroopilly.
Is it the drug wars
or is it something else?
Caitlyn, you're still
on the special investigation we discussed?
Yeah? All right, Carl,
you're gonna tag team with Sam
on the state of the National Party.
Now, as I see it,
there are two parts to that story.
Is Queensland going down the toilet,
and how does Mike Ahern plan
to get us out of the toilet.
So, what else have we got?
Ooh, does anyone wanna write
on the annual
Queensland Champions wankfest?
-Um, actually, I--
-Eli, you're not even supposed to be here.
No, I know.
It's just that my brother's on the list--
Why, what did he do?
Pogo-stick to Cape York?
Actually, he and his friend raised
almost a quarter-million dollars
for people with disabilities.
Okay.
-Do you wanna write that story?
-Yeah.
Actually, Eli, write 'em all.
We can use them as, uh, space filler,
before and after the ceremony.
Here you go, knock yourself out.
There's a, uh, housewife there that sailed
single-handedly around the world
and a bloke who climbed Everest
with one eye and no toes.
Yeah? Triumph of the human spirit,
"Aren't Aussies amazing?"
That sorta thing.
- Should I interview Tytus Broz?
- Why do you wanna interview Broz?
He's presenting the awards this year.
I thought it might…
He presents the awards every year.
In fact, it would be news
if he wasn't presenting the awards, so…
Close the door on your way out.
Sure.
Why do you wanna
interview Tytus Broz?
Um, 'cause he's hosting the awards
that I'm writing about.
Wanna take a break outside?
Tytus Broz is involved
in some dodgy stuff.
You started all of this, you know?
When you said I should go
and speak to Bich Dang.
She said she thought her life was at risk,
and I dunno, I just--
I just thought she was being paranoid,
but she was dead a few days later.
Supposedly of another stroke.
And then this gets sent to me
at the newspaper.
-What's this?
-Bich Dang's lawyer sent it.
Overseas cash movements
from an account in Vanuatu.
Now, it's an account
secretly owned by Tytus Broz,
with Bich Dang as the sole signatory.
I'm still digging into who he's paying.
My question is, why would Tytus Broz
be in business
with a Vietnamese restaurateur?
You know, Tytus Broz hires
ex-crims, current crims, and ex-addicts
to work at his warehouse.
That's how Lyle got a job there.
What if Tytus had Bich Dang
recruit them to sell heroin,
like he did with my stepfather?
Okay, so now we're saying
Brisbane's greatest philanthropist
is controlling a heroin business.
What if that's how he got rich?
I mean, I bet you it pays a lot better
than artificial limbs.
Okay.
These crims he has around,
do you have any names?
Apart from your stepdad.
Teddy Kallas, all-round sleazebag.
Okay. Anyone else?
Ivan Kroll.
Ivan Kroll is the one
who cut my finger off.
And he's also probably the one
that chopped up my stepdad too.
Have you told anyone this?
No.
Payments from a secret account
owned by Tytus to companies in Australia.
The one I really wanted
to talk to you about was this one.
Alpaca Glamour.
What do they make?
Don't tell me, fake pubes.
The company's owned by Ivan Kroll.
-So, Tytus is buying alpaca hair?
-Well, a half a million dollars' worth!
Bloke makes a lotta prosthetics.
Well, I don't think
he makes hairy prosthetics, Tim.
Maybe you should ask 'im.
Well, I'd be more interested
in speaking to Ivan Kroll.
Mm-hmm.
You in touch with 'im?
Why would I know that scumbag?
Oh, I dunno, just figured
you know every other scumbag.
A colleague of mine saw you and him
together at a function,
a dinner hosted by Bich Dang
before she had a stroke.
We may have chatted. You do know
he's never been charged with anything?
So what were you chatting about?
Come on, Cait. You go
to a knees-up for community outreach,
and you have a few sherbets,
and there's a big-time philanthropist,
and some guy whose face he fixed up.
-Did you discuss alpaca farming?
-Maybe. Can't remember.
Hey, it's Tim.
Can you please call me on my other phone?
I need to update you on something.
- Hello, is that Mr. Leary?
- Yeah.
Uh, I'm Caitlyn Spies
from The Courier-Mail.
Go fuck yourself.
That's awesome.
Um, can I just get a bit of clarification
on why you buried
the glass eye in the snow?
Actually, it fell outta my pocket
in the push to the summit and…
…I couldn't afford to lose
any more fingers lookin' for it, so…
Right, okay. All right,
I mean, no, fair enough.
Yeah, actually,
it was on the way back down.
Uh, do you mind
if I just give you a call back?
- Oh yeah, sure, yeah, sure, mate.
- Thank you.
Hey, what's goin' on?
Quick update, you were right.
Tytus was making regular payments
to Ivan Kroll.
He also was in business
with Raymond Leary.
Who's Raymond Leary?
Remember the guy who tried
to brain himself against the front doors?
- Step away from the glass, please.
- Let me in!
Yeah.
He did a concreting job
for Tytus once.
Now he won't speak to me,
but it's possible he'd remember you.
Mr. Leary, I'm Eli Bell.
I'm Caitlyn Spies.
I said I wasn't gonna speak to her.
Mr. Leary, I know the newspaper
didn't handle your complaint well.
They didn't handle it at all.
We're revisiting the case.
Tytus Broz was paying you
from an offshore account.
We're interested
in what you were doing for him.
Look, no one's accusing you of anything,
we just wanna understand
why Tytus Broz was so keen
to keep your project off the books.
I went bankrupt.
My wife killed herself from the stress.
You lot are four years too late.
It's never too late.
My pal, Slim Halliday,
he did 25 years in a prison
for a crime he didn't even commit.
He told me you can spend years
thinking about the shitty parts of life,
or you can find a way
back to the good bits.
We just need to know
what you built for Tytus, Mr. Leary.
Please.
Yeah, here's the, uh--
the initial specs.
He had this medical architect,
who used to change the specs
and then blame me for the cock-up.
What's a, uh-- a medical architect?
Architect for hospitals
and shit. Excitable little prick.
Nothin' was standard,
all the fittings were imported.
Who knows what it was?
What do you reckon
Tytus was building in his backyard?
No idea.
Sterile area, chemical storage, research.
It's obviously much more
than just a drug operation.
Leary was nervous
just talking about it.
Is it Ivan Kroll he's scared of?
You know he chops up people
with chainsaws, right?
You know, I'm sure he wants
everyone to believe that.
But the thing about these people
that live in the shadows,
they're only safe when no one knows
much about them, ya know?
As soon as their crimes
become public knowledge,
their power evaporates.
Cops withdraw protection,
witnesses start to talk.
Daylight catches up to them
and they're a pile of dust.
You and me, we're the daylight.
This is a picturesque spot.
I came to say that I'm gonna have to draw
a line under our relationship for now.
That kid whose hand you remodeled,
Eli Bell,
he's working for the newspaper now.
And they have dug up
some kind of money trail
between you and Tytus Broz…
…that could be embarrassing
for both of you.
Well, the boss won't like that.
So…
on balance,
it might be convenient for everyone
if you shift your arse overseas for a bit.
I told you years ago, we should've dealt
with those little rat bags.
We're past that now.
Ivan, if you do anything silly,
it's just gonna draw more attention.
I mean, drug dealers and scumbags,
it's fine, but newspaper reporters…
I mean, I'm sure the boss
wants this all to go away very quietly.
Fares to Europe are pretty cheap
this time of year.
Might be a good time to…
…I dunno,
research your family ancestry.
Research your own fuckin' ancestry.
Just understand, if things do get messy,
it'll be hard for me to cover for you.
Just so we're clear on that.
Crystal.
Good.
-Thanks for bein' straight with me, Tim.
-Yeah.
Appreciate it. Just need to tidy up.
Hi, darling.
Oh, darling, hi.
Such a good girl.
- Eli.
- Jesus! Fuck, Gus.
Sorry, I was worried.
I thought I saw Ivan Kroll hangin' around.
So I-- I came to get you. You all right?
Fine until you came along
and scared the shit outta me.
Let's get goin', hey?
What's goin' on? You used to be
Mr. Cool, Calm, and Collected.
- Gus?
- I dunno.
I just keep havin' all these bad thoughts.
You know, like I did
before Teddy attacked Mum.
Well, thanks for tellin' me
that was gonna happen.
Eli… …I didn't know.
Honestly, I don't know
what you'd like to imagine,
but I'm not some fortune-teller.
It's just… it's disconnected images
that come to me.
I mean, you can't expect me to tell you
every random picture that comes to me.
Well, yes, actually, if it's gonna stop us
from being beaten up.
I'm tryin' to explain to you,
it's-- it's not even complete thoughts.
You know you sound completely mad, right?
Yeah, but it's funny, isn't it?
All the mad stuff
it keeps turning out to be true.
Yeah?
Hi, sorry. Um…
I can't sleep
and the light in my room is conked out.
Brought a book.
Yeah. Uh…
Uh, yeah. Yeah. Hop in.
Thanks.
I-- I can go and sleep on the couch
if you want.
No, it's okay.
Hm. Okay.
Are we gonna have to talk
about the car accident?
Can we not?
Okay.
You know, I love those boys.
I would throw myself
in front of a bus,
if I had to, for them.
Well, let's hope that won't be necessary.
Mum, don't!
-Hi.
-Sorry to wake youse.
You need to sign for this.
You know there's a doorbell, right?
- Oh, well, there used to be a doorbell.
- Hm.
Okay.
- Have a good day.
- Thanks. Cheers.
Whoo.
"Queensland Champions
official presentation of awards."
- Ta-da!
- Did you and Dad just, um--
-No.
-Well, I didn't finish my sentence yet.
Well, don't, 'cause we weren't.
And even if we were,
it's none of your business.
Okay. Well, can you just be careful
opening the door?
Eli, I think I'm old enough
to answer the door by myself.
-You're not getting it too now, are you?
-Wait. Getting what?
You know, the, uh… agoraphobia.
-No, no. I just care about ya, that's all.
-Okay.
Oh, Eli, that's sweet,
but I think I can take care of myself.
That update for you, line one.
Thank you, Sophie.
Just to let you know,
that matter we discussed
is now dead and buried.
We can discuss the journalist too if--
No, it's all coming from the kid.
I'll get 'im out here
and find out what they know.
What's goin' on?
Tim Cotton's disappeared.
Shit. Did you go and talk to 'im
about you-know-who?
Yeah. He denied all knowledge, of course.
- It was almost a--
- Eli, in my office.
I'll see you later.
This is good stuff. Keep 'em coming.
"My Year Going Backwards" was a cracker.
Now, you said you wanted
to interview Tytus Broz.
Did I?
So he has just called outta the blue,
and has asked us
to give his company a plug.
So, all you need to do
is get your skinny arse out to Brookfield.
Jeff the photographer has booked a car,
he'll pick you up outside at 2:30.
- I've got the Queensland Champions to--
- That's an evening thing.
-You'll have heaps of time.
-Was there no one else?
Eli, the man asked for you personally,
he's a huge fan of your work.
Interviewing someone like Tytus Broz
is a huge step up.
Do you want to be a journalist or not?
-Yes, I do.
-Good!
So get your notebook and fuck off.
You've got five minutes.
I think Tytus is on to us.
He wants me to go meet 'im in Brookfield.
I'm comin' with you, okay?
Don't leave without me.
- Hi.
- Get in.
Okay, fine.
Sorry, I was expecting
Jeff the photographer.
-He'll get over it.
-Well, what about Brian?
Fuck Brian.
Look, the main thing
to understand about Brian
is that ultimately,
he's only interested in one thing.
Scoops. Bring 'im a scoop
and he'll forgive you
for just about anything.
The thing is, I'm more concerned
about staying alive.
Yeah, well, I care about that too, Eli.
What are we?
We're the daylight. Here comes the sun.
How do I look?
Like Caitlyn Spies in a beanie.
If he's as dangerous
as we think,
he's gonna come after you
and me and everyone we love.
So don't provoke him too much.
Mr. Broz will receive you
in the reading room. This way.
Mr. Broz will be with you shortly.
Who's there? Is this Gus?
Uh, I have a question. Uh--
Are-- Are you me?
Well, what do you think?
That's just another question.
I-- I need proper answers.
There are no proper answers, Gus.
You-- you should know that by now.
Everything depends on everything.
Ask me another.
Is…
Is-- Is Eli gonna die?
We're all gonna die, Gus.
It's all just a matter of time.
Wh--
Gus! Are you all right?
-Yeah.
-What happened?
I'm just a bit panicky.
I hope not,
it's just a bloody award ceremony.
No, it's not about that.
Just, I'm… I'm really worried about Eli.
Why?
It's just a feeling that he's in trouble…
…that I should be doing
something about it.
Okay.
You wanna know what I think?
Yeah, always.
I think you've always been
his guardian angel,
just like my mum is with me.
But it's okay to think about yourself,
you know, just for one night.
Yeah. Yeah.
Eli Bell?
I'm the, um… photographer.
Sit.
You're Lyle Orlik's stepson.
My condolences.
Sad loss.
Do you like that?
It's… certainly very detailed.
That's because it's an actual arm.
Someone donated it?
A dead person, obviously.
Well, the process is called plastination.
That's when the bone
and muscle are all turned into plastic.
So, you couldn't actually wear it?
No, of course not, it's much too heavy.
Electromechanical arms have many problems.
No substitute for the real thing,
unfortunately.
-Do you mind if I record this?
-Yes, I do.
I remember you made a speech about how
your daughter was born without arms,
and that's when you decided
to devote your life to, um,
spare parts, or prosthetics.
She faced many challenges.
I notice you've lost
a finger yourself.
Accidentally cut off.
Except nothing is entirely accidental…
is it?
May I see?
Ah…
Neat job.
Did you ask them
to sew it back on?
They said they couldn't,
it'd just be stiff and useless.
Same with limbs, same with faces.
How to keep everything mobile and flexible
till everything grows back?
And are you working on that?
I'm gonna see if it's okay.
Damn birds. Brainless creatures.
You'd think they'd learn
from their mistakes.
Eli?
Excuse me.
It's not dead.
"Your end is a dead blue wren."
Is that a quote?
It's something my brother said.
Eh, it wasn't dead.
Only a matter of time, I imagine.
Can we go for a walk
in your garden?
No. I think you have
everything you need,
and I need to get ready
for this awards thing.
-I'll just grab my stuff, then.
-Yeah.
Now, you listen to me, Eli Bell.
I know exactly who she is,
and I know who you are.
And you know exactly who I am.
Sophie! Let them out.
Did you see when he grabbed my hand,
and he goes "neat job"?
As if he's recognized Ivan Kroll's
handiwork and given it a mark outta ten?
So you're not buying
"Brisbane's greatest philanthropist"?
This is it, Eli, your first scoop.
Brian's gonna kill me.
No, he'll just yell and thump the table.
I'll explain we were on a scoop, okay?
I'm supposed to be at the awards tonight.
- I told my brother that I'd be there.
- Eli, just… …focus, okay?
Raymond Leary built some kind
of private medical facility for Tytus,
possibly funded by the illegal trade
in heroin,
and now Tytus doesn't want us
roaming around his property.
That doesn't pique your interest
just a little?
Is it worth losing my job?
We wait till dark,
and make sure Tytus goes,
hop over the wall, try the bunker.
And if it doesn't work,
we go back to Brisbane.
And if Brian threatens to fire you,
I will tell him he has to fire me too.
What do you say?
Half an hour to deadline, folks.
Now, where's Caitlyn Spies
and where the hell is Eli fucking Bell?
Oh fuck.
- Hey.
- What am I doin' here?
Give it here, let me do it.
Oh…
Hey, relax, you're doing great.
Okay.
And I appreciate you doing this for us.
I know that big groups of people
aren't exactly your…
…favorite thing
in the world.
But it is Gussie's big day
and it's Eli's too, in a way.
And it's yours and mine too.
Sending our boys out into the world.
One's a proper journalist
and one's a Queensland Champion.
Oh!
That's somethin'
to be proud of, hey?
Yeah, we did good, Frankie.
Oi.
Yeah.
Piece of cake.
Ah…
♪ You know you can't fool me ♪
♪ I've been lovin' you too long ♪
♪ It started s-- ♪
♪ Ever so gently ♪
♪ Desire… ♪
Fuck.
Are you all right?
-Can I ask you something?
-Is it about work?
It's a bit more personal.
Okay.
I was just wondering how you felt
about colleagues being in relationships.
Okay.
I mean, ideally, if we weren't colleagues,
what do you think would've happened?
Oh Jesus, Eli, you never give up, do you?
It's a mark of a good journalist.
According to Brian Robertson.
Oh shit.
Do you think he saw us?
Okay, let's go.
- Ivan.
- Yes, boss?
I need you to do something for me.
Our young friend and the journalist
are showing an unhealthy interest
in the research facility.
-Just get rid of them.
-I'm on my way.
Come on.
This is fuckin' insane.
This just gets
fuckin' worse and worse.
He's farming limbs.
It-- It's
a spare parts facility.
You knew him?
It's my stepdad.
Eli.
It's fucking Lyle.
I'm sorry.
Hey, stop, what are you doing?
- Eli, what do you need that for?
- It's evidence.
Okay.
Let's go.
Hey, wait. Just…
Emergency.
What service do you require?
My name is Caitlyn Spies. I'm…
…in some kind of bunker
in the Tytus Broz estate in Brookfield.
I'd like to report a murder.
Is your own life in danger?
Shit.
Whoa!
Go! Go! Go!
Eli!
The fuck!
Oh shit!
Eli, come on! Come on. Are you okay?
Oh fuck, did we kill 'im?
I don't fuckin' know.
I don't fuckin' care. Just go!
Is he following us?
I dunno.
Oh, fuck, we're in so much shit.
Ooh!
Okay.
We're good.
- Gussie. Shelly, you okay?
- Hey.
- Hi, Mum.
- Yeah.
Where's Eli?
Uh, he's… he's stuck doin' a story
in, um, Brookfield.
Brookfield?
It's all right, Mum. He's comin'.
I'm gonna give him a ring,
all right?
Is Gussie okay?
Um, it's probably nothing.
You know how it is. Pre-match nerves.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
-I'll show you where we're sitting.
-Okay, let's do that. Lead on, MacDuff.
Cabin doors to manual. Comin' through!
- Sorry.
- Champion comin' through.
Any word?
Anytime now, all right? He's coming.
Ladies and gentlemen, honored guests,
we are here to celebrate
the accomplishments
of six very special Queenslanders.
Would you please give
a warm Brisbane welcome
to a man who needs no introduction,
Tytus Broz?
Thank you, Lady Mayor.
I'd like you to come with me
on a journey of discovery.
Hey, we're gonna make it, okay? Promise.
Biomechanical implants
have restored hearing
to thousands of patients,
and may one day do the same for eyesight.
But the ultimate barrier
is not technological,
it's human squeamishness.
And if we can overcome
that final obstacle,
we will arrive very quickly at a time
where every single part of the human body
can be replaced by functioning elements,
manufactured… or farmed.
The future is closer than we may think.
Go further,
dare to break society's taboos,
and never let anyone
stand in the way of your dream.
This guy's evil!
Don't listen to this bastard!
He cut off my stepfather's head
and put it in a jar
so he could experiment on it.
- No idea what he's talking about.
- You're a fucking murderer!
- He's a fuckin' fraud!
- Can we get security?
- Can we remove this young man?
- He's insane!
Mr. Broz, we're taking you in
for questioning.
What are you talking about?
I've done nothing wrong.
He's the one you need
to remove from the stage.
Uh, I'm terribly sorry,
ladies and gentlemen.
We will take a break
until we sort this out.
I'm sorry, Mum, it was the only way.
Chaos.
I've just seen Ivan Kroll.
You need to get your family out of here.
Just stick with your family, okay?
See you soon.
Mum! Dad, Gus!
Oh!
Oi, hey, no!
Eli!
Eli! Dad!
Oh! Robert! Robert?
You stay with Dad, I'll get Eli.
I got you. I got you.
Hey. Stay with me.
- I love you.
- I got you.
Ah!
Ah…
I'm here.
It's Gus, all right?
Come on, stay with me.
Come on, stay with us all.
You're not gonna die, all right?
I promise you're not gonna die.
No.
Eli.
Stay with me.
You can't die.
Come on, stay with me.
Promise me you're not gonna die.
Caitlyn?
Hi.
You're in hospital.
How's Dad?
Did he make it?
Yeah.
They were just here,
been taking it in turns.
How do you like the family?
They're great. I mean,
a lot more normal than I expected.
I think they've been working on it.
I didn't write this.
No, but you're going to.
It's just a teaser,
and Brian's got a whole series planned,
with a TV tie-in.
Welcome to the crime desk, partner.
-Do you wanna sit up?
-Yeah.
Slim Halliday once told me that…
that time can be anything
you want it to be.
If you want it to go fast,
you could trick it into whizzing by.
And you can slow time down
by focusing on every tiny detail.
I was doing that when I wrote this.
There he is!
Oh, good to see
you sittin' up, mate.
You had us all a bit worried there.
- Oh…
- How's your neck, Dad?
Ah, you know, just a nick to the jugular,
it's nothin', mate.
It just looked a lot worse than it is.
You took a knife for me,
Dad, you know that.
Ah, just happened to be in the wrong place
at the right time, you know?
Gussie was the real hero of the hour.
Yeah.
You saved me, Gussie.
Nah, you're all mad.
It's funny, isn't it?
How all the mad stuff
turns out to be true.
Come on, all of you.
Group hug.
Oh! Ho!
Oh!
-It's so sweet.
-It's divine.
♪ I never thought I'd miss you ♪
♪ Half as much ♪
♪ As I do… ♪
Oh you gotta be careful,
I'm still a bit sore.
Sorry.
Gus was right.
My end was a dead blue wren.
But that moment was also the beginning.
For all of us.
An exploding supernova of stories,
endlessly expanding
from that single moment.
Looking back on what happened,
it's hard to separate real life
from make-believe.
But I know the heart of it's true.
♪ It must be love… ♪
Man Finds Mojo.
Mum Gets Life.
♪ Nothing more… ♪
Artist Finds Voice.
- Dinner's ready.
- All right.
Come on, Shakespeare, move your arse.
Have a look at that.
Okay.
♪ How can it be that we can… ♪
Oh!
So that's my story.
Quite a lotta this
was foretold by my brother Gus,
when he first saw me yawning
my head off against a background of stars,
and suggested that maybe I'd bitten off
a bit more than I could chew.
Or, as he put it at the time…
♪ I've got to be near you every night ♪
♪ Every day… ♪
- Yes, please.
- Stay there.
♪ I couldn't be happy, baby
Any other way ♪
♪ It must be love, love, love ♪
♪ Nothing more, nothing less
Love is the best ♪