Look what I found.
You're a natural.
Hi.
Just got off with the FBI.
No abductions, no missing persons.
Oh.
We're keeping her, right?
I mean, someone left her here for us.
Yeah?
Do you want to stay over?
My luggage is in the car.
Look, this... If we're gonna be...
We can't just...
We don't really know each other.
Okay.
What do I need to know?
Uh, I've been...
I've been walking in my sleep.
Uh, I was taking medication.
Uh, so I tossed my pills.
I figured that'd be the end of it,
but then I, um...
I grabbed Patti Levin.
And I took her to a cabin.
And when I woke up,
I tried to let her go,
but she wouldn't let me.
And she killed herself.
So I called your brother, Matt,
and we buried her.
And nobody else knows.
And I smoke.
I hire prostitutes to shoot me.
I lied to you about my gun.
I won't ever do that again. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's okay?
Do I have to say something crazy now?
It's okay.
Do you know whose baby that is?
Sorry?
She's mine.
Hey, hey, hey. Hey.
What's going on?
Hello.
Hello...
One second.
Hey, I'm on my way home.
The old washer is busted,
so I had to be at the laundry...
What? No.
You said 11:00.
Oh, shit. Look, I'm, I'm sorry.
I love... Fuck.
- I swear to God I thought you said 11:00.
-It's okay. Here, give her to me.
I've got to fix
that fucking washing machine.
Kevin, it's okay. Here.
Three loads at the laundromat.
- You're gonna do all the talking, right?
- You'll be great.
Just tell them
it felt like it was meant to be.
Felt like it was meant to be.
- You can put it in your own words.
- I got it.
Deep breath. Clear it out, man.
Good.
Let's go make a family.
Come on.
She was on your porch?
No, it was Kevin's porch.
- I was just the one--
- Was there a note?
Uh-uh. it was just her in her car seat.
- So no idea of who left her there?
- No.
Kevin was the chief of police,
so we assumed--
You're a cop?
I was. I took a leave
so I could help with the baby.
It felt like it was meant to be.
Any other kids?
Uh, my daughter lives with us.
She's great with the baby.
My children were both departures.
- Sorry to hear that.
- Thank you.
Any other relatives in the area?
Um, my dad lives nearby.
He's not really in the, you know...
Not really what?
He's in a psychiatric facility.
But he's not
dangerous or anything.
- He's...
- No.
Marital status?
- Well, we live together.
- We were both previously married.
- We're committed, obviously.
- We love each other.
- Very, very much.
- Yeah.
In the event of a separation,
who would take care of the child?
- We're not going to separate.
- But if you did--
We're not.
Would you like to adopt another child?
We want this one.
In addition to this one.
Um...
MAN". One month old, adorable.
He's white, though.
I'm sorry, no. We're... We're good.
- Yeah, we're pretty...
- Yeah.
Name of the child?
Lily with One "L."
Now, I want you to take this
to any of the judges down the hall.
The wait shouldn't be too bad.
So...
Congratulations.
She's all yours.
She's all ours.
We got you.
Fuck!
You see a tag on this?
I think it's $17.95. Cool?
What?
I'll take that, too.
Please turn off the vehicle, sir.
There's a body in the back of my truck.
You're my sister. Did you know that?
We're sisters. See?
What's she wearing?
It was in the box that your brother sent.
- Check it out.
- Aw.
That was sweet of him.
Hi. You want to go for a walk with us?
Urn, no.
I'm gonna meet a friend for coffee.
Is he cute?
Not as cute as he used to be.
Remember, we have dinner at 7:00.
Dad's gonna wear a sport coat
and everything, so get ready to celebrate.
Oh, I'm ready.
- Thank you.
- Anything else I can get you?
Sorry, it's not for me.
Waiting for someone
-who's just 20 minutes late.
- Okay.
"Looking good, Billy Ray."
"Feeling good, Louis."
- Sorry, I'm sick.
- Oh.
I don't want to infect you.
That sucks.
I ordered you a cheeseburger.
Ah, thank you.
Um, school good?
It's August.
it's August.
- You're right.
- Yeah.
Um...
Dad and Nora adopted the baby.
Wow.
They still calling it Lily?
Yeah, you don't like that?
Who cares what I like?
I care.
I mean, you gave her to us.
- Did you tell Dad?
- No.
- Jill, did you?
You can't tell Dad.
I promised you that I wouldn't.
You know, you should really
just call him sometime.
- He worries about you.
- We're not starting that, Jill.
- Why are you so angry?
- I'm not. I'm not angry.
Well, can I just tell him
that I know you're okay?
No, Jill, you can't.
Why not?
'Cause nobody's okay.
I am.
And so is Dad and Nora.
We're all okay.
That's good for you.
You deserve that.
One big, happy family.
Well, you can be a part of it.
I mean, anytime.
I'm sorry.
She, um...
She wanted me to give this to you.
I love you.
I love you, too.
- Hello.
- Nora, Mike from Century.
- Are you sitting down?
- No, I'm standing.
There's an offer on your house. 2.7.
- Million?
- Yeah, million.
But we listed it for $600,000.
- Why would they--
- It's a preemptive bid.
Listen, they put it on a clock.
We have until end of day to respond.
So, I'm saying yes, yes?
Nora?
Why are you offering me four times
what I'm asking for my house?
Your residence has been flagged
as a highly desirable property
by a number of separate institutions.
What's your institution?
We're from MIT.
- Good school.
-It is, thank you.
We're spearheading a research project,
and the university is financing the grant.
- To buy my house?
- Yes.
- Why?
- Because it is anomalous.
It's a deviation
from the statistical norm--
She knows what it means.
You want to buy my house
because my husband and children
disappeared from here.
Yes, and our deepest condolences
for your loss.
- So you have a guess?
- Sorry?
If they're writing you a grant that big,
you must have a guess
as to where my family went.
We can't determine where, only why.
I don't understand.
Our guess is that
it's a matter of geography.
Places.
And the richest data
can be gathered from sites
where multiple departures
have occurred in the same proximity,
like right here.
But I was here with them.
Our understanding is that
your family was here at the table,
but you were over by the sink, yes?
You're saying if I was sitting right here,
I would have gone, too?
If you sell us your house, we'll be
one step closer to answering that.
- Then what?
- Sorry?
If you're right, then what?
What does it matter?
People want to be able to
protect themselves against a recurrence.
You think it's gonna happen again?
Why wouldn't it?
Staties offer you anything?
Some shitty coffee out there.
Lois Makepeace from ATFEC.
Kevin Garvey.
Want to ask about the eye?
No.
Most people are curious.
So they confirmed the ID
of the body in your truck.
Patricia Levin.
Regional leadership of the Guilty Remnant.
- She went by Patti.
- Did you kill her?
No, I disinterred her body.
You know who did kill her?
- She killed herself, but I was--
- So she killed herself?
Yes, but I was responsible for--
But she killed herself?
Yes, she did.
-I--
- Don't care.
I don't care how you knew
where she was buried,
or why you dug her up
because I don't care about her.
I read your official resignation.
Chief Kevin Garvey of Mapleton PD.
You quit being a cop.
Probably 'cause
this piece of shit, Levin, liked smoking
and telling those
other chickenshits in her little club
to cause a riot in your goddamn town.
So she killed herself.
The world spins on.
Good riddance, Patricia,
we hardly fucking knew you.
Are you letting me go?
Do you want to blow your life up?
What?
No.
Then go home, Kevin Garvey.
What the fuck was that?
- I'm losing circulation.
- I know.
GARVEY SR; She's got a grip on her.
Hey, there he is.
Hola, bambino.
Your dad's been released.
Isn't that great?
Released? When?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
You're dubious.
I'm supposed to trust you
just because you're wearing
normal clothes, not a bathrobe?
Good fit, huh?
Guy I stole them off
is in a ditch, bleeding to death.
Boys.
Do you want to call the nuthouse?
What are they gonna tell me if I do?
That I'm cured.
And he's moving to Australia.
Not moving, just visiting
for an indefinite period of time.
I'm gonna take her up for her nap
and hop in the shower.
Okay.
Hi. Your son's taking us
to dinner tonight.
He made a reservation and everything.
What a gentleman.
NORA". Why don't you two catch up?
She's a great woman.
You said that about Laurie, too.
Well, I still like Laurie.
I just like Nora more.
Try not to drive her
into a fucking cult, okay?
Jesus, your sense of humor is back.
Will wonders never cease?
I got to admit, it's pretty convincing.
What?
You.
You seem pretty normal.
You implying that I'm not?
Well, watched you for four years
yelling at shit that wasn't even there.
Who says it wasn't there?
I don't know.
Laws of fucking nature.
Well, son, wouldn't you agree
that the laws of fucking nature
seemed a bit upside down, as of late?
So, what, your voices,
they just went away?
No, sir.
I just started doing what they told me to.
They tell you to go to Australia?
God, I love this town.
But now everywhere I look,
all I see is what's gone.
So, I can sit around and cry
about how the world fucking ended,
OF...
I could start it up again.
And we offer that grilled
on a bed of daily cut spinach.
Or you can have it roasted
in our brick oven
with fingerling potatoes.
The pasta is homemade agnolotti
with veal ragu,
and we prepare that al dente.
Just a little brittleness to the bite.
And just to remind you,
the chef requests no substitutions.
Can I get the pasta
with the sauce on the side?
Yes, of course.
And can I, um, get that
without the brittleness to the bite?
That's not technically a substitution.
I'd be happy to ask.
Thanks.
That'd be great.
What?
Do you want to get out of here?
Out of the restaurant?
No.
Not the restaurant.
Jill, honey.
We're here.
Please proceed to the visitor center
to get your wristbands.
If you do not have a reservation,
you'll have to turn around
before the bridge.
Excuse me, sir.
- Do you want to sell your wristbands?
- Uh, sorry?
We, my family,
we've been camped out for two weeks,
and I've got cash.
Uh, we rented a place,
so I don't think we need a wristband.
Come on, keep on coming.
If you do not have a reservation,
y'all need to turn around
before the bridge.
Morning.
Do you mind
if we get the keys to your trailer?
Some folks hitch a ride in.
We just want to make sure
you didn't pick up
any unwanted guests along the way.
Here you go.
Thanks. Y'all got a reservation?
Uh, we rented a place in town.
Good for you.
Just need to see a copy of the lease,
and we'll let y'all on in.
Is this okay? We did it all online.
Yes, ma'am.
So, you just take this to the rental desk
at the visitor center.
It's just over the bridge.
They'll set your vehicle up
with some stickers
so you can drive on into town, okay?
Great. Thanks so much.
Welcome to Miracle.
Welcome to Miracle National Park.
Nonresident vehicles
are prohibited in Miracle.
Visitors must ride a shuttle bus
to and from the center.
- All visitors must stay...
- Come on, buddy.
...near the visitor center
with their wristband before borders close.
Sir. Sir, you're gonna need
to take that animal to quarantine
if you're going into town.
What? No one told us
there was a quarantine.
Sir, it's right over there.
Rules are rules.
All right.
You go on in. I'll take him.
Okay.
Sixty days?
No wildlife admitted into the park
until we can clear their blood work.
But it's not fucking wildlife. It's a dog.
Here we go.
I will call you
as soon as he can come home,
but you're free to visit anytime.
I'll let you say your goodbyes.
Come on. Come on.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. It's all right.
Hey, come here.
Come here, buddy. It's all right.
Come here.
I know, I know, I know.
I'll be back.
I'll stay with him if you want.
Maybe he'll fucking talk to me.
Welcome to Miracle National Park.
We're excited to have you.
Within the boundaries of the park
sits the town of Jarden,
a town with a unique history.
The most populous bordered area
unaffected by the sudden departure.
All visitors access the park
via Miracle Way.
There are shuttles from the visitor center
every 30 minutes.
The visitor wristband
is your ticket into Miracle.
Visitors must wear
their wristband at all times.
Each wristband is valid between
the hours of 8:00 a.m. and 7:00 p.m.
on the day of issue.
Miracle isn't just a national park.
It's a living, functioning town
with a rich history.
That was true before October 14
-and incredibly has remained true since.
- I am the Lord your God...
The residents of Miracle
request that you join them
in the project of preserving
this extraordinary place they call home
by honoring these rules and regulations.
Once inside the park,
you may purchase goods
from any of Miracle's registered vendors.
As you explore our town,
you'll notice that
we've designated
several areas as historical sites,
each marked with a white reference number.
Most of these sites have been
preserved exactly as they were...
Auction's in five minutes.
Oh, we've already rented a house.
- I'm just looking for my family.
- Temporary residential?
Right next to the day-pass line.
Thank you.
So, please, make safety
your number one priority.
How are you?
Sorry?
I'm fine, thanks.
I'm out on Leddecker Road.
Under the big oak.
Trailer with all the Christmas lights.
You should come see me anytime.
I can help you...
With your situation.
NORA". That's unacceptable!
We drove here all the way from New York.
I can't believe this.
This is unbelievable.
We paid a deposit. A $50,000 deposit.
- What's going on?
- They say our house burned down.
- The house we rented?
- Yes!
If you talk to the owner, maybe they--
We did it online. We don't know the owner.
Nora, calm down for one second.
- Are there any other rentals available?
- Not currently.
But we'll get y'all to the top of
the wait list, should one come available.
- When's that gonna be?
- Hard to say.
Y'all were lucky
to get one as easy as you did.
Lucky? Our entire house
is in the back of a U-Haul,
and you took our fucking dog.
Well, I can make a call
on over to quarantine.
- See what I can do.
- Dad!
AUCTIONEER 450,000 where?
I think she's buying a house.
500,000, 25 where?
500. Can I get five and a quarter?
25, thank you.
-525?
- MANI 500.
Five, at 500. Now give me 525.
- Five and a quarter, 525 and half.
- Here.
- NOW 600. Not' 575, 600.
-650!
- I have you. I'm at 650.
-750!
- What are you doing?
- Bidding.
Ladies and gentlemen, remember,
there are no escrow.
All sales are final. On 750. 750, 800.
-800!
- I've got you at 800, ma'am.
Can we talk about this?
We talked about it
when we committed to the rental.
That was for six months.
Okay? We're gonna take this
one step at a time.
- Our steps burned down.
- Nora, you need to take a breath.
There's gonna be other chances.
How often do they have auctions?
That's the first one
they've had this summer.
-950!
- I've got you at nine and a half.
- One million.
- I'm looking at $1 million now.
We don't have to do this.
There are other places that we can live.
This place.
This is the place we decided on.
- Yeah, but--
- You want to live here, buddy?
- Yeah.
- You in, Jill?
Yeah, I'm in if you guys are.
Three million!
Ma'am, you realize the current bid
is $1,600,000?
I understand that. Thank you.
All sales are final.
- We clear on that?
- Yup.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I have a $3 million bid on this house.
I'm at $3 million. Three one where?
I'm at three million,
now reeling three one.
Three million once.
Three million twice.
- I have sold the house for $3 million.
- We won!
Hey, we won.
Please don't take these off
till you get
your permanent resident cards.
It'll keep the rangers in town
off your back.
- Too tight?
- No, it's fine, thank you.
Once the wire transfer
from your bank goes through,
y'all can come pick up the keys.
- Initial here and here.
- Okay.
There's no hotels in the park,
so y'all are gonna need to find
other accommodations for tonight.
We don't need accommodations.
We have family here.
Think this is the right place?
Yup, he said the cottage
next to the church.
Looks like a storage shed.
- Hello?
- Matt! It's us.
Oh!
You're here! Oh!
- Hey, hey.
- Hi.
My God, she's so big already.
Hey, I'm your Uncle Matt. Remember me?
Okay, come in.
Mary will be happy to see you.
Let's go.
Hey, I'm glad you're here.
Me, too, Matt.
- Come on.
- All right.
Hi, Mary. How are you?
This is Lily. Can you say hi?
Yeah.
I know it's not much,
but we have our own bathroom.
And Reverend Massey, it's his church.
He and his wife let us use the kitchen
in the main house whenever we want.
How was it coming into town?
The visitor center's something, huh?
It was, you know... They took our dog
and they told us our rental burned down,
but other than that,
you know, smooth sailing.
What?
We were hoping we could stay
with you guys tonight.
Oh, sure. Of course.
We're just a little short of space.
Oh, we have a tent.
$3 million?
That's almost exactly
what I got for my place back home.
- Weird, huh?
- Yeah, it was meant to be.
I'm sure it's very nice.
We haven't actually seen it yet.
Guess that's why they call it
a leap of faith.
Yeah, a leap of something.
You know, why don't you and Mary
come stay with us for a while?
No. That's very generous,
but I don't think it's a good idea.
You'd rather live in a garage
than stay with us?
No, it's just I've been
helping out at the church.
I should be close by.
What aren't you telling me?
He doesn't want to, Nora.
- But why doesn't he want to?
- He just told you. Let it go.
Oh, so you two bury a body together
and now you got each other's backs, huh?
You told her?
Yeah. We tell each other everything.
It should be coming up here
on the right in just a sec.
There it is.
At least it's big.
I get to call my room.
Oh, no, you don't.
Watch yourself.
You're carrying a baby.
Come on. Fucker.
Ah! Fuck! Jesus Christ.
Kevin.
I'm sorry I had to do that to you,
but we just cannot go on
with you treating me like I don't exist.
I do exist.
I need you to talk to me.
I just need you to talk-- Aah!
Kevin?
What happened?
Just... I slipped on some water.
I was checking the stove.
There's got to be a leak.
- You're bleeding.
- I'm fine.
I'm fine.
- Are you--
- Go ahead and get that.
I have Band-Aids in my purse.
- Okay, I got him.
- Let's go answer the door.
Come on. Let's go see.
Feel like such a fucking idiot.
That 'cause there's no water on the floor?
Well, I slipped on something.
Obviously.
Sit down.
Please don't put that on my head.
It'll clear out.
Ow, careful. Just be careful.
Don't be a baby.
There you go. No more owie.
Hey, sweetie.
Who was that?
- Who was that?
- Our new neighbor. You okay?
Uh-huh.
You want to go to a birthday party?
What? We just got here.
We haven't even unpacked.
We'll just drop by for 15 minutes,
make an appearance.
- Fifteen minutes?
- Fifteen minutes.
All right.
Shit.
Evie.
Evie. Come back, Evie.
Evie, come on, baby.
Evie, come back, baby.
- I went away?
- Mmm-hmm.
Um, she has epilepsy.
This doesn't happen
unless she forgets to take her meds.
Sorry. I ruined your cake.
No, no, no. It's... I burned it anyway.
The pie! They brought us a pie.
It's on the kitchen counter.
Will you run and get it?
- Oh, yeah. I'll be right back.
- Do you have any more candles?
Chief Garvey has secured the pie.
Pie is secure. Over.
Very interesting family, those Murphys.
Hard to tell if they're part of your story
or you're part of theirs.
I'll see you when you get home, Kevin.
I'm not going anywhere.
You just bring
this pretty little thing over here.
You'll be sorry you said that.
- Let's go, sweetheart.
- Thank you for having us.
Oh, well, thank you for stopping by.
I'm looking forward
to getting to know you better, Kevin.
Yeah, me, too. Bye.
See you later.
Oh, Jesus.
Hey-
- Are you the new neighbors?
- Uh-huh.
Welcome to Miracle.
Thanks.
ERMA". Bye, sweetheart.
Happy birthday.
I like them.
They're nice.
What?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah, just tired.
God damn it! God damn it!
Jesus Christ, it's just a lightbulb.
No, it's not just a lightbulb.
It's the whole fucking house.
What's wrong with you?
This was not the plan.
This was not what it was supposed to be.
- What was it supposed to be?
- Not this!
Not spend all our money on a house
that we've never even seen or been in.
We were supposed to try it out,
see what happens.
And you went all fucking in.
Why? For what?
What?
She needs to be here
'cause it makes her feel safe.
And what if it's no safer here
than anywhere else?
Then why do we have
these awesome wristbands?
Please don't fuck this up, Dad.
I'm fucking it up?
Well, not yet, but...
You're showing potential.
She asleep?
Uh-huh.
I'm an asshole.
I'm sorry.
I like it here.
Me, too.
Kevin.
Hmm?
If there's something you want to tell me,
whatever it is, I can handle it.
I love you.
Dad!
The water's gone.
Evie!
Uh-oh.
English - SDH