No, no, no. Causality.
Correlation.
Everyone can show correlation.
Even fucking Denzinger
can show correlation.
What is the cause, huh?
What's the cause?
I'm here for research.
I'm not putting my equipment
through your fucking machine.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Is this the home of Evangeline Murphy?
Who are you?
Gracias.
Hey!
- Nora Durst?
- Yes.
Hello, my name is Dr. Joaquin Cuarto.
May I speak to you for a few minutes?
- About what?
- Um...
May I ask when you moved into this house?
What?
Um, the records say
you purchased it on the 21st.
But when did you actually take residence,
on the 21st or on the 22nd?
Uh, I don't remember.
Why are you asking me that?
The girl next door
disappeared on the 22nd.
Um, is that the day you moved in?
Did you make contact with her?
- What?
- Evangeline Murphy.
Did you touch her at all on that day?
- What is that thing?
- May I ask, were you in physical contact
with your husband
and your children on October the 14th
at the moment of their departure?
Get the fuck off my porch.
This will just take a minute.
If you'll just hold still.
- Get off my porch.
- Please don't-- Just hold still.
Get out of here!
I'm just trying to help you.
You okay?
I'm fine.
Good morning, Mary.
Hope you slept better than I did.
Would you like to visit Matt today?
You must miss him, huh?
- Hello?
- Hello. Is this Nora Durst?
Yes.
Miss Durst,
my name is Dr. Allison Herbert.
- How are you this morning?
- I'm fine.
I believe my colleague Dr. Cuarto
paid you a visit yesterday?
- Miss Durst?
- Please don't call this number.
Morning.
You Okay?
I'm just tired. I didn't sleep great.
Go back to bed. I can feed Mary.
You sure?
Go. Sleep.
ls the baby awake?
- Not yet.
- Okay.
Uncuff me?
Maybe in a minute.
If you cooperate.
And if I don't?
Then you will pay.
Hmm.
What? Did I hurt you?
No, I just got a cramp in my leg.
Shit.
Babe.
Somebody threw a rock
through our window.
What?
Somebody threw a rock through our window.
You slept through it?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah.
What do you think this is about?
Wait, babe, where you going?
To get a broom and dustpan.
- Who is it?
- It's him again.
Mr. Murphy, can I speak
to you for one moment?
Don't answer it.
On, baby.
Morning.
Can I ask you a question?
- Is there a place--
- Who are you?
- Sorry?
Oh, uh...
George Brevity.
I'm with the DSD,
the Department of Sudden Departure.
Nora Durst, Northeast Division.
I'm on leave.
Small world, huh?
- What branch?
- Benefits. You?
Secondaries.
Oh, of course.
Do you know them? The Murphys?
Not well. We just moved in.
- Lucky you.
- Lucky me?
I mean, it's hard to find a place here,
you know, since we verified.
What did you want to ask me?
Oh, is there a good place
to get breakfast?
The tourist stuff is getting old.
Try Smitty's. There's no sign outside.
There's a green awning
across from the guy on the pillar.
- Smitty's. Thanks.
- Mmm-hmm. Mmm-hmm.
Excuse me, Mrs. Murphy.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
Mrs. Murphy!
Could I just talk with you a moment?
Mrs. Murphy.
Poor woman, huh?
It's horrible.
Erika.
Loretta. Emily.
We need you to talk John
into talking to the DSD.
John isn't the one that
doesn't want to talk to them, I am.
Why not?
We've talked to the police,
we've talked to the FBI.
And they're the ones
that are looking for our girls.
But they haven't found them.
The man from the DSD
said that he could rule out--
Rule out what?
What questions did he ask that
we haven't already been asked?
We're not supposed to say.
- We signed a--
- Nondisclosure agreement.
What are y'all wearing tonight?
To the fundraiser.
I'm wearing whatever I want.
Okay, well, then I'll see you tonight.
Emily, you smell like alcohol.
Order up.
Hey, you found it.
Yeah, the promised land.
Mind if I sit with you for a sec?
I ordered some carryout.
Be my guest.
Forget the water.
- This brisket's the miracle.
- Mmm.
Barbecue is a religious experience
down here.
- You're not from Texas?
- D.C.
Oh, I thought they'd send
someone from Regional.
You're living in the only municipality
with a population above
5,000 with no deeps.
Three girls lifted from here?
They're not calling Regional.
But they're gonna rule it
unconfirmed, right?
Not gonna rule anything
till your neighbors talk to me.
I administered the new questionnaire
to the parents of the other girls.
None of the fraud flags popped.
- There's a new questionnaire?
- Uh-huh.
The algorithm came from the Japanese.
Getting some interesting results.
Can I see it?
You kidding me? They'd fire me.
They want me to sleep
with this thing under my pillow.
I mean, if the questions got corrupted,
there'd be no way to confirm
the secondary is the real deal.
Hmm, the real deal.
The girl's Mercedes was found running
like a foot just disappeared
off the gas pedal.
Music still blasting.
All the personal effects
are still inside the car.
Purses, phones.
No sign of any kind
of struggle whatsoever.
No reason to run.
Everybody I've talked to around here
says these are good girls.
Choir girls.
Three weeks gone and there's
not a single sighting of them anywhere.
If the questionnaire says they lifted,
maybe they lifted.
Can I ask you something stupid?
My favorite kind of question.
Have you ever heard of someone
being responsible
for another person's departure?
You mean the lensing thing?
Lensing?
You know, like a lens.
Like a kid taking a magnifying glass
and frying ants with it.
The idea is that someone gives off
ultraviolet rays or whatnot,
causing everyone around them to lift.
It was in that Scientific American
article they e-mailed us last month.
Can you forward that to me?
- Dr. Murphy?
- Mmm.
We need you in exam three.
Can somebody else take it?
It should probably be you.
I didn't do anything wrong.
I was just selling water.
How much?
Just a couple of bottles.
How much are you selling it for?
$500 a milliliter.
The samples I took from the spring
that drained are genuine,
so if people are willing to pay that much,
then what did I do wrong?
Want to let me take a look at your hand?
Yeah.
They took my palm print.
Why would they do that?
Can you make a fist?
I want a copy of your report.
The rangers want a list of my injuries
when I go in to describe my attackers.
One of them black, 40, clean-cut?
He's the one that hit you the hardest?
Yeah.
That's John Murphy.
Maybe you let him slide just this once.
Why would I do that?
Because I have plans tonight
and I don't want to miss them
because I'm back in here
fixing you up again.
Let me get you some ice.
Hey-
What are you doing out here, Miss Lily?
Oh...
Let's get out of there.
Oh, oh, okay.
Hey-
Aw.
"Researchers found
themselves intrigued
"by the anomalous phenomenon
of the Departure Cluster,
"the most extreme example of which
is the notorious Brandenburg Carousel."
They never confirmed
that fucking carousel.
Some genius in
German tourism cooked it up.
- Lily?
- She was on the hood of the truck.
Oh, my God.
Oh, Kevin was watching her.
I thought she was down for a nap.
No worries.
When Evie was five years old,
I thought she was playing in the backyard.
I had no idea she was gone
until her friend's mom called
and asked when was I gonna pick her up.
My daughter Erin
did that same thing when she was four.
I didn't know you had another daughter.
I used to, but she's gone now.
My son, too.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Well, thank you again.
Don't tell me how to fucking do it.
I know how to strip fucking...
It's wallpaper.
Well, then don't fucking tell me.
Who are you talking to?
Myself.
Oh, shit.
I took her to the hardware store
and I had all that shit to carry
and then I...
I forgot to go back out and get her.
- I am so sorry.
- Kevin. Kevin.
It's okay. it happens.
It's okay.
- I'm sorry.
-It's okay.
I'm so sorry.
You should hop in the shower.
I'm gonna take Mary to visit Matt,
and then I'll meet you at
the visitors' center for the fundraiser.
Yeah.
- Wait, what?
- The fundraiser.
For the Murphys
and the other missing girls.
- We're going to that?
- Why wouldn't we?
Because we asked them for help
and they fucking banished your brother.
Matt banished himself.
And people aren't at their best
when they're in that kind of pain.
We should support them.
That's what neighbors do.
Oh, shit. Fuck.
Fuck.
- Have you seen my batteries?
- What?
The batteries for my ears.
They're not in the kitchen drawer.
You want me to run out to the pharmacy?
No, I have some upstairs.
You think this is on me?
What?
People throwing rocks through our window.
You think it's because of what I do?
That man that you beat
the shit out of this morning,
he thinks it's because
he was selling our water.
No, he was selling lies.
Then Why'd you take his palm print?
Because I seem to recall
there being one left
on the car that our daughter
disappeared from.
- Let's just call this what it is.
- What is it?
You need to hit people
because you need to hit people.
I'm trying.
I know, babe.
SPF 75? What a joke.
Anything over 30 is basically useless.
Hey.-
We're going to visit Matt.
Do you want to come to the fundraiser
with us or go with your dad?
Actually, Michael asked me.
How do his parents feel about that?
I don't think that he asked them.
And I'm not really asking you either.
Well, if you were,
I'd say he's a sweet guy
and I'm happy for you.
Thanks.
All right, I'll see you there?
See you there.
Hello.
Miss Durst, please don't hang up.
It's Allison Herbert again.
If I could have one moment, please?
What do you want?
I need to apologize
for my colleague Dr. Cuarto.
He's a great scientist,
but he lacks people skills.
He should not have come to your home
to collect the data from you
without permission.
Data?
Yes.
I must say the measurements he took
were very promising. Very.
If you'd allow us,
we could guarantee their accuracy
by replicating them
in laboratory conditions.
You think I'm a lens?
You're familiar with this theory?
Not really. I don't, um...
I just read an article.
Miss Durst, you moved to Jarden,
a town with no departures,
and that very night,
three girls disappeared,
one of whom lived next door to you.
Yes, we believe you are a lens.
Why? Do you know why me?
Well, this is where our research is, um,
divisive.
I would like very much
to discuss this in person.
Please just tell me.
Miss Durst, we believe
that the demon Azrael
has chosen you
as his earthbound instrument.
This entity resides in you
through no fault of your own,
and is responsible
for the chaos that surrounds you
and possibly many others.
Dr. Cuarto and I have
contacted the Vatican--
Hey!
- Why'd you run?
- I was just dropping off...
Wait, wait, wait.
Say it again and say it slow.
What the fuck is this?
That's a pie.
Why'd you send it to my house?
Well, 'cause I know you're in pain.
John got a pie on his birthday.
We weren't in pain then.
You weren't?
Is this about Michael
coming to pray with me?
What?
He didn't tell you.
I'm not gonna say this again.
Stay away from my family.
I know what I did.
And I know I can never make it right.
And I also know
that you wish it wasn't so,
but I am your family, Erika.
You want to take a bird with you?
Why the fuck would I do that?
Hey-
I come bearing gifts.
Hey!
- Thanks.
- Yummy.
-Hey.
- That was for you.
- No, we share everything here. Hup.
Hello, my love.
I'm sorry you have to come out here again.
Not all the people are degenerates.
So this is, what, your new congregation?
Nah, just a bunch of folks
who needed a little guidance.
And all you had to do to win their respect
was humiliate yourself in the stocks.
No, all I had to do was
refuse to let someone else take my place.
Suffering breeds compassion.
Nobody does it like you, Matt.
- You clean the tube every night?
- Of course.
And we got the bed
like you had back in Mapleton.
They're expensive.
You and Kevin didn't have to do that.
It's fine. We rented it.
The OB appointment is this Friday,
so we'll pick you up
on the way out of town.
I bet you're looking forward to that, huh?
Get our first peek.
Hear the heartbeat.
Any sign of her?
Waking up? No, Matt.
- Give her time.
- Hmm.
You look nice.
Going somewhere special?
We're going to the fundraiser
for the families of the missing girls.
They need money
to continue the search, so...
What?
You bringing Mary'?
- Yeah, we're going straight from here.
- Hmm.
What, Matt?
The Murphys don't believe
what happened to her. They deny it.
You bringing her to their party
may be regarded as hostile.
They lost their daughter.
Why would I feel hostile towards them?
I don't know. Why would you?
Fuck you, Matt.
- Let me help you with that.
- I got it.
Thank you.
She loved that on you.
I think she just wanted you
to give it to her,
but you never took the hint.
I took the hint.
Just wanted it for myself.
Michael.
I'm in here.
- You gonna get dressed?
- Yeah, just a minute.
I know you go out there to pray with him.
Who?
Don't make me say his name.
Do you know what your father
would do if he found out?
Shoot him again?
Michael, you can't go out there anymore.
- He deserves forgiveness.
- No, not him.
Everyone who asks for it deserves it, Mom.
Even him.
Michael, go get dressed.
But again, thank you.
Listen to me,
if you call this number again,
I will report you to the fucking police.
Do you understand me?
Is this Nora?
Who is this?
It's Laurie Garvey.
Nora, are you there?
How did you get this number?
Uh, on the Internet.
It's really easy to unlist if you want.
I'm sorry to call you.
I know it's not fair,
but I just need to know, is Tom there?
- Tom?
- My son, Tommy.
Is he there with you in Texas?
No, he's not here.
I've never even met him.
Is something wrong?
Well, if you do see him,
if he comes there, um,
will you tell him
that I'm worried about him?
Can, can you tell him I'm sorry?
Okay, I'll do that.
All right. Thanks, Nora.
Goodbye.
Bye.
- Hey, how was Matt?
- Fine.
- You okay?
- Yeah, let's go sit.
Hi there.
We're taking donations for the reward fund
and for the families to hire
out-of-state resources for the search.
Oh, yes, of course.
We'd like to give $500, please.
That's very generous.
Do you have a PayPal account?
- Sorry?
- A PayPal account.
That's how we do the donations.
If you don't have one,
I can set one up for you.
- No, I have one.
- Then you know the drill.
There you go.
Let's grab those seats up there.
Sure.
Excuse me.
- Evening.
- Oh, hey there.
Oh, Kevin, this is...
I'm sorry, I forgot your name.
- George Brevity, DSD.
- Oh.
- Did you guys work together or...
- Mmm-mmm.
I sent you that article. Did you get it?
- Yeah, it was horseshit.
- Really?
Our research guys thought there was
some pretty interesting stuff there.
They're working some of that data
into the new questionnaire.
Okay, if everybody
could just take their seats.
- Excuse me. I've got to record this.
- Okay.
We're gonna go ahead and get started.
Thank you.
r r
On behalf of me and Sam and Loretta
and John and Erika,
we are so grateful
for y'all coming out to support our girls
so we can get them back
to that beautiful choir real soon.
If Taylor and Violet
and Evie are out there,
we're gonna find them.
Our girls were such good friends
ever since they were little.
Emily and I put together
this little sideshow.
I hope you enjoy it-
Uh-uh.
No.
No. How do I stop this?
Jerry, uh-uh, no.
You got to get out of here.
- Let him do it.
- No, Jerry.
- Come on, let him do it.
- He's trying to help.
He's trying to help? This man is crazy.
He killed a goat on October 14th
before any of us knew what happened,
and he was locked up in jail
where he should have stayed.
But then, all of y'all decided
that Jerry must have saved us,
that Jerry knew something.
He sacrificed something to protect us.
So now, he's holy man,
and he gets to walk around here
killing goats whenever he feels like it,
just in case?
JOHN". Babe, can you calm down, please?
No, you let him do it, too.
If there aren't any miracles in Miracle,
then why does he get a pass?
Cecilia, you were trying on your
wedding dress when it happened, huh?
So now, you put it on every day and you
take pictures with the tourists, huh?
Number 13 on the audio tour.
Well, maybe you were
the one that saved us.
Maybe, huh?
We are the 9,261, and we are spared.
We're spared.
We're not spared.
We're not safe!
All this shit we're walking around
here doing, it doesn't matter.
It doesn't work. My daughter is gone.
So, no. No, Jerry.
She departed.
I'll see you at home.
Where are you going?
Okay, folks,
everybody just stay seated.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Hi.
I was at the fundraiser. Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Here.
It's the questions
the DSD wants to ask you.
Where did you get it?
I borrowed it.
That man,
the agent isn't going to leave you alone.
I wanted you to have it so you could see
there's nothing to be scared of.
I'm scared?
Yes.
Of What?
You're scared that if you
answer these questions,
everyone's gonna know
that your daughter didn't depart.
She didn't?
And those questions will prove it?
Well, come on in and ask them.
Did the missing person
bite or chew his or her fingernails?
No.
Did the missing person
recently commence new dietary habits
including but not restricted to vegan,
gluten-free or Paleolithic?
No.
Would you describe
the missing person as generous?
Yes.
Would you describe yourself as generous?
Generous people
don't describe themselves as generous.
So no?
No.
To your knowledge, did the missing person
consume one or more
alcoholic beverages per day?
No.
Do you consume
one or more alcoholic beverages per day?
No.
Did the missing person
use aluminum-based antiperspirant?
She uses Secret.
It's aluminum-based.
Is the missing person
a product of a multiple birth?
Yes, Evie and Michael are twins.
Did the missing person
have visual impairment
or wear corrective lenses?
Yes.
Was the missing person diagnosed
with any neurological conditions
such as essential tremor,
Tourette's syndrome
or any disorder that manifested seizures?
She has epilepsy.
She had a seizure
the night she disappeared.
You were there.
Yeah, I remember.
How often on average
did you dream about the missing person
prior to their disappearance?
I don't know.
Three or four times a month.
How often on average
do you dream about them now?
Every night.
To the best of your recollection,
what were the last words
the missing person spoke to you?
I don't remember.
You don't remember?
No.
To the best of your knowledge,
did the missing person
ever express a desire
to hurt him or herself? If so, why?
Absolutely not.
Have you ever expressed
a desire to hurt yourself? If so, why?
No.
To the best of your knowledge,
did the missing person
withdraw more than $1,000
from his or her bank
within 30 days prior
to their disappearance? If so, what for?
Evie's account is connected to ours.
She didn't withdraw any money.
Did you withdraw
more than $1,000 from your bank
within 30 days prior to the disappearance?
If so, what for?
Yes.
I was gonna leave John.
You're surprised because we seem so happy.
My grandmother was born here.
She lived here all her life.
She used to tell us kids
this place is chosen.
The good Lord pointed His finger
down on the final day of creation
and said, "You. The Jarden of Eden."
We didn't believe her,
but she said there was a way to prove it,
a way to make your wishes come true.
You take a bird,
you put it in a box and you bury it.
Anywhere in the woods is fine.
And you wait.
You wait three days, you come back,
dig it up, and if it's alive,
right then is when you make your wish.
Little girls believe all sorts of things,
but I knew pretend when I heard it.
Birds living in the ground
for three days is pretend.
Making wishes is pretend.
The good Lord is pretend.
And then on October 14th,
people went away
from everywhere except here.
That was real.
That happened.
My grandma had been dead for 10 years,
but she was right.
This place was chosen.
And about a month ago,
I was walking out to my car
and I saw it.
A sparrow right by the driver's side door,
lying there like it was
trying to get me to help it.
It was dehydrated.
Almost dead.
You think I nursed it
back to health, Nora?
Depending on the size of the box,
a bird can survive 20 hours.
Anything over 30 hours
is medically impossible.
And like I said, this bird,
it didn't have anything left.
So, I waited the three days.
I jogged out to the woods,
I dug up the box,
and I made my wish before I opened it.
I wished that my kids
would be okay if I left.
Because they had no idea I needed to go.
No idea what it's like to pretend.
Michael, he has his faith.
He'd be fine.
But Evie...
She wouldn't understand.
It would break her heart.
So, I wished
that she'd be okay without me.
I opened up the box,
the bird flew out.
And the next night my daughter was gone.
Well, Erika, that's just...
That's quite a stretch.
Your logic, I'm sorry,
it's a little all over the place,
don't you think?
Well, what do you think?
You wanted to leave your husband.
Okay, so why didn't he go?
Why didn't you?
A hundred and forty million people
disappeared three years ago.
Did you wish them away, too?
Because that's a lot
of birds to bury, Erika.
That's a flock of epic proportions.
I get it. I felt the same as you. I...
I felt responsible for losing my children.
I thought it was my fault.
But I moved past it.
I evolved.
Because that's pathetic.
Terrible things happen in this world.
And the only comfort we get
is that we didn't cause them.
So, I'm sorry,
but, Erika,
this had nothing to do with you.
Did they depart or did they die?
What?
Your children.
You said you lost them.
Did they depart or did they die?
They departed.
What were the last words they said to you,
to the best of your recollection?
Hey.-
Mary's asleep.
Jill's putting the baby down upstairs.
Okay, I'll go up and help out.
We need to talk.
Can we do this tomorrow?
It's important.
Yes, honey, I know it's important,
but can we just--
I need to talk to you now, Nora.
Have you been noticing that I've been
kind of losing my mind?
What?
I'm letting you handcuff me
to the bed every night,
and we're acting like
that's totally normal.
I left the baby... I forgot the baby,
and you act like that's no big deal.
- You had your hands full. it happens.
- I'm seeing someone.
What?
Um...
I've been seeing someone.
Who?
Patti Levin.
She ran the Guilty Remnant in Mapleton.
But she's dead.
It started happening
right after we found Lily,
when you moved in.
I thought she'd go away when we came here.
She didn't.
Are you seeing her right now?
Yeah.
Is she talking to you?
What's she saying?
She's saying...
She's saying
I never should have told you about her.
And...
Uh...
That I just made a big mistake.
English-SDH