Kevin?
Hey. Hey.
Oh, God. Oh, thank God.
Shh. It's okay. Okay, let's go see.
Hey. Hey. Oh, my God.
- Hey. What's happening?
- Nothing. It's okay.
Go back to sleep, sweetheart. It's okay.
Kevin?
Ah, fuck.
- She's still not answering.
- Wait. Get in the truck.
Hi, this is Kevin Garvey. Leave a message.
Kevin, where are you? Your truck is here.
You need to call me.
I don't know where you are.
Are you okay?
Evie didn't come home last night.
She was out with her friends
and they're gone, too.
Gone?
No.
Oh, fuck! Oh, fuck!
No fucking cable.
Fuck.
Okay.
911, what's your emergency?
Did...
Did it happen again?
Ma 'am, can you repeat--
I can't find my...
Uh, my boyfriend isn't here.
Did it... Did it happen?
Ma 'am, if you've experienced
the earthquake--
No, no, not the fucking earthquake!
Not the fucking earthquake!
Did it... Did...
Are the people gone? Are they gone?
Looks like you have
some explaining to do, sport.
Hey, did you see my phone?
I had cigarettes in here.
Maybe you smoked 'em
while you were out sleepwalking.
Where'd you go?
I woke up in a drained pond.
When I crawled out,
there was a car parked up on top.
A white Mercedes. It was empty.
Then I saw another car coming.
And it was John, the neighbor.
His son was with him.
I think my phone is probably up there.
They're gonna find it.
I think I should tell the cops.
Tell them what?
You're gonna say
you don't remember anything
before you woke up in the exact spot
where our neighbor's daughter
and her two friends disappeared from?
Wait, Evie's missing?
This your truck parked out front?
Yeah.
Putting together
a search and rescue out the woods.
Gonna need to rig some winches.
Think you can help us out?
Yeah, sure.
Just follow me over here.
- Yes, I'll unhook my trailer over here.
- All right.
- Need help?
- No, I'm good.
Okay.
This area is restricted.
We need you to stay behind the line.
Come in. Go, go.
- Stay behind the tape, please.
- Hold on.
Do not park your vehicle here.
There's a table up the road
for volunteers.
Jesus.
You woke up down there?
Yeah. I came up that embankment.
That's when I saw the car.
You should get down there.
If someone else finds your phone,
you can say you just lost it today.
That's pretty fucking smart.
Thanks.
You might want to start at the car
and work your way back down.
- Where are you going?
- To find the girls.
Hey. Can I help you?
Oh, I'm part of the rescue.
I brought the winch in.
- Wristband.
- Sorry?
I need to scan your wristband.
Oh, yeah. Of course.
We had to close the park down.
Make sure everyone belongs here.
It says temporary,
but we just bought a house, so...
They told us to keep wearing it.
You bought a house? Where?
Um...
Uh, Stanton.
You have an address?
It's 41, I think.
- You think?
- Yeah.
Vega, that's my neighbor.
Oh, yeah, sure, John.
Want to give us a hand?
Yeah.
Take that.
Thanks for coming out.
We appreciate you helping us with this.
You see anything that don't belong,
don't touch it.
Leave a ribbon, find one of us.
Let's go.
God be in my head,
and in my understanding.
God be in mine eyes, and in my looking.
God be at mine end, and at my departing.
We are the 9,261. We are spared.
We are the 9,261.
We are spared.
For that, we are grateful.
- Amen.
Our Father, Who art in heaven,
hallowed be Thy name.
Oh, shit. Okay. Whoa.
Hi.
I heard about your sister.
My dad and Nora went to go help, you know,
look for her.
Thanks.
Why are you wet?
Do you know how to fix a sink?
That's it.
- I got it?
- Yeah.
You got it.
Sorry I bothered you.
Didn't know what else to do.
It's okay.
What?
Why aren't you with them looking for her?
I'm sorry. I'm an idiot.
You don't have to answer that.
My sister isn't here anymore.
Where is she?
When I talk about this to people like you,
they just look at me like I'm crazy.
People like me?
Who don't believe in God.
I think
I just made your sister uncomfortable.
You don't make me feel uncomfortable.
I should get back.
Thanks for saving me.
Any time.
Get back!
I'm not telling you again!
Make room for these people, now.
Come on!
Let's go, let 'em through.
Let 'em through.
- Close it up.
- Hey, step back!
- Nothing down there.
- You sure?
- Certain.
- Thank God.
This is our neighbor Kevin.
- How are you?
- Sam and Loretta.
- Sam.
- Emily.
Their daughters were with Evie.
Oh, I'm sorry.
If there's anything we can do to help--
Hey, they're towing the car up to Austin.
Didn't find anything?
Nothing came up on the black light.
They did pull a palm print
off the driver's side window.
What?
Yeah, the state guy said it was too big
to be one of the girls'.
A palm print?
Stop that! No, stop!
God, these fucking animals.
Okay, we'll get 'em out of here.
No, let them.
It's just water.
Any luck?
No.
If the phone turns up,
I'll just say I dropped it today,
you know, like you said.
So, I should just keep looking?
That's probably a good idea.
Here.
- Are we okay?
- Yeah, we're okay.
- Love you.
- I love you, too, Kevin.
Thanks.
- Earthquake?
- Yeah.
What can I do you for?
Can I get a fifth of Wild Turkey
and a carton of Reds, please?
Shit, forgot my wallet.
Put it on my tab.
- You don't have to do that.
- Eh, my pleasure.
Looks like you got a fun night planned.
But you really shouldn't smoke.
They're for my boyfriend.
- I'm enabling him.
- Ah.
Give me your address. I'll pay you back.
No, no, consider it a gift
from me to your boyfriend.
Thank you, sir. I'm Nora.
Virgil. Virgil.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
What?
Your loss.
What a horrible thing.
God damn it, Virgil,
what did I tell you?
You want to come in here,
you can't do this shit.
Get out.
I'm sorry if I caused any distress.
PATTY. I know exactly
where your phone is.
I can tell you
what happened to those girls, too.
All you have to do is ask.
Smart. Retrace your steps.
You're a regular fucking Hardy Boy.
Dipshits, those two.
Hey, why didn't you tell Nora
about the whole cinder block
tied around your ankle thing?
You afraid she'll jump to conclusions?
I know what conclusion I'd jump to.
You're cold, buddy. Cold, cold, cold.
Cold.
Warm.
Oh, yeah. Getting warmer.
Oh.
Oh, yeah. Warmer.
You're getting real hot now, Kevin.
Oh, you're on goddamn fire.
Don't get in that car, Kevin!
You still here, man?
Yeah, I just...
I lost my phone
when I was out here earlier today.
Find it?
Yeah, I did. It's bricked, so...
I was gonna maybe go
check with the rangers,
see if they needed some help in the woods.
They ain't gonna find
nothing in the woods.
Hop in, I'll give you a ride.
No, Nora was gonna come back,
swing around, pick me up.
Hop in, man. I got you.
All right.
What's that?
Birthday present.
Feel that quake last night?
- What?
- Earthquake.
Did it wake you up?
Oh, yeah. Yeah, that woke us.
Hand me one of those.
- You can help yourself.
- I'm good.
Thought you didn't drink.
My daughter's missing.
Don't... We live back there.
- Patrick.
- John, hey.
- How you holding up?
- Open the gate, please.
The natives in the camp are restless
'cause we closed the park.
- You might want to roll your window up.
- Will do.
We're here for you, man.
These fucking people
wait for weeks to get in for 10 hours
just so they can buy a T-shirt.
I think they're looking
for more than a T-shirt.
Yeah?
Well, what are you looking for?
A fresh start.
No, you paid $3 million for a house
that's cracking apart
just so you could live
on the other side of that bridge.
What you were looking for is to feel safe.
Hey, what's going on in there?
Why won't they let anybody in?
What happened to you guys?
No safer here than anywhere else.
Of that I am sure.
There are no miracles in Miracle.
God damn it.
What's happening?
Stay in the car.
TA". You need to go home now.
No, I told you guys what I need.
Now move your damn truck.
What's he doing here?
I asked you to go with me,
you said no, so he's coming.
- Now move your truck.
- John, listen to me.
Isaac didn't do anything.
There was a palm print on the car
that my daughter was in.
Like it was left for me.
A goddamn palm print.
PATTY. Lucky duck.
We have a problem.
Now I'm going to take care of it.
Looks like you framed someone
without even trying.
- Isaac didn't do anything.
- I don't have time.
- I'm not hearing that.
- Jesus,John.John!
Hold on.
John!
John, don't do this.
Come on, brother, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Hey, hey, what are you doing?
I'm gonna go talk to somebody.
- Who?
- A liar.
Said he could tell people their future.
Said something bad was gonna happen to me,
now my daughter's gone.
Why would he have your daughter?
Well, I might have burned down his house.
You coming with me?
Hey, hey! Why'd you bring me here, man?
- What?
- You picked me up.
Why? 'Cause you wanted company?
'Cause your friends said
you weren't thinking straight?
- No.
- Well, you're not.
- Let me talk to this guy.
- No, come on, man. Step aside.
Hang on, hang on.
You think he's gonna let you in the door
with that bat?
I was a cop.
- No shit.
Look, if he knows
anything about your daughter,
or knows anything about these girls,
then I'll fucking know.
We'll take it from there.
What's his name?
- Isaac.
- All right, Isaac.
What room is he in?
- Twelve.
- All right, so I'll go talk to Isaac.
You wait here.
All right.
Wait here.
Gosh, you sure defused that bomb.
Nice work, Chief.
My husband, Neil... Sorry, my ex-husband
was engaging in
some pretty suspicious texting activity
and then he would leave late at night
to go to the office.
"To the office."
That was the best he could do.
I mean, put some
fucking originality into it, Neil.
So, I followed him
to a motel just like this one.
Sat in the car.
I watched while he walked into the room.
And I considered turning around
and going back home.
I was scared, Kevin.
Scared that when I caught him,
it'd be over.
He would leave me.
But I needed to see,
to know.
So, got out of my car,
walked over to the room and I took a peek.
There was Neil buck naked and some woman.
She had her shirt on. That was it.
She was taking a shit on him, Kevin.
A shit.
I was married to that asshole for 17 years
and never once
did he ask me to shit on him.
Laurie ever tell you about that?
- She was my shrink for a long time.
- Security.
I always wondered whether
that doctor-patient confidentiality thing
was bullshit.
Security! Can you please open your door?
- Is Isaac here?
- Who?
Open this door!
I know you're in there!
You used your credit card!
John!
Open this...
Oh, shit.
Let go of me!
He knows where she is! Where is she?
Enough of this shit, John!
Hey, relax. It's okay.
Relax? Get the fuck out of my room!
You've been shot. You've been shot.
- Where is she?
- Who?
My daughter.
Whatever you're looking for,
it ain't here.
Now get the fuck
out of my room, John Murphy. Go!
Let's do that. Let's go back.
Go.
Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go.
Ain't nothing more dangerous
than a man who don't believe in nothing.
Hey-
We gotta get you to a hospital, man.
- No.
- You're shot.
- You need to go see a doctor.
- No hospitals.
You said before you'd do anything to help.
Well, help.
Hey, I'm driving.
JOHN". Hey, babe.
I got shot.
-Hey.
- She asleep?
- Yeah.
I couldn't find the box with the books
in it, so I made up a story.
Did it have a happy ending?
What kind of a sick fuck
do you think I am?
Where's Dad?
Oh, he's still out there looking.
You're 18, right?
Seventeen.
Close enough.
Why do you think he sleepwalks?
I don't know.
Stress?
The town was losing its shit
and he was in charge.
And I guess now,
he needs to lose his shit, too.
He's not in charge anymore.
And we left town.
Wherever you go, there you are.
Young lady, you are wise.
Michael, the boy next door.
He says his sister departed.
She didn't depart.
- How do you know that?
- Because I do.
How?
Before I worked in benefits in the DSD,
they had me
in the fraudulent claims department.
People who said their family members
departed so they could get a check.
My beat was secondary departures.
I got assigned this woman.
She and her husband used to
walk their dog together every morning.
It was about a year
and a half after the 14th.
And as they're walking out the front door,
the phone rings.
So, she goes back inside
and she picks it up.
Talks for like 30 seconds and hangs up.
When she steps back outside,
there's the dog,
leash just lying on the ground,
husband's gone.
So, the logical explanation
is that he went
where 140 million other people went.
Into thin air.
I found that fucker in Puerto Rico.
He was careful.
He made small withdrawals
from their bank account
for six months
so he could build a nest egg,
and then he just chose his moment
and he ran.
Why?
Because he had the greatest scapegoat
in the history of civilization.
The Sudden Departure
was a one-time-only event.
The flood happened
three years ago on October 14th,
and the ark took on
all the animals it needed.
Why in God's name
would it take on any more?
All right.
Easy, easy.
- Lay back. Lay back.
- Easy. Just lie back, lie back.
You're all right.
- What was it?
- .22 through the door.
It's not that deep.
I can see the bullet.
- I think I should just go.
- You're good here.
- What's that?
-It's for the pain.
No, no,
I don't want to be knocked out.
Okay.
Just relax.
That's better.
She knocked me out.
I thought I could find her.
I know. I know.
I gotta go out.
Will you keep an eye on Lily?
Yeah. Where are you going?
Church.
If they asked me,
I'd say lean into it.
That's the sermon they need to hear.
These people haven't been
in this situation.
I offer expertise based on experience.
But they're not gonna ask.
I'll sit there
while Winston goes on about Proverbs
and the congregation's eyes glaze over.
Nora.
Is it real?
What?
Is this place real?
I'm not sure I understand the question.
One of the only reasons
we chose this place
was because you said it was special.
You told us we would feel safe here.
Now I'm waking up to fucking earthquakes
and missing teenagers.
My boxes aren't even unpacked and
it's the same goddamn thing I left.
Mary woke up.
What?
The very first night we were here.
I thought I was dreaming,
but she was back.
I said we should go to the hospital,
but Mary, she just wanted to talk.
The last thing she remembered
was the accident,
so I told her everything
that happened since.
We talked for hours.
And we cried.
Until we fell asleep in each other's arms.
And when I woke up,
she was like this again.
For some reason, the people in this town
don't want me to talk about what happened.
Maybe they don't believe me.
Maybe you don't.
But I got a glimpse,
a moment.
And every day since, I've wondered
if it's ever gonna happen again.
If I'll get her back for good this time.
But the one thing I've never wondered
is if it's real.
It's real.
You left this at our house.
Thanks.
What are those for?
There's one on our house, too.
Um, before park services took over,
some people from the government
came by to every house
to make sure it was true.
That no one was gone.
Oh.
Do you want to come in?
I can't. I'm watching Lily.
You alone?
Mmm-hmm.
Me, too.
John said he, uh,
burned that guy's house down.
The guy who shot him.
Well, then I guess they're even now.
Burning down houses is new.
Usually, he just gives a warning.
Warning for what?
When people found out
about what happened here,
there was a lot of confusion.
And then there were claims,
claims that were untrue.
John was in at the time.
But when he came home
and saw what was going on...
He wasn't having it.
"There are no miracles in Miracle."
- He gave you the speech?
- Mmm-hmm.
Evie was a miracle.
She came too early. Twenty-four weeks.
You know, a lot of people don't know
that twins can be born two months apart.
Michael, he stayed put,
but Evie,
she couldn't wait to get started.
She was one pound, one ounce.
Now look at her.
I know what people are saying.
They're saying
that something bad happened.
She's...
Playing a joke
and she's giggling in the woods.
No one would ever want to hurt Evie.
She would never want to hurt anybody else.
She's better than that.
She is exceptional.
Exceptional.
Just like this town.
Things are gonna change now.
I like them, the Murphys.
They're exciting.
And that Erika is something, huh?
Gets the call
her husband's been fucking shot.
She just pulls the bullet out,
no questions asked.
That's real commitment. That's trust.
That's love. Not like what you've got.
What you've got, Kevin, isn't love.
It's damage control.
Your family blew up,
Nora's family blew up.
And now you're all
just clinging on to each other
'cause you need to cling on to something.
That's why she bought the house.
She didn't really care
whether you wanted to, or not.
Her money, her choice.
That must have been emasculating.
And, you, Jesus.
If you loved them, you'd trust them
enough to tell them about me.
If you loved them, you wouldn't lie.
Shut the fuck up!
I didn't tell them about you
because you're not fucking here.
I love my family.
I love them.
Then why did you try to kill yourself?
What?
Come on.
This isn't a big mystery.
I was right there with you.
You walked out of your house
in the middle of the night
and you found a rope and a cinder block
and then you tied it to your ankle
and you threw it into a goddamn lake.
Let's face it, Kevin,
there are people
who try to commit suicide for attention.
And then,
there are people
who really want to fucking die.
Like me and you.
I watched you do it.
And you did not hesitate, my friend.
Plunk.
Right into the wet abyss.
And if not for an act
of divine intervention,
you'd be gone.
I'm sorry, Kevin,
but these are not the actions
of a man who loves his family.
I don't want to kill myself.
Well...
You're certainly entitled to your opinion.
I'm just glad we finally talked about it.
Oh.
Since you didn't seem
to give a shit enough to ask me,
I'll tell you.
They vanished.
The girls.
Drove right by in their car
listening to their music,
not a worry in the world.
Then, poof. Gone.
Mama was right.
Things are gonna change indeed.
Hey!
Who's your friend?
Did you find it?
Yeah.
What a relief.
Kevin.
Whatever happened to those girls,
I know you didn't have
anything to do with it.
Thank you.
But I can't wake up alone like that again.
I found these in the box
with your uniform.
We're in this together, right?
Right.
I hope you found the key, too.
Kevin.
Hmm.
Are they ever going to find those girls?
I don't think so.
English - SDH