Fire!
Close the gate.
Haniwa!
I'm here.
If you leave my side again,
I'll kill you myself.
That's fair.
Trivantians!
Advance!
Gather your wits and your breath.
We'll make our stand here.
There's too many of them.
We don't have enough soldiers.
- We'll hold them.
- For how long?
Baba.
Long enough to send word
to your mother to evacuate the city.
Kofun, Haniwa, ride to Pennsa
as fast as you can.
What?
There's nothing more
that you can do here, my son.
Dad, we can fight.
I'm your only archer.
If you stay here, you will die.
Then we die.
The two of you are stubborn fools!
Commander Ferik.
Witchfinder General.
Send your swiftest rider to Queen Maghra
with this immediately.
Yes, sir.
They retreated into the fortress
and closed the gate.
Let's get those gates down, now!
Lift!
Forward!
Halt!
Soldiers, take your positions!
Move.
- Dad.
- Shh.
Do you hear that?
- They're breaking through the gate.
- Not that.
That.
What is that?
The Hidden Tribes.
Bow!
Kofun. You're alive.
- Paris!
- Baba.
Baba.
Lion. Ah.
- We stand with Baba.
- You brought the Valier.
We've brought you more than that.
The Valier stand with Baba Voss!
- The Salvin stand with Baba Voss.
- We fight!
The Yeliss stand with Baba Voss.
The Reyenne stand with Baba Voss.
How many fighters?
More than 100.
A hundred mountain warriors are worth
twice as many Witchfinders.
They'll have to be.
Kofun, take Paris to safety.
I'm uphill.
Chet-chet.
Toad.
Kofun.
Seems like they'll let anyone
into the wars these days.
Any advice?
The Trivantians are
all leather and steel.
If it rings, stab it.
I can see, remember?
That's what I'm afraid of.
Who's there?
Maghra.
Surprised you have
time to check in on me,
what with the war you're waging.
The war you started.
Mmm, yes.
I understand your own children
have joined the cause.
All that time you spent nattering away
at me about keeping them safe...
Oh, be quiet.
I'm not here to have a conversation.
I just need you to answer one question.
This baby you carry...
whose is it?
Oh, come on, Maghra.
I know you must have suspected as much.
Sweet Kofun.
Not my first choice, I'll grant you,
but he performed admirably.
You're lying.
I should have let Tamacti kill you.
My son won't just be your nephew.
He'll be your grandson as well.
He will be neither,
because he will never be your son.
I will take him from you
the moment he is born,
and he will never know you.
Not even your name.
I may be your prisoner now, sister,
but you watch what you say to me.
It's not the first time
I've been in chains.
They tend not to hold me very long.
I will have you buried in these chains.
Take care of my crown, Maghra.
I'll be wanting it back.
How are you feeling?
I've felt better.
I'm told you will heal just fine.
Yeah, well, either way, you're welcome.
I'm sorry?
Uh, for saving your life?
Ah. I believe it was I who saved you.
No, no, it wasn't.
It's not how I remember it.
It's certainly not how I'll tell it.
Those were Lowland Assassins.
Very few people meet them
and live to talk about it.
It was brave of you to attempt a rescue.
You'll get no disagreement from me.
My Queen, Lord Harlan.
The army reached Greenhill Gap,
as did the Trivantians.
Our next runner should
have news of the battle.
Thank you.
It begins.
We have spent our lives
cowering in the shadow
of the Trivantian empire...
wondering when the day would come
when they would march their army
into our land to make it their own...
making slaves of our wives,
husbands, sons and daughters.
And now,
and now that day has come.
On the
other side of that wall
is the army that we have
all feared for so long.
And their victory
will mean the end
of everything that we hold dear.
But when they come through that wall,
they will not find the frightened army
they are expecting.
We are Payan soldiers,
mountain warriors, Witchfinders.
Former enemies banded together
for one purpose and one purpose only:
To protect what is ours at all costs!
I know this enemy.
I was this enemy.
They fight to enslave.
They fight for greed.
We fight for love.
They fight for conquest.
We fight for our families.
We fight for our freedom!
I am a father
fighting side by side with my children.
I am a husband
fighting to protect my queen.
I am your friend
fighting for your freedom
until the day that I die.
I am Baba Voss,
and I say let us not wait
until they knock down our gate!
I say we open it right now
and welcome them to hell.
Baba.
They're opening the doors.
Scouts.
Crossbows, advance.
Forward march!
Aim high! Three quarters!
Forward march.
Aim left, one quarter.
Forward march!
Aim center high!
Aim center high.
Fire!
Full attack! Take the fucking fort!
On your left!
Please.
Is it still lit?
Yes.
Shit.
No!
- "No"?
- Fuck!
You're a mountain man.
Can't you light a fire?
Yes, I'm a man. I can light a fire.
Go hold them off.
Baba!
Almost!
Hot.
Good, because there's a war
happening out here!
Now!
Crossbows! To me!
One quarter left!
Fire!
Three one quarter right!
Two left!
Fire!
- Three one quarter right!
- Fire!
Aim high three quarters.
Aim left one quarter.
- Toad, follow that voice!
- Two left!
One quarter left!
Two left!
One quarter right!
One quarter left!
Kofun. Kofun!
Saving your ass is starting to feel
like my only job.
Don't stop now.
Shit.
- Kofun!
- Toad.
Get off me.
What are you doing?
There's a battle going on.
I'm not leaving you like this.
It's not you who's leaving.
Tell Paris...
Tell her what?
She'll know.
Now, do me a favor.
Go kill someone.
Tamacti Jun!
Baba Voss!
Just checking to see if you're dead.
Not yet.
There are more of them.
Many more.
No!
Bow Lion!
Now!
Now, where... where are they?
Where are they?
Come on! What?
What's happening?
What was that? What?
Oh, no.
Fall back!
Fall back! Fall back!
Wren?
Wren!
Kofun!
Haniwa!
Kofun! Haniwa!
- Papa! Papa.
- Baby.
We did it.
We won.
- You're not hurt.
- No, um, I'm okay.
And so is Kofun. I-I-I saw him earlier.
You stay here.
- What is it?
- Do as I say.
You find Paris and make sure she's okay.
Okay.
I love you.
You can see.
We have the same father.
Jerlamarel is your father?
Yes.
But you're fighting for the wrong side.
No.
People like us,
we're always on the same side.
This is Charlotte.
I'm going to take you somewhere safe.
I don't want to go with her.
Well, I don't want to take you.
But you won't hear me complaining.
You okay to get up? Yeah? Okay.
Edo.
You always did hear better
than the Ayuras.
You still have Ranger's whistle.
He gave it to me
right before they locked him up
for helping you escape.
Everyone close to you
always ends up suffering.
Now it's your turn.
Leave this place, Edo.
Please. It is over.
No, it's not over,
not while you're still breathing.
I don't want to kill you.
Don't worry.
You're not going to.
Goodbye, brother.
Our father couldn't make me kill you,
and neither can you.
No!
Edo.
What did you do?
There was no going home for me
after this defeat.
You could have come with me.
Even you could not have kept me
from a Payan rope.
It didn't have to be this way.
We were raised as warriors.
It's always been our fate
to die like this, Baba,
bleeding into the earth.
Tell me...
did our father really
instruct you to kill me?
Yes, he did.
What a prick.
Edo.
Is there anything I can say
to convince you to come back with me?
You wouldn't have to hide
who you are anymore.
You know I can't do that.
Why not?
My family,
my home,
I couldn't leave them any more
than you could leave yours.
I can't be at war with you.
I don't want that either.
You're still wearing the necklace.
Well, it does say "forever".
Well, then...
don't ever take it off.
What are you doing?
Let's talk later.
You just freed a Trivantian officer
because she can see.
Is that how it works?
- If you have vision, you're forgiven?
- Of course not.
I heard what you said
to the kid, Haniwa.
"People like us are always
on the same side".
After everything,
you still think you're special?
We are special.
She's just killed dozens of our people!
She is my people!
She is my people.
So what am I?
What am I?
Here he is.
Toad's horse?
Yeah.
Where is Haniwa?
- Haniwa.
- I'm here.
It's time. Let's go home.
- I don't even know where that is anymore.
- Yes, you do.
It's where she is.
Haniwa?
Mama.
Haniwa!
Mom.
- Kofun?
- Mama.
Thank you...
for bringing our babies home safely.
I think it was they who brought me home.
You were right.
It is time for us to stop
treating them like children.
They fought bravely.
They don't need me anymore.
I think they need you
more than you know.
We all do.
I'm just so happy to have you back.
I don't belong here.
You belong with me.
For generations, the Witchfinders
have been the backbone of this monarchy.
Holy warriors in service of the crown.
And for that, I offer you all
my enduring gratitude
and the gratitude of this nation.
But the world has changed,
and in this new world
there are no longer any witches,
so no need for Witchfinders.
But, more than ever,
there remains the need
for brave warriors.
Tamacti Jun.
Witchfinder General,
your charter is changed,
but your rank remains.
From this day forward, you are
High General of the Payan army.
And you, brave and loyal soldiers,
are all officers of the Royal Guard.
There are those of you
who will not agree,
as a matter of principle,
with this change.
I will not compel you
to a service you did not choose.
For any of you who feel this way,
I absolve you of the blood oath
you swore upon conscription.
You are free to leave
with one year's honorarium
in grateful recognition
of your holy service.
- This will not stand.
- Ferik.
You should know better.
Baba Voss.
Your heavy gait gives you away, Baba.
Harlan.
I wanted to express my gratitude
to you for protecting my city.
Your city?
Well... Yeah, I built it, bled for it.
So I'd say it's mine.
Whatever gives you peace.
Baba, wait.
You would be a great asset
to the Payan army.
I'm not a soldier.
Well, you might surprise yourself.
This war isn't over, Baba.
It is for me.
How many
Witchfinders did we lose?
Twenty-two... today.
So, not that many.
As Witchfinder General,
Ferik had some measure of influence.
He'll recruit more.
Will they be a problem?
Undoubtedly.
But not immediately.
You sound tired.
You try
serving your sister for 20 years.
Well, I hope I can make
the next 20 years a little easier.
I think my days of service
have finally come to an end.
Tamacti, Paya needs you.
- They have you.
- I need you.
I'll consider it.
Thank you.
Your command of the
council is inspiring.
You are your father's
daughter in every way.
You will truly be a great queen.
And Paya will have
the leader it deserves.
Oloman.
You have a demonstration for me.
- Yes.
- Hmm.
Let's hope for your sake this one goes
better than your last attempt.
It will.
Get on with it.
You're testing my patience.
Wait for it.
The guard said you were
crying out in your sleep.
A presage as a midwife.
For many years now.
Describe what you are feeling.
The pain of motherhood.
It is early yet for that.
Let me examine you.
How odd...
you being so concerned for me.
My concern lies with the child.
Something's wrong. I can feel it.
Your womb is intact.
This baby will come on its birth day.
Maghra says this child
will never know me.
You're a midwife, Paris.
Surely you agree,
a child should never be taken
from its true mother.
It is not my place to question
the intentions of the queen.
No, of course not.
You can't really expect Kofun
to raise a child.
He's practically one himself.
He is very much a man.
And he's much stronger than you know.
Will you help him?
Of course I will help Kofun.
No, you won't.
And hear this, mountain woman.
I will kill this child
before I let it be taken.
And I'll kill anyone who tries.
Everything is gonna be all right.
Rock-a-bye.