- Paris.
- Help! We've been betrayed!
- Intruders! Wake up!
Paris!
Haniwa. Haniwa.
Your mother, Baba. They must not leave.
They've already left. What's wrong?
I dreamt betrayal.
Blood. Blood and betrayal, Haniwa.
Okay. You stay.
Can't you just send someone else?
Who should I send? Do you want
me to trust a Witchfinder?
Can you even ride a horse?
Kofun does it. How hard can it be?
- That's it. I'm coming with you.
- You'll just slow me down.
- Just grab me a horse!
- Charlotte!
There's no time.
- Swear to me you'll be safe.
- I'll do my best.
I promise.
Keep to yourself.
Pay attention to all that is said.
I don't see how an agreement
will be reached, but...
if you feel our delegates weakening,
you will make them see reason.
Yes, sir.
You're troubled.
I understand the queen wants war,
but an attempt at peace
costs us nothing.
Every day we wait to strike
is another day she grows her forces.
I've buried enough soldiers this year.
You represent me
at the conference.
The other delegates will be wary of you,
but they will also listen to you.
No one will listen to a lieutenant.
That is why I am making you a captain.
The Payans have killed our people.
And instead of avenging their deaths,
the Triangle would prefer
that we appease the enemy.
Wren.
Sometimes in order to
best serve the republic,
you must work around its government.
The talks must fail. Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
The delegation is leaving. Here.
In case you get hungry.
Are you okay?
Kerrigan was always gonna get
himself killed one way or another.
I'm pleased he did it in the service
of the princess, my wife...
not crossing the border with a bag
of thornflowers stuck up his ass.
I need another drink.
We can drink later when we
toast the Trivantian delegation.
You can toast those bastards.
I'm drinking to my brother.
- Harlan. We...
- Sorry.
You have nothing to be sorry for.
But there's a lot at stake here,
and if you're unable to participate...
- I know what's at stake. It's my city.
- ...you have to let me know.
I'm fine.
If we fail, Sibeth will have her war,
and the Trivantians will destroy us.
I just got my family back.
I will not let any harm
come to them now.
Nor will I.
Actually, you're the only
family I've got now.
That's pretty sad, huh?
That's 12 heads you've lost today.
- I blocked you twice that time.
- Oh.
We'll tie a knot by your grave
to remember that stunning achievement.
How do you do it?
It's like you know where
I'm gonna be before I do.
Movement is a language. Hmm?
Dance, combat, fucking.
It's all just bodies
talking to each other.
Now, I'm trying to teach you to listen,
but you just keep swatting at my sword.
Cover your eyes.
Don't think I'm ready for this.
Oh, believe me, you're not.
But sight clearly isn't helping you.
So either it's hurting you,
or you're simply hopeless.
I just wanna find out which it is.
Let's go.
Okay.
Dropped my sword...
Stop!
What...
Good news.
You may not be hopeless.
- But we're done training for today.
- No, I wanna go again.
Well, then you better find
someone else to fight.
That is the Payan banner.
Commander Watts
of the Trivantian Empire.
Captain Gosset of the Payan kingdom.
As has been the custom
between our two nations,
soldiers shall maintain their
company outside the camp.
All others who enter will be unarmed.
Agreed.
Our soldiers will check your delegates,
and yours will check ours.
Agreed.
Then let's begin.
Clear.
- Clear.
- Next.
Clear.
You're fine.
- Arms up. Arms higher, huh?
- Arms up.
- What is this?
- Move on.
Chet-chet.
Haniwa?
What are you doing here?
- I have a message from Paris.
- Shh. Come down here.
- When did you learn to ride?
- I didn't.
- It hurts a lot actually.
- What does Paris say?
She says you will be betrayed.
We should go now.
If we leave the talks,
we are assured of war.
She dreamt it, Mama.
She seemed very sure.
Paris's premonitions might come true,
but if we walk away,
thousands of people will die.
That is a certainty.
Papa.
Your mother will handle our business.
We will stay close in case
this betrayal does come to pass.
Thank you.
She has been wrong before.
Paris or Mom?
Both.
It's good you came.
Find a perch. Keep watch.
Okay.
My guards told me
you'd taken to riding.
I was so pleased to hear it.
With your sight...
you must be able to ride so quickly.
How exhilarating.
I wonder,
would you take me on a ride?
It would mean so much to me.
You okay?
Great.
I haven't felt freedom like that
in such a long time.
Really? You're the queen.
Don't mistake power for freedom.
My position binds me to my people,
but it also keeps me
forever at a distance.
That sounds lonely.
Everyone does
as I command, but...
no one laughs with me...
wishes to know how I feel.
Am I happy? Sad?
I'm... I'm the queen.
It's been a very long time since someone
treated me with
simple, honest affection.
Thank you.
Should we go again?
For years there was bloody
conflict between our nations.
But for a long while,
the peace has held.
And now we hear your queen
has assembled a war council.
Know this now,
it will be a sorry day for all Payans
if we answer this call to arms.
But we have no particular
desire to go to war.
Perhaps once you explain
your queen's behavior,
we can reach a less bloody solution.
The queen has responded
to Trivantian aggression.
Your soldiers have been
encroaching on our land,
occupying border towns and
taking our people as slaves.
If your accusations were true,
we could talk about settling them.
But Trivantian law prohibits
any slaving company from
crossing the eastern border.
And we have occupied no Payan towns
except in retaliation
to military incursions
and smuggling across our borders.
It's hard to talk about borders
when your government has repeatedly
re-knotted the surveyors' maps,
claiming Payan territory as your own.
To be clear, is that
a formal accusation?
It's a fact.
I know that voice.
That's Wren.
The woman who saved us in Trivantes.
Sounds like you're happy to see her.
I am.
It's always the hard way with you.
If this was a
simple border dispute,
perhaps you'd just review the maps
and agree on our respective territories.
Yes, but...
any peace must come
with an official apology
for the attack on Kanzua.
An apology?
You can't be serious.
We will not apologize
for something we did not do.
You destroyed the dam
and tried to murder our queen.
We did no such thing!
Come on. We're talking a simple apology.
We are the strongest military
power on the continent.
If we wanted your queen dead,
she'd be dead.
It's that strength that makes you
the only nation
capable of pulling off
an attack on Kanzua.
Your queen is despised
by many of her own.
I would not be surprised
if this so-called attack
came from within her own camp.
Regardless, we will not take the blame
for something we did not do,
just as we will stand by any actions
we did take in defense of our nation.
For instance, Lord Harlan,
we made no secret
of beheading your brother
after he was caught spying in our city.
As a matter of fact,
we sent his head back
to you as a courtesy.
We tried to make it quick,
but he refused to cooperate.
- Captain Gosset!
- I'll kill you!
Come on!
All right. That's enough.
Have you lost your mind?
- Fuck you!
- I want him arrested at once!
This is a peace summit on neutral
grounds. There will be no arrests!
- Shove a poker up your ass!
- I apologize.
Don't apologize to them.
This conference was a waste
of time. We're done here.
Are you leaving? Oh, no.
Bye-bye. Good night.
Sweet dreams, assholes.
- Paris.
- Most people chop firewood outside.
I'm doing sword drills.
And... you just do the same
motion over and over
until it becomes thoughtless.
In battle, there's no time to think.
Mmm. Did Toad teach you that?
No, it's a fundamental rule of combat.
Remember...
there are weapons more powerful
than swords. Hmm?
Compassion, love...
Love didn't save our people.
I sense you're different, Kofun.
So much anger.
Of course I'm angry.
I've been lied to my entire life.
You've spent
time with the queen.
Be careful. Be very careful, my dear.
This queen...
serves only one interest.
Her own.
Or maybe she's just careful
about who she trusts.
Well, at least she doesn't pretend
to be someone she's not.
I'm busy, Paris.
You both need to calm down.
No harm was done.
No harm?
You almost started the war right there.
I may have had a bad moment, granted...
Your bad moment has ended
any chance of a negotiated peace.
Well, if that's true, why haven't
the Trivantians ridden off yet?
Maghra, you're new to this.
And, Boo-Boo,
you don't strike me as the kind of guy
to negotiate his way out of a fight.
So you'll both have to trust me
when I tell you
we've gained invaluable knowledge.
And what is that?
The Trivantians might actually
be serious about peace.
They will never return to the table.
Yeah, well, they will.
But the table doesn't matter.
What matters is the deal you make
before you get to the table.
What are you talking about?
What have you done without my authority?
I acted in your name
and with your best interests
at heart, Princess.
We have a meeting tonight
with Ambassador Scopus.
It's a private meeting,
away from the bluster and the
threats and Torrance's spying.
We negotiate the peace tonight,
and then we pretend to do it again
at the table in the morning.
You will not go to this meeting.
Excuse me?
You mean my meeting
that I set up for me?
Yeah, I think I will.
No. You have another one
of your bad moments,
you and Maghra will be dead right there.
I will go with her.
Oh, yeah.
A Trivantian traitor wanted for murder.
What could possibly go wrong?
Just... Just stop it, both of you.
Lord Harlan, that is the last time
you will negotiate anything on my behalf
without my express permission.
Is that understood?
- Is that understood?
- Yes.
Now.
This is how we move forward.
Harlan, you will attend the meeting
with me, but so will Baba Voss.
And if you speak one word out of line,
he will render you speechless
with a method of his choice.
Now, where is this meeting
you've arranged?
You forgot to mention
you were Payan royalty.
I would have... if I had known.
You didn't know?
It's a long story.
Well, you'll have to tell me sometime.
Every day since I escaped,
I've dreamed of seeing you again.
I know this is difficult.
Our nations are about to go to war.
Not if this conference is successful.
It won't be.
You can't know that.
Can you?
And if our people go to war...
...you will fight for yours,
and I will fight for mine.
We just can't let that happen, Wren.
I know my mother doesn't want war.
I'm not sure there can be peace...
between our people.
And I don't wanna fight you.
Wren.
I will never fight you.
Scopus?
You here?
Where else would I be?
Harlan. And who is with you?
As promised, brought the princess.
- Princess.
- Ambassador.
Please let me offer
my most sincere apologies
for Lord Harlan's inexcusable outburst.
You did make a fool of yourself, Harlan,
acting out like a temperamental child.
Imagine if you'd actually harmed Watts.
Come on. It's not a summit
till someone gets hit.
So... we gonna do this?
Where do we begin?
We know you didn't attack Kanzua.
Princess, I appreciate your candor.
A refreshing change from earlier today,
but I didn't need to crawl down here
to hear what I already know.
Then I'll tell you something
you don't know.
Within a very short time,
my sister will no longer be queen.
I'm listening.
The queen has not been
herself since the fall of Kanzua.
She has suffered greatly, and her
judgment has become questionable.
And your judgment is more sound?
There'll be no victor in a war
between our countries.
I'm quite confident there would be.
You're asking my government to apologize
for an attack we did not commit.
When I am queen,
I will disavow the apology
and make the truth known.
Why would I agree to this?
For the same reason
you're here at all.
We all know the Triangle
does not want a second war.
You turn your back on the Ganites,
and they'll be through your walls
in a matter of weeks.
The Ganites are cockroaches
and crushed under our boots
on a daily basis.
And all those boots are
mobilized in the west.
It would be a grave error
to underestimate our capabilities.
Yeah, I know.
But you know our queen
is capable of such errors.
So, do we have a deal?
So, Harlan, you've married
yourself a future queen.
A bold gamble, even for you.
Well, we're all slaves to
the vagaries of true love.
Thank you
for dining with me.
Gets so quiet when everyone's away.
Thank you for the ride this morning.
It was nothing.
It was not nothing.
I'd like to return the favor.
- Harmony?
- Your Highness?
Do you have it?
Yes, a portion for each of you.
Your service is a blessing.
Thank you, my Queen.
Have you
had thornflower before?
The journeyer?
It's forbidden.
I won't tell if you don't.
I've never taken journeyers before.
I'm honored to take your
first journey with you.
What are its effects?
I cannot explain it to you any more than
you can explain sight to me.
I'll give you the same amount I take.
Surely a man your size can handle that.
Now me.
And now we wait.
I don't feel anything.
To feel, you
have to touch.
Touch?
Yeah, I feel, uh...
I... I feel...
Not like that, Kofun.
Do you feel that?
Yes.
Oh, I feel that.
- Sibeth.
- Mmm?
Sibeth.
Should I stop?
No.
So, what do you think?
Scopus will make
the deal. Trust me.
- I don't trust you or him.
- Hey, Baba.
Ask your husband
how it is he has the ear
of a high-ranking Trivantian ambassador.
He does make a good point, Harlan.
It is suspicious.
I'm no spy.
So, what then?
The queen's tax.
It's fucking high and stupid.
So, in order to keep the city fortified
and keep my citizens
fed in leaner times,
I occasionally have to make the odd deal
beyond the reach of Kanzua.
It's thornflower. Coal.
So, you broke the law?
Cute. Yeah, I broke the
law for my people.
Mmm. No doubt taking a good
percentage for your efforts.
A fair one. The risk was all mine.
Look, we all have our
questionable pasts, don't we?
And you should be grateful for mine,
because otherwise we'd all be
skipping off to war right now.
So, Baba Voss, unless you got
any more pretty little threats for me,
I'm gonna go to sleep.
We have a peace to pretend
to negotiate in the morning.
It's been a long day.
We should all go to bed.
We can argue more tomorrow.
Uh, excuse me.
Get out of my way.
No.
How we sleep in private is one thing,
but Scopus just made a deal
with queen-to-be Maghra
and her king-to-be Harlan.
Can't let anything confuse that, can we?
If you touch her...
One of these days,
I'm gonna make you finish that sentence.
I'll sleep out here with you.
What?
He's a jackass, but he's right.
I don't want to be the reason
for your failure.
It's too cold for you out here anyways.
Go in.
You sure?
Yes.
We all know Trivantes
did not attack Kanzua.
But we also know your queen is
deranged enough to go to war anyway.
So, we will deal with her the way
you deal with a child having a tantrum.
In the interests of peace,
we will grant her the
apology she craves.
Thank you, Ambassador.
And in exchange for this lie,
you will accept the borders
as they are knotted on our maps.
Agreed?
We accept your proposal and thank you
on behalf of the Payan people.
Excellent.
Our clerks will have the day
to redraw the maps,
and we'll review them tomorrow
before we depart.
Uh, one more thing before we adjourn.
This, uh, business of your
queen embracing sight,
that must end.
If the sighted are allowed
to grow and prosper there,
no amount of border concessions
will save you from destruction.
Hello, Paris.
Hello.
I don't recall inviting you to join me.
I didn't want you to dine alone.
Maybe I like dining alone.
No one likes dining alone.
When I asked you to stay close to Kofun,
I did not mean turn him into a soldier.
Believe me, there's no risk of that.
I'm serious. He is under your care.
It is your responsibility to...
to guide him.
I'm teaching a boy
how to protect himself,
- nothing more.
- Toad.
My whole life, I was
taught to kill witches.
Now you tell me I must protect them.
So, why should I trust you?
You must trust yourself.
You, and you alone, are responsible
for every choice you make, man.
What if I choose wrong?
You won't.
How do you know?
Because...
I can tell you are a good man...
with a very stupid name.
Good man.
Good morning.
Hi.
Are you regretting last night?
I... I've just never done that before.
What is new is always frightening...
but also exciting.
I wouldn't wanna do anything
that makes you uncomfortable.
These days that seems to be everything.
You've had a hard time.
You don't know who to trust.
Let's make a pact, right now.
I will never lie to you.
You will never lie to me.
Even when the things we tell each
other might be painful to hear.
Agreed?
Agreed.
This peace...
it's built on so many lies.
And it won't stand.
Maybe there's a greater truth
beyond all the lies.
And what truth is that?
That no one wants war.
I wish I was as hopeful as you are.
Well...
if you stay close,
maybe it will rub off.
Intruders! Wake up!
What's happening?
Commander Watts?
Who's there?
Who's...
Help! Help! Guards!
We've been betrayed!
Scopus.
I'm sorry.
- No.
- Wren.
Papa, stay back!
You. You did this.
Wren. No.
This was your plan all along.
No, it wasn't us.
You knew I was the only one
who could stop this.
- Wren.
- You kept me up there.
You used me.
No. No.
Wren, wait!
This assassin has Payan markings.
Sibeth.
Shit.
She was never gonna allow a treaty.
This whole summit was just a way
for her to wage a war we couldn't stop.
I almost admire her,
if it weren't for the fact
she's gonna get us all killed.
We need to move.
The Trivantians will be here
before the God Flame rises.
Kofun?
Sibeth.
I'm so sorry to wake you.
No, what's wrong?
Something's happening.
I'm not safe here.
What... What's... What is it?
What's happening?
Well, nothing yet, but
something will. I'm sure of it.
You are the only one I trust.
Y-You can stay with me.
Thank you.
How was your trip?
You don't seem surprised.
That Queen Kane
wanted war? No. I'm not surprised.
I tried to warn the Triangle.
Those soldiers didn't have to die.
There's something else
you should know.
The attack...
I believe it was led by Baba Voss.
So Baba and his children
fight for the queen now.
It was I who drew him here
and let him escape.
If this gets out, the Triangle
will call for my head.
They will not hear it from me.
You're the only survivor.
The Triangle will have questions.
The first of those questions will be:
How is it that the lone survivor
of the attack was my own captain?
You think I'm a traitor?
No. Of course not.
I've known you since you were a child.
Still, the ground does continue
to shift under our feet.
So I need to know the answer
to this question, Captain.
How is it that you alone survived?
- I would have thought you would be glad...
- Answer me.
Because I can see.