Okay, Barnaby.
Okay, sweet boy,
it's time to go.
I love you.
Go ahead.
Hi, you've reached Simone.
I can't get to the phone right now
but leave a message...
Jesus.
- They had just over...
- Ow! Son of a bitch!
...face the most formidable enemy
the United States had ever encountered.
- For the first time, American troops...
- Dad.
...would go head-to-head
with Hitler's entrenched defenses.
You're just getting in?
I didn't hear the car.
Yeah, I had... a rough night.
It's impounded.
Again?
Jesus, could your movie be any louder?
Leave it.
I like it. It's good company.
What's that?
It's an edible arrangement.
I found it on the stoop.
A what?
It's, um...
a flower arrangement made out of fruit.
You're supposed to eat it.
Who the hell would send us that?
Oh, Simone.
Why would she send us fruit?
Because she is a self-centered,
gutter-rat whore.
Don't talk about your sister like that.
She was nice to send this.
Ooh, a strawberry.
Fuck this.
Dad...
...there's beer and Stouffer's pizza
in the kitchen.
I'll be back.
Where are you going?
- Devon!
- Bitch.
Bitch.
Hey.
Ethan.
I have to go.
I'm late for work.
- Mmm. No, no. Simone. Wait. No.
- No, I have to go.
- Wait, Simone. Stay.
- There's too much to do.
I can't be late.
No, wait, hold on a second.
I just had
the craziest, most amazing idea.
Why don't you just tell Michaela
that we're dating?
- That's really funny.
- It's not like she's gonna care.
What do you mean?
She's definitely gonna care.
She's my boss,
and she said I cannot date anyone here.
Yeah, but th... that's cuckoo bananas.
Our summer fling is about to end anyway.
Ouch.
Well, I mean, like, logistically.
Practically.
Labor Day is on Monday,
so all summer romances are
categorically over.
Keep talking logistics to me.
It's so hot.
Okay, but I... I really have to go, so...
- I'll see you later. Okay, my love?
- Mmm. Mmm.
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
Uh--
Did you just call me your "love"?
I'm rushing. I didn't, um...
Doesn't sound very categorically over.
- What?
- I'm gonna go.
- Just wait, wait...
- Okay, bye.
Wait. Come here.
- Okay. Okay.
- Come here.
You can be a little bit late.
- Mmm, yeah.
- Yeah.
Yeah, you're gonna stay.
Oh my God.
What's up, pink pants? You got a problem?
Kids.
Can't smoke out here, miss.
I can't hear you.
No smoking on board.
You light that, you will be fined.
Well, it's a two-hour ride,
Paul.
I gotta put something in my mouth.
Do we have an ETA?
Anyone have eyes on her?
One minute.
You're cutting a little close there, honey.
- What's in that?
- Turmeric, uh, bee pollen, ginger.
She's off ginger. Make it again.
- She's not gonna drink it?
- Make it again.
Oh, okay, great.
I was hoping I got to do that.
Get these out of here.
She'll shit.
- Good morning, Mrs. Kell.
- Hi, Kiki.
Oh my God, feel my hands.
They're still shaking.
He hesitated at first,
but then he unfurled his wings
and he soared into the sky.
It was sublime.
I am so proud of him.
Congratulations.
- Hey hey.
Mrs. Kell, your smoothie.
Thank you so much, Patrice.
Not today.
What time does Peter get back today?
I got an alert
that they were delayed leaving Tokyo,
but, um, let me see what I can find out.
Just ask Liam.
Oh, Peter gave him
the weekend off for Labor Day.
Oh my God.
- Should I have given you the weekend off?
- With the gala? No, I wouldn't let you.
I'll get an ETA. I'm into it.
Great, thanks.
Oh, your dress is done.
They're flying it in today.
Setting a fitting for Sunday a.m.
Perfect.
And I told Tom you wanna do the gold eye.
No, bronze.
- I want a bronze eye.
- Bronze eye? Right, sorry.
Bronze eye.
We should sext Peter,
let him know I'm looking forward to
some husband and wife time.
Okay, good idea.
Got it. Right.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay, wait.
Give me more boob.
We need more boob squeeze.
- Okay.
- Yeah, right.
- Okay, chin up.
- Uh-huh.
Hot, literally so hot.
- Ah.
- You're literally a goddess.
Oh, come on, don't.
No, you are.
Say something dirty, but not too dirty.
Uh...
Okay.
I wanna ride you
when you get home,
Daddy.
- Nice.
We have a few time-sensitive things
for when we're back.
- Like?
- Last minute gala RSVPs.
I did a pass on our revised seating chart.
- And what's the head count?
- 110.
And John Legend agreed to do
a short set for such a good cause.
Excellent.
- We need to write my gala toast.
- Oh. Done.
It's in your cloud.
- What would I do without you?
- Uh, you would hire a new assistant?
No.
I wouldn't.
You're irreplaceable.
And I don't wanna imagine a world
without you in it with me.
Me neither, Kiki.
Hey, do you happen to know
where this house is?
Sure, everybody knows the Cliff House.
Fare is 75 bucks.
- Holiday pricing.
- Oh, fuck.
Or you can walk.
Last house, way out on the point,
few miles past the lighthouse.
- A few miles past the lighthouse?
- Yeah.
Hi, Joel.
Oh, Mrs. Kell, hello.
- How's he doing?
- Oh, he's doing amazing.
- Where is he? Can I see?
- Yeah, of course.
Here, come on back.
All right.
You see, you let Barnaby out
here on Grand Point,
and he's already here.
Caught a southwest wind.
He's really feeling himself.
I told you he'd be okay.
You said it was too soon, but I know him.
You were right.
What an amazing rehabilitation.
Most rescue organizations,
they would have left Barnaby for dead.
We are not most rescue organizations.
Where's our new visitor?
Right over here.
Hi.
Hi there, little guy.
What's your name?
What do you think, huh?
Hi.
Good boy.
Yeah.
Aw, Winston.
We're so happy to have you.
Oh God.
Fuck!
Stop talking about me, Jose.
- I'm not.
- I know you guys shit-talk me.
On your little group text chain.
What group text chain?
Why are these blue?
Hydrangea is blue.
No, we wanted white or white-ish blue.
Never blue. Who signed for this?
I don't know.
Okay.
Listen up, everyone.
It is Labor Day weekend.
The Kells are entertaining every day,
and we have a black-tie event Monday.
We need to tighten up our game, okay?
All details flow through me.
Yeah. Simone is captain now.
Shut up, Jose.
I'll get floral back over here too.
- Simone.
- What?
There's a transient person
at the house asking for you.
She's carrying hot garbage.
What?
She says she's your sister.
Oh my God. No. No, no, no.
Do not be Devon. No. No, no, no.
No. No. No. No.
Oh no.
No, no, no. No.
No, Devon, no.
- No. Why?
- Fuck you, you fucking bitch.
- You sent me an edible arrangement?
- How did you even get this address?
I told you dad got diagnosed
with early-onset dementia,
and you sent a fruit basket?
Okay, okay, I can see that you're upset,
but this is a really bad time for me
right now.
- We're about to host a reception.
- Okay.
Well, then don't send me fruit,
you stupid bitch!
Welcome, ladies.
Sips and nibbles are in the back.
Thank you.
What is this place?
And why does everyone
look like an Easter egg?
Look, Devon, I can't talk right now.
I am working.
- I work here.
- Mmm. You are always working.
You've been sending me
to voicemail for months.
Yes, it's the high season.
What the hell is a high season?
It's when society is here,
like, summering.
Who are you?
- Devon.
- No, seriously.
You're dressed like a doily.
Where are your tattoos?
I removed them.
Our matching sister tattoo?
It was trashy.
It was trashy?
And your face is weird too, isn't it?
- Did you do something to your face?
- No.
Oh my God.
- You got a nose job?
- No, I...
When did you get a nose job?
Okay, I... I fixed my deviated septum
back in April. Kiki has a guy.
The fuck is Kiki?
Oh, Michaela, she's my boss.
I get to call her Kiki,
which is a... it's a really special honor.
Hi, girlies. Hi, just go on back. Yeah.
- Easter egg. Easter egg. Easter egg.
- Okay.
Devon.
You have to go.
- Where?
- I don't know where.
All right? Just anywhere but here.
Simone, I just traveled 17 hours
to see you.
I don't know. You should've called first.
I don't have time for you.
I don't have time for you today.
I don't know why I didn't think of that.
Make time.
Otherwise,
I'm gonna be having sips and nibbles
with all the rest of those Barbies.
No.
You wouldn't.
Okay, fine, fine, fine.
I will hide you in the... guesthouse
until this is over.
You, clean this up.
Is this still their property?
Uh, yeah, it's a compound.
Jesus, you said they were rich,
not oligarch rich.
Who is this guy?
Peter Kell of the Kell Securities.
The famous hedge fund.
Worth billions.
Asshole.
He's actually, like, super nice.
So is Kiki.
Yeah? What does she do?
Well, she was a high-powered attorney,
but now she does, like, volunteer work
and animal activism.
- Bitch. Whore.
- Devon.
Sorry. I have rich people Tourette's.
Okay, uh, don't touch anything.
Don't talk... to anyone.
Uh, don't sit on the furniture,
and don't touch the linens.
Uh, Zeus, turn up the AC.
Yeah, cool, Georgia O'Keeffe. I have that.
No, you don't. That's real.
- Okay, I will be back.
- When?
When I am done working.
Okay? Oh, you can make yourself a drink.
Not top shelf, though.
I don't drink.
- You don't drink? Since when?
- I'm sober.
I've been trying to be sober
for the past six months.
Is that why you texted me "Sirens"?
Not much of an SOS code
if you don't answer.
Dad keeps asking me where Mom is.
His memory's getting really bad.
Last week he got lost
trying to get to the VA,
and, um, the police found him
in the parking lot of a 7-Eleven.
I have to drive him
to all of his doctor's appointments.
- I have to pick up all of his medications.
- I can send you money.
I don't want money, Simone.
I need help with Dad.
I don't do Dad.
Tough titty. It's your job too.
I've been... losing my mind
trying to do all of this by myself.
We have some tough choices to make.
He's not gonna be able
to take care of himself much longer.
- That's not my problem, so.
- Simone.
Who's this?
Kiki. Oh my God!
Hi!
- Our guests are congregating.
- Uh...
Th... This is my, uh, sister, Devon.
She just... showed up here
completely unannounced.
- Did I know you had a sister?
- I'm sure I've... I've mentioned her, yeah.
Hi.
Hi, Devon.
I'm Michaela... Kell.
How's it going?
It's, uh...
It's quite the house you have here.
Oh, quite a sister you have here.
Not a huge resemblance, is there?
No.
Uh, Devon looks like our dad.
I look more like our mom.
You did, before you fucked with your nose.
By the way, um,
the next time one of your "guys"
is gonna do plastic surgery on my sister,
maybe let me know.
People die under general anesthesia.
- I didn't know she was going under.
- I didn't know you existed.
Well, now you do.
Wow.
I just, um...
I can't believe that you two
are meeting right now.
My brain is like, "What?"
- It's crazy.
- I know. It's marvelous.
And I just wanna tell you
how much I adore this sister of yours.
- Aw.
- She is sweet and kind and good
and we have been true-blue friends
from the minute we met.
- Right?
- Yeah, instant besties.
It's like a total mind merge.
Good for you.
I can't usually be friends
with people who pay me.
Okay.
So, let's head over to the reception.
- Yeah.
- And we'll let your sister unpack.
Oh, she's not staying here.
I'm just sticking her in here for now.
- Okay. Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
Yeah, I'm just gonna crash
wherever Simone lives.
- Where do you live?
- I live here, stupid.
You live at work?
I'm a live-in assistant.
I have my own suite in the main house.
Oh. Looks like I will be staying.
That's fine.
We're very, very happy to have you.
Let me know where your luggage is.
I'll have it sent over, sweetheart.
Oh, no luggage.
I'm just gonna wash my undies in the sink.
Great.
How did I not know you had a sister?
I don't bring her up
because she does stuff like this, like...
She shows up, periodically, to smear
her hot mess disaster sauce all over me.
I'm so sorry, Kiki.
- Do you want me to make her leave?
- No, I mean, she came all this way.
I'll get her out of here tomorrow.
What do you think she wants?
What she always wants.
To make me feel guilty
because I left Buffalo.
Anything in my teeth?
Nope. Me.
Perfect.
Breath?
Ten out of ten.
Mine?
Six.
Mmm. Take my gum.
OMG, Kiki, you look drop-dead.
Predicting a major fundraising today.
I feel alive, and also happiness.
Let's go save some wildlife, bitches.
Oh yeah!
Hey, Ray.
Where the hell are you?
Your shift started two hours ago.
I'm glad you called. I need a favor.
No, no, D. You're supposed to be
on the floor right now.
I just sat you.
Yeah, not gonna make it in.
- What do you mean?
- I had to go out of town quick.
Devon, this is your job.
If you don't show up, I have to fire you.
Ray, you know you can't fire me.
Listen, I need you to go to my house
and check on my dad, okay?
What? No fucking way. I'm not doing that.
His pajamas are in the dryer.
Just drink a Labatt with him, you know?
Maybe help him with his butt cream.
Hell no! I'm not babysitting your dad, D.
I have a restaurant to run.
I'll call your wife.
That is not funny.
Tell her you're my sometimes fuck boy.
- Do not call me that. That's hurtful.
- I know her number.
No, you don't.
716-847-1065.
All right, tell your dad
I'll be there before dinner.
Hello, can I help you?
Yeah, I'm trying to go outside
and I can't.
So sorry about that. Here, try now.
Oh, and by the way,
there's a strict no-smoking policy
on the grounds, Miss DeWitt.
Hello?
Jesus Christ!
Fuckety, fuck, fuck, fuck!
Jesus!
There's no smoking on the property.
I'm outdoors. This is outdoors.
Oh no, no.
This is a nature preserve. You are in
a federally protected wildlife sanctuary.
It is illegal to smoke.
Please do not light that cigarette.
- One puff.
- You don't understand, lady.
No, you don't understand, man.
I just worked a double at Falafel Balls
and spent the night in jail
and then I slept
on a fucking Peter Pan bus.
Can you just throw me a bone, please?
You a Bills fan?
Yeah, go Bills! Why? You?
- Dolphin fan.
- Oh.
- Ah.
- Yeah.
Fuck the Chiefs?
Oh, the Chiefs can get fucked.
- Fuck the Chiefs.
- Yeah.
Okay, we have a spot. Follow me.
Right here, see?
No cameras.
This is the staff.
This is Missy, Eddy. Guys.
This is Simone's sister, Devon.
What the hell, Jose?
She's gonna rat us out to her sister.
Oh, relax. She's cool.
I vetted her.
She just wants to have a cigarette.
Give me a bagel.
You guys are pretty hungry, huh?
Carbs aren't allowed on the property
ahead of the Gala Monday.
- Fucking starving.
- Who banned carbs, Michaela?
We can't talk about her.
Whole staff's on an NDA.
Oh, excuse me.
Guys, break is over. Come on, let's go.
- Yes, Peter.
- Jose.
Be careful here, sis.
Careful of what?
- Simone.
- Sorry.
Yeah.
- Look at this.
- Hmm?
He hasn't liked our sext.
I mean, he's seen it,
but he hasn't replied.
- He usually replies immediately.
- Uh...
Maybe he's lost signal.
He's in the air, after all.
Is he definitely in the air?
Yeah, I assume so. He's gone so quiet.
Stop.
Where's the rose garnish?
Manifest said he departed
2130 local time, so...
- Let me know when you get confirmation.
- Yeah, of course.
Your sugar, yes, please
Won't you come and put it down on me?
Hey, don't bury it, huh?
I'm not the valet.
Oh, God, I'm sorry. You were coming at me.
You're dressed like a... like a valet.
- There he is.
- Yeah, that's...
Sorry about that. Um...
- Can I escort you to the kitchen?
- I'm not going to the kitchen.
Oh, aren't you a... Are you?
Sorry, are you not a cater waiter?
You're... You're wearing all black,
and you've got a whimsical hairstyle.
Yeah.
I don't work here.
I'm just visiting my sister.
Oh. Who's your sister?
Simone.
Simone? The... The assistant?
Yeah.
Oh. Um...
You are her sister, huh?
I don't know how
I can make it any clearer, buddy.
Oh, sorry. Um...
Simone and I, we... we talk a lot,
and she's just never mentioned a sister.
Huh. Well, she should have.
I basically raised her in Buffalo.
- Buffalo, New York?
- Yeah, that's where we grew up.
Well, it's where I grew up.
She was in and out of foster care
until I finally got custody of her,
but you know, that's...
Who are you?
Ethan Corbin.
Uh, Ethan Corbin III,
if we're... if we're going all in.
Yeah, I live next door.
Well, not exactly next door.
All the way down on the end there.
- Hmm.
- Maybe Simone has mentioned me?
No.
Well, uh... can I escort you inside?
Okay.
Then I will walk adjacent to you,
like in Victorian times, yes?
No, did you, uh... did you two meet?
Yeah, very briefly.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
No, we didn't get properly introduced
because I, uh...
- I... Well, I...
- He thought I was the valet.
- You didn't.
- Yeah.
Uh, I'll go fetch us some drinks.
What would you like, milady?
Pass.
- And for Ms. DeWitt, the usual?
- Yeah, thank you so much. Thank you.
That guy's an asshat. I hate it here.
Are you almost done?
I told you I'm at work.
I came to talk to you,
not sit in some weird guesthouse all day.
What is this, some kind of ceremony?
Devon, Devon, please,
go back to the house.
I'm just gonna sit in the back.
No one's even gonna notice I'm here.
Everyone is noticing you.
You're dressed like a roadie.
It's fine. I'll be cool.
Let us come together.
Hi. Hi.
Oh, thank you.
So, um, I didn't realize
you were from Buffalo.
Yeah, upstate New York.
Yeah, but you said upstate New York
in a Westchester way
or... or like Darien, Connecticut, you know?
No one knows where... where Buffalo is,
so it's just... it's easier to say upstate.
Right. I thought you were a Yale girl.
I am a Yale girl.
People who don't come from money
can... can also go to Yale.
- You know? Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
And, I mean, you were in foster care?
That's, like, you're from tough times.
I'm so sorry that that happened to you.
We will begin as we always begin.
Whoa, is she holding a scepter?
- "In every outthrust headland..."
- Why?
"...in every curving beach..."
"...in every grain of sand,
there's the story of the Earth."
- What is this?
- "There is something infinitely healing..."
It's a... It's a poem by the patron saint
Rachel Carson. That's how we always begin.
"The assurance that dawn comes after night
and spring after winter."
"Change is eternal,
change is life."
Hey hey.
- Okay, this is officially a cult.
- Now...
- You're in a cult.
- Okay, stop.
I am very proud to announce
that this morning...
Ow, what's your problem?
- ...released Barnaby, the peregrine falcon.
- Stop it!
- Did you tell Ethan I was in foster care?
- So? Who cares?
I care.
It's my past.
It's up to me who I share it with.
I'm sorry.
I didn't realize that was a secret
we had to keep from rich douchebags.
He's not a douchebag. He's...
He's my boyfriend.
Simone, don't be mean.
He's 400 years old.
You... You cannot tell anyone, Dev,
but, um, we've been quietly dating
since June.
- Promise me you won't say anything.
- Wait, you aren't joking?
No.
There's duckies on his blazer.
I... like his duckies.
No, you don't. You like his Rolex.
Our biggest fundraiser of the year,
the Labor Day Gala, is on Monday.
You don't know the first thing
about our relationship.
What I know, Simone, is that you've been
too busy waiting on a trophy wife
and fucking Mr. Duckie to show up for me.
No. These people are my friends.
Oh, grow up, Simone. You're the help!
...support--
Where was I?
Um, the proceeds will support
the rehabilitation...
Don't move.
...of our newest resident,
Winston, the baby red-tailed hawk.
Aw.
- Can I get a "hey hey"?
- Hey hey!
Hey hey!
Hi.
Let's you and me take a walk.
What do you think of the view?
Uh, where did Simone go?
I love to stand here and look out.
Makes me think of Moby Dick times.
Cool.
All those sailors
crashing their boats on the rocks.
All the blood.
Sometimes I think
I can still hear the whales
singing their mournful song.
Do you hear it?
Mournful whale songs, yeah.
- So listen, I really gotta find Simone.
- There she is. Thank you.
This... is for you.
What is it?
Look.
What is this? Why are you giving me...
$10,000?
It's a gift for you.
I...
I don't want your money.
No, caring for aging parents
is such an expense to pay.
No.
No, Michaela, not okay. I didn't come here
because I want your money.
I came here because
I want my sister...
to help me.
And voilà.
- Jose.
- Sí, mi amor.
Would you take Devon to the Whaler Inn?
We have you booked in the Admiral Suite
and you are leaving
in the first flight out tomorrow morning,
business class.
Sorry, what?
Um...
Are you kicking me out? Is that--
Well, it's just...
it's such a busy weekend, so...
Yeah.
Can I speak to you privately, Simone?
I think that it's best that you go, Devon.
Hello?
Are you seriously gonna let
this bitch bribe me to leave?
- This way, please.
- Wait.
It was terrific to meet you.
Simone!
Safe home.
Hey, let's go. Come on.
Hey, you wanna go see the old lighthouse?
It's got the best sunset view.
I can drive by if you want.
No.
Thanks.
Hey, come on,
don't take it so personally, huh?
How much did they give you?
$10,000.
$10,000?
Wow, that's...
that's not bad.
You know, the... the Whaler Inn is nice too.
Oh, uh, sorry, but when you can,
you know, if you... if you don't mind,
uh, can you sign this, please?
No, I'm not signing an NDA.
Well, if you don't sign it,
then it'll be like a whole thing.
Just sign it
and forget about this place, you know?
Good.
You wanna come up front with me?
I'll let you smoke.
You're gonna eat your words
when the Dolphins win the Super Bowl.
Okay. No, no, no,
let me get the door for you. Come on.
Uh...
- You don't have to do that.
- Stay there.
The car service will be here at 8:00 a.m.
to take you to the airport.
Hey, thanks.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, no, yeah.
- What are you doing?
- Ugh!
- I have a wife. I have a son.
- Yeah, sorry, I'm sorry.
Ugh!
God.
It's a thing I... It's a thing I do.
You lick people?
I don't mean to do it. It's... I...
I don't do it on purpose.
I'm texting someone about it.
Texting someone?
Yeah, I got a text therapist, you know?
Real one's too expensive, so...
Okay, crazy.
The room is under your name.
She put a card down for incidentals,
so go ahead and do your worst. Okay?
- Hey, Jose.
- Yeah.
I'm really sorry.
It's fine.
Okay.
Don't lick nobody in there,
though, please.
I won't.
Okay. Okay.
Oh shit.
Uh...
Hey, Dad, you okay?
No, someone's breaking in.
No, Daddy, I texted you about this.
Remember, that's my friend Raymond.
Remember Ray from high school?
He's not in high school. He's old.
I'm 32, sir.
I asked him to come check on you.
He's fine. He's watching war movies.
I'm gonna go.
No. You gotta stay
and cook the pizza for him,
and then cut it up
into little pieces, all right?
When are you coming home?
Uh...
Tomorrow.
And, hey, in the morning, Ray's gonna
bring over your medication, okay?
What? I am?
Where are you, honey? I... I miss you.
Thanks, Dad. Uh...
Yeah, I, uh... I'm with Simone.
Simone?
Why didn't you say so?
How's she doing?
Great.
Yep, really good
and, uh, really excited to see me too.
So, just, uh...
We're just having some sister time.
Really, she's okay?
I don't hear from her.
Does she get my emails?
Uh...
I... I don't know, Dad.
Will you tell Simone that I love her?
And if she ever wants
to come home to visit,
it would be wonderful to see her.
I know I don't deserve it.
Yeah, listen, I gotta go, all right?
- I'll talk to you later. Bye.
- Wait. Wait, no.
Can I help you?
Yeah.
Can you put all this on room 19?
Thanks.
All right, there you go.
Hi. Something to drink?
Uh, seltzer water for me
and whatever he's drinking.
You're buying me a drink?
Expense account.
- Thank you.
- Oh, for sure.
Enjoy.
So,
where are you from?
Can we just go,
or do you need a little small talk first?
Uh, I think I need some... some small talk.
Oh, cute, okay. Um...
Christina
Grey from Seattle.
Uh, I'm a tech millionaire.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
I feel like you just made that up.
- Your turn.
- Okay.
I'm Jordan St. Clair from L.A.
- I'm in real estate and high-end sneakers...
- Ah.
...and that's my yacht out there.
Oh.
I was gonna suggest my hotel room,
but a boat...
That's way better.
So, have you had enough small talk yet?
- Yeah, I'm good.
- Okay.
Can I finish my drink?
I don't know.
Are you gonna sip it like a baby?
Dock's this way.
- Wait, you actually have a boat?
- Yeah.
And keys.
- Got something for ya.
- Ooh.
Wait, why do you have this?
Anderson's Beef on Weck.
This is my sister's sweatshirt.
What's Beef on Weck?
This belongs to my sister.
How do you know Simone?
Simone's your sister?
Oh God.
- Are you dating her too?
- No, no.
Simone is... is dating my boss, Ethan.
This is his boat.
What? I thought this was your boat.
I'm the captain.
Sorry. We were...
We were doing the lying game.
Oh, I just fucked
my sister's boyfriend's boat guy
in my sister's boyfriend's bed.
Wow, sorry. Uh...
I wasn't lying
about being into you, though.
We were really vibing down there,
don't you think?
I mean, come on,
is your... is your name really Christina?
- It's Devon.
- Yeah.
And you're the second guy
I fucked on a boat today.
Okay.
I think I miss the lying game.
Don't say it.
- I have to go. I know.
- No, no, no.
Peter's flight keeps getting delayed,
and... and Kiki's restless.
Okay, can I...
can I talk to you about something?
What about...
- About what? What?
- No, it's okay.
Well, I know we kind of stumbled
past it this morning, but, um...
I really do love you, Simone.
I'm in love with you.
I wanna know everything about you,
even your childhood.
If you love me,
you won't make me talk about this.
Can I at least know
who your family members are?
Well, I had a mom,
but she died.
I have a dad.
We don't speak.
Um...
I have a sister.
- Ah, yeah.
- That is her.
The rest is control-alt-delete.
Why were you in foster care?
Please. Can we...
- Okay.
- Thank you.
All right.
But did you hear the "I'm in love
with you" part of what I said?
I love you too.
Ah.
Is that the Cliff House?
Hard to miss.
There's a scope over there
if you wanna take a better look.
What's the deal with that place?
- It really seems like a cult.
- Yeah.
Don't let Michaela hear you say that.
What's with all the cameras?
And apparently she, like,
controls everything the staff eats.
Yeah, I've heard.
You know they call
your sister Mini Michaela, right?
She does this.
She gets swept up in other people.
Loses herself.
The only person
who knows the real Simone is me.
Who's the real Simone?
A traumatized little girl
who's always trying to outrun her past.
She was really not herself today.
I mean, there was something, like,
gone... behind her eyes.
- You know?
- Yeah.
Like a zombie.
I don't know.
Something just doesn't feel right
about leaving her up there.
Barnaby!
Oh no!
No! No!
Barnaby! No!