[haunting vocalization]
[alluring vocalization]
[vocalization ends]
[buoy bell tolling in distance]
- [seagulls cawing]
- [boat horn blowing in distance]
[Simone] Kiki!
[wind whooshing]
Kiki!
Kiki, wait!
[echoing] Kiki, I'm sorry!
Kiki!
[wind howling]
[man screaming]
[scream echoing]
- [ominous music playing]
- [labored breathing]
[labored breathing]
[music intensifies]
Monster!
- [gasps]
- Hey, hey, it's a dream. You're dreaming.
It's just a nightmare. You're okay.
[inhales deeply] I'm here.
[breathing heavily]
Where am I?
You're in the guesthouse. I brought
you back here last night with Jose.
- You had a really bad panic attack.
- I did?
Yeah.
Did anyone see?
[breathing heavily]
No. Um...
You were in the pantry.
I told them all you had food poisoning.
Wait, what... what... what time is it?
- Like, 7:00 something.
- In the morning?
- Yeah.
- Wait, in the... [mumbles]
- Hey, Simone.
- Uh...
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa. Be careful.
I gave you two Xanax. Take it slow.
[panting]
Where's my...
What's the...
Um... [exhales]
I don't know what to do.
About what?
[exhales] I don't...
I don't know what... what to do.
- What's going on? Talk to me.
- I missed jogging.
- Okay.
- 'Cause... 'Cause...
'Cause we run, you know,
we run every morning.
- Where's... Where's my phone?
- Hey, Simone. Breathe.
- I lost my phone.
- You didn't.
- I plugged it in. It's right over there.
- Okay.
[Simone panting]
Did you do something to my phone?
- I don't have any messages or texts.
- Hey, whoa, crackhead.
I picked you up off the floor last night
and took care of you.
No, you don't understand, Dev.
I'm going to get fired.
- For missing jogging?
- [sobbing]
No, because she knows
that I'm dating Ethan.
She knows I've been lying.
Oh my God, I'm such an idiot.
This is all gonna... gonna...
It's all gonna go away now.
I'm gonna get fired.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
- [sobbing]
Hey, would it be the worst thing
if she did fire you?
- Yes. [sobbing]
- This place is giving you panic attacks.
No, you are giving me panic attacks.
What are you still doing here?
I told you. I need help with Dad.
[Simone] And I said, "No."
You don't get to say no to me, Simone.
And guess what? Everything that happened
to you as a kid happened to me too.
This isn't just the Simone show.
I had to live what Mom did.
So? I had to see it,
and I had to sign for it.
- I had to save you from it.
- [scoffs]
- You don't think that fucked me up?
- No, I don't. I am the fucked up one.
- I think we're both fucked up.
- No, it's me. It really is me.
- I... I am super fucked up.
- Oh yeah? Well, quadruple your fucked up.
Climb to the top of Fucked Up Mountain,
and that's how fucked up I am.
- You're absolutely fine.
- I am not fine.
- Yes, you are!
- I just got my second DUI.
Wait, what do you mean your second?
I'm a drunk like Dad.
And I'm drowning,
and I'm waving a flag at you,
and your hand's on the doorknob.
Please.
Let her fire you.
[door slams]
[footsteps receding]
[curious music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[Simone] Kiki.
Kiki.
Kiki!
[music intensifies]
Ki-- Kiki!
[music fades]
[pensive music playing]
[bottle scraping]
[liquid sloshing]
[leaf blower whirring]
[contemplative music playing]
[sighs deeply]
[door creaking]
[leaf blower whirring]
[leaf blower powering down]
[Simone] Kiki.
Kiki!
Oh, hey, Simone.
I am... I am so sorry I'm late.
It's not the Army.
You don't have to do morning PT.
[Michaela panting]
How's your tummy?
Your sister said you were, uh,
and I quote, "Peeing out your ass."
Oh, I'm fine now. I am. Look, I'm so sorry
I disappeared on you last night.
Don't worry about it.
Get some rest.
We'll... We'll catch up later.
Kiki, are you mad at me?
Is that a yes?
You seem mad.
Why would I be mad?
Me and, uh, Ethan,
I... I know that you know.
Honey, I don't care who you date.
Your love life is your business.
- You're... You're not upset?
- No. Over a summer fling?
No.
Enjoy yourself.
[panting]
Use a condom, though. That man
greets the ferry with his fly down.
- Wait, does he?
- Yeah, and, uh, his finances are a mess.
He blew through his trust fund
a long time ago.
You're not serious about him, are you?
Well, I mean,
we... we were kind of getting serious.
He, um...
- He told me he loved me.
- [sighs] Ah.
I'm sure he did.
You know, I just... [sighs]
I just hate that you felt
that you couldn't tell me.
- Like I'm some kind of a monster.
- What?
Now I have this awful feeling
that you... that you keep things from me.
I don't, Kiki.
You are dating my husband's friend,
and you have a sister
that I don't know about.
Is there anything else?
No, that's it. I swear.
Did your mom really die in a car accident?
No.
But... But that's... that's not a lie.
Um...
She didn't...
- She didn't die in... in a car accident.
- Okay.
But, um, yeah, she did die in a... in a car...
Um...
She... She ran a tube from...
from the exhaust pipe
to the front seat and, um...
and killed herself.
Oh...
- How old were you?
- I was seven.
Um...
[sniffles]
I...
I was in the... I was in the back seat,
and she told me to...
Um...
[chuckles sadly] She...
She told me to color in my coloring book
until I fell asleep.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
Devon, she... she found us, pulled me out,
and rushed me to the hospital.
It's okay, Kiki.
They were able
to resuscitate me right away and...
Honey, nothing about that is okay.
- You know, it's not like--
- It's not okay.
It's not like I understood
what had happened to me at the time.
You know? I didn't... I didn't know.
I'm gonna take care of you.
[Simone sniffles]
And you'll get nothing but kindness,
nothing but goodness from now on.
- Yes, please. Thank you.
- Okay.
Thank you so much, Kiki.
[Simone sighs]
Thank you.
[Simone sobbing]
[Eddy exhales]
How long are you in town?
Bye.
[breathes deeply]
[exhales deeply]
Hey fucking hey.
[breathes deeply]
[bright music playing]
[birds chirping]
[indistinct chatter]
Oh, hey, Jose, Patrice.
Missy.
- Iron chefs.
- Wow, okay.
Does that dress, like, come
with batteries or something?
Ha-ha.
Shut up. Have you seen Simone?
- No.
- She's still out jogging with Mrs. Kell.
Nice. Do you mind if I make a coffee?
You know you can have that
brought to your guest house?
Oh, I got it. I'm not a real guest.
Are you sure? Because you were just added
to the VIP guest list for the gala.
I was?
Yes, you were.
Now, don't let it go to your head.
Okay.
Just be over here, then,
activating the chrome.
- I got you.
- Thanks. [sighs]
So, what's all this?
Is this, uh, prep for the gala?
This is for the cocktail hour
before the gala.
Ah, the party before the party.
Right. I like that.
How many of these galas
have you done, Patrice?
Uh, sixteen.
[softly] Sixteen. Wow.
So, you would know
Jocelyn Kell,
the first wife, wouldn't you?
[cutlery clatters]
Or should I say "knew"?
Past tense.
I feel like you guys
should be able to hear...
me, the words that I'm saying.
[unsettling music playing]
How far do these bitches run?
[phone clicks]
[keypad clacking]
[line ringing]
Hi, you've reached Bruce DeWitt.
This is his daughter, Devon.
He hates the phone, so just call me.
Uh...
[keypad clacking]
[line ringing]
[line clicks]
[on voicemail] Hey, you got Ray's phone.
[sighs]
[phone thuds on railing]
[gentle music playing]
Hey! Big sister!
Up here.
Oh, that's the way
to start the day, Big Cheese.
Come on in. The water's fine.
[Peter exhales]
I like the decor in here.
It's, uh, nautical, but make it stoner.
One corner of the house
that still gets to be mine.
- Isn't the whole house yours?
- Mmm.
[inhales deeply]
So, you having a nice time on the island?
[exhales] It's a vibe, man.
[both laugh]
[Peter] Yeah.
Hey, how are your dreams?
I... I always have the craziest dreams
when I'm on-island.
- Really?
- Mmm.
I don't dream.
Never?
I looked it up once.
It's either because I drink too much
or I have
a very severe personality disorder.
Um...
Both track, honestly.
Hmm.
You stay here long enough,
you'll start to dream.
Maybe you're dreaming right now.
[chuckles]
Who's dreaming? Me or you?
We could be sharing a dream.
It tends to happen around her. [chuckles]
Her?
Mmm.
I mean, here.
Sorry.
[Peter sighs loudly]
So, what are your plans today? Beach?
No, I'm just waiting
for my sister to get back from
the world's longest run with your wife,
who she seems to, uh,
really worship.
Yeah.
Kiki has that effect on people.
How did, uh...
How'd you guys meet?
Well, it's not the most romantic story.
Her firm represented
my company in a merger,
and she had to step down from the case,
and I had to step out of my marriage.
[inhales deeply]
But here we are. [exhales]
Happy ever after.
You okay, Big Cheese?
[inhales sharply]
Yeah.
Uh, actually, I have a tee time.
I gotta go.
[Devon] Oh.
Hey, finish this off for me.
I can.
And I will.
I'll see you when we wake up.
[footsteps receding]
[footsteps descending stairs]
- Mrs. Kell, FedEx--
- Terrific. Thank you, Missy.
[indistinct chatter]
[Patrice] Your smoothie.
Oh, it looks delicious.
No, thank you. Not today.
[sighing] The step and repeat.
Gives me chills every year.
Thank you, Jose, to you and your team
for all your hard work.
I know it will look amazing.
- Bravo.
- Thank you, mi amor.
Bravo.
[whispering]
Okay. Listen up, everyone.
- I have notes.
- [staff groaning]
[Jose] Oh, goodness.
[pensive music playing]
[Devon snoring]
[keypad clacking]
[slurping]
Wow.
Patrice, you make one hell of a smoothie.
- [both laugh]
- Thank you, sir. Thank you.
You know,
it's really a creative outlet for me.
[Peter] Hmm.
- It's one of my main creative outlets...
- Simone.
- ...'cause it's something-- Okay.
- Hold on one sec.
How are you feeling after last night?
Oh, I'm... I'm...
I'm okay. I just, um... I had a bad oyster.
[softly] Jose told me.
[Simone] Uh...
[mouthing] Yeah.
I get panic attacks too.
But, of course, you know that because
you schedule our marriage counseling.
Yeah, um, just please don't tell Michaela.
I just don't want her
to worry about me or...
No, no, no. I... I won't.
She views my attacks
as a... as a failure of will,
so I'm gonna spare you from that,
but I just want to make sure
that you are okay.
I find them really scary.
Yeah, they... [chuckles]
Yeah, they are, um,
but, um, yeah, no. I'm... I'm okay.
Okay.
[door opens, closes]
- Simone?
- [Simone] Yeah?
- Come look at this.
- Okay.
Uh, they're identical.
- Are you blind?
- No.
This ribbon is matte,
and this is ever so slightly metallic.
This is from Tokyo,
and this is from someplace sketchy,
like Soho House.
Well, the labels are the same.
If he didn't buy it in Japan,
he sure went through a lot of trouble
to make it look Japanese.
Exactly.
Oh, I... I don't know.
Kiki, like, I... I have his flight log,
and it says, "Arrival, 1300 hours,
Wednesday, Tokyo."
It's his jet.
He can say Planet Vulcan if he wants to.
Well, if he wasn't in Japan, where was he?
- [door opens]
- And with whom?
[door closes]
[Peter] Honey, are you in here?
Yeah. Um...
Hey. I thought you went golfing.
I was supposed to,
but Ethan is not picking up.
Hi.
[gasps]
Actually, you don't have
any idea where he is, do you?
Uh... Uh, no, we haven't talked yet today.
I can tell him you left word, though.
Yeah, right. I could...
I could leave word with you.
His lover. [inhales deeply]
- Simone?
- Yeah, sorry.
Are you having a stroke?
I just don't...
I just don't know what to say.
The whole thing is just so awkward.
What did you say to him, anyway?
It's weird that he's not texting me back.
- Who?
- Ethan.
When you were walking with him
on the cliff last night.
Oh... Oh, he won't be
bothering Simone anymore.
What does that mean?
[inhales deeply]
I know you weren't in Japan.
You said you were in Tokyo last week.
I know you weren't in Tokyo.
Honey... [chuckles]
I barely know where I am right now.
I mean, this is such bad jet lag.
Where were you, Pete?
Okay.
Fine.
I wasn't in Japan.
You figured it out.
I hope you're very happy
with yourself, Detective.
[dramatic music playing]
Where are you going?
We're in the middle of something.
[Peter] Or is it the end?
[keypad clacking]
[phone whooshes]
[dramatic music continues]
Jose.
Yes, Peter.
[pensive music playing]
Can you bring my Jeep around back?
Yeah, yeah. Right away.
Hey, uh...
[inhales deeply]
I want to go dark for a while.
Off the grid.
Can you, uh...
I'll handle it.
- Thanks, man. I appreciate you.
- Of course.
[tools whirring]
[tense music playing]
Follow him.
[softly] What?
What, like, actually follow him?
- Go.
- Okay. Okay.
[footsteps receding]
[dramatic music playing]
[music intensifies, ends]
Hi, Phil. It's me.
Sorry, I know it's a holiday
and you're on vacation,
but I need to talk to you.
Will you call me back?
[somber music playing]
[wind whooshing]
[gasps]
[breathing heavily]
[mysterious vocalization]
[inhales deeply]
[exhales]
[mysterious vocalization continues]
[exhales sharply]
[alluring music playing]
[music ends]
Like what you see?
Sorry. Sorry. Um...
I thought I heard singing.
First the gardener and now me.
Busy morning, Devon.
How do you know about that?
[water sloshing gently]
I know you.
[Michaela inhales deeply]
Simone is out on business
for the rest of the day.
She wanted me to tell you
she'd be back for dinner.
Dinner. [inhales]
I... I'm gonna let you get dressed.
- No, stay.
- [water sloshing]
I want to talk to you.
[footsteps treading]
Simone told me about your mom.
My mother died when I was young too.
It leaves a mark.
Walking around in the world, I can always
spot the motherless woman in the room.
Can't you?
[inhales sharply]
Let's pick this up when you're dressed.
Were you jealous?
When she chose Simone?
What kind of question is that?
Being spared is sometimes worse.
You're left to wonder,
"Why not me?"
My mother didn't spare me, Michaela.
[unsettling music playing]
She left me with a very sick man
and a very traumatized
little girl to raise.
That's too much responsibility
to put on you at such a young age.
You've worked so hard for so long,
haven't you?
Underneath all that armor,
you just need someone to say, "Good job."
I didn't do a good job.
Yes, you did.
You saved her.
No, I left her.
I went to college.
And she was all alone in that house
with... a clinically depressed dad
who didn't feed her
or bathe her
or keep the electricity on.
I was getting drunk at Ohio State.
She was in hell.
You came back.
She missed most of seventh grade.
When I came back,
she was dangerously thin.
She was suicidal.
You didn't know.
I did.
I just lied to myself. I...
I told myself she would be okay...
[inhales deeply]
...because I wanted to leave so badly.
[sobs softly]
What about Devon?
Who cares about Devon?
Who mothers Devon?
No one. [sobs]
I see you.
How special you are.
[eerie music playing]
I can help you.
We share the same pain.
You, me, and Simone.
We're birds of a feather.
Say it.
Birds of a feather.
[softly] Hey hey.
[eerie music continues]
♪ Whores in this house ♪
♪ There's some whores in this house ♪
♪ I said, certified freak
Seven days a week ♪
♪ Wet-ass pussy
Make that pullout game weak, whoo! ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
[singing along] ♪ Yeah, you fuckin'
With some wet-ass pussy ♪
♪ Bring a bucket and a mop
For this wet-ass pussy ♪
♪ Give me everything you got
For this wet-ass pussy... ♪
Take it, Dev!
♪ ...catch a charge
Extra large, and extra hard... ♪
What?
♪ Put this pussy right in yo' face... ♪
Sorry. Do I know you?
- [Lisa laughs]
- You're so funny, Devon.
So funny!
We met at the house.
We're Lisa, Astrid, and Cloe.
How did I get here?
Michaela told us
to take you out on the town for...
[in singsong] Girls' day!
What? No.
♪ ...park that big Mack truck... ♪
No! No! No!
You have to pull over.
[sobbing] No!
♪ There's some whores in this house ♪
Missy said you wanted to speak to me,
mi amor.
What a pretty dress.
- Shall I send the tailor up?
- Hmm.
Come in and take a seat.
Okay.
[Jose clears throat]
[grunts]
[keypad clacks]
- Jose.
- Hmm?
I just logged on to see when Peter
might be available for dinner tonight,
and our calendars are no longer synced.
- Hmm.
- Yeah.
All the passwords and PINs
have been changed,
and locations are off.
That sounds like an IT problem.
Don't play games with me, Jose.
What?
[laughs]
What game is this, huh?
English is not my first language.
- Oh, sí, sí. Claro.
- [Jose] Hmm.
[speaking Spanish]
[inhales sharply]
I'm sorry. Your accent.
[speaking Spanish]
Why'd you lock me out of the system?
Did Pete ask you to?
I don't even know how
to turn on the computer, mi amor.
All you do is computers.
I'm just a property manager, okay.
Okay.
Where was Peter last weekend?
Japan.
Where was he, really?
- Japan.
- All right, fine.
If you want to do it this way,
you're fired.
I... [laughs]
- You can't fire me.
- Oh, yes, I can.
It's come to my attention
that you've been writing abusive texts
about Simone to the staff,
so get your things and go.
No.
No?
What do you mean, no? You're fired.
I work for Peter, not for you.
I've been with him 19 years now.
Much longer than you have.
Contractually, you cannot fire me.
Neither could the first Mrs. Kell.
Not that she ever would have,
you see, because, well,
she was a kind woman.
Will there be anything else, mi amor?
No.
Okay. [clears throat]
Watch your fucking back, Jose.
Very good.
I'll call the IT guy and let him know
that you have an issue. ¿Sí?
- Sí.
- Good.
[indistinct chatter]
[Michaela on phone]
All right. What's he doing now?
Uh, he's buying weed at the Baked Clam.
[sighing] Ugh!
[Simone] Oh, it's a big haul.
Yeah, gonna be a very chill day.
Oh. Now he's looking
in the window of a bakery.
[Michaela] This is thrilling.
Um, he's not sure about the muffin.
He wants it, but he's torn.
[sighs]
[phone vibrating]
Ooh. I need to take this.
I'll call you back.
Everybody out.
[phone clicks]
[suspenseful music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
[indistinct chatter and laughter]
All right, have fun. See you later.
[redeeming music playing]
[car engine starts]
- [Michaela] What'd you find out, Phil?
- Yeah, there is a no-cheating clause.
That means if he is having an affair,
we can get the prenup voided,
but we need proof of infidelity.
Well, what counts as proof?
Not chocolate boxes.
You know, emails, pictures, videos, texts.
I can get that.
Look, I can't believe
someone let you sign this thing.
You're an attorney. I can't believe
you let yourself sign this thing.
I was being love-bombed by a billionaire.
I didn't care what it said.
I just dotted my i's with hearts.
I understand. All right.
Let me get into things on my end.
I'll call you back.
Phil, Phil, wh... what...
What if he's not having an affair?
You said he is.
What if I'm wrong,
and... and he files for divorce anyway?
Are there... are there
any financial protections for me?
Well, there are a lot
of provisions in the prenup,
primarily if you'd been able
to have children.
Well, that wasn't in the cards, was it?
Sorry. I know this is a painful subject,
but try to keep things positive at home.
Don't get shut out.
Just quietly gather proof.
Copy that.
Thanks, Phil.
All right. Talk soon.
[phone chimes]
[birds chirping]
Oh shit, shit, shit.
Simone?
Oh!
Peter!
That's a... That's a weird coincidence.
Did my wife have you follow me?
No, I just come here sometimes to clear...
[hesitating]
Yeah, I...
- I'm so sorry. Um...
- Wow.
She really is shameless.
Well,
park your bike right over there.
Oh, I'll just...
I'll tell her that I lost you.
Uh, nope. No, no, no.
You're busted.
Your penance is
you have to come quahogging with me.
What... What? What hogging?
Quahogging.
What's a...
- Come on.
- Oh, okay. Yeah.
[Lisa, Cloe, Astrid] Gala dress!
Gala dress! Gala dress! Gala dress!
Oh my God. Look at you serving
royalty-slay-smash-mama, ten out of ten.
[in unison] We'll take it.
No. This dress is $22,000.
- Kiki's treat.
- She insists.
- Treat, treat.
- [Devon] No.
I don't even look good in this dress.
I look like Beetlejuice.
[pensive music playing]
Devon, you listen to me right now.
- Listen to her, Devon.
- Listen to her.
You are beautiful.
You contain multitudes. You're a goddess.
- [in unison] We'll take it!
- No.
No.
Are these things really called quahogs,
or are you pulling my leg?
Quahog.
Also, the official clam of Rhode Island,
where I hail from.
I thought the Kells were OG New Yorkers.
On my mother's side.
Her father...
[grunts]
...was a fisherman
and her grandfather too,
which is why I look so good in these.
[Simone laughing] Okay.
It was the chocolate, wasn't it?
Michaela knew that
I didn't get it in Tokyo somehow.
Yeah, she, um...
she had a comparison box
overnighted from Japan.
The ribbon on one was matte,
not metallic.
Rookie mistake.
She thinks you're having an affair.
You think I'm having an affair?
You weren't where you said you were.
You cheated on your first wife.
I... I can see how she got there.
Oh.
The salsa is spicy.
[laughs]
The salsa works for Kiki.
Do you think my wife would be relieved
to hear that I'm not having an affair?
That I, in fact, was attending
the christening of my grandson?
Behind her back?
No, she'd shit.
Yeah.
You know how loaded this topic is for her.
And your kids have been awful to Kiki.
Well, they blame her
for my breakup with their mom.
Do you think that's fair?
I think it's maybe not a good woman
that wants me to sever ties
with my children for any reason.
I haven't seen my son in a decade,
and now, he's a dad.
He's holding his son.
That was...
That was the most glorious moment
in my life,
meeting that little baby,
and I'll...
never get those years back.
[sniffles]
Do you have a picture?
- Yes.
- Photo? Yeah?
- I do. Yeah.
- Can I see?
[gasps] Aw.
What's his name?
Jonathan Joseph Kell, after my father.
Johnny Joe.
He looks like you.
- Nah. You think so? [laughs]
- [laughing] Yeah. Yeah, he does.
Aw.
Thanks for listening.
Yeah, sure thing. [chuckles]
[laughing] There's nobody else
I can really talk to about this.
It's all good.
- All right.
- Okay.
[Peter] Quahog on.
[Simone] Quahog.
[glasses clinking]
[in unison] We'll take it.
[exhales sharply]
I... Uh...
I can't... I can't accept this.
Yes, you can.
Kiki calls it radical generosity.
It's a really big deal
that she invited you to the gala.
- She obviously sees potential in you.
- [chuckling]
Potential in what?
To... waste my day shopping?
I'll handle this.
We aren't just shopping, Devon.
We're manifesting the life we deserve.
Yeah, with money.
I'm a... fast food cashier in Buffalo.
I was a teaching aide in Trenton.
I was a nail tech in Florida.
I'm a Sagittarius.
Kiki saw potential in us too.
- To what, marry rich guys?
- I'll handle this.
We didn't pursue them, Devon.
They... came to us.
We have special powers.
[in unison] All of us do.
[Cloe] When you love yourself,
when you project strength and confidence,
Mother Nature bends to your will.
Your gravitational force.
- Men will come running.
- [door opens]
- I don't really think--
- [Morgan] Devon?
Is that you?
[mystical music playing]
Um...
I was just walking by
and I saw you.
You look beautiful.
[in unison] See?
[insects chirping]
[Peter] Michaela wouldn't know a quahog
if it bit her in the ass.
[Simone chuckles]
- What are you gonna do with them?
- Oh.
I guess I'll make my famous... chowdah.
- You like clam chowdah?
[chuckling] Um...
I like New England clam chowder.
Oh no.
- Yeah.
- No, not that painted hussy.
I make Rhode Island clam chowdah.
No cream.
No cream, ew.
You're cold.
[Simone] Uh...
Yeah, a bit.
Oh, you... Oh.
- No, no, stop.
- Well, it's... it's...
- You're... You're doing it. Um, so, yeah.
- There you go.
Uh, look, um...
about Ethan.
- No, Peter, we don't have to talk about...
- I... I... Yeah, I know.
But I... I love the guy.
I've known him since he was in diapers,
but he does this.
Does what?
He ghosts the beautiful women
that he's been courting all summer,
and then, come Labor Day,
poof.
He's off to London.
Ethan hasn't ghosted me.
Oh.
Well, sure, look,
I would love to be wrong.
[smacks lips]
Well, I'm sorry.
- No, it's...
- No, I ruined the afternoon.
No, you... No, it... I...
Look, I appreciate you telling me.
Um... [smacks lips]
Yeah.
It's beautiful out here,
so thank you again for taking me clamming.
Uh...
What?
[both] Oh!
- I forgot, qua...
- Quahogging.
- Don't you mean quahogging?
- [chuckling] Qua... Qua...
- I wanna hear you say it.
- Okay.
- Quahogging.
- Quahogging. Not hard.
- Qua...
- Qua... hogging. [laughing]
Um...
Sorry. I...
[spluttering] I thought that...
I... I don't... I don't know what I thought.
Okay. Um...
- Yeah, I'm gonna...
- Okay, wait.
- Uh, Simone?
- All right. No.
Simone, wait. Wait.
[tense music playing]
[discordant music playing]
[keypad clacking]
[line ringing]
[on voicemail] Hey-o, this is Ethan.
Leave me a message at the beep.
[line beeps]
Hi, um, I just...
Please call me back. I just...
I... I'm just really worried about you.
I don't really know where you are
or if you're okay.
So, um, yeah, if you could just,
like, send me a text, that would be great.
Okay, bye.
[keypad clacking]
[discordant music continues]
[phone chiming]
[Michaela on phone] What's he doing now?
- Um...
- I wore emeralds last year.
Yeah, there's not much to report.
He's clamming off of Hughes Point.
Oh hell, he's not gonna make
that fucking clam chowder again, is he?
I don't know.
This isn't big enough.
No, I'm not... I'm not wearing
a yellow stone with a yellow dress.
Can I be done spying now?
You all right?
- [gasps] Oh. Save this for the Met.
- [Simone] Yeah!
Just, um, Peter's not doing
anything suspicious,
and, um, I need a break.
Oh.
You're probably just tired
and your blood sugar's low.
Go get a snack.
Ooh, let's try this one. Okay.
Kiki, you don't know
where Ethan is, do you?
Uh, no. Why?
I'm really worried.
I haven't heard from him today.
It's like he's missing.
Oh. I'm sure he's fine.
[Simone] I have a bad feeling about it.
I'm too petite for this.
Um, look, will you... will you call
Rebecca at Fred Leighton,
send her a picture of my dress,
and tell her we need
more choices for the gala?
- On it.
- You're the best.
[keypad clacking]
[grunts softly]
[door lock keypad beeping]
[door unlocks]
[automated voice] Front door open.
Ethan?
Hello?
- Ooh!
- [Morgan] Ooh! Score.
Hmm.
[Devon laughing] What?
The champ is here.
So, how's undercover going?
Really good. Yeah.
When you said
this bitch kills people yesterday,
were you talking about Jocelyn,
Peter's first wife?
- Why, do you have intel?
- I asked around a little.
- I thought you might be in danger.
- Aw.
People really think she got murdered.
She was, like, at the Yacht Club one day
and gone the next.
Family never addressed it.
Her schooner was just out there
in the harbor rotting for a decade.
This bitch is the goddamn devil.
I saw it in her eyes today.
She was naked in the bath, singing to me.
Anyway, I should go.
Oh, wait. Um, I want to ask you something.
- Yikes. What?
- [Morgan chuckles]
Um...
Every year at the end of the season,
Ethan pays me to take the boat
down to Palm Beach for the winter.
- That sounds nice.
- Yeah, it's beautiful.
I take my time,
stop at the beach in North Carolina,
and, uh... I was wondering
if you wanted to come.
[chuckles]
- What? Why not?
- [sighing] Uh...
Uh--
I take care of my dad full-time,
back home, for starters.
You can't take a vacation?
[playful music playing]
How long is this trip?
It's about a month.
There's no phone signal.
It's just me
and the stars
and miles of blue.
[chuckles]
Think about it.
[softly] I leave the day after Labor Day.
[playful music continues]
- [phone dings]
- [Morgan] Mmm.
[phone chiming]
Goddammit.
Weird, it's your sister.
- Huh?
- Simone, are you okay?
- [Simone] Look.
- It's luggage.
Exactly. All five pieces.
[Devon] Sorry, this is interesting, why?
He's not packed.
Ethan didn't leave the island early.
He wouldn't go anywhere without his stuff.
Without his watches.
He wouldn't leave
without telling me. He wouldn't.
Slow down. Who said he was gone?
Well, Peter said he ghosted me
and left for London early
because that's how he treats
his girl du jour every Labor Day.
Is that true?
I... I... I mean, he has, historically,
not been the most stand-up dude,
no, but he's really smitten with you.
Okay. Have you heard from him today?
[Morgan] No, not since yesterday.
[Simone] Something is wrong.
When... When did you last see him?
[Morgan] Uh, after the service thing
for the dead bird.
He was walking off towards a cliff with--
with Michaela.
- [gasps]
- What?
- I saw that too.
- Oh my God.
She was walking him towards the cliff.
- Don't.
- Holy fuck!
Don't say it. You'll upset her.
Wait, you don't think she urdered-may
the ouchebag-day,
just like she did the irst-fay ex-wife?
Okay. No, no, no, no, no.
Michae-- No, Michaela
didn't murder Jocelyn, Devon.
- That's island gossip.
- That's what Lily-Rose said.
- Who the hell is Lily-Rose?
- My cellmate in jail.
Oh, right.
Your boss put me in jail two nights ago.
[laughing] Wait,
what are you talking about?
This is what I've been trying to tell you.
The wool's over your eyes.
She's an evil bitch who legit
murders people.
Jocelyn's not dead.
- Have you ever even laid eyes on her?
- No! [splutters]
She and Peter are estranged.
- But she's not--
- Because she's dead.
Just like Ethan is.
She found out that you guys were dating,
and she pushed him off a cliff.
Wait, okay, everyone just calm down.
Like, this is insane.
My boss didn't murder my boyfriend.
She didn't.
Simone, I get it now, okay?
She's got like a weird power.
She used it on me today.
She got her claws in my brain.
I was talking about my feelings.
- I went shopping.
- You can hear yourself, right?
Oh God. It's so much worse than I thought.
[inhales deeply] We have got to
get the fuck out of here!
Boat boy, when's the next ferry?
- Uh, 6:40 if we leave now.
- Okay, let's get the fuck out of here!
Wait, Devon. Wait, wait, wait.
- Wait. Can you just... Can you just stop?
- Stop it.
- I need a second to process all this.
- Process it on the ferry.
I can't just flake on Kiki.
Oh, you'll be long gone
by the time she realizes.
[phone chiming]
[whispering] It's her.
Don't answer it.
Okay, okay, okay.
Where are we gonna go?
- Huh?
- We'll figure it out on the ferry.
[phone ringing]
Is she Find my iPhone-ing you?
Yeah. I mean, she does it
when I don't answer it.
No, th-- this is stupid, Dev.
I don't like running from my problems.
I feel really good about it.
[Michaela over speaker] Simone.
Simone. I know
you're at Ethan's house right now.
- What the fuck?
- My locations must be on.
She has Ethan's Nest code for emergencies.
- Stay put. I'm on my way over there.
- Quick. Let's go out the back.
Okay. Okay.
[frantic music playing]
[door lock keypad beeping]
Shit!
[mumbling]
What is she, The Flash?
How did she get here so fast?
[automated voice] Front door open.
[man] Where is the crapper?
[Ethan] It's three doors down on the left.
- Sounds like Ethan.
- [Ethan] Drink?
[man] You got any Labatt Blue in a bottle?
Ethan, hi!
[screaming]
- Oh my God.
- It's okay. It's okay.
[Ethan] Ooh! What are you guys doing?
I was so worried about you.
Why didn't you text or call me back?
I left this morning in a hurry,
and, um, well, I forgot my phone charger.
Well, actually, no,
I brought my phone charger.
You know how the old iPhone
had a different thing--
- Look, you scared me. Where were you?
- [man] Oh my goodness.
Is that you, Simone?
All grown up.
Look at you.
Ethan, why did you bring our father here?
[exhales] Um...
[smacks lips]
I... Well, I just... I flew to Buffalo quick
to talk to him about something,
and then he and his nurse, they wanted
to come back to the island with me.
I'm not his nurse. Who's this guy?
That's Captain Morgan.
Like the rum?
That's cool. What's up, Simone?
Wait, I... I... I am... I'm so confused.
Why are any of you here?
Um...
Okay. Okay.
Yeah, no, I was gonna wait.
I was gonna do this
tomorrow morning, but, um...
we can do this now.
[dramatic music playing]
[dramatic music continues]
[music ends]