What d'you say now?
I don't know.
You said your dad wouldn't
be home for an hour.
I know, but it,
- it, you know...
- Don't you love me?
Of course, you know I...
Come on. Let's do it.
All right.
Where are they?
Nightstand.
Gentlemen, start your engines.
I so want this car!
Oh my god, you're bleeding!
Look out!
What lie are they telling you?
Okay, yes.
Come on.
Okay, thank you.
Okay, pharmaceuticals were
delivered this morning,
but shipping accidentally sent the
box with vicodin to research.
That's a tough one.
If only we had some way to communicate
with another part of the building.
16-year-old MVA victim.
He's been in and out of the hospital
for three weeks with internal bleeding,
no one can find the cause,
Internal bleeding after a car accident,
Wow, that's shocking!
Let me talk to shipping,
I speak their language.
It's been three weeks...
Your hospital doesn't
have my pain medication.
Shipping says it's going to be an hour.
- This is Dr. Cuddy, what's going on?
- The crash didn't cause the bleed.
Right, the bleed caused the crash.
Blood got on the road, it got all slippery.
Anyone here got drugs?
She saw his blood, she got distracted,
and she crashed his dad's porsche.
Dad loved that.
- He was...
- Don't talk.
It's gonna be an hour.
Well, thank God you took control.
If you can't wait one hour to get your...
Kid's got hemolytic anemia.
Kid? How old?
He must have inherited it...
He's gonna die. My condolences.
It wasn't inherited.
The problem's outside the red blood cells.
This is impossible. A 16-year-old
doesn't get hemolytic anemia...
Give her back the file.
You have bigger
problems to tend to, like my meds.
Elevated indirect bilirubin,
low-serum haptoglobin...
He's got meningitis.
No.
- Artificial heart valve.
- No.
Get everyone in my office.
Kid's gonna be dead in a matter of days
if we don't figure out why his
red blood cells are disintegrating, so...
Differential diagnosis, people.
Well, it's not environmental.
Dad hired a company to clean the house,
maid washed all the clothes,
and bought hypoallergenic
sheets and pillows.
You want us to recheck?
No. If it's environmental
he'll get better just from staying here.
It could be an infection.
No fever, no white count.
Well, he's 99.2.
Barely above normal.
But above.
His body's reacting to something.
We could account for the lack
of fever and white count if it's lupus.
Drugs'll fit just as much as lupus.
Meth'll cause hemolytic anemia.
A lot of meth.
He also doesn't seem like the type.
Because his dad drives a porsche?
Rich kids do drugs just like poor kids.
Didn't mean to offend you.
Okay, so it's infection,
lupus, drugs, or cancer.
Cancer?
Why not? Great meeting.
Shouldn't we narrow it
down before we finish?
My leg gave us 'till 11:15.
I'll talk to wilson about lymphoma,
ana for lupus, radioimmunoassay for drugs,
you test for... whatever
you thought it was.
I've got a date with a pharmacist.
Come on, come on, come on...
Excuse me.
You know, there are other
ways to manage pain.
Like what, laughter?
Meditation?
Got a guy who
can fix my third chakra?
You're addicted.
If the pills ran my life,
I'd agree with you.
But it's my leg that's busy
calendaring what I can't do.
You're in denial.
Right, I never had an infarction in my leg,
no dead muscle, no nerve damage.
Doesn't even hurt.
Actually, it kind of tickles.
The chicks dig this.
Better than a puppy.
It's not just your leg.
You wanna get high!
You're doing what, 80 mg a day?
Oh, that's way too much!
Moderation is the key.
Unless there's pain.
It's double what you were
taking when I hired you.
'Cause you're twice as annoying.
I can't always be here to protect you.
Patients talk. Doctors talk.
About how big your ass has gotten lately?
Not me, I defend it. You got back.
You can't go a week without the drugs.
No, I don't want to go a week
without the drugs, it'll hurt.
No, you can't.
If you're just getting off
pain medication, it will hurt,
but you won't be having a great
time, but you'll make it.
If you're detoxing you'll
have chills, nausea...
Your pain will magnify five,
ten times. You won't make it.
Well, I guess we'll never know.
I'll give you a week off clinic duty
if you can go a week off narcotics.
No way! I love the clinic.
You love the pills. Two weeks.
Pills don't make me high.
They make me neutral.
A month.
You're on, mister.
Drugs could cause this?
Cocaine and meth are very hard
on the blood system.
Has he had any erratic behavior?
No, but...
She was in rehab in the 9th grade.
She's supposedly clean now, but...
She obviously cares for him.
Yeah, what she
cared about was the car.
Anniversary present from my wife.
We drove it up north
to watch the leaves change.
She was dead a year later. Cancer.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Foster, we're going
to test Keith for drugs.
I don't do drugs.
No, it's not that we
don't trust you, but...
His hair will tell us any drugs
he's taken in the past sixty days.
It's kind of
like rings on a tree.
Negative.
Have you been sick?
No, nothing.
Have you been out of the country?
We went to china, but we got all
of our shots before we left.
It could be an infection.
We're going to give him a
gallium scan just to be safe.
We inject a radioactive
isotope into his bloodstream,
and we check to see if there's
inflammation anywhere in the body.
Has he ever complained of any joint pain?
Sensitivity to light, rashes...
No, no, nothing.
Any relatives ever been
diagnosed with lupus?
I don't even know that that is.
In simple terms, the body
becomes allergic to itself.
The immune system attacks healthy cells in
the circulatory system
and destroys them.
Would it be treatable?
It can be manageable.
We can test for the antibodies.
95% of patients with lupus
test positive for ANA.
Not cloudy. Negative.
What about bruising?
He ever complain about tenderness
under his arms or his groin?
I'm not sure he'd tell me if he did.
I guess I really don't know
what's going on in his life.
He's a teenager.
Yeah.
What type of cancer did your wife have?
Pancreatic.
It's his lymph nodes we're concerned about.
We're going to do a biopsy
to check for lymphoma.
Okay, you feel this?
No.
Good.
I have cancer, don't I?
We're just testing.
That's what they told my mom.
Definitely not cancer.
Nothing?
Nothing.
Negative for drugs. Ana was negative,
gallium scan was clear...
Yeah, I got that from the "nothing".
Where's his hematocrit?
Thirteen.
Drops any lower
he's not going to have any red blood
cells to bring oxygen to his body.
He'll suffocate with his
lungs working perfectly.
You okay?
Excuse me, someone?
Help, please?
Polite for a dying kid.
How long has it been?
I'm fine.
There's something in my eye, up top.
Which eye?
This one. What's happening?
It's all right. Just, look down for me?
It's clear. There's nothing in it.
It's getting worse!
Is it fuzzy, or...
No! It's dark!
I can't see!
It's a retinal clot in the left eye.
Coumadin would dissolve the
clot, fix his eyesight.
You can't use bloodthinners,
he's got internal bleeding.
Fix the eye, you kill everything else.
Surgery's out for the same reason.
We have two hours to figure this out.
Either we restore the blood
flow or he loses the eye.
Forget the eye.
Tell him to use the other one
to look on the bright side.
The clot tells us something.
It could help us figure out what he has,
which could mean he gets to live.
Differential diagnosis, people.
How does internal bleeding
suddenly start clotting?
It makes no sense,
they're opposing processes.
It can happen in lupus.
Increased platelet count
can cause blood clots.
Ana was negative. It's not lupus.
This is true.
But why are you the one saying it?
What are you doing here?
I thought we ruled out cancer.
I was lonely.
Well, go see Cuddy.
She needs a friend.
That's funny, she said you might need one.
That's why you're here?
She wants you to keep an eye on me,
make sure I don't cheat.
No, I want to make sure you don't start
firing shots from the clock tower.
I'm fine.
What's going on?
He hasn't had vicodin in over a day.
Does your leg hurt?
You ever been shot?
There's gonna be side effects.
Insomnia, depression, tachycardia...
Withdrawl symptoms.
Not applicable.
The only side-effects I'm going to have are
some pain and thirty days of freedom.
Am I the only one who's
concerned about a dying kid?
If it's not lupus, what else?
Most likely candidate for throwing
a clot is infection or cancer.
Checked the biopsy twice, it's not cancer.
It's not an infection.
Gallium scan didn't reveal anything.
Okay, what hides from a Gallium scan?
Cardiac.
Right. Clot slips off, travels through the
artery, and
gets backed up in the eye.
I'm sorry, I wasn't paying attention.
What happened?
It's an infection. In his heart?
Great.
Echocardiogram for the heart and
iv antibiotics for the infection, stat.
Is it my birthday?
I'm not lonely, my leg hurts.
She's a real masseuse.
She's five hundred dollars
an hour, minimum.
She's hot, so she's a hooker?
What kind of pathetic logic is that?
The envious, jealous,
I-never-got-any-in-high-school
kind of logic, hello!
She's a legitimate masseuse, come on.
God, she's beautiful.
Because she's beautiful I should do it?
What kind of pathetic logic is that?
The envious, jealous,
I'm-married-and-i-can't-do-anything logic!
Hello.
Hi. Listen, I'm, I'm sure you're really
good at whatever it is you do but...
Dame su mano.
Huh?
Hey, no, let go
of my hand. Come on.
She doesn't speak english.
Oh, my god.
Bueno.
Take off your clothes.
Not a fan of the stroganoff?
I'm not hungry.
The antibiotics can cause nausea.
So can the food.
Shouldn't you be looking at my eye?
The blood clot isn't life-threatening.
We're focusing on figuring out
the cause of your problems.
So the blindness will
be permanent, won't it?
Thank you.
Bye.
I had a massage.
Looks like you had a masseuse.
Help the pain?
I'm fine.
I know.
Kid's echo was normal, no sign of
any vegetations on heart valves.
Never met a diagnostic
study I couldn't refute.
And the antibiotics aren't doing anything.
So, double the dosage. 70mg.
That'll box his kidneys for sure!
Oh, you're right. Save the kidney.
The guy we transplant it
into will be grateful.
Also, I have an idea for his eye.
Nothing we can do about his eye.
- He's got a clot in his retinal...
- Read the memo.
If we remove some of the liquid from
the eye itself, the vitreous humor,
it might make some extra room
around the retinal artery.
If the artery expands, the clot
might move out on its own.
That's very creative.
Why didn't you mention this before?
Well, I didn't think of it before.
You should have.
This isn't going to hurt.
Your eye's numb.
You'll only feel pressure.
Give it a minute.
I can see.
I can see you.
I heard! Congratulations.
Don't. I haven't brushed
my teeth in two days.
Ah, I'm so scared they're not gonna
find out what's wrong with you.
No biggie. I'm fine.
I feel so bad about all this.
It's all my fault.
No. No, it's not.
But your father. He hates me.
He's just pissed about his car.
Help, help help!
What's wrong?
Ast is 859, we're getting him to the ICU.
ALT and GDT were in the tank.
Our antibiotics...
Would not have caused this.
She must have given him drugs.
I wouldn't do that!
It's not drugs!
His liver is shutting down.
What? What does that mean?
It means he's all better.
He's ready to go home.
What?
What do you think it means?
You can't live without a liver, he's dying!
What is your problem?
Bum leg, what's yours?
Hey, we don't have
time for this, let's go.
His son's dying and
you're mocking him?
It was a dumb question.
No, it wasn't.
You're right, it wasn't.
Is proving Cuddy wrong worth all this?
You know, House shouldn't even be here.
Because he said something inappropriate?
If we sent him home every time he did that,
we wouldn't need this office.
He's in pain.
What does the man have
to do to piss you off?
He's been without pain
relief for seventy hours...
Exactly! He's detoxing,
can't you see he's out of his mind?
That's what they said about manson.
Do you want to continue talking about me
or should we discuss
what the liver damage tells us?
I was born in a log cabin in illinois...
Hemolytic anemia doesn't
cause liver damage.
Add the fact he's coughing blood,
you've got three of the indicators
of organ-threatening lupus.
It's moving too fast.
Could be hepatitis-e.
There's only been one case of hep-e
originating in the US since...
Its history. Since he's been in and out of
the country four times in the last year...
You really think he's got Hep-E?
No. I think the lupus is way more likely.
All right. Then let's start him
on IV Cytoxan and Plasmapheresis.
No, we should rule out Hep-E.
You just said it wasn't hep-e.
I said lupus was way more likely,
but if we treat for lupus and it is hep-e.
He's toast.
Exactly.
But there isn't a treatment
for hepatitis-e.
Either he'll get better on his own
or he'll continue to deteriorate.
Yeah, I went to medical school, too.
Start him on Solumedrol.
If he's got Hep-E that's only
going to make him worse!
Not as much. Goldilocks, people.
It won't hurt him so much
that it'll kill him,
and it won't hurt him so
little that we can't tell.
It'll hurt him just right.
And if it does nothing...
We'll know it's not Hep-E and
start treating him for lupus.
Now watch me do it while
drinking a glass of water.
What do we tell the dad?
"We think your kid has Lupus, so we're
gonna treat him for hepatitis-e..."
And oh yeah, if it really is Hep-E,
we're not actually giving
him Hep-E medication,
"so it's gonna make him worse, not better?"
You think he'll go for that?
So you want us to lie?
No. I want you to lie.
Why me?
Because he trusts you.
This is a mistake.
This is a lawsuit.
Hep-e is possible.
House always pulls these stunts
and he's right more often...
He's delaying treatment because
of a one-in-a-million chance
that even he doesn't think is the problem.
I don't want to lie to him.
Then don't.
And get fired?
Like he's going to fire you, he loves you.
I've got to do something,
the kid needs treatment.
Treat him for lupus.
That will get you fired.
You really think House is losing it?
Yeah.
He's fine. He knows what he's doing.
We're recommending a
drug called Solumedrol.
For hepatitis?
Did that show up on his blood tests?
The tests are never 100% accurate.
Well, then all the other
tests could be wrong, too.
This could still be an infection or cancer.
They don't fit any of
the most recent symptoms.
Well, what, just hepatitis does?
I know, I know, I know,
you can never be sure.
When Linda was in the hospital,
the doctor told us there was this
aggressive experimental treatment
which might extend her life
by two or three years.
We figured if there was
any hope at all that
we could have her with us a little
while longer, it would be worth it.
3 weeks later, she was gone.
I don't think it's hepatitis.
I think your son has lupus.
I think it's broken.
What did you do?
Accidentally closed the car door on it.
No. Door would have broken the skin.
This looks like something
hard and smooth smashed it.
I want my lawyer.
The brain has a gating mechanism for pain.
Registers the most severe injury
and blocks out the others.
Did it work?
Well, my hand hurts like hell.
Yeah, I feel much better.
Don't splint it.
I want to be able to bang it against the
wall if I need to administer another dose.
Just... tape it up.
Why did you tell Cameron to lie to Mr.
Foster?
Make it tight will ya.
Answer me.
Nothing I could say is going
to change how you feel,
and nothing could come out of your reaction
that is going to change what I plan
to do, so I prefer to say nothing.
So, that was you just saying nothing.
The guy is furious.
And scared.
So, what are you going to do?
The father's
insisting on the lupus treatment.
Yeah, Cameron told me
and I told her to tell him no.
Well, you can't just sit
back and let the kid die.
Neither can the father.
So that's your plan? You're gonna
play chicken with the kid's life?
Well, he's the dad. I should win easily.
Take the week off.
What, 'cause I lied to a patient?
I take risks, sometimes patients die.
But not taking risks causes
more patients to die,
so I guess my biggest problem is I've been
cursed with the ability to do the math.
I told him that you wouldn't
treat him for the lupus until...
What did he say?
He said he wanted to transfer
Keith to another hospital.
He's not stable enough, he'd
never make it through the door!
That's what I told him.
And that's when he caved.
Yeah. He agreed to do it your way.
Two plus two equals four.
If it is hepatitis-e we
should begin to see a marked
decline in liver function
tests within the hour.
Why bother explaining it to me? It's not
like I have any choice in the matter.
If there's no hep-e we'll start
treatment for lupus immediately.
Keith? What's wrong?
What's happening?
Get off!
Keith? It's Dr. Chase,
where does it hurt?
Jules, no!
He's hallucinating.
Is this from the medicine?
We haven't started the medicine.
Keith, we're in the hospital.
Keith, there's nothing on you.
- Keith!
You okay, buddy?
I think I wet the bed.
Don't worry about it, it's fine.
Let's get you up.
Oh, god!
He's had a major bleed.
Bright red blood per rectum.
I didn't mean to, I'm sorry.
He's going into hypervolemic shock.
Pressure's 60, heart rate's 140.
We need an angiography, stat!
Angiography revealed major
upper and lower GI bleeding,
severe hemodynamic compromise,
and liver failure.
He's also hallucinating.
Thinks he's being talked to
by someone named "Jules".
Hallucinations are a symptom of psychosis,
which is the fourth diagnostic criterion.
It's official. This is lupus.
Who's Jules?
Any mention of her in the medical history?
It doesn't matter what he's hallucinating
about, it matters why! It's lupus!
There's no need to get snippy.
This kind of lupus takes years to get
to this point, it's been a week.
Yeah, and a 16-year-old kid
shouldn't have hemolytic anemia,
or be bleeding out of
every orifice, but he is.
We had an opportunity to treat this,
instead we diddled around
with hepatitis-e and now it's too late.
He needs a new liver.
We screwed up.
You're saying I screwed up.
Yes.
Then why didn't you just say that?
You gonna just blame this on her?
Did you agree with my
recommendation to treat for hep-e?
No, I didn't.
And she made herself quite clear.
And then she went and lied to the father.
That's why you're angry.
Yeah, I trusted you.
You always trust me. It's big mistake.
Lupus is a bad diagnosis.
It's the best diagnosis we've got.
That doesn't make it good.
No, it just makes it this
kid's only chance to live.
Put him on the transplant list.
Cafeteria. Stay away from the sushi.
And what happened to your hand?
Got stuck in a drawer.
Yeah, right. You're going
through withdrawl.
No, I am going through pain.
Pain causes nausea.
I took this job to work with
you, not cover your ass.
Your vicodin.
And your solution is to give me drugs.
It's interesting.
No. Now I'm covering my ass.
Take your pills before you kill this kid.
Lupus is normally treated with medication,
but in Keith's case the
disease is too advanced.
Because you lied.
Because House wanted to play
games with my son's life.
There's no way to really tell what
progression the disease may take...
You're right, and I'm sorry.
So what do we do?
He needs a new liver.
There are over 15,000 patients
on the transplant list.
But how many are about to bleed to death
unless they get a new liver?
In Jersey? I'd say, uh, twenty.
2000 patients die each year because
a donor liver can't be found,
that's almost five a day.
So he's screwed.
I'll see what I can do.
Could I donate part of my liver?
Sorry, you're a different blood type.
So we just wait?
I'm afraid so.
And hope for someone to die.
Who's Jules?
Dr. House, you should get
back to your office...
Jules. There's
no Jules in the history.
It was a hallucination.
Of what?
Our cat. Does this matter?
No, I'm sorry.
We'll continue the
transfusions and the treatment
for the anemia and liver failure
while we're waiting for a donor.
How long can he wait?
Not long.
I don't think this is lupus.
This is lupus.
Come on, let's just go...
Your fourth diagnostic criterion
of lupus is psychosis;
This is just a kid missing his cat.
He was being attacked by an
animal that wasn't in the room.
That's psychosis.
There's a difference between
psychosis and hallucination.
So, if he was imagining a
fake cat it'd be lupus,
but since it was a real cat it's not?
Take your damn pills.
Psychosis requires...
There's no cat! Jules is dead.
You have a dead family pet,
and you never mentioned it?
Nice family history.
Family history is asking
about family members,
meaning people related to the patient.
Let's go.
How did the cat die?
Can you get him out of here?
Dr. House, come on, let's go...
What happened to the cat?
Old age. She was fifteen years old.
When?
About a month ago?
Does this have anything to do with...
Where'd she sleep?
With keith.
This is not a cat allergy.
It's not lupus. Where is Jules?
Four years of college, four at med
school, two years of residency,
another four of sub-specialty training,
and where do I end up?
Talking instead of digging.
Come on, the ground's frozen solid.
What's that?
Out of the way!
We have the liver. Prep or 4.
All right, Keith. Start
counting backward from ten.
Ten...
nine...
eight...
Scalpel.
Stop the gases.
What the hell are you doing, house?
Saving a sixteen-year-old
kid from a lifetime of
immunosuppressant drugs
and a very nasty scar.
This kid doesn't have lupoid hepatitis.
He has acute naphthalene toxicity.
Naphthalene.
You're talking about mothballs.
Nope.
Termites.
They create naphthalene
to protect their nests,
which I'm assuming is rather large and is
inside all four walls of his bedroom at home.
And your assumption is based on what?
The autopsy I just
conducted on his pet cat.
Call Cuddy. And security.
You are not removing that kid's liver.
Now!
Have you completely lost your mind?
No, but I have been feeling
a little sick lately.
Achoo!
There's no way we can do this surgery now.
You think?
You've already cost him his
liver, don't kill him too!
Why are you so eager to
cut into a healthy kid?
Healthy? He's in the toilet!
He just needs some chicken soup.
I'm telling Hourani to re-scrub.
We're doing this transplant.
No, you're not.
You said it!
If Keith's symptoms had
an environmental cause,
they would have disappeared
as soon as he got here.
They've only gotten worse.
If the food here wasn't one step below.
Riker's island he would've gotten better.
He's lost fourteen pounds.
Yeah, sure. This is nothing
but a dietary thing.
Naphthalene is a gas,
a fat soluble gas.
The kid breathes it in,
it gets stored in his fat cells.
Outside the hospital his body
burned protein and carbs for energy
and the naphthalene stayed in fat.
But once the car accident
put him in the hospital,
and he started losing weight,
his body had to get its
energy somewhere else.
It started to burn fat.
The floodgates opened, the
poison poured into his system.
So, getting away from the
poison is what poisoned him?
Getting him away from his dad's
meatloaf is what's killing him.
You wanna explain to me why
you stopped the surgery?
Oh, my god! My god.
I want him locked up!
Hey! Take it easy.
Your cat did not die of old age.
He died of massive internal bleeding
and acute liver failure caused
by naphthalene poisoning,
the exact same thing your son has.
You lie to me, you mess
up my son's surgery,
and now you expect me to trust you?
Give me twenty-four hours,
we'll pump your son full of calories...
That liver is going to somebody right now.
We're doing that surgery.
If you do the surgery,
you'll be killing a mother of four.
Father of three.
I was guessing.
Like you are now?
Naphthalene poisoning
is the best explanation
we have for what's wrong with your son.
It explains the internal bleeding,
the hemolytic anemia,
the liver failure...
It also predicts what'll happen next.
If you do the surgery he's gonna lay
on that table for fourteen hours
while his body continues to burn fat
and release poison into his system.
Either way, I did you a favor.
He's awake now,
you've got a chance to say goodbye.
I think you should trust Dr. House.
Give the liver to the other guy.
INR is down, and his
blood count is climbing.
It means you made the right call.
His liver is healing.
He's gonna be just fine.
You made it a week.
And won my prize.
Congratulations.
Cuddy's a sucker. I would have
done it for two weeks off.
Yeah, it was a piece of cake.
You learn anything?
Yeah, I'm an addict.
Okay.
I'm not stopping.
There are programs.
Cuddy would give you the time.
You could get on a different
pain management regimen...
I don't need to stop.
You just said...
I said I was an addict.
I didn't say I had a problem.
I pay my bills, I make my meals.
I function.
Is that all you want?
You have no relationships.
I don't want any relationships.
You alienate people.
I've been alienating
people since I was three.
Oh, come on! Drop it!
You don't think you've changed
in the last few years?
Well, of course I have. I've...
I've gotten older. My
hair's gotten thinner.
Sometimes I'm bored, sometimes I'm lonely,
sometimes I wonder what it all means.
No, I was there!
You are not just a regular guy
who's getting older, you've changed!
You're miserable, and you're
afraid to face yourself...
Of course I've changed!
And everything's the leg?
Nothing's the pills?
They haven't done a thing to you?
They let me do my job,
and they take away my pain.
How'd it go?
He admitted he's addicted
to the narcotics...
Well, admitting you have a problem
- is the first...
- And he says it's not a problem.
Maybe it's not.
What do I know?
What are you going to do?
Nothing. I've done enough damage.
Better hope he never finds
out that that was your idea.
He'd never believe it.