It's all about the tongue, man.
You stick it in their mouth.
Not all the way.
They like that?
Dude, they love it.
What're you doing?
Climbing.
Just deep enough to lick her teeth.
Slow, one at a time.
Like you're painting them.
This girl, Rachel?
She's a junior, she's experienced.
Mom says I gotta be home by five!
Just chill, okay, and hop the fence
before someone sees you!
- Are you sure this is okay?
- Dave's mom's a realtor.
If it's for sale, and empty,
it's a clubhouse.
And if you say anything, you're dead.
I told them you were cool.
These are very serious dudes.
Cub scout meeting's down the street, boys.
Oh, loser.
Gabe's cool, man.
He's one of us.
He better be.
Uh... I'm not thirsty.
What's this?
Club business, little man.
Put your hands on.
Oh, dark spirit!
Will any of us die in the year to come?
- You're moving it!
- Put your hands back.
Now.
Who among us will die?
G...
A...
Oh, man.
B...
E.
Gabe.
That blows.
That's it.
We're going to the hospital.
No, Mom. I'm too tired.
Oh.
Oh, my God! Gabe! Are you okay?
Baby, what's wrong?
I'm dying.
12 year old male, spiking
fever, congested chest,
coughing up green sputum,
pain in breathing...
Baffling.
Though I vaguely recall a disease
called noomonia, numania?
But his X-ray and CT scan show an
atypical patten for pneumonia.
Pneumonia! That's it.
Just a guess here, but are
his parents big donors?
No infiltrate!
Just enlarged hilar lymph nodes.
Tiny unicorns goring his
bronchial tubes would be cooler.
And the way you're ignoring my question...
Wow, they're extremely big donors.
He's not responding to cefuroxime,
his pulsox is dropping much faster
than it should for pneumonia,
and plus, he's got an odd little rash.
Excessive irritation.
He's 12, he's on auto-stroke...
On his arm.
Papular lesion, one centimeter,
on top of a long thin scab.
Ah, you need a dermatologist.
If it's dry, keep it wet,
if it's wet, keep it dry,
if it's not supposed
to be there, cut it off.
I never could master all of that.
There you are.
Are you scared?
It's okay. You're home now.
Fine.
Cuddy.
As a special favor to you...
No! Admit it, I got you with the rash.
The rash is a total snooze.
Unless it's connected to the pneumonia,
then it's party time.
Purulent sputum, dyspnea,
bronchi bilaterally.
What causes this kind of rash?
Legionnaire's disease?
Usually means industrial
ventilation systems,
convention centers.
He's twelve years old.
Send off a urine antigen and check
if he's joined the Elks. Next?
Fungal.
Excellent. Maybe the Elks went spelunking.
Chlamydia and pneumonia.
Twelve year olds don't have sex.
Their mistake.
That's it? Other possibilities?
What if you're thinking
about this backwards?
The rash came first, caused
the pneumonia. Nice.
Rickettsial. Tick bites.
Nymphal ticks are out now,
they're bloodthirsty little bastards.
Rash would be more pustular.
Not always. And there's
only one rash, which fits.
New Jersey, it's most likely Lyme disease.
All right. Let's keep him on
fluids and cefuroxime to be safe.
And biopsy that rash.
And take another history.
Even if we don't learn out what's
causing this we definitely
need to know if 12 year olds
are getting any action.
What are you doing now?
We're collecting fluids from the rash.
Why?
They know what they're doing, Jeffery.
Oh, great endorsement coming from the woman
who thought it was a nasty cold.
- If I'd had him last week and...
- This isn't helping.
We're checking to see
if your son has a tick bite.
Gabe, have you been camping recently?
Playing sports outside, anything like that?
I'm not that good at sports.
No hanging out anywhere new?
- Strange places?
- We've been through this.
We don't let him run wild through
the neighborhood. Right?
Okay, this might be a bit delicate.
We need to know if you're sexually active.
I beg your pardon?
Who do you think my son...
- Mr. Reillich, we need to...
- No!
Nothing like that.
We've got to get another CT
scan, check his lungs again.
Third floor, right?
- Yeah, Radiology is just...
- Sorry, medical personnel only.
Where's the machine?
We passed it, actually.
Little tension in the room back there.
Thought you could use a break.
Your dad's a pretty high-powered guy.
Yeah. He was an Air Force test pilot.
Real top-gun stuff.
Flew a Mach 3.
Hard to deal with, sometimes?
I guess I'm more like my mom.
Listen, I promised to keep my mouth shut,
but I need to know.
You definitely haven't had any
sexual contact of any kind?
I wish.
Know what?
Girls like the cool guys now.
You give it a few years,
they start liking the smart guys.
You'll be all right.
Can you keep a secret?
I have to, it's my job.
I'm cursed. I'm not kidding.
This seance thing the kids did?
It spelled out my name,
said I was gonna die.
First name and last name?
We've got a Gabe upstairs.
He's very old, very sick.
No! It's me.
I have the worst luck.
One time, I broke this mirror.
The next week,
my parents got separated.
My parents got split up, too.
Every kid feels like it's
his fault, it never is.
So what about the rest of the stuff?
Any playing outside that your parents
don't know about, anything like that?
Maybe you were somewhere
you weren't supposed to be?
Oh, man.
Gabe, it's important.
Secret club.
What's the secret,
they're all morons?
He fell on something in the attic,
scraped his arm, got the rash the next day.
Said it smelled really moldy up there.
Fungal pneumonia without the cave.
Clever.
I'm gonna get a sample.
Dr. Chase.
You have a few moments.
Sorry, I've gotta go.
These young doctors.
It's like they don't care about people.
No manners.
My fault, probably.
That's an interesting
accent you have there.
I'd say Czech, with about
thirty years of Aussie.
You have quite an ear.
You're Chase's dad.
Hard to miss, you know, the big hug
and how happy he was to see you.
Need a consult.
With a patient.
Urgent doctor stuff.
26-year-old male,
sudden loss of the ability to speak...
Just because you got out of clinic duty
doesn't mean everybody did.
To his father.
Differential diagnosis?
Chase?
Dad swoops in, Chase swoops out.
Dad say why he was here?
See? You asked.
Dad comes 5000 miles and
you're more curious than Junior is.
Can't just be about the divorce.
It's been fifteen years and
mom's been dead for ten of them.
You think Daddy murdered her?
You want to get to the bottom of this,
you're doing it exactly right.
Don't talk to the people
involved, drag your buddy
away from work for some
pointless speculation.
You want to know how two chemicals
interact, do you ask them?
No, they're going to lie
through their lying little chemical teeth.
Throw them in a beaker and apply heat.
Even I don't like you.
You know, words can hurt!
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Hold on, guys,
I don't care that you're up here!
You a cop?
Doctor. I'm treating Gabe Reillich.
He said he fell over near some pipes?
Yeah, over there.
What, here?
Yeah.
Right, any of you guys
been feeling sick lately?
Rash, cold, anything?
No.
Oh, crap. He is a cop!
Damn it!
He fell on it.
Some weird kind of insulation.
It's old, house was built in the sixties.
What's it made of?
Felt. Fibers are made of what, cotton?
Sorry, forgotten how funny your dad was.
Not as funny as you.
High praise.
I know how protective kids
can be of their parents.
Not cotton, animal hair.
Get me the CT scan.
First, find the name of company
that made the insulation
and second, tell me what I'm seeing that
makes me want to short their stock.
Uh, enlarged hilar lymph nodes.
Parabronchial thickening.
Purile effusions.
Less obvious, more scary.
Well, the mediastinum doesn't look right.
Slightly widened.
Oh God, it can be transmitted
through infected animal hair.
But the gram stain would have shown...
No, the cefuroxime would have killed
some of it, clouded the result.
We've gotta get this kid on levaquin.
What does he have?
Anthrax.
This house belonged to old man Hussein?
Maybe he is cursed.
Anthrax. So, what, you think
there were terrorists in that attic?
It's a naturally occurring bacteria.
We believe it was in the insulation.
How sick is he?
Anthrax is very dangerous,
but we've caught it early.
He's on levaquin,
it's the best antibiotic we have.
Lisa, you buy this?
Jeff, you've helped our hospital a lot.
I wouldn't have assigned Dr. House to your
case if I didn't have every confidence in...
Then who's this guy?
Jeffery!
There's all these weird
diseases that can cause a rash.
What about leishmaniasis
and filariasis?
Where'd you hear about those?
The internet. I did some research.
Well, those are very rare conditions.
Oh, and anthrax grows
along the interstate?
Leishmaniasis doesn't cause
pneumonia and filariasis...
Just look into everything,
this is my son, all right?
And I'm going to stay on top of you
until I know he's safe.
I wouldn't expect anything else.
Everyone's a doctor.
Breathe, baby. It's okay.
Breathe, honey.
His breathing! It's on the inhale!
What does that mean?
It means his airway's closing up.
Is the anthrax doing it?
All right, hold still, Gabe.
This is going to be a little uncomfortable.
We've got you, it's okay.
Two nodules in his throat.
Airway's inhibited?
We've got to intubate. Ativan!
Pushing 3 ccs.
Airway's too tight.
What's wrong? What's wrong?
No. You're killing him!
Jeffery! Jeffery, let them do their job!
Airway's too tight,
get me a smaller tube.
We're traching.
Smaller tube!
His lips are cyanotic.
Oh my God, he's not breathing.
Foreman! We're traching!
No, I can do it, I'll get it.
Foreman, you're not getting through!
He's not getting air.
Oh, we have to trach him right now.
- No, I can do it.
- Betadine.
I'm doing this.
Got it!
He's okay.
Allergic reaction to the antibiotics?
I don't think so.
We switched him to rifampin and
there was no change in swelling.
We should try another antibiotic...
You really think he's
allergic to two antibiotics?
I want to know what Dr. Chase thinks.
It's possible to think he's
allergic to both anti...
Oh, I'm sorry! Not you.
Understandable mistake.
The other Dr. Chase.
Boy gets anthrax, but happens to
be allergic to two antibiotics.
Hate to step on anybody's toes, but is it
possible that your guys got this one wrong?
The rash is classic anthrax.
Except the color.
The rash hasn't turned black yet.
No necrosis, no anthrax.
Necrosis can theoretically take
as long as two weeks.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Guys, it's not a competition!
It's a diagnosis! Okay.
Who thinks Junior wins?
Four to one, it's not anthrax.
So we start over, what's changed?
What do the nodules tell us?
Sarcoidosis.
Excellent. Send an ACE level.
If it comes back positive,
put him on methotrexate.
We ran some tests, and
the results point toward sarcoidosis.
It makes the body's tissue swell up.
It seems to have gone after Gabriel's skin
and lungs, and given him this fever.
Doctor.
We don't know what causes it.
But you're sure he has this one.
We have a world-renowned doctor consulting.
He's convinced this is sarcoidosis.
Is it treatable?
Very, actually.
See, this is IV methotrexate.
It's an anti-inflammatory,
which should make all the swelling go down,
and get you all better.
Stop!
My God, it's black.
Necrosis.
It's definitely anthrax,
and it definitely can't be anthrax.
It doesn't cause throat nodules.
The only explanation is
this kid has got anthrax and sarcoidosis!
Right, two incredibly rare diseases
just happening to strike at once.
Unless you've got a better theory.
Anthrax plus an allergic reaction.
Call the Lancet, because
that's one bizarre allergic reaction.
Come on, there's no reason
you both can't be wrong.
It's not allergy,
but it's not coincidence, either.
Disease number one set
off disease number two.
Anthrax weakened his immune system.
And triggered a dormant sarcoidosis.
Keep him on antibiotics
for the anthrax and
start him on methotrexate
for the sarcoidosis.
See what happens.
Fine.
Better go with him.
Make sure he doesn't
snap and hurt somebody.
You... you're treating
him for both diseases?
We're covering all the bases.
What, throw everything against
the wall and see what sticks?
Works for spaghetti.
Are you being funny?
Apparently not.
You know why I give money to this hospital?
It's the only way to get attention.
You see this?
Is this a magic trick?
Because I am a total David Copperfield fan,
although that "Tornado of Fire",
that seemed a little fake...
Pain in the wrist.
Won't go away for months.
Six doctors' brilliant
conclusion is to take it easy.
I write a check, name goes on a plaque,
and forty-eight hours later
I've got two MRis, a bone scan,
and a diagnosis: Carpal tunnel.
I'm in surgery that afternoon.
Fascinating story.
You thought of adapting it for the stage?
I love my... look at me! Love my son, I love
him more than anything else in the world,
and you're going to start
paying attention to this case,
- or I'm going to make things miserable for...
- Go back to your son's room.
I'm not leaving here until you
- get your ass in gear...
- There's a problem.
What is it?
I don't know.
Skin lesions are spreading
all over his body.
They're opening and the fatty
tissues are oozing out.
He'll be septic in a matter of days.
Death by dermatitis.
Where's Robert?
He has clinic duty this morning.
No, he doesn't.
I rescheduled you guys...
- so you'd be free.
- Yeah, but he re-rescheduled himself.
It doesn't hurt yet.
Keep going.
You page me?
No, I don't need you.
Oh, come on.
We all need help now and again.
You're getting a consult.
Okay, we've got new skin lesions, bigger
and uglier. What would cause that?
My hand hurts.
What if his body worked so hard attacking the
anthrax that it started attacking itself?
Auto-immune.
Wouldn't present this aggressively.
It's not likely, but it is possible.
What, in a twelve-year-old male?
This isn't about me, is it?
Gabe's dad found leishmaniasis and
filariasis on the internet yesterday.
They didn't fit then, but
now they kind of do.
Sure, except for the nodules and
we're not working out of Calcutta General.
Multiple neurofibromatosis.
You think this is neurological?
The only reason you're thinking auto-immune
is because you're a rheumatologist!
If you were a proctologist
you'd think rectal cancer.
Gotta go with Senior.
He literally wrote the book with this one.
Auto-immune is a big universe.
It could be anything from
scleroderma to churg-strauss.
Whatever it is, we should start him
on steroids, keep the swelling down.
And 100 mg. Of cytoxan, it
treats most auto-immunes.
We'll give it to him now, before the
fat starts dripping out his eyeballs.
Hey! My fingers are numb!
Your watch is on too tight.
You're messing with my head.
Your relationship with your dad is messing
with your ability to do your job.
Only because you made
my dad part of my job.
Good point.
Haven't seen him in years,
he flies across the Atlantic to see you...
Pacific.
You breeze by him like he's a
Hare Krishna at the airport.
You don't even ask why he's in town.
It's probably a conference.
Probably.
I was hoping to do this
by sheer manipulation,
but if you insist on
talking, fine, talk.
What did he do to you?
How would you feel
if I interfered in your personal life?
I'd hate it. That's why I
cleverly have no personal life.
I'm going to biopsy his skin lesions.
Good thinking! Prove your dad wrong.
That'll solve everything.
Who extubated him?
I did. Temperature's down two degrees
and the swelling's almost gone.
And his skin looks better, too.
The cytoxan is working.
Feeling better, Gabe?
Yup, a lot.
Dr. Chase, can you and I have a word?
Your diagnosis is wrong.
No auto-immune disease.
The swelling's probably just down
because we've got him on steroids.
It's masking whatever's really wrong.
ANAs are unreliable.
Phospholipid antibodies are
negative, so no lupus.
Same for churg-strauss.
You're arguing with a rheumatologist.
There's about twenty distinct
auto-immune diseases...
Why are you here?
SLE conference.
You were in New York last
year for the scleroderma
conference, I didn't
hear anything from you.
Just wanted to say hi this time.
You said it, you're still here.
I miss you.
I was 15 years old
when you walked out.
Now you're walking back in?
I left your mother.
I didn't leave you.
Mum was living on gin and tonics,
how was I supposed to take care of her?
- She wasn't your responsibility.
- I know! She was yours.
I'm sorry she died.
I'm sorry you had to deal with that.
But she was falling apart long before...
I've got to talk to House
about this treatment.
But the patient's getting better.
In spite of the cytoxan.
On the other hand, getting better.
Cytoxan makes him more
susceptible to infection.
The anthrax could relapse
and be more resistant.
Better!
You want a negative test for
every auto-immune disease known to man?
Fine, I'll get them!
Be home by midnight or
he can't have the car this weekend.
You guys talk?
Did he tell you why he's here?
The SLE conference.
Going back to the conference?
Afternoon panel.
I hope I can stay awake.
I hope you can get in.
You're not registered.
I get it. You had to make up a lie.
Can't just tell your kid
you're here to see him.
What father does that?
That little blue dot under your collar.
It's a tattoo for guiding
radiation treatment.
I was looking for it after I saw
what you had for breakfast:
Brown rice and vegetables,
macrobiotic diet.
Popular with Hollywood
starlets and cancer patients.
Lungs, stage four.
You look good.
I'm not.
Came to the States to go to
Sloan-Kettering, and to see Dr. Wilson.
What'd he say?
Three months.
But you haven't told Robert.
You don't want to burden him
because you were such a lousy dad.
I'd prefer you not tell him.
Yeah, it's better.
I'll get to see his face
when he reads his dad's obituary.
It's not your business.
I suppose it isn't.
You sure do a lot a tests.
If we figure out exactly
which auto-immune
condition it is, we can
get you better quicker.
Was that your dad before?
Yeah.
That's so cool.
Do you guys work together a lot?
Not really.
When can I go home?
We'll see. Looks like you
got your appetite back.
That's a good sign.
Want some water?
Yes.
Okay.
Whoops.
It's all right. Water's cheap.
Oh, God.
What?
I can't, I can't move my hand.
Squeeze my fingers for me, Gabe?
He's getting worse.
Now his entire right hand
and forearm are paralyzed.
And his fever's back,
it's back over 105.
If we don't stop the nerve deterioration
quickly, he'll be paralyzed for life.
Well, luckily, at this rate,
that should only last about a week.
Okay, so...
I told you we should get
him off the cytoxan.
This is toxic neuropathy.
We've been shoving drugs into his system
for a disease he doesn't have!
Well, it could be neurological.
What kind of brain process
would cause a paralyzed hand
skin lesions, and
swollen throat nodules?
Robert was right.
You said multiple neurofibromatosis.
Are you saying that for
the chance of a beautiful
family moment, or is there
some medicine involved?
Fits better.
Too bad. I was hoping for the other reason.
I was gonna go get my camera.
Get a CT scan. His brain this time.
You think three copies
will be enough, right?
One's always been more than enough for me.
Why didn't you tell me that
Rowan Chase was in to see you?
Excuse me.
Ethics, confidentiality?
Does any of this ring a bell?
You could have covered yourself.
Called me in for a consult.
It is a juicy piece of gossip.
You know what happened?
I got all focused on his cancer
and lost perspective.
You can't tell Chase, but I can.
What should I do?
Oh! This is where I give
you advice and
pretend you're going to listen to it.
I like this part.
Did Rowan ask you not to tell?
I promised I wouldn't.
My fingers were crossed,
though, so I'm wide open.
I was wrong! This is the
musing-out-loud part!
Do I actually need to be here?
Telling him,
now that's got real entertainment value.
Hmmm, he might even cry.
On the other hand,
there is the "do unto others" thingy.
Then I should definitely tell him!
I'd want to know.
You want to know everything.
There's also the "keeping
your promises" thingy.
Oh, you never run out of thingies.
Like that blonde thing
you were chatting up.
She's the hospital accountant!
We were going over billing procedures!
Double-entry bookkeeping?
What are you going to do?
Billing procedures.
They're so complicated, aren't they?
You know, parents are never
as bad as kids think they are.
You like my dad so much, ask him out.
I'd make an excellent
step-mom, I'm very lenient.
He's your father, you never
see him, and he's here.
Unless he's done some unspeakable thing,
you should lighten up.
Right, thanks for the tip.
Okay.
He beat your mom. He beat you.
What did he do?
Really, don't push it.
All this hate. It's toxic.
Then stay away.
There's nothing there.
No masses, no fibrous tangles, nothing.
It's not neurofibromatosis.
Drs. Chase are 0 for 3.
Even when they agree they're wrong.
So, next. What else could cause neural
damage as well as all the nodules?
Burger's disease.
He's never been out of the country.
Have his parents?
They could have brought it back.
- I don't think so.
- Doesn't matter.
His lesions are in the wrong place,
his feet are the one clear spot.
Kid's dad mentioned leishmaniasis.
Yeah, and filariasis, but the throat
nodules still don't fit with that.
Two diseases pretty much exclusive
to Southeast Asia.
What if the anthrax didn't
set off the second disease?
We're back at coincidence again?
No. What if something else was the trigger?
Nothing else happened.
We happened.
Antibiotics?
We've been through this,
it's not an allergy.
I've gotta pee.
What did the CT scan tell you?
Nothing.
On a scale of one to ten, how painful?
About half as painful as when
I punch you in the face.
Don't do that. It'll hurt you.
Carpal tunnel surgery
obviously didn't work.
Who are you?
The little ones call me Uncle Gregg.
Your dad never had carpal tunnel.
You mentioned two obscure
diseases to Dr. Chase.
How'd you know about them?
I read about them on the internet.
So, what'd you search for?
"Diseases from Asia that don't
match my son's symptoms"?
You heard about them in Asia.
I've never been there.
Well, you probably just forgot.
Let me refresh your memory.
Some remote, dusty village, close quarters,
at least a year... starting to come back?
I'm calling Dr. Cuddy.
Excuse me, what does this
have to do with our son?
Your dad's pissed off.
He should be.
Comes here, expecting us to
do an extra good job because
he gives a whole lot of
money to this hospital...
Don't talk to my son like that!
Just telling him my job,
my obligation to this...
Stop! What's going on?
There's only one thing that
you guys have got to do.
Tell the truth, or your son will die.
How long were you in Asia?
Jeff, it's a simple question.
Two years, in India.
Why would you lie about
something like that?
It was '87 and '88.
This, uh, this guru,
I thought he had some answers.
I went to his ashram, and,
ended up with no money and no answers.
I was embarrassed,
I didn't want anybody to know.
No. No, you were a test pilot.
I'm so sorry, Gabe.
What does this have to do with my son?
Clue number one:
If I were Jesus, curing this kid would
be as easy as turning water into wine.
Demonic possession?
Close, but no wafer.
Clue number two:
Rheumatology Rowan was almost right.
It causes auto-immune symptoms.
Leprosy?
Yeah, that's real big
in the Jersey suburbs.
It's leprosy.
Run a FITE stain, it'll be positive.
Daddy hung out on the wrong
kind of Indian ashram.
But it's obviously dormant in the dad,
how could the kid catch it?
It's not dormant in the
dad, it's just slow.
Damaged his ulnar nerve, was
misdiagnosed as carpal tunnel.
Never trust doctors.
Run a FITE stain.
No wonder he got anthrax.
The leprosy weakened his immune system.
Vicious circle.
The leprosy made him
vulnerable to the anthrax, and
the anthrax treatment put
the leprosy in overdrive.
But the antibiotics we gave him,
they cure leprosy.
Yeah, that's where the trouble starts.
The antibiotics hit the nerve strands,
they kill the leprosy bacteria.
The corpses get tossed into the system.
And as fascinating as our bodies are,
they're also stupid.
They produce antibodies
to beat dead bacteria.
And these aren't the polite antibodies,
they're the ones that won't sit still,
kick during naptimes.
They attack his neural and
fat cells, cause some
inflammation and all the
rest of his symptoms.
So the cure's killing him!
I want you to call down
to Carville, Louisiana,
home of the last leper
colony in the lower 48.
Get them to send up some thalidomide.
Thalidomide?
Twelve year olds don't have sex, right?
So he can't be pregnant. Make the call.
I need to speak to your boy.
Why does everybody need
to know my business?
People like talking about people.
Makes us feel superior.
Makes us feel in control.
And sometimes, for some people,
knowing some things makes them care.
I'd tell you my dad left,
my mum drank herself to death...
you gonna care about me more?
Cameron would.
Me, I just like knowing stuff.
I know you hate your dad,
but I'm gonna tell you something...
I don't hate him.
I loved him until I figured out
it hurts a lot less to just not care.
You don't expect him to turn up
to your football match?
No disappointments.
You don't expect a call on your birthday,
don't expect to see him for months?
No disappointments.
You want us to go make up?
Sink a few beers together, nice family hug?
I've given him enough hugs.
He's given me enough disappointments.
Okay.
That's it?
That's it.
Breathe.
Breathe again.
You gonna have to tell
my friends I'm a leper?
You had the antibiotics.
You're not contagious any more.
What if they already caught it?
Leprosy is incredibly hard to catch.
Even your mum didn't get it.
All right, I want you to make a fist.
It's still kinda stiff.
It'll get back to normal in a month or two.
Your skin, two or three weeks.
You haven't asked about your dad.
He lied about everything.
He lied to my mom. He lied to his boss.
He's just a liar.
He loves you.
I don't love him.
Yeah, you do.
Nothing you can do about it.
He's your dad.
It doesn't matter what he does,
you're gonna love him.
Here. Thanks.
Hey!
When's your flight?
You got time for a drink?
Wish I did.
Dr. Chase!
I've got it.
You're going to be getting
down to Oz any time soon?
Not too long. Next autumn, I hope.
I'll call you.
Well, you're all set.
I'll see you.
Yeah. I'll see you.