And the only thing wrong...
the only thing wrong
with the American dream is people.
Too many people. Too many of us telling
young people that the dream is dead.
They told me that when I was growing up in
the slums of Trenton,
and they were wrong.
They told me that
when I decided to run for Senator
with only $58 in my savings account
and they were wrong!
And they are still telling me that now,
that I don't have a chance:
Because I'm black,
because I don't have the right nose,
because I still have only $58
in my savings account.
With your help, we can
keep that dream alive.
And in closing...
just...
let me say...
Let me say that you should
all donate the legal
maximum to the next President
of the United States!
Are you okay, do you need
some water or something?
No, no, I'm fine,
I'm fine, really.
A handsome guy like you,
I bet you get 70% of the women.
Here's hoping.
Of course, it helps
your wife died of cancer.
I mean, I'm sorry,
but the sympathy vote's in your pocket.
Yeah, I appreciate your support.
Listen, Senator,
my union has a hell of a war chest.
I've always been strong on the union.
The thing is, you always go
on in your speeches about
the workers in Indonesia,
Cambodia, Timbuktu...
Because I think we have... a moral, uh...
My union members are hurting.
They don't care about moral this
or moral that. Are you all right?
Senator?
Hey!
The guys are gonna love that.
Tell him to breathe!
Back off please! Give him some room!
Senator, are you all right?
The Senator's suffering from nausea,
headache, and mental confusion.
Yeah, bad sushi is so hard to diagnose.
You're being childish.
Look, if his case is as
trivial as you think
it'll take you three
minutes to diagnose him.
Nope. I never liked
Cameron or Foreman.
Do you know why I'm forcing
you to fire one of them?
Because you need to prove
to me that you're a team player.
Now, if you did that,
you wouldn't need to
go through this exercise.
Fine. I'll hold the Senator's hair
while he upchucks.
Oh, and by the way,
I need you to give a speech at
the National Cardiology Conference.
Next week.
I don't do speeches. I'm shy.
Eastbrook Pharmaceuticals has
developed a new ACE inhibitor.
I would like you to extol the virtues
of this breakthrough medication.
Eastbrook Pharmaceuticals...
wait a second,
don't I own that company?
Oh, no, that's right, you do.
Viopril is a significant improvement
over the old version.
All there in study.
I know its price tag is
significantly improved.
You can either give one ten
minute talk and one three
minute diagnosis or you can
fire one of your pets.
My understanding was
that you believed
in rationality above all else.
Viopril...
I appreciate your keeping the media way.
We're keeping your staff away as well.
You're taking it easy, now.
I'm in the middle of a campaign.
The fast we can get you better,
the faster you can get out of here.
Anyone else at the fundraiser get sick?
I don't think so.
And I don't think that's it,
I mean, I've been under
the weather for weeks, you know.
Lots of traveling, supposed to be
in the Sudan next week.
Helps me concentrate.
Even better than drugs.
Open your mouth, please.
That's quite a scar.
When I was six,
I fell off the swings and bit my tongue.
Couldn't talk right
for the longest time.
Lots of teasing.
But, you know, it just made me fight
harder, speak up for those who can't.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Tongues heal too fast.
Your political consultants
have written you a nice story.
In a tight race the lispers alone
could put you over the top.
You a Republican, or
you just hate all politicians?
I just find being forced to
sit through drivel annoying.
You find sincerity annoying.
You're a black kid from
the ghetto who made
it to Yale Law and the
United States Senate.
That's a sufficiently mythical story,
you don't need to lie about your tongue.
Must have missed it.
What's wrong?
What is it?
It's not the food.
It's your brain.
Get an MRI and
a lumbar puncture.
Cancel your travel plans.
The senator's LP showed no sign of
infection and the MRI looks fairly clean.
I guess we can tell him
he's fairly healthy and can go home.
Well, there is something in Broca's area,
but it's small, low intensity.
Most likely just background nose.
Care to bet your job on that?
What was that?
What was what?
You got annoyed.
That was clearly an annoyed face.
I get annoyed by glib remarks
about our futures.
But last week you didn't get annoyed,
you made poopie in your pants.
It's weird, it's almost like now you know
you have nothing to worry about.
Chase has nothing to worry about?
None of you has anything to worry about.
What happened?
Vogler saw the error
of his ways and repented.
The lesion could be nothing.
It could also be
a brain tumor or infection.
There's only one way
to find out which.
You wanna cut into his brain.
Dangerous, I know.
Especially as he's a politician,
his brain's all twisted.
But I weighed that against the risk
of him stroking out before lunch.
Call surgery, get it scheduled.
You're not pregnant.
Well, I told you that.
But there's gotta be some other
reason I'm still spotting.
Sure. You were pregnant.
Based on your hormone levels,
you had a miscarriage.
I haven't even been on a date.
Right, since it's physically
impossible to have sex
without someone buying you dinner.
I haven't had sex
since I split up with my husband.
That was almost a year ago.
Fine, have it your way.
Immaculate conception.
What do I do?
Well, it's obvious.
Start a religion.
In my office.
Afternoon delight.
She just loves the hard wood.
You're not doing a brain biopsy
based on a spot on a MRI.
Where'd you get that?
Not on an United States Senator.
Oh, just so I'm clear, if he was
a janitor, that would be okay.
- Do you have a list?
- A brain biopsy
can cause permanent
neurological damage.
Where as tumors are really good for
brains, make 'em grow big and strong.
It's my call.
No, it's not.
You're pulling rank
on patient care?
It's not my call, either.
It's up to you.
Either it's a tumor or it's an infection
that the lumbar puncture didn't pick up.
Either way, if we don't treat it
immediately, it could kill you.
Or it could be nothing.
Reading brain MRis is not an exact science.
What caused my symptoms?
Wow, excellent question.
Many doctors wouldn't have gone there.
It could be a transient ischemic attack.
You could make the argument
for watching carefully for the time being.
But you'd only make that
argument if you were an administrator
covering your own ass.
That's absurd, and insulting.
Insulting, yes.
What will the voters think?
If they find out
I've had a brain biopsy?
This could leave you brain damaged,
and you're worried about NASCAR dads?
It's not a brain tumor.
It's not a bacterial infection, either.
So you biopsied his brain for nothing.
If that were true, would Dr. Wilson's
mouth be contorted into that ugly shape?
It's toxoplasmosis.
You sure?
Which means the Great Black Hope
has full-blown AIDS.
They're gonna love that in Dubuque.
Toxoplasmosis is a fairly
common fungus you can get
from eating undercooked
meat or touching cat feces.
In rare cases the fungi
travel up the blood stream
and into the brain causing
a lesion or inflammation.
So, what's the prognosis?
Toxo usually responds to treatment,
but it only causes a lesion
in your brain if your
immune system is extremely
weak to begin with.
Senator, I'm afraid you have AIDS.
- As I'm sure...
- No!
As I'm sure you know,
people with HIV can live a long time.
What else could do this to me?
Theoretically, certain cancers...
If you have toxo in your brain,
you have AIDS.
I do not have AIDS.
I don't shoot up drugs,
I don't sleep with...
This is very bad news.
I get that, and I sympathize.
But we've gotta speed through
the denial phase because
you need antiretrovirals
and you need them fast.
But... you haven't even
tested me for HIV!
We will.
But the toxo drugs are going to piss off
your fungi, and when fungi get pissed...
I am not gonna take the pills.
You're afraid word will leak out.
Trust me, you're not going to be
President either way.
They don't call it the White House
because of the paint job.
Here's what you're gonna do.
You're going to give me
the drugs for the toxo only.
You are going to test me
for HIV under a false name.
You are going to test me for cancer
and anything else that
could have done this to me.
If I have cancer,
I will deal with it.
But I do not
have AIDS.
"Eastbrook Pharmaceuticals are pleased
to announce that Dr. Gregory House
will present the latest research on
their exciting new ACE inhibitor."
You're making that up.
That's Vogler's company.
Press release.
Doing an address at the
North American Cardiology Conference.
House never gives speeches.
But when I really believe in something...
Gosh dang it, I've got a chance
to make a difference here.
You made a deal with Vogler?
It's all the rage.
Everybody's doing it.
So, what's the deal?
You get to keep all of us
if you flog his products?
One speech, no biggie.
Foreman's doing a bone marrow
biopsy to check for cancer.
Cancer? The Senator's got AIDS.
Cancer sounds better
on a press release.
I need you guys to rush
the ELISA test for HIV.
Thank you.
For the speech.
When I said rush,
I meant, you know, fast.
Stat's the word you doctors use, right?
I know it's hard for you...
Double stat?
This may sting a little.
Sorry.
It wasn't the shot, it's...
my head, it's killing me.
You know, Senator,
we don't have to do this now.
We can hold off until
your HIV test comes back.
Guess you figure
it's gonna come back positive.
Well, in my experience...
Patients lie.
Politicians lie more.
And black politicians...
I don't think black politicians lie
more than white politicians.
We lie less.
You figure we're morally superior?
I've got my theories.
No, we, we just can't
get away with it.
No one's gonna give us
the benefit of the doubt.
No one's gonna cut us
a second chance. And,
and when it happens it's not just
a bad politician, it's, it's,
it's a bad role model,
it's a discredit to the race.
You ready?
Yeah, yeah.
Take a deep breath.
Dr. House. I just wanted to...
You're welcome, again.
I want you to know how much I...
Got it. You're grateful.
Apparently you seem to think
it'll mean a lot to me to know that.
Do you know
why people pray to God?
I thought you didn't believe in God.
I don't.
Well, then you better be
making a very good point.
Do you think they pray
to Him and praise Him
because they want Him to
know how great He is?
God already knows that.
Are you comparing me to God?
I mean, that's great, but just so
you know, I've never made a tree.
I thank you because
it means something to me.
To be grateful
for what I receive.
You are the most naive
atheist I've ever met.
Dr. House,
you have a patient in Room One.
Thank God.
People pray so that
God won't crush them like bugs.
I'm not gonna crush you.
Petechial bruising?
I don't know if I'm pronouncing that right.
Gosh, the internet is
such a wonderful tool.
It could be leukemia.
Definitely possible.
The more likely diagnosis is hickey.
Well, it can't be a hickey.
Why is everybody so ashamed
of sex all of a sudden?
I'm not having sex.
I've barely even thought
about sex since my marriage.
I say you're having sex,
you say you're not.
Either you're lying,
or I'm wrong.
Or there's some middle ground.
You mean like oral?
I mean you're having sex
without knowing it.
I'm testing you
for booze, drugs and GHB.
I don't drink,
and... what's GHB?
The date rape drug.
It's positive.
Your T-cell count is eight,
which means there's
a good chance you'll die.
I'm telling you this because we need
to contact your sexual partners.
I've only had two girlfriends.
Two, after my wife died.
I used condoms.
You know the chances of you getting HIV
from heterosexual sex with a condom?
Yes.
Some day there will be
a black president.
a gay president.
Maybe there will even be
a gay, black president.
But one combination I do not see
happening is gay, black, and dead.
You need to stop lying to me.
It must be miserable,
always assuming the worst in people.
Oh, cut the crap, you're dying.
You're clever, you're witty,
and you are a coward!
You're scared of taking chances.
I take chances all the time,
it's one of my worst qualities.
On people?
Wanting to believe the best
about people doesn't make it true.
Being afraid to believe
it doesn't make it false.
Well, that's very moving.
It's a shame I don't vote.
This is who I am.
I believe in people.
I'm not hiply cynical and
I don't make easy, snide remarks.
I would rather think that people are
good and be disappointed once and again.
I need to draw some more blood.
Nurse!
The antiretrovirals aren't working.
That's not surprising.
He's just going to keep getting worse.
You realize that, right?
Why are you spying on my case?
Why are you giving
that speech next week?
We're both just doing
what we have to do.
And you don't see a problem with that?
Checking in on a patient?
Yeah, wow, how do I
look myself in the mirror?
You're not the one being asked to
perpetrate a fraud on the American people.
It's a ten minute speech!
That I've been ordered to give.
Vogler's drug works!
Don't care.
Oh, why do you have to make
everything so dramatic?
Because I'm a very
high-strung little lapdog.
No pills.
What's going on??
The antiretrovirals aren't working.
Why not?
Because you don't have AIDS.
The first test was a false positive.
Happens one time in every five thousand.
You ran a second test.
Yeah.
You're still dying.
The only difference is
now we don't know why.
He's continuing to lose control of
the muscles on his right side,
his brain is getting foggier, and his
T-cells are in the single digits.
Why are we doing this here?
So Cuddy can't find us.
Unless we figure out the underlying disease,
this guy's lied to his last constituent.
False negative on the PCR AIDS test?
Ran it twice.
Immunoglobulin deficiency?
No history of respiratory problems.
Ideopathic T-cell deficiency.
Ideopathic, from the Latin
meaning we're idiots
'cause we can't figure
out what's causing it.
Give him a whole body scan.
You hate whole body scans.
'Cause they're useless.
Could probably scan
everyone of us and find
five different doodads
that look like cancer.
But, when you're 4th-down, 100 to go,
in the snow, you don't
call a running play up the middle.
Unless you're the Jets.
I hate sports metaphors.
Why did you order the second AIDS test?
Standard procedure.
Oh, well, that's you.
Mr. Standard Procedure.
You suspected the first test
was a false positive?
I knew he was going to Africa
and I figured
he was vaccinated for Hep A and B.
That could cause a false positive.
Yeah, but you knew that before
you ordered the first test. What changed?
I should have ordered both.
You were sure he had AIDS, then you
talked to him, then you had doubts.
What, what did he say?
He said he had not engaged
in any risky behavior.
And you believed him.
Well, he didn't have any reason to lie...
Everybody lies,
except politicians?
House, I do believe
you're a romantic.
You just didn't believe him,
you believed in him.
Do you want to come over tonight
and watch old movies and cry?
Dr. Cameron's getting to you.
Well, I guess you can't be around that
much niceness and not get any on you.
Is that why you haven't
put the moves on her?
What makes you think
I haven't put the moves on her?
Oh. Oh, boy! You're in trouble.
You have restored my faith
in the human race.
You're lying.
No, I'm not lying.
I just got your results back.
No GHB, no nothing.
It means you're having sex,
and you're lying about it.
No, and I have a new symptom.
I have a rash on my butt.
Do you want to...
What is it?
It's a carpet burn.
No! It can't be!
Doctor, I love sex.
I miss it.
I haven't had any in over a year.
Well, you managed to
keep this appointment,
so you have no
short-term memory problem.
Multiple personalities?
Do you find yourself
losing chunks of time?
Do you wake up and
you don't remember falling asleep?
No, I just wake up
really exhausted.
Is something upsetting you?
No.
My ex lives in the apartment downstairs.
He's always calling me,
always wanting to get back together,
complaining about mixed signals.
Get out of my life,
how much clearer can you get?
We have a sleep lab
in the basement.
If nothing else, it'll get you away
from your ex for a night.
Slightly enlarged lymph
node in his left armpit.
How slightly?
Quarter mil.
Lymphoma?
Sure, or he's had a cold
in the last six months.
What, you've got her on speed dial?
I just follow the scent of arrogance.
Another slightly enlarged node over here.
Two more in his neck
and one in his groin.
And there's a cyst in his liver.
Looks complex. Central necrosis?
Spontaneous bleeding, it's benign.
I was rooting for a really cool tumor,
instead we're stuck with this crap.
Doesn't matter. Once you find 'em,
ou've gotta check 'em.
Well, knock yourselves out.
I just saw Senator Wright,
he looks like hell.
That sushi must have been
a lot worse than you thought.
Mr. Vogler, would you like
a free whole body scan?
A man of your stature should get himself
checked at least three times a year.
Here's a few key points I want
you to cover during your speech.
Fourteen pages. The audience will
be comatose by paragraph two.
Throw in a joke.
Dr. Chase. We need to talk.
How do you see this ending?
What ending?
I can't fire you, so you
have no reason to fear me,
and therefore no reason to lie to me.
You told Cuddy where I was.
You told Vogler what I was doing.
Yeah.
So how can I work with you?
Well, you don't have a choice.
This might hurt a little.
Lie to me.
Okay. It'll, feel like
a gentle massage.
House is a lousy teacher.
You can't lie for beans.
Have you ever told
any really big ones?
Oh, I might be messed up,
but I'm not that out of it,
no no no no no...
Strap his arm down.
Am I gonna be okay?
I hope so.
I am selling my soul.
Just a little piece.
And you are getting something in return.
I said I was selling it.
I didn't say I was giving it away.
That would be immoral, and stupid.
All they've done is added antacid.
Does it work?
That's not the point!
Well, of course it's the point!
He's not asking you to lie, he's not
asking you to do something illegal...
He's not asking me to do anything.
He's not ordering you.
He gave you a choice.
You chose your staff.
I know this isn't easy for you.
You'll suffer. Vicodin sales
in Jersey will triple.
But you are doing a good thing.
Only you could feel like crap
for doing something good.
Kidney and liver cysts are both benign,
and lymph nodes all came back clean.
His left armpit node has
antibodies for CB 11.
Well, not enough to indicate lymphoma.
We never tested for hairy-cell leukemia.
No, but we would have picked it up
somewhere besides one lymph node.
And his spleen isn't enlarged.
Size isn't everything.
The spleen is the mother
load for hairy-cells.
Let's cut it open.
You can't biopsy his spleen.
It'll bleed like...
In the Senator's condition, a spleen biopsy
could easily cause sepsis and kill him!
Why do you do this to me?
Now, if I kill him, I can't tell the judge
I had no idea of the risks involved.
His brain's turning
into mush, and he's at
risk for more infections,
so we have to do it.
See, that'll sound much better in court.
Okay, go tell our human pincushion
we'll be sticking him one more time.
Cuddy.
Don't you hate doing this?
Yeah.
What's up?
You like me.
Why?
That's kind of a sad question.
Just trying to figure out
what makes you tick.
I am not warm and fuzzy
and you are basically
a stuffed animal made by grandma.
I don't think that's why you're asking.
I think it's because of the speech.
Oh God,
don't try and pick me apart.
Then why are you asking?
What do you want to hear?
Hey, Senator. We need to do one
more biopsy, on your spleen.
I'll have to sign lefty,
my fingers aren't working.
You've been coughing a lot?
Does it hurt?
It's like I can't get air.
Is that from the toxo?
No, this is, this is new.
You don't need to sign,
we can't do the biopsy.
The Senator's breathing
is severely impaired.
His O2 stat levels are at 89.
His silver stain indicates
pneumocystis carinii pneumonia.
Another killer fungus.
It's consistent with hairy-cell leukemia.
But we can't biopsy his spleen.
Respiratory distress?
His platelets are 20 and dropping,
his blood won't clot worth a damn.
There's gotta be another way
to diagnose hairy-cell.
No, his bone marrow's indeterminate,
spleen's the only way to go.
You know, when the Inuit go fishing,
they don't look for fish.
Why, Dr. House?
They look for the blue heron,
because there's
no way to see the fish.
But if there's fish,
there's gonna be birds fishing.
Now, if he's got hairy-cell, what else are
we gonna see circling overhead?
He should have all sorts of weird viruses.
HTLV and ATLV.
We can test for them.
Run the titers.
These were your brain waves at 2:45 AM.
Now, here it comes, there's
an abrupt jump from slow-wave sleep.
This indicates partial sleep arousal.
The most common type is somnambulism...
sleepwalking.
That would explain why I'm
so tired when I wake up.
Yes, and also why you were pregnant.
And the hickies.
And the carpet burn.
I had sex in my sleep?
Sexsomnia is a documented disorder.
You said your ex lives downstairs...
I'll kill him.
Okay, but he probably didn't know
that you were asleep.
Sexsomniacs can act pretty normal.
I'm going to write you a prescription
for a low-dose antidepressant.
It'll let you sleep better.
If you want to save yourself the $15 co-pay,
you can have sex while you're awake.
He's my ex, I...
You live in the same building,
you haven't had sex with
anyone else for a year,
you sleepwalk right into his arms.
Call me crazy, but
I'm sensing unresolved issues.
Negative for HTLV-1 and 2
and Negative for ATLV and
everything else. It's not hairy-cell.
Hey. You really gonna give that speech?
You've got an opinion, too?
I'm a little surprised.
Frankly, I thought you were too much
of a self-absorbed ass to do this for us.
You're welcome.
He's positive for Epstein-Barr.
So what? It doesn't point to
hairy-cell, it's irrelevant.
Hey!
You didn't fall off the swings
when you were eight.
Six!
Ever.
Give that back!
We have to talk.
You had an epileptic seizure.
That's how you bit your tongue.
I haven't had a seizure since I was...
What medication did you take?
No seizure since I was six.
No drugs since I was ten!
Yeah, that's it.
Don't worry about what the question is,
don't worry that you're starting to
feel dizzy, just stay on message.
My mother used to call it physofin...
- Phenytoin?
- Yeah!
Okay, okay, you're okay,
it's okay.
Everybody lies.
Senator Gary H. Wright of New Jersey
had childhood epilepsy.
He took phenytoin.
That drug, with the Epstein-Barr
virus, is associated
with common variable
immunodeficiency disease.
T-cells down, B-cells down, it keeps
you from forming enough antibodies.
See, antibodies are basically
your defensive line.
And your brain is like the quarterback.
And then the fungi are like blitzing
linebackers, plunging up the middle.
Your lungs are like...
okay, you've got two quarterbacks...
CVID? That's a type of
immunoglobulin deficiency. I said that.
Yeah, well, it was a stupid idea
when you said it.
Then he got the respiratory problem
and tested positive for Epstein-Barr.
That's pretty much a childhood disease.
Another reason why
Chase's suggestion was idiotic.
He got it when he was a kid.
Didn't get any symptoms
until now, it happens.
It gets triggered by stress,
like public speaking.
So you're basing your
diagnosis on a virus that's
relatively common and a drug
he took thirty years ago.
Start the senator on
IV immunoglobulin stat.
If he gets better, I'm right,
if he dies, you're right.
Dr. House!
You faked that.
No.
Say "antiretroviral".
Antiretroviral.
Now say it three times fast.
We just got back your latest blood results.
Your white cells are up, your
T-cells are back over 100.
Well, that's good, right?
In a week? That's terrific.
You'll need medication for
the rest of your life, but
other than that, you're fine.
Am I well enough to run for president?
Well, why not run for pope
while you're at it?
Oh, come on.
Kennedy had Addison's, FDR had polio.
Two of the best presidents
in the last hundred years...
If they were running today
they wouldn't stand a chance.
So, you figure you'd be Surgeon General
if you didn't have the limp.
No, there's things I can't do, and
like you said, I have to live with reality.
Well,
then I'm running.
Good for you.
No, don't get excited,
he's right, I, uh, I won't win.
Then why run?
Oh, I see, your point being the only way to
make a difference is to win every fight.
But hey, why listen to me?
I own the company,
I'm certainly not to be trusted, right?
Dr. Gregg House,
on the other hand, has a reputation.
For integrity, among other things.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Dr. Gregg House.
Eastbrook Pharmaceuticals'
extraordinary commitment to
research excellence is exemplified
by their new ACE inhibitor,
a breakthrough medical approach that
will protect millions from heart disease.
That's not a speech.
I thought it was pithy.
You got enough for a press release, anyhow.
Foreman or Cameron?
A few things I forgot to mention.
Ed Vogler is a brilliant businessman.
A brilliant judge of people, and
a man who has never lost a fight.
You know how I know
the new ACE inhibitor is good?
Because the old one was good.
The new one is really the same,
it's just more expensive.
A lot more expensive.
See, that's another example
of Ed's brilliance.
Whenever one of his drugs is about
to lose its patent he has his boys
and girls alter it just a tiny bit
and patent it all over again.
Making not just a pointless new pill,
but millions and millions of dollars.
Which is good for everbody, right?
The patients, pish. Who cares,
they're just so damn sick!
God obviously never liked them anyway.
All the healthy people in the room, let's
have a big round of applause for Ed Vogler!
I threw in a joke.
I'm sorry.
I should have taken a couple of extra
Vicodin and just held my nose.
I'm guessing you did take
a couple extra Vicodin.
True.
You don't need to worry
about firing anyone.
I'm leaving.
Why?
Is this another noble,
self-sacrificing gesture?
You trying to protect Foreman?
No.
So this is just, "Don't fire me, I quit."
I'm protecting myself.
You asked me why I like you.
You're abrasive and rude,
but I figured everything you do,
you do it to help people.
But I was wrong.
You do it because it's right.
There are only two ways
I can deal with things.
One is in my control.
That's to leave.
Goodbye, House.