Are you thinking about taking drugs?
Well...
think again, because drugs
are not the answer.
Take it from me, Hank Wiggen.
Oh, don't remember this ugly mug?
Two years ago, I was a star.
I won nine games in a row.
But by the end of August I was a goner.
Cut, cut!
Not good, huh?
Well, you caught the ball.
Yeah.
Look, I usually don't give line readings,
but try this, here, here.
Hollywood ain't holding its breath.
Well, they're doing it wrong.
I mean, for Hank.
Tell the director.
I thought I'd give the marriage a few months
before I'd go for the meddling wife thing.
His arm came back day
after he hooked up, I say meddle.
You okay?
Just gas. Go help your man.
Give me a little room here to work it out.
Take it from me, Hank Wiggen.
Like that?
No...
Hey, sweetheart.
Hey.
Hi, Bryan.
You boys having a little trouble
with the big speech?
Yeah, you got any ideas?
It's your story.
Just be yourself.
Drugs were there,
you took 'em. Simple.
Why'd you get clean?
Because I was gonna die.
And come April, 'cause you're clean,
You're starting, opening day,
against the Yanks.
Try it her way?
Yeah.
- Okay.
Let's start with the 2nd part first.
That'll get him in the groove.
Okay.
We'll do the throwing thing first.
Everybody wants to direct...
Warner alright?
Yeah, he's good. You just
bring it, babe. Just tell your story.
Come on, kid! Show 'em what
you're gonna give the Yankees!
Alright, action!
Oh, God!
It's gonna be okay,
It's gonna be okay.
He's got osteopenia.
His bones are too thin to fix the arm.
No, price is not a problem
if you have what I need.
- Osteo...
- Young man?
How did you know?
Well, if he's an old man,
osteopenia would just be a fact of life,
you make him comfortable, send him home,
which means you're just boring me.
So he's young, which means
it's most likely caused by cancer,
and you're here
because you haven't found it.
Have you looked really, really hard?
MRI and PET scan are both negative.
Well, how old is he?
Maybe the osteopenia is just early onset.
Well, let's see. Born 9/21/77.
It's Hank Wiggen?
- He signed it, sweet.
- Yeah.
To Jimmy Wilson,
the Cy Young of medicine.
You ask for that?
I just the Jimmy part.
The bone's too thin to support the kind of
surgery that would let him pitch again.
But if we figure out
what's causing the osteopenia,
we can reverse the bone damage,
then do the surgery.
Beat the Yankees, and save the free world.
It was a working dinner.
My work, company pays.
I dunno. I just feel kinda weird
after what it turned into.
Well, then it stopped being work.
You know, if it'll solve
your ethics problem
you can reimburse me for these.
What are they, five dollars and
fifty-seven cents, I believe?
. You let me know about Friday?
Yeah.
None of the usual suspects!
Age isn't right, in apparent
perfect health before
this incident, MRI and PET
scan negative for tumors.
Test him again,
it's gotta be cancer.
Sorry I'm late.
Car broke down on the interstate.
Don't believe you.
Chem 7 also shows
a poor kidney function.
Now why would a guy in
his twenties have a poor kidney?
Cancer. It first attacks the bones,
and then the kidneys.
Come on, people.
He was 17 and 7!
His ERA was 2.1.
You want it to be his kidneys,
because if it's his kidneys,
then maybe we can treat it,
maybe we can fix it.
And if it's cancer,
then he'll never pitch again.
If this were a regular guy who
came in and broke his arm lifting a box,
you would've packed him up
and sent him home!
My God, you're right,
I lost my head.
All life is equally sacred.
And I promise you, the
next knitting injury that
comes in here, we're on
it like stink on cheese.
He weighed 175 his rookie year.
Stop.
Now he's 195 after playing
a year in Japan. Why?
He let himself go.
Steroids!
I mean, the guy was a drug user,
I'm sure he wouldn't have balked
at pumping up through chemicals.
That'd explain the weight gain.
And the kidney problems.
And the bone loss.
Go ask him what he's on.
When he says nothing,
have him pee in a cup.
If your car breaks down,
you're an hour late, not two minutes.
And two minutes isn't late enough
to use a clever excuse like car trouble.
I was coming in early.
Unprompted lies,
that's a bad sign.
Either a guilty conscience or
something personal's going on.
See, that's all you had to do,
Just walk in, sit down, do your job.
No, no, I never took them.
We're gonna need a urine sample.
Oh no, you don't trust me.
Baby, I'm worried about
taking this morphine.
You're in pain,
the doses are monitored.
It's not a slip.
Besides, opiates weren't your thing.
They should've been.
Mr. Wiggen? The urine sample.
I wanna say no, so I am. No.
Trust is a big issue in early recovery.
He really did gain the weight honestly.
If you say so.
You're not getting it.
He thinks I'm an idiot.
He sure does.
Should we save the sample?
Dr. Sportsfan can put it in Lucite
and hang it around his neck.
Hey, Friday night?
Can you cover for me?
I think so.
Oh, Friday. No, I'm sorry, I have to go
to that oncology thing... that seminar.
Oh.
What's going on?
Dinner with the... drug rep.
Casting pharmaceuticals.
Arnie?
Claims he has 500 lawyer jokes,
only tells one?
New guy.
You need cash?
No. I don't have that much on me...
No no, it's not a problem.
Ya, I'll be over by 6. 'Kay.
5 p.m., Dr. House checks out.
It's 4:45.
I was rounding up.
Carol Moffett,
please see Dr. House in Exam Room 1.
Whoa, whoa, not so fast, Kathy.
It's Carol.
Ah.
Uh, trouble with the leg?
When's the wedding?
This Saturday.
Oh. Not much time to fit
into that pretty dress,
and no time for practical shoe-shopping.
You're running two miles a day
further than you should be.
It hurts right here...
New shoes, less miles, and ex-nay on the
afternoon Cokes, you're gonna look beautiful.
What's wrong with you?
I can't get my contact lenses out...
Out of what?
They're not in your eyes.
But they're red.
That's because you're trying to
remove your corneas.
What's wrong with you?
Uh, lately, my wife has noticed that...
Yeah, yeah. Symptoms,
we're working on a personal best here.
Yeah. Numbness in my feet
and hands, constipation...
And?
Maybe he doesn't feel comfortable
talking about his private matters...
Well, neither would I, if I was having
trouble controlling my pee pee!
You're a dentist.
Nitrous oxide poisoning,
which means you're either dipping
into your own supply,
or you've got a bad valve in the office.
Laughing gas rehab's probably
more expensive than the plumber.
Meanwhile, get yourself some B12.
Who's left?
I can't see...
Nah, I'm just screwing with you.
It's a hangover,
my English Lit prof. Told me
he'd fail me next time
if I didn't show up with a doctor's note.
Well, make friends with the dentist.
He can give you a note, and maybe
a little nitrous to take the edge off.
Dr. House!
He tested negative for steroids.
Elevated beta 2 proteins, though,
could be cancerous.
Amyloidosis, or lymphoma.
Or steroids.
You guys got any money on you?
He tested negative for steroids.
I, um, I have a couple 20s on me.
50 of them?
Foreman?
The FAT PAD biopsy and abdominal CT scan
were negative for the cancers, but...
Well, that just leaves us with steroids!
He tested negative for steroids.
Less money is made by biochemists
working on a cure for cancer than by
their colleagues struggling valiantly
to find ways to hide steroid use.
But there's one thing they can't hide...
Hi. I'm Dr. House.
And this is the coolest day of my life.
See? Steroid use shrinks the testicles.
I am clean, man,
no steroids, no nothing.
Your lips say no,
your prunes say yes.
Hypogonadism.
Isn't that a great word?
Thanks, we don't get to
say it nearly enough.
Start him on Lupron right away.
These freaks are willing to defile themselves
for mass entertainment, for money.
I feel sorry for them.
He drops a clean urine,
denies using steroids,
then you're giving him a drug
for what, steroid abuse?
No, no, it's not.
It's got calcium in it.
It's very good for the bones.
Basically, on a molecular level,
it's just milk.
How long do you figure
before I get a call from Cuddy?
You put him on Lupron.
And, you told them it was like milk.
Yes.
Is there any way
in which that is not a lie?
It's creamy.
But, I had 3 reasons.
Good ones?
Well, we'll see in a minute,
I'm just making them up now...
He lied to me first.
Your mother did teach you
2 wrongs don't make a right.
If he lies to me
about not taking steroids,
then I lie to him about not treating
steroids, he's cured. Adds up for me...
Second reason.
If I told him the truth,
he wouldn't have taken the stuff.
And if he told you the truth,
what would this stuff do to him?
Severe respiratory problems.
Third reason.
I wanted to eliminate the placebo effect.
Excellent!
You and your lawyer can write a paper.
Which brings me to my fourth reason.
I thought you said there were only three.
I thought you'd buy one of them.
Seriously?
He's not gonna sue.
Because his lawyer is a nice guy,
who realizes it's unfair
to blame us for ruining
this kid's hundred
million-dollar career.
Good guess, but no.
If the Lupron causes respiratory problems,
it means he's not on steroids,
which means there's something
else wrong with him.
And the choices, for that something else,
are almost universally very bad.
Osteopenia messing his bones up.
Hypogonadism.
Impaired liver function,
kidney function, and...
we have managed to find
the only professional
athlete in the galaxy
who is not on steroids.
And it's not cancer.
So, what's killing him?
Who shares my suspicions that
the Yankees were somehow involved?
Shrunken testicles indicate his body's
not putting out enough testosterone.
Throw out the lungs,
that was the Lupron, my fault.
Don't worry,
I'll send him a nice note.
What about something environmental?
Arsenic, mercury,
the symptoms could indicate...
Pretty small environment.
Wife's fine, no one else is sick.
If you throw out the kidneys,
everything else adds up.
The testicles, the bones,
the impaired liver function,
could all be caused
by a breakdown of his adrenal glands.
Addison's disease, I like it.
Mainly of course,
because the treatment is...
Steroids.
Enough irony for all of us.
Treatment would cause him to retain fluid.
With the kidneys almost shut
down already, he'll die.
Well, we'll get him a new kidney.
Your theory is that
Addison's is causing all
the symptoms except for
the kidney problems.
What's causing the kidney problems?
Cameron, if you could make
an ironic guess right about now?
- He tested nega...
- Negative for steroids.
Agreed. He's not on steroids now.
If he was on them
anytime in the last five years,
it could've caused the kidney damage.
You see, kidneys don't wear watches.
Sure, gallbladders do, but it doesn't
matter, 'cuz kidneys can't tell time.
Steroid damage could take years.
No steroids.
How many times does he have to tell you?
I don't know.
How many times did he lie about cocaine
before coming clean with the league?
That is completely different.
Oh, that's right, I remember.
You never did come clean.
The league was out to get
you, they faked the blood test,
you had to get yourself
a lawyer and everything.
If Hank says he never used steroids,
that's the truth.
That's too bad.
Because our theory is that
the kidney damage is caused by A,
and everything else is caused by B.
The beauty of this theory is that
we can treat A and B.
But if you add the kidney symptoms
back into the mix,
then we are looking at
another letter altogether,
one that is apparently not in the alphabet.
Can't fix the bones, no more baseball, no
more breathing... no more brain function.
Get another explanation.
Okay. Yeah.
Think I've got one in my other pants.
Hold on.
Five years ago, Bangor, Maine.
My pitching coach had me on something,
I never knew what it was.
And you never tried
too hard to find out either.
I gained 12 pounds of
muscle in like, 4 weeks.
I'm sorry, baby.
How you doin' Doc?
Good. Very good, yeah.
You want me to put Hank Wiggen
on the transplant list.
He needs a new kidney.
I was thinking
the kidney people might have some.
Well, they like to save
them for people who have...
how do I put this... kidney problems.
He's a professional ballplayer,
brings joy to millions.
Do you really want to be known
as the hospital that sent him home to die?
That's a great idea, we can be the
hospital that killed two people.
The guy who deserved the kidney,
and the ballplayer we bumped
up the list when we weren't even
sure what was wrong with him.
Everything else is related
to the Addison's.
The test for Addison's was inconclusive.
The test for Addison's
is always inconclusive.
Why do we do it at all?
We should just ask you.
You're not putting him on the list.
Your powers of deduction are breathtaking.
You take a perverse pleasure
at turning me down.
It's what I live for.
Once in a while, though,
try to ruin my day.
Ask me something I can say "yes" to.
Oh, I'm sorry Doctor,
I didn't know you were busy.
Want me to come back?
Is he on the list?
No.
Then I'm giving him one of mine.
Okay.
You're not gonna tell me
it's a bad idea?
Why give a kidney to someone
who might not be able to use it?
Not my area.
That is, however, my chair.
When do we do it?
Very noble gesture.
My favorite kind,
dramatic, yet completely empty.
The chances of non-identical twins...
- being a match...
- Do you live alone?
You writing a book?
I made it a question
just because it's more polite.
You got a big "Keep Out" sign
stapled on your forehead.
That explains it,
I told them to put it on my door.
Even if real human contact is something
you don't have or even want, or need,
you should at least be able to
see it in other people.
Yeah. Right. True love.
That's just how we match organs these days.
There's a couple in France, high school
sweethearts, they're trading brains.
We're a match. Run your tests.
Hey. The lab call, is she a match?
Haven't heard yet.
You got a text message, though.
Friday night, very cryptic.
Gee... thanks for checking.
Can you cover for me?
Oncology seminar.
Right.
Friday night the same thing
as the car trouble?
I had car trouble.
House says you were lying.
I believe him.
What's that?
You got a little wet smudge
at the end of your nose!
Hey, I like the guy.
He says what he wants, does what he wants.
He won't talk to anyone
unless he can jerk them around.
Or needs a thousand bucks.
What is with that?
I scored.
It's a brave new world, Doc,
and we are at the cutting edge.
You are looking at two all-access
passes to Paradise itself!
How much?
True cost, no man can say.
Could that man's accountant say?
One thousand dollars.
Friday night, the biggest official monster
truck jam in the history of New Jersey!
Okay, please tell me
you didn't just say Friday night.
Whatever you've got, you cancel.
I can't do it!
Listen, they only give
these tickets to owners.
Anytime.
We wanna be in the middle of the track,
we're in the middle of the track.
These tickets are so good...
we have to sign a release.
I mean it. We do this, we could die.
I've got the oncology thing!
I...
The rectal cancer lecture,
they booked me a year ago!
I can't get out,
there's no way out!
Fine.
I'll ask one of my other friends.
What, you're saying
I've only got one friend?
Uh, and who...?
Kevin, in Bookkeeping.
Okay, well first of all,
his name's Carl.
I call him Kevin.
It's a secret "friendship club" name.
It's hookers.
Oh, my God!
Multiple hookers!
But House is House, right?
He's gotta have his way.
Four or five of 'em.
That's not even funny!
What, you don't think he has sex?
No, of course he...
Of course not, he doesn't have sex,
he makes love!
I didn't say that.
It's the lab.
Dr. Foreman.
If you have the results,
I'd like you to talk
to both of us. If you
don't, wait for me to...
Believe me,
I'd much rather be with your better half.
And by better half, of course,
I mean the one who struck
out Sammy Sosa on three
pitches and talks a lot less.
But I thought I would talk
to you first, and alone.
I got your results back from the lab...
you do match.
I do?
You're also pregnant.
You can't be a donor.
Not in your current condition.
Excuse me...
I have to go talk to my husband.
Heart looks good.
We can schedule the transplant.
No transplant.
Lola's not gonna have an abortion.
Actually, your wife just told me
that she was making an appointment.
Well, I don't care what she said.
I think you two need to
discuss this further...
We've been trying to
get pregnant almost since we met.
Well, it's your wife's decision
whether or not she...
She wants to trade a child for a kidney,
that's murder!
I'm not gonna let her do that.
Foreman says we've got a problem
with the transplant.
If she terminates the pregnancy, he's not
going to let himself die on principle.
Would you give up a baby
for someone you love?
Please tell me I don't have to decide.
Depends, how long would they live?
Is this a pragmatic question for you?
Fifty years, no problem.
Six months, I say let 'em die.
Well, I've actually given this
a lot of thought,
and my personal tipping point is
seven years, eight months, and 14 days.
I couldn't do it.
You found religion.
Do you have to be religious
to believe a fetus is a life?
There seems to be a correlation.
I'm, uh...
Do you like monster trucks?
I don't know what they are.
Right.
I got two tickets.
Friday night.
You asking me to go with you?
Sure. Sounds good.
Like a... date?
Exactly.
Except for the "date" part.
Forget it.
Ah... no, I was gonna
go to the oncology dinner...
'Course, you have to
hear Wilson's lecture.
No. I just found out
he canceled like, two weeks ago.
So... what do we wear?
Still with us, Hank?
Yeah. My chest feels funny...
Tachycaridia.
Your heart's beating too fast.
We're sorting it out,
but you stay with us, alright?
Keep talking to us, Hank.
Where's Lola...?
10 units of insulin sub q, an IV push...
It's still dropping.
Why's his potassium up?
Damned if I know.
We've got to suck the potassium out of him.
We gotta get his heart rate down.
Need a crash cart!
It's definitely not Addison's.
It's not steroids either.
His heart rate is 130 and rising,
like a Randy Johnson line drive.
A for effort.
There's no point in doing the transplant.
Even if he was stable enough, it's obvious
that we have no idea what's wrong with him!
First it's too high, and now it's too low?
His heart's not responding to the atropine.
Heart rate's down to 40.
I thought it was up.
Now it's down.
Last time he went out at 35.
What's wrong?
I have no idea.
Hit him with the atropine
before he gets to 35 again.
We've already given him 3 ml.
Apparently, that's not enough.
We can't stabilize his heart rate.
What did you do to him?
Kayexolate.
His pulse was through the roof.
So is his potassium.
It wouldn't do this.
But something did.
Call me when he's stable... or dead.
I remember the first time.
You weren't even supposed
to be pitching that day.
I'd flown all the way to Tokyo
to watch this kid, and he gets tossed
for arguing a call in the first inning.
Ah, your pitches... perfect.
Ball seemed to go faster than your arm.
It was like the rules didn't apply,
like physics couldn't slow you down.
Goddamn, it was beautiful.
Hey, Warner.
Hey, kid. How ya feelin'?
I hurt. My arm,
my head... everywhere.
They must have dialed down the morphine.
That's just wrong,
you're in pain.
Hey.
I got something for ya.
No...
A doc in St. Louis gave
'em to me for a migraine.
I'm an addict, I can't take that.
Even Lola was okay with the morphine.
This stuff's just a little stronger.
Go on.
I'll just try one, Warner.
Three more symptoms.
Heart rate up, heart rate down,
now he's hallucinating.
You gotta promise not to tell Lola...
He's not just dreaming?
No REM. He's actually awake.
Drugs?
Not psychedelics,
not with the heart symptoms.
All hallucinations would
point to digitalis.
It would also mess up his heart.
But, he's not on it,
and why would he take it?
Yeah. Pithy analysis.
I can see why they asked you
to speak at the cancer dinner.
I'm sorry I'm gonna miss it.
I'm sorry about the monster trucks.
No, I think it's great.
You're... giving back.
The only thing is...
the digitalis...
it would only explain the later symptoms,
not the original ones.
Sure, it's got a lotta movement,
problem is everybody sees the movement.
Yer throwing yer curve ball,
like yer throwing a curve ball.
Deception, that's it.
Same motion, less movement,
so it won't come back at ya.
How'd you get in here?
Spoke Spanish. Told them I was the
new shortstop from the Dominican.
How's Hank doin'?
Lousy.
Around your fingernails,
that swelling, it's called clubbing.
Hippocrates noticed that a lot
of his friends who also had
that, tended to frequently
grab their chests and die.
Yeah, I got a heart condition.
What's wrong with Hank?
What do you take for it?
Digitalis.
Got 'em with you?
That's weird.
I just filled this prescription
a couple days ago.
There's another bottle here.
Don't bother.
Hank Wiggen stole your pills.
He tried to kill himself.
So what happened?
He left the bottle open,
while he went to get some water?
Next time, just take the whole bottle.
Hey man, you got no right...
See, people remember how many they've got.
Date's right on the label, number of
pills, regular person can do the math.
But a junkie doesn't have to.
It's how many pills he's got left,
that's all he's thinking about.
Bought a big insurance policy?
This isn't about the money.
Not for you, no.
Most reputable stores won't cash
your checks after you're dead.
But for Lola... well, girls like that,
they're all about the money...
Don't you say that.
She already saved my life.
I was dead in Japan
and she brought me back,
everything since then, that's gravy,
it's more than I deserve.
- You owe her.
- Everything.
So, the attempted suicide,
the scaring her to death, that's...
what is that, that's... gratitude?
Love? Yeah, I get that.
We'll take out what you did
to yourself yesterday,
we're back to the kidneys and the bones.
I'm scheduling the transplant.
Never visit a patient.
I want that baby!
Even if I'm gone,
that's a piece of me, and Lola.
Breathing. Walkin' around town.
Goin' to baseball games.
If there's any more transplant talk
from you, or Lola, or anybody else...
I won't screw it up this time.
I'll take myself out for good.
I'll start treating the Addison's,
which will most likely
destroy what's left of your kidneys...
Fine. Start the treatment.
Hey.
What?
Hank Wiggen peed on me.
What d'you think these
pants are worth on eBay?
I've got some big-boy diapers in my office,
the rep. Hands them out like candy.
Is it that bad?
No! Not if you like the smell of urine...
'Course, why should I trust someone who
lies about what he's doing Friday night?
Question is, what are you
really doing Friday night?
Or more to the point, what could
possibly be better than monster trucks?
Or are we breaking up?
Stacy's coming into town this weekend,
we're having dinner. Just...
catching up.
I definitely had pants here.
Wait a second, is that Stacy the Stripper?
I heard she's playing Atlantic City.
No, Stacy the Constitutional Lawyer.
You thought I couldn't handle this news.
You talk to her a lot?
No. It's been a long time.
If you don't want me to see her...
What is this, eighth grade?
I'm fine.
It's fine if you're upset...
No! It's...
I have no right to be upset.
You two are friends.
You should see her. Say hi for me.
So... you're okay.
I'm not the cancer doctor
who's lying about the cancer dinner.
I'm not the one who's betraying
all those poor little...
bald-headed dying kids.
I'm gonna go get some pants, I stink.
You're treating him for Addison's
and you don't think it's gonna work?
He tried to kill himself.
I know. He's confused.
We can have another baby,
I can make him understand that.
I'm having an abortion. We do the trans...
No.
I can make decisions about my body.
And he can make decisions about his.
He doesn't want your kidney.
So... he'll die?
Probably.
If you keep that appointment,
he'll also probably die.
Keep the baby.
Are you just being polite?
See, my pants are...
Oh, they're all wet.
You can't smell that?
I think she'll abort anyway,
try to force his hand?
No, she's not gonna risk losing him.
That's funny?
No, the monster trucks?
House asking you,
that's... that's funny.
I was the first person he ran into,
he just... asked me.
Yeah, like a date!
Exactly.
Except for the "date" part.
If the patient decides to
go the dialysis route,
we got some product
you should check out.
Hey, Dr. Foreman.
Courtesy of the generous Sharon and
the good folks at Casting Pharmaceuticals.
I was just telling the guys
about the Bermuda conference in April.
Three days of sun and scuba,
and one hour of lecture.
Oh God, do we have to go to the lecture?
So, you're the new Arnie.
Dr. House. It's, uh, good to see you.
Would you get me a coffee?
Black, no sugar.
Okay, so who is it?
Come on, she's sleeping with one of you.
Oh God, please tell me it's you.
She buys lunches! She doesn't...
Don't worry, you're not gay...
you're adventurous!
You think she's gonna prostitute herself?
The three of us are that important to her?
I'm afraid not, no.
The groupies sleep with the roadies
in order to get to Mick.
And... you're Mick?
That was the metaphor I was making, yes.
Why are you here?
Damn, it's you.
It's not Addison's.
New symptom: The inability to smell.
I was just in Hank's room,
and he said it smelled
like the men's room at
Veteran's Stadium. He was right.
We rejected environmental causes
because the wife was healthy.
Well, she's not.
Last six months, she can't smell a thing.
If you think of them as one single patient,
add her symptoms to his...
Cadmium poisoning.
It explains everything. Even why they
had so much trouble getting pregnant.
How could they have gotten
exposed to that much cadmium?
Unless they were eating steel
and batteries for breakfast.
So, where else is cadmium?
Some foods, polluted groundwater,
we should check their home...
I think I know how it happened.
I'm gonna need another urine sample.
- What for...
- Sure, whatever you want.
Why wouldn't you give it to me before
but now it's no problem?
I'm dyin', right?
So you've got nothing to lose this time.
Begs the question...
what were you worried about last time?
The funny thing is, when we tested you
before, we were just looking for steroids.
What should we look for now, Hank?
Hank?
What's the story?
A little weed every now and then
when no one was looking?
I don't believe this. We quit.
You did. If you'd kept going, you wouldn't
have just lost your sense of smell.
No, I quit the hard stuff.
I just needed to relax.
Based on the symptoms,
you're a lot more than a social user.
So you've been lying to me all this time.
I'm sorry.
There must've been cadmium in the soil
where the marijuana was grown.
Some people get bone loss, kidney failure,
some people's testes shrink, and...
some people lose their sense of smell.
We'll start treating it right away.
You should be fine by opening day.
Baseball's in the summer, right?
It didn't hurt the baby, did it?
The cadmium?
If you've been clean,
the baby should be fine.
Okay.
Please. I'll stop everything,
I'll go to meetings every day!
Lola.
Twice a day.
How'd the ballplayer doing?
Much better.
Too bad about his career.
What d'you mean?
Major League Baseball's
collective bargaining
agreement requires medical
reports on all treatment.
Even Hank's history is not
likely to get much leniency.
Why should they care that
he's being treated for Addison's?
You're not treating him for Addison's!
My report says I am.
You're lying on the report?
Everybody does stupid things, it shouldn't
cost them everything they want in life.
No, it shouldn't,
but it usually does.
On the other hand, it means someone
can actually beat the Yankees.
So what about House,
is any way we get him down there?
You really wanna... talk about work?
No. Not at all...
That was amazing!
I'm telling you,
Gravedigger never disappoints.
You ever been married?
Well now, let's not ruin a lovely
night out by getting personal.
I lived with someone for a while.
You gonna finish that?
I'll race you to the car!