This is a really nice room!
Yeah, it sounds thick.
Too bad he's not coming.
Look, I talked to him myself.
He'll be here.
Right.
You're the one who said the song could
use a horn part, so I got the best.
John Henry!
Do you think I'm stupid?
Of course I do, but that's not the point.
He'll be here, okay?
Take a left up ahead.
South Street?
I canceled this gig.
You said you didn't want to
do any sessions for a while.
For a while.
I called her, I un-cancelled it.
But you up to it?
Let's find out.
You lied to me, John Henry's
never gonna show up!
Will you stop?
It's been, like, two hours.
And we will keep waiting.
I mean, you've heard this
guy play and you know
what he does, so can you
just shut up, Tommy?
Oh, my God!
Am I late?
You need to hear it again?
Nope, I get it. Let's try one.
See what we get. Let's do it.
John! You okay? You okay?
I can't breathe, I can't breathe.
Call an ambulance!
Now!
I want in.
John Henry Giles, you a fan of his music?
He's a musician?
That paralysis thing, guy
can't walk for two years
and nobody knows why, that
seems mildly interesting.
Forget his paralysis.
Tell that to the rest of his bowling team.
As far as this hospital is concerned,
this is a simple case of low-bar pneumonia.
Boring.
But that “not walking” thing,
that could turn into something serious!
Marty Hamilton is his
primary physician out in California.
He's dealing with the paralysis.
Know all about it.
Multiple treatments,
multiple surgeries.
Making real progress.
Fixed everything but the legs.
Dr. Hamilton already called
and asked for your team.
And by team, I don't mean you.
Like I always say, there's
no "I" in "team".
There is a "me", though,
if you jumble it up.
Foreman did his residency with Hamilton.
I know. I did accidentally glance
at his resume before I hired him.
He wants someone he can trust.
He must have spoken to
Foreman's parole officer.
Someone who will stick to the pneumonia.
John Henry's on an experimental
protocol for the paralysis.
I respect that.
I'm not going to get in his way.
It's Foreman's case.
It's pneumonia, he can handle it.
Guy's already paralyzed,
how badly can he screw it up?
So, what are his stats?
Staying in the 90s on the nasal canula.
Coughing up much sputa?
Almost none, he seems to be stabilized.
Dr. House, is there
anything back from Micro?
Not yet. You gonna fire me?
You can make up for it by washing my car.
Oh, this is fun.
Let's keep him on the
broad-spectrum antibiotics,
and since he's displaying
septic physiology,
draw blood for adrenal
and thyroid function.
How about the paralysis?
We're sticking to the pneumonia.
Well, you certainly are, boss.
Like a wet tongue sticks to dry ice.
The paralysis has already been
diagnosed by Dr. Hamilton.
It's ALS.
Lou Gehrig's disease.
It's a lovely diagnosis.
They make movies about it.
No tests, no treatment.
It's a disease of exclusion.
Because Hamilton has
excluded everything else.
I haven't.
What else could it be?
Guillain-Barre, which would be reversible.
Excellent.
No, the progression of the
paralysis would be symmetric.
This wasn't.
Transverse myelitis.
Hamilton tested for it.
Negative.
And he was negative for
masses, and AVM, and...
Antibodies could be attacking the nerve.
Multifocal motoneuropathy.
Uncommon, but it fits.
It's also treatable.
Did Hamilton try putting the guy on IVIG?
No, because the MRI showed...
Well, let's do an MRI of our own.
Guys? It's my case.
ALS fits. It even predicts the pneumonia.
The paralysis is progressive.
It's a death sentence.
That doesn't make it wrong.
So, you think the breathing
stuff is connected to my ALS?
It makes sense.
So, it's just gonna get worse, huh?
Well, Dr. Hamilton...
Great guy. Really smart doctor,
but his treatment obviously isn't working.
Do you think I'm gonna die here,
or you think I'm gonna
get to go back home first?
An MRI would give us a better idea...
An MRI? Come on. For pneumonia?
Well, Dr. House thinks
we should test for...
House? Yeah, I heard about him.
Obsessive son-of-a-bitch?
That's him.
So, who do you think is right?
Hamilton or House?
They're both excellent physicians.
Come on.
One of 'em says ALS, the
other one says not ALS.
You gotta pick one, son.
Everything points to ALS.
Then no MRI.
And I want one of them
papers that say I, I
don't want nothin' done
if something go bad.
A DNR?
Mr. Giles, you don't want to rush things...
It's been two years, I ain't rushing.
I wanna sign one.
Now, while my arm still works.
He signed a DNR.
He rhymes with dinner?
Oh. That makes more sense.
You tell him it might not be ALS?
No.
Well, no wonder he signed.
Who wouldn't?
I started him on IV
steroids and ancinthroid.
Great.
If it was my case, I'd be adding
a little IVIG to the mix.
For his pneumonia?
That's my story and I'm sticking to it.
He doesn't want anything done.
No treatment.
DNR means "do not resuscitate",
not "do not treat".
You do nothing, it doesn't
matter which one of us is right.
And hang on to that DNR.
That signature could be worth
a lot of money real soon.
This is Dr. Foreman.
What's Mr. Giles's status?
Okay, increase the steroids
to 100mg every 12 hours,
and, ah, start him on IVIG.
Yeah, I'm sure. One gram per kilo.
My nature isn't what it used to be.
The little man has lost
some bounce in his step.
He needs to crank it up,
have himself some fun this weekend.
He wants the blue pills.
You're talking about your
penis in the third person.
Me and him, two people.
Separate vacations?
That'd be a drag for one of you.
I don't think you need the pills.
I think you have a conflict of medications.
You need to up your insulin to
"chocolate chip ice cream" levels.
Insulin?
Yeah, you remember.
That's the stuff you take for the diabetes
that you forgot to tell the nurse about.
Your hands.
No hair, which means nerve damage.
And your shoes look about
two sizes too small
which means you've lost
sensation in your feet.
And then there's your pants.
My pants tell you I have diabetes?
No, they tell me you're an idiot.
Powdered sugar on the right pant leg.
Based on the two napkins
in your right pocket,
I'm willing to bet it's not
your first donut of the day.
You're giving me the pills?
Sure, why not?
If you've got heart disease from
ignoring the diabetes they'll kill you.
Otherwise, you two have a fun weekend.
O2 stats are dropping.
Breath sounds?
Junky.
Mucus plug?
No, it's our mistake.
He's sludging from the IVIG.
Blood can't get through to his lungs.
Start Heparin. 500ccs, IV push.
He won't last long enough for it to work.
We've got to intubate him, stat.
We can't!
He's DNR.
What?
Someone likes music.
Oh, yeah.
His stats are in the 70s.
How long has he been like this?
10 minutes.
- Well, why aren't you doing?
- The IVIG put him
into respiratory failure.
You put him on the IVIG?
We did this.
So undo it! Chase!
It's too late! We killed him.
Nobody killed him!
He's not dead!
Chase, intubate him!
He's DNR.
What are you doing?
You can't do this!
Bag.
Bag!
He had a bad reaction to
some medicine we gave him.
What did you just do?
He saved his life.
He's stable on the ventilator.
Oxygenating well.
The IVIG made him worse,
which means multifocal
motoneuropathy was a bad diagnosis.
Okay, what's really wrong with him?
What's wrong with you?
Everyone knows what's wrong with me.
What's wrong with him
is much more interesting.
You tubed him and he didn't wanna be tubed!
He has a legal paper saying just that.
To intubate or not to intubate,
that is the big ethical question.
Actually, I was hoping we could avoid it,
maybe just practice some medicine.
There's no question.
It's the patient's decision...
if the patient is competent to make it,
if his thyroid numbers
aren't making him sad.
Oh, my God.
You don't believe that.
His thyroid levels were a little...
It's nothing. Do not defend him.
Why did he sign that DNR?
I didn't talk him into...
No, he signed the DNR 'cause he didn't
want a slow and painful death from ALS.
What was happening to him had
nothing to do with his ALS.
Right! Exactly! It's the
IVIG, you screwed up!
You're not gonna let him die
because you screwed up!
Technically, your case.
You screwed up.
Is that what this is about?
Looking bad in front of your old boss?
You assaulted that man.
Fine. I'll never do it again.
Yes, you will.
All the more reason this
debate is pointless.
His lungs are worse. Any theories?
Oh, I'm sure he just went
to the little boys' room.
Come on, people.
Uh, vasculitis?
Wouldn't likely hit both lungs.
It could be Wegener's granulomatosis.
Dr. House?
Cuddy sent me a stripper again?
Ah, love that woman.
So thoughtful.
Sorry.
There are case reports of Wegener's
hitting both the lungs and the spine.
Well, it's not great, but
it's better than ALS.
At least it's treatable.
It's a restraining order.
You're not to come within 50
feet of John Henry Giles,
and they've asked the DA to file
criminal charges for battery.
Cameron, test the blood for C-anke.
These are criminal charges.
They aren't going to let you
take blood to make more tests.
He has blood left in the
lab, just add on the c-anke.
Foreman's still got you doing bronchioscopic
suctioning for the pneumonia?
Every four hours.
Well, while you're down in
his lungs, grab a biopsy.
We'll need it to confirm Wegener's.
And move the patient to
the second floor ICU.
Why?
It's right about the clinic.
I'm pretty sure it's 50
feet in any direction.
It's nice having a court order saying
you don't have to work clinic duty.
Dr. Cuddy!
Excuse me.
You paged me.
Why the yelling?
His bed is behind that wall.
The plaintiff's.
I can't, you know, come any closer.
It's right over the clinic. Very cute.
Can we get the lecture over
with, because I've got a...
actually, I've got nothing to do.
Take your time.
You need a lawyer?
You don't have a problem with what I did?
When I hired you,
I knew you were insane.
I will continue to try and stop you
from doing
insane things, but once they're done...
Trying to convince an insane person
not to do insane things is,
in itself, insane,
so when I hired you
I also set aside
$50,000 a year for legal expenses.
So far you've come in under budget.
Great.
Any chance you could
help me run some tests?
Dr. Foreman called Dr. Hamilton.
He's flying in from L.A.
You can talk to him.
Dr. Hamilton is flying in as a friend
of John Henry's to pull the plug.
Yeah. I need a lawyer.
Your Honor, on behalf of Gregory House,
we have convened an emergency
session of this court to bring
a motion requesting John Henry
Giles remain on life support.
Mr. House faces criminal charges for
battery against... John Henry Giles.
You beat up a guy in a wheelchair?
Dr. House is alleged to have forced a tube
down Mr. Giles' throat against his will.
A medical tube, saving his life.
Dr. House, please let your
attorney speak for you.
I'm sorry, your Honor.
I was way out of line.
So, your client forced the
patient into this position,
and now he wants a court order to
force the patient to stay that way.
Without the tube, there's a high
likelihood that Mr. Giles will die.
Well, I assume the patient
knows that, he had a DNR.
That's why your client is
facing criminal charges, right?
Exactly.
And Mr. Giles' death will violate
my client's Sixth Amendment right.
His right to face his accuser.
That's clever, huh?
Your Honor, in Commonwealth
of Pennsylvania v. Hozelton,
the 3rd district ruled
that a defendant may not
use that status to rule
against a felony charge.
Why are you doing this?
It's not going to keep you out of jail.
No.
Even if you win, the restraining order
and battery charge stay in place.
What have you gained?
Time.
To diagnose him?
You can't get near him!
I don't want to get near him.
You know how some doctors have the.
Messiah complex,
they need to save the world?
You've got the Rubik's complex,
you need to solve the puzzle.
Are you done, or do you have
more references to 1980s fads?
I'm trying to listen to this.
That DNR may not be valid.
The patient was suffering from depression
brought on from a thyroid imbalance.
The DNR order was witnessed by Dr.
House's own staff, a Dr. Foreman.
My staff are idiots.
I'm sure you know what
it's like, your Honor.
Sit down!
The validity of the DNR
is a question of fact.
Dr. House should have the opportunity
to make his argument at a full trial.
And this poor guy has gotta stay on life
support until we can schedule a trial.
Your Honor...
Dr. House, I will hold you in
contempt if you don't sit down.
I have a medical issue.
If it pertains to this case
your attorney should...
It doesn't.
Do you have any history of
heart disease in your family?
Your Honor!
Your fingers. They show signs of clubbing,
which indicate a health problem.
Remember Bart Giamotti?
Same thing, just dropped dead one day.
Please see your doctor.
He's admitted this isn't relevant.
Can we please get back to the motion?
Of course, I'm sorry.
Your Honor, a person's right to control
the treatment of their own body
is fundamental to understanding
this case. A long line of...
Congratulations, impressive legal argument.
I watched Matlock last night.
Oh, say no more. I didn't notice any
clubbing on the judge's fingers.
Neither did I.
So, the family history thing...
Every family has some
history of heart disease.
And mental illness.
Biopsy only shows inflammation.
Start him on Cytoxan.
You're diagnosis Wegener's based
on a little inflammation?
Well, unfortunately I think we've
exhausted all the tests we can do
in the capacity as the doctors he
doesn't want doing tests on him.
But you don't...
We'll know I'm right if he starts walking.
You can't do any more tests,
but you want me to treat him?
The medicine's in the pharmacy,
patient's immobilized in the ICU.
Sounds like a simple geography problem.
Are you asking us to jeopardize our
medical licenses for this treatment?
Can I help you?
Uh, I'm Dr. House, I'm...
Gregg, right?
I'm Marty Hamilton,
John Henry's doctor.
We should talk.
I'd appreciate any list of
medications, anything like that.
I've started him on Cytoxan.
For Wegener's, right?
Look, Gregg.
I checked you out, you know?
I know you're a good doctor.
You have to appreciate that
I'm a good doctor, too.
Why?
Wegener's is one of the
first things I looked for.
The biopsy and the blood tests
were negative, just like yours.
There's an error rate, Marty.
And there's a time to let go.
Look, I'm gonna take him off the
ventilator, and John Henry's gonna die.
He's accepted that.
Dr. Hamilton.
Hey! How you doing?
Listen, Dr. Hamilton, I'm sorry.
I should have never put
your patient on IVIG.
It's not your fault, Eric.
No, it's mine. Eric.
That's not what I said.
Everyone asks about you back in L.A.
How's the old place doing?
Oh, this is wonderful.
But before you guys break out the oil,
I should point out you can't pull the plug;
I have a court order.
You used to, but...
I have the right to face my accuser.
Judge said so.
Not if no one's accusing you.
All the charges have been dropped.
He doesn't have to die.
It's not Wegener's.
If it's Wegener's, his lungs
won't be able to handle it.
As soon as they pull that plug he'll die.
That's why they call it pulling the plug.
I'm gonna miss you.
He's still breathing!
His O2 stats are holding.
He's holding his own.
He's still breathing.
It's not Wegener's.
Wrong again.
He's stable, but one of his
arms is now paralyzed.
The real question is,
why is he still alive?
Do you think he's just being stubborn?
He's alive because you were wrong.
It's not Wegener's.
Yeah, seem to be doing that a lot, lately.
People keep living because of my mistakes.
Progression of the paralysis pretty
much confirms Hamilton was right.
It's ALS.
Assuming this is a progression
of his paralysis.
He can't move his arm.
Yes, his arm is paralyzed.
Yes, his legs are paralyzed.
Why is everyone so gung-ho to
connect those two conditions?
You could think I'm wrong,
but that's no reason to stop thinking.
How about this one?
He's not our patient.
Nope, not good enough.
He could have suffered a
stroke when he was intubated.
Well, blood clots are common
in paralysis patients.
The inactivity causes...
Not interested in why.
Let's get an MR-angiogram
for an embolic stroke.
He doesn't want you treating him!
They dropped the court order.
Yeah, and that girl dropped
the charges against Kobe.
Doesn't mean that he should call her
and see if she's free to get a sundae.
Good point, but I can go
within 50 feet of him now.
If you need anything, page me. Any time.
Okay.
Get outta here.
Sure. That makes sense.
You hate me for saving your life.
In fairness to your side,
you were also dying because of me, so...
You know I didn't wanna be saved.
That's what's interesting.
Your thyroid was low, but not
low enough to cause depression.
So, you came here to tell
me that even if I can't walk
I can still hear the birds sing?
Enjoy the rainbow, and feeling
the sun shine on my face?
Those things are fun.
Okay, life sucks.
Your life sucks more than most.
It's not as bad as some,
which is depressing all by itself.
But do me a favor.
Just let me find out what's wrong with you.
And if you still want to kill yourself,
I'll give you a hand.
That sound fair?
Yeah, sure.
I'll stick around to
indulge your obsession.
It's over. I lost my air.
The session the other
night, with those kids?
That was a test to see
if I could still play.
I can't.
And that's all you are?
A musician?
I got one thing, same as you.
Really?
Apparently, you know me
better than I know you.
I know that limp.
I know the empty ring finger.
And that obsessive nature of yours,
that's a big secret.
You don't risk jail and your career
just to save somebody who doesn't
want to be saved unless you got
something, anything, one thing.
The reason normal people got wives
and kids and hobbies, whatever.
That's because they don't
got that one thing that
hits them that hard and that true.
I got music, you got this.
The thing you think about all the time,
the thing that keeps you south of normal.
Yeah, makes us great, makes us the best.
All we miss out on is everything else.
No woman waiting at home
after work with the drink and the kiss,
that ain't gonna happen for us.
That's why God made microwaves.
Yeah, but when it's over, it's over.
Yeah.
What are you doing?
It's not over for me.
Either you're gonna call the
cops again, or we're doing this.
If you wanna die, you can do it just
as easily inside an MRI machine.
So, I go back to L.A. I'm going the
Dana lectures again this year.
Wow. That's quite an honor.
It's all political.
Don't be modest, you've earned it.
I got lucky on a couple
studies I was doing.
It all sells tickets.
You remember last year's
lectures, don't you?
I remember the cigar bar afterwards.
The only reason to attend
the thing: Cigars and pool.
You enjoy working with Dr. House?
Not the word I'd use.
We work too hard not to
enjoy ourselves, right?
You seeing anybody?
Kinda sorta.
Serious?
I don't know. Could be.
You think she would enjoy L.A.?
Hamilton offered me a job.
You gonna take it?
I haven't decided.
You already have the most
prestigious fellowship.
It's a partnership.
Three times the money, car allowance,
moving expense, pension plan,
the chance to work for a guy who gives
a crap what other people think.
So, why didn't you just tell him yes?
I made a commitment here.
Right.
House would let you out
of it in a heartbeat.
Or he wouldn't, just to jerk me around.
Would you guys have taken the job?
Don't need the money.
I'm not like you.
I don't hate House.
You guys really don't have a problem
with him, with what he did?
He knows we disagree with his choice.
Choice?
Chase, it's not apples and
oranges, its right and wrong.
And he does it like he doesn't care!
He assaults the guy and
moves on to the next
differential diagnosis
like it's nothing...
What do you want from him?
More hand-wringing, more torment?
You want him to
cry himself to sleep at night?
Yeah! Yeah, I want some clue
that he knows it's a big deal.
That it scares him, that it matters.
Whoa, what's that?
It was a stroke!
Well done, Cameron.
House called it.
The arm and legs are unrelated.
You make enough calls,
one of them is bound to be right.
Yeah, he's
just a lucky, lucky guy.
Listen, listen, I just think it wouldn't
hurt him to learn a little humility.
So, what's the verdict?
Embolus.
The arm problem's caused by a clot.
There's a good chance we can
still bust the clot with TPA.
Do it. See
what happens to his arm.
We found a blood clot in your brain.
We'd like to start you on heparin,
it's a blood thinner.
What are the side effects?
Well, your lungs are kind of
chewed up from the pneumonia.
Good chance there'll be an infusion.
Bleeding?
Into his lungs.
It's our best chance to give
you back the use of your arm.
I don't need my arm without my air.
The damage would likely be minimal.
No.
It's his call.
Or we could do an embolectomy.
Basically, we'd go in
and pull the clot out.
He's saying no to drugs and you're
recommending brain surgery?
Bypasses risk to the lungs.
It'll either help your arm, or...
Or it'll kill me.
From your point of view,
it's a win-win.
Okay.
We'll set up the procedure for today.
We're in your carotid artery.
This is going to take us all
the way up into your brain.
You all right?
Yes.
The sludge is blocking the blood
flow to the part of
the brain that controls your arm.
All done.
You still okay?
I think so.
I don't know, I guess...
It's just with Dr. Hamilton here,
I notice a difference in styles.
His style involves humility.
Another difference in our styles:
I don't care much for apologies.
You can go.
I didn't know you were standing
there when I said that, okay?
It was completely rude.
Do you mean genuine humility?
You know, with all the self-doubt
and the self-questioning,
or Hamilton's polite, patronizing
"Aw, shucks" humility?
You're both excellent doctors.
Thank you.
And humility is an important quality.
Especially if you're wrong a lot.
You've been wrong every step of the way.
Of course, when you're right, self-doubt
doesn't help anybody, does it?
We gotta go.
Congratulations, Gregg.
Congratulations...
Why, Marty?
John woke up, he can use his arm.
Thank you.
Now look, I know we've had our differences,
but I think when a person does something
well it ought to be recognized.
The phone works.
Next time you want to make me feel
all warm and fuzzy, leave a message.
Don't get me wrong,
I'm overcome with joy.
Doc?
Yeah?
What?
You just touched my leg.
What, you gonna charge
me with assault again?
No, I felt it.
He now has feeling all the way up to calf.
This is the way medicine evolved.
Patients sometimes get better.
You have no idea why, but unless you
give a reason they won't pay you.
Anybody notice if there's a full moon?
You're saying he just
spontaneously got better?
No, I'm saying let's rule out the
lunar god and go from there.
Something he's on is working.
The enzyme replacement protocol
is working, reversing the ALS.
The timing doesn't suspicious to you?
Do you think Dr.
House will see it that way?
Figure it's his medication doing the job?
I'm sure he will.
It's one of ours.
How do we figure out which
drug is doing the trick?
Easy. We stop all of them.
One of those drugs is helping him.
And the rest?
Steroids, antibiotics,
anti-inflammatories,
they're toxic if we leave
him on all of them.
He'll walk again.
Yeah, to his own funeral.
But if we stop
everything, he'll get worse.
True. And then we'll add our
medications back, one at a time.
If he gets better, then
we'll have our answer.
And if he doesn't get better?
Then we're in trouble.
Not as much as he is.
I suppose that was your point.
I assume you want me to convince
Hamilton to stop his treatments, too?
Don't care.
You know at least five of the
medications are part of his protocol?
If his stuff was helping the guy would
be playing tennis months ago.
It's our round of treatment that's helping.
Right. So that's what you'll stop.
So your philosophy is,
"If they don't want treatment,
they get it shoved down their throat,
but if it might cure their paralysis,
whoa, better slow down."
Yeah.
My old philosophy used to
be "Live and let live,"
but I'm taking this needlepoint class and
they gave us these really big pillows.
What's your philosophy
on employee relations?
That's a very tiny pillow.
Great. Sounds like you
know what you're doing.
Gregg. Can I have a word?
Can it wait for the commercial, Marty?
Say "hi" to my friend, Jimmy.
Pleasure.
Your diagnostic trial...
Seriously, commercial's
in about five minutes.
It's a dangerous game.
Only if we're watching in the bathtub.
I need to know exactly what
medications you were giving John Henry.
Forget it.
And if Foreman tells you what
John Henry used to be on...
You're gonna fire him?
Nope. Make him live out every
day of his two-year contract.
Foreman asked to leave?
Not yet.
But how do you know I made him an...
You're a polite twit,
but you're not an idiot.
I need to know what medications
you've taken him off of.
Wait a second.
You're not an idiot.
You need to know what medications
I've stopped, because...
He's getting worse.
Right now you still work for me.
Come on!
No feeling, no wiggling.
The bad news is, John Henry's
back where he started.
The good news is, Hamilton looks bad.
Yeah, it's not whether you win or lose,
it's whether the other guy loses.
What was the first thing we put him on?
Steroids, for the pneumonia.
Well, put him back on them.
Give them 24 hours, see what happens.
His lungs aren't great.
It might cause another
respiratory collapse.
Sure hope not.
I didn't much like that lawyer.
And get an MRI.
He already got one. And an MRA.
Well, obviously something is different now.
Do it again.
Chase, take care of the scan.
Cameron, put him on the steroids.
We should probably talk, huh?
Thin cuts.
What levels?
T9 through the quarter-equinus,
same as the last time.
You really think House would let
Foreman out of his contract?
He has to.
If he doesn't, he's telling
Foreman he needs him.
House can't handle that.
Oh, my God!
I checked him out.
He's a great doctor.
You think he's better than I am.
This about your ego?
Answer the question.
It's not going to change
how I think about myself.
Might affect my opinion of you,
but that
shouldn't affect your opinion of yourself.
Now I'm getting confused.
If you think he's a better doctor than
I am, then you should take the job.
Otherwise, you should get
him to buy you two or
three more nostalgic lunches
and politely decline.
It's that simple?
I should just ignore the mockery and abuse?
Oh, how do I abuse you?
How do you not?
If I make a mistake...
I hold you accountable, so what?
Dr. Hamilton forgives.
He's capable of moving on.
That is not what he does!
I screwed up his case, he told me...
He never said you were forgiven.
I was there, he said it wasn't your fault.
So?
So, it was.
You took a chance,
you did something great.
You were wrong,
but it was still great.
You should feel great that it was great.
You should feel
like crap that it was wrong.
That's the difference between him and me.
He thinks you do your job,
and what will be, will be.
I think that what I do
and what you do matters.
He sleeps better at night.
He shouldn't.
Arteriovenous malformation.
Intradural, compressing his spine.
Causing his paralysis.
How could Hamilton have missed an AVM?
Well, we missed it, too.
'Cause it wasn't there before.
You saying it just grew overnight?
No. It was on the spine,
it wasn't on the MRI.
Same anatomic location.
It's not there.
Well, what is there?
Nothing.
Or something that looks like nothing.
Background noise, static.
Scar tissue? Inflammation?
If it's inflammation, the steroids
would have shrunk it down.
Revealing the AVM,
which has always been
there, hiding behind its
own swelling. We remove
that, he'll walk again.
Dr. House!
Cora's meeting me outside with a limo.
I'm being discharged.
Fifty bucks says I can
beat you to the curb.
Thanks for sticking with the case.
I can't do anything else.
You're much more easily
amused when you can walk.
How bizarre.
I'm guessing you
weren't exactly Mr. Sunshine
even before your leg got messed up.
I want you to have this.
Wow.
You can sell it if you want to,
just promise me you won't play it.
How many of those pills you taking?
I'm in pain.
Yeah.
Aren't we all?
So, where do you buy these things,
do they have cane stores?
Oh, don't worry about it.
You'll be jogging before
you need a second one.
See you tomorrow, Eric.