Will it be much longer?
We'll call you when we're ready.
I've been waiting almost an hour.
I'm sorry.
So she's really coming back?
Who's coming back?
You don't know her.
You give her a raise?
Increase her benefits?
Don't have TiVo on this thing,
can't rewind. Shut up.
You lower her hours?
You don't even know her.
Who is this guy?
He's a patient.
He's examining me.
He's got to go back to work
as soon as I'm done with the examination.
Guess I do, too.
It's got to be something.
I mean, she didn't come back
because she likes you.
Wait a minute!
She did come back
because she likes you!
You dog! You slept with her!
Keep talking. I'll finish your exam
with a prostate check.
I've agreed to take her on one date.
What?
So, you into this girl?
Yes.
No! She's not giving me any choice.
Wait... she's making you do her?
Date her.
Young ingenue doctor
falling in love with gruff, older mentor.
Her sweet gentle nature
bringing him to a closer,
fuller understanding
of his wounded heart.
Do her, or you're gay.
For God's sake.
- Sitting in a tree, K-i-s-s-i-n-g.
- Grow up. And learn to harmonize.
- Damn it!
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Who the hell walks around
with an open urine sample?
I'm sorry, I didn't,
uh, I didn't...
You think that was
a bit of an overreaction?
Well, he peed on me.
I'm not into that.
It's apple juice.
Now go find that man and apologize.
One more patient complaint
and you're looking at a suspension.
I forgive you for ruining my jacket.
Look, you seem like
a regular kind of guy,
not the type to get another regular
guy into trouble, am I right?
Twenty bucks cash if you'll stop crying.
Forgive me, yell at me, just give
me something I can work with, okay?
Game's over. You two make nice?
Get a wheelchair, and
get this guy into the ER.
- What happened?
- Right pupil's blown.
Holy... you gave the guy a stroke?
So the bear wipes himself with the rabbit.
Lame.
Hey!
Yo!
What are you doing here?
I work here.
What, here in this office?
House practically
begged me to come back.
Please tell me
you took him to the cleaners?
Same lousy salary.
Then why'd you do it?
'Cause this is the happiest place on Earth.
21-year-old male, comes in
with grinding of the teeth.
And House gives him a stroke,
totally blows out his pupil.
You scared a guy into stroking out?
Does that surprise anyone here?
Blown pupils usually means
brain stem edema.
Sure, but since he's not dead or in a coma,
I'm going with stroke to the optic nerve.
CT scan shows two things.
Ischemia. Death of brain tissue.
Means there's been some damage,
hopefully not permanent.
And?
That's it. There's nothing there to tell us
what the underlying cause is.
We've got to do an MRI.
You're looking at the
wrong part of the scan.
I'm looking at the brain,
what else is there?
The jaw.
The jaw tells us why he stroked?
No, the jaw tells us
why we can't do an MRI.
Unless we want his jawbone
flying across the room.
Metal plate.
He's had major reconstruction
and there's no way we're removing it,
so we're forced to be clever.
Angiogram to rule out vascultis,
EMG for peripheral neuropathy,
tox screen to eliminate drugs,
an echo to rule out cardiac emboli.
Dr. Cameron.
I'd appreciate you keeping the terms
of your new contract to yourself.
Don't want everyone
clamoring for the same perks.
What perks?
Nothing you'd be interested in.
So it's not money, then?
Office space,
insurance, parking...
anything he could offer
you, we'd be interested in.
He agreed to go on a date with me.
A date? Date, dinner and a movie,
naked and sweaty date?
He only committed to the first two.
He's so, he's so old!
And you're so young.
It's a big mistake.
It's my boss. I'm allowed
to sexually harass my boss.
I'll arrange for the EMG,
you want to set up the angiogram,
and you get the blood samples,
patient history, patient consent?
Like watching an accident
about to happen.
Morning! Harvey, I'm Dr. Foreman.
I'm here to discuss your case.
I'm Annette, I'm Harvey's friend.
Nice to meet you.
I need your next of kin, you didn't
fill that out on your intake form.
Harvey's parents are dead.
They died two years ago in a car crash.
I see. So, Harvey,
you have any siblings?
No, and no grandparents
or uncles or aunts.
Annette, I don't want to
have to ask you to leave.
I want her to stay.
Well, she can stay.
You do the talking.
Why'd you come
to the clinic this morning?
About six months ago,
I started grinding my...
you know, in your mouth,
you get, you chew with them...
Teeth.
Harvey's experiencing
a little nominal aphasia,
you know, when you can't
remember nouns.
Yeah, I think I know
what nominal aphasia is.
Have you had any treatment
for the teeth grinding?
I went to a, you know, they do that
thing with sharp, uh, pointy things.
Needles?
Someone took your blood.
No, they make you breathe.
Pulmonologist.
No, she had this, uh,
electrical machine...
He saw an acupuncturist.
Do you know what the acupuncturist did?
She diagnosed Liver Qi stagnation
and sent Harvey to a Shen balancer.
He referred him to a homeopathic
doctor who sent him to chiropractor.
Naturally.
Well, the chiropractor
thought it might be food
sensitivity and sent
Harvey to a naturopath.
The naturopath sent me back to the...
Back to the acupuncturist.
Yes.
Okay. Well, we'll need to see the records
from all of those practitioners.
Thanks.
Everything set for the angiogram?
Cameron's got the EMG first.
Who's that?
Harvey's guru.
That's what she called herself?
That's what she acted like.
Hi. I'm having vaginal pain.
Pleasure to meet you.
My OB/GYN died recently.
He's a nice man. Warm hands.
Not anymore. So,
does it hurt when you tinkle?
Yeah, it's when it's worse.
You have some vaginal tearing.
No sign of brusing, no indication
of trauma, forced entry...
Ramona. You naughty girl.
You've either got yourself
an 18-year-old boyfriend
or an 80-year-old with
some little blue pills.
Myron thought
he'd just try them out!
Lucky you.
I guess.
You prefer it
if Myron was a little droopier?
Maybe a little. We used to hold hands,
or read together, or watch Jeopardy!
I haven't seen Jeopardy!
In almost a month!
Have you talked to him about this?
You try talking a 73-year-old out of sex.
With all these male enhancements
the pressure to put out's incredible.
It's worse than high school.
He doesn't get
what he wants from me,
he'll get it from Connie
in the corner condo.
She's dying her hair red!
Major league slut.
Here's a prescription for
vaginal estrogen suppositories.
It'll help with the lubrication.
Thank you.
Maybe you could give
Myron a prescription.
Something weaker
than he's got now?
Tell him it's better
for his heart, he'd buy that.
You can't tell him the truth,
so you want me to lie to him?
Would you?
Close your legs.
Nerves stimulate muscles to move
by creating a small electrical current.
The machine will measure that.
And I will insert this needle into
various muscles and ask you to flex.
Sometimes it can be painful.
Let me know, and I can pull back...
No. I mean, it's okay.
Okay. Put your arm out to the side.
You all right?
I'm good.
You don't have to stop.
Raise your arm up over your head.
The EMG was clean.
Well, based on this history
it's either toxic herbs from
the homeopath, spinal damage
from the chiropractor,
infection from the needle
that the acupuncturist
accidentally let sit in eye of
newt, or the Shen balancer.
What the hell is a "shen"
and how come it's lopsided?
The only abnormal test result
we found was on the echo report.
Mitral valve prolapse.
Hang up a shingle and condemn the
narrowness and greed of Western medicine,
you'd make a damn fine living.
Clot's formed on a faulty valve,
gets sent to the brain, voila! Stroke.
Of course, no harm, no foul.
It's just taking a few bucks
from superstitious idiots, right?
Could also be an aneurysm due to trauma.
Trauma? From what,
the chiropractic treatments?
It's bacterial endocarditis,
an infected valve.
We should do blood cultures.
Except the six months that
he had with these charlatans
might have been better
spent going to someone who
looks at things that
exist in the real world.
But that's just me
being all narrow again.
I noticed a small bruit when
I listened to Harvey's left carotid.
You could hear that if you had
an aneurysm from trauma.
Aneurysm would have
shown on the angiogram.
No, not necessarily.
Quite a dilemma.
Oh, great pool hall oracle,
grant me guidance.
Do we go with Foreman's theory,
which is at least marginally
supported by medical test
results, or Chase's theory,
which is completely
unsupported by medical evidence.
What to do...
The guy obviously broke
his jaw somehow.
Who knows what other
trauma he's suffered?
We should do the angiogram again.
And all signs point to...
Sorry, Chase.
The gods have spoken.
Start Harvey on blood thinners
and antibiotics.
Wow. Yeah, I get it. House is adorable.
I just want to hold him and never let go.
Oh, my God! What the hell are you doing?
You're choking him!
Foreman, stop. Let her go.
She was trying to kill him!
No. No, she wasn't.
His vitals seem okay.
Please. Please don't hurt her.
What the hell is going on in here?
She's... she's a dominatrix.
Right, Annette?
The patient asked
you to strangle him?
Harvey is an asphyxiaphyliac.
He likes to be strangled or smothered.
That's just sick.
Well, that's an intriguing legal opinion.
Geez, what kind of a lawyer is he?
You want a legal opinion?
Call the cops.
I was careful. I watched the monitors,
made sure his O2 stats were over 90.
I would never hurt him.
Then what was the point?
Harvey was upset.
He needed to calm down.
To feel in control
by being controlled.
He pays you for this?
In return, he does
my taxes and cleans my house.
We're not done here,
we have to talk!
Call the cops, bar her from the hospital,
force her to pierce your nipples...
not really medical decisions.
It was a long time ago.
I was seeing this woman.
A banker, and turns out
she liked to be burned.
You actually dated someone
who likes to get burned?
Yeah, why would you want to
be in a relationship with
someone that's so obviously
only going to lead to pain?
Shut up.
It was a weird scene.
I observed...
Chase. Did you know about this woman?
What she does?
I met her at some parties, yeah.
I wouldn't have tortured you
if I knew you liked it.
Well, here's a phrase to remember:
"Hey, this guy might have been pounded
on the head one too many times!"
I said I thought it was
a trauma induced aneurysm.
Yeah, could have carried a tad more weight
if you'd mentioned the "liking pain" thing.
You're on my naughty list.
Sorry, no leather
stethoscope this Christmas.
I'm not into...
I assume you never started
him on antibiotics or blood
thinners before Mistress
Ilsa's rude interruption.
It was probably a good thing.
Start him on antibiotics
and blood thinners.
You still think Chase is wrong?
No, he's probably right.
Then we should schedule him
for vascular surgery.
Go into the carotids,
find the aneurysm, repair it.
If we put him on blood thinners,
he might bleed out.
But if Foreman's right about it
being bacterial endocarditis, and we...
I think Chase is right.
Okay, if Foreman used to be right
about it being blood clots,
and we take the surgery route,
then we'll probably kill the guy.
So, start him on blood
thinners, and if he has
another stroke, then we'll
schedule the surgery.
Yeah?
You Dr. House?
I have a feeling
I'm going to regret this, but yes.
Ramona said I should
come to you for my refill.
With, for the beginning to droop?
She said you'd probably
want to talk to me first.
She lied.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Always happy to
make people happy. Goodbye.
I... I don't know
how much more of this I can take.
How much more of what?
Sex.
You don't want more sex?
My golf swing is all messed up.
Hey, here's a radical thought.
Talk to her.
The truth?
Sounds crazy when you put it like that.
Oh, Ramona's got a big appetite.
If I don't perform,
I don't want to lose her.
You got a pharmacy around here?
In the hospital? Could be.
Let's see if we can find it.
Got any blue pills?
You looking for ED medication?
Well, that's one example
of a blue pill. Name six others.
There's a brand of acetaminophen out...
Perfect. Fill her up.
Dr. House.
Little busy here.
I heard about Dr. Cameron's conditions
for coming back to work.
It's purely business.
I'll make sure you get the recipt.
Well, I think it's a good thing.
What happened in your
last relationship, it's
no reason to wall yourself
from people forever.
5 years of self-pity is probably enough.
Wow. Well, you've certainly
given me a lot to think about.
If only I was as open as you.
Well...
Actually, it was your blouse
I was talking about.
Bear in mind Cameron's probably
the only female that can tolerate you.
Wear the sky-blue shirt.
It almost makes you look nice.
They said she couldn't
come back into the hospital.
They won't let me see her.
Harvey, you're lucky
she wasn't arrested.
What were you thinking,
doing that at a hospital?
Squeeze my fingers?
I was scared.
I need you to squeeze with both hands.
I am.
Weakness in his right arm and hand.
Harvey's having mini-strokes. The blood
thinners aren't making a difference.
Stop the treatment.
Sorry, we tried your way,
you could not have been wronger.
I said Chase was probably right.
Oh yeah, we've all got
perfect 20-20 hindsight.
Get a hold of Main in vascular, see if his
surgical dance card is free for tomorrow.
About tomorrow night.
You couldn't keep your mouth shut.
I didn't see any reason to.
Where are we going? I want to
make sure I dress appropriately.
That would be army boots and t-shirt.
It's the county paintball tourney.
First prize is fifty bucks. I'll split
it with you if you hold your end up.
I'm not sure if that was the deal.
Relax. I made a reservation
at Cafe Spiletto.
Regarding wardrobe:
Are you too young to
remember spandex?
I'll figure something out.
The surgery will repair
the damaged blood vessels
in your neck and your
strokes will stop.
All this is because of the strangulation?
More like strangulations.
My parents were right.
I'm a loser.
I don't know what to do.
Harvey, calm down.
I need to talk to Annette.
You can do this on your own.
Surgery's the only...
She hates me. I've been calling,
I've been calling and she's not picking up.
Harvey, you don't need...
I can't, I can't.
Harvey, you will do what I say.
I don't want surgery!
Sign the consent. Sign it!
I can't do anything.
No surgery! No surgery!
No surgery!
We could give him anti-depressants,
see if he changes his mind.
I already did.
Mashed them up in his applesauce,
it'll lighten him up soon enough.
Someone should just
tell him to do it. Way faster.
Except that's forgery.
Also illegal.
- And I already tried.
- Not you.
Where's a good dominatrix
when you need one?
Annette's barred from the hospital.
If you get caught, Cuddy's got a hairbrush.
And believe me, she knows how to use it.
They let you come back.
Not because you deserve it.
You've been bad.
You will have the surgery,
do you understand?
Do not laugh at me.
You will respect...
Where do you get off
telling me what to do?
Get out of my way,
you back-faced witch.
Is that part
of their deal, or...
This isn't like him.
Something's wrong.
Get out!
Get out, get out!
Emotional swings, he's having
another stroke. Harvey!
He's crashing.
Can we get a cart in here?
So, what's that, two strokes
you've scared this guy into?
Yeah. It's making me question
my view of myself as a people person.
Now you want to do surgery
on him without his consent.
The kid's in a coma,
he needs the surgery!
He said no. We can't do it.
Emergent situation,
invoke heroic measures.
You need a court order.
Great, where do I get me one of them?
Do I need to lawyer up?
I'll need to show the judge
an affidavit from next of kin.
Well, they might have a problem signing
anything seeing as how they're dead.
He'll want proof.
Like what, dad's hand?
I don't even know where they're buried.
Bring me a published obit or
a death certificate and we'll run with it.
I don't want you to mess up your clothes.
His parents were accountants,
maybe there's an obit in the trade papers.
They guy lives in Market Town.
I don't know if he grew up
there, but we could check
the local funeral home.
Great, and when your
searches turn up nothing
you should try to find
out where they live.
He said they were dead.
Accountants,
they're usually pretty good with money,
so how come he lives
in a slum like Market Town?
Maybe they were bad accountants.
Two bad accountants from the Pacific Rim?
The odds are astronomical.
Maybe Harvey burned through their money.
Or maybe they cut him off when
they found out about his proclivities.
That'd be my bet. Go to his apartments.
See if you can find his folks.
Number, address, something.
Hey, can I talk to you?
Sure.
Look, Cameron's a friend.
This whole dating thing...
Time's up. Thanks for playing.
Hey, I've been on the scene
more than you recently.
Way ahead of you.
I've got a case of malt
liquor stashed in the trunk,
Mr. Marvin Gaye on the CD,
we are gonna get all the way down.
Now move.
Come on, you're not into her.
Most guys who aren't interested in
a woman try to sugarcoat it, be nice.
Oh, you know me too well.
That's what I'm saying.
I think you should go with
your instincts here. Be a jerk.
I'm missing my soap for this?
Women love to be right.
You've got to leave them feeling superior.
Like they've dodged a bullet.
If you're nice, she'll blame herself...
And fall for me even more.
The Love Doctor has made
an art of breaking up with women.
'Cause you're convinced
that the loss of you would be
too devastating for
any woman to handle.
Yeah, I'm the one with
the serious ego problem here.
I'm just saying:
Some relationships aren't meant to happen.
Harvey's school registration.
Permanent home address?
Emergency contacts?
Annette Raines.
Mistress Annette.
You have to extort
a date out of House.
You think that's a bad sign?
Cameron?
High school yearbook.
Think this might
give us a clue, Sherlock?
House isn't going to
hand you anything.
You want him,
you've gotta take him.
Jump him.
Harvey. H-a-r-v-e-y.
I'm sorry to have bothered you.
Thank you. Okay.
Yes, Harvey Park.
Great, we've been looking for you!
I'm calling from
the Princeton-Plainsboro Teaching Hospital.
Harvey's here, and it's rather...
He hung up.
You tell him why you were calling?
I didn't get a chance.
Call back.
I'll do it.
Let the master show you how it's done.
Mr. Park? This is Dr.
House calling from.
Princeton-Plainsboro Teaching
Hospital in New Jersey.
Your son Harvey is dead.
We need you to identify the body.
Yes, I'm sorry, it's the law.
Okay.
There's a real art to
delivering bad news.
They're gonna show up at the morgue.
Be sure to let me know
when Cuddy starts screaming.
You lied to them!
He told us our son was dead.
It's only a white lie.
Technically, all I did was
call them a little early.
Trust me, he'll be dead real soon.
Actually, I saved you
some rush hour traffic.
I'm calling our lawyer.
Fine. Just as soon as
you sign this surgery consent.
I have a pen.
Marilyn Park
from Oc Learner. Yes, I'll hold.
Harvey's your son.
I'm sure you still care about him.
He humiliated us.
Everybody we know
knows about his perversion.
But you don't get off on embarrassment
the way your son does.
I guess it skips a generation.
How much money would it take
to compensate you...
Yeah, you guys can haggle in a minute.
But here's the thing.
Humiliation comes in
all kinds of packages.
People finding out that your son's a perv,
that's pretty high up there.
People finding out
that you'd rather let your son die
than sign a piece of paper.
Where's that rank?
And trust me, if I have to paste
up a sign in every nail salon
and dumpling shop in Pennsylvania,
I'll make sure they know.
Your son will be in surgery
first thing in the morning.
Dumplings, that was a cheap shot.
Hi. Are you, can we talk?
Gee, I wonder
what this is going to be about.
I just want to make sure
no one gets hurt.
I will be fine. Everybody's acting like
I'm going out with Jack the Ripper.
Oh, it's not you
I'm worried about.
It's been a long time since
he opened up to someone, and I...
you better be absolutely sure
you want this because...
if he opens up again and gets hurt,
I don't think
there's going to be a next time.
You're worried
I'm going to break his heart?
The wide side's too short.
You're gonna look like Lou Costello.
This is a mistake.
I don't know how to have
casual conversation.
You think you're
talking about one thing,
and either you are and
it's incredibly boring,
or you're not because it's subtext
and you need a decoder ring.
Open doors for her,
help her with her chair...
I have been on a date.
Not since disco died.
Comment on her shoes, her earrings,
and then move on to D.H.A.
Her dreams, hopes and aspirations.
Trust me. Panty-peeler.
Oh, and if you need condoms,
I've got some.
Did your wife give them to you?
Drug rep. They've got
antibiotics built in, somehow.
I should cancel.
I've got a patient in
surgery tomorrow morning.
And if you were a surgeon,
that would actually matter.
That's a good idea, settle your nerves.
Get me a beer, too.
No beer.
You're gonna eat before dinner?
This is pretty lame, right?
I think she likes lame.
It's beautiful.
And you look very handsome.
Thank you.
I've always loved this restaurant.
Yeah. It's changed a lot
since the last time I was here.
It used to be a strip joint.
Nice earrings.
My mom's. Thank you.
Nice shoes. Comfortable?
I'm not expecting you
to be someone you're not.
We're in a restaurant,
we're dressed up, we're eating.
If not small talk,
what is there?
According to Freud,
and I'm paraphrasing,
instinct of love toward an object
demands a mastery to obtain it,
and if a person feels they can't control
the object or feel threatened by it,
they act negatively toward it.
Like an eighth-grade boy
punching a girl.
I treat you like garbage,
so I must really like you.
Given your Freudian theory, what does
it mean if I start being nice to you?
That you're getting in touch
with your feelings.
So there's absolutely nothing I can do
to make you think that I don't like you.
Sorry, no.
I have one evening
with you, one chance,
and I don't want to
waste it talking about
what wines you like or
what movies you hate.
I want to know how you feel
about me.
You live under the delusion that you
can fix everything that isn't perfect.
That's why you married a man
who was dying of cancer.
You don't love, you need.
And now that your husband is dead,
you're looking for your new charity case.
That's why you're going out with me.
I'm twice your age,
I'm not great looking,
I'm not charming,
I'm not even nice.
What I am is what you need.
I'm damaged.
Came in late.
Had a good time last night?
How's the surgery going?
Harvey's doing fine so far.
How'd the night go?
It was fine,
how was your evening?
She had the ravioli,
I had the puttanesca.
Yes, I really want to know
about the quality of the food.
Either something very good happened,
or something very bad. Which is it?
Well, I did have a little
indigestion afterwards.
Maybe it was the garlic bread.
Or the wine.
Something made my eyes puffy.
Yeah. Crying in your pillow can do that.
It was the wine.
We had a nice, candid conversation.
Nothing deep, mostly small talk.
I'm sure.
Took your advice, complimented her shoes
that's fifteen minutes of chat right there.
No snide comments?
I guess, when we talked about you guys.
Just answer one question:
You two going to do dinner again?
I don't think so.
I don't know.
Hey kids, you were wrong.
No aneurysm, no nothing.
This guy's clean.
Which means we've got no idea
what's causing the strokes.
He's had two more post-op.
We won't know the
extent of the damage
until he comes out of the coma.
If he comes out.
Maybe we should go back to
the blood thinners, up the dosage.
If it's not clots, a
loading dose of blood
thinners is gonna make him
bleed out of his ears.
Then he won't be able to hear.
Oy ve.
Nobody home, leave a message!
This is important!
Chase, Cameron,
get another angiogram and echo.
Better get a full-body scan. If it is
clots, it'd be good to know where they are.
Sorry about that. Guy dying.
Those pills you gave Myron,
they're not working.
Well, glad to see you've got
the correct perspective on the thing.
Well, the old ones, you know,
made me feel like a tree!
Nice visual.
The new ones, well,
might as well be eating candy.
Candy wouldn't
take away your headaches.
What?
You came to me and told me that
you were having too much sex.
I never did!
You too, Sequoia.
Well no, that's not true, I...
I know that everybody lies, but
you'd think that after a certain
amount of time together you
wouldn't be trying so hard.
Your rings don't match.
What, well, why would they?
Well, style is one thing,
but one silver, one gold?
How long have you guys been married?
- 55 years.
- 49 years.
Damn it, you're having an affair.
Did you really say
you wanted to have less sex.
Well, less. If I wanted none
I'd stay home with Esther.
I just need a little rest.
You guys aren't the victim of
the little blue pill, you're the problem!
I'm sorry.
Me, too. I should just
have told you how I felt.
Aw.
Oh, welcome to hell.
Hey, how 'bout the pills?
Looks like you guys are good
to go drug-free for a while.
Dr. Chase, these breath mints
you've been popping since yesterday.
Are they a new fetish?
Oh, I got them at Harvey's.
What, I just took two boxes.
the guy's got a whole drawer of them!
And you didn't find that interesting.
Well, there's lots of
interesting stuff at his place.
The mints weren't
high up on the list.
Wrong.
Chase, get your nose in here.
If you're trying to humiliate me,
I told you...
Come on,
just put your face in his mouth.
Rich, wouldn't you say?
Smells like old vomit.
Number one sign of
fulminating osteomylitis.
Infection of the jaw?
Probably from the original break.
Never healed properly.
Infected tissue from the jaw breaks off,
blocks blood flow to the brain,
and life just isn't worth
living without blood.
It was hidden from the scans
by the metal plate.
And an infection of the jaw
isn't likely to show up on blood tests.
So how do we confirm?
Like this.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we have pus.
We're gonna remove the jaw.
Anybody got a buzzsaw?
Okay, call a surgeon.
Hi, I'm Dr. House.
How's tricks, Annette?
I just wanted to see
if he was okay. I'll leave.
No, it's okay.
I came to talk to you both.
Like I tell all my patients, you've
simply got to say "no" to strangulation.
Me, I'm a freak,
I get off on not being in pain.
That, and chocolate-covered
marshmallow bunnies.
He's not a freak.
Yeah, he is. A little.
But it's got to stop. Or he'll die.
It's not about pain.
It's about being open, being completely
vulnerable to another person.
If you can learn to be
that deeply trusting...
it changes you.
Well, lock him in a cage.
That should be fine, medically.
Dr. House.
Were my parents here?
Did they come to see me?