Jessica!
Jessica, come on!
We've gotta go!
Move it or lose it, sister.
I don't feel good.
Oh. You don't feel warm.
My stomach hurts.
Honey, if you don't have a fever...
I don't want to go to school,
I can do my work at home.
Jessica, what's wrong?
Everybody hates me.
Oh, they don't hate you.
They don't even know you
because they're too ignorant to try.
I hate myself!
Jessica, don't say that.
Oh, honey,
look at me, look at me.
You are a wonderful,
beautiful, little girl.
- Don't let a few bad apples...
- A few?
Try my whole class.
Remember the story where the guy keeps
saying that he hates green eggs and ham,
and then at the end he realized
he really loved them?
One day they're gonna realize
what a great kid you really are.
You've just gotta be like
Sam I Am, and don't give up.
Okay.
- Come on, Jessica, hurry!
- That's it, keep going.
Good, nice!
You're doing great, Jessica.
Hey, hey Seth? You want to spend
the rest of class sitting on the bench?
No.
Keep going, Jess,
you've got 40 more seconds.
My arm hurts.
Come on, tough it up,
you can do it. You can do it.
My chest hurts.
How do you think the ground feels?
Hey, Seth? Two laps, bye.
Hey, Jess, it's just a stitch, okay?
Just keep breathing, you got it.
I can't.
Only 10 more seconds,
you got it.
Jessica, Jessica!
Jessica!
One of my students is
having a heart attack.
Yeah, she's ten.
Don't you think I know that?
Just send the damn ambulance!
Come on, wake up.
Come on, sweetie.
You ever see an infected pierced scrotum?
No, but I know a few people on whom I'd
like to see it happen. We need to talk.
Well, if pain's what you're after
the penis is really the way to go.
I'd recommend the Abadirabia.
We're not talking.
Oh? Sounded like we were.
No, you're attempting to avoid talking
because you know what I want to talk about.
Nipples?
You need to get rid of
one of your people.
Absolutely. As soon as
I do performance reviews.
And then review the reviews, of course.
Because a decision like this can't be made
without proper, you know, review.
Shouldn't take longer
than a month, maybe two.
Four at the most, unless
it gets complicated.
There's no way out on this.
You may as well get it over with as fast
as you can, like ripping off a band-aid.
Only instead of a two-cent piece of
tape and gauze, it's a human being.
- Like you care.
- Like you don't.
You have a week. Get it done.
We have a referral from Dr. Linkowitz.
Don't know him.
He knows you.
What's the problem?
Heart attack.
Definitely don't know him.
The patient's ten.
Ten year olds do not have heart attacks.
It's gotta be a mistake.
Right. The simplest explanation is
she's a forty-year-old lying about her age.
Maybe an actress trying to hang on.
I meant, maybe the tests were wrong.
That's what the ER thought.
Three CKMBs were positive, the EKG
shows classic signs of ST elevation.
It's a heart attack.
She's morbidly obese.
The "morbid" part of that raises alarms.
Come on, it takes decades to
eat your way into a heart attack.
Doesn't take decades to kill yourself.
If I was that fat, I'd be pretty
tempted to knock back a bottle of pills.
It's not a drug overdose.
The fatigue, muscle pain, and
difficulty concentrating
have been bothering
her for over a year.
That's because of her weight.
That's because of her depression.
That's what five pediatricians,
two nutritionists, and a psychologist said.
The heart attack would seem to
indicate that they missed something.
It's got to be something genetic.
What about Metabolic Syndrome X?
Insulin resistance?
Syndrome X could cause a stroke,
but I don't know about a heart attack.
Could, if her blood
pressure was high enough.
Which is likely, considering her weight.
It fits the symptoms. Me likee.
Do a hyperinsulinemic euglyemic clamp.
Oh, and one more thing.
I've been told that I've got to get rid of
one of you guys by the end of the week.
New sheriff, belt tightening,
you know how it goes.
Okay, carry on.
It's some kind of game,
House's own version of "Punk'd".
It's not House, it's Vogler.
We can't let it get to us,
we've got to stick together.
Why?
What are you suggesting,
we start slashing each other's throats?
I'm suggesting it's a zero-sum game.
Your loss is my win.
That's not conducive to team play.
Which is what House seems to want.
Come with Cameron.
May be a bad strategy, but I don't
want to give House his satisfaction.
Come on, sick kid, remember?
She's diabetic?
No, but it's similar.
MSX patients don't respond
normally to insulin,
which causes her body to create too much,
and that leads to metabolic abnormalities.
We're going to do a test to be sure,
but there are certain dangers.
Is this thing treatable?
It's controllable
through proper diet and exercise.
Wait. Jessica already eats right.
And she exercises every day!
I know you've already seen
several nutritionists...
And we've done everything they recommended.
I understand, but...
Why can't any of you doctors
see past her weight?
If diet and exercise are the treatment,
then the diagnosis is wrong.
It might be,
but the only way we'll know is
if you'll let us do this test.
It's really bad, especially at night.
It's like my heart is on fire, like it's,
I don't know, like it's...
- Burning?
- Exactly!
Sounds almost like heartburn.
So, can you give me something?
Like a thesaurus?
What?
I take it you never mentioned this
during any of your prenatal visits.
Prenatal?
I'm not pregnant.
Sorry, you don't get to make that call
unless you have
a stethoscope. Union rules.
I know when I'm pregnant,
all right? I have six kids.
That's why my husband had a vasectomy
and we use condoms.
Vasectomies can reverse themselves,
condoms break.
Okay.
This is what a woman
is supposed to look like.
Okay, we're not just skin and bones.
We have flesh. We have curves.
You have little people inside you.
Okay, okay, I'm sorry.
I guess I must have just
been brainwashed by the media,
and all those years of medical training.
Damn right.
Let's see if I can find some antacids
while the nurse gets some blood.
Blood, why?
The heartburn,
gotta make sure it's not spreading.
I don't want to.
The test involves some
pretty precise measurements.
If we don't know exactly how much you
weight, we won't get the right answers.
Tell you a secret.
When I was your age, I was heavy, too.
Were you over 100?
Way over. The kids in my neighborhood
used to call me Rerun.
Rerun?
He was a heavy guy from TV.
I used to pretend I liked it, but I didn't.
How come you're not heavy any more?
Ninth grade, grew five inches,
everything kind of evened out.
You think that'll happen to me?
Well, yeah! I mean, your mom's tall,
and you are a little short for your age.
You'll probably spring right up.
Obesity isn't something
you just grow out of.
Take it you've never seen a baby?
She's not a baby, she's ten!
And you figure making her feel like
crap would do her a world of good?
Yeah, if it gets her off the couch!
I'm sure she's already
under enough pressure.
Enough from mummy.
Everything in society tells us
we have to be thin to be successful.
No, society tells you
you have to be thin to be attractive.
And guess what, that's what attractive
means: That society likes looking at you.
I think we should be telling our kids
it's fine as long as they're healthy.
All right. You weigh 90 pounds
because it makes you healthier?
Forget it.
He's just cranky because he knows
he's the one to get the axe.
So, any thoughts?
On what? Sharon's plan for Gaza?
Who you're gonna let go.
I'm thinking I can convince
Vogler it would be
more cost-efficient to
let me keep all of them.
Yeah, you should be
able to pull that off.
Most billionaires aren't
very good with numbers.
It will be more cost-efficient
once I've grabbed Cameron's ass,
called Foreman
a spade, and Chase...
well, I can grab his ass, too.
You are uniquely talented in many areas,
but office politics is not one of them.
Don't take Vogler on.
Separate or together?
Together.
Increasing glucose to
6.9 milligrams per minute.
Are you okay?
I'm thirsty.
Just a little bit longer,
and you'll be done.
Like Dr. Chase.
Wanna put some money on it?
I said I'm thirsty.
Just five more minutes,
okay, sweetheart?
I'm not your sweetheart,
don't call me that.
Jessica, that's not nice.
- You're the ones who aren't nice.
- Jessica...
You're not either!
I don't want to do this anymore!
Jessica! Jessica,
you have to calm down!
No! Let me go!
Check her blood sugar. She's
gotta be getting hypoglycemic.
Never seen her like this before.
What goes wrong?
- Hey, calm down!
- Let go of me!
Get it out of me,
you son of a bitch! You bastards!
She's sedated.
Mrs. Simms, don't worry.
Hypoglycemia can cause
temporary psychosis and
it's a common complication
during a HEC procedure.
I never wanted it done in the first place.
We understand you're upset, but...
You were supposed to be
monitoring her condition.
But instead you were
bickering and placing bets.
I apologize if we looked
we weren't paying full attention
to your daughter, but
I assure you that...
Oh, please. Save your pathetic
insincerity for your boyfriend.
You're wrong. She is, in fact, pathetically
sincere. And they didn't screw it up.
Who are you?
I'm from the lab.
The blood tests showed
your daughter wasn't hypoglycemic,
which means her psychosis wasn't
caused by anything these doctors did.
So then what was it caused by?
I have no idea,
but you'll be happy to hear
it can't be cured by diet or exercise.
What else could cause
uncontrollable rage in a ten-year-old?
Nothing that could also
cause a heart attack.
I assume I don't have to point out
that now would be an extremely
good time for one of
you to distinguish yourself
with a brilliant idea.
A hypocoaguable state
could cause a blood clot.
Blood clots can cause a heart attack.
More likely to cause a stroke,
not the psychosis.
No, you're wrong.
If the clot made it to
the amicdal area of the
brain, it might cause
uncontrollable rage.
Right, because anything's possible,
but nothing's going to cause
multiple clots in a kid this age.
She's fat!
Obesity doesn't cause blood clots.
Extremely obese patients
can get a fat embolus.
Right, after they get liposuction
which she's clearly never had.
How do you know?
Because we have her medical records.
And because no plastic
surgeon in his right mind
is going to give a
ten-year-old liposuction!
Have you ever met a plastic surgeon
who was in their right mind?
She hasn't had liposuction.
Thank you.
But what about some other
ridiculous obesity treatment?
Like what?
Diet pills can cause
heart attacks and blood clots.
Her tox screen was negative.
Wouldn't show
over-the-counter weight loss drugs.
Her mother wouldn't give her diet pills.
Yeah, she thinks her daughter's perfect
just the way she is.
She's lying.
Okay, you two, heparin and warfarin
to prevent further clotting.
And you, find those pills.
Not diet pills.
You might want to broade
the search just a little.
And don't just ask the mom, if she
hasn't mentioned yet, she's not gonna...
If you're gonna fire
someone, go ahead and do it,
but don't treat us like lab
rats, testing how long
it takes us to get us at
one another's throats.
So what should I do?
I don't give a damn what you do.
Yes, I had noticed your
complete indifference.
You don't even offer
a medical opinion any more.
Who would you fire?
Not my call.
I want your opinion.
Fine, it's you.
Either way, you're making a choice.
Chase.
Because he screwed up
an angio a month ago?
Anyone can make a mistake.
Right, it's the money.
You resent it, but you're going to tell me
he doesn't need the job.
He doesn't appreciate the job.
He was ready to go
three rounds with Cameron for it.
He wants the job.
He just doesn't appreciate it.
There's nothing wrong
with just wanting to hang out,
but this is not
the place to do it.
I'm surprised.
You thought I'd pick Cameron?
I didn't think you'd pick at all.
I guess he's not the "rise above the
fray" guy he likes to think he is.
You practically forced it out of him.
He's scared of losing his job,
just like everyone else.
I've been thinking. You've made it quite
clear that you're miserable here...
I am not miserable.
You're not happy.
And you are?
With... my job, yes.
I am exactly where I want to be
doing exactly what I want to do.
I think I sense a hint of sarcasm there.
Why don't you pick yourself? Quit?
Hmmm... I was wrong.
About Vogler or Foreman?
Mrs. Hernandez's pregnancy tests.
Who's Mrs. Hernandez?
Either a woman carrying an alien baby
or your newest patient.
So, you never saw her with any pills?
She never mentioned anything?
No, of course not.
Would it be all right
if I talked to a couple of her friends?
Her friends?
Well, I'm not going to interrogate them,
but I just want to ask if
Jessica ever mentioned anything.
It's pretty important,
she's very sick.
I understand, it's just, well,
Jessica really doesn't have any friends.
Not one?
I've tried to help, make the kids
include her more, but kids can be...
Kids?
Heh, I was going to say jerks.
All the fifth-graders are
assigned an eighth-grade buddy.
Maybe you could talk to her's.
What's the status on House?
He asked for time to complete performance
reviews on everyone in his department.
And you told him no
and gave him how long?
A week. He'll do it.
Guy's never done what he's told.
Don't see why he's going to start now.
Hi! Edward Vogler.
Is Dr. House claiming that
I'm forcing him to get rid of one of you?
I assume his goal is to
stir up antagonism toward me.
And your goal is?
I am forcing him.
I'll do whatever I can to ease
the transition for whoever he chooses.
If you're feeling guilty about your
decision, there is an easy solution.
I don't feel guilty.
Then why approach me
and tell me all this?
I don't feel guilty,
that doesn't mean I don't feel bad.
I'm rich, but I'm still human.
I just wanted you to know that if there's
anything I can do for you, my door's open.
Thank you.
You looking for info?
I thought you already had
House all figured out?
I do.
Don't know his team, though.
The ultrasound and biopsy
confirmed our worry.
The tumor is extremely large,
at least thirty pounds.
Oh, God.
It's actually
a personal record for this clinic.
But it's completely benign,
there's no sign of cancer at all.
I've already spoken with Dr. Bergin, and
he's available first thing in the morning.
For what?
For the surgery.
But if it's not cancer,
it can't kill me, right?
No.
I'll have a huge scar!
I won't be able to wear a bikini!
You wear a bikini now?
Yeah, you got a problem with that?
Nope, but I've never gone
swimming with you.
I knew it. That's
what this is all about!
You are trying to force me
to have cosmetic surgery!
Yeah, that's exactly why I planted
a thirty pound tumor on your ovary.
It's not gonna kill me.
The only thing surgery is going to do
is change the way I look.
That is the definition of
"cosmetic surgery".
It would also relieve
your heartburn and discomfort.
Yeah, right.
Why give an antacid when
you can cut someone up
and make them look a little
easier on your eyes?
My husband loves my body.
He can't get enough of it.
You think he's gonna want to touch me if I
look like I've been gutted like a fish?
That was unexpected.
Yeah, it was.
All she does during recess is
run laps around the playground.
She says she's exercising,
but everyone knows
it's just because no one
wants to play with her.
I mean, I'm only her buddy
because Ms. Ayers assigned her to me.
That does not mean
I am her friend.
I'll make sure her doctors
are all clear on that.
Thanks.
So, has she ever said anything
to you about diet pills?
She told you that, too.
What do you mean?
I totally busted her
for taking drugs one day.
She totally lied, said they were
diet pills her mom had given her.
Come on, get real. No way a girl
like that is taking diet pills.
I didn't give her diet pills,
I would never do that!
Right, so it was her imaginary mom.
She didn't take any pills,
the girl's lying!
Why would she lie?
Because she's another mean little jerk?
Mom.
I'm sorry, honey.
Clemmie didn't lie.
I did. I took the pills.
I told her you gave them to me
'cause I didn't want to get in trouble.
Where did you get them?
I took them. From the store.
Why? Why would you do that?
Because I didn't want to be ugly anymore.
Oh, baby. You're not ugly.
Yes, I am! I know you don't think so,
but I am! I'm disgusting.
Jessica, please, don't say that.
I just, just wanted to fit in.
You know, have friends?
Or at least have one person
my age be nice to me.
Listen, the pills cause blood clots,
heart attacks, and insomnia.
It explains everything.
We'll keep her overnight to
make sure, but she'll be fine.
Thank you.
I can't believe she was that desperate.
Yeah, I'm sure that
if everyone I knew hated me,
I couldn't bear to look at me.
I wouldn't go so far as to shoplift.
I'm not talking about the shoplifting.
I'm sure she didn't even know
they were dangerous.
She probably saw them
advertised on TV or over the internet.
Right, so I guess it's the media and
pharmaceutical companies' fault now?
Not the fact that she can't stop
shoving food down her throat.
No one forced her to get fat.
No one forced a cancer
patient to get cancer.
Give me a break,
it's not a disease.
Have you seen the latest research?
Yes, I have.
What I haven't seen lately is a kid
eating an apple or riding a bike.
You Americans can't even
compete with the rest
of the world in basketball
anymore, unless,
of course, it's the type you play with
a remote control on a big screen TV.
Right.
Wait!
Are you going to let him say that?
He insulted our basketball teams!
Oh, my God! Mommy,
they hurt so bad!
What happened?
Please help me!
She's bleeding!
From where?
Oh, my god!
Just please stop it, please!
Diet pills don't cause skin necrosis.
Could be something related to the pills.
- Or not.
- Or both.
Diet pills brought her to us,
we gave her the sores.
You think she got a staff infection
from something here?
I'm not saying the hospital gave
the sores, I'm saying we did.
By treating her.
Warfarin-induced skin necrosis.
Highly unlikely. We started her
on heparin before the warfarin.
Who gave her the heparin?
I did warfarin, she did heparin.
Sure you didn't both give her warfarin?
Yes, I did not screw up.
Did you actually see her prepare
and administer the heparin?
Enough said.
You were standing right there.
I was preparing my own dose.
Yeah, right. There's gotta
be some other cause.
None that I can think of.
Let's fix the mistake.
Give her unfractionated IV
heparin and low molecular
weight heparin by
subcutaneous injection stat.
Making me look bad is not
going to save your job.
You think you're incapable of
making a mistake?
You think that I am that weak that
I am just going to roll over and take this?
House isn't just going to protect you
just because you kiss his ass!
Vogler wants to know what he can do for me.
Hey!
Stop worrying about your asses and
start worrying about the patient's.
She sleeping?
As a result of the sedatives, yeah.
Can't let her wake up, too much pain.
"Warfarin-induced skin necrosis".
I have no idea what that means.
But it says here we gave her the warfarin,
and I do know what "induced" means...
we did this?
At this point it's not exactly clear.
You know, I should
probably talk to Dr. House.
Oh, you two need time to
get your story straight.
He doesn't tell me what to do.
So you don't just blindly
follow his commands.
You're your own man.
And yet, here you are working
for a man you can't stand.
I respect him.
What exactly is it you respect?
His attitude toward humanity?
He thinks we're all idiots and liars.
How 'bout his attitude toward you,
plays with you like a
cat with a ball of string...
What do you want?
I want to know if you
want to keep your job.
If he chooses to let me go,
I can live with that.
That's not an answer.
You offering to protect me?
Still not an answer.
I want my job.
Dr. Chase.
Boss.
What was that about?
Wanted to know what warfarin is.
I don't know.
Icy.
Definitely think twice before
correcting one of your mistakes again.
Correct all you want.
Of course, it's a bit more productive
if there's an actual mistake.
Right, I always forget that part.
I gave her the heparin,
which means the necrosis is
not a reaction to the warfarin,
which is probably why she's not
responding to your treatment.
Yet.
If you didn't screw up,
then what is it?
You don't have an answer.
Yet.
When you come up with
something, let me know.
I'll be in the clinic,
warming up.
I'm the only one who's always
stood behind you when you've screwed up.
Why? Why would you support
someone who screws up?
Because I'm not insanely insecure.
And because I can actually
trust in another human being
and I am not an angry,
misanthropic son of a bitch.
I'm sorry, you said you weren't angry.
Who would you fire?
No one.
Not an option.
If everyone took a paycut
and put in a few more hours
we could all stay for the
same amount of money.
Figures you'd try and come up with
a solution where no one gets hurt.
The problem is, the world doesn't work
that way just 'cause you want it to.
Figures you'd stall and refuse
to deal with the issue.
Problem is, the world doesn't go away
just because you want it to.
Excuse me, Dr. House?
My wife saw you yesterday,
Lucille Hernandez?
Uh, he's not in today.
My wife said
he walked with a cane.
He's also got a bit of a drug problem.
Sometimes doesn't show up for weeks.
The MRis are rented, but...
Did you make a decision?
- He's not gonna fire anybody.
- Yes.
I'm going to cut the pay of all four of us.
17% across the board will allow you to
keep us all for the same amount of money.
I believe it's what you
suits call "win-win".
- All right, if you can...
- No.
If he can work it so we can
keep the current staff for
the same amount of money,
what difference does it make?
It's not about the money.
This is not a negotiation, it never was.
I need to know that whatever
I ask you to do,
however distasteful you
find it, you'll do it.
And just as importantly,
you need to know that.
What's going on with my wife?
Even if I was Dr. House,
physician-patient
confidentiality protects me
from annoying conversations.
But she told me about the tumor.
Yeah? She also tell you
why she's refusing to have it removed?
I don't care about a scar.
And she can always gain the weight back.
You want her to regain the weight?
Yeah. I mean, only if she wants to.
Why?
I've always thought she's looked sexiest
when she was pregnant.
Something 'bout knowing
she's a mother makes me want to...
Yeah, tell her that and leave me alone.
I did. You gotta talk to her,
I couldn't bear it
if something happened to her...
The tumor is benign, nothing's gonna
happen. Except maybe some more heartburn.
What if it gets even bigger?
Or if it changes?
You know where to find us.
Building's not going anywhere.
Tell her it's cancer.
You obviously don't have
a problem with lying.
Oh, way to win me over.
We have six kids.
She can't afford to take a chance.
You have kids! How novel!
That changes everything.
So if Mommy has heartburn,
one of them might catch on fire.
Please,
I don't know what we'd do.
They are cute.
Have her come back in.
What?
Your plight has moved me.
Tell your wife to come back.
Her necrosis is getting worse.
Maybe because we're
treating her for the wrong thing.
Have you found the right thing?
No.
Then we continue the treatment.
Hope it's just taking
longer than it should.
At this point it doesn't matter
what caused the necrosis.
Or who.
If we don't stop it from spreading
it will kill her before the end of the day.
What else can we do?
Get rid of it.
Remove the dying flesh
before it penetrates the abdominal wall.
Do it.
There's still a chance that the heparin
treatment could start to take effect.
We're gonna wait as long as we can,
but if there's no change
in the next few hours,
we're gonna have to treat
the symptoms directly.
So you can get rid of the sores.
Through surgery.
Technically, it's an amputation.
Amputation? But the sores are...
Warfarin-induced necrosis attacks
fatty tissue, mainly in the breasts.
Wait, are you talking about
cutting off my daughter's breasts?
She's ten years old!
A radical mastectomy may be
her only chance of survival.
I'm sorry, but I'm gonna
have to ask you to sign this.
Can we talk?
What, no roses, no chocolates?
- If you're here to apologize...
- I'm not here to apologize.
Uh-oh,
that means you're here
for something more complicated.
Do you want to fire me?
Yes. I was just waiting for an excuse.
Thank God Vogler came along.
It's the only reason I can think of that
you're insisting that I made a mistake.
Really? Because there is
another explanation.
Perhaps not as much fun
as your Freudian analysis, but
maybe you actually made a mistake.
You're doing this because you can't
deal with your feelings for me.
I believe that you are
the only one to express feelings.
And if we're going to look
at this from a first-year
psych point-of-view, maybe
you want me to fire you.
Maybe that's why
you're acting weird. You...
You're the one being different!
You're always pushing things, pushing the
rules, pushing us, but not this time.
You just jumped on this
idea like a life raft.
Not one question about what else it could
be, no riding us for other answers.
I have the answer.
Then why aren't you watching TV?
Or playing your damn Game Boy,
or whatever else you have
fun doing by yourself?
Maybe I should just quit.
Make it easy for everyone.
Maybe you should.
Men are pigs.
You call me in to tell me...
I should have realized the
vasectomy and condoms
was overkill, but this
was too obvious to miss.
Cute kids.
Love her green eyes.
And his baby blues.
Of course, since you and
your husband have brown eyes...
Where'd you get that?
From the father of three,
maximum four of your six children.
So I'm thinking maybe the reason
you don't want surgery is,
while your husband may find you
attractive no matter what,
all the other men you're sleeping with
might not be so open-minded.
Which brings me back to
my original thesis: Men are pigs.
You got nothing to worry about.
You know, pretty much have sex
with anyone, fat, skinny,
married, single, complete
strangers, relatives...
You? You're sick.
So are you.
I'm sure there are websites full of men looking
for married women with surgical scars.
So have the surgery.
Please?
Okay.
Why have you been talking to Cameron?
Well, if House picks you
I'll be needing a new source in that room.
If he picks me?
Sure.
Foreman's smarter,
House has got a thing for Cameron.
I've been feeding you information
so you'll protect me.
I will protect you as long as I need you.
And you will feed me information
as long as you need me.
I spoke with Cameron
because if I have alternatives,
I don't need you.
She's not gonna rat on House.
Foreman ever said anything
about talking to me?
Interesting, huh?
It's been almost three hours,
still no change in her condition.
I think we should get her into surgery.
So what do you want to do?
Assume that Cameron didn't screw up.
What if it's not the warfarin?
It has to be.
The sores presented right after we...
Right, right, right,
but let's just say it's not.
Come on, come on,
what have you got?
Can I have a second to think?
No, there's no time to think! Just say
the first thing that comes to you head.
She's fat.
Enough already, okay?
We've got it, you hate fat people.
That's not what I meant.
We already considered obesity as a cause.
So did all her other doctors.
No, what if it's not a cause?
What if it's a symptom?
Okay, so what could cause
obesity and skin necrosis?
Listen, I don't care if it makes sense,
just give me something.
Ulcers secondary to vaculitis.
No, that's just sores, not obesity.
Pyoderma gangrenosum?
More sores. Okay,
let's look at it from the other side.
What has obesity as a symptom?
Hypothyroidism?
Genetics are more likely.
Her mom's heavy, too.
She's not just heavy. She's tall.
We have any history on the dad?
Yeah.
6'1".
Kid's short.
We've got stunted growth, high blood
pressure, blood clots, obesity...
it's Cushing's.
No, necrosis doesn't present in...
In rare cases Cushing's
can cause hypercalcemia,
which can lead to the same
skin necrosis as warfarin.
It's perfect. It explains everyting.
Except it's not Cushing's.
She's had multiple blood tests and
none show abnormal cortisol levels.
The hypercortisolism could be cyclical,
we just didn't catch it in the right phase.
- We'll have to do another UFC.
- There's no time!
We've got less than an
hour to make the call.
If we treat for Cushing's
and we're wrong, she's dead.
If we assume it's not Cushing's, she'll
lose her breasts and may still be sick.
Do an MRI.
You want us to look for
hypercortisolism with an MRI?
No, I want you to look for what could
cause hypercortisolism with an MRI.
Nothing on the adrenals.
Heard Cameron went home.
Is she sick?
Go back to the pituitary views.
She seemed okay.
Think she's got another reason for leaving?
I hope so.
Wait, stop. There.
What's that?
A tumor.
It's Cushing's.
The tumor causes Cushing's.
Cushing's messes with hormone production.
Hormones control everything:
Growth, weight...
Can you fix it?
She'll need surgery to remove the tumor.
Once it's gone, everything
will get normal very fast.
No mastectomy?
No.
Thank God.
The surgery's dangerous.
The pituitary is located
between the caverns of
the sinuses, basically
right between the eyes.
The area contains the
nerves that control eye
movement and the major
arteries that feed the brain.
Oh, my God.
Your surgeon will approach
the gland transphenoidally.
An incision will be made under the lip in
which he'll insert a fiberoptic microscope.
Once the tumor's found, he'll
cut it into small pieces
and remove it from the
same hole under the lip.
The whole procedure should
take about three hours and
your daughter should be able
to go home in a few days.
The sores will go away,
as well as her fatigue and her muscle pain.
She'll even start losing weight.
Jessica.
Hi.
Is that really you?
Yeah, it's me.
You look fantastic!
She always looked fantastic.
Yeah.
It's been a week.
Actually, it's over a week.
Where have you guys been?
Who is it?
Chase.
No, Chase stays.
Pick someone else.
- The deal was...
- Deal's changed.
Pick someone else.
No.
Pick someone else or
it'll be the whole department.