Gary, what the hell
did you do?! She gasps
so, you've just been made homeless,
and you want to place your
daughter in emergency care?
Come here. Don't go,
mummy, please don't go.
'I love my daughter so much.
'I fully intend on getting a job and
a place of my own to support us.
'I just need a chance.'
- if I did have something to sell...?
- What?
Some stones, loose.
How'd you get them out?
'Grabbed them from the
safe. Necked 'em, walked.
'So, can you sell them for
me?' 'Might take a few weeks.'
right, I need cash now.
Would you do a bit more work, then?
'So, what am I nicking?'
'Clothes, designer gear, luggage.'
'but I wanna Nick jewels, not
shoplift with a dodgy chequebook.'
'all in good time.' 'I'm
only doing this one job.'
once you Nick the gear,
we're going to Spain tomorrow.
Spain?
'We need to courier some jewellery.
'My mate albie sells it out in Spain
'where the pigs aren't looking for it.
'We take it over, he pays us on delivery.'
'so you want me to take it on the plane,
'bear all the risk?'
so, we'll swing by his club.
'You need to act dumb
around his missus.'
business and pleasure all
in one cute, little package.
Yeah, no, I reckon
we'll make a good team.
I found out your ex did a
job for me back in the day.
You've spoken to Gary?
Says you was a right nightmare.
Ran off with his kid.
Gary's a bloody liar.
When am I coming home?
It won't be long now, I promise.
Our only concern is for Kelly's welfare.
I'm afraid we think that
she's better off where she is.
I need money. I mean "money" money.
Know what I mean?
Yeah, I reckon I do.
'The love cats' by the cure
today's special. Thank you.
So, what's the set-up?
It's perfect.
The house is miles from anywhere.
Crap security, no window locks.
We'll wait till it gets dark and break in.
Oil's halfway up the stairs.
It's definitely a real stubbs?
Classic. Worth thousands.
Enough to buy me and Kelly
a new home with a garden?
A mansion, with a Butler thrown in.
So, what about the owner?
Woman. Lives on her own.
Drinks a lot, according to Hugo.
Your man at the auction house? Yeah.
When did he value it? This morning.
She was already half-cut.
Why?
Hard life when you're filthy rich.
No, no, I mean why get it valued?
I dunno, probably insurance.
Or she's planning to sell it. Your point?
Well, I mean, if she's
already got a legit buyer,
they'll come looking for it when it goes.
It's much harder for us to sell on.
No, we'd have to hold
on to it for a while anyway.
Well, I don't want to
hold on to it for a while.
I need cash now. To
set myself up for Kelly.
Right, we'll go back to London
now, get Jim Cho to knock up a sham.
Come back.
I'll find a way in by
day, let you in at night.
Swap the pictures.
No-one will know it's gone.
We can sell it on straight away.
She grunts
thunder rumbles.
I was out walking. I was
I was out... I was out walking.
I was out walking.
Bell rings dog barking
get down! Who is it?
Sorry to disturb. Er, I need help.
I don't open the door to strangers.
Well, I've twisted my ankle.
I was out walking.
If... if I could just use your
telephone and call a friend?
It's getting dark.
I don't know what I was
thinking, setting off alone.
And then I turned my
ankle on a stile and...
Dog barks get back!
You're obviously a long way from home.
I just... I need a pick-me-up.
Well, I could open some Brandy.
Of course, if I could afford
to heat this bastard place,
I wouldn't need it.
It's a beautiful house.
It was, before my husband
walked out, left me with all the bills.
Fuck-face.
Sounds familiar.
Can't believe that anyone would
abandon a little poppet like you.
You'd be surprised.
Another woman?
He packed a bag and said
he was "going on the run."
Classic. I know. Fuck-face!
Woman chuckles, dog
barks shush! Dog barks
shush! You'll get your sausage.
He'll be back soon enough.
Dog whines
tail between his legs
with a peace offering.
Bottle of gin or something.
But don't let him back in! I won't, I won't.
That's always been my problem.
Well, you've got a kind heart.
You'll stay the night.
Thank you. That's very kind.
Aw... your daughter?
Married a kiwi last year.
Buggered off to the
other side of the world.
I'll see you for breakfast.
My friend needs to come
early, so I'll just slip out.
Everyone leaves me in the end.
Well, thank you for having me.
Good night. Night.
Dog pants shh! Good boy.
Boo.
Dog barks shh!
Here, give him a sausage.
Why me? You're the stranger.
We're fine for now. I put
that valium in her nightcap.
Ok. Where's the sham?
It's in the Van. Let's
get the real deal out first.
What a beauty.
1760, 1765... Come on, then.
Look at the detail.
Joan grunts stop, stop, stop.
It's fine, it's fine.
Careful. Don't touch the oil.
Door unlocks, dog
barks door creaks, closes
- shit.
- Henrietta?
Hen?
Forgive me. Hen?
Scream. Joan screams
out my way! Dog barks
glass smashes put it down. Now!
Dog growls
who are you? A friend of hen's?
Go in the kitchen, call the police.
Gun cocks out my fucking way.
Dog barks move.
Move, or I'll blow your brains out!
Dog barks.
Man grunts don't fuck with me.
Fuck's sake! Get in! Car starts
you brought a gun?!
It's all right, I wasn't gonna use it.
Do you think he'll call
the police? Yeah, course.
Just drive.
You're over-thinking it.
He was drunk. He saw you for a second.
But I spent all evening with her.
You were in disguise, and
she doesn't know your name.
She's got no means of tracing
you. Well, she'd get me in a line-up.
A line-up?!
Well, it's all right for you.
You had a balaclava on.
Yeah, to make you
the victim, protect you.
Protect me? You pulled out a gun!
You turned it into an aggravated assault.
I wasn't gonna use it. I don't care.
What was I supposed to do, joanie?
Follow me upstairs. Run
out the back, like I did.
Without this? Yeah, without the painting.
It's not like we can sell it now.
I'm taking it to the
warehouse. Order a Chinese.
Be back in an hour.
But I wanna come with you.
Let me come with you. Sorry, joanie.
So, I graft for you all day,
put my neck on the line,
and you don't fucking care?
You can't just shut me out!
Fuck you.
Sighs.
Bell rings
what can I do you for?
Selling stones.
Loose?
Who sent you? No-one.
Well, who are you?
Joan. Joan who?
You interested or not?
Where'd you get them from, Joan?
Does it matter? Well,
it should to you, darling.
You've been royally done. Cut glass.
I can see it from here.
She sighs serious?
What you doing? Might
as well Chuck them, then.
No, no, no. Look. Let
me take another look.
I might be able to give you a few quid.
It's all right. I think they're
worth more than that.
You never told me
where you got them from.
I'm not going to.
Then I'd better keep hold of them.
Call my mate down the cop shop.
They're only worth something
if you know how to sell them!
Stupid cow.
Murmur of conversation.
Enjoy.
'Nocturnes op.9, no.2' by chop in
same again, without the... veg.
Would you let me buy
this? No, I wouldn't.
She never accepts
drinks off strange men.
Of all the gin joints...
How did you find me?
I never buy what I can steal.
This came. From social services.
She sighs they want to visit.
Check out the suitability of
my new living arrangements.
So come back.
You've gotta let me in, boisie.
I mean, men have been
pushing me around my whole life,
keeping things from me.
I won't have it any more.
I'll show you mine if you show me yours.
I'm not a grass.
Never have been.
Keys jingle
key's in the glove box.
Glove box opens, keys jingle.
George iv. It's mahogany.
Here you are. Look at
the craftsmanship here.
How beautiful.
She chuckles.
Wow.
Never seen you so happy.
I had nothing as a kid.
Me neither.
Not a bean. Yeah, not just.
Stuff. I mean... No family.
My mum.
I get it.
My dad beat me.
A lot.
What did she do?
She... chose her fella over me,
gave me away when I was a kid.
He plays piano melody
then one day, she
said I could come back.
That's good. Yeah.
So they could claim family allowance.
Five shillings a week.
25 pence?
Least I knew what I was worth.
They'll be safe here.
Choose something.
Ringing tone
'southern well social
services. Good morning.'
hello, it's Joan O'Connell again.
I-I'm still waiting for a
visit from the social worker.
Any idea when they're coming?
'I'll have to check
where you are on the list
'and get someone to call you back.'
but I've got my flat all ready.
'Yes, I appreciate that.'
I'm just... I'm desperate
to get my little girl back.
'I'm sorry, but we are
really busy at the moment.'
ok.
Thank you.
Vacuum whirrs.
'To get your motor running smoothly,
'choose Becker type o grade,
'the finest engine oil in the world.'
'when words are not enough.
'Fall in love with diamonds.'
'sapphire goldsmith's, London.'
Thanks.
Can I help you, madam?
Er, yeah. Coffee?
Certainly, madam. Thank you.
Show me the emperor
again. Of course, madam.
We can always adjust it.
I'm in London again next
week. I can try it on then.
Absolutely. If you send the car?
To the dorsington? Yes.
And I need the spec. The
carats, the cut, the mount.
My husband likes to know
what he's spending his money on.
Salesman chuckles of
course. I'll write it all down.
I've been thinking, boisie.
If we can't sell the painting now.
I still need some money.
Thanks.
Well, I'll sell something
from the warehouse
to get you some cash.
No. I wanna earn my own money.
So you can buy Kelly a horse?
Sorry, two horses.
I don't want her to ever wish
she was back at the ashburys.
She won't.
I've seen a ring I wanna Nick.
Worth 250 grand.
He scoffs
they won't even get the ring out of
the cabinet if they don't know you.
Unless I convince them I'm a somebody.
An American. Loaded.
Dress up proper fancy,
drop in that I'm staying at a posh hotel.
You know, string them along.
Tell them I need a spec
made up for my lover.
Ok. Take the spec up to hat ton garden.
Get a sham made up.
So then... when I return
to actually buy the ring...
Swap it, walk out, sell it on.
Well, you don't need me at all.
I do. I need a sugar
daddy to come with me,
help me sell my character.
Come with you? What,
like your assistant?
I can't leave the shop. No, sorry, Joan.
You'll for ego 80 grand because
you won't close up for half a day?
She scoffs
do you even want me to succeed?
As a thief or as a mother?
Doorbell rings
boisie? Can you get it?
Might be the social.
Indistinct conversation
hello, Joan. It's you.
Nice to see you, too. Albie chuckles
what are you doing here?
Val was getting sunspots. And the rest.
So, back for good? Joan.
No, that's fair. Let her quiz me.
If we're about to work together.
What do you mean? What's he said?
Can you act?
With you on my arm, anything's possible.
Great
look, I'm happy to get
involved. He clears throat
but why don't you just do it on your own?
I need help selling on.
The fence won't work
with someone new.
It's all planned out. I've got the spec.
I know what I'm doing, albie.
Well, I don't doubt that for a minute.
Bell rings
need a word with king, darling.
King. What?
There's a bloke here to see you.
Once you've made the
introduction, I'll do the talking.
Er, no. King's the kind of geezer
who'd rather talk with a man.
Hello, mate. Hello.
Didn't know you was
knocking round again.
Only so long you can lie on
a beach, know what I mean?
King chuckles
you should've told me
you was working for albie.
I'm not. He's working for me.
Working together, mate.
Er, we need a piece made up.
Not selling stones any more, then?
Sold them. You missed out.
What kind of piece? It's
my job. I've got the spec.
You need to get your
trousers back, mate.
He whistles in appreciation
where did you get this
from? From the jeweller's.
I want an 18-carat four-claw
mount with the fake set in.
Made of? Cubic zirconia.
It's got to match this exactly.
He exhales
that's a lot of work. It'll cost you.
You're gonna do it for free.
You mad cow. Hey, Joan, no...
In return, you'll get the real deal
when I bring it back the next day, ok?
Retail's 250 grand. I want
80 in cash, unmarked notes.
75.
80. And I want the
sham ready for Thursday.
Ooh!
He whistles through his teeth forget it.
Not the only bent
jeweller in hat ton garden.
All right, all right. You're on. You're on.
I'll do it.
How'd it go?
All right. Is he shaping
up as a good sugar daddy?
Well, he's not exactly Sidney poitier.
Thanks well, maybe Eddie
Murphy on a good day.
He chuckles
so, what's the set-up?
Er... pick up the sham from king
on Thursday, go home, get changed.
Take the tube to Heathrow,
pick up a black cab,
check in at the st James's park
hotel as mrs Stephanie sutherland.
I have cases. No problem,
madam. Thank you.
'Stay the night, get
prepared for the big day,
'get into character.'
Knocking.
Just wanted to say good luck.
Go. Why?
Because I'm jet lagged.
Having a quiet night in before I meet up
with my sugar daddy in the morning.
You love all this, don't you?
Dressing up.
Pretending.
Job satisfaction isn't a crime.
But the rest of it is.
Just go.
He sighs
so albie's not staying?
Don't be ridiculous. You know the story.
I'm meeting him in the shop.
All right. Bye. Bye.
Phone rings
she clears throat
hello.
Yes, I'll be straight down.
Yeah, checking out this
afternoon. Thank you. Bye.
For fuck's sake. Where
the fuck did that go?
Morning.
Mrs sutherland. Thank you.
Hello, mrs sutherland.
Mrs sutherland, how
lovely to see you again.
I trust the car arrived ok?
Thank you. And how was your flight?
I think I picked up a cold. She sniffs
you know, I can't get that
cute little ring out of my mind.
It's an exceptional piece.
I-I told my, er... My friend all about it.
Are we to expect him?
Well, I thought that he'd be here already.
Maybe I could try it on again?
Of course. Thank you.
Thank you.
It goes beautifully with your eyes.
Hello, sweetie.
They chuckle.
I've been thinking about you all night.
What do you think?
It is stunning. Isn't it?
And you really, really want it?
More than anything. Please?
It's a very special piece,
sir. Totally unique, in fact.
Of course. I saw the spec.
And the price is very...
Da-da-da-da. Not in front of her?
Let's talk.
They chat indistinctly
she sniffs.
It's not too much, is it?
For you, my love... It's a bargain.
Stephanie?
Honey. We said we'd
meet at the restaurant.
You didn't need to come here. Er... er
Steph and I just bumped into each other.
We were friends in college.
Hi. Sorry. James sutherland.
- He's always been the jealous type.
- Good to meet you, James.
Well... Let's go and get some lunch?
Next time.
Thank you.
You could surprise her with it.
No. I don't think so.
My apologies.
Good work.
Thought you really were a
green-eyed monster for a minute.
Right, some of us
have still got work to do.
I'm off to king's. Er, you
want me to come with?
In case he's funny about
giving money to a lady.
Well, then he needs to learn.
I'll get you your 20% later.
Gonna need to keep her on a tight rein.
'Sweet dreams ' by eurythmics.
I wouldn't have any
work if I ripped people off.
I always count the money.
Folk music plays albie barely sets foot
in the kitchen. That's not true.
I know you can cook.
She is so bloody lucky.
Look... what is this, Boise?
I bought a load of antiques
off this Russian geezer. He
threw in his record collection.
Did you make them from scratch?
Course I did, you stupid
cow. He's transformed you.
Maybe I've transformed myself. Yeah
you like him, though?
Yeah, I do. I think he's great!
Apart from his weird taste in music.
I'm proper happy for you,
Joan. Come on. Let's go.
Got 'em? Yeah.
Let's go.
Ta-da!
Right, val. Don't let me
down. No, I couldn't, Joan.
You could, couldn't you? Well,
if you made it, course I can.
What is it about London
that makes you so hungry?
Well, I have been working
pretty hard these last few days.
You're working here? What you doing?
This and that. Er... Me and Boise,
been working on a scheme
with an American couple.
Americans? Don't ask, Joan.
This... This... dessert is gorgeous.
You know what Jerry hall
says. Cook in the kitchen...
Whore in the bedroom. Albie!
Sorry, Joan. She doesn't mind.
Come on, Joan. Top me up.
Come on.
Nice.
Toast to Joan.
Look at her. She's perfect, isn't she?
God! What are you on about?
I fell for her the moment I met her,
scrabbling for coins in a pub.
We got as drunk as
lords. Nothing's changed...
Laughter
except I love you even more.
I love you.
Marry me, joanie.
What?
Are you sure?
Course.
I adore you.
Let's get married.
Marry me.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Whooping
congratulations!
Yes, grab the champers!
Music echoes and fades doorbell rings.
It was a one-off.
I'll take that, sorry. Once Kelly's here,
there'll be nothing like this, I promise.
Do you want a coffee? No, thanks.
We've got freshly
ground. Honestly, I'm fine.
Joan sighs if I'd known you were coming
I mean, I've been keeping
the place spick and span.
I've been obsessed.
Hoovering night and day.
We're not too bothered about mess.
As long as you're making progress
towards building a stable home.
Yeah, I am, definitely.
Because Kelly's doing
well where she is now.
Yeah, course she is. She's a good girl.
It-it's not about compliance, Joan.
Mrs ashbury tells us she's really thriving.
Kelly's flourishing at school.
Yeah, well, she would
say that, wouldn't she?
Do you want to sit down, Joan?
I've got something I need to tell you.
What? Sit down.
Spit it out.
The ashburys have asked
us if they can adopt Kelly.
It's just a request at the moment.
You're her mother,
and no-one's doing
anything without due process.
We do always try to keep
children with their mothers.
'It's really important
that Kelly moves back
'into a settled, stable environment.
'Right now, we're not
convinced you can provide that.'
TV plays faintly.
Door opens.
Good night, sweetheart.
Subtitles by accessibility@itv.Com