There's nothing left.
You know, how'd they
even find the warehouse?
I don't know.
Just lay low.
So, what is it? Punishment for
bringing the pigs to their door?
'Or a warning.'
if you help them to land a bigger fish,
one of your associates...
Not a chance. Trying to rip off the ra?
You'd better be tougher than you look.
If I make a deal, the ira kill
me. If I don't, I get ten years.
We have to run. To Spain.
It won't be cheap. You got
the Irish in. You owe me.
Joan? I miss that smile.
Bernard's. I mean clear the place out.
Every single piece of
that premier collection.
Now, that would buy us a new life.
We go on our own, and
I'll come back for her. Ok.
'More cameras?'
and a panic button,
straight through to the police.
Access is through the alley here.
We'll need another man to watch him.
Are you in? I'll let you know.
'I need you to add Kelly to my
passport so I can take her with us.'
promise me you'll tell him.
Before the job. Promise.
'Hello, king's Morton.'
'hello, it's Simone highsmith
'from the New York herald.'
Door unlocks, footsteps
door closes
phone rings 'hello, king's Morton.'
hello, it's Simone highsmith
from the New York herald.
I'm just calling to confirm my
visit to the school tomorrow.
'Yes.
'The headmaster is asking
if you could bring it forward
'to three o'clock.' No, I can't.
I'm unavailable until
3:30. I'm sorry. 'Right.
'As long as you're aware that
the children will be outside then?'
great. As I told him, my article
is about British children at play.
'Ok, I'll let him know.'
Thank you so much.
See you tomorrow. 'Goodbye.'
bye.
Phone rings
'hello?'
albie, can you talk?
'Yeah, briefly. What is it?'
I need the bloody passport. Door unlocks
'midday, at the caf.' All
right, lunchtime. Got it.
- Albie, can you...?
- Joan?
'Joan?'
forgot my cigs. What did alb want?
Nothing, really.
I mean, just confirming
the meet with Paul.
It's gonna be ok.
What?
Nothing. I was just
gonna say... You love me?
You're finally gonna admit it?
No, not today!
- Morning.
Toilet flushes
morning. Morning.
Joan.
We're still on for the, er,
stock take tomorrow lunchtime?
Course.
Val. What can I do you for?
1920s cigarette case?
Absolute steal at £15.
My husband and your wife.
What about 'em?
They've been meeting up... "For work".
Well, Joan's in the
business. You know that, val.
So, do you want to buy something?
Door slams
no-one else. Scope it out Sunday week.
Haven't heard from me
unless there's a problem.
All right. No fuck-ups, please.
Albie.
Hello. How you doing?
Just hand it over.
Please.
Sorry, I'm stressed. Yeah,
well, doing a job on bail
I'm not going to prison.
I'm not losing Kelly. All right.
Anything I can do to help?
It's just the timings are
so tight. For getting Kelly.
I have to be at the
school tomorrow at 3:30
so she's outside playing, 3:40 latest.
Right, thanks.
Better go, or we'll be late for Paul.
You get there first. I'll
walk round the block.
So, boisie's cool about Kelly?
I'm telling him tonight. Jesus Christ.
Look, just... just, please,
don't screw this up...
Or he'll pull out the whole job.
You think I don't
fucking know that? Jesus.
Paul applauds bang on time. Yeah.
Right, is everyone clear on the plan?
Me and boisie break in, scare Bernard.
Paul stays with him while you
and me do the safe, clear the shop.
You work in total
silence. Fast as we can.
Slow and steady. No rush.
No, we need to be in and out,
Paul. I don't wanna fuck around.
I get it, Joan. No fucking around.
Look, I'll be in the alley.
Soon as we're loaded, we
head to wrentham street.
Where the getaway car will
be. We share out the gear, then...
Then you drive here. Directions.
Albie clears throat there's a caravan.
Bit basic, but it's out of the way.
Stay there till dawn,
then head to newhaven.
Why can't we get an earlier ferry?
We need to wait for
albie's man to be on shift.
So... one o'clock, I'll give albie the nod,
he drives round the back, two
of you break in straight away.
We wait till half past.
Five past.
What if he decides to serve another
customer? Go out for a sandwich?
He won't. We need
to build in some slack.
Look, I can control
Bernard, all right? Trust me.
He's got a point, Joan. It's
not worth cutting it too fine.
You want me to cuddle up
to Bernard for half an hour?
Does that not bother you, no?
Quarter past, then? Fuck's sake!
I know what I'm doing.
Look, I think we should
trust Joan on this.
Should we?
Yeah. It's her job.
Thanks, alb. Five past one.
If we're done?
Where the hell are you going? Work.
If that's ok with you?
Fuck's up with her?
Gun clicks.
Boisie?
I need to talk to you.
I was just about to tell you, I promise.
Before the heist or after?
No, that's... that's not fair.
Job's off.
Hey.
Leave me alone.
I mean, what was I
supposed to do, Boise?
If you really, really want something...
Why don't you get it?
It's not about what you want.
It's about Kelly, what's best for her.
Is it?
Or is it what's best for
boisie fucking hannington?
What?
Insecure, jealous...
Prefers paintings to people.
Doesn't trust a soul.
Convinced his own wife is up
to all sorts with his best mate!
Cos you were. No, no, no. No.
No, that's not what this is.
What is it, then? Tell me.
You just don't want her to come.
You'd rather I lost my daughter
than allow her into our life.
Are you crazy?
I'm coming back to get her.
I'm returning as a wanted
man, risking years inside,
and I'm doing that for you.
For you, Joan.
I can't, boisie. I can't... I
can't wait. She'll forget me.
No. I'll lose her. It's already started.
She's... she's happy there. She's settled.
She sits on that.
On that woman's lap.
Do you know how that feels?
It's like a... a blade to my fucking heart.
Joan, listen.
No, I won't. You know why? Cos.
All I want... is to be happy.
Is that so bad?
To want a family?
A home?
What I've never had, you've never had.
This is our chance, boisie.
Door opens, shuts.
Thought I'd find you here.
Your mum gave you up.
You must understand
why I can't do that to kel.
I can't.
I won't.
I'm her mother.
She needs to be with me.
When I was a kid, I
learnt not to need anyone.
Anything at all.
I just wanted to feel safe.
I know.
And I'm fine here.
Then stay.
Or... take a risk.
And if it doesn't work out, that's fine.
But don't spend the rest
of your life... wondering.
Boisie sighs.
Joan sniffles
you're crazy, do you know that?
She chuckles
yeah.
You're stuck with me now. She sniffles.
I love you.
I love you so much.
Joan laughs.
I'm heading off.
Joan.
I dunno, it doesn't feel right.
No, it'll be fine. I've worked it all out.
It's gonna be ok, Boise.
Five past one, you and
Paul storm the back door.
'Paul takes Bernard into the
back while we empty the safe.
'Once the safe's done, we move
to the shop and clear the cabinets.
'It's... it's a good plan, Boise.
'Foolproof.'
Penny for your thoughts?
She laughs worth more than that.
He chuckles.
I hate it when it's quiet. It's so boring.
Do you wanna hear my
theory about this place, Joan?
You listening, Joan? Yeah.
Mondays, the blokes come in
engagement rings if they've
popped the question on the weekend...
Phone rings ..Or little gifts for the missus
if they've had a row.
Tuesdays, dead as a doornail.
Bernard Jones, can I help you?
Joan? Wednesdays, people browsing.
Starts to pick up around
lunchtime. No, that won't be possible.
And Thursdays, normally busy.
Absolutely not. Goodbye.
That was for you. Urgent, apparently.
What? Who was it?
You know you're not
allowed personal calls.
Sorry.
But did he say who it was?
Wouldn't leave a name.
Said he needed to speak
to you about this afternoon.
If you've got other plans,
I can always ask Kirsty
to do the stock take.
No, no, no. I'd never let you down.
Then, er, maybe we should
just close up and push on with it?
No.
We might miss a sale.
True enough.
You haven't even had
your morning coffee.
Look, why don't the
two of you take a break,
and I'll, er, organise the stock?
Good idea.
Just the one sugar, Kirsty.
Can I bring you one, Joan?
No, thanks.
Well done.
Here's your sale, smarty-pants.
Hello, sir. How can I help you?
I saw a ring in that case.
So, Paul's decided he can't
trust you, just pulled out.
Fuck.
We'll have to stand down, set it up again.
No, we can't. I've already cut the wires.
Fucking hell.
Tell albie we need to find someone new.
In an hour? Who?
I don't care. Anyone.
Tell albie to offer a third of the take.
Christ.
I mean, he knows half of
London. He'll find someone.
And we leave that
someone alone with Bernard?
You take care of Bernard,
I'll work with the new guy.
Just find someone, anyone.
Everything ok over here?
Fine. You said you'd come back.
Eternity ring, married a
few months, madly in love.
Never forget a face.
Joan, you try it on for him.
Best way for the gentleman to decide.
I think you should go ahead, sir.
Yes, trust the lady.
It's a big decision.
You won't regret it, I promise.
Your wife... your wife will...
It's an eternity ring.
She'll love you forever.
Are you sure?
Ok, then. You talked me into it.
Excellent.
Final sale before the stock take, Joan.
Mark it down.
We're on.
Knocking.
I left my purse somewhere.
Do you really need it now?
What? I could lend you a tenner.
What did I do with it?
What am I like? Right, off you go.
Bye! Bye.
Shall we start with
the premier collection?
Why don't we just go
straight to the safe?
You go get the ledger. I'll open her up.
Three minutes.
Do you want me to open
the safe? Just a minute.
If you could pick any one
I can't afford diamonds, Bernard.
Present... from me.
I mean, I'd feel bad. Are you sure?
Choose one.
I know you want it, Joan.
Why don't I give you a back rub first?
Stick with her. Follow her orders.
Joan'll love that. You know her?
Yeah, I'm Kelly's dad.
Don't want any trouble,
just my share of the gear.
Go!
We're in. Go!
Joan screams you, out
the back. Go on! Move!
Don't hurt her, please. Open the safe.
What are you doing?
Where are you taking me?
Gary, what the fuck? Go on, then!
Sit down. Keep your gob shut.
Stop fucking about.
Open it. Get out of my face.
Calm down, joanie.
Go in the front. Start on the cabinets.
If you're sure, boss
quiet and fast as you can.
Shit. Fucking keys!
What the hell are you
doing? You said fast.
And quiet. Someone'll hear
us, if they haven't already.
Give me five minutes.
Grab as much as possible.
Stop. Stop! Is that an order, is it?
Stop! I said stop, you fucking idiot.
What do you fucking call
me? It ain't even loaded.
Isn't it?
Out my way. Through there. Now. Now!
Engine revs
get in the Van now. I'm getting my share.
You're getting fuck
all. You ain't in charge.
Get in the Van. Fuck off.
Tell him, Joan. You're in charge.
You fired a fucking gun!
Get in the fucking Van.
No. N-No.
What the fuck?
No, don't!
Boisie grunts and
whimpers no. No, no, no.
Help me. Help me!
It's ok. I'm all right. I'm all right.
Tie, give me your tie. Joan...
What the fuck happened?
Boisie got himself shot.
Fucking drive.
Tyres screech
you fucking liar.
Ok.
Boisie grunts tight.
Tighter. I've cut the wires.
Let us get away, or I will fucking kill you.
Ok. Right. You need to lean on me, ok?
A few steps to the Van. Come on. I can't.
You have to. You have to, boisie.
Come on. Come on.
Joan groans
that's it. Come on. Use your good leg.
You're doing it, boisie.
Keep going. No, keep going.
No, no, you're not trying.
Try again. Try again.
Get Kelly. No. No, I'm
not leaving you. Stop.
Boisie!
Come on. Come on, get up. Please.
Please, try. Please, try. Please, try.
Try.
No. No.
You fucking bastards.
No! Come on.
Hey. Hey.
I'm right here. You're not going.
No, you're not going.
Hey. I'm right here, hey.
Boisie. Boisie.
Boisie. Boise, you wake up. Boisie, no...
No. She sobs boisie! Boisie!
Joan sobs
police sirens wail.
Joan sobs.
You're fine. You're fine. You're fine.
Welcome. I'm Walter
Roberts, the headmaster here.
Simone highsmith, New York herald.
Sorry, it's warm in here.
Thank you for agreeing to the article.
Of course. It's a
subject close to my heart.
Here at king's Morton,
we value play just as much
as time spent in the classroom.
That's great.
I-I actually heard the kids on the way in.
Is it afternoon play now?
For another few minutes.
We might just be able to catch them.
Hopscotch. It's a
traditional English game.
Do you know it? Miss highsmith?
Sure, yes, it's popular. May I? Of course.
Now, girls, we have a visitor
all the way from america.
- Say hello.
- Hello.
Come on girls, speak up. Hello.
Maybe some of the older
girls might be less shy?
Good idea. I'll find you a couple to talk to.
Thank you.
What's your name? What do you mean?
Come on.
Listen carefully, kel. Don't
go back to your lessons.
Why is your hair like that, mummy?
Don't worry. It's still me. It's ok.
Listen very carefully.
I need you to meet me by the gate, ok?
I'll explain to you when
I see you, all right?
Here we are. This is poppy. This is Olivia.
Poppy, Olivia, I'm Simone.
Nice to meet you.
Ok, sweetheart?
Shall we have some music? Yeah?
Radio crackles
come on, kel, sing along!
Dial tone rings
'hello. Alb, is that you?'
it's Joan. Where is he?
You tell me.
I've just got in and found a
note saying, "I've gone abroad."
"Don't expect to hear
from me for a while."
'What the fuck is going on, Joan?'
if he does call, will you
give him a message?
'Tell him I'm looking for him.' Joan.
'Joan.'
I'm gonna fucking destroy him.
It smells funny.
We're only gonna be here till tomorrow.
And then we're gonna get on a boat,
and we're gonna drive
all the way to the sunshine.
Is boisie coming with us?
Why?
Kelly, I need you to be a good girl.
Just do what I tell you, ok?
Not asking me any questions. Is that ok?
Shall I find you a colouring book
so you can do some drawing?
'Boisie! Boisie!'
mummy?
Mummy, I've finished.
Kel, it's brilliant. That's me.
And is that peanuts? Yes.
And, look, there's me next to you. No.
That's mama sue, my other mummy.
Joan sobs
mummy, stop it. Stop crying.
Look, why don't you go and
take your lipstick off, yeah?
There's tissues in my bag
inside. And take off that silly wig.
Go on.
Joan sobs.
'It's already started.
She's... she's happy there.'
'it's like a...' No.
'A blade to my fucking heart.'
she sniffs and sobs.
Mummy! Mummy! Joan gasps
god. God. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, kel. I'm so
sorry. What have I done?
It's all right. I'm scared, mummy.
I'm here. It's all right, kel. She sighs.
I'm so sorry.
I want to go home.
I need to keep you safe.
So you're gonna go and...
And stay with mama sue now.
I've got to go away.
I'm so sorry.
I love you so much, kel.
Never, ever forget that.
Bye, Kelly. Bye, mummy.
Bye.
'All I wanted was my own family.'
now without Kelly, boisie...
There's no point.
So, how'd you get out
so soon? You know me.
Good behaviour.
You got my money?
Yeah.
You can put your feet up
now. Going back to work.
Necking stones, snatching rings?
No. No more little cons.
I'm gonna build myself a bloody empire.
So, you, er, wanna talk business? Pfft.
You think I'd work with you again?
You left us in a fucking alley.
I'm done with men.
Just go. Fuck off.
Be careful... Joan.
And you. Watch your fucking back.
Subtitles by accessibility@itv.Com