'Brass in pocket' by pretenders.
Hello?
Yes, I'll be straight down.
Yeah, checking out this afternoon.
Thank you. Bye.
Fuck's sake. Where the fuck did that go?
'Making your mind up' by bucks fizz
here you go, love.
Thanks, mummy.
K...
E... L-l-y.
Kelly! Brilliant girl!
You're crazy!
Car horn outside
happy birthday.
Gary!
Gary, you're on the
wrong side of the road.
Am I?
Move away, Gary. Gary!
Tyres screech, horn beeps
my god! Slow down,
slow down, slow down,
please, please, please.
Look in the back.
Happy birthday, joanie. My god.
Gary!
She squeals
where did you get it?
Come on, Joan, you know not to ask.
Yeah, about a telly,
but this... And the car.
Tyres screech
'tainted love' by soft cell
are you done with this?
Thank you.
Bourbon?
And one for yourself.
How many times?
I don't know. Tell me again.
We could just be friends, you know.
I think you want more
than that, I can see it.
Salesman?
Same again?
Music fades Gary?
Gary?
Door opens and closes
where have you been?
You left kel on her own.
Where have you been?
I've got to be on my toes for a bit, love.
What did you do?
Gary, what the hell did you do?
She gasps
cheap.
Who is she?
Maybe I want to screw a bird
who don't expect me to mind her kid.
Your kid.
You keep your trap shut!
What can I say? I don't know anything.
Door opens I'll change the locks!
He scoffs.
We'll have to smash it with a rock again.
You know what, I think I've got it.
Kelly gasps what's that? I don't know.
Kelly giggles all right.
You see how many you
can find, see if you can find
the prettiest, prettiest shell, ok?
Ok.
I'll be on the bench, ok?
Find the prettiest one you can.
Cute kid.
Thanks.
I thought you lived in ashford.
Have car, can travel.
Shouldn't you be selling windows?
You trying to soften me
up for a set right now?
He scoffs
who are you?
Just a friend, someone to chat to.
You're undercover.
Slow down.
Look, I know Gary's done a big job,
ok, he's in trouble. Bollocks.
Talk to me.
Ok? Tell me where he is.
I can help you, I can keep you safe.
He's away on business.
Come on. Sports cars and fur coats,
it's not rocket science, Joan.
Oi, talk to me. For her sake.
I'm not a grass.
Joan, come on.
Kelly, it's getting cold, let's go home.
Or shall we go and get
a hot chocolate, yeah?
Yeah.
Creaking
kel?
Kelly?
Are you all right?
Creaking.
Gary's not here.
He... he hasn't told me
anything, I swear. You're...
You're wasting your time.
Get up.
He owes us money, Joan.
Where is he? I don't know.
She whimpers where is he?
If I knew, I'd tell you.
You need to open up.
She whimpers.
I said open it.
Wider.
Now close.
In the morning, your brains blown out,
imagine little Kelly's face.
He's got a girlfriend, he stays out,
he'll be back in the morning.
She breathes shakily.
Well, let's hope Gary comes
home for breakfast, then.
Otherwise, it will be
little Kelly who gets it.
Door closes she sobs.
Kelly.
Kelly, wake up. Come on, love.
You need to wake up, all right?
We're going out.
But your nose is bleeding.
It's all right. Get dressed.
Good girl.
Where are we going now?
A safe place.
It's ok.
So, you've just been made homeless,
and you want to place your
daughter in emergency care?
I don't want to, obviously.
Of course.
And there's nowhere
else you can go for a bit?
Your parents'?
Get hold of my old file,
see what I went through as a kid.
What about a sibling?
I've got a sister in London,
but I can't take her there.
Is there something else going on, Joan,
that I need to know about?
No.
Is Kelly in danger?
No, no. Not at all.
Just, er... Just... Need...
need a bit of a break.
It's ok.
That's what we're here
for, to help people in trouble.
And it's only till I find a new flat,
and that won't be long, I promise.
A few weeks.
We're gonna place her in a foster family.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, I wouldn't
want her in a home.
I was in a home as a kid.
And it's definitely just temporary.
I-I won't... I won't lose her, will I?
Promise me I won't lose her.
Of course not.
Now, tell me a bit about Kelly.
She, er... She loves beans and nuggets.
She'll notice if you sneak any veg in.
She hates scratchy jumpers.
She's a good girl.
She won't complain.
Look after her.
Course we will.
There's your bag.
Come here.
Hey.
My mummy... gave me this ring
so I'd remember her
when we were apart.
Look how pretty it is, it sparkles.
I want you to stay, mummy.
I know.
Knock at the door
hi. It's time to go.
Come here.
You'll be all right.
Kelly sobs will you be all right, mummy?
Of course I will, sweetheart.
Come here.
Don't go, mummy, please don't go!
'Time' by culture club
what's happened? Are you all right?
Yeah, yeah. It's nothing.
Where's Kelly?
Hello, are you all right? Come over.
She's in foster care for a bit. She, er.
I have to keep her
safe, they can't find her.
Why? What's happened?
Gary's got gangsters after him.
Don't you dare bring
him anywhere near here.
It's fine, I've left him, I've left him.
I just... I've got nowhere else to go.
Nance.
You can sleep on the
settee for a few days,
until you find somewhere else.
Thank you.
You can borrow my
clothes, help out in the salon.
But none of your bloody chaos.
I mean it, Joan. Upstairs.
Don't worry, she's a
good kid, she'll be ok.
She sniffs
it's the chemicals.
You need to make a
fresh start for you and kel.
Nancy.
What?
I'm gonna try.
I know. New hairdo will help.
Bit quiet, aren't you, sweetheart?
Smile.
That wasn't hard, was it?
You're not so bad
when you make an effort.
Aw, thank you.
You're like my missus,
just need a little nudge now and then.
She's got an excuse - we've got kids,
she's knackered.
Product?
Yeah. It's come out nice, Dave.
You've made a nice job of that.
I'll leave you with Nancy to pay up, ok?
She sighs I've just lost
one of my best clients.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Why can't you just be normal?
I'm an O'Connell.
So am I. No bloody excuse.
Phone rings
hello?
Yeah, sure. I'll just get her for you.
It's for you. Social worker.
Hi.
Fine, thanks. How's kel?
I'm desperate to see her.
See you. Night.
See you, girls. Have a good one.
Night.
Feet are killing me. Yeah.
Tenner.
Fiver, then, please.
End of the week, you'll
get paid like everyone else.
All right, just the train fare.
The foster mum said
I can visit tomorrow.
I need you here tomorrow,
we're fully booked.
But Kelly's expecting me now.
I'm really sorry, but you
should have checked.
You can't just have a
day off whenever you like.
Engine starts.
She chuckles
kel! Come here.
Come here.
Aw!
My girl, I'm sorry.
You've had your hair cut.
Do you like it?
I like it.
What's she doing? She's walking in.
And who's that?
Here you go. Nice hot drink.
Thank you.
Have you cut Kelly's hair?
Just a bit. We just
thought we'd try a change.
She looks pretty, doesn't she?
Do you like it, kel?
I like how you do it, mummy.
I-I-I gave her a ring.
We put it on a chain, didn't we?
So you'd always be close to mummy.
Thank you for being...
She's a lovely little girl.
Phone rings.
Sue answers the phone.
Sirens.
Fuck.
All right?
Door lock clicks.
What are you doing here?
Saw your name on the custody sheet.
I had to see Kelly.
What, by nicking a car,
ruining your chances
of getting her back?
Dumb blonde.
What do you want, Joan?
A normal life.
Get Kelly back.
Then tell that to the magistrate, right?
Tell him you're gonna get a job and a flat,
that you're gonna do
everything right from now on.
Like he'll believe me. I'll write something.
I'll back you.
Why would you do that?
Cos I think it's true.
Just... just don't report
me to the social, please.
Cell door closes door lock clicks.
'I know that I've been stupid, reckless,
'but it won't happen again.
'I mean, I haven't been
in trouble with the law
'since I was a teenager in care.'
and I love my daughter so much.
It would be.
Disastrous for her if I were
to get a custodial sentence.
And I fully intend on getting a job
and a place of my own to support us.
I just... I just need a
chance to prove myself.
Er, where have you been?
Sneaking back in like that.
To see Kelly.
I, stayed at a mate's.
I'm really sorry. I should've called.
I'm sorry, Nance. But look.
How was it?
Brilliant.
Sad.
I can't have you working
in the salon, Joan.
You're not reliable enough.
Find a new job, something
you're interested in.
You're more likely to stick at it that way.
Indistinct chatter
where are you heading? Into Mayfair.
You're heading to Mayfair?
Actually, I do need to look
for a present for my mother.
Shall we go together? Let's.
I was thinking a piece of jewellery.
A diamond ring or something.
I'm looking for a present for my mother.
Mother.
I'm looking for a very
special present for my mother.
Can I help you, madam?
Yes, I'm looking for a special present
for my mother - a diamond.
Absolutely. Do you see
any you particularly like?
They're all so beautiful.
How does one choose?
Would you like some advice?
Yes. How kind.
I want to know the
details of what I'm buying.
Of course.
Here you can see our diamond rings,
which we grade using the four cs
the carat, the clarity,
the colour and the cut.
Just there, you'll notice
what we call the scintillation.
- 'That's the sparkle a stone.
- Diamond, in this case
'emits when it's moved,
'and it's most visible in bright light.'
I've come about the job in the paper.
O levels? References?
No. But I'm keen.
Well, I don't need a Dolly bird.
I'm not. I know all about diamonds.
The four cs - the carat,
the clarity, colour, cut.
Tell me about the cut.
Well, the grade of the
cut is measured against
three different types of reflections.
Which are?
Brilliance, fire and scintillation.
Tell me about the scintillation.
Well, that's the sparkle a
diamond emits when it's moved.
That's most visible in bright light,
so that's why you have the contrast
of the bright lights on your cases.
Where did you learn that?
In books.
I'm interested.
I'll give you a month's trial.
We do have a very, very special
emerald and diamond
necklace in our collection.
Mrs Asher.
How lovely to see you.
I do hope Joan is looking after you.
She's charming.
I'd love to see that special necklace.
Well, miss foley can show
you our premier collection.
Joan, I think you're ready.
Miss foley sighs
there's the key.
Thank you.
Drawer unlocking.
Would you like to try it on?
I don't want to take all this fur off.
Let me see it on you.
Stunning. I'll take it.
Excellent.
This way, mrs Asher.
Joan, you can take it off now.
Door opens.
Gary, what are you doing here?
Looking good, joanie.
You can't be in here. No, it's all right.
Please. Outside.
Come on, joanie. Come on.
Joanie... go on, let me...
Get off me! I mean it.
Fuck off, you fucking psycho!
Joan? Joan, what's going on?!
Get out of here, Gary.
You've always hated me, Nancy.
No, Gary! No, no, no!
I'm calling the police.
Come on, then! Gary! Gary, leave her!
Leave her alone.
Fuck off.
Go back up. I can handle this.
Are you sure? Go.
Girlfriend threw you out, did she?
Fuck off.
Get out. I want nothing
more to do with you.
What about Kelly?
You don't give a shit about Kelly.
I want to see Kelly!
No, you don't, Gary. Now fuck off!
He spits
be careful, Joan.
Door closes.
Packed you a bag.
Thanks, Nance.
Sorry for all of the, er... chaos.
I've packed undies,
pyjamas and some makeup.
You don't have to leave. Not like this.
You've put up with enough.
Sure you can afford to stay
in a hostel till you get paid?
I'll be fine.
Ok?
You're in early.
It's 8:15.
Told you to come in at midday.
We're doing the stock take tonight.
Forgot.
Well, I mean, I don't mind
working a couple of hours extra.
Look and learn, Linda. Look and learn.
Mr Jones, can I ask you something?
You can call me Bernard.
Is there any way that I could
get an advance on my wages?
Bernard. Bernard.
Have to see how we get on
at the stock take, won't we?
Night.
Door lock clicks.
Lock ourselves in, shall we?
Can be tricky, that.
Here you are. Let me help you.
Lock clicks I thought
we'd start at the back...
With our loose stones.
I've already opened the safe.
Why don't we start in here
with the premier collection?
All right.
'Emerald and diamond earrings. 50,000.'
diamond fringe necklace.
60,000. That's it.
Sapphire and diamond earrings.
25,000.
Would you like to try it?
I think we should push on.
Somewhere to go?
No.
Boyfriend to see?
There are no cameras out the back.
Let me freshen up.
She sighs
fuck's sake.
Water flushing.
Joan, what are you doing?
One minute.
The, er... The painters have arrived.
Down below.
Sorry, Bernard. Not feeling great.
No. Well.
Maybe we can postpone
the stock take till next week.
I'll see you on Monday morning.
You take care of yourself.
Double vodka and orange, please.
Coming up.
1.40, please.
Sorry, mate, I'm gonna be short.
I'll get it.
Stick it on the tab. All right, sure.
I never accept drinks from strange men.
Strange?
Yeah, I'd say.
Thanks anyway.
You could always pay me back.
Just round the corner.
Bring you the 1.40 tomorrow.
Deal.
'Wicked game' by Chris isaak.
It's been a tough day.
Yeah? What do you do?
I'm a thief.
Fancy another?
"boisie."
Holy fuck.
'Take five' by Dave brubeck.
She gasps.
Yeah, it's walnut. Mid-19th century.
Yeah, escutcheons inlaid at
a later date, though, I'd say.
It's in my warehouse,
so I'll bring it in if you let
me know when you're coming.
Thanks. Right, bye.
Morning. Hello.
How are you feeling?
Fine. Fresh as a Daisy.
Just making coffee.
So, where do you get it all from?
I've just been doing it for years, really.
I know people, people who know people.
Auctions, furniture sales.
Do you ever buy jewellery?
Stolen?
Why would you say that?
You just walked out of
your job at a jeweller's.
Wild, crazy guess.
All right. What else did I say last night?
You're unemployed and homeless,
you've just lost your kid,
but you're gonna be rich.
Well, thanks for the coffee.
If I did have something to sell... What?
Some stones. Loose.
Well, I'd need to have a look first.
Why should I trust you?
Got any other options?
How'd you get 'em out?
Grabbed 'em from the
safe, necked 'em, walked.
You've got some balls, girl.
It was an impulse. I've
never nicked before.
I mean, nothing big.
Why now?
Means to an end.
You enjoyed it, though.
Yeah.
So, can you sell 'em for me?
Might take a few weeks.
Why?
Well, gotta find you the right fence,
get you the best price.
Look, I told you, I've got nothing, right?
I need cash now.
So.
Would you do a bit more work, then,
get yourself back on your feet?
I mean a job for me.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Proper job. Not necking
stuff and legging it.
Yeah, I'll do whatever you want.
I wouldn't promise that.
I'm a hard worker. That's what I mean.
Excellent.
Hair of the dog? Can you face it?
Course I can.
Think you and I are
gonna get along, Joan.
It's just work.
Yeah.
And it's just one job.
Yeah, I know.
If you rip me off, I'll fucking kill ya.
Snap.
Subtitles by accessibility@itv.Com