Bring it up
about six more feet.
Okay, go ahead
and start dropping it.
Whoa. Whoa!
Class is over.
What's going on? Who are you?
I'm a doctor. Did you have
a corneal transplant five years ago?
Yes.
Every other patient who had
a transplanted organ from that donor
is either dead or dying.
You got a purse?
I feel fine.
I don't mean to scare you,
but so did the others.
One living, one almost dead,
four fully dead.
Nothing in common
except their donor.
Carl got a new heart and lung,
liver kills him.
Tibalt got a new liver,
lung killed him.
Holly got a new kidney,
her heart blows up.
And Frank, the old guy
gasping for breath upstairs,
he got an intestinal graft,
his pancreas is failing.
All within eight months
of each other.
And in each case,
serious complications
came on suddenly
and without warning.
Which means arrhythmia,
massive pulmonary embolus,
or cerebral bleed.
What did Wilson do for me?
If the donor had an infection
that somehow slipped by screening,
it could lay dormant.
Five organs systems hit,
would need five infections for it
to somehow slip by screening.
Oh, sure, he made me laugh
on a rainy day,
made me see the colors
I never knew...
None of the donated organs were hit.
Means whatever they got
came from the donor's blood.
That wouldn't help us
narrow down what...
It narrows down who.
Corneal transplants are bloodless.
Means Apple's gonna be fine.
You secure enough in that
theory to send her home?
Guess we could wait till we figure out
what's wrong with Frank.
On the other hand,
Gilbert Gottfried makes me laugh,
and how many colors are there, really?
Once you've got
red, blue and green...
He paid for your lunch, liked
monster trucks and was your conscience.
Autoimmune disease.
ANA at autopsy
of all four victims were normal.
Wouldn't cover vasculitis.
Henoch-Schonlein purpura.
Antiphospholipid antibodies normal.
Then that leaves cancer.
Cancers have names.
They have a progression.
They affect specific organs.
Bone cancer can't turn into
liver cancer. Forget cancer.
It's cancer.
It's not cancer.
You're right, of course.
What was I thinking?
No single type of cancer
blew up three organs in the chest
while also herniating
the fighter's brain stem.
- The fighter's irrelevant.
- You don't like coincidences?
It'd be a coincidence
if six transplant recipients
had nothing else
wrong with them,
like being an idiot, which leads
to getting your head knocked off.
The others had cancer.
Four autopsies and about 1,000 lab tests
say it's not cancer.
Redo the 1,000 tests
and the four autopsies.
Taub and Kutner, check out the donor,
find out which cancer...
He didn't die of cancer. His head got
chopped off in an industrial accident.
Find out which cancer
would have killed him.
Check the home and office
for carcinogens, toxins...
He's been dead for four years.
I assume his home has been rented
to someone else by now.
Find out which cancer
killed them.
Did I forget you?
You can check out
the patient's eye.
You can put this on Dr. O'Shea.
And some chips.
- Forget your wallet, House?
- No.
I'll take care of it.
Check.
Why are you following me?
Word is
you're into monster trucks.
- My kids like it.
- But not you?
Predator's okay, but I think
the California Crusher is over-rated.
Are you checking me out?
You're astute.
- No.
- How many pills did you just take?
Vicodin, opioids, some B12.
Need a little kick
in the afternoon.
You got a problem with that?
I think I'm falling in love.
Her right eye's failing.
No, it's not.
Everyone else's transplanted
organs were fine.
Means her eye is fine.
We need to remove the eye.
It's her only working eye.
We could remove the other one,
but since it's not killing her,
I thought
this way was less insane.
Do you have some ethical problem
with what I'm doing
that you can express
in a unique way,
which might actually make me think
that I'm wrong,
even though
I'll never admit it?
Yes.
You are funny.
The problem's not in her eye.
It's in her head.
You want to come over and watch
Prescription Passion
at my place tonight?
You know I'm not gay, right?
Neither am I.
If you don't want to have sex,
that's cool with me.
I'm not coming over
to your home.
I'll grow on you.
"L-P-E..."
Do I have to be
in the same room with him?
Whatever he's got, you've got.
Fifth line.
Are you sure?
Pretty sure. Fifth line.
Am I going to die?
Could we talk about something
besides you for a moment?
Like, maybe, the fifth line.
"F-E-O-S-P."
Damn.
I'm sorry.
We need to remove your eye.
MY eye?
A moment ago, you thought you were
dying. Blind is actually good news.
Unfortunately, he's wrong.
You just did the test...
But she didn't squint.
Which means the eye
thinks it's fine.
It was wrong.
I know. But the eye doesn't think.
The brain thinks.
Which means thinking's wrong,
the brain's wrong.
Which means
it's spread to the brain.
Which means it's too late
for us to remove the eye.
Which means we're gonna have to
remove your whole head.
Don't worry, it doesn't hurt.
Hallucination.
That's a brain thing, right?
Five hundred different things
can cause hallucination,
doesn't mean it's neurological.
It does if one of the other
organ recipients also had a brain issue.
Did he just drop his hands?
No. None of them
had brain issues.
If his pupils dilated,
if his pupils were fixed,
if there's a twitch...
He got hit in the head, he died.
No mystery,
that was your point.
Yesterday. You live, you learn.
Who shot this?
The guy who runs the gym
has a camera.
Uploads the nasty stuff online.
Can't see the dead guy's face.
If I can't see his face,
can't see the twitch,
can't see the pupils...
We know the tennis player
had a heart problem.
We can maybe tie that
to the tuba player's lungs,
and then somehow
tie both those things
to the construction
worker's liver,
and then possibly meander over
to Frank's pancreatic failure.
But nothing causes
simultaneous brain and heart problems.
Cancer made no sense.
The head and heart
make less than no sense.
That makes no sense.
I know. I was making a point.
Oh, good,
I thought you were an idiot.
Why are you talking?
Oh, what? The guy doing manual labor
can't have an opinion?
I might be a genius
who just happens to have
a passion
for fixing coffee machines.
No, I'm obviously not,
but that's rude
to make assumptions
about people.
Donor's history came up clean.
Did he just laugh?
No, no, I sneezed.
He's a genius coffee repairman.
A coffee repairman
who wears Argyle socks?
I thought I already talked about
not judging.
What kind of idiot wears Argyle socks
with construction boots?
I'm not an idiot.
I'm just not good at disguises.
Who is he?
He's apparently a very bad
private investigator.
Why is he pretending
to fix the coffee machine?
Because I wanted to find out
what you guys found out
before I found out
what he found out,
so I can find out
if I need a private investigator.
So, new.
The donor has no history
of unusual infections,
no international travel
in the 12 months...
Well, seriously,
that's how I sneeze.
He was in Madrid
and the Bahamas.
Credit card receipts
showed no...
The girlfriend paid.
There is no girlfriend.
She was his high-school sweetheart.
High-school sweetheart is married
to his best friend.
I know.
She had a kid four years ago.
Timing fits.
She's still pretty hot, though.
You find out anything medical?
Kid has a tummy ache.
Also, the dead guy
was exposed to mercury,
mold and anhydrous perchloric acid
because their sex pad was
next to a garage that was demolished
after those toxins were found.
Oh, yeah, that will be $2,300.
I'll get you a check.
No, I don't take checks.
You think I'm gonna
stop payment?
- Aren't you?
- Of course I am! $2,300? It's insane.
Actually, that price includes
footage of the boxing match
from four different angles.
30 percent of the crowd
paid by credit card. I got their names.
Four of them
had digital cameras,
which I composited like NASA did
for the pics of Mars.
You know, the rovers and all that.
Pupils were dilated.
But he didn't drop his hands,
means he maintained
muscle tensity...
Say it.
You were right.
God, that was petty of me.
He maintained muscle tensity,
but was momentarily distracted
when he got hit.
That's a temporal lobe seizure.
Does that Pl guy mean
we don't have to break
into people's homes anymore?
It's the whole reason
you went to medical school.
I'm not gonna take
that away from you.
He's better than we are.
He costs more.
I'm gonna biopsy the brain.
No.
Say it.
You were right. But, no.
Temporal lobe controls
speech, hearing, memory.
She loses those things,
she's gonna be a terrific date,
but beyond that...
We cut out a piece of it,
good chance she's a vegetable,
nothing to hear, nothing to say,
nothing to look back on.
You're right.
She has so much to live for.
Do we have another patient who is
almost finished with all their living?
So it's okay to stab his brain
because he's old?
No, it's okay to stab his brain
because he's dead if you don't.
Get the widow to say yes.
No.
The lung inflammation is a complication
of the pancreatic failure,
which is reversible.
This is actually
his best chance.
If we can find
out what's wrong...
How can a test
that will probably kill him...
I didn't say...
You said it was extremely risky.
What does "extremely" mean?
Please.
I'm sorry. I can't.
I have a husband.
I have a two-year-old daughter.
Her name is Julia.
You'd be saving her mother.
I think you're lying.
You haven't had one visitor, not
one phone call since you've been here.
Does she have a child?
No, but her life is still worth...
More than my husband's?
I lied to save my life.
Wouldn't you?
Not at another human being's expense.
No, you just rob me
of my only chance
so your husband can struggle to breathe
for a few more days.
Just shut up!
I don't want to hear...
- Ladies...
- ...from you anymore.
- You want to hate me...
- Shut up!
- ...so you won't feel guilty.
- Frank!
Give me a scalpel.
Frank!
He's coding.
Clear.
- Frank!
- Clear.
Clear.
- Did you get the consent?
- No.
Tell Foreman to get it.
Old people are scared of black people.
It won't matter.
Patient's dead.
Save the brain.
I don't need consent for an autopsy.
Well, at best, we're gonna bat
one for six on this one.
Thin slices
through the parietal
and temporal lobes were clean.
Occipital and frontotemporal
regions were also...
Brain's clean. Moving on.
To where? We've gone from
making no sense to making less sense,
and then taking
a step backwards.
Each of these people were killed
by one thing that attacked one organ.
But never the same organ.
Could the donor have had
two things wrong?
Or six things wrong?
Metabolic diseases specialize,
everything else specializes,
but cancer plays the field.
You're back to cancer?
Metastasis is just a fancy word
for "screws around."
- Any type of cancer?
- I don't know.
There would be
evidence of cancer.
There is.
We just haven't found it, yet.
You need it to be cancer so you
have an excuse to talk to Wilson.
Give me something else that explains
this constellation of patients,
then you can call me an ass.
I didn't call you an ass.
Perforated intestine.
If this thing started as normal bacteria
living in the intestines,
but got into a blood vessel
through a vascular anomaly
in the bowel wall,
then they would affect every organ
through the bloodstream.
Screws up everything.
For everyone.
Okay, it's a long shot.
It is possible I'm an ass.
Ironically, we need to do
a colonoscopy to confirm.
We checked Apple inside and out
when she came in. She's clean.
Anomaly would have
to be intermittent
or they all would
have died within a day.
If she starts getting abdominal pains,
shove a tube up her rear
before it can get away.
And test anyone else
with stomach pain.
Everyone else is dead.
Not everyone.
The one thing this donor gave
to each of these people was his DNA.
Anyone else have his DNA?
You want to do a colonoscopy
on a healthy four-year-old?
She has a tummy ache.
If Kutner's right,
it's not a tummy ache.
It's a fatal brain or heart or lung
or liver or pancreas ache.
I'm not gonna scare the hell
out of the poor kid's mom
because of a long-shot corollary
to a long-shot theory.
Fine. Tell her the truth. Then ask
if Daddy knows who the real daddy is.
Does she have to be awake?
We need her to
tell us when it hurts.
She'll get over it.
Your husband might not have.
What if a kid wants ice cream?
Sign outside says "closed."
Dr. O'Shea's not right for you.
What did you find out?
Why are you investigating him?
Because I need to know
if he lends money interest-free.
What did you find out?
I want some ice cream.
Not until you learn to read!
You're supposed
to trust friends.
I don't know the guy.
I've got no logical reason...
To be his friend? Have you never seen
an Afterschool Special?
That is part of the pleasure
of friendship.
Trusting without
absolute evidence,
and then being rewarded
for that trust.
You're taking pictures of a guy
who's having an affair
with his own sister
and you're lecturing me
about the rewards of trust?
There are two types
of people that hire me.
No, actually, there are three types
of people that hire me,
but the third type's irrelevant
to the point I want to make.
Do you have a special rate plan
for being a pain in the ass?
One type wants to find
out that they're right,
one type wants to find
out that they're wrong.
Which type am I?
You're the third type.
You lead with
the irrelevant types?
You're the type who doesn't care
if you're right or wrong
because they've hired me
to investigate the wrong person.
That's an actual type?
You want me to
check out Wilson.
You want to find out if he's...
How do you know about Wilson?
What do I do for a living?
You've been checking me out?
Have I been paying for that?
So far you haven't
paid for anything.
You want to find
out if he's pining.
You want to find out
if there's something about him
that will tell you
he's going to come back.
Or something you can use
to make him come back.
Is there?
No. No, there's nothing. Sorry.
That will be $900.
I gotta go.
I'll get you a check.
Colonoscopy was clean.
Then that just leaves cancer.
The fact that the kid's
colonoscopy was negative
doesn't prove anything.
Yes, the fact that it
didn't prove anything
didn't prove anything.
Excellent point.
We don't know
if the kid inherited anything.
Even if she did, Kutner's theory
is that the thing's intermittent.
The opening would have to be open
shortly before death.
Unfortunately, we can't know
when shortly before death is
until shortly after death,
and that seems like an obstacle.
What if there was
a way around that?
Then we're kind of
all sweating over nothing.
Not around death,
around death as an obstacle.
We need to see
his colon at work.
You do know what
"death" means, right?
Without a living system,
there's not enough pressure
to get fluid all the way up.
Life, we can't create, yet,
but pressure's easy.
We use the same
high-pressure water jet
we use to test
cardiac workload.
I mean, he's not gonna be awake
to tell us where it hurts, but...
- That's not gonna...
- Do it.
It's kind of stuck.
It's more than stuck.
That bowel's been dead
for six hours.
No matter what you shoot up there,
it's closed.
- This is nuts.
- It's adjustable.
It's working.
Yeah. Wow.
Well, not much.
Increase the pressure.
The endoscope is bowing.
Push on his stomach.
Those are normal bodily fluids.
Yeah. Normal bodily sewage.
Put the pressure back on.
That's the end. No leaks.
Wait, what's that?
It's just dark
because I'm at the end.
What if you're not at the end?
What if it's a core lesion?
Maybe a little more pressure?
Not too much.
If it is the end and we...
It's finally accelerating.
Apple's heart rate
has become irregular.
Breathing is labored.
Colonoscopy's still showing no leaks.
What if it is autoimmune?
What if we don't have conversations
we've already had?
Four out of the five didn't linger.
They got sick and died.
We don't have time to dismiss things
we've already dismissed.
Nothing fits.
See, that's an example of a conversation
we've already had.
She's sick, something fits.
MS?
No!
Okay, from now on,
no one says anything
unless no one
has said it before.
- Where are you going?
- You guys start immunogels on her CSF
to look for hidden
protein markers,
then start sequencing her genes.
I'm going to start treatment.
- Treatment for what?
- Cancer.
It's not cancer. Chemo's toxic.
It's something. Which means
we should treat her for something.
She's fine. Where's her chart?
You rang emergency
to get her chart?
I know, that was bad of me.
But I'm pretty sure the chart's supposed
to be attached to the bed
so that gimp doctors don't have to look
all over the place while patients die.
Thank you so much. And some
peppermint tea when you get a chance?
I need you to sign something.
Consent to chemotherapy.
You found cancer?
No.
Then you have
tests indicating...
- No.
- Then why should I sign it?
That's a good question.
And deserves
a complicated answer.
Placebo effect.
People have confidence in doctors,
they have confidence in diagnoses,
confidence in medicine.
Sometimes they get a little better
just because they think they will.
And that can make us think that
the wrong answer is the right answer,
which is very bad.
So, you do have proof that
it's cancer but you can't tell me
because it might affect
the way I react to the medicine?
If that were true,
and it would certainly make sense,
do you think I could
tell you that it's true?
I was practically blind
before the transplant.
20/200 vision.
Didn't you cover all this personal stuff
with Dr. Foreman?
You don't care
who I used to be?
You're a post-corneal transplant
math teacher.
I deduced that you were
a blind math teacher.
I was an architect.
You gave up architecture
after you could see?
The world was ugly.
You think the world would be
any different if your leg was fine?
No.
You think you'd be any different
if your leg was fine?
I mean, the doctors told me
that my life was going to be
so much better once I could see.
I would date, I would dance.
But the guys I hated dancing
with before, I hated dancing with after.
My parents were still dead.
I was still alone.
You're fun.
You don't seem
all that different.
I haven't given up.
Wilson's got a new job.
Hasn't started yet, but...
So, who are we following?
See that lady up there?
You point at the target?
No. I'm following the one halfway
in-between that point and that point.
Pretty. Who hired you?
No one. I just like her.
You're stalking her?
No, no, I followed her
out of that bookstore back there.
You are stalking her,
just not for very long.
So what else can you tell me
that I might care about?
He attends this grief counseling thing
twice a week
where they go around the room
and cry about who's dead.
Cameron's been to his house
several times.
They just talk about death
and losing loved ones.
What... What are you...
If she turns her head,
she's gonna see
that we're walking
in the wrong direction.
No, no, she won't.
I'm very nondescript.
Well, I'm not.
Well, then,
you stay four feet behind me.
How do you know
what they're talking about?
I'm in the same grief counseling group.
I recently lost my mother.
You'd get laid more often
if you told them you lost a kid.
I didn't lose a kid.
You're a Pl, you can't lie?
I can lie,
I'm just not all that good at it.
Dr. (Buddy's been over to Wilson's twice
and phoned a bunch of times.
Foreman called him.
And the rest of the time.
Wilson's been reading
meditation books
and magazines
about restoring barns.
Are you following me?
- No.
Are you lying?
- Yes.
Lesson one, commit.
It's making me uncomfortable.
Sorry.
You' re very New! -
More uncomfortable.
She's not your type.
Your type is much
stupider than her.
What did Wilson say about me?
You've never come up.
In the grief counseling,
or in the other...
Anywhere. I got three bugs in his home
and one in his car.
If I didn't know you,
I wouldn't even know you existed.
Which is good news.
Only two things you ignore,
things that aren't important,
and things you wished weren't important,
and wishing never works.
She's better.
I could tell at once.
Vomiting is a side effect
of the chemo.
Her heart rate's stabilized,
breathing's good.
Amylase and triglycerides
are both coming down.
I guess it's working.
Can't believe it. It's cancer.
It's not cancer.
Labs show
that our patient is healthier.
She's gonna get sicker.
Then she's gonna die.
- I brought Thai food.
- What did you see in her?
Nothing. It's not cancer,
all the tests say it's not cancer.
They've always
said it's not cancer.
Treatment proves it's cancer.
Treatment proves
it could be cancer.
It's not cancer.
This was your diagnosis.
I never thought it was cancer.
You treated for cancer.
I thought that what she had
acted like cancer.
If it acts like cancer,
maybe it would respond like cancer.
It did. Because it's cancer.
We have to find something that
walks like cancer, talks like cancer,
tastes like cancer,
but isn't cancer.
No, we don't.
Better is better, who cares why?
I do. And so does Tetrault.
Who?
- The dead tuba player.
- Tibalt.
The point is, he died last,
but he died,
which means she's gonna die, too.
Tibalt wasn't receiving
cancer medication.
There's a cancer drug
that's used off-label for arthritis.
There's no record of arthritis.
Did you interview
all the tuba students?
If he had joint pain in his hands,
he couldn't have played.
Then it wasn't in his hands.
Then why do we care
about his students?
One of them is Canadian,
brought him methotrexate,
so he could hide his arthritis.
He already couldn't
afford his insurance.
And that little piece
of business cost me $700.
I'm gonna pass it on
to the patient with a steep mark-up.
This makes no sense.
I know.
She's dead, unless we can find
what's cancer, but not cancer.
Something's missing.
I need an epiphany.
What are you billing out at?
$300 an hour? Here's $400.
There are other oncologists.
Better oncologists.
But I need you.
Let me describe the symptoms,
problems, issues,
and you say whatever
you feel like saying
until something triggers
an idea in my head.
That's not the way it works.
You have a way
of thinking about things.
It's sloppy, it's undisciplined,
it's not very linear,
it complements mine, drives me
down avenues I wouldn't otherwise...
House, please go away.
Cancer, but not cancer,
responds to cancer treatment,
but there's no...
How are you?
Don't do this, please.
Please don't do this.
I'm trying to move on.
By hanging out with Cameron, and talking
to Cuddy, Foreman, but not me?
Lull
I paid a private investigator
to spy on you.
You didn't.
You want to move on from me,
you gotta deal with me, talk to me.
You had no right.
We're not friends anymore.
There's no trust to be breached.
I can have you followed,
I can call you names, tell your secrets.
Foreman did a CT.
Temporal and frontoparietal regions,
normal. Occipital lobe, normal.
I have the right
to walk away from you, House.
There is a world beyond you,
you need to realize that.
And even if you don't,
I'm moving on.
The next time you knock,
I'm not answering.
Nothing yet. Keep talking.
I'm sorry.
You charge me for listening in
on my own conversations?
Yeah, why wouldn't I?
How many friends do you have?
Seventeen.
Seriously? You have a list?
No, I knew this conversation
was really about you,
so I just gave you an answer
so you could get back
to your train of thought.
Well done. I have one. Had one.
Friends are important,
you're gonna miss...
Shut up.
Friends allow you
to not sit in a room by yourself.
Are you charging me for this?
- Are we friends?
- No.
Then, yes.
Do you want to be my friend?
No. You scare me a little.
He thinks if he's not a friend,
he can't talk to me.
We can talk,
we can be two human beings talking.
I'm with him.
Sorry, didn't mean to interrupt.
Yes, you did.
I was in the middle of a sentence.
Yes, I did.
You were repeating yourself.
I'm grateful. Make your point.
It's like that "cancer, but not cancer"
thing you were talking about.
Friends are friends,
customers are customers,
and everything else
is everything else.
If it's not,
nothing is nothing.
And anything can be anything.
10:10, stop the clock.
What?
The world is not as ugly
as she thinks it is.
Cancer, but not cancer.
It doesn't make
any sense, unless...
Brain, but not brain.
Occipital lobe's normal,
but her eyes suck.
That lobe should
be compensating.
Since it's not,
that tells me that
something's in there
that shouldn't be in there.
Brain, but not brain.
Why are you in my office?
To find the anomaly, I need
to chop off the top of her head.
Pretty sure I need
your approval for that.
I'm going to trust
your first instinct.
I'm not usually confused
when you say things like that.
I'm ordering her cancer treatment
to be continued.
Why does it cost $2,300
to fix a coffee machine?
Cancer stem cells are real.
They explain everything.
They're like
embryonic stem cells,
they can become
whatever they want.
The donor had them,
the recipients got them.
They floated around,
they landed on an organ,
got bathed in cytomes,
partially differentiated.
And the key word
there is "partially."
In the tuba player,
they became lung, but not lung.
In the tennis player
they became heart, but not heart.
Stop me if you've
figured out the pattern.
They looked as
if they belonged,
but they weren't
doing their jobs.
And when they were
really needed, boom.
Chemo worked
because the cells were basically tumors,
chemo shrunk them.
You're still gonna say no,
aren't you?
You have no proof.
I have the brain scan.
The normal brain scan.
This is why I need
to take off her head.
To treat?
Or to prove you're right?
To treat.
Chemo's not killing anything,
it's just hiding the real problem.
She's gonna crash.
If we wait until she does crash,
it might be too late.
So, the next step is what?
I say no, and then you do
something to make her crash,
so that I'll think
you've proven your theory?
I would never do that.
No. You won't.
She's crashing.
You might want to check her IV.
From here, it looks like saline
instead of chemo.
Yeah, they look identical.
Still,
you should probably check.
You switched her meds?
How could I? I had no access.
Close her back up.
Do the surgery.
There's no reason.
There's no reason not to.
The stupidly dangerous part
is already over with.
We're ready
with the neural net.
Is that someone's brain?
Except for the part
that isn't brain.
Hey, that's the patient I...
You said she'd be fine.
I'm a better liar than you are.
I swapped her meds.
I mean,
she's got a brain problem?
- I could have killed her.
- Yeah.
The neural net will show us
how fast her neurons are firing.
If there's something in the way,
say brain that's not brain,
her normal neural impulses
will be sucked into a vortex,
because they're
unable to do their job.
The computer
will then process it,
give us a picture
of where to cut.
Cool.
Excuse me?
Sorry, I thought
that's what you wanted to hear.
You think all this is amazingly cool
and you have no one else,
so you're paying a guy to listen.
Sorry, just trying
to save you some cash.
I'm on the clock?
Yeah, why wouldn't you be?
You think this is
interesting to me?
House.
I see it. Can you get it?
I think so.
Turns out you didn't kill her.
Cool. You owe me $5,000.
Why are you just standing there,
Dr. House?
How'd you know who it is?
I can smell you.
Yeah,
like you're a field of roses.
Peppermint tea.
You ever hear
of the boy who cried wolf?
Never really bought that.
I don't care how often a kid cries
he's being eaten by a wolf,
Mom's gonna come running.
The world is ugly.
People kill, they go hungry.
Just proving a point.
People are asses.
Why are you telling me this stuff?
Because the world isn't as ugly
as you think it is.
Your transplanted cornea is fine,
your eye is fine,
but your brain
wasn't working right.
I'm gonna take the gauze
off your eyes now.
- It's gonna be bright.
- I know.
The brain cells
that weren't brain cells
were in the way of processing
visual information correctly.
After the transplant,
you could see, but not see.
I could see, I could read.
Yeah, but it was dull,
or foggy, or gray. I don't know.
What I do know
is that you were not seeing
what everyone else was seeing.
And now? Things are gonna be
beautiful?
Things will be what they are.
How do I look?
You look sad.
Hey.
Is there any way
I could put you on retainer?