You have a patient
waiting. See?
I'm waiting for a follow-up.
If you're talking
about Mr. Casdin,
he has a deceased
sticker on his file,
as do all the other follow-ups you have
scheduled for today.
Whoops!
I had colds all winter.
I've been in this room a while,
but it's spring now, right?
I feel run down,
like maybe something big is coming on.
Run down? Come on, give me
something. Sore throat?
- No.
- Runny nose?
No. I know it
sounds weird, I'm a nurse,
but could you
run maybe a CBC or a thyroid...
Dr. Cuddy, need a consult!
Until she stops seizing,
may as well go back
to my office and get my diagnosis on.
She's urinating on herself.
She's having a seizure.
If she hadn't peed...
It's green.
Interesting.
Thirty-five-year-old woman.
Head of nursing
in an old-age home.
Neurological symptoms and "P"?
Oh, green pee. I get it. Nice.
Neuro is also written in green.
Does that mean she
has green neurological symptoms as well?
From now on, I'm gonna use two colors.
Green indicates irony.
Pseudomonas infection.
She'd have a fever. Toxins?
Why are we taking this case?
Welcome, Your Lordship, we were just
preparing your morning briefing.
Sorry I'm late,
and, yes, green pee does meet
the only diagnostic requirement
you care about.
It's interesting.
But is it worth
us taking this case?
"Us" aren't taking anything.
I'm taking. You're accepting.
Okay, I accept. She has
adult-onset epilepsy,
and she really likes
those St. Patrick's Day beers.
Go check out the house and the office
for toxins and infections.
Her neuro exam was normal,
no subsequent seizures.
It's not life threatening.
It's not important.
Luckily, neither are you.
- You okay?
- Fine.
You and House this morning?
The way you were arguing?
Airing disagreements
doesn't qualify as arguing.
Come on, man, I'm just trying
to help. We're friends.
There are 400
Japanese teenagers
you were playing
Halo with last night
you're better friends with.
Your avatar should ask their avatars
how they're doing.
I consider you a good friend
even if we don't
hang that much outside of work.
I wasn't arguing with him.
You kind of were.
Fine, I was. And you know what?
I was right.
You got conned.
Methylthioninium chloride.
Notable side effect,
green urine.
She's a nurse,
she knows the dosage,
knows how to fake a seizure.
She pees pea soup and gets the warm
attention of doctors all week long.
She's a Munchausen,
and you're her mark.
So your insight is based on
discovering an anti-Alzheimer's drug
at an old-age home.
No good reason it'd be
sitting on her desk.
You ever tried to pee on yourself
in public? It's not easy.
Sorry, I rushed the Jewish frat,
we peed in private.
For good reason. I can spot
a fake seizure,
which means this was real,
which means
her problem is phenol.
Carbolic acid?
Yeah, maybe she
accidentally inhaled some
at a gout treatment
facility, circa 1890.
It's still in some
antiseptic throat sprays.
She's been chugging
it all winter for her colds.
Phenol explains the
seizure and the urine.
She'd have to drink
five bottles a day.
Which is why I'm sure
you won't have trouble
discovering the evidence of it
when you search her house. Bye.
And you can start her on charcoal
hemoperfusion for the phenol poisoning.
Seriously?
Oh, you were lying
about the throat spray.
That does make more sense.
So why are you
wasting Taub's time?
Because I don't want him to know
that I'm wasting my time
disproving his fake
seizure theory. Zip!
Chris?
Chris Taub, right?
Neil Zane.
I was two years under you at
Collegiate High, remember?
Sure.
So you are some big
doctor here now?
I'm a doctor. You?
I was speaking at an econ course
over at the university.
I tripped and banged my leg.
I have some time. Come with me.
Hi. Tests back?
Head CT was negative.
What about a thyroid uptake
or abdominal ultrasound?
Sure. How about I flash
some lights in front of your face first?
You want me to have
another seizure?
We're gonna have to
give up the room
unless we can
confirm a problem.
Okay-
Damn it!
Oh, God.
Please forgive me. I'm so sorry.
What are you worried about? You'll have
maybe a night in jail for fraud.
I have to go tell one of
my employees he was right.
I'm not a Munchausen.
I'm gonna die unless you help me.
You'll have to come up
with something more original.
A cat predicted my death.
Cats make terrible doctors.
Oh, no, wait,
that's women. You're screwed.
How'd you slip?
I've had this
dizziness problem for a while now.
You get checked
for labyrinthitis?
On antibiotics for
a week. No difference.
- Lie down a sec.
- Whoa, whoa, I'm dizzy.
That's normal.
So what are you teaching?
Entrepreneurship.
I'm a CEO. OstTech Industries.
We make medical devices.
All right. You can sit up.
So, did that tell you
anything? Did I...
Oh, my God.
You just cured me.
I figured you had a tiny calcium deposit
in your inner ear.
I just shifted it around.
I've seen three
doctors for this.
- I'm buying you dinner.
- Forget it.
Come on. I'm also an investor in a club,
we'll make it a night out.
Well, I'm married, boring.
I know some married people
who aren't boring.
A few years back,
I was one of them.
Good luck, Neil.
If you're gonna kill me and rape me,
please do it in that order.
This is the cat. Debbie.
Have you heard of her?
Debbie? Sorry, but
without a last name...
She was on the news.
We found her as a kitten.
She lives in the nursing home.
She only sleeps next to people
when they're about to die.
Ten patients in the last year.
And then yesterday, she did it to me
while I was sitting on my couch.
Please. The whole staff, the doctors
even, we all know this is real.
Can you come back later?
I have some business I'm conducting
with the Prince of Nigeria.
Just watch this video.
It'll prove I'm not lying.
Dr. House, I am begging you.
Chest.
Quick, before she goes without attention
for eight seconds.
House.
- She's faking. The cat told me.
- Listen.
Soft breath sounds.
Means it's bronchospasm.
You can't fake that.
Debbie the cat
spends most of her time
just prowling the halls,
the queen of
her own private world.
I gotta say, I don't think
the changes they've made
to American Idol
really work for me.
When Debbie climbs on a patientk bed
and goes to sleep,
we call the loved ones
and tell them to come in.
You wanna treat her?
She's a nut job.
Don't we all have quirks?
Aren't those eccentricities
what make us human?
It's like Debbie's here on Earth
to bring people to the other side.
The doctors that we spoke to
also agree that the cat...
Nut jobs get sick, too.
So you think this
cat story is nonsense,
and you admit she faked her
earlier symptoms,
but you still think
she's actually sick now?
Well, anything would sound ridiculous
if you said it in that voice.
Confirm she's faking
or I'm gonna have to kick her out.
There's that voice again.
I'll give you 24 hours.
Consecutive?
What are you doing?
No, Mr. Bond,
I expect you to die. Bronchospasm. Go.
- Bronchitis.
- No cough, no fever,
and Blofeld didn't
smoke a cigar.
He might have. Dude had a lair,
means he was rich.
Rich people enjoy a good stogie,
sometimes send them as gifts.
Hey, Taub, did that sound like
I was awkwardly trying to segue
into making a point?
- Yes.
- Emphysema.
Lungs were clean on the CT.
Dogs can be trained to predict
diabetic comas, epileptic seizures,
they can smell cancer. It is possible
there's something to this cat.
It's more possible
it was just a coincidence.
Ten million nursing homes,
hundred million pet cats,
one of them was bound
to pick a few winners.
Debbie was able to predict
there was something wrong
with the patient before you were.
Is that a coincidence, too?
Maybe the cat didn't predict anything,
it might have caused the deaths.
We should've
listened to Ted Nugent.
Yeah. It could be cat scratch fever,
or visceral larva migrans.
Maybe it didn't kill everyone
at the nursing home,
but it may be killing Morgan.
The worms hop from the cat to the
cat lady's lungs. I could buy that.
Those cigars were for me.
Hey, that reminds me.
Why is some fancy CEO sending you
a box of Cuban cigars?
Is it related to
your money worries?
What money worries?
Extrapolating from the fact that he's
been skipping his morning muffin,
I'd say that he lost almost all
his money in the market last year.
I'm on a diet.
I'm also extrapolating from the online
portfolio you forgot to log off,
but it's mostly the muffins.
Scope her for
worms in the lungs.
We could help out in there.
Yeah, it takes
at least four people
to look inside a crazy woman's lungs
for imaginary worms.
So, you're in
a good mood again.
Do you need another speech
about what a great friend I am?
I'm telling my wife
we don't need to downsize,
but maybe we do.
You really lost all that money?
I don't care about the money,
I just feel bad for Rachel.
She married a guy in one situation,
ended up with another.
- That's hard on anyone.
- Thanks,
makes me feel much better,
hearing my wife's a gold digger.
No, I just meant she married
this master-of-the-universe
successful surgeon,
and now he's basically a flunky
for this mad scientist,
who saves lives,
so that's good.
There are no worms
in the lungs.
What else could
cause bronchospasm?
Severe acid reflux.
No esophagitis,
it's not reflux.
Why are you
pushing a crash cart?
Because patients sometimes crash,
and they haven't yet invented
a crash tractor for me to drive wildly
around the hallways.
Why are we in the
coma patients' room?
You actually think the cat is going
to predict someone's death?
No. I know the cat is not going
to predict anyone's death.
And then I will have
scientifically disproved...
You didn't keep this patient
despite the cat,
you kept this patient
because of the cat.
You're scared there's
something to it.
If I could prove the non-existence
of an omniscient God
who lovingly guides us
to the other side, I would.
Cat version will have to do.
Are you scared?
Cats' brains are
always in alpha mode.
The few scientific tests that have
seemed to confirm psychic phenomena,
that's where it takes place.
Please tell me that you were kidding,
so I won't have to fire you.
I was kidding.
We still have
a human patient, right?
- Airborne allergens possible?
- Skin test was negative.
Lungs may be more sensitive.
Or House just screwed up.
If you misinterpreted the breath sounds
as soft instead of loud,
it's laryngospasm
instead of bronchospasm.
Which she can
get from a simple panic attack,
which she was having.
I also heard the lung sounds, too, Taub.
You saying I screwed up?
"Screwed up" is maybe
too harsh, but yes.
Don't you
wanna check their charts?
Of course not,
this is a double-blind.
I don't want to even subconsciously
signal to Teddy which one's the sickest.
Her name's Debbie.
Are those welts
on that guy's arm?
Were they here
when we got here?
He has a severe cat allergy.
That never happened.
Look at Debbie.
Good news, Mr. Limpert.
When you don't die tonight,
you will finally have done something
good for the world,
as opposed to your
life as a fireman.
Foreman's airborne allergen theory
makes the most sense.
Do a methacholine
challenge on Catgirl to check it out.
I told you to
get rid of Death Cat.
- You see a cat?
- I see a litter box.
This is a disability,
Dr. Cuddy.
- I can't make it to the men's room...
- You pee on the mice, too?
Well, now, you see, the mice actually
prove that I don't have a cat.
Are these...
Are these the genetically modified
lab mice from oncology?
Genetically modified
for tastiness.
Get rid of the cat,
and get rid of your patient.
My team is doing
a methacholine challenge.
Your team just completed
a methacholine challenge,
which came up negative.
Who told you about
the test? Taub?
I'll never say. But yes.
Her airway's clamped
down. I heard it.
We kick her
onto the streets, it could happen again.
Wish there was
a "lawsuit cat," it could warn you.
I'm sorry, but if you
won't escort her out,
I'll have to get
security to do it.
You're joining me
for a goodbye smoke.
I don't smoke.
Fine, if you don't want the seventh
graders to think you're cool.
I went through your purse.
Horoscopes, good-luck charms.
You went to a good college,
good nursing school,
so you weren't always
a superstitious idiot.
I'm not a superstitious...
How about four years,
that sound right?
That's when you switched
from the family insurance plan
to the one you're on now.
I was married, I got divorced.
Two years before that,
you got chickenpox shots,
which you only
get in adulthood when you have a kid.
Or I should say
when you had a kid
because no kid
has come to visit you.
Which all makes me think
something bad happened.
It was my stepson, Timothy.
What happened?
He was in school.
He was having
his morning snack, and he choked.
And the teachers saw it, and they did
everything that they were supposed to.
He shouldn't have died.
You wanna make it make sense.
What's wrong with that?
It's meaningless
is what's wrong.
What's wrong is that it doesn't
do a thing to bring your kid back,
or put you and
your ex together again.
Rash on your neck.
Probably not enough for Cuddy.
- Can't breathe.
- Hey, Doc.
Breath sound soft to you, Doc?
Hooray, you're officially sick.
Churg-Strauss fits best.
Here's the plan.
Taub, change the litter box.
This is pathetic.
You're still punishing me for calling
you out on the green urine lady?
Nope, this is for
ratting me out to Cuddy.
I'm not asking you to apologize,
just scoop some poop out of a box.
Just clean it.
Let House do it.
Yeah, that'll happen.
He won't just continue to let
our room smell like cat pee.
I'll clean it next time.
I'm out of here.
Now that you've delivered
that important lesson,
I'm gonna go
test the patient. Whoa!
What, you think
your bag's going to die now?
Now you're punishing me
because you think I'm superstitious?
What do you care?
It's not so much
about me caring, per so,
it's more about me wondering
why you're such a credulous idiot.
Thirteen, start the patient on steroids
for the Churg-Strauss.
Unless we have something
we need to argue about?
This is good stuff.
The best.
It's made from
the distilled sweat of
recently-laid-off
hedge fund managers.
Aren't you happy
you came out tonight?
Yeah. I wasn't actually going to,
but not the greatest day at work.
I used to have
an office like this.
Used to?
When I was a plastic surgeon.
But one day, I took
stock of my life and...
Oh, screw it.
I had an affair with the daughter
of one of my partners.
They signed a non-disclosure,
I signed a non-compete.
And the funny thing is
I wound up telling my wife anyway.
You like your job?
Same as you, same as everyone,
it has its ups and downs.
You're lying
to make me feel better.
Yeah. It's the best. I'm in charge,
you know. I'm a kid with toys.
Speaking of which,
what do you think of the prototype?
It's amazing.
You gotta make it
a half-inch smaller, though.
- You serious?
- I got small hands,
6.5 gloves,
like women surgeons,
which are your
fastest-g rowing market.
Me and the girls would have to use
two hands to hit the switch.
Why do I bother paying
the idiots that work for me?
Put down that crap
you're drinking,
because I am breaking out
the really good stuff.
What's wrong?
I went to the bathroom.
My urine...
- Green again?
- It's brown.
I didn't do anything. Honest.
I'm just a girl
who can't say no.
It is possible
she's still faking.
She didn't fake
the bronchospasm.
You think she's faking some stuff,
but not other stuff?
Maybe she's Unchausen?
I'm just saying the brown urine
doesn't make sense.
- What?
- Nothing.
We've ruled out every
possible cause for brown urine.
No blood in the urine,
liver and kidneys fine.
Brown could be fecal. Fistula.
We checked.
How do we know
the urine is still brown?
Had to be. Once
you've gone brown...
If we've ruled out everything
that can make the urine brown,
what if it just looked brown.
If the green dye never left her system,
what plus green makes brown?
Purple.
Strep bovis infection
from colon cancer.
Paraneoplastic syndrome
would explain the bronchospasm.
We scoped
her when we checked for the fistula,
there's no tumor.
Oh, no.
I wasn't scared
by the umbrella, either.
What? Not everything's
about you, Kutner.
I realize it's stupid.
I just don't know everything,
- I don't want to invite...
- Great.
I thought your
superstitiousness
had to do with your
folks being killed,
but "you're stupid"
works just as well.
Why is there a ladder here?
Whoops. Forgot that one.
Scopes don't work as well as pillcams.
Give her one, find the tumor.
Come with me, Tiny Taub.
Sorry, I was late again. I've got
a long commute from the poorhouse.
Knew it when I hired you.
You'd eventually
miss the money,
being the big shot
like your new CEO friend,
if that nightclub
stamp on your hand is any indication.
- Don't worry, I'm not quitting.
- I know.
A guy who signs a non-compete instead of
just telling his wife that he cheated
doesn't have the guts to quit.
Bad example. I did tell her.
From guilt, not from courage.
And bravely running
to Cuddy behind my back,
and arriving heroically
late every day.
Cowards make lousy employees.
Well, maybe you're a coward,
maybe you're quitting.
Either way, I'm screwed.
You'll note how Faster,
Pussycat! Kill! Kill!
Has snuggled up
by coma guy over there.
More importantly,
she did yesterday as well.
And he's still breathing.
We done?
Thank you for showing me this.
But maybe she's just confused
in this new environment.
In 1844, a preacher
in upstate New York
added up some dates in the Bible
and predicted Jesus' return.
His followers gave away
all their possessions
and showed up in a field.
Guess who didn't show.
So the preacher said
that he miscalculated,
and they went right
back the next month,
but with more followers.
Every time he was
irrefutably proved wrong,
it redoubled everyone's belief.
I know I sound just like them.
But I also know you're wrong.
Something terrible
is gonna happen to me.
You trying to prove
to her she's not dying?
That would be dumb,
as she might be dying.
This woman lost her kid.
Why are you attacking beliefs that give
her a little bit of comfort?
I don't care if her superstitions
make her feel better.
- I just want her to think more clearly.
- Oh.
Maybe that can make her
as happy as you are.
Where are we going?
Experimenting.
Stop it, Dr. Wilson.
It's just not cute anymore.
You already experimented
on the coma guy.
- Haven't you proved your point?
- Not to the patient,
and not to the
millions of idiots
who drooled over that news item
about the magic cat.
Why are you so
obsessed with this?
Can't you just call
her an idiot and leave everyone alone?
Hey, look, kids, therapy cat.
You're a liar. Therapy animals
are dogs, not cats.
Aren't you feisty?
This one's special.
If she likes you,
interesting stuff happens.
No. Okay. Kids,
playtime's over.
You know what,
this is a good thing.
Because either you're
starting to doubt yourself,
which is healthy, or...
I don't believe
in the legend of Goodbye Kitty.
Or you're starting to give a crap
what other people think,
which is just another way of saying
you give a crap
about other people.
I'd love to hear more of your theory,
but I don't give a crap.
Also, the pillcam's back.
Polypoid. Raised edges.
Raised edges are
actually necessary,
since that's the opening
to the appendix.
How many times are we
gonna watch this? There's no tumor.
Oh, my God,
the Death Cat is attacking your legs,
you're gonna die.
Maybe it has something to do
with that little red dot
dancing around down there.
Oh, my God, the death laser
is attacking your legs,
you're gonna die.
We're wasting time
looking for cancer.
She's still walking around,
she's still pretty healthy,
maybe it's something minor.
Maybe we're not wasting time.
We wouldn't have
seen a flat lesion.
Skin cancer could have metastasized
to the intestines.
Cool.
Check for melanomas.
Here, kitty, kitty,
kitty. Come here. Here, kitty.
What?
It's not cancer.
We found spider veins
on her back.
They weren't there
when she came in.
Spider veins means Cushing's.
Could cause an abdominal
disturbance, brown urine.
But the bronchospasm?
Cushing's myopathY-
It's uncommon, but...
Wait a second.
You didn't wake me up to tell me
a symptom that's not killing her.
What else is going on?
I think she's dying.
I just told you,
it's Cushing's. We treat...
I don't mean because
of the spider veins. Mr. Limpert died.
If that's my
high school gym teacher...
It's your coma patient.
He was stable for a year-and-a-half,
and he just died.
The cat was right, House.
Here, puss, puss,
puss, puss, puss.
Say "puss" one more time. It's the
sixth "puss" that really does it.
You're right. Sulking
will solve everything.
That cat sat on my lap,
and that cat knows something.
- You believe it now?
- Yesterday, it was all a coincidence.
Yesterday, it was, till I
unintentionally proved it wasn't.
Patient must have Cushing's. We have
to figure out whether it's based in...
A cat's nose is powerful, could smell
liver or kidney failure.
Exactly. Except that if you'd glanced
at the nursing home files
I had faxed over this morning,
you'd know that most of the patients'
livers and kidneys were fine.
- What else?
- The MRis aren't telling us
if the Cushing's is in
her adrenals or her brain.
So check her ACTH.
The cat's vision
is at the blue end of the spectrum.
ACTH is 11.7.
It's too close to tell.
And we can't treat the wrong organ,
'cause that won't solve anything.
She could have
a cortisol storm, could kill her.
Well, maybe, as the senior fellow,
you could have made sure
that my doors were closed so that I
could be concentrating on the cat
instead of looking for the cat.
You all right?
Your nose.
What'd he say?
Sounds like he said,
"Do you like cranberry juice?"
Crap.
Cheaper than fake blood.
And more cran-tastic.
Don't ever leave my door open
like that again.
You're playing pranks
and this woman could be dying.
So have Chase do
a venous sampling in her brain.
If he finds something,
it's there,
if he finds nothing,
it's the adrenals.
I'm not who I used to be.
I'm scared.
It's not a way to live.
I wanna come work for you.
Jeez, Chris,
you didn't think...
I didn't mean to imply
that I could hire you right now.
You said you needed
guys like me.
I know, but you
don't have an MBA,
and I just hired
a Chief Medical Officer.
Then let me invest in that laser
scalpel start-up.
I got money saved,
not a ton, but...
We put in a two-million-dollar minimum
for the first round of financing.
Look,
I guess I could take you on,
on a smaller number,
but you have to understand
it wouldn't be
some quick payoff.
Yeah, I know. I know it's not gonna
change my life overnight.
I just need to
start changing it.
Okay, then. Let's start.
What exactly are you hoping to find
inside your dead coma guy?
Catnip, chew toy... I don't know,
that's why I'm looking.
Your patient had a cardiac arrest
during the venous sampling.
We got her back, but
her heart's still tenuous.
- That tell us anything?
- She's weak, possibly dying.
So nothing.
- What about the ACTH?
- Slightly elevated.
It confirms the Cushing's
is in the brain. Go.
Are you sure
that it's Cushing's?
You'd expect central body obesity,
she's in good shape.
If it had a normal presentation,
there wouldn't be a cat involved.
So it's the brain,
means the next question is whether
to remove her pituitary right now...
That's not a question for me,
that's a question for the patient.
Now present both sides,
let her decide.
All right.
I've got to stop
telling you my theories.
You always just
try to prove me wrong.
You mean the theory about Cuddy's ass
getting bigger at the full moon?
I confirmed that one,
photo's on my blog.
Normally, you'd be up
in the patient room,
hectoring her on what to do,
instead you're up to your elbows
in some irrelevant dead guy,
who may or may not be
connected to a magic cat,
because you want to prove to me
that you don't care.
Case is over. I'm exploring
a scientific mystery.
I put up with your obsessions,
I even encourage them,
for one reason,
they save lives. I don't know
what you're doing now.
Cushing's means your body is
overproducing a hormone called cortisol.
The recommended course of action
is to suppress it with drugs.
And that will cure it?
Just treat it.
It could come back.
The only permanent solution is
to cut into your brain and remove
your pituitary gland,
but surgery's dangerous.
Your heart stopped
on the table once already.
I want the surgery.
This thing is gonna kill me
if I don't kill it first.
Because of the cat?
Do you wanna tell me
what an idiot I'm being?
No.
I really believe that there are things
that science can't understand,
that there is a role for faith and
prayer, but it's in the waiting room,
not the OR.
There's a reason I got sick.
There's a reason for all the bad things
that have happened to me.
I don't know what that reason is,
but I know that if there isn't one,
if there's no greater
purpose in the world,
then it's not a world
I wanna live in.
I'll schedule
an operating room.
You're early.
I'm not staying long.
I'm quitting.
- You got a new job?
- No.
Well, then you're not quitting.
I'll see you
back here tomorrow.
You're not accepting
my resignation?
Easier this way.
It avoids the whole thing
where you panic, run back and grovel,
and I punish you,
and then take you back.
Bye.
Bring donuts. Everyone loves
those bear claws.
Here, puss, puss,
puss, puss, puss. Puss?
Mr. Taub?
I've been waiting 15 minutes.
Where's Neil?
Neil doesn't work here anymore.
But he's the CEO.
I'm sorry. I wish
I could help you. Sorry.
This is crazy.
I'm investing with his company.
He doesn't have a company.
He worked here, but he
was a receptionist, a temp.
- Where is he?
- He's in custody.
I really am not
supposed to say anything else.
I went to high school with him.
That's what everyone
else thought, too.
I'm guessing you also
cured his ear problem?
Did you give him the money yet?
No.
I was right,
and more satisfyingly,
you were wrong.
It was coincidence.
That cat was not
predicting deaths,
it was just trying
to keep warm.
Yes, dead people are
renowned for their warm glow.
They are if they're feverish,
like three of
the patients were.
Or if they are wasting away,
like the other eight.
- Wasting doesn't...
- It does,
if it means someone sticks
a heating blanket on you.
Congrats. Because of your
crazy obsession with this cat
you've solved
a completely trivial mystery.
Completely trivial?
My God, it's clearly
only partially trivial.
Debbie climbed on Morgan, too,
which means she was overheated.
So what causes flushing,
mimics every Cushing's symptom
except central body obesity?
Cancer.
A corticotropin-producing
carcinoid tumor of the intestine.
But your pillcam
didn't find anything.
Means it must be somewhere
the pillcam couldn't go.
The appendix.
Congratulations.
You probably saved her life.
You definitely
saved her needless surgery.
Yes, I did.
What's the OR extension number?
Just curious.
Thank you.
I wouldn't come here for thanks,
that would be ungracious.
It's more about gloating.
You were about to cut out
a piece of your brain
just to chase some
crazy superstition.
But I didn't.
You didn't didn't
do anything. I stopped it.
And what made you do that?
Science. Logic. Reason.
Pick any three.
A cat chooses that exact moment
to sit on your computer.
Maybe that's science
and logic and reason,
or maybe it's something else.
You're an idiot.
I looked up the preacher
from New York State.
His followers never faded out.
They became the
Seventh-Day Adventists.
A major religion.
That man changed the course of history.
Because his followers
were as deluded as he was.
Maybe he just gave them
something to live for.
Feel better.
Kutner!
Cat pee on my chair?
- Blood on my face?
- Fake blood.
You pay for the dry-cleaning.
Why are you still alive?
I'm not sure.
I guess he was impressed
you stood up to him.
And got a cat
to pee on his chair.
Yeah. A cat.
- See you tomorrow.
- Yeah.