I want to reassure you.
Your child can have
a completely normal life.
How can a baby have
male and female DNA?
It's a condition
called genetic mosaicism.
The ambiguous genitalia
can be surgically repaired.
Repaired?
Made to look more typical.
More typical?
But you haven't even
told us if the baby's a boy or a girl.
That's a choice
you have to make.
Nice job, Jackson.
Take it.
He had the shot.
He lost his nerve.
Honey, it's okay.
He's doing great.
Three.
No fear that time.
Melanie.
Oh, my God. Jackson!
Black heels or the boots?
You know I'm a fan
of those heels.
Boots it is.
For all we know, House knows you're
a fan of those heels.
You think House is
going to figure out
we faked our break-up
because of your shoes?
Go with the boots.
You gonna eat that?
Have at it.
Did you just ask my permission
before you took my food?
Yes, we can.
Adolescent genetic mosaic,
collapsed during a basketball game,
presenting with
persistent pelvic pain.
Fun.
The parents haven't told their son
that he could have been their daughter.
They want assurance
that you won't either.
Less fun. But still.
That was easy.
Our new patient.
Part girl, part boy,
all Thirteen's dream date.
Severe pelvic pain started during a
basketball game. Could be dehydration.
ER gave him fluids
when he came in.
Still, if it was chronic...
We got a kid who could mate
with himself, and we're thinking
he didn't have enough to drink?
There are dozens
of intersex disorders.
Persistent pelvic pain could mean
congenital adrenal hyperplasia, PMDS.
Those conditions occur
in intersex kids
who are chromosomally
XX or XY, not XX and XY.
Parents recently started him on
testosterone, maybe there's something...
Vitamins wouldn't
cause pelvic pain.
There's a note in here.
We're supposed to refer to his
testosterone shots as vitamins.
His parents aren't just liars.
They want us to be liars, too.
I won't do it.
You guys will, though.
He's a kid. Parents don't think
he's ready to deal with it.
My dad was the same way about me maybe
having Huntington's. It's...
Well, if that was
your experience,
it must surely apply
in this situation.
Pain could be caused
by a blind uterus hidden in his abdomen.
He needs an MRI.
Right. Boy with girl genes.
I'm sure you're the first doctor
brilliant enough to check for a uterus.
He could have complications
from the surgeries on his penis.
That can cause pelvic pain.
Way to multi-task.
Impress your boss
and humiliate your ex.
MRI is a waste of time.
But to continue
the humiliation,
go put a camera up his penis.
You're Dr. House, aren't you?
What do you think
is wrong with our son?
These people were just
coming to tell you.
This is better.
Don't have to worry about
them losing their way.
We think that he has a blind uterus.
He should have an MRI.
Did you send them a text?
Over the past 13 years,
we've educated ourselves.
Who needs med school
when you've got Wi-Fi?
Go schedule their son
for an MRI with contrast right away.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
You just said an MRI
was a waste of time.
So is arguing with them.
Contrast's in.
Jackson, we're going
to get started, so try to lie still.
How long do you think the post-break-up
awkwardness is going to last?
Foreman and I are
both professionals.
Stomach and liver are clear.
If by "professional" you mean he's a
T-1000 built by Cyberdyne Systems.
I never understood
what you saw in him.
He's not really your type, huh?
Moving down through
the pelvic floor.
Here's my impression of Foreman
on the happiest day of his life.
Now, the saddest day
of his life.
We just broke up. I'm not quite ready
to mock him yet.
House was a jerk
to split you two up,
but bottom line,
he did you a favor.
Area around the
intestinal tract is clear.
No blind uterus.
I think there's
something wrong with House.
Who's he making miserable now?
Actually, no one.
He okayed an MRI
just because the parents wanted to look
for a blind uterus.
There was no fighting,
no arguing, he just went along.
It's a valid medical theory.
He doesn't think it is.
House decided to
humor these parents.
Maybe he had
a great cup of coffee,
or a tremendous bowel movement.
Bottom line is,
your boss is in a good mood.
Stop analyzing it
and just enjoy it.
We're going to use this scope
to fill your bladder with saline,
then examine your urethra
for any narrow spots.
Why would there be
a narrow spot?
Sometimes it just happens.
Can my parents come in?
Sure.
I thought it'd be awkward for you
having them here.
I have this feeling
they've seen me naked before.
Now, take a breath,
just try to relax.
Mom.
It's okay, honey. It's okay.
Hey, remember those sprints
they made you run in practice?
Those were so hard,
but you pulled through.
You can do this, too.
I'm to the bladder.
Start the saline.
I'm going to look around
and pull back on the scope.
Feels tight.
That pressure's normal.
Just try to hold on
for a few more minutes.
It's not down there.
It's my chest.
I can't breathe.
Can't... Can't breathe.
Is he okay?
Muffled heart sounds.
- Jugular's distended.
- Pericardial effusion.
We need a 10 gauge
and a syringe.
What's happening?
His heart is filling
with exudate.
If we don't drain it,
it'll stop beating.
We drained the fluid
from his pericardial space.
His heart rate
is back to normal.
Pelvis plus heart.
Doesn't fit with any of the syndromes
associated with mosaicism.
It could be drugs,
toxins, an infection.
You're okay with this?
With what?
That we're considering a diagnosis
unrelated to this kid being a she-male.
Assuming a coincidence
like that would usually torture you,
but you're completely unfazed.
Completely unfazed? You think
I'm totally lacking in any fazing?
The idea that I'm anything less than
half-fazed, I actually find offensive.
It greatly fazes me.
He started testosterone...
Vitamins.
A few months ago.
That can cause autoimmune diseases
like polyarteritis and SLE,
which can cause pericardial effusion
and pelvic pain. So, it is related.
Now I'm unfazed.
Start him on corticosteroids
for the autoimmune,
finasteride to block
the vitamins.
You slept with House.
He asked permission
before taking my bagel,
took the case without a fight,
honored the parents'
request for an MRI.
Yes, those were my terms
for sleeping with him.
He's in a good mood.
Sex with me would explain that,
but it doesn't explain why I'm not
curled up in a ball, weeping in shame.
I did not have sex with House.
If you two aren't keeping
something from me,
that means he's keeping
something from both of us.
- That can't be good.
- Or he's just in a good mood.
This is not a crisis.
Maybe you can get back
some of that money he owes you.
Hmm.
Testosterone blocker?
Does that mean if Jackson has SLE,
or whatever that other thing was,
that he'd have to go
off the hormones?
Probably.
Then Jackson
will stop developing,
he'll never go through puberty.
Maybe this isn't
what's wrong with him,
maybe the testosterone
didn't cause it.
Yeah. But if it is,
then he'll never be a man.
Did we make the wrong choice?
You'll need to tell him the testosterone
blocker is something else.
Or maybe this is a good opportunity
to tell him the truth.
It might make it simpler
for all of you.
You want us to tell
a sick adolescent boy
that he's really not an adolescent boy?
That doesn't seem
simpler to me.
No. Just
give him the meds.
So, you have
pain in one arm and both your legs.
Does it hurt right now?
No.
It's when I, like,
put pressure on them.
See, it hurts when I do this.
Ow!
And this.
What about this?
Ow!
Did you give House the moron
with the broken finger?
They've been in Room 2
about 10 minutes.
The patient should've been screaming
for another doctor seven minutes ago.
Thanks, bro.
If I have this IV,
why do I need a shot, too?
Just some extra medicine,
just to be safe.
I hear you're quite
the basketball player.
- What position?
- Point guard.
Small forward.
How's your crossover dribble?
It's okay. I'm not really
that into basketball.
Gonna feel
a little pinch, okay?
So, if you're not that into it,
why'd you join the team?
My mom kind of made me do it.
My parents were the same way,
always pushing me
to try new things.
It was more like
what she didn't want me to try.
I wanted to take dance,
but she flipped out,
and made me choose
between basketball and hockey.
What does your dad say?
He seemed okay with it,
then he just caved in to my mom.
Your palm is red.
What does that mean?
That we still don't know
what's wrong with you.
You were right,
he is in a good mood.
Bummer it didn't work out
with you and Thirteen.
It happens.
You guys seemed happy together.
It's probably for the best, you know,
the bisexual thing and all.
That was never an issue.
No, it never is. Until it is.
This is Thirteen.
Before you guys got together,
she was hooking up
with a different girl every night.
Long term, you really think
you could compete with that?
House, wake up.
We have to talk.
Stop pretending
to be asleep, we're not leaving.
House.
What's going on?
House?
- He's not breathing.
- Can you get a pulse?
- Barely.
- Call a code.
Get an Ambu bag
from the nurse's station.
Heart's still working,
means synapses are still firing.
We just need to get
a message through to him.
You stopped breathing.
What the hell is going on?
I think my penis
stopped breathing. Do you know CPR?
Looks like your brain is okay.
Pupils are equal,
round and reactive.
I'm fine, other than the fact
that my nurple is now purple.
No wonder you
broke up with him.
I'm surprised yours
are still attached.
By the way,
I could see that from here.
I assume those are our
patient's lab results.
The patient can wait.
You could have died.
The only reason you'd ignore a
near-death experience is you don't care,
or you already know
why it happened.
It's called Vicodin.
I took too many.
Can I please get
some information about our patient?
The patient's palms are red. Lab test
confirmed liver and kidney dysfunction.
I don't remember you
taking any Vicodin today.
I don't remember
hiring my mother.
And what causes the enzymes in
little Boy George's existing
heart problem and pelvic pain?
You didn't take any yesterday
at breakfast, either.
I don't remember
having breakfast with my mother.
Amyloidosis with
systemic involvement.
Protein levels are normal.
This kid's depressed.
If he's self-medicating
with drugs and alcohol,
that'd explain his symptoms.
Search the school.
Search the home.
Seriously? Or are you
just deflecting?
Both.
- Where are you going?
- Nowhere.
I'm staying right here,
so we can properly discuss this.
- He's on heroin.
- How can you...
Number one, he's happy,
which means he's high.
Number two, when he moved his bad leg,
he didn't use his hands to support it.
Whatever he's taking,
it's stronger than Vicodin.
What are we gonna do?
You really think House
took too many Vicodin?
Guy pops them like candy. I'm surprised
it hasn't happened before.
Do you miss
sleeping with women?
- Excuse me?
- Simple question.
Yes. It's a simple answer.
I'll check under the bed.
I also miss
sleeping with other men,
and I'm sure you miss sleeping
with other women.
Monogamy is like saying
you're never going to have
any other ice cream flavor
besides Rocky Road.
So, you're saying if you don't have
pink bubblegum for a while,
that one day you're
gonna chase down the ice cream truck?
No, Rocky Road is great.
It's a very delicious
and complicated flavor.
I also know that if
I have other flavors,
then Rocky Road is gonna be left in the
freezer where anyone can just dip in.
Can we please
drop the metaphor?
Why is this coming up now?
Kutner said the silver lining
of our break-up
was I wouldn't
be dumped for a girl.
There's nothing
in here, either.
Seems like you're wrong
about this kid having drug or alcohol...
When did he bring that up?
Earlier today, right before...
This morning,
Taub called you a robot.
Hmm.
Either it's a big coincidence
or they're jerking us
around, they know.
And if they know, House knows.
This is bad.
No, this is good.
House only has two ways to handle
us still going out.
He jerks us around
or he fires us.
He chose option A.
This is good.
But this is bad.
"I stand alone, my soul and me,
beneath the mask that others see."
His chest is still rising.
He's just screwing with me
'cause Cuddy made me baby-sit.
"A pain that tears and bites
and will not bend."
"Only when I sleep
will it end."
Downer.
And medically irrelevant.
You sure his chest is moving?
House.
If he's faking, you think he's going to
come clean because you said his name?
Back off. Only Thirteen
gets to grab my nipples this time.
You know, recreating the moment
when you made us crap our pants
isn't actually all that funny.
That is sweet that you're
worried about House.
Unless the next stanza reads,
"Hoping to fry my brain to death
I smoked some primo crystal math,"
I'm not interested.
You can't deny that
this kid may be suicidal.
We're not here to make him happy,
we're here to diagnose him.
It's an infection.
Swab of the kid's water bottle turned up
toxoplasmosis.
I'll start him
on pyrimethamine.
I had no idea he felt this way.
Is there a therapist here
that you can recommend?
It might help more
if you talked to him.
He's not ready.
If telling him the truth
would help him stop feeling like this.
If I knew that it'd
make him less confused,
I'd tell him right now.
But if she's wrong,
we'd only make things worse.
He obviously senses
he's different.
He's looking for answers.
Every teenager feels different.
He's sick. This isn't the time
to spring this on him.
Okay-
When you give Jackson
the antibiotics,
will you please re-start
the testosterone?
Sure.
I get House wanting to jerk me
and Thirteen around, but you guys?
Told you they were
still together.
How'd he know?
He noticed you smell like
Thirteen's soap every morning.
- You figured it out?
- Yes, I'm a little slow.
Maybe someone should let me know
when I should be insulted.
Then House doesn't know.
Probably does now
that you felt her up
during that last differential.
You noticed this,
but House didn't?
Yes, I get it.
He's generally smarter than me.
Can we please move on?
He's not generally
smarter than you,
he's always smarter than you.
Unless...
Hello?
House is on heroin.
Well, that's certainly
an interesting notion.
It's why his lungs stopped,
it's why he okayed the MRI,
it's why he missed things
he wouldn't ordinarily miss.
We'll run some tests,
and I'll let you know.
He's there, isn't he?
Well, that would certainly explain
the inappropriate responses.
I got to go. Okay-
Sorry. Consult.
When did you order these?
When you were in the bathroom.
I thought a celebration
was in order.
To cheating death.
You off bourbon?
Can I get you something else?
I came here expecting a burger.
Figured I'd have to endure
a little lecture on moderation.
You never listen, so why...
But instead, I get a drink.
A nice little serving
of respiratory depressant
on the day that my lungs
stopped working.
You seem fine now.
You don't believe
that I OD'd on Vicodin.
You figure I'm
on something stronger.
And because you can never,
ever assume anything
but the most screwed-up scenario
as far as I'm concerned...
Funny how I'm usually right.
You think that I'm on heroin.
This is your version of a tox screen.
Because if I am on heroin,
I can't drink that without risking
another bout of not breathing.
Well?
Good night.
Another shot?
I'm afraid so.
That looks like the vitamins
my parents give me.
Same red top.
These aren't vitamins.
What is it?
I can't tell you that.
You should ask your parents.
You idiot.
Okay, I admit it.
I have bulimia.
I look good though, don't I?
Heroin. Heroin!
House, of all the stupid...
I'm not on heroin.
I just caught you
with your fingers down your throat.
I'm on methadone.
Stupid product,
heroin without the high.
Yeah, and twice
the risk of death.
But no risk of arrest.
You nearly died.
Today was a fluke,
I nodded off.
Right, you're safe
as long as you never sleep again.
Mis-time your dose, you die,
couple of drinks, you die,
mix it with
the wrong drugs, you die.
You want to detox from Vicodin,
pick something
that won't kill you.
I'm not detoxing.
If you're looking for something
to help with your pain.
It doesn't help my pain.
It eliminates it.
My leg doesn't hurt anymore.
She completely
disregarded our instructions.
He asked a question.
I was tired of lying.
I didn't tell him anything
about his genetic condition.
I want her removed
from our son's case.
I'm sorry for the position
Dr. Hadley put you in,
but I can't do that.
She's a valuable part
of Dr. House's diagnostic team.
If he stays on the case,
so does she.
We have to deal with Jackson.
These questions
aren't going to go away.
He's not ready for this.
Let's hope you're wrong.
I'm sorry.
I'll stay away from their son.
No, you won't.
In about 15 minutes, you're the only
person that kid's gonna trust.
If he needs a hand to hold,
make sure yours is available.
So, what, am I a boy or a girl?
Some of your cells are male,
and some are female.
So, basically, I'm a freak.
No, no, buddy.
You're just a little different.
You've known this since I was born
and you never told me?
We didn't want you
to be confused.
So, you lied to me.
Oh, please, sweetie,
we were just trying to protect you.
Don't.
Just leave me alone.
Get out.
Let's go.
You still breathing in there?
Because if not,
I'm sending in janitorial.
I'm not breathing,
but it's strictly voluntary.
You should've seen the guy
who was in here before me.
I know about the methadone.
It's legal.
I have a prescription.
Whatever doctor
you conned into writing it
clearly had no idea about
your addiction issues, your lack of...
He knows I'm in pain. What I put
in my body is my business.
If you keep taking this,
you could die.
If he'd said that if
I keep doing this, you could die,
then it'd be your business.
I can't sit by and watch you
kill yourself.
As long as you're in my hospital,
you can't do methadone.
I'll send someone for my stuff.
That's it? You're quitting?
You're choosing methadone
over this job?
I'm choosing lack of pain
over this job.
Eventually you have to talk
to your parents again.
No, I don't.
I have this one friend
on my basketball team, Will.
We hang out a lot.
I really like him.
Now I'm worried that I,
you know, like him.
Maybe I'm supposed to.
Because if I'm really a girl...
Do you feel like a girl?
I like dancing
more than basketball.
Is that what that means?
Jackson,
as hard as it is right now,
at least it's out in the open.
You don't have to
hide behind a mask.
I found the poem
you wrote in your room.
No matter how bad things get,
killing yourself
is never the answer.
This was an English assignment.
We were supposed
to write a poem
in the style of Sylvia Plath.
You don't feel this way?
I'm sad sometimes.
But I don't want to die.
At least, I didn't.
Are these antibiotics
supposed to make you nauseous?
Yeah, they can.
- We're on our own.
- Is he okay?
He's fine. He's just not here.
Did he quit?
Did she suspend him?
She didn't say.
Just told me I was in charge
until further notice.
So, if we add bloody vomit
to our patient's list
of symptoms...
Surgeon reports the bleeding
was caused by a gastric fistula
caused by
necrotizing pancreatitis.
She must have
told you something.
Nothing that would
help us with this patient.
Heart, liver,
kidneys and pancreas.
Obviously, whatever this kid's got,
it's something systemic.
Zollinger-Ellison.
Or systemic scleroderma.
Zollinger-Ellison fits better.
Why?
Can we at least call House?
We can, I have,
he's not answering.
Put the patient on
proton pump inhibitors.
If he gets better,
it's Zollinger-Ellison.
If not, it's scleroderma.
Zollinger-Ellison
doesn't fit better.
You don't want it
to be scleroderma
because that means
he's going to die.
Patients die all the time.
Not the ones whose
families you've ruined.
I don't think that, you do.
It's not your fault.
He was no more confused
than any other teenager,
then I started a fire
and threw gas on it.
You were trying to help.
Hi, is House here?
He's getting dressed.
I'll be back
around 10:00 tonight.
Go on in.
Okay-
Who is she?
I hired her to watch me sleep,
make sure I don't
stop breathing.
Home nurses
usually wear scrubs.
She's not a nurse.
You hired a hooker to watch you sleep?
That just can't...
Surprisingly,
hookers are cheaper.
They don't sue for sexual harassment.
Which one?
You shaved!
The red one then.
You have two ties?
Meeting at
St. Sebastian's today.
I'm going to try
and talk them into
starting up
a diagnostics department.
That sounds great.
I just came by to check up on you,
see how you were doing.
I'm fine.
I guess you are.
He hasn't responded
to the medication at all?
I'm afraid not.
So, that means
he's got the other thing?
I'm so sorry. We'll start him
on anti-inflammatories.
If we're lucky,
that will slow down the progression.
My son has a death sentence,
and I can't go in there and be with him
because of you.
I'm sorry.
You find a homework assignment
and decide he's suicidal,
make it your own
personal mission.
I let my feelings...
Oh, don't you dare apologize.
Like it could absolve you
of what you've done
to me, my family.
He was fine.
I understand why you're angry.
But this isn't where
you belong right now.
He won't let us in the room.
He's a teenager,
you're his mother.
This is not the time
to start listening to him.
Go be with him.
Thank you.
I didn't do it for you.
We made a mistake.
No, we didn't.
The methadone is good for him.
The methadone
is gonna kill him.
He shaved.
He was wearing a tie.
He has a meeting
at St. Sebastian.
If he buys a new pair of shoes,
should we let him smoke crack?
Cuddy, he's happy-
House doesn't do happy,
pain or no pain.
Okay, maybe.
But he's our friend,
and this is his one chance
to not be miserable.
The heels, very nice.
No reason not to wear them
now that House is gone.
You Okay?
Yeah. Just tired.
Got some good news.
The patient's scleroderma
is responding to
the anti-inflammatory meds.
His AST level
has dropped a bit.
So, he's dying
slightly less quickly than we thought.
That's great news.
I'm not okay.
Next time, just say that.
What's his AST?
185, I think.
That's a pretty fast drop.
Are we sure it's from
the anti-inflammatories?
What else could it be from?
He's been off the antibiotics
for a while.
Proton pump inhibitors
wouldn't...
He's back on testosterone.
Testosterone wouldn't help
his liver function.
But it could improve
his kidney function,
which would also lower his AST.
But not in kidneys damaged
by scleroderma.
Which means
it's not scleroderma.
I have an interview
in two hours.
Wow.
Hand over my letter
of recommendation.
Sorry, I haven't done it yet.
You have no right
to sabotage...
I was busy with this.
It's a list of requirements
for your methadone treatment.
Weekly drug tests, supervised doses
administered on a precise schedule,
by me or one of the nurses.
Seems weird,
getting my meds here,
when I'm working
somewhere else.
Yes.
I'm offering you your job back.
- I want a raise.
- No.
And a bigger office,
but in the same spot.
No.
We both know
this is where you belong.
Okay-
Welcome back.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You Okay?
I have issues
with authority. You?
We thought you were gone.
Cuddy missed me.
And what happened to your cane?
She asked to borrow it
for some reason.
Patient dead,
or do I need to do anything?
He's got scleroderma.
It's not scleroderma.
Wow, two days and you've
already got two separate theories.
You're back. Good.
We noticed a drop in AST levels.
It's not from the anti-inflammatory.
It's because his kidneys
got better from the testosterone.
Which rules out scleroderma.
When did you two
come up with this?
We ran into each other
in the lobby.
So, what did we miss?
When I say "we," I mean you,
since I wasn't here.
We've ruled out
Zollinger-Ellison.
That was a dumb idea.
- Why?
- Because it was wrong.
Also Toxoplasmosis, dehydration,
SLE, various intersex disorders.
Oh, crap.
Does this kid like
energy drinks?
I saw some empty bottles
in the team's locker room.
But energy drinks
don't explain...
Nice work.
So, we're okay?
Why wouldn't we be?
Nice heels.
This is all
your parents' fault.
Excuse me?
You chug a lot of energy drinks before,
during and after practice?
Your son came in here
with simple dehydration.
That's why he collapsed
during the game.
The ER treated him for that.
It didn't help the pain.
That's where
the energy drinks came in.
They put a strain
on his kidneys,
so he needed more time to rebound
from the initial dehydration.
Then why isn't he better?
That's where
your idiocy came in.
Before we could give him
another glass of water,
you two insisted I do an MRI.
So, I go down a blind alley,
looking for a blind uterus,
and my team injects him
with contrast material.
If his kidneys
had been healthy,
he would've filtered out the contrast
in a couple of hours.
Since they weren't,
it went around and around,
eventually getting absorbed by his
heart, his liver and his pancreas,
getting in trouble
everywhere it went.
Your son was fine
when he got here.
It was
your freaked-out over-protectiveness
that nearly killed him.
Nearly?
He's young. A few weeks of dialysis,
he should be fine.
You gave birth
to a freak of nature,
doesn't mean it's a good idea
to treat him like one.
How are you feeling?
A little bit better.
I saw you talking
to your parents earlier, that's good.
My mom asked
if I wanted to take dance lessons.
That's great.
I'm actually worried
I might miss basketball.
I was starting to get good.
No reason you can't do both.
Starting tomorrow, you'll come
to my office for your fix.
I'm done with the methadone.
I screwed up.
The kid's parents
wanted that MRI.
I knew he didn't need it.
I did it anyway.
That's what got him sick.
You just solved a case
that no one else could solve.
I created a case.
I played nice because I was in a
good mood because it didn't hurt.
You don't need your pain
to be a good doctor.
I'm not interested in good.
You're afraid to be happy.
Why do you care if I'm happy?
You're afraid of change. The one thing
you have is your intellect.
You think if that's compromised,
you have nothing.
Just take it.
No.
Don't do this.
It's already done.
This is the only me you get.