We're starting a fund.
Then you don't need me.
- The man's injured, can't work.
- His fault.
We're family,
we depend on each other.
We're not family,
we're co-workers.
He's not even that any more.
I can't believe
you just said that.
Can't come between a man
and his beer money.
See the big heavy machinery?
I'm sorry, but he should give.
You gave.
Go back to work.
Paolo is the one
who got you off the night shift.
It's not like I asked him.
Also covered for you
Labor Day weekend.
But, hey, it's America,
if you don't want to contribute...
If you don't want to...
Oh, gosh.
Get an ambulance.
- Morning.
- Don't want to hear it.
So, I take it you
did not ask Cuddy out.
Yeah.
"Yeah" I didn't
or "Yeah" I did?
Whichever one means you almost
had me convinced it was a good idea.
Oh.
- Nothing to say?
- No.
"No" you don't
or "No" you don't don't.
Whichever one means no.
- Is this some kind of a reverse...
- No.
House?
Sixteen-year-old girl
with fluid in her lungs.
No previous trauma,
lung or cardiac issues.
Gram stain was negative,
no bacteria, no pneumonia.
She's a factory worker,
means she probably works close
to a lot of recent immigrants.
Thank God some of those
offshore sweatshop jobs
are coming back to America.
She's an emancipated minor.
In a factory?
Either an Olympic gymnast
who busted her leg,
a child star who blew
all her sequel money on drugs,
or she's just a lying runaway.
Her parents died last year.
No relatives.
To avoid foster care,
she got a GED and got emancipated.
Could have picked up
a parasite from a co-worker.
She'd be having GI problems.
Pregnancy's more likely.
Sparks a fluid overload, hits the lungs,
causes the pulmonary edema.
Her history says
she's not sexually active.
And our history says
she could be lying.
But not every teenager
is having sex.
But every teenager is stupid.
Teenagers on their own
are stupider.
The girl's holding down a job,
makes her rent.
On the one hand,
Kutner's right,
maybe she's a sweet young thing who's
not a screw-up lying through her teeth.
On the two hand,
pregnancy test only takes five minutes,
and we no longer kill rabbits,
so, in conclusion, shut up,
do the test. What else?
Drugs could damage the heart.
Pressure imbalance allows fluid
to build up in the lungs.
Tox screen's clean.
For drugs used recently,
not for drugs used before recently.
Sixteen doesn't automatically mean
a risky lifestyle.
Didn't we just
have this conversation?
Kutner trusts her, someone else doesn't.
So, in conclusion, shut up,
check her home and work
for toxins or drugs.
Kutner and Foreman, do an echo,
find the extent
of the heart damage.
Kutner can do the echo
on his own.
Yes, but he'll be very lonely,
so I have to ask why.
I've been asked to help
run a clinical trial.
That okay with you?
Good for your career, great for
your street cred. What's in it for me?
You have four doctors
and never more than one case.
Means I have time
to work on other things,
and they all have more chances
to step up, stand on their own.
And if there is
an emergency with Annie,
should she wait
until you finish grooming lab rats?
If there's a problem
with Sophia,
or any other patient,
you know I'll be there.
Your patient is my priority.
No.
What? You want a reason?
Clinical trials take time,
your time is my time.
I told you, I don't do drugs.
Still a good idea
to check your heart.
Something else
could've damaged it.
You find it hard,
being all on your own?
Having to do
everything without...
Drugs to ease my pain?
- That's not...
- A teenager on her own,
I wouldn't trust me either.
I meant it must be hard.
No one there to back you up.
I know you're trying to be nice,
but I'm not into the whole pity thing.
I was actually doing
the "I get it" thing.
I lost my parents
when I was six.
It doesn't go away, but it gets easier.
You learn to deal.
I still get nervous
when there's a knock on the door.
Always think it's the state trooper
with more bad news.
You already got the worst news
and survived. That's sort of the upside.
Your heart's healthy.
Isn't that good news?
For your heart, yeah, but it also means
we still don't know what's wrong.
Check book balanced,
place spotless,
looks like she builds
her own furniture.
If you're this grown-up at 16,
what happens at 30?
You turn back into a kid,
like Kutner.
Kutner's not that bad.
He needs everything to be nice,
wants to see the best in everyone.
- Kitchen's clear.
- Yeah, friendly is a dangerous thing.
There is such a thing
as too trusting.
Corollary is there's such a thing
as not trusting enough.
Too much, you get hurt.
Not enough, you don't live.
So, the object in life is to get hurt
just the right amount?
Excuse me if I don't go out of my way
to take relationship advice from you.
And trust should be earned.
Bong means nothing,
drugs are irrelevant.
Relevant if she's taking them.
Even if she is, irrelevant.
Echo showed no heart damage.
Would that be the echo
that Foreman chose not to run with you
after I dashed
his new drug discovery dreams?
You mad at me because you think
Kutner screwed up the echo?
I didn't screw up the echo.
I know.
No structural heart damage.
- So, if it's not the heart...
- It's the heart.
Didn't you just say it's not?
Not all heart damage
has to be structural.
Drugs could have caused
intermittent tachycardia.
Irregular heartbeat
would account for the pulmonary edema.
Edema was acute,
vasculitis makes more sense.
There's no sign
in her blood work,
and if she had vasculitis, she'd be
too weak to work in the factory.
She builds her own furniture,
you think she skips work
'cause she's feeling a little weak?
She needs steroids.
Steroids could cause
an irregular heartbeat,
making her current
one irregular-er.
Foreman,
start her on beta-blockers.
Rest of you, do anything that isn't
starting her on beta-blockers.
Start her on the treatment.
Page me if you need me.
Irregular heartbeat causes blood to back
up behind the heart and into the lungs.
The beta-blockers keep
this from happening.
I thought the test showed
my heart was fine.
It's tricky.
An arrhythmia can come and go.
So, you don't believe
me or the test.
You guys are more cynical
than I am.
We found the bong
in your apartment.
You went into my apartment?
Extended drug use can damage...
The bong belongs to my ex.
It's why he's ex.
That doesn't mean
you didn't use it.
No.
You have no reason to trust me.
You have to do your treatment.
The other possibility is
you have vasculitis.
The treatment
for that is steroids.
If you've been using drugs,
if they've damaged your heart,
and I start you on steroids,
they could kill you.
I haven't used drugs.
I'll get the steroids.
Why are you here?
- I owe clinic hours.
- No, you don't.
I'm here because House
doesn't want me to be here.
I'm guessing he said no
to the clinical trials.
He didn't need to say no,
he just wanted to say no.
House did something solely
out of self-interest?
Freaky.
- Don't suppose you want to override...
- No.
What do you think
this is going to prove?
Does it matter? Just figured
you could use some help down here.
And you spending two hours wiping noses
will annoy House.
If that is your dream,
God bless.
If you want to prove
you can do his job and something more...
His puke is red.
That's blood, right?
That hurt?
How about that?
Four days he's been like this.
It's just getting worse.
Maybe he just needs to poop.
- Evan.
- What?
Worked last time
I had a stomach ache.
That's actually a smart idea,
which is why that's the first thing
the other doctors checked.
His insides are clear.
- Anyone else sick at day-care?
- No.
- How about his friends?
- No. No one.
- What's happening to him?
- Not sure yet.
Don't worry, I've got an idea.
You can make him better, right?
That's my plan.
You need to make him better.
Stay the hell away from me.
Just calm down.
What happened?
I adjusted her IV,
and she went crazy.
Don't touch me! Leave me alone!
Sophia, it's okay,
we're here to help you.
Just stay away from me!
Don't touch me!
I said don't...
Get your hands off of me.
Get your hands...
Beta-blockers don't
cause psychotic breaks.
She's not on beta-blockers.
We started her on
haloperidol, she's stable.
Lab tests show the delirium
wasn't caused by a metabolic problem.
Means we still don't know
what caused it.
Yeah, we do. Nice job, Foreman.
I didn't switch her meds.
But your decision
to stick it to the man
clearly inspired Oliver Twist.
I treated her based on
the symptoms she presented.
You treated her based on
empathetic orphan syndrome,
and almost killed her
in the process.
She wasn't on steroids long enough
for it to cause the delirium.
- It's a new symptom.
- One that rules out vasculitis.
And arrhythmia. The psychotic break
caused a surge of adrenaline,
but no irregular heartbeat. Heart's
not the problem. We're both wrong.
So, what causes
lung issues and delirium
and is not based on wishful thinking
that she's safe and happy?
Prinzmetal angina.
Silent and unhappy
is better than vocal and unhelpful.
If you'd run the echo
that you didn't run
before giving her the beta-blockers
that you didn't give her,
if you'd listened to
what Kutner said,
you'd know it's
not a heart problem.
I'm not talking about her heart,
I'm talking about her head.
Prinzmetal angina
doesn't affect...
No reason it couldn't cause
an artery in the brain to spasm.
Leads to the delirium
and the pulmonary edema.
Foreman, give her Ergonovine
to cause vasospasms
and run an fMRI to see
which artery's dancing.
And when I say Foreman,
I mean Foreman.
I want his signature on the paperwork.
I want videotape.
I want photographs of him
with the patient and today's newspaper.
Set her up.
When you're ready...
House wants you...
To do the procedure.
When you get everything set up, page me.
- That's really a camera?
- Pretty cool, huh?
This can go places
the other scopes can't.
Jonah, I need you
to swallow this pill.
- Don't wanna.
- It doesn't hurt, promise.
Jonah, please,
this will help make you better.
I don't want to be mean, but if you
don't do this, we'll have to make you.
It's a power pill. It's not just
a camera, it makes your muscles grow.
Like the vitamins we take, except
this was made with a secret formula.
You did great, sweetheart.
You're very brave.
Jonah's lucky. I was pretty cruel to
my little brother when I was your age.
Why?
I guess I thought it's what big brothers
did. Obviously, I was wrong.
Is he a doctor, too?
No.
Does the pill tickle, sweetie?
He can't feel it.
What's funny? Your brother?
- What's happening?
- I don't know.
How are you guys getting along?
And you suddenly care why?
House was asking
questions last week.
I assume Foreman needs us,
and he's worried that if we're sniping,
we might be distracted.
- That's kind of insulting, isn't it?
- Very.
You're obviously fine.
I need a differential
for uncontrollable giggling.
He's four, they laugh.
Yeah, nothing like diarrhea
and bloody vomit
to put you in the mood to goof around.
I've looked down one end
and up the other.
All the tests came back clean.
Can't figure this out.
You can't? Don't you work with
three other doctors and a grouchy gimp?
This isn't House's case.
Just so you know, whatever you're
trying to prove, it won't be enough.
Gotta go.
Sorry.
You didn't miss much.
No spasms yet.
Nothing in the anterior
or posterior cerebral arteries.
How much longer?
Just a few more minutes.
Were your foster homes all around here,
or did you have to change schools?
Is chatting about lousy foster parents
supposed to relax me?
Left middle cerebral artery
looks good.
My foster parents were great.
I think most foster parents do it
because they want to do
something decent.
Which is why
you didn't get emancipated.
Nothing around the vertebral artery.
No sign of spasms.
But that's odd.
How'd you find out
about your parents?
Told you. State trooper.
Look at that.
Arteries are fine.
You can stop.
Not that.
I forget. Did he come to your house,
or call you down to the station?
Came to my house. I cried
into the guy's shirt for an hour.
Wow.
FMRis tell us
where the blood flow is.
You were using
your limbic region.
Lights up when we use our imagination,
doesn't light up
when we're telling the truth.
Your parents aren't dead,
are they?
I risked my job,
put you on a different treatment.
I didn't lie about the drugs.
Then why lie
about your parents?
Because I wish they were dead.
I got emancipated
because my dad raped me,
and my mom pretended
it didn't happen.
No signs of spasm,
impeded blood flow,
or brain dysfunction.
It's not Prinzmetal's.
All the fMRI showed is House was right.
She was lying.
Only relevant if it could cause
pulmonary edema and delirium.
We find out our patient's been raped,
and that's your response?
Is she a psych patient?
Rape could mean STD.
Thank goodness,
one of you doesn't have a heart.
Maybe if we all stop wringing our hands,
we could solve this thing
and let her live to have
a few more nightmares.
Gonococcal endocarditis would explain
the pulmonary edema, the delirium.
No sign in her blood work.
Could be lying about the rape.
Yesterday, you were all BFF,
now you think she's pathological.
Yesterday,
I had no reason to doubt her.
If she'd been honest
with us from the beginning...
She lied about dead parents
because it's better than rapist parents.
You find that unsympathetic?
That's it.
What's it?
Her whole life's a mess.
What rhymes with mess?
It's not stress. She has
none of the usual manifestations.
No hormone imbalance,
no cardiac...
Yeah, she's drowning in her own lungs,
and she's delirious.
She's a picture
of emotional health.
Severe emotional stress can lead
to asymmetric function of the mid-brain.
Explains the delirium.
Interruption in the brain-heart coupling
could cause pulmonary edema.
Even if House is wrong, the treatment's
basically anti-anxiety meds.
Hard to argue with.
Yes, I agree,
it does explain everything.
Thirteen, load her up on diazepam.
Foreman, make sure she does it.
Thirteen,
make sure he makes sure.
I went to Cuddy's house.
But I didn't go in.
Went home without ringing
either her metaphorical or actual bell.
Huh.
You're processing.
I'm scrubbing.
"Huh" means processing.
"Huh" means acknowledging.
If you prefer,
I could say "hah" or "hmm" or...
No insights? No opinions?
- You're disappointed.
- You made a decision.
I can't tell you
what's right for you.
Seriously?
Because last week you could.
Last year, you could.
Seems to come pretty easy to you.
Do you want me to tell you
what you should do?
I want you to stop thinking
that acting inscrutable
makes you anything other than annoying.
Interesting.
Holding things in
can give you cancer.
Kid's in day-care,
could be meningitis.
No fever,
no stiffness, no rash.
You check his thyroid?
TSH, T3, T4 were within range.
Ruled out all
the usual suspects.
Nothing's usual
for a 4-year-old.
And as fun as this is,
it feels like we're your goomah.
Your feelings are hurt?
Either you can handle
both these cases or you can't.
If you can't,
it's dangerous and stupid.
On the other hand,
stomach cancer, leiomyosarcoma.
Long shot. Altered mental status
means porphyria's more likely.
No abdominal pain. Cancer explains
the lethargy, the GI symptoms.
Neither is perfect.
Then we test for both.
And by "we" you mean
the collective, not you?
Thanks.
Severe stress scrambles the way
the brain communicates
with the rest of the body.
I have a problem with my brain?
Not exactly. The problem would be
with your body chemistry.
Where's Dr. Kutner?
There's four of us,
it's my turn.
I'm sorry I lied
about my parents.
You did what you thought you had to do
to protect yourself.
If we're right, we should see a change
in your lungs pretty fast.
Then we can figure out
how to manage your stress.
It might help to turn him in,
file a police report. Get closure.
Won't help.
Not addressing what happened
won't make it go away.
Yeah? What do I have to do
to make it go away?
I didn't mean that.
I just mean that you...
I addressed it.
I got away from him.
Reporting it just labels me
"girl raped by dad."
It doesn't have to define you.
It's how you see me.
It's why you're treating me
with tranquillizers.
Not any more.
Stress wouldn't change
your urine color.
Labs show the brown urine
was caused by shredded red cells.
So, what messes with her lungs,
her mental status,
and runs her blood
through a wood chipper?
Factory lunch rooms
aren't the cleanest places.
Could have picked up E. Coli.
Or Shigella, from the restroom.
Either would account
for the red cells, the delirium.
But not the original lung symptoms.
Legionnaire's could and cause delirium.
No, her sodium's normal.
What did her furniture
look like?
You said it was homemade.
Old boxes, what?
It was wood, nailed together.
The wood have
little dents or holes?
I didn't see any on the bookshelves,
but they were painted.
The desk did. Looked like
she'd stapled stuff all over it.
Holes means that
it was pressure treated.
Sawing or burning it releases
arsenic into the air and into her lungs.
Tests didn't show...
'Cause it found a cloak
of invisibility hiding...
Arsenic gets absorbed
in the internal organs
so it doesn't show up
on the blood test.
Test her hair. If it's positive,
chelate it out of her blood.
No cancer, no porphyria.
You paged me
with negative test results?
Yes, because it means
we're done.
Since we still don't know
what's wrong,
this kid has a real problem.
- Talk to House?
- Not his case.
There's a point
when Cameron and I aren't enough.
We're not there.
We need to run some more tests.
A week ago, he was a happy little boy,
playing with his brother,
and now he can
barely lift his head.
We'll figure this out.
I just need...
Mom. Help.
We need a crash cart.
- What's going on?
- He's in cardiac arrest.
Get them out of here.
- Clear.
- Nothing. Go again.
- He's back.
Foreman, we're there.
Chelation's complete.
You're arsenic-free.
So, I can get out of here?
In the morning.
That's it? No advice?
No, "Be careful out there, kiddo"?
You want my advice?
Want is one thing,
expect is another.
I wish I could
tell you what to do.
But you're strong. You've made
good choices. You'll be fine.
Thanks.
Need four milligrams
of Lorazepam.
After the seizure,
we ran a new MRI.
This is Sophia's brain three days ago,
this is her brain today.
Lesions.
Magical lesions,
which appear out of nowhere.
She was cured, then she wasn't.
Lesions grew
too fast for cancer.
Could be infection, MRSA.
WBC count would be
through the roof.
Put the arsenic back.
You wanna treat a patient
nearly poisoned to death
by giving her more poison?
Just because we call something a poison
doesn't mean it's bad for you.
It was killing her.
But since she's still dying, the
arsenic, obviously, wasn't killing her.
And since she's now getting worse,
the arsenic was obviously
fighting the killer.
It's a hero.
We should be organizing a parade.
So, what does arsenic treat?
Syphilis. Before penicillin,
the treatment was arsenic.
We already ruled out STDs,
and even if we were wrong,
that much arsenic in her system
would have wiped out the syphilis.
Acute promyelocytic leukemia
is still treated with arsenic.
APL explains the lesions and why they
appeared after we took the arsenic out.
So, put the arsenic back.
We still have a problem. Arsenic
slows leukemia, but it can't cure it.
If she wants to see 17, she's gonna
need a bone marrow transplant.
The best match would be
a sibling or a parent.
Biopsy a lesion, confirm that she's
dying, and load her up with arsenic.
Keep her alive till
you can convince her that
rapist marrow
and rapist-enabling marrow
work just as well
as the unleaded stuff.
We need to talk.
This about the case
you didn't want me to know about?
- Cuddy?
- Foreman.
You didn't flinch
when you found out about
a 16-year-old who could be
dying in the next few days.
Means you're here about
someone even younger, dying even faster.
- He needs you.
- But he has you.
This boy is going to die.
You selfish enough to let it happen?
- Pot calling a kettle a pot?
- You're a hypocrite.
If our job is to find out what's
killing patients, you'd help this kid.
But you'd rather play mind games
to prove
you're the only one
with magical powers.
You wanted something all your own,
now you got it.
Your disengagement won't work.
I can see that.
You think that when you tell me
what I should do,
my instincts are to push back,
so that by not telling me
what you think I should do,
I'll do what
you think I should do.
I sound convoluted.
Disengagement is neither
artful, nor effective.
So, my not doing anything
isn't causing you to do anything.
Right.
I'm okay with that.
No, you're not.
You are designed to have opinions
and to force them on people.
I'm starting to
sound desperate.
Don't screw with my stuff.
I just need a donor with
the same blood type or something, right?
Actually, bone marrow's
a little more complex.
The best donors
are immediate family.
But those donor banks
have thousands of names.
Your parents' similar DNA
- gives you a much better chance...
- No.
If I do this,
I'll owe my life to them.
It would mean everything else
that happened was somehow okay.
They don't deserve that.
They're not in my life.
If that means I'm dead,
then I'm dead.
I have Huntington's disease.
I'm dying-
I don't know when it will happen,
but it'll be sooner than I ever planned,
and I'd do anything to stop it.
Because the only way
to make anything right,
the only way
to make your life matter,
is to live as long
and as well as you possibly can.
Have you ever been raped?
No.
Don't try to walk in my shoes,
and I won't try to walk in yours.
You had no right.
To try to convince her
to do the right thing?
To lie to her.
It's a true story.
Who cares if it's not my story?
- It's my life.
- It's her life.
The point wasn't I'm dying,
the point was she should live.
You should have told her.
Instead you tell her to call the cops,
give her stats on DNA markers.
Everything's by the book,
nothing is ever personal.
Trying to sleep here.
Biopsy confirmed APL.
She needs a bone marrow transplant.
Run the donor banks.
I'm going home.
We need to track down
her parents.
I assume she's already
said no to that idea
or there'd be no need to screw up
your courage before saying it.
Children who've been through trauma
can't think clearly.
and are dying...
Guess I'm the only one
who cares about patient rights.
What she wants could kill her,
what she needs could save her.
Our job is to find out
what's killing patients,
not treat them for chronic idiocy.
Idiocy is what's killing her.
And since we can't cure that,
I'm going home.
We could save this patient, but all
you care about is getting your answer.
Your point being?
Taub and Kutner can check the donor
banks. I'm gonna find her parents.
Can't see why you're surprised.
You push against House,
he's going to push back.
Against me, I get,
but his ego's killing my patient.
You liked this case
because he wasn't looming over you,
the decisions were yours.
Only difference now
is he decided not to loom.
Doesn't change the fact
that your patient's dying.
What are we missing?
What's not in the file?
The mother.
Overburdened, at the end of her rope.
Makes her kid sick,
so someone else will take care of him,
sympathize with her.
Munchausen by proxy?
She brought him to the clinic, was with
him when he went into cardiac arrest.
The brother would have noticed,
said something.
Evan's even more protective
than she is.
Then maybe it's the brother.
- He's eight.
- Could be jealous.
He's the opposite of jealous.
He includes Jonah in everything he does.
Makes sure he eats,
brushes his teeth...
You think we gave him an idea?
Either that
or he's off to kill House.
- Mr. Valez?
- Yeah?
I'm Dr. Remy Hadley
from Princeton-Plainsboro Hospital.
We're treating your daughter,
Sophia, for leukemia
and we need to test both you
and your wife for bone marrow donation.
I'm sorry, you said
you're from Princeton-Plainsboro?
I know this is unexpected,
but time is short and...
What's going on?
This doctor says you have leukemia.
I don't have leukemia.
- Sophia Valez?
- Yeah?
- Sophia Isabel Valez?
- Yeah.
Do you know something I don't?
Just that liars lie.
You stole her identity.
To protect myself.
So they can't find me.
We can protect you,
but we need to find your parents.
Why?
You have my blood,
you don't need my name to find a donor.
You're a minor, you, obviously,
forged the emancipation papers.
Even if we had a donor, we'd still
need your parents' consent to treat you.
Can't you just pretend
you didn't go to that house,
that you didn't find that girl?
Calling your parents
doesn't mean a family reunion.
You don't even
have to see them.
When I get sick enough,
it'll be an emergency.
You'll have to give me a transplant,
even without consent.
An iron overdose?
From his vitamins.
If I'm right, we can treat him tonight.
He'll be back to his old self
in the morning.
But they're children's vitamins,
I only give him one.
I know.
I thought more
would make him strong.
I didn't mean to make him sick.
He's gonna be okay.
He's gonna hate me.
That's the great thing
about brothers.
You can make mistakes,
and they'll still love you.
Donor list turned up
a partial match.
So treat her.
It's only a three out of six.
So don't treat her.
She may not last the week.
Partial's better than nothing.
- So treat her.
- She'll reject it,
then she'll be too weak to try again
when a better match turns up.
- It's my turn now, right?
- If a better match turns up.
Well, when you decide,
get back to me.
She's scared.
Not scared enough.
Tell her the thing
about emotional reactions is
they're definitionally
irrational or stupid.
You might want to phrase
that in your own words.
She wants to deny her parents
the satisfaction of saving her life.
That's your rational explanation
of her emotional response.
That was her explanation.
That makes sense.
How long did it take her
to come up with that?
It was her immediate reaction.
That doesn't make sense.
The fact that it makes sense
doesn't make sense?
Emotional is immediate.
She went to rational first,
means there was no emotional to process.
You're saying
she's lying about being raped?
Wouldn't be her first.
She lied about one trauma
to cover a worse trauma.
So, what's worse than rape?
Hi. I'm Dr. House.
What did you do?
- I don't...
- Something happened,
but it wasn't rape.
Believe whatever you want.
You're scared and stubborn,
and you don't like people
feeling sorry for you. Why not?
I don't want pity,
I just want to be normal.
But you know you're not.
You need people to see how independent
you are, how well you're coping,
so they won't see the lost,
hurt little girl.
Because that's
not what you see.
You see someone
who did something terrible,
who deserves to suffer,
who doesn't deserve to live.
What did you do?
Eventually, we'll find your parents,
if only to deliver the body.
And they won't care.
You're an idiot.
You'd rather die
than face your parents because of what?
You broke their Fabergé egg?
I killed their son.
I killed my brother.
I was supposed to watch him.
He was in the bath.
I could hear him laughing.
Every time they'd look at me,
it's like I killed him again.
If you don't take
your parents' bone marrow,
you'll be killing
their other child.
If they don't hate you now,
they will then.
I don't care.
Sure you do.
You want someone to tell you
that it was just an accident,
that it's not that bad.
Well, it is that bad,
and you know it.
There's nothing
you can do to change that,
but there is one thing you can do
to not make it worse.
If you're here to celebrate the kid's
bone marrow transplant working,
you missed cake.
I want to do clinical trials.
Already had this conversation.
I've proved I can work
two cases at once.
I can do this,
and I'm doing it.
Okay-
Okay? Just like that?
Can I give my reasons later,
or never?
Three days ago you said no.
Three days ago, you asked me.
Now you told me.
Can't say no
if it's not a question.
Nice thing you did for Foreman.
He speaks.
He deflects.
I almost cost
a 4-year-old his life.
You knew Foreman
would figure it out.
Did I?
You just needed
to prove it to him.
You're an ass, but a noble one.
I sound clever.
Thank you.
Your little game didn't work.
I'm not Foreman,
and you're not me.
You want to talk about her?
Nope.
All right.
You're gonna be okay, House.
Good to know.