The risotto isn't bad, but it's not
what Chef Zane did back at Fortunato.
He replaced the rosemary
with saffron, for one thing.
And what is this stock?
Did he get it out of a can?
My fish isn't bad.
But it's not great either, I'm sure.
I warned you against the snapper.
Do you think it'll calm down?
God. I hope so.
That guy is a bit of a blowhard,
though, isn't he?
The food's not spicy at all,
you can barely taste it.
Mine's pretty spicy. Try it.
I don't taste anything.
Have you been throwing
rolls at me?
It wasn't me.
Really, he didn't.
I'm sorry someone would choose
to behave that way. Really, I...
I'm so sorry.
Really, really, really sorry.
No, no, no, no. I swear, I...
It's not me.
A bloody tear could just mean
subconjunctival hemorrhage.
He sneezed too hard from a cold,
which caused his lack of taste.
House isn't going to care.
Does "black tie optional"
really mean black tie,
'cause I don't want to rent if...
There's been a glitch
with the wedding.
And House will be interested.
A "glitch"?
Patient had his
corpus callosum cut
to correct a seizure issue.
A "glitch"?
The seizures stopped
after the surgery.
But he's having trouble
adjusting to a split brain.
A "glitch"?
This is Dr. Taub.
Tell him about shopping.
I go into a grocery store,
everything seems normal.
I get to the checkout, and there's
all these extra items in my cart.
Stuff I didn't put there.
Stuff I hate.
My left hand hates me.
Yeah. I think House'll
be interested.
Just warning you.
I'm in a good mood
and largely pain-free, so I've got
no idea how things are...
Alien hand syndrome.
Set off by a stroke, or is
there a pony in the backyard?
Split brain. Right hemisphere
controls the left, and...
It's making life miserable.
Non-logical thinkers often do.
The current issue isn't the split brain.
The surgery corrected...
You're dissing
the right hemisphere?
Most people who have this operation
don't even notice
they're missing anything.
The left brain has language,
arithmetic, rationality,
and right brain
is a mute loser.
The right brain
is more aesthetically oriented,
has greater facial recognition.
I couldn't have been a
plastic surgeon without it.
Yes, and where
would junior high be
without our ability to judge
people on aesthetics?
Right brain's also more aware
of the present moment,
our place in the universe.
It's a universal daisy chain of peace
and love that throws buns at people.
His present symptoms
could mean autoimmune disease,
a nasolacrimal tumor,
an infection or just a cold.
Good morning, sunshine. We got a brand
new toy, you want to play?
We need to talk.
Great. I love euphemisms.
By "euphemism," I mean when you say
something but mean something else.
Begin eliminating.
Search the home.
Isn't that like locking the barn door
after the horse has put his face
between your breasts
for an hour and a half?
I'm your boss.
You're an employee.
I'm not normally into role-playing,
but if you want to...
People who get close
to you get hurt. That's a fact.
You're also a valued doctor
in this hospital. That's another fact.
From now on,
we're going to focus on the second fact.
So, this isn't you freaking
out over last night?
This isn't an emotional decision.
I'm just giving you the rules.
You can either
accept them or leave.
I slept with Cuddy.
After she helped me
detox from Vicodin.
I've been clean for
almost 24 hours now.
Okay. Thought I'd mention it.
Wow.
One for each.
That's what she said. Ah!
How's the pain?
She's probably
got some bruising.
Yeah, I get it, you're a stud.
This is serious, House.
I feel better than I
did four hours ago.
Four hours from now,
I'll feel better than this.
The other "wow."
You were sober? She was sober?
Clean and sober and hot.
Wow. This is fantastic.
How are you gonna screw it up?
Several good options.
Unfortunately, I don't
think she's gonna give me the pleasure.
She left before I woke up
and five minutes ago, she told me
that I'm just an employee.
- Ha.
- Yes.
Well, either she's
actually in love with you and scared,
or she realized last night
was a gigantic mistake.
You were needy and vulnerable,
she was maternal.
You think she
jumped me out of pity?
No, I'm saying whatever is going on,
you need to talk to her.
Absolutely.
Does our patient
freak you out a little?
No.
If he's two people, then we're all two
people and we just don't know it.
And what does that
say about identity?
It says we're making it up as we
go along, which I find freeing.
Wow, I haven't been in a bathroom
this size since my dorm in med school.
Is that fungus?
It's from the steam buildup.
What do you think of this "glitch"
with Chase and Cameron's wedding?
It's always a sad thing when
sperm comes between people.
I hear the sperm
is very good today.
I mean, the salmon.
- Go away.
- No other tables.
You'd let your wife
keep another man's offspring on ice
next to the frozen peas,
just in case?
That's what this is about.
She's not ready to commit to me.
She's planning for failure.
Did you know that male fruit flies have
toxic chemicals in their seminal fluid
that inhibit the sperm
of other males?
Wilson says we need to talk.
- We talked.
- I agree.
This has clearly gone
past the talking stage.
What?
Hey.
Great, did you find my MP3?
Not yet. But I got your shaving stuff,
toothpaste, deodorant,
some magazines,
and this cactus from your window.
You didn't have to do that. Really,
the hospital supplies all that stuff.
I'm still trying too hard, huh? Trying
to get your other half to like me.
No, no, no. Don't say that,
okay? I like you, which means that...
We shouldn't read into that.
Anti-fungal meds.
Ordinarily we'd put
them in your IV,
but since your right
brain doesn't seem too fond of IVs...
You should be feeling
better in a few days.
I have to get back to work.
Rick says your shift will be waiting
for you when you get back.
Thanks.
Oh, my God. I'm sorry.
I'm so, so sorry.
I'm sorry.
I have to go.
I have to get back to work.
Babe, wait. Hold on.
No, no. It wasn't me...
I can't walk.
Well, obviously
it wasn't the fungus.
And it's not a coordination issue.
Dehydration can cause loss of balance.
We haven't had him on IV.
No. Good skin turgor,
not orthostatic.
Could be our tax
dollars at work,
constantly building new
roadways and bridges.
Meningioma. Slow-growing.
It could extend along the sub-osteal
layer of the cranial cavity,
and be hidden by the bone.
The cancer cells are actually
re-growing a connection
between the left
and right hemispheres.
If you're right, the two halves
have begun sending messages again,
but it's too early in the process
for him to pick up on it.
But we can test for it.
Proof.
You didn't talk
to her, did you?
If I'd talked, she'd have lied,
I'd have lied,
and though two negatives
make a positive,
I thought thermal-imaging
photos seemed simpler.
Note how many more heated areas appear
after less than a minute with me.
So it's either love,
or possibly rage.
Don't talk to her.
I have no plans to talk to her.
Manipulation is in
your genetic code.
You think I'm making a mistake,
you move in to correct.
- You are making a mistake.
- She lied to me.
Either last night or today.
I need to find out which and why.
And clearly, thermal
imaging is the way.
This isn't a case. You're not
looking for a diagnosis.
If this matters at all to you, please,
for once in your life, be an adult.
Keep your eyes
focused on the plus sign.
Any image that appears
on your far right will
only be seen by your left brain,
and any image on your far left will
only be seen by your right brain.
Okay-
Just start by saying the words.
Book, giraffe,
willow, fortunate.
You're not saying the word.
I didn't see a word.
Could you draw a picture
of what you think the word might be?
Look, I didn't see...
Candle.
This is so cool.
Yeah, that's not freaky at all.
No communication.
So far.
Scott, why are you standing?
I'm a little chilly.
I thought I'd get a sweater
or something from my room.
Is that okay?
Just a few more minutes.
And that, ladies and gentlemen,
is the left hemisphere.
The side that's obsessed
with finding answers,
the one that needs
things to make sense, the interpreter.
That's where we tell the story
of who we are and why we do things.
That's also the side
that was wrong.
The right brain's advantage
is that it isn't logical,
it doesn't choose which
details to look at.
It makes connections
you could never see.
You owe your
insight to the "mute loser."
I'll send it tickets
to a Phillies game.
Confabulation means no communication.
Means your theory's wrong.
But he is cold.
Why are you scratching?
It itches.
Ammonia breath.
Your liver is failing.
I know for them to approve
this price,
they'll need
statistical documentation...
What? Why are you
looking at me?
When you first walked in,
I was under the impression
you wanted to
say something else.
- Nope.
- About House and me.
There's nothing to talk about.
I want permission
to do a liver biopsy.
We're looking for sarcoidosis.
Fine.
What do you mean, "Fine"?
What do you mean,
what do I mean?
Do you mean that because
a liver biopsy is not a test
that by any stretch of the imagination
could be considered risky,
so asking my permission is
essentially wasting my time,
and you're wondering
what my reaction to that will be?
Yes.
Are you trying
to make me angry?
Yes.
Do your biopsy. And also,
do your clinic hours.
I'm blowing off
my clinic hours.
Really?
Let's see how that goes.
Still not angry.
Try again later.
Sorry. I know
I'm a little ripe.
- Just a sweaty guy.
- Recently?
Always.
With a crazy left hand. Sometimes I
fantasize about cutting it off.
Just a fantasy.
It's the hand that's crazy, not me.
What?
If it doesn't like an ultrasound wand,
how's it gonna react to a needle?
Can you get music
into this room?
I think you're using your relationship
with Cuddy as a replacement for drugs.
You should be in more pain
so soon into detoxing,
but your body's full
of romantic endorphins,
and on top of that, you create
this distraction of looking for proof.
You think I should stop
and let the pain flood back?
Cuddy is not
a Vicodin substitute.
Quite the opposite.
You have to wait
for her to be ready.
Great advice. You pretend that
I'm going to do that.
You've made two major
changes in your life,
not a time anyone's
judgment is at its best.
Didn't you used to argue that my
judgment would be better off drugs?
Admit it. You're curious
why I want to make her angry.
I'm sure it's convoluted,
wrong and stupid.
You're dying to know
what I found on her coffee cup.
- No, because...
- Oxytocin.
Oxytocin, the chemical
involved in emotional bonding.
Her lips say "no," her hormones say
"Oh, my God, yes, more."
No. For you to know
her levels were elevated,
you'd need a baseline
to compare them with.
I paid the guy in the gym to retrieve
one of her water bottles from the trash.
Love inspires us to greatness.
So I need to make
her lose her temper,
which breaks her delusion,
which demonstrates to me, and to her,
that there is something
underneath this facade.
And then what happens?
She admits everything
and falls into your arms?
That's outcome one.
Outcome two is she kills me.
I think it's 50-50 right now.
Great.
I thought you'd say that.
You're committing
yourself to something. To someone.
I mean, it's childish in
a way, but ultimately great.
Assuming... Are you absolutely sure
you want this to succeed?
Why is an old guy
standing in my doorway?
Eugene Schwartz.
Dr. Cuddy asked me to come
up here from the clinic.
She says you're seeing
patients in your office.
It's still free,
though, isn't it?
She sent him.
That's gotta mean something.
I'll go get my decoder ring.
I squawk. Like a parrot.
No, that's not it.
It started a few months ago.
I was doing some woodworking in my
garage. I was trying to make a chair.
Was it the chair?
Anyway, all of a sudden,
from nowhere,
this strange noise
comes bursting out of my mouth.
Tough to fake that.
Nice pants.
My wife Mona thinks I'm busting
her chops. It's ruining my marriage.
Where are we going?
So your left hand would rather play air
guitar than give me a hard time?
It'd rather play air guitar
than tie shoes, eat dinner...
Your right hand's playing, too.
I don't want to discourage it.
Splinter hemorrhages
under his fingernails.
What's that...
BP and O2 sat are dropping.
We need a bag
of B-negative in here!
So much for sarcoidosis.
Points to a clotting issue.
Clots would explain all his symptoms.
Why aren't we in the office?
I'm tired of clinic duty.
There's only one thing
that could cause squawking, right?
Yeah.
We gave him heparin
and did an echo of his heart
to see if it was
throwing clots, but...
More air guitar?
The heart's fine.
We wanted to test for Factor V Leiden,
Protein C, Protein S,
but the hand got tired of cooperating.
We finally knocked him out.
And all those tests came
up negative anyway,
or you'd have opened by telling me
your brilliant diagnosis.
He apologized for being sweaty,
said it had always been an issue.
But what if it's a symptom?
There are cancers that cause night
sweats and can lead to clots. Lymphoma.
Or pancreatic cancer.
Go scan his pancreas.
And try Led Zeppelin.
We've always remembered
what this hospital did for Leo
when his appendix burst.
Still, a check this size...
Sorry to interrupt,
here's my poo.
Dr. House said to bring it over and
leave it with you as soon as I could.
I don't know if you people
have an official term for it.
- Stool sample.
- Ah, yes.
Thank you.
I'll take care of it.
It's hard to rush these things. Even if
you've eaten a lot of broccoli.
Where are you going?
Annie called.
She's not coming back.
This is not the best time...
Look, you said the heparin
would keep new clots from forming.
Maybe. But something's
obviously causing the clots.
If you have
pancreatic cancer...
We're not trying to scare you,
but even in its early
stages, the fatality rate...
You walk out of here...
Stop!
Look, I'd ask you to put
yourself in my place,
but nobody can put
themselves in my place.
Did she find somebody new?
Was I not being attentive enough? No.
She's just tired of being
insulted by a limb.
She said that my feelings
toward her were mixed.
Well, my feelings aren't mixed.
You're not going anywhere.
Unless you want to go naked.
Your right brain knows
you need to stay.
My right brain's an ass.
Got a minute?
There's something
wrong with this cup.
I need someone to bounce ideas off of.
Someone to be my whiteboard.
That's how you
taught me to work.
I have three choices.
First, I can accept it's over, pretend
we don't work in the same hospital,
have selective visual impairment
when we pass each other in the hall.
Second, I can accept
it's over and leave.
Or you could try
making him angry.
Standard choice number three.
Third, I can talk to him.
But it's not like I have
any new facts I can present,
and Chase has this romantic view of love
that reality can't compete with.
I know how you could succeed.
How?
Just say the magic words,
"I will destroy my husband's sperm."
You mean, succeed without
doing that? Probably not.
I have doubts. Normal doubts.
It's not wrong to prepare for
bad things to happen,
even if
you don't expect them to.
I don't expect my condo
to burn down, but I have fire insurance.
Patient's girlfriend left him,
now he wants to leave us.
If your condo rules don't let you buy
insurance, do you go homeless?
His room is this way.
What? You think I can fix this?
We need to offer this guy
something he can only get
if he stays in the hospital.
Relationship counseling.
I don't know if
his girlfriend is...
I mean his two hemispheres.
That's the breakfast of relationships,
the most important one of the day.
We need your special skills.
Ls the guy out there?
The guy that's gonna
make my right brain work?
Oh, for...
What do you think
your right brain wants?
How should I know? It's crazy,
it does things I would never do.
Duct of Wirsung slightly enlarged,
but within normal parameters.
Say something.
It's mute. It can't
communicate with you.
Maybe you should try
communicating with it.
"Talk to her."
The well isn't deep, is it?
You're the dominant half,
you make all the decisions.
The right side has no control over
anything. It must be frustrating.
No masses in body
or tail segments.
I can't communicate with it,
that's the whole...
When you decide to
go and get groceries, what do you do?
What do you mean? I put on my jacket
and I go to the store.
Your right brain has no idea
why you're suddenly
getting up and putting on your jacket.
It just gets dragged along.
Next time, try saying it out loud.
Just say to the empty air,
"Hey, I think I'll go to the store
because we're out of peanut butter"?
How much did they teach you
about people like me
when you were learning
to be a therapist?
I'm an oncologist.
Your right brain likes what he's saying.
Hasn't moved the entire scan.
Hasn't gotten us anything, though.
Sean's clean.
It's not pancreatic cancer.
Clotting could be a problem
well before a solid tumor forms.
It could still be pancreatic.
Yes, but if you want
a diagnosis backed by actual evidence,
we should probably
look at other cancers.
- House.
- I just squawked!
- What?
- Eugene Schwartz.
Your patient from yesterday.
I just squawked!
I was buying some flowers for Mona.
It happened when I was paying the clerk.
I assume Dr. Cuddy
gave you this number.
Yes. She told me to call
you any time I squawked, day or night.
I'm sorry, but I'm
about to lose you,
because I'm about to drive into a tunnel
in a canyon on an airplane
while hanging up the phone.
I might be getting some more phone
calls, so let's make it fast.
- Lymphoma.
- That's right, pancreatic.
I know it's pancreatic.
I know there's evidence.
I know we've seen it.
I just can't...
Right brain/left brain issues?
If the cancer's too small
to find, let's make it easier.
Let's open him up and paint it.
There's a new procedure using
scorpion toxin and infrared paint.
The paint only works on the cancer
cells, makes them easier to spot.
Just agitating the pancreas
can cause clotting,
and you want to do it to a guy
whose problem is clotting?
If I'm right about
pancreatic cancer,
the only chance he's got is finding
and removing those cancer cells now.
His brain MRI showed narrowing in the
blood vessels leading up from the neck.
If we do shake something loose,
we could kill him.
Or one of him.
A clot in his brain could kill one
of them without affecting the other.
He might actually
be okay with that.
How long is it going to take?
Assuming he doesn't
crash, a few minutes.
Hey, you and Cameron...
I'm sorry.
I'll be right back.
I don't want to be homeless.
Okay. You can stay in
the condo. I'll find some other...
That's not what I mean.
I want to marry you.
I got the forms to destroy the sperm.
You sure?
Yeah.
I want to hug you, but
then I'd have to re-scrub.
I know.
BP is dropping.
Go.
No sign of cancer.
BP is 90 over 60.
You never answered my question.
Relax. Our friendship
is not doomed.
Thank God. But my question was,
do you really want Cuddy,
or is this just
another challenge?
You're worried that once
I'm in a relationship,
you and me will be over.
Hey, I'm actually for this.
I think this is great.
But if you're serious,
and you don't treat it seriously,
then you will get hurt.
And if you don't accept that,
then accept that she will get hurt.
I was told it
was your birthday.
I understand.
So, so sorry.
I know.
Clearly, there was a mix-up.
Have a nice day.
Does she look angry?
If you're standing there
when she looks up here...
Oh, no.
Systolic's 80.
Gotta finish this
suture before I can get out.
Give him a dopamine drip.
We weren't looking up
at the right time.
Get to your point.
We're a little busy here.
The clots aren't from cancer.
They're coming from his heart.
We echoed the heart. No clots.
Not while we were looking.
Didn't! Open with that?
The clots were caused
by an arrhythmia.
No arrhythmia.
Not while we were looking.
Intermittent arrhythmia.
This guy pulls our equipment off
at the slightest provocation.
We'd have to be watching at
the exact moment it happened,
which I'm guessing,
given the way you two
are scrambling around like idiots,
is right now.
Yes, I'm saying
do a transesophageal echo.
We have to get his BP stable.
Absolutely.
Right after the echo.
Systolic's 70.
The heart looked healthy
at the last echo.
And an arrhythmia wouldn't
cause clots in a healthy ventricle,
so start with
the left atrial appendage.
- Wow.
- Yep, I did it again.
Now get this poor guy's BP under
control and seal off the appendage.
And then all we have to do is
find out what damaged his heart
before it goes
after something he really needs.
So what damages
a healthy 20-year-old heart
enough to make it send out clots
- like it's bombing Dresden?
- Rhabdo.
Would've fried
his kidneys, too.
What about Graves'?
Thyroid function
tests were normal.
Cushing's. Cortisol overproduction
could interfere with heart rhythm.
Run a dexamethasone
suppression test.
Annie.
You hit me.
I know. I'm so sorry.
But it wasn't me.
I know you would
never have done that
if you were in
control of yourself, but...
But you came back.
To talk with your doctors.
I've been going over
and over what happened.
And I had this thought,
out of nowhere.
Ever since I've known Scott, I've seen
his left hand throw things,
but always sort of playfully,
thinking it's fun.
But when he threw this, it was angry.
And that's when his hand slapped me,
too, when I brought it to him.
Could it mean something?
Deodorant shouldn't...
How often do you use it?
A few times a day. It's special,
heavy-duty stuff.
I have to send away for it.
Sprayed around a bathroom
the size of a shoebox.
I'll check the ingredients
from the manufacturer.
I'll check for any references
associated with health issues.
Somebody's grateful.
We'll just leave
the three of you alone.
Why is there
no lipstick on this cup?
Cuddy was wearing lipstick
when she drank from it.
It was on my face.
Why isn't it on the cup?
Why is it always reasonable, in
Houseland, to take an emotional problem
and sidestep it by turning
it into a mechanical problem?
Because, in Houseland, and the rest
of the universe, by the way,
when a question presents itself,
it calls for an answer.
If the left brain is
the interpreter of reality
and the one that tells us the story of
who we are, then what is your story?
Do you want to be the man
with the answers?
Or do you want to be
the man with Cuddy?
What do I do?
You make her angry.
Do you really think that was
the best time to mock me?
I'm as surprised as you,
but I think I'm serious.
Communication can't start
unless you're both...
I've been trying to
make her angry for...
No, you haven't.
Come on. Poo? Strippers?
It's routine stuff.
You've been pulling your punches.
You're scared.
You should be.
Now go terrorize her.
You don't want to
destroy it, do you?
I said I was gonna
do it, I'll do it.
But you don't want to.
I want to be with you. Maybe I'm not
comfortable with it, but...
Let's say
it's our fifth anniversary.
Are you ready
to destroy it now?
Tenth. Three kids.
They spend their summers
in Melbourne and have annoying accents.
It's disgusting
how happy we are. You ready now?
You don't have doubts.
You just don't want to kill the only
thing left of someone you loved.
Don't do it.
I do have trouble
giving things up.
For example, I never cancelled
any of our wedding plans.
Attention!
I have an announcement.
As you go about your day,
I would like you to be aware of the fact
that I slept with Lisa Cuddy.
This is beyond asshood.
You have the luxury of not
caring about your image. I do not.
I can permit a lot of crap,
but an employee shouting
about his sexual exploits with me, no.
That is zero tolerance.
So congratulations, House, I'm angry.
I was wondering if we
should move in together.
You're fired.
I wouldn't worry about it.
I think she likes you.
If I'm fired, I think that probably
means I don't have to see patients.
I'm here as a squeaky wheel.
I know how you doctors
are, you're busy, you get distracted.
My lab results could be
sitting in your inbox.
I don't need your labs,
you have acid reflux.
Well, how could you...
Acid splashes on
the vocal cords,
they tense, make that squawking sound.
It's completely harmless.
I'm gonna give you a prescription,
and you're gonna go away.
You are a great doctor.
Why'd you move your belt?
I always move my belt.
It makes me sore.
You didn't tell me that.
At 86, what isn't sore?
Soreness is less
important than squawking.
It's the squawking
that was bothering my wife.
That's not a potbelly.
That's a tumor.
That's why pancreatic
cancer was on my mind.
My brain was trying
to tell me...
This isn't sounding good.
Pancreatic cancer?
Can cause acid reflux.
We should scope you.
So it's not good.
Even for cancer, it's not good.
No, it's not.
The deodorant has a high proportion
of propylene glycol.
Same stuff made a kid in Singapore
develop a heart condition
and, get this, seizures.
Our patient may never have needed
split-brain surgery.
I'm sure he will half
appreciate the irony.
Can you take this man to Radiology?
Pancreatic scan.
And stay with him.
Eugene Schwartz.
Whatever it is,
just say it quickly.
Do you have more than one lipstick
in the same shade?
Maybe one that has a sealing agent,
and one that doesn't?
How could that possibly
be relevant to anything?
You really don't think you're just
overreacting to the other night?
Fine. I am overreacting.
You've said plenty of lousy
things to me before.
But reaching the final straw
has been a good thing,
because it made me realize we not only
don't have a personal relationship,
we never could.
You're...
You've been overreacting
to something I said?
You insulted me, I walked out.
It's nothing that hasn't happened
a hundred times before.
I quit.
Great.
My nanny is off the clock at 7:30.
So your week off...
You can go suckle
the little bastard child
who makes you
feel good about yourself.
Screw you.
No, no. That's
not what happened.
I told you that I needed you.
You helped me.
Are you okay?
So, this is the story you made up
about who you are. It's a nice one.
Too bad it isn't true.
No.
I'm not okay.