(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(SLOW BREATHING)
(GROANS SOFTLY)
Aah.
(GROANS)
It's like fucking school again.
We got so wrecked.
Should have come. It was a good night.
Proper laugh.
♪♪
(EXHALES)
Uh, so look, I, um...
I am not gonna be here for the summer.
Yeah.
Like, I can't pay the rent.
And Niall's gonna sublet the room, so...
I'll have to move out.
When?
Uh, pretty soon. Next week, maybe.
So you'll be going back to Sligo, then.
♪♪
CONNELL: I mean, um...
I guess...
I guess you want to
see other people, or, uh...
I guess so. Yeah.
(DISHES CLATTERING)
♪♪
MS. NEARY: Connell Waldron.
CONNELL: Ah, Ms. Neary.
MS. NEARY: Oh, my God.
Would ya not call me that?
Haven't seen you since school.
♪♪
Ah, it's weird seeing ya.
Good weird.
Mm.
(LAUGHS)
Ooh.
You're so fucking hard.
(LAUGHS)
(LAUGHS) What?
Do you wanna come back to my place?
Oh...
I'm gonna be sick.
What?
Uh... mm.
Hey, um...
I should go.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(THUDS)
CONNELL:
So I guess we should see other people.
I guess so.
♪♪
CONNELL:
You didn't tell me you were in town.
Yeah.
(RAIN PATTERING)
I got your text...
when you were home.
Feels a bit weird running into you
with no warning or anything.
MARIANNE: Warning? (SCOFFS)
You know what I mean.
I'm just back for the weekend.
It's my father's anniversary mass.
I'm sorry.
Can I come?
Obviously, if don't want me to
I won't, but I'd like to.
Sorry.
No?
Okay.
You're with Jamie now, I hear.
He always liked ya.
What about you?
- You seeing anyone?
No.
Not at the minute.
Embracing the single lifestyle?
Yeah.
Yeah, you know me.
I did once.
(SEAT BELT CLICKS)
Look, if you don't want to be friends,
that's fine.
I'd just rather know, so we can...
Course I want to be friends.
Okay.
Do you want to come in?
For, like, a tea, or‐‐
I can't. I've got shopping in the back.
Thanks for the lift.
(RAIN POURING)
Length of days is not what makes
age honorable,
nor number of years
the true measure of life.
Understanding.
This is man's gray hairs.
Untarnished life.
This is ripe old age.
He has sought to please God,
so God has loved him.
As he was living among sinners,
he has been taken up.
He has been carried off so that evil
may not warp his understanding,
or treachery seduce his soul.
For the fascination of evil
throws good things into the shade.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(CAR ZOOMING)
(TRAFFIC NOISES)
(CAR HONKS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
You didn't need to run.
Ah, my bus got caught in traffic.
Some protest.
Got you a coffee.
Ah, thanks.
How are you feeling about Schols?
How are you feeling about them, Connell?
Hmm. How am I feeling about my entire
future being potentially secure, or...
mind‐numbingly difficult?
Yeah, it's, ah...
casual.
How's Jamie?
Be nice if you guys
could actually be civil.
Ah. I'm civil.
Oh.
You could just, like, uh,
try not to intimidate him quite so much.
(CONNELL LAUGHS)
Are you telling him
not to intimidate me?
(SCOFFS) As if, Connell.
- He's barely my height.
Ah.
I'm not sure intimidation is
strictly limited to height, though.
No?
From where he's standing,
you're the tall guy
who used to fuck his girlfriend.
Right.
Is that how you describe me
to all your friends?
The tall guy who fucked you?
Pretty sure we fucked each other.
We had mutual,
equally‐involved kind of sex.
It's different.
With Jamie.
What do you mean?
Do you want to hear about this?
He's into pain.
Like, inflicting it.
Turns out he's a bit of a sadist.
(CONNELL CHUCKLES)
Are you serious?
Just during sex, that is.
Not arguments.
Your face.
And you're, you're into that,
are ya?
Yeah.
You're so shocked.
We really don't have to talk about this.
(INHALES)
What does he do to ya, specifically?
Slaps me. Uses a belt.
Things like that.
Right.
Sounds fucking horrible.
It's not.
It's just different.
You never said any of this to me
when we were...
Well, it was different with you.
Things were different.
Right.
Didn't have to play any games with you.
It was just real.
With Jamie, I don't know.
It's a bit like I'm acting a part.
I just pretend to feel a certain way.
Like I'm in his power.
But with you,
I actually had those feelings.
I'd have done anything you wanted me to.
Anyway...
How are you?
(TRAIN RUMBLING)
(JAMIE GRUNTING)
♪♪
(JAMIE PANTING)
(GASPS)
♪♪
(CROWD APPLAUDING)
PROVOST:
The English scholars are...
Marion Pickard...
(CROWD CHEERING, APPLAUDING)
David Sexton...
Ashley Tobin...
(EXCITED CHEERING, APPLAUDING)
Connell Waldron...
NIALL: Fucking yes, mate.
(LAUGHING)
Fucking right, you absolute fucking nerd.
(CONNELL LAUGHING)
Fucking five years free tuition,
free accommodation.
Five years, you jammy fucker!
Unreal, man.
PROVOST: And Mairead Button...
(CROWD CHEERING, APPLAUDING)
PROVOST:
The history and politics scholar is...
Marianne Sheridan.
(CROWD CHEERING, APPLAUDING)
(JAMIE LAUGHS)
Aah!
(CHATTER AND LAUGHTER)
(LAUGHING)
(LAUGHTER AND INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Traveling from west to east
is literally like crossing a border
into a completely different city.
It's totally surreal.
I mean, I've been, so, I, uh...
Yeah, because everyone has been to
fucking Berlin, Peggy.
You're making out like you
just got back from Syria.
Marianne's not been to Berlin.
I'm explaining for her benefit.
They don't let people from Connacht
travel that far.
(JOANNA LAUGHS)
PHILIP: Ooh.
Extremely hilarious.
Yeah, and Marianne has been to Berlin.
MARIANNE: Does anyone want more food?
SOPHIE: Yeah, it's so good.
Joanna cooked it. Yeah, I can
make, like, one thing. (LAUGHS)
Anyway, should we do, uh,
a fuckin' toast or something
to the cleverest history and politics
student Trinity has ever known?
- JAMIE: Hear, hear.
Stop it.
Yeah, yeah. Don't mind fuckin' me.
JAMIE: Ooh, we won't.
Poor Peggy.
It's fine. I never studied.
(LAUGHTER)
To Marianne.
PHILIP AND JOANNA: To Marianne.
PEGGY: To Marianne.
(GLASSES CLINKING)
To the cleverest girl in Trinity.
Jesus, stop it, please.
(ALL LAUGHING)
(PHONE RINGING)
Thank God.
(ALL CHATTERING)
(PHONE RINGING)
Eat up.
Hello?
Oh. Hi.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
What? Are you okay?
Where are you?
(ENGINE RUNNING)
Jesus Christ, Connell.
I know, it's fine. It's, uh...
It's not as bad as it looks.
Thank you.
- DRIVER: Thanks.
(ENGINE ROARS)
(DOOR SQUEAKS, SHUTS)
What happened?
Uh, just this lad.
Asked for my wallet.
I should have handed it over,
but I said no,
and he hit me in the face.
I'm fine.
Your phone number was the only one
I knew off by heart.
I'm really sorry. I'm really drunk.
How drunk?
Ah, well, I've been out
since they announced Schols, so...
Right.
Mm‐hmm.
Do I still have pupils?
Just about.
- They're huge.
Mm.
They always get like that
when I see you, anyways.
Aah.
Mm.
Mm. You must be drunk.
How do you mean?
Jamie's downstairs.
Oh.
Uh...
Ah, maybe I'll just go back out
and get punched in the face.
(LAUGHING) It really wasn't that bad.
Connell.
Ah. (LAUGHS)
Ugh. Fucking lowlife scum.
What?
Fucking lowlife scum?
Well, that's quite the welcome, Jamie.
You know, uh, we can't, uh...
We can't all be the spawn of millionaires.
(ALL LAUGHING SOFTLY)
Yeah, well, I was talking about
the dickhead who robbed you to buy drugs,
- obviously.
Drugs?
Yeah. Well, he's hardly using your cash
to buy loaves of bread for his kids.
Be up his nose or in a needle, won't it?
SOPHIE:
Looks pretty bad, Connell. You okay?
It's not as bad as it looks.
Okay, I mean, will we get going, or‐‐
You're such a sweetheart, Peggy.
He just said he was fine.
I am. Thanks.
I'll join you in a bit.
Get this one cleaned up first.
JAMIE: Well, they stop letting in at 12.
I'm pretty tired anyways.
You go. Call you tomorrow.
JAMIE: Right.
If you're sure?
(KISSES)
Okay?
Thanks for dinner, mate.
PHILIP: Thanks, Marianne.
Thank you. It was delicious.
SOPHIE:
And congratulations again, Marianne.
You, too, Connell.
JOANNA: Yeah, congrats, Connell.
Thanks.
JOANNA: Feel better.
SOPHIE: Come on, you guys.
(FOOTSTEPS DEPARTING)
- JAMIE: Connell.
Jamie.
(DOOR SLAMS)
(WATER STEAMING)
You could have a different boyfriend,
you know.
I mean,
guys are consistently
falling in love with you,
from what I hear.
Stop that.
Tea?
People love ya or hate ya.
Right.
(CLATTERING)
You don't hate me.
No.
No, I'm immune to ya.
Because I knew you before, in school.
When I was ugly and pathetic?
No.
You were never ugly or pathetic.
I'd rather literally anyone else,
Marianne.
I'd rather the lad that mugged me
was your boyfriend.
Why do you care?
Do you love him?
We don't talk about that, do we?
I thought that stuff
was off‐limits for us.
All right. Okay.
You know, I probably should have
mentioned this before,
but I've been seeing someone.
Been with her a while. Yeah.
Should have mentioned it before,
but then again,
I feel like we've hardly seen each other.
Barely spent any time together, and, uh...
Yeah, her name's Helen Brophy.
I don't know would you know her.
She studies medicine.
(CLATTERING)
(MARIANNE BREATHING SHAKILY)
Why were you trying to get me
to break up with Jamie?
No, I'm not.
I'm not.
I just want you to be happy is all.
'Cause you're such a good friend, is it?
Yeah.
Mm‐hmm. Yeah. I, I mean, I‐‐
I, I think I...
(SOBS)
Jesus. Marianne.
I feel awful. I'm sorry.
I should have said it before.
I don't want to talk to you, Connell.
Just leave. (SNIFFS)
- Please, can you just go?
Yeah.
(MARIANNE SNIFFLES)
(MARIANNE SOBBING)
Look, I'm, uh, really sorry
to have to ask. It's just, I, uh...
I can't get home.
(MARIANNE SOBBING)
Uh, uh...
Would I be able to borrow the money,
like you said?
MARIANNE: Oh, God.
(SNIFFLES)
Sorry.
I managed to forget you've been
beaten up somehow. I... Yeah.
Mm.
(DOOR OPENS)
Here.
Uh, thanks.
Um...
You know, uh...
I don't know what happened with us
last summer.
Uh, like, when I had to go home and that.
See, I... I kind of hoped that I
would have been able to stay here.
That you would have let me.
Yeah, I, I just, uh...
I don't really know what happened
between us, to be honest.
(SNIFFLES) You said you wanted
to see other people.
No.
I thought you were breaking up with me.
You never said anything
about wanting to stay here. I...
That would have been...
Always.
Obviously.
Uh...
Right, well, I, I should go. I'm, uh...
Have a good night, Marianne.
("METROMA" BY THE SEI)
♪ We brought this on ♪
♪ Resisting ♪
♪ Dead or alive ♪
♪ We're missing ♪
♪ Don't ask why ♪
♪ I close my eyes ♪
♪ Something inside ♪
♪ Insisting ♪
♪ Better than God ♪
♪ Just listen ♪
♪ Take my time ♪
♪ This is the place ♪
♪ I met you ♪
♪ Say I'm found ♪