(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
ERIC: It's a simple game.
You have 15 players.
Give one of them the ball,
get it into the net.
CONNELL: Very simple.
Isn't it?
Oh, what?
Oh.
Brilliant.
ERIC: How's it going, Rachel?
Talking tactics, there, for the game.
We're getting a master class.
How incredibly boring of you.
Yeah.
Did you get your hair done?
RACHEL: I did, yeah.
ERIC: It's very pretty.
RACHEL: Thanks.
Can I use my locker, by any chance?
Yeah.
Yeah, I sort of need you
to move, Connell.
Oh, sorry. Excuse me.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
"Uh, sorry. Ex‐squeeze me."
All right, relax, will ya?
MR. KERRIGAN:
But you know that's important.
Because it's turned up in the exam twice
out of the last three years.
(TREES RUSTLING)
Marianne?
Yeah?
Something outside caught your attention?
I suppose so.
MR. KERRIGAN:
Eyes forward, okay?
I wasn't aware my eye line fell under
the jurisdiction of school rules.
ROB: Here we go. Jesus.
Trying to impress your classmates?
They don't look too impressed to me.
I'm pretty sure I was just
looking out the window.
Come on, Sheridan.
MR. KERRIGAN: If you're staring
out the window daydreaming,
then you're not learning,
are you, Marianne?
Don't hurt yourself.
I have nothing to learn from you.
(SOFT SHOCKED LAUGHTER)
Okay, in that case, principal's office.
Yeah. I might go there.
Or I might just head home.
It's not really your business what I do,
is it?
ERIC: Don't worry, sir.
She's a psycho to everybody.
MR. KERRIGAN:
Do you want to follow her, Folan?
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(CAR APPROACHING)
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
(DOORBELL RINGS)
- MARIANNE: Hey.
Hey.
Come on in. Your mum's in the kitchen.
LORRAINE: Hey, love.
Marianne was telling me
you got your mock results back today.
CONNELL: Uh, just English.
They come back separately.
LORRAINE:
I hear you did very well.
He did.
CONNELL: Yeah, well...
Marianne did pretty good, too.
Can we go?
Didn't realize we were in a rush.
Just put these away,
and then we'll be off.
- Immediately, okay?
Mm‐hmm.
(SNIFFS)
Do you want some?
N‐no thanks.
Didn't you get French back today?
Yesterday.
Yeah.
Got an A1.
What'd you get in German?
Are you bragging?
(CONNELL CHUCKLES)
Got an A1.
Ah, you're gonna get 600,
are ya?
You probably will.
Yeah, well, you're smarter
than me, so...
Smarter than everyone.
Ah, well, you're not
top of the class in English.
Maybe you should
give me grinds, Connell.
(CHUCKLES)
- LORRAINE: Good to go?
Yeah.
Oy.
MARIANNE:
Thanks for everything, Lorraine.
LORRAINE: Tell your mum
I'll clean upstairs tomorrow.
(MELANCHOLY MUSIC)
♪♪
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
LORRAINE: Did you rob the place?
What?
The quick getaway.
You could have said goodbye.
I did.
She doesn't exactly have
an easy time of it, Connell.
You could try being a bit nicer to her.
I am nice to her.
She's actually a very sensitive person.
Oh, look. Can we talk about
something else, please?
♪♪
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
You enjoying your book there, Marianne?
(CHUCKLES) I said,
are you enjoying your book?
You're not getting distracted
by the fuckin' window, are you?
(ALL SNICKERING)
RACHEL: That is absolutely tragic.
(LAUGHTER)
COACH:
That's it, that's it, Connell. That's it.
Right. Let's focus it. Yeah. Here.
COACH: Beautiful. Keep it going, boys.
Fast, fast, fast.
(RUBBING FABRIC)
Sorry. Am I disturbing you, Marianne?
No.
(DRYER WHIRRING)
If I knew what I wanted to study,
I'd obviously tell you.
LORRAINE:
Well, you must have some idea.
No. I know what I don't want to study,
but that's about it.
Jesus, how long is that list?
Fairly long. (CHUCKLES)
That's a great way to decide, Connell.
Rule out marine biology and astrophysics,
and all the rest
till you're left with one.
I could be a marine biologist.
Yeah, that sounds like
your area of interest, all right.
You've not got long. Forms are due soon.
Yeah. I'm aware.
(DOOR CLOSES)
DENISE: Is this just out?
About five minutes ago.
Made some salad.
Could you not have drawn the curtains,
Marianne?
It's literally only just getting dark.
You've got the heating on full
and the curtains wide open.
(WINE POURING)
Did you have a good day?
Depends on what you mean by good.
You can get rid of one client
and another one arrives.
Isn't that good business?
Yes.
Where's your brother?
Don't shrug, Marianne.
I don't know. I haven't seen him.
And how was school?
Okay.
Got some results back.
- Mocks.
And?
Good.
- (DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
ALAN: Is there any food?
DENISE:
Your sister's reheated a lasagne.
Oh, good effort, Marianne.
How was your day?
All right.
Not too busy.
DENISE: You out this evening?
Yeah.
'Cause I got this thing called
a social life.
Right.
You know, like, actual friends.
Lucky you.
RADIO ANNOUNCER: Fermanagh now
completing the list of qualifiers.
Draw for the next round
will be held on Thursday.
Finally, at the Cricket World Cup today,
it's the semi‐final clash, as India...
(CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
(PHONE JINGLING)
Hello? GER (OVER PHONE):
Alan, it's Ger. How's it going?
Good, yeah.
Uh, listen, I'm after missing the bus,
and I hate to ask you,
but any chance of a lift in?
Yeah, no bother at all, man.
You at the house, eh?
I'll swing around for you now.
Oh, thank you so much.
Sound. Stall it there. I'll see you
in a few. Yeah, oh, you're a star.
(RAIN POURING)
What are you doing?
ALAN: Uh, did you not hear
that entire call?
I have to go pick up Ger out in Garryduff.
You hop out here.
Are you serious? I'll get drenched.
Right. Shit buzz for you, pal.
Maybe you should learn to drive.
Go on.
(SEAT BELT CLICKS)
(RAIN POURING)
(GROANS)
MS. NEARY: "It was sliding beneath
the big, black wave."
"Another and another.
Then I was back in it. The war was‐‐"
(DOOR OPENS)
Class begins at nine, Marianne.
MARIANNE: Yeah.
Thanks for that.
Excuse me?
Can you just give me a detention
and move on?
(CLASS CHUCKLING AND CHATTERING)
Quiet.
"Then I was back in it.
"The war was on outside,
in Worcester, Massachusetts..."
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
I'm having people over Friday,
after the match.
Come celebrate, or drown your sorrows.
Whatever.
Yeah. Sounds good.
What happened to you
this morning, Marianne?
You're looking a bit
on the drowned rat side.
Thanks, yeah. It was raining.
You should have brought an umbrella.
Good advice.
You strip off in the toilets
to dry yourself again?
Not this time. No. Why?
Would you like an invitation next time?
ERIC: (MOCKING):
"Just give me detention,
and move on."
(CHUCKLING)
ROB: That was a good one.
MARIANNE: Glad you enjoyed it.
ROB: The shit you get away with
'cause you're smart.
I understand you're at
a disadvantage there, Rob.
Fuck off.
- (CHUCKLING)
(SNICKERING)
Hey.
You're not heading home, no?
I did actually get a detention.
Sorry.
Technically, I requested it.
You were fairly harsh
on Kerrigan the other day, as well.
He's actually pretty decent.
I don't know why you had to have
such a go at him.
I object to every thought or action,
or...
feeling of mine being policed
like we're in some authoritarian fantasy.
Well, it's not that, though, is it?
It's just school.
It's the same for everybody.
It's not unique for you.
You try to act like we're friends,
but you know you're
not that kind of person.
I'm not acting.
Maybe I am that kind of person.
Why are you talking to me, then?
Yeah.
What was Ms. Neary
talking to you about after class?
Oh, don't know. Uh...
getting out of class early for training
or something.
She must find training
highly amusing, then.
Well.
Does she fancy you or something?
Why'd you say that?
God, you're not having
an affair with her, are you?
Please. You think it's funny joking
about stuff like that, do you?
Sorry.
People going at me like I fancy her. I‐‐
I don't fancy her.
Well...
maybe it's because you blush a lot
when she talks to you.
Aah.
But you know, you blush at everything.
Thanks.
Guess you have one of those complexions.
Great.
You're blushing right now, actually.
Yeah. I'm aware.
Sorry.
I don't want to get into a fight
with you or anything.
(CHUCKLES) We're not fighting.
I know you... probably hate me.
But you're the only person
who actually talks to me.
I never said that I hated you.
Well...
I like you.
Oh.
Got to head to training, so, uh...
Good luck at the match tomorrow.
Thanks.
TEACHER:
Marianne, you gonna join us?
Come on, lads. In you go.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER AND YELLING)
(CROWD YELLING)
COACH: Keep going, keep going.
(PLAYERS YELLING)
(CHEERING AND YELLING)
(YELLING)
Come on, sink his ass!
Fuck!
- (CROWD GROANING)
(SOFT MUSIC)
♪♪
(GRUNTS)
Push through it, Kiernan!
Come on!
Score!
(YELLING)
♪♪
Yeah!
- (CROWD CHEERING)
- (WHISTLE BLOWS)
Yeah!
Fuck, we did it!
Fuck! (LAUGHS)
Come on!
(CROWD CLAPPING AND CHEERING)
(BOTH YELLING)
(CHEERING AND CLAPPING)
(WHISTLING)
Grand.
Good lad.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(CHEERING AND WHISTLING CONTINUES)
BOY: Woo!
♪♪
(SEAT BELT JANGLING)
(DOORBELL RINGS)
LORRAINE:
You're early. Come on in.
Have a bit do, yet.
Grand.
Quick as I can.
(DOOR CLOSES)
No, not in there.
I've just finished mopping.
And well done, man of the match.
Marianne told me.
Did she?
She did.
(BIRDS SINGING)
You played well today.
Oh, thanks.
That's nice of you.
I can be nice.
I know you can.
You know, the way you are in school,
I don't think you're like that, really.
What am I like, really?
Ah.
You can borrow it, if you like.
Oh, I‐I actually read it already.
I don't know why I picked it up.
Any good?
Yeah. I liked it.
You‐You'd like it, actually.
It's got a lot about feminism,
and all that.
Do your friends know you read so much?
Yeah, they wouldn't really be interested
in all that stuff.
You mean they're not interested
in the world around them?
Eh, not in the same way
that we would be,
but they have their own interests,
I suppose.
Right. Like, uh,
bragging about
who they're having sex with.
Yeah. They can do a bit of that.
I'm‐I'm not defending it.
Doesn't it bother you?
Most of it wouldn't.
And then they do some stuff
that's a bit over the line,
and that would bother me,
obviously, but...
they're my friends at the end of the day.
It's different for you.
Why is it different?
(CONNELL SCOFFS)
CONNELL: You know, um...
You were saying the other day
that you like me.
B‐by the photocopier, you said it.
Yeah.
Yeah. Did you mean "like" as...
a friend, or what?
No.
Not just as a friend.
Yeah.
I thought that might be implied.
I just... wasn't sure.
(CLEARS THROAT)
See, I'm...
just a little confused
about what I feel, I think.
Uh, it'd be awkward in school
if something happened with us.
No one would have to know.
(CONNELL GRUNTS SOFTLY)
That was nice.
(CHUCKLES)
What, what are you laughing for?
Nothing.
Well, you're acting like you've
never been kissed before.
(CHUCKLES) I haven't.
(BOTH LAUGHING SOFTLY)
LORRAINE: Connell.
CONNELL: Uh...
Don't tell anybody
in school about this, all right?
Like I talk to anyone at school.
(SCOFFS)
(SIGHS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
♪♪
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Yeah, I'll pop in for a bit, all right.
See ya in there.
Yeah, busy. Yeah.
See you inside, all right?
(PEOPLE CHATTING)
(BASS POUNDING SOFTLY)
All right?
How's things, boss? Keeping well, yeah?
All right. Thanks.
(CROWD YELLING AND CHEERING)
ROB:
Come here to me. Fair play to ya.
Man of the hour!
CONNELL: Ah, no, not really.
Thought you'd change your mind.
Oh.
Well, I'm glad you're here.
Shots.
Go on, get that into ya.
Cheers. All right.
Cheers!
ALL: Cheers!
(ALL CHEERING)
(DISTANT DOG BARKING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
How's the craic, Waldron?
All right.
You were on form on Friday.
So you were feelin' it, were you?
He was almost as drunk as Rachel.
Fuck off, Rob.
You passed out in a hedge.
ROB:
That, I did. It was a good night.
GIRL: From what I can remember.
RACHEL: It was a good night.
Hey.
All right.
ERIC: Waldron?
Yeah.
ERIC:
Have you got that French homework, there?
Yeah, I do. Yeah.
Can I get it off you before break?
Give it to you now. I have it handy.
You're a lifesaver, man.
Throw it back to me, yeah?
Yeah.
(BACKPACK ZIPPING)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(SOFT MUSIC)
♪♪
(BRAKES SQUEALING)
(INSECTS CHITTERING)
(CAR APPROACHING)
♪♪
Hiya.
MARIANNE: Your mum's not here.
Yeah, um...
Can I come in?
Thanks.
You're not busy or anything, no?
No, I'm just...
Are you going to start kissing me again?
(MOANS SOFTLY)
Can we take our clothes off?
(CHUCKLES) No.
Not here. It's...
Uh...
Got a free house on Saturday.
You could come over then,
if you wanted to.
Will anyone else be there?
No.
Are you sure we can't
take our clothes off?
Oh, no. Yeah.
(CHUCKLES)
I said I'd take Lorraine to the shops,
and this is, uh...
(CONNELL SIGHS)
MARIANNE:
You were tempted, though, for a second.
Not really.
You were tempted.
I tempted you.
So you'll come on Saturday?
("WARPED WINDOW" BY ANNA MIEKE)
♪ I have been wandering ♪
♪ Long ♪
♪ Came across your, oh so delicate ♪
♪ Delicate frame ♪
♪ Brittle boned you sat ♪
♪ Crouched and decayed ♪
♪♪
MARIANNE:
Everyone's a mystery, in a way.
I mean, you can never really know
another person.
CONNELL:
Do you actually think that, though?
♪♪
Do your friends know about us,
that we were together?
MARIANNE: No.
No one would have to know.
CONNELL:
I just like talking to you.
MARIANNE:
How do you know what you want?
Most of the time, I don't have a clue.
What about now?
I feel nothing for you. Nothing.
Why are you saying this?
It's funny.
The decisions you make
when you like someone,
and then your whole life is different.
MARIANNE:
It's not like this with other people.
♪♪