My name is Michael Scofield.
My brother is facing the electric chair,
framed for a crime he didn't commit.
What is it about this case
that the Secret Service is so interested in?
The man killed
the Vice President's brother.
After his appeals
were exhausted,
there was only one way to get him out.
This is the police.
Put down your weapon.
Michael?
I'm getting you out of here.
- It's impossible.
- Not if you designed the place, it isn't.
- You've seen the blueprints.
- Better than that.
I've got them on me.
I've been at Fox River
nearly a month now.
In that time, I've assembled
a group that has all the resources
we need to not only break out,
but to stay out.
I'm Michael, by the way.
- Dr. Tancredi...
- Tancredi like the Governor?
While we dig on the inside,
our lawyer searches for the truth
on the outside.
I have information that will lead
to the exoneration of Lincoln Burrows.
Somebody on the inside
claims they can exonerate Lincoln.
Someone's been talking.
Anyone that's a threat is expendable.
They're ready for you,
Madam Vice President.
24 hours from now,
my brother is scheduled to die.
But the way I see it, 24 hours from now,
we'll be out of the country.
He's there.
It can't be done.
We're not getting out of here.
Unfortunately, pretty,
that ain't an option.
You are gonna get us out of here.
Unless you're gonna use your shank
to take out the pipe, put it away.
I'm gonna put it in your neck,
you don't get us out of here.
- Bring it down a peg, T-Bag.
- Shut your mouth!
Remember, pretty,
I am serving life plus one.
So if I get busted for attempted escape,
I'm gonna throw in a homicide,
no problem.
That's like a parking ticket to me.
Yeah, I didn't want to throw up
on the floor, so I just came to the drain.
Just let me walk this off. I'll be fine.
Lincoln, there is no reason
for you to be here if your IV isn't in.
- Everything all right in here?
- It's fine.
Why isn't he cuffed to the table?
What's he gonna do, steal a cotton ball?
Can't have him walking around, Doc.
You know that.
What was that?
Put your wrist out.
You gonna turn this into something?
I'm not gonna say it again.
Put your wrist out.
Hey, Keith, come check this out!
Keith?
We got to go. Now. Give me the rope.
Give me the rope now!
Tie that off.
Let's just stay here, okay?
Okay, I'm down.
We gotta go, Michael.
Get down. Let's go.
- Did it break off or did someone break it?
- I don't know.
Here's the other half.
Hey, hey.
- What's up, Brad?
- Heading over to Sharkey's.
It's two-for Tuesday. Wanna hoist a few?
Man, I'd love to, but my wife is
cooking dinner and I told her I'd be home.
Wuss. Anybody else?
Suit yourselves.
Ain't none of the Sheetrock
in front of the break room been touched.
- The PI's are letting it dry out.
- Still?
Westmoreland!
I'm caught
on something.
Come on, come on, come on, come on!
Stay there! Stay down there!
- Why was this door locked?
- It wasn't locked, boss.
The fan kept pushing it open.
So we just had to wedge it closed.
You've been in here all night
not doing a damn thing.
The room is still wet, boss.
There's nothing we could do.
It's not like we've been having a picnic.
Bunch of shiftless, no-good convicts.
You got something to say, Scofield?
Wrap it up.
And all four of you,
get your asses back to the block.
Hey!
Get these nitwits back to the cell block.
You seem to be one light.
Right here, boss.
No, no. No way!
I should be halfway
to seeing my family right now!
Let's go.
Now!
Keep it moving. Move it.
Go, ladies.
Do you think he knows?
Lincoln?
I'm here with Henry Pope,
who is the warden of Fox River Penitentiary
where Lincoln Burrows is scheduled to die
by electrocution at 12:01 a.m. Tomorrow.
Warden Pope, can you tell me what's
gonna happen in the next few hours?
There are strict
Department of Corrections guidelines
that govern every aspect of an execution.
Measures taken to make sure that
the process goes as smoothly as possible.
Such as?
The correctional officers will do
a walkthrough,
we'll review the list of witnesses,
the chair will be checked and rechecked
to make sure there's no problem.
And Mr. Burrows himself.
Have you spoken with him?
What are his thoughts
in these final hours?
I'd say that's between him and his God.
And maybe the Governor.
I understand Burrows' attorneys
are going to request a stay.
I wish them the best of luck.
Does that mean you believe he's innocent?
It means...
I believe in the process
but I don't relish the prospect of
taking another man's life.
Whether it's just or not,
there's no joy that lies before us today.
Okay, thank you very much, Warden.
And we will be here with you
throughout the night
watching and waiting to see
if Lincoln Burrows does in fact become
only the 13th person to be executed
in the state of Illinois since 1976.
Just so you got one less thing
to worry about,
I want you to know I ain't mad at you.
Thank you.
- How long until...
- 16 hours.
Are his lawyers making any progress?
Is there still a chance with that?
No. There's only one person
who can really stop this execution.
Hey.
I need to see my brother. Just to talk.
For five minutes.
Yeah. Yeah. I'll try.
I'm sorry. I'm told
that you have to wait until final visitation.
Would you talk to your father
for me, please?
Believe me, my father knows
where I stand on the death penalty
- and I'm just as clear on his...
- Sara... Dr. Tancredi, I'm sorry.
This isn't about the morality
of the death penalty. This is...
This is about killing an innocent man,
my brother,
and surely your father
can't be in favor of that.
Just talk to Lincoln's attorneys,
just for an hour,
and I swear to God
you'll be convinced of his innocence.
Michael,
I would pick up the phone right now
if I thought there was any chance
that I could make a difference,
but you have to understand,
I'm the last person in the world
that my father listens to.
He hates what I do,
he hates what I believe in.
And if I'm the one asking for clemency
for your brother, your brother won't get it.
I'm sorry.
Look, if Terrence Steadman
is still alive, Lyle,
then it can't be Terrence Steadman
buried in the ground.
Yeah, but a secret informant
claims that Steadman is still alive?
I don't know, Nick.
It all sounds pretty far-fetched.
You're his clerk, just get us on the docket.
Nick, you're asking him
to commit political suicide
by granting a stay of execution to
Illinois' most notorious death row inmate.
Officially, all we're asking
is for an exhumation order.
If he grants it, he can order a stay
until the tests come in.
An exhumation order?
Oh, well, that's better. Digging up
the Vice President's brother. No way.
Lyle, Lyle, look, we took Intro
to Civ Pro together, remember?
We studied for the Bar day and night
in that crappy little apartment of yours,
talking about how we were going to
make a difference.
Nick, you filed an 11th-hour motion,
and Judge Kessler's docket
is full this afternoon.
Come on, Lyle,
everyone knows you run that courtroom.
You can't adjust things around a bit?
The informant that was killed yesterday,
I was there.
I know firsthand,
these people will do whatever they can
to frame Lincoln for Steadman's murder.
All we're asking is to be heard.
I'll give you 15 minutes this afternoon,
that's it.
- Thank you.
Yeah, you're welcome.
- He doesn't even know what happened.
- He knows you tried.
- Do you think so?
- He's your brother. He knows you.
So, yes.
I promised
I would get him out of here.
You promised a lot of people, pretty.
- Enough, man, all right?
- This don't concern you, boy.
You don't get a man's hopes up
like that and then just...
Back up or I'll beat your skinny ass
into the ground.
And it wouldn't take much to do it.
- All right, ladies, rec time is over.
- Back on the block!
You owe me a ticket out of here, pretty.
And I will collect.
- I'm really sorry about your brother.
- Thanks.
Look, I know you were
counting on this, so...
Let me worry about my problems.
'Cause I know you've got enough
on your mind right now.
For what it's worth, over the years,
I've known a few men
who've sat on that chair,
and as the day gets near,
all you can really do is pray it goes quick.
Once, about 10 years ago,
there was a man caught a few sparks,
not enough to do the job.
Had to wait another three weeks
while they reset the whole process.
And it may sound crazy, but he said
it was the worst three weeks of his life,
because it's not the lightning
that kills you, it's the wait.
So, take solace in the fact
that your brother's wait is over.
So if something happens to the chair,
he's got three more weeks?
There's a lot of protocol in killing a man.
A new death warrant,
another medical clearance.
A lot can happen in three weeks.
Yo, what scrapes, yo?
Thanks.
- What y'all talking about?
- Nothing.
Keep it together.
Go, keep it together!
I'm going in.
It's daytime.
I'll hang a sheet.
Do you have any questions about
what's gonna happen tonight?
When I get to eat,
when I'm supposed to walk,
how it's gonna feel
when they tighten the belts.
Any of that gonna help come midnight?
Some feel it's best to be prepared.
- How's Michael?
- He's anxious to see you.
Unfortunately, we've been told that
that's not possible until final visitation.
- You've been through this before?
- No.
Just so you know,
a doctor needs to be present, so,
for what it's worth, I'll be there tonight.
- Can I ask a favor?
- Yeah. What?
When I'm gone, can you
look out for my brother?
What were you doing back there?
- So you like doing that, too?
- Dipping a fry in the shake? Hells, yeah.
Good times. Good times.
So what's going on out there?
Nothing, you know,
just staying out of trouble.
I meant in terms of any office gossip
you might have for me.
Yo, check it.
This one fool has been trying
to cop a joint.
So, I'll keep ear-hustling for that.
We had an agreement. You were supposed
to bird-dog Scofield and get back to me.
I been trying, man, I've been working
the corners. Trust me. I ain't got nothing.
I seen you talking to him in the yard,
him and the geezer.
Yeah, I talked to Scofield,
but he ain't told me nothing.
Then it's 100 bucks
for the burger and fries.
- Boss, you know I ain't got no money.
- Then you better start selling your ass.
100 bucks by the end of the shift,
or there's gonna be a bidding war
to see who gets you as their new cellie.
Beat it.
In the yard today,
I did hear Scofield say something.
And?
He said if something goes wrong
with the chair,
his brother gets three more weeks to live.
We're square. Get out of here.
- How's it going in here?
- Ready for liftoff.
- Chair is working?
- Yeah. Why?
Run a test.
I already did. The electrical contractor
signed off on the diagnostic this morning.
- We're good to go.
- Run it again.
- Why?
- Run it.
It ain't working.
Son of a bitch.
I don't know what could've happened.
So once they redo all the paperwork,
your brother gets three more weeks.
Right.
- So we got time, then.
- Not a lot. But some.
Are we still going through the infirmary?
If I corrode that pipe again,
they'll know something's up.
You got another way?
Right now I'm just worried
about getting through tonight.
Careful. There's 2,000 volts
running through that thing.
Oh, God.
I came in here a man. Give me
the strength to walk out of here a man.
I came in here a man...
I came in here...
Give me the strength to walk...
I want to see my brother.
- When we move you to final visitation.
- When's that?
Right after we do this.
Just...
It's your last day, Linc.
I'd prefer to keep you out of cuffs
as much as possible, but
I need some assurances.
You've always been straight up
with me, Stolte.
You have my word.
Your Honor, from the outset,
Mr. Burrows' case has been tainted
by conspiracy characterized
by destruction of evidence,
distortion of the truth
and witness intimidation.
Again, Judge, I have to object.
These are some serious accusations
with absolutely no proof.
No proof? What have I been arguing
for the past 20 minutes?
You got me.
Judge Kessler, Mr. Tucci
might not appreciate the weight
of what we've just presented,
but surely you must.
As Miss Donovan stated,
a top video forensic analyst
has disputed the authenticity
of a surveillance tape
that was the key piece of evidence
in convicting Lincoln Burrows.
That's the tape
that no longer exists, right?
Because your client had it destroyed.
Unless my client is a rusted water pipe
in the County Records Office,
I'm afraid you're mistaken.
Judge, Miss Donovan's apartment
was blown up in an attempt
to silence both her and me.
That was independently corroborated
as a gas leak, Your Honor.
Judge, a month ago,
a Secret Service agent
named Paul Kellerman visited my office.
I saw Kellerman last night, when he shot
and killed another agent, Daniel Hale,
right after Hale told me that
Terrence Steadman was alive and well.
Your Honor, I'm presenting to the clerk
an affidavit from the director
of the Secret Service Agency.
It states that at no time
has there ever been
an agent of that organization by the name
of Paul Kellerman, or Daniel Hale.
In addition, there were no other witnesses
to this shooting.
No bullets were found, no blood,
no shell casings.
The only witness to this alleged murder
is Veronica Donovan,
Lincoln Burrows' ex-girlfriend.
Now, Your Honor, I feel for Miss Donovan.
- Save it.
- I do.
But desperation causes desperate acts.
And that's what we're seeing here today,
Your Honor.
My client,
the Vice-President of the United States...
Judge Kessler.
Do either of you have any evidence
that is admissible?
Even just tangible?
Your claims, if true, are terrifying.
But anything or anyone
that could verify your story
is either gone, missing or dead.
I know time is of the essence.
I'll reserve judgment for now.
I'll take your arguments
into consideration,
and I'll have a decision within a few hours.
These little bastards are the bane
of my existence, I swear to God.
You get this a lot?
Yeah, they're attracted to the heat
when they're cold,
plus, they got collapsible vertebrae
or some deal,
so they can squeeze through a crack
yea big, if they're determined.
And he shorted out the wire
just by biting on it?
Not by chewing on the wire alone,
but if the tail touches metal,
it acts as a ground, and boom, fuse pops.
- Along with the rat.
- I'll be damned.
So, can you change the fuse?
Yeah, there's another one right here
in the box.
Can you do it now?
Right after I notify the state
and fill out the paperwork.
Now, hold up a minute.
Both of you.
We're gonna give more time to a guy
who killed the Vice President's brother?
- This guy's a terrorist.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Forget about losing our jobs,
we could all face charges.
Only the three of us know.
Real easy to keep it that way.
It's your guys' call.
How much longer?
- Six hours.
- Open on 40!
Scofield, your brother's gonna be
transported to final visitation soon.
You can meet him there.
You look surprised.
You knew it was scheduled today.
No, I...
You were saying?
They'll be transporting you
to final visitation in a minute.
Thanks for keeping your word, Linc.
Linc, you're gonna have to change
into these.
What's that?
At the moment of death,
the body becomes incontinent, so...
- It's a diaper?
- Yeah.
You need to wear it.
Make me.
Good look, huh? It's for the electricity.
Hair gets in the way or something.
I did everything I could.
I know you did.
Last time I had my head shaved
was when I was running with Derek.
- Remember Derek?
- Uh, yeah.
Bet me 40 bucks I wouldn't shave it.
I said, make it $100.
Still owes me.
- Have you heard from Veronica?
- She's supposed to be coming.
- Is there any news on the appeal?
- Don't know.
'Cause there could still be a...
Stop, Michael, please.
This thing's gonna happen.
I got to get my head straight.
Let's just share memories, swap stories,
talk about the damn weather,
anything but torturing myself
with the idea of hope.
I can't take it anymore.
All right.
- You can't go, LJ.
- I don't care. I have to see him.
You can't go to the prison.
You'll never make it through the gate.
There will be cops everywhere.
Look, you got to wait until
we get all this cleared up, all right?
It's the judge's clerk.
Lyle, what do you got?
Yeah.
- Thanks, man.
- They ruled against us.
Yeah.
- I'm gonna go and see him.
- I'm gonna stay here with LJ.
- You gonna be okay going alone?
- Yeah, I'm gonna be fine.
Tell Lincoln... You know, just, we tried.
Go to the back room. Go!
You're the attorneys for Lincoln Burrows?
You letting me win, Michael?
- No.
- Show me your cards.
- I'm not gonna show you my cards.
- Give me your cards.
- Gin.
- Funny, that.
Three out of five.
- How often would you make those for LJ?
- Whenever I had him on weekends.
May be the only decent thing
I ever did for him.
- No. You were there for him.
- Not enough.
I don't know how I can
stomach this stuff before...
We lost the appeal.
Your friend Sara came by, though.
- Did she hear you out?
- She did.
- Is she gonna talk to her father?
- I sure as hell hope so.
It doesn't matter anymore, guys.
You've done more than enough for me.
That's the most important thing.
I couldn't bring LJ.
I know.
I can get him on the phone, though.
What do I say?
LJ. It's your dad.
Hey, Dad.
LJ. So this is it.
Yeah.
I... I want you to
stick with Veronica and Nick
and clear your name. You'll be all right.
I wish I could be there, Dad.
Me, too.
'Cause there's something
I want to tell you.
- What's that?
- I had a dream last night.
You and me were working on a house,
pounding nails.
And in the dream,
it felt like we were older.
It was so clear. The whole dream.
And when I woke,
I knew that today
wasn't going to be the end.
That...
That we'll see each other again, Dad.
I know it.
I love you, Dad.
Those numbers support Burrows' claim
about Terrence Steadman's
pending indictment.
Now, with the related murders,
and then the confidential informant,
I just wanted to make sure that
you were fully aware of the circumstances.
I'm fully acquainted
with the Burrows case, Sara,
but I never heard about any of this.
Well, I hadn't either, until I spoke
with Burrows' attorneys this afternoon.
And I understand
that most of this evidence
is technically considered circumstantial,
but I think you'll agree it's hard to ignore.
And how did you get involved
with all this?
These men are my patients.
It's my job to advocate for them.
Come on, Sara. How many of these guys
say that they are innocent?
Eighty, ninety percent?
It's not like you're asking me
for a new bike here, kid.
Being tough on crime,
capital punishment,
it's all part of a philosophy
that I believe in.
Part of a philosophy that I campaigned on,
was elected for.
I have to go back to Fox River.
I have to be there when they kill this man.
The least you could do is review his case.
And, Dad, if it helps,
pretend it didn't come from me.
I've never given a damn
about what people thought of me.
Never. The last couple of days...
I gotta admit, you know...
Lee Harvey Oswald, John Wilkes Booth,
Lincoln Burrows.
I'm gonna go down in history
with these freaks.
Bitch of it all is I didn't do it.
I didn't do it!
I didn't do it.
It's time.
Warden!
- What is it?
- It's the Governor.
Yes, Governor.
Okay. I understand.
The Governor has
reviewed your case fully.
He's not granting clemency.
Let's proceed.
You did your country and your party
a great service.
It won't go unnoticed.
- Thank you, Madam Vice President.
- Thank you, Governor.
Can't go past here.
Once he's in the death chamber,
you'll be escorted to the viewing room.
Can I...
Yeah.
I've loved you
since the first time I saw you.
Uncuff him.
Let's go, son.
- I didn't kill that man, Michael.
- Swear to me.
I swear to you, Michael.
Preparation can only take you so far.
After that,
you gotta take a few leaps of faith.
Don't give up on me.
- What if something happens to you?
- You just have a little faith.
Just have a little faith.
How about every Sunday,
we have our own special breakfast?
- Just you and me.
- Yeah.
- Give me your hand.
- You gotta have faith, LJ.
I love you, Dad.
I came in here a man.
Give me the strength
to walk out of here a man.