Previously on Prison Break:
What are you doing?
I'm trying to remember those
blueprints, what we lost to the burn.
Without them, we'll never
be able to navigate those pipes
beneath psych ward.
Then I need to know
where you got that burn. Right now.
Otherwise, your ass is going to solitary.
I put my blood into this...
How about you elaborate on that?
How about you
stop with all the questions?
You are a glorified bodyguard, that's it.
Okay, I got it.
- Put it down.
- You're not a killer.
Get out of the way.
You know, maybe they give you
those things for a reason.
Yeah. To keep me
in their invisible freaking handcuffs.
Hello, roomie.
You were right about my tattoo.
It is a path...
And I need you to remember
when you saw it, Haywire.
Who are you?
Scofield. Michael Scofield.
Doesn't ring a bell.
We met a while ago in Gen pop. Cell 40.
- Gen pop?
- General population.
Officer Bellick assigned you to my cell.
I have a tattoo, you drew it.
Haywire, do I look even
vaguely familiar to you?
Are you the guy who stole my toothpaste?
Yes, yes. I stole your toothpaste.
So you do remember.
Candy man.
Mr. Patoshik.
- Mr. Scofield.
- No, thank you.
Medication is mandatory.
It's just a mild sedative
prescribed by Dr. Tancredi. Come on.
Then I'll talk to her directly.
I'm feeling better.
Oh, really? That's great. Now take the pill.
Take them. They're good.
I'm fine. Thank you.
Carter, could you come here a sec?
- So he's not coming back here?
- Doubt it.
They had him in the whack shack.
- What about Sucre?
- He's in ad seg. Why?
Middle cell, middle tier,
prime piece of real estate.
- You thinking what I'm thinking?
- Maybe.
We promise to keep it a single
for a couple of months, auction it off.
Make it happen.
I don't need medication.
Swallow it, or it's going in the rear door.
All gone?
Nice.
You were right, Haywire.
I did steal your toothpaste,
and you drew that tattoo from memory,
and I need you to do it again.
Middle cell,
cool in the summer, warm in the winter.
How much you asking?
- How much you got?
- $200.
- We got a deal?
- Deal.
Now get your ass out of here
and I'll put in the transfer.
Hey, man,
the toilet's leaking.
Look, it's dripping.
I'll put in a work order.
It'll be replaced in 24 hours.
You got it, boss.
- I heard you was moving some real estate.
- Already been moved.
- Ain't that Scofield's cell?
- Not anymore.
Close on 40!
Is that your daughter?
My wife gave me this when she was born.
Outliving your wife is bad enough.
Outliving your daughter...
No man should have to endure that.
How long does she have?
Hospital says a week, maybe two.
We got us a problem.
Mojo's moving into Scofield's cell,
and that ain't all.
He's bitching about the toilet,
so Geary's putting in a work order.
- They move that toilet...
- They find the hole.
We are all screwed.
- How much Mojo promise?
- $200.
Oh, Gomer, now you see,
you had me scared there for a second.
- I hear you got a cell.
- Not anymore.
And if you were smart,
you'd keep quiet about that.
- Hey, look, I'll double what you're getting.
- I'm getting $250.
$500? Ain't a problem.
I ain't talking cigarettes
and extra chow line desserts here.
I'm talking green paper
with dead white guys on it.
I said it ain't a problem.
Come on.
- Where?
- It's a surprise.
- I don't wear a diaper.
- I never said you did.
Then what are you doing?
You got something in your teeth.
- What?
- Oh, yeah. Right there.
- I don't...
- It's right there in the back.
Come on.
- Why are you doing this?
- I am helping you.
Remember what you used to call
those little pills?
"Invisible handcuffs."
Handcuffs on your mind.
You hate them, remember?
You got a phone call.
- Who is it?
- Your son. It's an emergency.
Oh, LJ, what were you thinking, kid?
I don't care
what happens to me anymore, okay?
They won. They'll always win.
I just wanted
to take one of them down with me.
Put Veronica back on.
Lincoln?
What are the charges?
Attempted murder.
He's also being arraigned for the murder
of his mother and his stepfather.
- I guess bail is out of the question?
- Exactly.
Anything you can do?
Right now, his only shot is
if we can get him tried as a minor.
But he needs to show some remorse.
I need to sell to the court
that he was just a scared kid.
But where his head's at right now,
he won't listen to me.
He'll listen to me. I need to see him.
Lincoln, there's no way.
He gets tried as an adult,
he may as well sit in my lap in the chair.
- You got to do something, Veronica.
- Okay.
Look, I'll petition the DOC,
but it's a million-to-one shot
they're gonna let you out to see him.
All right.
Yo, Trumpets.
You all gotta round up all outstanding
debts that are due ASAP, all right?
Do it right now?
Like yesterday, all right?
- I'll put it out there.
- Good.
Are you insane?
You are done, bodyguard.
Lincoln's son, a 16-year-old pothead,
managed to track you down
and shoot you.
You are now
a witness in his criminal investigation.
I can still do my job.
You are not to make a move on Burrows
under any circumstance.
We make that call.
You know what, trixie?
There are actually higher agendas here.
Yes, there are,
and they don't belong to you.
Paul Kellerman no longer works
for the Secret Service.
You're just good old Owen Kravecki
from now on.
Have I made myself clear?
Hey.
I need you to focus.
I need you to remember what you drew.
Haywire. Time for group.
Come on, buddy. Let's go.
There we go.
It's a path.
Yes. It is a path.
Let's go.
So, what's up, man?
Here's the thing. You got nothing coming.
All your outstanding markers,
they're mine now.
Is that so?
You got a problem with it,
go cry to your new crew,
T-Bag and the white boys.
Okay, so that's what this is all about.
This is about staying true to your own.
Well, you know what, man?
I can have tea
with the grand wizard of the KKK if I want,
and I still get my money.
- You got that, little boy?
- No. We don't got that.
Now, out of respect
for what you once were,
I'm gonna let you walk away.
You were right.
The pills don't let me see the pathway.
That's a pathway to hell.
No, it's not. It's just the opposite.
I remember.
Looks like the Bank of Africa
wasn't allowing any withdrawals.
Look, we are gonna have to find
another way to get that money, okay?
Well, then I reckon
it ain't too much of a problem
for our friend here to rummage up,
ain't that so, D.B?
A, I'm not D.B. Cooper,
and, B, there's no visitation today.
Which means that none of us can get
any money from the outside world.
I guess that only leaves us
with one real option.
The kitchen game.
Gambling? And that's your solution?
Son, trust me.
When I play cards, it ain't gambling.
There's maybe five people in this country
that can do what I do with a deck of cards.
So why are you just bringing this up now?
'Cause if Jesus, over there,
catches you sleeving aces
in the kitchen game,
well, let's just say
there are lots of knives handy.
Of course,
you need 50 bucks just for the sit-in,
and since we don't have any money,
I'd say we're in a catch-doubley-deuce.
You sit right here.
There you go. Take this.
And this.
Oh, no. It's gone.
That's why I need you to fix it.
That's why I need you to remember
what was there before.
Oh, this is bad. You can't break a path.
- Then it doesn't lead anywhere.
- That's right.
That's why I need you to remember
what was there before it was broken.
I remember. I remember the demons.
Wait, no, maybe they were pilgrims.
They were pointing to the way,
and they were saying,
"This is the way, this is the way."
I can't see it.
I can see it, but I can't see it.
I'll be right back.
Hey!
I need you to give Sucre a message.
Tell him I'm okay,
and that I'm trying to fill in the blanks.
He'll know what that means.
- You're trying to fill in the blanks?
- Just do it. Please.
What the hell am I gonna do now?
You've been down in 13
as long as I can remember.
Why the sudden interest in moving?
Second-story units like this
don't come on the market too much.
I figure since I'm getting on in age,
maybe it's time I retired in comfort.
Open on 40!
Make it quick.
Hey, Bob Vila, it's a cell.
Quit kicking the tires and make a decision.
I'll give you 100 bucks for it.
You wasted my time.
Get the hell out of here.
Sorry, boss. I thought it was a good bid.
Close on 40!
Hello, Benjamin.
Now, let me see,
minted in 19 and 72.
That's your buy-in.
The rest is up to you.
Hot damn.
- Keep walking, peckerwood.
- Got the buy-in for the card game.
Go get our money, boy.
Unfortunately, you and I are gonna
have to be partners in this endeavor.
Oh, hell, no.
I don't play cards, I'm a dice man.
Look, all you need to know is this,
every time I deal,
you bet big and never fold.
See, if I'm winning every time I deal,
I end up with a Colombian necktie.
You know what I'm saying?
But if you're the one raking in all the cash,
well, I seriously doubt anyone would
ever think you and I are working together.
It's all right, baby, yeah.
Excuse me.
I've been all over town.
I can't find a charger for this.
- Well, let me check.
- Thanks.
How you doing, Savrinn?
- Where's your girl?
- She's doing her job, all right?
Filing a petition down at the courts.
She'll be at my place in about an hour.
See, that was easy.
I shouldn't have to chase you down
to get that information.
Why don't you just take a step back?
And why don't you remember
who you're talking to, who I work for?
You need to keep
an eye on Veronica Donovan.
Not some of the time, all of the time.
'Cause pretty soon,
we're gonna call in our favor,
unless you want to go back on our deal.
- No.
- Good.
Be in touch.
Haywire.
Haywire, did you take your meds?
Well, come on.
You got something in your teeth again.
You should be careful when you tell people
to remember things, Michael.
Because I remember everything now.
I remember how you set me up!
How you smashed your own head
and had me sent back here.
I also remember this.
The pathway.
Your map.
Your escape.
Give me that.
Don't. Don't.
Now, do I tear this up
or do you tell me exactly where
and when you're doing this?
- It starts in the basement.
- Okay.
This line leads
from the hatch in the coal room,
to this pipe system here,
and that runs to the infirmary.
That's how we'll get out.
I just need to get out of psych ward
to set things up.
But three days after I'm gone,
I'll come back up through the basement
and get you out.
You're just telling me what I want to hear.
No, I'm not.
I need you to let me get us out of here.
I need you to trust me.
If you try to screw me over again
I'll kill you.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- How did it go?
- Filing the petition was easy,
getting it approved,
that's a whole 'nother story.
- You found the charger?
- Oh, yeah.
- Why didn't you plug it in?
- I was just... Just thinking for a minute.
- About what?
- Nothing.
We're in business.
What is it?
His entire phone book is still in here,
322 numbers.
No open seats. Gotta wait.
- C-Note, crap or get off the pot.
- I'm thinking.
We ain't betting on CPT here, man.
Either you gonna see his bet
or you can go outside
and Million Con March
or whatever your people do.
Either way, get on with it, son.
I'm in.
Three bitches, bitches.
What you holding?
You tell me.
- Full house.
- A full house?
That's a concept a Mexican should be
quite familiar with, eh, Jesus?
She said what?
She said, in unequivocal terms,
that I was not to move on Burrows.
Whatever their agenda is with Burrows,
it is not the same as ours.
This whole business with his father,
it interferes with the one thing
that we set out to do in the first place.
Put Lincoln Burrows in the ground.
If he lives,
you're the one that stands to lose,
not the Company.
They get themselves another candidate,
and you're the one
that suffers the brunt of it.
Then maybe it's time we broke ranks.
We do that,
they pull support for the campaign.
You know that, don't you?
That is, if they know, Paul.
Smell that kitty.
Jacks or better, Trips to win.
Last hand.
I'm tired of losing all my money today.
- How much you up?
- I don't know. $300.
- Does it hurt?
- What?
The horseshoe up your ass.
Rather be lucky than good, ping-pong.
Misdeal. Bury the card.
- Man, I don't care if you all saw my card.
- Yeah, I bet you don't.
- Bury the card, young blood.
- Hey, chill, wrinkles.
Ain't my fault saltine here
got a sloppy deal.
That there was just uncalled for.
Now, all right. You know what?
I'll tell you what.
I'm gonna deal another hand,
you gonna be such a baby about it.
On a misdeal, you bury the card,
finish out the hand.
House rules.
- Warden.
- I have some good news for you, Linc.
Somehow, your lawyer's
petition went through.
The Department of Corrections
is allowing you a one-hour visit
with your son.
I've never seen
one of these granted before, ever.
- Good lawyers.
- No lawyer's that good.
I'll make the travel arrangements,
but this is not going to be
a ride in the country.
You're gonna be y-cuffed,
and the men are gonna be heavily armed.
- I don't want any problems.
- There won't be, I just want to see my son.
I'll bet all I got.
$82.
You better have some aces
shoved up there with that horseshoe,
or that pot's mine.
You in or out?
I'm in.
And I raise you $74.
- I said I only got $82 left.
- Well, then I guess you're out of luck.
- You never heard of a gentleman's game?
- Yes, I have, but this ain't it.
You want to borrow some money?
Ask your boys.
But I'm in here to make money, bro.
You want welfare,
you'd better vote Democrat.
If you know what's good for you,
you'll stay away from me in the yard.
You think you're smarter than me?
No, no, no!
Okay, there's a pathway.
No, there's a pathway! There's a pathway!
Look, he's trying to escape!
He's trying to escape. This is his map!
- Haywire, I need you to come back!
- He set me up!
- Zap him!
- No! No!
There he is.
Hey, boss.
I think you dropped something, man.
That's half a G-note.
- So when do I move in?
- You don't.
What?
- Oh, come on, chief, now, we had a deal.
- Renegotiation, the price is $700 now.
That ain't right. I just gave you $500.
What you gave me was a down payment.
If you can't come up with the rest, well...
No, no, no! Wait, wait, wait. Just hold on.
One minute, all right?
Oh, man, he's trying to shake us down.
- I'm gonna need that watch.
- Not an option.
Look, would you rather be
looking at a picture of your daughter
or holding her in your arms
once you get outside?
Hey, look, man,
Father Time owed me a few bones.
He gave me this in trade.
That should be
more than enough to cover it.
Not bad.
Your problem is somebody
already gave me $700 for the cell,
so, you're S.O.L.
No! No! Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Wait a minute, wait a minute,
wait a minute. Look.
So you're just gonna
take my money and walk?
Yeah, well, write to your congressman.
Oh, come on!
- Hey.
- Hi.
- They said you wanted to talk to me.
- Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
Good.
Please.
Thanks.
I made you something.
It's an ashtray.
- I don't smoke.
- Yeah, I know.
But they only
let us make these and jewelry,
and I didn't figure you
for the macaroni necklace type.
It's very sweet.
How about we talk
about how you're doing?
I think we both know I don't belong here.
I don't remember much about that night,
but being locked up in ad seg,
something must've snapped.
What I'm trying to say is,
I think I've had enough of arts and crafts.
But that's your call.
And the doctors here
do say that you've been acting fine.
The problem is that
if you don't tell the Pope who burned you,
he's gonna lock you back up in ad seg.
And after a couple days of that,
you're gonna be right back here.
Michael, I hate what happened to you,
and I hate that you're here.
But you have got to let me help you.
If you want to get out of psych ward,
and stay out,
you've got to tell the Pope
the truth about that burn.
Out with the old, in with the new, cons.
I got a message from your cellie, bro.
He says he's okay
and he's trying to fill in the blanks.
Did he say he's trying,
or that he already got the blanks filled in?
Yo, man, I don't know.
I didn't write it down.
Okay. Now you gotta tell him
that I filled in the hole.
Yeah, yeah, I'm done
with your little secrets and messages, bro.
I saw Scofield's back.
He's got a burn in the same spot
as the burn in that guard's shirt.
I don't know what you're doing
but I have an idea, huh?
And I'm through helping you
until you tell me what's going on.
I can't, bro.
- Then good luck in the hole, jefe.
- No, no, no! Wait, wait.
Manche.
- Who's that?
- That's Linc, bro.
- Linc the Sink?
- Yeah.
Come here.
I think we can work something out.
All I can say is, before I get out of here,
Geary will pay. Believe that.
No one's getting out of here
if maintenance goes to
replacing Scofield's toilet.
I got a way to help you
with your Scofield problem.
- What'd you say, slim?
- I said I got a way to help you with...
- Who the hell said we had a problem?
- It's cool, man. Relax.
Lincoln and Sucre told me everything.
What in the hell did they tell you?
Exactly, what did they tell you?
Everything. They said I can come with you,
you know, on early parole,
if I can help get the Fish out of psych.
What are we, the A train?
Everyone gets to ride with us?
Why don't you take a walk,
before I give you a smack?
You got another solution to our situation?
I didn't think so.
Me and my cuz and Lincoln
came up with something.
Now, it can work, but it's risky.
You ready to get out of
this aquarium, Fish?
Assure me I'll be protected.
Michael, you know me
well enough by now.
Such assurances are not necessary.
With all due respect, Warden,
if I had been protected in the first place,
none of this would have happened.
- A name.
- Geary.
Geary?
He shakes cons down for money,
anything he can get his hands on.
He knew I went to college, so he must've...
He must've thought
I was rich or something.
Anyway, when I couldn't pay up,
he held me down with one arm,
and burned me with the other.
I don't know what he used,
but it was hot as hell.
What a surprise. Disconnected.
Two-hundred and fifty businesses,
72 residences, covering all 50 states.
- London, Martinique, Jakarta, Dakar.
- All the numbers out of service.
As soon as Quinn disappeared,
they must've
erased the paper trail within days.
Is there anything they can't do?
My P.I. Buddy in DC.
What if I send him all this,
see if he can make
a connection between the numbers?
I'll tell him I need it ASAP.
- Thank you.
- Oh, it's no big deal.
I'll just overnight him all this stuff.
No. For everything.
For hanging in there, keeping me going.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Guy with a six ERA,
signs for four mil a year.
Sucks at his job, he still gets a raise.
You suck at your job.
You should ask the Pope for a raise.
Very funny.
Warden, what brings you
to our little clubhouse?
Hey, what gives?
Hey, that was a gift from my old man.
Since when is your name Charles
and your dad's name Ann?
This is a railroad. I didn't do nothing!
Don't look at me like I'm some con.
You're as crooked as scoliosis.
I don't get caught.
When we get there,
I'll take you out of the y-cuffs
and put you in a four-piece.
- Got it?
- Got it, boss.
You play nice, I play nice.
- Understand?
- Got it.
She's here. I've got her.
Scofield for re-admission
to Gen pop.
- Welcome home.
- Thanks.
Never thought
I'd be so glad to be back in my cell.
Pope wanted me to give you this.
- What the hell are you staring at, anyway?
- Everything.