Previously on Prison Break.
You got a couple foxes
in your hen house, right?
They both want out of here.
They'll behave until then.
Look, this is it, man.
Ain't no do-overs this time.
We break out tonight,
or we ain't never getting out.
Brains of the outfit, huh, Scofield?
He's leading you off a cliff, boys.
Now you're acting
like you still in charge.
Pretend I ain't here.
Yeah, you and the radio.
The thing I can't quite figure is
with the crap storm this thing's become
why they haven't killed you.
We have an employee.
She's not working out.
We fire her. It needs to be that simple.
She's the Vice President
of the United States.
And that's all she'll ever be, Jim.
What's going on?
You get to Blackfoot,
you find Steadman.
Just give me a chance.
- No!
- Where's the lawyer?
We're through.
- Hey, hey, hey. You okay, old man?
- No!
Oh, my God!
Sound the alarm.
- Come on, Michael!
- Sound the alarm!
Come on!
Michael, come on, move it!
Michael, grab my hand!
Grab my hand.
- Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
- Get down!
Don't shoot, please!
We got a 10-98! Inmates over the wall!
- Who was with you? Who was with you?
- Nobody!
- Nobody, huh?
- No.
Talk or I swear to God,
I'll snap your neck right here!
I don't know! I don't know!
Names. I want names.
Scofield, Burrows, Sucre.
- And that Vanilla Ice kid.
- Who else?
- Was there anybody else?
- I don't know.
Was there anybody else?
Westmoreland.
We got inmates over
the wall. Repeat.
- How many?
- Eight.
Warden, they just found Bellick.
Get me my shotgun.
Pope's already given orders
for all the COs to hit the streets.
Did I stutter?
Get me my shotgun!
Those piles of crap,
doing what they just did,
they just signed their death warrant.
Every last one of them.
When those men
went over the wall, they made a choice.
That choice makes them
a threat to society once again.
Now, as many of you know, some
of those men are convicted killers.
Now, our job
is to protect and ensure
the safety of the general population.
That means if we have to bring them
down to ensure that safety,
by God we will do it!
This time we're playing for keeps,
gentlemen.
Now it's been at least 12 minutes
since they went over that wall.
That's one mile on foot at best.
If they've got their hands on a vehicle,
they could be 10 miles from here.
So let's get moving!
Yo, come on, man, we got to roll.
We don't got to do anything but wait
right here and let them get ahead of us.
I don't know
if we're gonna get a chance, papi.
Dogs. Son of a bitch.
- They're coming right for us.
- Nobody move.
They can't smell us.
But they can see us.
Hey, this is Nick. Can't get
to the phone. Leave a message.
Hey, Nick, it's me.
Look, I just landed in Montana.
I'm about an hour outside of Blackfoot.
And this house, it's got something
to do with Terrence Steadman's murder,
I know it.
And if whatever's here can help free
Lincoln, then I wanted to say thank you.
Bye.
Soft money makes the world go round.
You know it, and I know it.
You cut my funding and I can't run
a proper campaign without it.
There was a lot of internal debate,
trust me.
And there's every chance that
you can still win with your message,
- and it would certainly be our loss...
- Oh, cut the crap.
Is there anything else
you want to tell me,
or did you just come here to
twist the knife you stuck in my back?
Well, actually, I came here
to express our gratitude
for all that you've done for us
over the years.
And to let you know
that this isn't personal.
Surely you've been in politics
long enough to know that.
Look, is this about the energy bill?
The energy bill has nothing to do with it.
Why am I finding that
so tough to believe?
I'm a grown woman.
How about you give it to me straight?
All right.
The bottom line, Madam Vice President,
is that
you can't effect change
in the Oval Office.
And that is what we need the most.
Certitude.
Simply put,
you can't get things done.
Well, maybe you don't know me so well.
I highly suggest
that in the coming weeks,
as the race narrows
and the candidates start falling out,
that you walk away, quietly,
of your own volition.
Otherwise, maybe it'll be
of The Company's volition.
Hey, hey, take the suit off.
You're practically glowing in the dark.
- I only got my Skivvies on underneath.
- Take the suit off!
- I'll freeze to death!
- Hey! Hey, hey!
Hurry up.
We got to do something
about that freak.
You got it, dude. Come on.
Come on, hurry up. Hurry up.
Where the hell is the van?
Eyetie, where in the hell is the van?
Ye of little faith.
Come on, come on.
I told you. I told you.
Behind the wheel, Cro-Magnon.
Hey, hey, hey.
- What the hell you doing?
- I'm getting us invisible.
- John, where are the keys?
- What?
The keys, where are they?
I told you, in the garbage can
by the trees in a plastic bag.
What are you waiting for?
Oh, the keys.
Come on, come on.
The keys.
Must find the car keys.
Where are the keys?
The keys. The keys. The car keys.
There's not even a plastic bag.
No! No, no, no!
No!
We got the on-ramps to 55 and 80
being monitored.
We've got traffic checks
on 171, 6 and 53.
Special Services has secured a watch
on passenger lists
at O'Hare and Midway.
How are we doing with the wiretaps?
They're being set up on all the family
members of the escapees as we speak.
Surveillance teams
are being established
- outside the residences as well.
- Thank you.
What do you got?
Door wasn't forced. Lock wasn't picked.
As far as I can tell,
they basically just walked right in.
I don't see how that's possible.
These doors are locked down
every night when we leave.
It's priority number one.
- Only thing I can think is...
- What?
Someone left it open for them.
Hey, John, I've got to ask you
why you were so intent
on Lincoln driving here
and you taking that particular seat?
Now, what is it exactly you got up
underneath there, huh?
What the hell are you doing?
You think that will stop me, huh?
Think twice, Johnny boy.
You shoot me, pretty here
will be dragging around 170 pounds
of dead Alabama flesh with him.
Will be dragging around 170 pounds
And considering how much
you need him to get this little
Fibonacci vendetta of yours...
So I just don't think
you're gonna be pulling that trigger.
No.
You're gonna give me the key
to those cuffs, T-bag.
Give me the key, you son of a bitch.
Get it, get it. Get it.
You looking for this?
- Come on. Spit it out!
- Spit it out!
Come on.
Oops.
They drink this,
it's only a matter of minutes.
This glycoside saxitoxin hybrid goes
to work in the blood stream instantly.
Five minutes is the outside limit
even the strongest cardiac muscles
can continue to function.
After that, massive cardiac arrest
with no chance of survival.
What about toxicology tests?
Well, they'll reveal nothing.
Death will appear to be
from natural causes.
This is high treason.
You know that, don't you?
- It's fresh, boss.
- From tonight.
Can't be more than an hour old.
- Dogs get the scent?
- Already have.
Hey, boss, check this out.
Captain,
this guy lives up the road.
Works on the property during the day.
- You see a vehicle parked here?
- I think so, yeah.
- What did it look like?
- Like a... Like a van. A blue van.
And you didn't think
to report it to the authorities?
A parked car?
Come on.
If you think I won't gut you myself
to get that key,
you're in for a big surprise.
I encourage you to remember the last
time you came at me with a knife.
Shut up! Shut up! Both of you!
You can settle this in Mexico.
- How far to the airstrip?
- I guess five miles, maybe.
You know your jet better be there,
Mr. Mafia.
You feel me? It better be there.
Canine unit being deployed.
Roger that.
Push past the search perimeter
before we can pick up track. Over.
- They're everywhere out there.
- Tell me something I don' t know.
You're saying you don't know
anything about this?
- Honestly, I don't.
- The door was left open, Katie.
- It wasn't me.
- Well, then who was it?
Only you and Dr. Tancredi
were left at the end of the night.
- The orderly confirmed that.
- It wasn't me.
Then you're telling me
it was Dr. Tancredi?
No...
I know you know something, Katie.
And anything you know,
you have got to tell me.
If you don't, you are gonna lose
a lot more than your job.
Withholding information
makes you an accessory.
And I will press that button
if you don't start talking!
- Sara.
- What about Sara?
Sara had a thing for Scofield.
Thank you, Katie.
All I want to do is touch her belly,
feel that he's in there.
After that,
whatever I got to do, I'll figure it out.
I just want to touch her belly.
We're close, papi.
We got trouble.
Yo, dawg, man, this is bananas.
We got to get off this road.
- Any other way to the airstrip?
- This is the only road.
Then let's just run this bitch.
Somebody shut him up, or I will.
- Can we go back?
- That won't do us any good.
It'll only get us farther
from where we need to be.
Which means we got to
bust that roadblock.
Maybe not.
We've got to try and go around.
Come on.
We're gonna get that key from you.
I don't care if you got to crap it out.
You got a foul mouth sometimes, pretty.
What?
- Son of a bitch, we're stuck!
- Everybody out. Everybody out.
You heard.
- This for the speech tonight?
- Need some ID.
- Secret Service.
- Have at it.
Come on!
- This thing ain't going nowhere!
- How far is the airstrip?
On foot? Maybe two miles.
What the hell are we waiting for?
Let's move.
Three-legged race over here
ain't going to make it 10 feet.
- We'll manage, won't we?
- Sure, pretty. We're teammates.
- Teammates till the end.
- Let's get out of here! Let's go!
Let's go.
Let's go. Come on.
- This is as far as you go, my friend.
- What?
No, man, you can't leave me out here,
not like this.
We had a deal, remember?
- Yeah, but come on, bro.
- You and I, we're not bros.
And I don't think you want me
telling the guys what I know.
Now walk.
We got trouble, pretty.
We got more than that.
Go! Go! Come on!
Oh, my God!
Oh, come on.
Now what?
- What do we do now, Michael?
- I don't believe this.
What now?
This area clear. Negative contact.
It's coming back, y'all,
it's coming back!
Make yourself small.
There's no way we are gonna make
two miles like this.
Especially with that bird up there.
We are if I got something to do with it.
Excuse me.
What can I do for you?
Sort of was gonna ask you
the same question.
I run the tower during the day. There's
no traffic allowed here after sundown.
Had some mechanical problems.
You need me to take a look at anything?
No, no, we got it.
Don't trouble yourself.
We'll be on our way in no time.
- You sure?
- Positive.
Okay.
- Have a good night, hey, buddy?
- Yeah, you, too.
Those guys better hurry up.
Hey, it's me.
I've got an unidentified aircraft here
at Goose Park.
I think you better have a look at it.
Tail number's 986-Delta.
Hurry it up.
Tranquilo. Just let papi work
a little bit of his magic, okay?
- You know what you're doing?
- Are you kidding me?
Hot-wiring this thing
is like hot-wiring a toaster.
Now, if it were to be an Acura,
or one of those Chinese cars,
that's a whole different story.
Electronic ignition, computer chips,
forget about it.
But, no, we're good.
Well, that chopper's gonna be
coming back again, so hurry up.
Hey, yo.
What they got in Mexico, anyhow?
You never been there?
Ain't never been nowhere
except for Iraq,
Chi-Town and Fox River.
What you looking at?
Look, man,
is it a good place
where you can have a family?
Lots of families down there, so I hear.
Man, you know what I'm talking about.
For a black man,
an American man with a family.
So that's the plan, huh?
They're gonna meet you
down in Mexico?
Yeah, it's worse to not see them.
And I can't do that no more.
Not much of a life for them.
But it'll be a life.
More than what me and them have been
having for the last two years, man.
They're family, snowflake.
Ain't no way in hell
I'm leaving them behind.
We're good.
I must have done this a thousand times.
Man, I thought you got busted
for armed robbery.
That's what they caught me for.
Red's the juice, white is the ground.
You strike them together
and we blow this town.
- What? What?
- I don't get it.
Great. That's just great.
It's okay.
Sorry.
Engine's still warm, and I don't see
any other tire tracks out here.
They're on foot,
and judging by how hot this engine is,
they haven't gone far. Five,
ten minutes ahead of us, at the most.
Where are you? Renwick road?
A quarter mile west of Weber
on Renwick.
Okay, we've got Renwick on the south,
Weber on the east,
143rd Street on the north
and 55 on the west.
Units are in place along all those roads.
And I've got a dozen more coming.
Brad, this could be over
quicker than we thought.
We've got them boxed in.
Sir, we've got an update
on Dr. Tancredi.
Tell me.
None of the staff
had any interaction with her.
She left work suddenly
in the early afternoon,
returned for maybe an hour,
then left again. All of it's very erratic.
Has anyone been able to reach her?
Doesn't have a home line,
cell phone seems to be shut off.
Chicago PD identified her car
outside her residence.
They're getting an emergency warrant
to go in.
Sir, it's none of my business,
but are you gonna call the Governor?
This is his daughter we're talking about.
- Captain, the dogs picked up a trail.
- Which way?
- That way and that way.
- They split up?
- Looks like it.
- What the hell we waiting for?
I think it's pretty clear that
our policies have been effective.
We've had 14 consecutive quarters
of GDP growth above 3%.
The tax cuts are working.
- Madame Vice President!
Peter.
Madame Vice President, a lot of people
question the wisdom
of granting tax cuts to the oil industry,
in light of the fact that
they're seeing record profits.
Do you have thoughts on that?
We're a market-driven economy, Peter.
Punishing companies
for being a good business model
doesn't make a whole lot of sense
to this administration.
- Madame Vice President!
- Yeah, Rebecca.
Thank you. Madame Vice President,
are you saying...
if you're elected president?
If those tax breaks result in growth, yes.
Excuse me. Excuse me. Sir? Yes.
Sir, can I...
Where are they?
They were way the hell back there.
Now they're
slowing us down, man.
This ain't gonna work like this.
We've got to do something.
This way.
Come on.
What's going on? What's going on?
- Guys, what are you doing?
- What the hell you doing?
- I swear to God.
- You swear what?
It ain't gonna work.
I guess it was just meant to be,
hey, now, fellas?
He's lucky I didn't take this to his head.
You cut his... You cut his...
- You cut his...
- Sucre, shut up.
Hello!
Hello.
Come on, let's go.
- We can't leave him to just like...
- You want to stay here? Be my guest.
Good boy, good boy.
Boss, we got something.
Yes, this is Warden Henry Pope
at Fox River Penitentiary.
I need to speak with the Governor.
- Yes?
- Governor, I'm sorry to bother you,
- but there's been an...
- Are you watching this?
- Watching what?
- I suggest you turn on your TV, Warden.
Doctors at Washington
Medical Center have corroborated
that President Mills
was admitted into emergency care here
a little more than 45 minutes ago.
In the chief surgeon's words,
President Mills suffered
massive cardiac arrest,
doctors were unable to revive him.
The news out of Washington
Medical Center is official now.
The President of the United States,
Richard Mills, is dead.
And keeping with protocol,
Vice President Reynolds
is in an undisclosed location,
being sworn in as the 46th president...
"I will faithfully execute the office
of President of the United States,
"and will to the best of my ability,
"preserve, protect and defend
"the Constitution of the United States."
I hereby recognize you
as the 46th president of this country.
And now, if you'll excuse me,
I have a lot to attend to tonight.
Thank you, all.
And you said I couldn't get things done.
Madam Vice President,
perhaps we could get together
and discuss how to move...
It is "President" now, madam,
and you're going to have to talk
to my organizers.
My schedule is suddenly quite full.
I'm sure you'll understand.
Sara Tancredi! It's the police.
We have a warrant to come in.
It's easier if you just open the door.
Otherwise, we're gonna come on in.
- Dispatch, this is 15 David on scene.
- Roll a bus to 1616 Vanlear Drive.
Apartment 236. Possible overdose.
Likely DOA.
Copy.
- Copy 15 David.
- Bus en route.
The airstrip's on the other side
of that field.
Just 500 yards,
and this whole thing's over.
He's not moving.
Every second we stay here is another
chance for them to find the plane.
- We got to go now.
- Wait, wait.
All right, let's go. Let's go.
Michael.
If this doesn't work out,
I want you to know...
I know. I know.
Freeze. Don't move.
- I'll tell you when we got to go.
- No, man. I mean, we got to go.
Fire her up.
We find the defendant charged of
murdering Terrence Steadman guilty.
This stunt by Lincoln Burrows'
defense counsel
is an affront
to the memory of my brother.
We made an imprint
of the deceased's teeth,
and compared them to the dental
records of Terrence Steadman.
They were a perfect match.
Who killed Terrence Steadman?
Nobody.
Hello, Terrence.
I can see it.
- Faster.
- Oh, God.
Come on, let's go.
- It's on the runway. Right there.
- Let's move it. Let's go.
I see it, baby.
Let's go.
- We're almost there.
- It better be there, man.
It better be there.
What's the deal? Hey!
- Hey!
- Where's it going?
No! No!
What do we do now?
We run.
This way, this way.
Run into the dark. Run into the dark.
Stop and put your
hands up. You are completely surrounded.
Stop and put your hands up.
You are completely surrounded.