Previously on "Prison Break":
- I didn't kill that man.
- The evidence says you did.
I was set up.
Put down your weapon.
I find it incumbent
that you see the inside of a prison cell.
- I'm looking for Lincoln Burrows.
- Man killed the vice president's brother.
- Why do you want to see Burrows?
- He's my brother.
- I'm getting you out.
- It's impossible.
- Not if you designed the place.
- You've seen the blueprints.
Better than that. I've got 'em on me.
- There's a lawyer poking around.
- Ms Donovan? I didn't mean to scare you.
- It's gone.
- Does anyone else have a key to this place?
You were here.
I walked over to the cabinet and I...
Got an issue with our little friend over there?
Yeah. Maybe it's time
I lit up that leather once and for all, huh?
- What happened?
- Don't make me lie to you.
- You heard the news?
- No. What?
- They're brothers.
- Who?
Burrows and Scofield.
Michael Scofield?
I'm going into the walls,
see if I can access the roof.
Take the only thing Burrows has left.
The chair isn't the only way
to take a man's life in prison.
Just a few more rides.
Then you have to wrap it up.
Wow. Adam's getting bigger. Ten.
Not here.
We need a favour.
- I've been out of the life for years.
- I know.
Problem is, no one's gonna believe that
if I take the heroin in my pocket
and put it in the glove box of the reasonably
priced minivan you got over there.
I will cuff you. I will drag you
out of here in front of everyone.
What do you need?
What America needs
is an environmentally friendly,
logistically feasible
and economically responsible
alternative fuel source.
Leave a message
and I'll call you back. Thanks.
It's Wendy. I know you wanted to work
with no distractions, so don't pick up.
I just wanted to let you know that
Nick Savrinn left six messages for you...
- What did you tell him?
- What you said to say that you were in a meeting.
If he comes by tomorrow,
tell him I'm not there.
- OK. Goodnight, Veronica.
- Thanks, Wendy.
Look, I appreciate everything you've done,
but I don't want your help any more.
Don't want my help. Do you really think I had
something to do with that missing tape?
No. I'm just gonna go grab
a cup of coffee and get back to work.
I don't have time for this right now.
Veronica, just wait a second.
Will you hold on a second?
- Listen, what are you avoid...
- Don't touch me!
Everything OK, Miss Donovan?
Lucasz, do you mind
walking me back inside?
Take a walk, pal.
You're being paranoid.
- You're being paranoid.
- Go away, Nick.
Show some skin, Scofield.
Hey, Scofield!
I'm trying to sleep, boss.
- I can't get through the wall.
- What do you mean you can't get through?
I know how to do it.
I just don't have the time to do it.
We're locked up. All we got is time.
You don't understand.
I planned this break on a schedule.
Constantly coming up here for count won't
let me do what I need to do to get through.
If I'm not back on schedule, which means
we're through by the end of the day mañana,
we're not getting out of here.
There's three things for certain in life -
death, taxes and count.
The only way to stop count is...
- What?
- Never mind. It's a bad idea.
Worse than the idea of losing Maricruz?
A lockdown. We get Gen Pop locked down
for a day, you'll have all the time you need.
- And no count?
- Bulls don't even come by.
Only one problem.
How do we get a lockdown?
- Can you get to the prison AC unit?
- Maybe.
You want a lockdown?
You'd better get the inmates riled up.
And if you wanna piss off
the meat in concrete,
turn up the heat.
Drills and the Devil (Part 1)
- I thought you were retired.
- Never mind me.
Heavy hitters want this done,
so that means I want it done.
No screw-ups.
For you, Diamond, it's not a problem.
Burrows is as good as dead.
- Hottest April on record.
- Global warming.
Probably. You got a minute?
About five years' worth.
Sorry. Right.
- You never told me Burrows is your brother.
- Never came up.
Right. I'm curious if that
isn't because of my father, the governor.
He may not be the one pulling the switch, but
he has power to grant clemency and he won't.
And he never does.
My old man was an abusive drunk
who abandoned his family.
I don'tjudge anyone by their father's actions,
or inactions,
if that was your concern.
Just so you know,
I don't agree with his politics.
And I'm sorry about your brother.
I appreciate that.
Hey, this isn't much...
Um...
I have to give Lincoln a weekly checkup.
If you want, I could schedule the visits
to end right before
you come in for your shots.
That way you could at least see each other,
even if it's just in passing.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Greetings from the kitchen, fish. 100 bucks.
Theodore Bagwell,
a transfer back from the infirmary.
Check. Open 14.
We got you a little "get well" gift.
It's just the right size.
Thank you, boys.
I'll catch up with you later.
What's your name?
Seth.
Are you new, Seth?
Scared? Look at me, boy.
You probably heard stories about me.
They're not all true.
What do you say we go for a walk, huh?
- Your co-counsel's already here.
- Excuse me?
- What the hell are you doing here?
- Talking to my client.
Don't talk to him.
We don't know anything about this guy.
He found somebody that could help us out.
You have one minute.
I've been going over the incident report.
Somebody made an anonymous call
claiming to see Lincoln running away
from the garage with bloody pants.
You can't cross-examine a witness
if you don't know who it is.
- We don't need to. We know where he is.
- What do you mean?
A PI friend of mine was able to backtrack
the phone call to the police department.
Whoever made that call
couldn't have seen Lincoln that night.
How do you know?
Because the phone call
came from Washington DC.
You were supposed to turn off the AC,
not turn on the furnace.
- It's getting so hot in here.
- Did I say you could talk, Cherry?
You'll know when
I want you to open your mouth.
Geary!
- Do something about the heat.
- Doing the best we can.
Your best is garbage.
It's 100 degrees in here.
- Look like I got frostbite to you?
Line it up!
Why don't you transfer us all
someplace cooler, like Africa?
Get your ass on the line, convict.
We'll move when
the temperature situation is rectified.
Bellick, this is Mack in cell block.
We got some cons popping off.
Smack 'em, throw 'em on the line
and write 'em up.
If you can't handle it,
don't cash your paycheck this week.
This is not a good time, Doc.
I got a call a prisoner has heat exhaustion.
- He's faking it.
- Is that your medical opinion?
We got a bunch of overheated cons
getting loud in A-Wing.
I don't blame 'em. It's an oven.
Everything's under control.
You should go back to the infirmary.
When things calm down, I'll have
your patients transferred from Sick Bay.
- Just looking out for your best interests.
- And I appreciate that.
But Officer Bellick, we both know
it's illegal to deny a prisoner medical care
and you could lose yourjob over it.
I'm just looking out for your best interests.
Go right on in.
Thank you, sir.
Don't be a baby, T-Bag. It ain't that hot.
Not that hot?!
When this guy woke up this morning,
he was white!
You wanna cool off?
Step back.
We'll step back
when we get some wind blowing in here.
All right! That's it! Lockdown!
Everyone back to your cells!
I said everyone back to your cells.
Now, convicts!
- Lockdown!
- You got your lockdown. Do your thing.
- You're coming.
What? No, no, no, no.
I'm the lookout man, that's it.
I need you down there. It's a two-man job.
Let's hang a sheet.
You only hang a sheet when you
and your cellmate wanna get friendly.
You wanna protect your prison rep?
Or you wanna get out of here?
- What the hell's going on in here?
- They got belligerent and refused to rack in.
You locked it down
with inmates out of their cells?
Figured we could handle
20 out-of-control inmates easier than 300.
Listen up, bros. Bellick.
I got one for you.
What do you call a piece of white trash
who couldn't pass the cops exam
and now makes less than a mailman?
A CO.
- Get your hands off the fence.
- Suck it, pig!
You really let me down.
And that's hard to do,
because I don't expect much
from the inbred child of a retard.
That's right, Teddy.
I read your psych records.
About how your daddy
raped his mongoloid sister
and then nine months later
little Teddy pops out.
I'm gonna kill you!
Hot as hell.
They'll wear themselves out eventually.
The call was a fake.
What about a stay of execution?
- It's legally insufficient.
- What the hell does that mean?
It means the prosecution could point out
the evidence from your criminal trial.
The blood, the video, the gun.
A questionable phone call
is not gonna stack up to that.
- It's something, right?
- Absolutely. We got an area code.
My contact will track it to someplace more
specific... a building, neighbourhood, a block...
- to the person who made this call.
- OK. What happens next?
We need to catch the next flight to DC.
That is, of course, if you trust me now.
It's coming.
It's coming! It's coming!
Get on the train! Whoo!
Get on the train! Get on the train!
Let's get to my office.
Oh, just what I thought.
Piglets are scared of the big bad wolf.
Big bad wolf!
Oh, just what I thought.
Get on the train!
Come on.
Marilyn, no!
Whose keys are those?
I guess in the commotion...
How many rounds you think you're going to
get off before they get their hands on you?
This is Bellick. Our wing has been breached.
I want A-Wing evacuated and shut down.
All access to B-Wing cut off now.
I'm gonna get some fluids into you,
you'll be good as new.
Nod your head if you believe me.
Good man.
Theo.
What can we do for you today?
- Hmm. This where it hurts?
- A little higher and to the left.
You're three weeks post-op.
Your knee's held together by a rod and three
screws. Tenderness is normal. No more meds.
OK. Kwame, why are you back?
Inmates have compromised
lockdown and breached A-Wing.
A- Wing is shutting down.
It's popping off up in G Pop!
Somewhere on the other side of this wall is
a drainage pipe to the prison's sewer system.
If we can get through this wall,
we can get into the pipe.
If we can get into the pipe,
we can get into the infirmary.
If we can get to the infirmary,
then we can get out of here.
Sorry, all visitors have to leave.
You have to leave.
A minor disturbance in cell block. A-Wing
is being shut down for safety purposes.
- A-Wing?
- Veronica, Michael's in there.
- Will he be OK?
- You have to leave now.
Go to DC. It's all we've got.
I'll take care of Michael. All right?
Please.
- Sorry about cutting you short.
- I told you not to apologise.
- It makes you look weak. What's going on?
- It's a minor disturbance.
Minor disturbance? My brother is in Gen Pop.
Give it to me straight.
Some clowns breached cell block.
But they won't get anywhere.
They always have locked doors at either end.
There's nothing to worry about.
Son of a bitch.
Additional sectors of A-Wing
have been compromised.
I'll be damned!
A rookie CO - and it ain't even Christmas!
Take the cuffs off. Give me the key.
Get out of here, T-Bag.
Oh, I see. You found him first.
Finders keepers.
You know, I respect that. I do.
- But I think we can work something out.
- What you got?
Oh, I can make your last few weeks
on Earth quite, quite enjoyable.
Get you some Demerol, some X.
Make you forget about that big bad chair.
No deal.
You gotta learn the art of negotiating.
Lesson one - bargaining position.
- Rules just changed.
- Get the pig!
What are you doing?
You're not gonna make it.
Chill, Sink. No blood needs to spill, Sink.
Then walk away.
We both know that ain't gonna happen.
Yeah?
That's one big pile of concrete.
How do you know where the pipe is?
- We've got someone to show us where it is.
- Oh, really? Who?
The infection's not bad.
I'll give you penicillin just to make sure.
Thanks, Doc.
This is Rizzo.
Does A-Wing need backup? Over.
Negative. A-Wing is evacuating
and locked down. Remain in B-Wing.
What's up, Doc?
Come on, Doc.
You don't wanna do this.
We're sorry. This line
is experiencing technical difficulties.
You ever see one of them safari shows where
a bunch of cheetahs jump up on an antelope?
Guess which one you are.
Tough little girl, ain't he?
I believe the devil's got some crazy power,
but I don't think shining him on this wall
is gonna bring it down.
- Not unless he's got a sledgehammer.
- We don't need a sledgehammer.
What the hell am I supposed to do with this?
- Sick Bay, report.
- Sick Bay, please report.
Sick Bay, come in. Is everything OK?
You know what to say.
All clear in Sick Bay. Over.
Roger that.
Let them worry about the noise.
You worry about how to drill
through a concrete wall
with what used to be an egg beater.
- We just need a few small holes.
- How can we fit through small holes?
Ever hear of tensile strength?
- Hooke's Law of elasticity?
- What do you think?
If we drill holes in strategic locations, we
compromise the wall's load-carrying capacity.
- How about speaking English?
- We'll be able to break through the wall.
Give me that.
We go in through the tip of each horn,
the eyes, the end of the nose,
the bottom of the fangs, end of the braids.
It makes a kind of X.
Let's get to it.
If I can get DIRT in there
with some of the newer firepower...
End the riot today
and start funerals tomorrow?
- I can contain this.
- Warden, I got a call for you.
- Not now.
- I think you should take it. It's the governor.
- Governor.
- Where's my daughter?
Not to worry, sir. She's fine.
She's in Sick Bay in B-Wing.
It's a different part of the facility,
locked off from the disturbance.
That's what you're calling a riot nowadays?
Can these animals get to her?
Sir, it's impossible for anyone
from A-Wing to get into Sick Bay.
A guard assures us everything is fine.
We have everything under control.
For your sake, you'd better hope you do.
I'm gonna dance with you, Doc!
I'm gonna dance till the sun come up!
- Come on, Doc!
- Open the door!
- All right. It's your turn.
- No. I ain't messing with no diablo.
We can't afford downtime.
We have to switch off with the drilling.
It's bad mojo. You kidding? I mess with him,
you drill into him, he gets pissed. Then what?
I got enough enemies already, papi. OK?
- You believe in God, right?
- You know I do.
So you're protected. He'll protect you.
From him.
Gentlemen!
Oh, gentlemen!
I assure you, once Bob and I
are done getting acquainted...
We blaze him!
Everyone else will get their turn.
We're gonna have a little fun, Bobby.
Don't worry.
I don't got the blickey. My pipes are clean.
Where are you going, rookie?
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
They always think they can run away.
Got a question for you, fish.
What if we do all this work
and the pipe is ten feet that way?
- It won't be.
- Have you got X-ray vision?
I calculated the drill point coordinates, hid
them in my tattoo and projected it on the wall.
Everything's been worked out so the image
hits the right spot. It's just math.
What if your math is wrong?
You'll drill into
one of a dozen gas lines behind the wall.
There'll be an explosion
and we'll be burned alive.
But you're good at math, right?
They're breaking out.
They're breaking...
Shh.
Come on! Come on!
Open up!
Open it up! Come on!
Yo, Stroke.
You got longer arms than me, man.
Agh! Son of a...
That bitch stuck me.
You think it's hot now?
I want all the water shut off.
- I'll call Maintenance.
- Mack, you take care of it.
Yes, sir.
Yeah, we... we have a problem.
That's right. Yeah, Bob here's seen the hole.
He's gotta go away.
- No one's going anywhere.
- He's seen the hole.
So have you.
Looks like your lockdown idea
didn't work out too good, huh?
I have a daughter. Please.
- We gotta kill him.
- The cops are right outside.
And they'll stay outside.
As long as they know we're keeping him alive.
- But he's a guard. He's gonna squeal.
- What the hell does this have to do with you?
This is not any of your concern.
Hm.
See, Bob here knows about our secret.
He knows about our escape.
So it's all of our concern now, isn't it?
Easy, big fella. It's just me.
Looks like you took a pretty good hit.
Cons got that rook guard in Gen Pop. Kid's
probably dead already, or wishing he was.
- Where's Scofield?
- Haven't seen him.
- I gotta find him.
- You looking for Scofield?
- Yeah, Turk.
- Come on.
Now you listen, pervert. You're in
as much trouble as he is. You understand?
Go ahead. Go ahead. Stick me, stick me.
Let's see how many times I can shout out
about your little hole before I bleed out.
Every con's gonna know about your escape
before one drip of my blood hits the floor.
So you see, friends,
either I'm through that hole with you
or I'm gonna sing like Johnny Cash.
Open the door!
Hey, yo! Check it!
Stroke is about to get the doc.
- Finish what we started.
- Where are you going?
- Sick Bay.
- There's no way to B-Wing. We're locked out.
I'm not. No one touches the CO.
No one.
You gonna clue me in, paisano?
Be faster if we cut through here.
Burrows is as good as dead.
Yeah! We're coming to get you!
Open it up!