Do you want a lean body for summer?
Well, the time to start is now.
No gimmicks, no crash diets,
and absolutely no drugs.
Think healthy, and be healthy.
You can start now,
just pick up the phone
and become the best you you can be.
Cut! Going again.
Sorry.
Did I mess up the commercial?
No, it's fine. Are you okay?
I think it's cramps.
Oh! I'm burning on my side.
Sit down, take a few minutes
and catch your breath.
Everybody else, keep running.
We're not filming.
We don't do this for the cameras,
we do it for ourselves.
We can't go again
with him sitting there.
Fine. But that felt phony.
At least let me get a little workout,
maybe if I'm breathing
as hard as they are
I won't seem like
such an evil taskmaster.
All right, take five, guys.
How you feeling?
I think I'm ready to do this.
You sure? That's it.
That's the way to fight through.
All right, concentrate on those knees,
lean into it and lift.
- Lifting. Lifting. Lifting.
- Come on, push it!
Come on,
you're almost at the top.
Those eight steps are the difference
between fat and thin.
Seven, six, five, four, one more.
Nice job!
Feel that burn?
That's your body
carving out its new shape.
New shape.
Don't sit, just take it slow
on the way down.
On, boy.
Are you okay?
You Okay?
Any idea why we're getting
half as many requests for you as usual?
Democrats' health care plan?
At least we have one case
that looks intriguing.
30-year-old fitness trainer
suddenly can't breathe,
collapses and breaks her ankle.
That's it? You're not gonna argue
why this case is beneath you?
No point, I'm in an elevator.
I can't run away.
You can't run away anyway.
That's just mean.
Why are we still together?
We are going to our office.
Pronoun confusion, starts kicking in
once you pass the childbearing age.
Now that's just mean.
My office was recently destroyed.
I thought I'd use the office
of the doctor directly responsible.
I think the patient
holding the gun to my head
was actually the one
directly responsible.
My desk won't fit in his cell.
You can use our outer office.
Where's Foreman and Thirteen?
Own in the R.
Thirteen started
her clinical trials today.
What's Cuddy doing
in your office?
Other than throwing off
the fang shui
with her ass that faces
all eight sides of the Bagua at once?
These walls aren't soundproof.
I'm well aware.
Normal CT means
that her lung problem
has the distinction of having
nothing to do with her lungs.
Steroids. No one looks
this fit without cheating.
Anabolic steroids
hack away at the immune system,
left her open
to a pulmonary infection.
Wow. Muscles and curves.
My penis is so confused.
She's not on steroids.
Her program's all about
getting in shape naturally,
exercising, eating right.
And you know this because?
She has infomercials
to sell her DVDs.
What? I'm up late a lot.
And you actually believe
what you see on TV? Go run the labs.
The labs are back
and there's no sign of steroid use.
Can someone please
read her file?
Can someone please stop
back seat differential-ating?
What about allergies?
She goes jogging every morning,
inhales car fumes during rush hour.
Perfect, except that she was jogging
half a mile from the nearest road.
In the cold.
Cold air hits the lungs, sets off
an attack, exercise-induced asthma.
Nice try, except EIA doesn't
account for the elevated BP.
If you'd read the file...
Come on, before the shrieking harpy
melts my brain.
- Her BP's fine.
- I know.
Exercise-induced
asthma actually fits.
I know. You know.
She can't know.
The only good way
to test for EIA
is to recreate the conditions
in which the attack occurred.
But we can't exactly make her
run out in the cold on a broken ankle.
Get creative.
It's gonna be okay.
Any shortness of breath?
Tightness in your chest?
Feeling pretty good, actually.
Not even breathing hard.
O2 sats and lung capacity
are still well within range.
Cuffs slipping down,
you wanna stop for a moment?
Rather not.
Haven't had any exercise in two days.
Take it you don't get
a lot of fat in your diet.
I take it from your tone
you think that's a bad thing.
Do you ever indulge?
There's more to life
than indulging your every whim.
I didn't say "every." But a whim every
now and then can make life a little...
You okay? Trouble breathing?
No, I feel fine. Why?
No pulse. This isn't asthma.
There are a lot of other people
in the trial?
I'm taking over the people that already
started it at Mercy, so I'm pretty full.
Stop.
One more time. No talking.
I shouldn't be here.
It's nepotism.
I know the guy running the drug trial,
so I get a spot.
You have Huntington's,
so you get a spot. Stop.
One more time.
Just the fingers, no mouth.
The point of this thing
is to improve neural cell longevity,
which doesn't matter much
before symptoms,
so you should give
my spot to someone...
Shut up.
Stop.
You can stop feeling guilty.
Your best tapping rate
was .004 taps per millisecond.
Means your nerves
have started degenerating.
You want to work in here?
Fine. Me, too.
We'll split the desk 50-50.
That side's yours, this side's mine.
You're right.
There's plenty of space here,
neither one of us needs all of it.
That's your strategy? Taking
the high road? It's not going to work.
Huh? Did you say something?
I couldn't hear you from all the way
over here on my side of the desk.
Patient's heart stopped.
We shocked her back to sinus rhythm,
she's stable.
Test didn't set it off,
her EKG was normal.
Well, she's consistent.
Lung problems have nothing to do
with her lungs,
heart problem that has nothing to do
with her heart.
Something is
strangling her system.
Carcinoid tumor.
Find it, cut it out.
Can a leaking breast implant
cause joint pain?
No, and she clearly
doesn't have implants.
Or joint pain. What's going on?
Got another patient.
I set up an online
second opinion clinic.
People who don't like or trust
their doctors e-mail symptoms,
I can knock off four or five cases
over lunch,
clear two grand by e-mailing them back.
Ascending colon's clean.
That's gotta be illegal.
Only in nine states,
and this isn't one of them.
Legal notice spells out
it doesn't replace doctor's visits,
so there's no opportunity
for malpractice.
How come you haven't said
anything about this?
It's no big secret.
I guess I'm just not very chatty.
You told us when you renewed your
subscription to National Geographic.
Small intestine looks clean,
moving into the pylorus.
So you don't mind
if I tell House?
Actually, House may sort of mind.
Because I sort of set it up
in House's name.
Nothing in the bile duct.
And by "set it up in his name,"
you mean?
I mean, it's Dr. Gregory House's
Second Opinion Clinic
with medical advice
direct from Dr. Gregory House.
You're insane.
With two days to live.
House's never gonna find out.
He will if I tell him.
Or you cut me in for 30%,
and I keep your secret safe.
That's blackmail.
Yes.
Moving into the... Whoa.
That's her stomach?
It's the size of a shot glass.
Because our patient's
a big, fat cheater.
Subtle. No way you geniuses
could have spotted this.
Gastric bypass surgery,
she had her stomach stapled,
then had the records
from her files pulled
so it wouldn't ruin her DVD sales.
Can you do this outside?
I could. But that would defeat
the purpose of doing it here.
Where are the smart guys?
If you mean
Foreman and Thirteen,
apparently the first appointment
of the drug trial is an all-day thing.
I said yes to this?
Her gastric bypass
procedure could cause...
Forget the bypass,
treat her like a fat girl.
Should we treat her like
a 60-year-old Asian man, too?
She's not fat.
Not on the outside, but on the inside
she's still tons of fun.
When she was obese,
she probably had Type 2 diabetes,
could have left her
with permanent nerve damage.
Ten points for doing what I said,
minus ten points for doing it badly.
If this was diabetes-induced nerve
damage, it would've kicked in years ago.
Have you seen my balls?
Can you hold on a second?
My balls. Have you seen my balls?
The giant one and the red one.
Your plan isn't going to work.
Of course it is.
I try to make you miserable
to make you leave.
You deny that it's
making you miserable,
you try to make me miserable
so I'll stop making you miserable.
And eventually you will leave,
citing reasons
that have nothing to do with misery.
You're not bothering me.
Step one, complete.
I'm gonna call you from my cell.
And then I will come back in here.
Hey. Yeah, I just had to explain
to him that I had his balls,
and he's not getting them back.
Excuse me.
Sleep apnea explains...
Apnea would've disappeared
when she shrank.
Not if it destroyed
the musculature of her trachea.
Apnea cuts off oxygen to the brain,
the resulting neurological damage...
She been snoring?
She didn't mention it.
Did she mention feeling tired
after a full night's sleep?
No, but...
This isn't apnea.
And this is a stupid room
to be doing a DDX in.
Cliff notes. Gastric bypass
only makes her skinny on the outside.
On the inside
we have heart and lung issues
not caused by heart and lung issues.
Private area, House.
It can wait.
You need to consider side-effects
from her gastric bypass surgery.
Forget the bypass.
Let the dying girl finish.
- You said forget the bypass...
- Shh.
Dr. Thirteen has the floor.
Bypass could create malabsorption
issues, leads to low potassium.
Very stupid.
Her potassium is fine.
But her intestines aren't.
Gastric bypass could cause malabsorption
by creating a blind loop of bowel.
It ulcerates during exercise,
bacteria get loose in the blood stream,
migrate to the heart and lungs.
Very not stupid.
Bacteria in the bowels means
there's bacteria in the poop.
Get some and test it.
He could have come up with SIBO
anywhere else in the hospital.
You didn't need to come down here
and screw with us.
But her wrong idea led to his right one.
It was a vital screwing.
We think your surgery might have caused
an infection called SIBO.
A stool test will help us to confirm.
Put some of what you're full of in here.
If surgery could somehow
make you taller, wouldn't you do it?
Sure, but I wouldn't call a meeting
of the Lollipop Guild
and tell them they can grow
if they work real hard at it.
I don't tell anyone
not to get gastric bypass.
I tell them how to get healthy,
how to improve their lives.
Yeah, by telling them to do
what you were unwilling to.
I was willing to do anything.
Thyroid hormones, crash diets,
none of it worked.
My body was like a prison.
When I got the surgery, I got healthy
and when I got healthy, I got happy.
I'm not sure you're happy.
But if you are, being healthy
didn't do it, being pretty did.
Poop in the bedpan.
House's office? Really?
Did he send you here
to beg for it back?
There are dozens
of other doctors...
Other doctors actually use their offices
for crazy stuff like seeing patients,
not throwing a ball against the wall
and calling it work.
It's his process.
That ball saves lives.
Did he give you talking points?
Yeah, but I added
one of my own.
Don't take his office and pretend like
all you're doing is taking his office.
You chose his room
because you want to be there.
But sitting near him and hoping
isn't going to get it done.
Leave here now
or I'll take your office.
No, you won't.
The boob lady e-mailed me again,
complaining of chronic fatigue now.
She's convinced
the implants are responsible.
- They're not.
- I told her.
She says something is
and if I don't find out what
she's gonna complain
to the Licensing Board.
- It's not funny.
- It is.
You just can't appreciate it because
it's going to destroy your career.
What happened? Did he call Foreman
clean and articulate again?
It is surprising.
Clinic patient's just whining.
What's the poop?
It's going to take about an hour
to spin down the sample.
What are we looking for?
You don't know?
I'm doing my famous Socrates impression.
Think I really nailed the accent.
High fat content
indicates SIBO.
And what does fat do in water?
It floats.
And what else floats in water?
The correct answer is a duck.
If it doesn't float,
Kutner missed the boat.
Looks like I was wrong
to dismiss apnea.
You guys can stay up all night
gloating in the sleep lab.
What about all that scar tissue
around the implant, could that be...
That amount of encapsulation
is perfectly normal.
I gotta tell her something.
Tell her to find a decent plastic
surgeon who can correct the placement...
Yeah, that's what she wants to hear,
she's sick and she's lopsided.
Tell her it's a virus.
It probably is, and it'll
get her off your back for a few...
Emmy's EEG is flat-lining.
Where would she have gone?
Hey, I looked for you guys in
the control room, but you seemed busy.
Get off of there, last time you
exercised you had a cardiac incident.
- I feel fine.
- You felt fine last time.
I only slept a couple of hours
but I feel great.
Can I get
one of those machines?
You're running on
a broken ankle.
It doesn't hurt.
And your leg is bleeding.
You feel that?
What does that mean?
The numbness in her left foot
is ascending into her leg.
How'd she manage
to sneak out for a run?
She said she needed
to use the bathroom.
You two get the results
of the sleep apnea test,
or did those need to use
the bathroom, too?
Alpha waves on the EEG
ruled it out.
I was mixing some hydrogen sulphide
for good and valid reasons
and must have spilled some
on my side.
Did it waft over to your side?
Cunning plan.
You do realize it's going to stink
for hours, on both sides.
Oh! Would you look at the time?
I hope your patient isn't still sick,
forcing you to stay here all night.
Ascending numbness means
her nerves are breaking down.
Or her brain.
- Or both.
- We've gotta go.
Let me finish,
I'll meet you down there.
You were 15 minutes late yesterday.
I don't want you to develop bad habits.
Appreciate the life lesson,
but 15 minutes, give or take,
isn't going to make a difference.
Get started on your other patients,
I'll be down there when we're done here.
Way to know where your bread
is buttered, sister. Up high.
If the problem is in her brain,
it could be MS.
Or early onset Parkinson's.
But if it's her nerves,
it could be transverse myelitis.
Or a million other things.
We're gonna stay in the dark
until we can figure out
if her electrical problem
is in her power station
or in the high tension wires.
Power station's the brain,
wires are the nerves. Run an NCV test.
The test will measure
the amount of time it will take
this electrical impulse
to travel along your nerves.
- Will it hurt?
- No. Give me your arm.
You can ask nicely.
I learned in med school,
you don't actually cure with kindness.
You're right, I'm a hypocrite.
But I don't have a choice.
Not really interested
in your rationalizations.
If I'm open about the gastric bypass,
no one would listen to me anymore.
You mean no one
would buy your DVDs.
It's not about the DVD sales.
I'm helping people.
My clients are making themselves
healthy. They're living better lives.
Can you honestly tell me
you've never done anything hypocritical?
I'm sure you had good reasons.
Give me your arm, please.
Keep your arm raised.
Does this mean something is wrong
with my nerves?
No. It's your muscles.
We don't need to run this test.
It's not what we thought.
She has muscle weakness,
could indicate myasthenia gravis.
Yeah.
Also could be
some kind of toxin.
Excuse me. Are you going up
to the personnel floors?
I'm going to see Dr. House.
Do you have an appointment
with him?
We've been emailing.
Joint pain and fatigue
thanks to these.
- I'm sure it's nothing.
- Oh, now this.
He's actually downstairs.
Gone. Gone for the day.
But we work for him,
we can set you up in the ER.
The antibiotics will make her feel
better, she's out of here by morning.
- If it is a staph infection.
- It's gotta be.
She has sleeves of tattoos and piercings
from God knows where.
She has muscle weakness,
could indicate myasthenia gravis.
I had the weirdest dream, you guys did
the test in a reasonable amount of time
and came back here
before I had time to fall asleep.
You guys still smell that?
Maybe you should just let her
have your office?
Or...
She sends one of yours to the hospital,
send one of hers to the morgue.
It's not myasthenia gravis,
her breathing's improving
and the weakness is in her extremities.
Could be a botulinum reaction.
I don't think sabotaging your
boss' office is a wise counterattack.
All that is needed for evil to succeed
is for good men to do nothing.
She probably used a lot of Botox
to tighten up her skin.
True. Could also be
any kind of heavy metal toxicity.
PSP or arsenic
from eating too much seafood,
cadmium from bad bottled water,
lead or nickel
from canned fruits or natural grains.
I don't think replacing that
was part of the renovation plans.
It is now.
Lucky for us, we can treat all those
toxins with the same thing, chelation.
You never showed up.
Get out of my house.
I wanted to find proof
that you were slipping back
into your self-destructive pattern,
confirm you weren't
worth my time.
Instead I found this.
You've followed
all of my instructions to the letter,
probably better
than any patient I have.
So why are you the only one
who can't show up for appointments?
I came down right after
I was finished with House.
You were in your office
with another patient.
And there was another patient
in the waiting room.
Janice.
I'm well aware
of what's going to happen to my body
over the next eight to 10 years.
I do not need a visual reminder
every time I walk into that place.
That's understandable.
It's human.
And you need to get over it.
Now, you show up on time tomorrow
or you don't show up at all.
Your mom is leaving. You're gonna
regret this the rest of your life.
The chelation didn't work,
her muscles are still deteriorating.
Rules out toxins. So what else that can
go wrong when the Hindenburg deflates?
Why aren't we doing
this in your office?
Obviously because it would be stupid to
do this in an office with no furniture.
Cuddy overreacted
to my overreaction.
Coronaro-cardiac fistula.
Even a small hole could cause...
They start in the lungs,
not the heart.
And why are you leaning
on a 45 degree angle away from Foreman?
I'm sitting straight.
Trouble in the Land of False Hope?
Everything is fine.
Austrian syndrome.
Nice deflection, but our patient
doesn't drink, she's a health nut.
And even if I was a cynical guy
and thought she was a liar,
I would have done a tox screen which
would've come back negative for alcohol.
You should come to
these gatherings more often,
keep you from
looking like an idiot.
You making book or did something else
happen to our patient?
Personal.
I'll put it on vibrate.
Guillain-Barre.
Usually starts as a muscle pain patients
compare to the pain of over-exercising.
So who's paging you? Your wife?
Does it worry you
that she paged Kutner first?
Guillain-Barré fits, patient
didn't notice the initial symptoms
because it's no different
than how she feels every day.
Her muscle weakness
is the precursor to full paralysis.
Gastric bypass
probably set it off.
At what price beauty?
Go start her on plasmapheresis.
She put the lime in the coconut.
She drank it all up.
She put the lime in the coconut
Deedee? Can you stop singing?
Musical automatism, she could
be having a partial seizure right now.
You need to get House.
Deedee!
Yelling at her is not gonna be
an effective treatment.
She's faking.
It's a cry for attention.
Her brain could be misfiring.
Right, a rare neurological disorder
is far more likely
than a cry for attention.
I mean, nothing about this woman
screams "look at me."
On the other hand, look at her.
She needs a full neurological work-up.
Get House.
Ultimate irony. I killed myself
trying to make myself healthy.
You're not dying, okay?
This disease is manageable.
Better start getting used
to that wheelchair.
Self-pity doesn't suit you.
Just take me down to the...
No.
You're strong enough to walk.
Come on, get your ass
out of bed and walk.
Could be an aneurysm,
we've got to control her blood pressure,
start her on
a calcium channel blocker.
Or you could tell House.
I can't tell House.
You'll be in trouble.
On the other hand, she's sick.
She's singing.
And bleeding out of her ears
and losing her hair.
And an aneurysm doesn't explain
her joint pain.
Wilson's disease does.
No Kayser-Fleischer rings.
Anorexia.
Now you're just desperate.
Biliary tumor causing
paraneoplastic syndrome.
That might actually fit.
I'll scan to confirm.
- You'd do that for me?
- You don't have the time.
Which means I can ask for 25%
of your income and you'll give it to me.
You going over the fence?
It took three visits,
but I finally convinced the contractor
that I'm Cuddy's boss and all the office
renovation plans need to go through me.
You did do the math
on this, right?
Screwing with her office
means her renovations will take longer,
means she'll be
in your office longer.
See there? I'm having a bidet put in
instead of a toilet.
Not in addition to, instead of.
You want to know
what happened to the old toilet?
She'll be with you
where you claim to not want her.
I smashed it
with a sledgehammer.
I think
in some ancient cultures
that was actually considered
a proposal of marriage.
Is this fun for you?
Analyzing everyone else's fun away?
Ask her out,
it'll cost the hospital a lot less.
I brought some visitors.
Cheer you up.
It's okay, come on in, guys.
We're all staying on your plan.
Nobody's cheating.
That's great. You're on my arm.
We found out about your gastric bypass.
How could you lie to us like that?
The doctors told you?
You're really hurting my arm.
You're not the best you
you can be.
You're a fraud.
You're a self-hating fat person.
You're really hurting me.
Feel the burn.
Burn. Burn.
Help. Help!
Burn. Burn! Burn!
- Burn! Burn! Burn! Burn! Burn!
- Help!
Get off of me!
Get off of me! Get off of me!
Mood congruent hallucinations.
Means it's not Guillain-Barré.
Which means whatever it is,
it's now in her brain.
Where are you going?
Sorry. Treatment.
Does Foreman schedule your appointments
by numbers on the clock,
or just by when
I'm in the middle of something?
Sorry if I'm dying at a bad time
for you. Could be CNS lymphoma.
So losing the 200 pounds
was just a coincidence?
What about a prion disease?
If her brain is slowly turning
into a Swiss cheese,
there's not a lot we can do.
There are some
possible treatments.
Get a brain biopsy to confirm.
You are not cutting
into this woman's brain before you test.
That is the test.
Not for CNS lymphoma, which is
a perfectly legitimate diagnosis,
one you can test for non-invasively.
You're, obviously,
not opposed to being invasive.
Rule out CNS lymphoma first,
then rule out astrocytoma,
then rule out
other brain tumors...
I hereby declare them
ruled out.
Run the tests.
You can do a brain biopsy,
but only as a last resort.
Start running down Cuddy's list
of "Diseases it's not."
You're not stopping me
for medical reasons.
You're stopping me
because you have the hots for me.
You're still here
Evidenced by the fact that
I'm the one who moved into your office.
It's the biggest office.
And I'm not the one that...
Why are you dressed like that? Why do
you try so hard to get my attention?
Are you screwing with me?
Depends on your answer.
Everybody knows
this is going somewhere.
I think we're supposed
to kiss now.
We already did that.
Seemed like the
logical next step.
Really?
I'm an idiot
for being surprised.
Can you leave these?
I'll keep coming.
But can you change my appointment time?
Can't. Schedule's full.
You're stuck with her,
might as well get to know her.
Your head MRI was clean,
means you don't have CNS lymphoma.
What's next on the list?
Other types of brain tumors.
Can we stop at the cafeteria?
I can have something
brought up for you.
- What do you want?
- Chocolate cake.
You can't give up.
We're going to figure this out.
What am I supposed to be hoping for?
That you find a brain tumor?
What else could it be?
You were so hard on me
about lying.
How about you take some of
your own advice and tell me the truth?
What's next on the list?
Prion disease.
And if that's what I got?
How bad?
There are a few treatments.
But there's no guarantee.
I'm sorry.
And you won't let me
have a piece of cake?
Where's Cuddy?
It's not CNS lymphoma.
I know.
She's getting worse,
you want me to find Cuddy
and get her approval
for the brain biopsy?
When you were philandering
with impunity, how did that feel?
Superficially, I loved it,
but deep down I think I was miserable.
Why? What's going on?
You weren't miserable.
You gave something away
to make a relationship work,
you rationalized
that you're getting something back.
Okay. I'm gonna go get Cuddy's approval
for the brain biopsy.
Leave them there.
I'm gonna do the biopsy myself.
Cuddy wanted us to eliminate
seven different things.
Cuddy doesn't always
get what she wants.
Bad idea to get into a power play
with somebody who has the power.
You're fired.
Just reinforcing your point.
Whatever personal drama you're playing
out, you'd be a lot smarter to...
I thought you said
she was sick.
Sick people don't
spontaneously get better.
Yes, they do,
it's called an immune system.
Sick people who are sick enough
to make it to me
don't spontaneously get better.
Not as pithy, but yeah,
technically more accurate.
What's the last thing
you gave her?
I took her for a MRI
looking for...
MRis detect, they don't treat.
What did you give her
after the MRI?
I didn't give her anything, she got
depressed at the lack of direction.
We went to the cafeteria
for some chocolate cake,
took her to her room,
hung a banana bag, let her rest.
You gave her cake?
She asked for it, I figured...
You figured you'd let me play
20 questions instead of just telling me.
Feeling crappy again?
I've brought your cure.
I'd give you an IV
of the stuff,
but the frosting tends to get stuck
in the little tube.
Is this a joke?
It's not a joke, not a lie,
not an attempt to defraud in any way.
Just an actual licensed physician
with an actual diagnosis.
Hereditary coproporphyria.
Your face is genetically blessed,
your body chemistry is slightly less so,
doesn't make enough of a certain enzyme
that I can't pronounce,
but it's apparently important
for your liver and everything else.
Treatment is a high-carb diet,
rich in sugar.
When you were a porker,
you were self-medicating.
So this is treatable?
We just have to reverse
your gastric bypass
and get you back on a high-carb,
glucose enriched diet.
The best you you can be
is a lot more you.
Open the hangar,
here comes the plane.
There's nothing else
you can try?
No. There's a drug that manages
the symptoms but it's not a cure.
Let's try that.
You don't want to have
the surgery?
Understand.
There's not many people
who have the guts to admit
they'd rather be pretty than healthy.
Income's better
and you get more action.
We'll start you
on your drug treatment right away.
I bought it.
I bought that it was really about
trying to make people's lives
a little better.
You're surprised
she's superficial?
You're a plastic surgeon.
This is the human condition.
No, she's a freak.
Every time you put someone under
to bob their nose,
you were risking their life.
What?
No singing. She's better.
No one was supposed
to let my patient leave her bed.
She had a respiratory arrest,
we coded her nearly 20 minutes,
but she didn't make it.
House is an unemotional child
incapable of intimacy or romance.
Trust me. It's done.
It's perfect.
I like the desk.
A lot of character.
That's not the one I ordered.
This is my desk
from med school.
You have it in storage
or something?
My mom did.
That was sweet of her
to do that.
She didn't. My mom has no idea
I'm redoing my office.
I lied to you the other night.
That woman in the waiting room,
she didn't freak me out about my future.
She freaked me out
about my past.
Your mother.
Must have been horrible
watching her die.
I wanted her to die.
She just yelled so much.
And for no reason. Just screamed at me
in front of my friends.
My father tried to explain to me
that her brain was literally shrinking,
that she didn't mean it,
that it was the disease.
But I didn't care.
I hated her.
I never said goodbye,
and she died
with me hating her.
Did Chase test
for the biliary tumor?
He said it was negative.
She was stable
when he left her.
We should have found more time,
we should have...
House is gonna kill us.
Slowly
and painfully.
You're not only idiots, you're frauds.
Fraudulent idiots.
Fraudulent idiotic killers,
as it turns out.
- House, this was really my...
- Your fault, yeah!
For pretending to be me
when you're not even competent.
And your fault for not ratting him out
while the patient was still alive.
What she had was easily treatable,
she could have been fine.
Damn treatment's so simple.
It might still be possible.
House?
House, she's clearly dead.
Oh, God! Oh, God!
She was dead.
She wasn't dead.
She wasn't even sick, you moron.
Seriously, how good was she? No
formal training. At least not in acting.
Did you see their faces?
I think we may have
an anal hygiene violation there.
So the CT?
That was from a patient three years ago.
That was hard to find.
But the hair, makeup,
getting Chase and Cameron
to play along, much easier.
We deserved it.
I'll take down the website before...
Take it down? You kidding?
It's way too lucrative to shut it down.
For Chase, for me.
I earn 50% for letting
you use my name.
Chop, chop, go to work,
first dollars go to expenses.
I booked our little thespian
here for two full days.
That's three G's I owe her.
And you still got
three hours left.
Do I?