The trick to onions,
cut them in half lengthwise,
but leave the roots on,
then make your vertical slices.
I need a dozen.
Think you can handle this?
A dozen is 12, right?
Next, we add mustard greens,
spicy and they pack a nice punch.
Plus, they're really
good for you, improve mental function,
protect against rheumatoid arthritis,
even inhibit certain types of cancer.
Are you going to chop those onions
or give them a Thai massage?
Well, I guess a happy ending
is out of the question.
I don't recall adding "making snide
remarks" to your list of duties.
Just taking initiative.
Porcini mushrooms.
You want to reconstitute them
in a bowl of water.
You also want to
hire an assistant
who can stay focused
for longer than 30 seconds.
- Why don't I hear you chopping?
- Just give me a second.
- You're kidding me, right?
- So sorry.
Are you okay?
You want to sit down?
My lips are blue. Cyanosis.
Pain in my back and chest.
Spontaneous pneumothorax.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm a doctor.
- You are?
- And I need a doctor.
You drool.
Shut up.
I know gas is expensive, but I
could have given you a ride.
Elevator's broken.
It was fine when
I came up from Admitting.
Dana Miller, the cancer researcher,
spontaneous pneumothorax.
Awfully thin file.
She just got admitted.
Lots of things can
cause pneumothorax.
Why don't we let eight or 10 other
doctors rule out the boring stuff?
We want to take this case.
She's maybe five or 10 years away
from curing retinoblastoma.
Which would make this case
attractive to anyone
who has some vested interest in people
curing the incurable.
She hasn't suffered from COPD,
she doesn't smoke,
she hasn't been scuba diving.
O2 sats are low, even after
chest tube insertion.
Pneumothorax could be secondary
to a bunch of things,
cystic fibrosis, lung cancer...
Or to be slightly
more optimistic,
late-onset asthma triggered
by an unknown allergen.
We have a case?
- Did you just get to work?
- Am I in trouble?
Did you take the elevators up?
Yes.
So, steroids for asthma?
Yeah. Do a CT looking for
hyperinﬂation to confirm.
And I thought my hospital was high-tech.
Have to wait all day for a CT.
Dr. House gets a few perks.
He has his own scanner?
No, just very loose interpretations
of hospital procedure.
I appreciate
the extra effort, but...
Our gift to society, we want to get you
back to work as soon as possible.
Well, I'm not working,
at least, not as a doctor.
I quit. I left
eight months ago.
You mean like a sabbatical?
I had a uterine myoma, benign,
but it ruptured, and I needed
emergency surgery.
I was lying there on the table thinking,
"I can't die now,
I haven't been happy yet."
Couldn't you just buy an overpriced
German sports car, or have an affair?
My sports car is doing
what I want when I want.
Right now, I'm learning
how to run a kitchen
from one of the best chefs in New York.
You're washing pots
and smashing garlic.
Smashing garlic makes me happy.
Before that, it was eight years
studying, twelve years in that lab.
It was always what I was supposed to do,
never what I wanted to do.
Come here. Look at this.
Come here.
Adorable. Elevators keep crashing.
Ls Mercury in retrograde or what?
Elevators can be capricious,
sometimes it just seems like
they're out to get you.
She keeps playing with the blanket.
Why would she do that?
Why do you think the elevators
would be out to get me?
I don't know.
Maybe they wanted to take time off to
spend with their little dumbwaiter,
but then they had to leave it at home
with an elevator sitter
because you drove the replacement
elevator to quitting
because you're incapable
of listening to anybody but me.
It's just a theory.
You're wrong.
I don't even listen to you.
Either do your job or go home.
Leave me out of it.
I am going to do my job. It doesn't mean
I have to do it happily,
doesn't mean I have to do it
without resentment,
and it definitely doesn't
mean I have to do it
without seeking vengeance
on the person making me be here.
Congratulations. You've officially
dragged me down to your level.
Okay-
Hey, Blue.
It's not asthma,
lung volume's normal.
She did have a uterine myoma
removed eight months ago.
Central line IV could've made a hole
near the lung that slowly expanded.
No pleural thickening.
I can't believe she quit.
People have a right
to be happy.
I saw a four-year-old with
retinoblastoma on my oncology rotation.
The cancer had eaten
through her eye and into her brain.
Horrible diseases exist.
It doesn't mean people should give up
recreational anything.
Why not? Big picture. I don't care if
Jonas Salk's life is a miserable shell,
I just want him to cure polio.
You can't live
your life big picture.
You've got to look out for yourself
and the people you care about.
Well, then,
why are you a doctor?
Why aren't you sitting by a pool
in Fiji knocking back Mai Tais?
People act in
their own self-interests.
You're all here because
you're happy to be here,
or at least because
it's your best option.
I'm here because
I want to help people.
No, you're here because
it makes you feel good to help people,
Taub and Foreman are here because
they've got no other viable choices,
and Thirteen is desperate to make
her life matter before it's over.
So, you're happy to be here?
Does it show?
Are those increased
interstitial markings?
It could be pulmonary fibrosis.
Do a biopsy.
Foreman.
"You've got to look
out for the people you care about."
That wouldn't have anything to do with
you screwing over your clinical trial
by slipping Thirteen
the real drug, would it?
You said that would be stupid.
Does she know?
Because Jonas Salk would not approve.
There's nothing to know.
Got it?
- Good?
- Yeah.
- You okay?
- Just a headache.
- I took some ibuprofen, but...
- Where's the pain, front or back?
Front. Why are there never any
interesting pictures on these cards?
They should make
a dirty version.
Sharp pain or more
of a throbbing...
Relax. This is not a side-effect.
People get headaches.
True, but I can get you an MRI.
If I'm on the drug,
it's been weeks.
It's not like something's
gonna suddenly crop up now.
Okay, first card.
Train, duck...
- You can't remember?
- ...piano.
We need a biopsy to confirm...
You need an open-lung biopsy
to confirm pulmonary fibrosis.
That's invasive surgery. I'd be
out of commission for weeks.
No offense,
but you're not working.
What does it matter if you spend
a little time in bed?
Not working doesn't mean
I don't have places to go.
I've got my book group, piano lessons,
cooking classes. They make me happy.
A warm apple fritter makes me happy,
it doesn't fulfill me as a person.
And working here does?
If it didn't, I'd have found a way to
go back to tucking tummies.
Good for you. If your job fulfills you
and makes you happy, that's rare.
I didn't say I was happy.
I loved being a plastic surgeon,
the money, the lifestyle.
And in a lot of ways,
this job stinks.
I'm making five bucks,
I'm always annoyed, but...
You can look yourself
in the mirror and think,
"I did something
worthwhile today."
Exactly.
That's important.
And I do miss that,
but it just wasn't
enough anymore.
- That doesn't feel right.
- Shun.
It's weird.
What is it, ascites?
Your belly's full of blood.
First her lung deflates,
like me after a cold shower,
now her liver starts to bleed,
like me after a...
You okay?
Great.
Just practicing
my clown college audition.
Someone set a trip wire.
We were with the
patient the whole time.
E were in the R.
Lung, liver. Go.
Shouldn't you be obsessing over
who did this to you?
Nope. Anybody bother MRI-ing
our patient's liver for tumors?
No tumors, no cysts,
no clear etiology.
If you're not obsessing,
you must have already figured it out.
Yes. So I'm obsessing about
why you're not obsessing
about why our patient's liver
suddenly sprang a leak.
There's a tiny spot on the caudate lobe.
Could be a granuloma.
Erodes into the hepatic artery,
causes the bleed.
What caused the granuloma?
Blastomycosis.
Could've been
asymptomatic for months.
It hits her lungs, we give her steroids,
it blossoms and attacks her liver.
Get a piece of her lung,
stick it under a black light.
If it glows, the sick children who need
her soufflés can breathe easier.
Foreman.
Again?
You have a problem.
I told you. I didn't...
Then you really have a problem.
When she turned her head
to look at the MRI,
I think she's losing
her peripheral vision.
Because she turned her head?
I'm happy for you.
A love so deep you're ready to chuck
your medical license
to give her powerful, unproven drugs
with dangerous side effects.
I don't want to make any assumptions
about your feelings for me,
but I do have
a birthday coming up.
I hear Cuddy's SEAL training
finally came in handy.
Should I be investing in a flak jacket?
You're safe.
No carpet bombing, no burning of Dresden
to teach her a lesson?
Well, since you're incapable
of taking the high road,
I assume there's some deeper,
more long-term strategy in effect.
Cuddy's not playing games,
she's not looking for leverage.
She wants pure,
unadulterated vengeance.
And your countermove
is to let her have it?
The only time to strike back
is when I want something.
All I want now is to get things
back to normal,
which I can't get
by escalating.
The only way to win this war is to
lose it. Let her punch herself out.
Yeah, that makes sense, too.
Too?
I was thinking you actually feel guilty
about taking her away from her baby,
but your explanation
is good, too.
It's completely inconsistent
with your character, but whatever.
Oh, thank you, Rationalization Man,
you have saved the village.
You wanna eat?
You forgot your file.
Dana Miller?
The cancer researcher?
Not anymore.
Dr. Miller, I doubt
if you'll remember me...
James Wilson, right?
Chicago, at the
adenocarcinoma conference?
Impressive.
You want some cortisone
for that itch?
Liver failure, itching is one
of the lovely side effects.
W“)! Did you quit?
Well, the worst thing is,
now, every time I get sick,
I have to listen
to a dozen people judge me.
Do you want me
to congratulate you?
I've got four kids in Pede-Onc
right now who are going to die.
Three of them within a year,
the other in a few days, probably.
Breakthroughs will happen.
With or without me,
someone will find the answer.
Maybe.
I'm in the trenches.
I'm doing triage as best I can.
You had the chance
to end the war.
How is someone like me
supposed to keep fighting
when someone like you
just walked away?
When I left my job, a lot of people
were furious with me.
It was easier to be angry
than to admit they weren't happy.
That they were stuck
in a rut somewhere in their lives,
unable to move forward.
What's your rut?
Okay, you're freaking me out.
Do you think
we should have kids?
We've had this conversation.
Ten years ago. Things change.
On our third date, I told you
that I didn't want to have kids,
and you said that
you were okay with that.
I said it because
I wanted to sleep with you.
And then
I fell in love with you,
and I realized
that I really could be okay with it.
It wasn't like I had
this burning desire to have children.
God, have you been resenting me
all this time? Is that why...
No, of course not.
I'm just revisiting.
This isn't a whim for me.
It's not a decision that I made lightly.
Don't you ever wonder
what it would be like?
All the time.
But just not enough
to make me want to do it.
I like our life.
Are you okay?
Can I turn the TV back on?
Look straight ahead.
Why didn't we do
this test this morning?
- Do you see that?
- No.
- Damn.
- I'm losing my peripheral vision?
I am on the drug.
Does this mean you have to tell them
and take me off it?
No and yes.
As far as they're concerned,
you're on the placebo.
I found out last week.
The trial was getting positive results,
so I switched you.
So my headaches...
I'll stop taking the drug
and everything should be fine.
Specimen's negative
for blastomycosis.
That's it?
I'll go give House the test results.
You can tell the patient.
Hey.
We have been dating
for two weeks.
You just broke trial protocol
and risked your entire career
to give me a drug
we're not even sure will help me.
I don't think
I'm ready for that.
Dr. Miller?
I'm sorry. The test was negative.
So, I'm gonna take you off...
What happened to your head?
I don't know, I was sleeping.
It's so itchy.
You were scratching it
in your sleep.
You scratched right through your skull.
- What?
- This is brain matter.
Oh, God.
Need some help in here.
I did a free flap closure
to avoid any scarring.
She was lucky, the scratching
didn't cause any brain damage.
But the first thing she said
when we woke her up was,
"it still itches."
Itch receptors are only
in the top two layers of skin,
which means she's not actually itchy,
she just thinks she is.
So the problem's in her brain.
Thank God we have you here
to interpret that for us.
Sorry. I have a headache.
It could be psychogenic.
She made a big,
sudden change in her life,
could be the
result of a mental imbalance.
She wants to do what she wants to do,
what's crazy about that?
Why do you have to quit to do it?
If I want to do something, I do it.
If you can figure out a balance,
there's no burn out.
Thanks for the lesson, Deepak,
but the itching started yesterday,
not eight months ago.
Meningitis, encephalitis.
Those are diffuse processes,
this is localized.
Could be plaques, MS would explain
the itching, possibly the lungs.
So would a brain tumor.
Well, how about we stop guessing
and MRI her head instead?
- You want to talk about your headaches?
- Not particularly.
You went off the drug, but the headaches
are worse. You need an MRI.
The patient needs an MRI.
If she had gangrene, would you be
amputating my leg?
These pills have codeine in them? You're
taking twice the indicated amount.
I've only been off the drug
for 24 hours.
So I think the bigger issue here is that
I've been off you for 24 hours.
You have worsening headaches,
loss of peripheral vision,
and a long history of pretending
bad things aren't happening.
You really think
this is just about my hurt feelings?
- I don't remember demoting you.
- Brought you something.
Latest issue of Parent magazine.
Really interesting column.
Apparently, working moms
are actually more engaged and attentive
than stay-at-home moms.
Something about personal fulfillment.
That's just a rationalization
by working moms who justify
not being with their kids,
which is fine, if that's what they want.
It's not what I want.
And this is Nurses Quarterly.
- The point is...
- You're only here to get back at me
by dumping dirty mop
water on my carpet.
Just get it over with
so I can get back to work.
I'm sorry.
I figured
only one of us needed to go
out on a limb.
I thought! Could help you.
It's hard to have a conversation
when I'm trying not to move.
Oh, God.
Patient's MRI was negative,
no tumors, no lesions.
- Where's your cane?
- Where are your co-workers?
- I paged them.
- It could still be psychogenic.
Technically, it can't still be that
because it never could be that.
She scratched through her skull
while she was sleeping.
Unless she was having
a dream about fleas...
Oh, hey, funny
you should drop by.
We were just talking
about this patient of ours.
Tell him the part about where two
of her doctors don't show up for...
Where are you going?
Polyneuropathy. If it's not
in the brain, it's in the nerves.
Explains the itching,
the lungs, the liver.
Shock the affected area,
re-boot the nerves, she'll be fine.
Foreman.
How bad is she?
She's got a tumor
in her optic chiasm.
You don't need your coat
to treat a tumor.
I'm going to the drug company.
To tell them that you compromised
their trial, your ethics,
and the patient's health.
That's a great idea.
They have records
on hundreds of patients.
I can ask them for access,
find out if other patients developed
tumors and how they were treated.
This drug inhibits cell death.
I think I can take
a wild guess on how I treat that.
Stop taking it?
Yeah, she tried that yesterday.
Oh, my God. It's been a whole day and
her brain tumor hasn't melted away?
If you get on that elevator
and it's only 'cause you're worried
about getting to sleep tonight...
I want to be able to tell her
this happened to other people,
and they're fine now.
So tell her.
- I'm not going to lie to her.
- A little late for that.
You need to wait.
Because if this thing
doesn't go away,
she's going to need you
to still have a medical license.
So I spoke with House.
He thinks we should just...
- My leg is bleeding.
- What happened?
I was going for the phone
and I fell over the table.
I can't see.
What do you mean?
I can't see anything.
- You gonna tip housekeeping?
- Get it from Cuddy.
Don't tell me. She burned
your apartment to the ground.
The warmth would have been nice.
No heat, no power.
Apparently, Mrs. House called the
utilities and told them we were moving.
You have 17 messages.
And your non-involvement strategy
doesn't seem to be working.
Hang up. He's here.
We've been
paging you all night.
By all means, let's discuss the failed
attempts to contact me,
not the reason behind them.
The patient started
experiencing spinal shocks
before the machine was turned on.
Lhermitte's sign.
Shocks without shock,
an itch that won't stop.
She needs Dr. Seuss.
Lhermitte's sign could mean Behcet's,
B12 deficiency...
No sores, no anemia.
Where's Foreman?
No idea.
Could be another
demyelinating disease.
Why are you asking about Foreman
and not Thirteen?
Because both questions
are bound to have the same answer.
Ebony and Ivory are joined near the hip.
Forget the brain, look lower.
A spinal tumor wouldn't explain
the liver or the lungs.
But an aggressive
spinal hemangioma could.
Go find it.
You didn't answer the door.
Probably because I didn't want
to talk to anyone.
You can leave your stolen key
on your way out.
I was looking for Foreman.
I figured...
You can't see.
- Where is he?
- On his way to the drug company.
- Tell him to come back. I'll dial.
- If they can help...
What, you think that drug company
has a magic tumor wand
that no one else knows about? You need
radiation, not ritual sacrifice.
He asked for my advice
before he switched you off the placebo.
I told him to do it
if he loved you.
He only thinks he loves me.
It's the same thing.
Yes, he's an idiot.
You didn't ask him to do anything,
you're pissed off that he did.
So let him torch his career
to pay for his sins,
unless you actually
feel something for the idiot,
in which case, you might want to
tell him to turn around.
You're hurting him.
Good, after all the stunts
he's pulled on me.
You're physically hurting him.
That's the point.
What's the point?
What do you think you're going
to accomplish?
House shouldn't be allowed
to make people miserable
- without paying for it.
- You're not miserable.
You're telling me how I feel?
You're here because you like this,
you like working with him.
Wow, if only I'd known
I was having fun,
I wouldn't have
canceled the bouncy house.
Fire him.
And go be home with your new baby.
I like what he does
for this hospital.
What he does is who he is.
And the same goes for you.
Slow down.
Unless you want to radiate her heart
instead of her brain.
Of course, then your problems
would actually all go away.
Thanks. I'm not beating myself up
enough already over this.
Entering the left
common carotid.
You broke the rules,
your girlfriend went blind.
You gotta be ready for losing
to be one of the possibilities.
You're at
the carotid bifurcation.
I knew that giving her the drug
would be bad for me if I got caught.
I never thought
it would be bad for her.
Nobody else was having
adverse reactions.
You did it because
you love her,
and, ironically, you never took her
into consideration.
I can't wait to see what you get her
for your anniversary.
Catheter's adjacent to the optic chiasm.
We're in position.
Nukie-nukie.
What's going on
with everyone today?
It involves House,
Foreman, and Thirteen,
which means it's either dumb, dangerous,
or tragic, or a combination.
I'm embracing my ignorance.
House was right about the hemangioma,
looks fixable.
What's that?
Hemangiomas travel solo.
This thing's brought a friend.
Masses in her lungs and spine.
One in her pericardium.
They're everywhere.
Classic mesothelioma.
It metastasized outward
to the spine and muscles.
The irony of it.
Maybe she wouldn't be sick at all
if some other lazy cancer researcher
hadn't gone home early.
Where are Foreman and Thirteen?
Shouldn't you be saying,
"Those weren't there when we scanned
her two days ago"?
- Mesothelioma shouldn't grow this fast.
- Good rephrasing.
Have Wilson do
a biopsy to confirm.
No.
Something weird is going on,
and it involves our colleagues,
we should know.
You want us to treat the patient?
Tell us what's going on.
Actually, all he needs us to do
is tell Wilson
to do something. So...
You always blab
to watch people react,
so not blabbing means you don't want us
to react, which can't be good.
Is Thirteen's headache
not just a headache?
If I check with Admitting,
am I going to find her name?
Little pinch.
I'm sorry about the other day.
I unloaded on you and...
You're not sorry.
You feel bad because mesothelioma
means I'm dying.
You're a good person.
I appreciate the sentiment.
I'm not apologizing
because you're dying.
I'm apologizing
because you were right. I am stuck.
My girlfriend died.
She was the only person
I've loved for a long time and...
I'm still living in her apartment.
I'm surrounded by her things.
I've left it
all exactly where it was.
I don't know how
to get un-stuck.
The only wrong thing
is to do nothing.
Yeah.
All right.
That's not supposed to happen.
Have you thought about going to
the drug company, see if they can help?
I thought about it.
We need to give it more time,
it's been half a day.
This thing keeps growing,
there's other stuff in your brain
you might need later on.
If I were any other patient, you'd both
be in the lounge eating donuts.
- You're not any other patient.
- Right.
Any other patient,
you don't feel guilty.
But you don't get to torch your career
to pay for your sins.
House told you
to say that, didn't he?
Does that make it
any less true?
- You think he's right?
- Who cares?
You're a hypocrite.
You don't ask her if she wants
to be on the drug,
but when there's a chance
you could help her get better,
suddenly you're letting her
call the shots?
That's not being noble,
that's saving your own ass.
I'd feel worse if he
destroyed his career.
Mesothelioma doesn't bleed.
So what causes
masses that do bleed?
AVM secondary
to schistosomiasis.
She'd be crawling with worms,
we would've noticed it.
Gorham's Disease
and Kasabach-Merritt
can both cause super-aggressive
vascular tumors.
Patient's heart just stopped.
So what causes that?
Cardiac tamponade.
She's bleeding into her pericardium,
smothering her heart. Syringe.
BP is going back up.
It's working.
No, it's not. Look.
We're transfusing platelets, FFP,
everything to try to keep her stable.
But we can barely keep up
with the blood loss.
At this rate, she could be dead
by the end of the day.
We need to resect
the vascular tumors, stop the bleeding.
Too late.
No surgeon's going to touch her now.
- So we give up? Just let her bleed out?
- Don't be silly.
Do you know what that would do to our
malpractice insurance rates?
We go on the offensive, cut off
the invading army's supply line.
You're talking
about embolization?
Cut off the arteries that feed blood
to the tumors, they wither and die.
Start with the ones
in her lungs,
'cause if they get any bigger,
she's gonna have a hard time breathing,
so she'll have a hard time
telling us she's dead.
You can't kill the tumors
without also killing healthy tissue.
If we wipe out
three-quarters of her lungs...
Let's hope that running marathons
wasn't on her happy list.
I found this.
In the coat closet
where I hid it.
I thought I'd never see you again,
Little Little Greg.
Yeah, you heard me right.
You are who you are.
It's annoying,
but that's not your fault.
It isn't about you.
I'm sorry.
Because you were doing this job
perfectly until the baby came along.
What?
I'm apologizing.
Can't you just accept my...
I accept.
Are we gonna have
to do this dance again in 28 days?
What the hell
is wrong with you?
Yesterday, you hate me. Today, you're
practically weeping on my shoulder.
I can only assume that what I'm hearing
is your Aunt Flow telling me...
When I was being a jerk,
you suddenly act human,
but when I act human,
you turn back into a jerk.
Guess our cycles
aren't matched up yet.
This is your way of saying you accept
my apology, isn't it?
Nope. This is my way of saying
you were doing a crappy job before,
you'll do a slightly crappier job now,
everything keeps going.
Nature of life,
nature of parenthood.
Or this whole thing
is just an act.
And you've gone back
to the part you think you need to play.
You should go talk to Wilson.
Rationalization Man
needs a faithful sidekick.
Now Rational Man
needs to go save a life.
House, if you're looking
for returnable bottles,
- Kutner's already cleaned it out.
- Damn! Oh, well,
it means the only thing I'm gonna
get out of this is a diagnosis.
So the nurses gave her pads
instead of tampons,
is that diagnostically
relevant?
The fact that the nurses
had to give her anything is.
It means she's bleeding
from her uterus.
Women do that. It's perfectly natural,
not scary at all.
She's menstruating
and she's bleeding everywhere.
There's about a three-or four-in-28
chance it's a coincidence.
Which leaves a much bigger chance that
the diagnosis is ectopic endometriosis.
She had a myoma eight months ago. The
surgeons cut through her uterine wall.
Every cut of the scalpel
could have sent endometrial cells
spilling out into her bloodstream.
Some of them took up
residence in her lungs,
some in her liver,
some in her spine.
And like all
horny little cells,
they went forth and multiplied until
they reached a critical mass.
In the days leading up
to her next period,
when her uterus is supposed to swell,
everything swelled.
Then when her uterus was supposed
to bleed, everything bled.
Yes, ladies, I am blaming her period.
Granted, it's the worst period ever.
Although, frankly,
not by all that much.
Cut out the masses,
she'll be fine.
Can't do surgery until her cycle's over
and she stops bleeding.
Let's hope she can
hold out until then.
In the meantime, get her
a pint of cookie dough ice cream
and a DVD of Beaches.
I'm sorry.
Foreman?
I can see you.
How you feeling?
Relative to the last
few days? Awesome.
You almost died.
- For the second time in eight months.
- I know.
How do you feel about
your life choices this time?
I didn't lie there
thinking, "What if"?
I always worry on my deathbed
I'll think, "I didn't do
anything really important."
You're gonna spend
one day of your life on your deathbed.
The other 25,000 are the ones
we should be worrying about.
Go to bed happy tonight.
Dr. Schmidt, it's Eric Foreman.
Actually, the trial
isn't going too well.
You told them, didn't you?
You really had no choice,
on account of being an idiot.
They gonna pull the drug?
I broke protocol.
Her results are
no longer admissible to the trial.
They don't have to do anything.
If anyone else gets a tumor,
they'll put a warning on the label.
You're gonna keep your license?
They'll come after me if I attempt
to participate in any more trials.
That's very decent of them.
Well, good for me.
See you tomorrow.
And the next day.
That wasn't your locker, was it?
It's a locker room.
How else are they gonna learn?
Do you think
you can't be happy without a kid?
I don't know.
I know I can't
be happy without you.
You snore.
Shut up.