Hey!
How long have I...
Blunt force trauma to the head did
the fatal damage.
Since the accident,
he's had a continuous...
Can't get up.
What's wrong with my legs?
Hey, someone talk to me!
Hey, you don't hear me
talking to you?
Great heart for transplant.
Who?
My heart? Oh, God.
They don't know I'm in here.
Hey, genius. I think it violates
certain ethical laws
to rip the organs out of a guy
that's still alive.
Possibly certain law laws, too.
Thank you.
Could you get back
in your bed, please, Mr. House?
It's actually Dr. House.
This guy's a doctor?
There's also a Navy SEAL House,
but you're gonna
have to save up for that one.
Really? Well,
that's interesting,
but you're here because
you crashed your motorcycle,
not because I need
a consult, so get back in bed.
Scraped my elbow.
Just need a truckload of Vicodin.
- Whereas this guy...
- He's brain dead.
No, I'm not!
So drop it.
See that?
Minimal brain waves
don't mean he's alive.
I am alive. I'm here.
No EEG response to painful stimuli,
hot or cold.
What you're seeing
is random, barely discernable.
I discerned it.
Listen to him. Please.
No. That's just the amplifier's
internal noise level.
It's on increased sensitivity.
No, no, no, it's not! It's me.
Then why is
his eye following you?
Exactly.
Following motion is
an involuntary reflex.
No.
You're a doctor,
you should know these things.
No, no. I'm not dead.
I need help. I'm here.
I also know about
locked-in syndrome.
And things are either
involuntary or voluntary.
Blink if you can hear me.
I hear you.
Oh. This is gonna be fun.
Eye movement is deliberate.
Can you blink once
for yes, twice for no?
I hope so.
Square root of nine?
He got that faster than you.
Brain is fully functional.
Where's Molly?
You were in an accident.
Lee, hit the brake.
Hit the brake. Hit the brake.
You sustained a traumatic injury
to your brain stem,
which has cut off
your brain's ability
to communicate with
the rest of your body.
Can you fix me? Where's Molly?
You still have
movement in your eyes,
so we can get you
to a rehab facility
where they can teach you
how to communicate.
No, I can't be stuck like this.
Unless the crash didn't cause
the brain damage.
Maybe the brain
damage caused the crash.
Yeah. I couldn't stop.
Why couldn't I stop?
Look at his palms. No scrapes.
He didn't even try
to protect himself.
Suggests slowed
reflexes or no reflexes.
You're not a doctor in this hospital,
you are a patient.
Yeah. And you're the guy
who wants to cut out my organs
and he's the guy who doesn't.
Stroke, cancer,
even a simple infection, anything that
insults the central pons could do this.
Then that means
I could be fixed.
You're giving him false hope.
He needs to accept
what's happened
and work on making
the most of it.
Molly.
Hey.
Don't look at me like that.
That's not making me feel better.
I love you.
I don't know how God is gonna get us
through this, but he will.
Stop it, I'm blushing.
What are you doing?
Just looking for
some reading material for the crapper.
- These CTs...
- Get back in your bed. Come on.
The children are in the waiting area.
Can I bring them in?
No. No, don't.
You don't wanna see them?
I don't want them having
nightmares.
I don't wanna scare them, Molly.
You don't want them to see you?
It's okay. I understand.
You're gonna be
better soon enough.
You really that sure?
Why are you so sure, babe?
How do you get so sure?
Are you okay?
Never better.
Here's your burger.
If you can't bring Mohammed to
Princeton, bring Princeton to Mohammed.
It's my diagnostics posse.
Hot, dark and darker.
Talk about getting
me better, please.
What are you doing
up in Middletown?
Who cares?
Buying a Gibson '57 Goldtop.
It's the guitar Duane
Allman used to play.
Next to the trauma,
the most likely causes of
a sudden onset of
locked-in syndrome
are basilar artery stroke
and brain hemorrhage.
CT was clean.
Man, those fries look good.
Certain circulatory diseases.
Guy's an active bike
rider, his heart's fine.
A well-placed tumor
could explain it.
Jeez, is the last thing I ate
gonna be the last thing I ate?
It could evade the CT, and still show up
on an MRI with contrast.
It was a melted PowerBar.
She's the smart one.
I just keep dark and darker
to fill out the quota.
If we find it, treat it,
you can be fine.
I never thought
I'd be praying for a brain tumor,
but please, dear God.
If you're praying
in there, stop it right now.
We'll get his doctor
to order an MRI.
His doctor's busy teaching him
how to blink out "kill me"
in Morse code.
Luckily, I found some
forms under the mattress.
Check it out,
they have those MRI video goggles.
- I heard these were awesome.
- What do you see?
It's a beach.
Oh, look. There's Taub.
Drinking a margarita and mocking us
for driving all the way up here
because House said "jump."
Easy. I can still feel in here.
Excuse Dr. Kutner. He gets a little
excited about new technology.
It can get loud in there,
and a little closed off.
These will put you
in a quiet place.
You can create
a relaxing scenario for yourself.
I hope they work.
Wow.
You're in my relaxing scenario?
I guess you like me.
Either that or
you got sent here.
What, by God?
I'm not sure if
I believe in God.
You spend an awful lot of time in church
for someone who doesn't.
I don't not believe either.
It's either one or the other.
I go to church mainly to
keep my wife happy, but...
I don't know.
I've never actually thought that
God could reach out
and affect my life.
But getting a brilliant
doctor in the bed next to me...
God is also the guy who opened his car
door in front of you.
I think Molly was right.
I think you were sent here
to make me get better.
I think so.
Hey.
Hey, Dad. Making a volcano.
Yeah. You're making a volcano. Looks
like it. What you doing, baby?
What time is it?
Hope you don't mind.
My new roommate snores.
And my new room
doesn't have you.
Your MRI showed
a lesion in the central pons.
What is that?
What does that mean?
See it there?
No.
Yeah, that's what they said.
But it's there, which means no way
head trauma did this.
It's cancer, causing a
paraneoplastic syndrome.
Unfortunately, your
current doctor thinks
its diffused nature
means an infection.
Now, the bad news
is the antivirals
he's got you on might kill you.
I'm not gonna die.
The good news is,
if they just almost kill you,
then Dr. Idiot will realize that
his name is not a coincidence,
and he'll let me
do whatever I want.
Thank you.
See, the irony here is,
you're kind of fascinating.
So many questions.
But if you could
answer any of them,
then you wouldn't
be fascinating.
I get it. You're a little
nuts, aren't you?
Your wife is the one
getting you through this.
Your wife and me.
Although, frankly, the MRI
was a lot more useful
than four hours of hand holding.
I think.
If he had a wife,
he'd know it matters.
You're a good guy.
Easy to talk to.
Wait, something's
happening. What's happening to me?
Need some help in here.
Your patient is seizing.
Why would he have a seizure?
Because he has cancer.
His brain stem is compromised.
Why are you still arguing with
this guy? You thought I was dead.
Welcome back.
And nicely played.
You almost died,
exactly as we planned.
You knew this was gonna happen?
Usually happens when you treat cancer
by pretending it's not cancer.
- Right, Doctor? My turn?
- It's cancer?
- No, it isn't.
- Yes.
Small tumor in his brain stem
causing paraneoplastic syndrome.
- He needs plasmapheresis.
- Can you give that to him?
No, no, I'm sorry. I completely disagree
with Dr. House.
Please shut up!
I don't.
Which means I can treat him.
Let him. Let him.
Is that what you want?
Absolutely.
Could you send up
a couple of bellboys?
I got the transfer papers,
plasmapheresis is all set up.
Are you okay?
Fresh infusion of
macho. You like?
I can't move, and she's worried
about his boo-boo?
What were you
doing up there anyway?
Antiquing.
Found you a late
Victorian corset.
Come by later. I'll tie you up.
He hitting on her? If she turns
around, she's into him, too.
And there you have it.
Sorry, I didn't show up
in Middletown. I didn't get the message.
Probably 'cause
there was no message.
I decided to accept
your resignation.
Uh, I thought we were past this.
I decided to stay.
No, you didn't, you had it
decided for you.
So now you're stuck here
with a boss
who knows that you wanna be
somewhere else.
Which means you're
no longer motivated to impress me.
Which means you're no longer motivated
to come up with good ideas.
Unless I'm wrong.
Save the cheerleader,
save your world.
I got it from here.
I thought you
already solved this.
You thinking you might be wrong?
What's going on?
Hey, just curious.
What're you driving
up to Middletown for?
Why do you care?
Why does he care?
Because I'm your friend.
- I was buying a guitar.
- Yeah. I heard that.
Used to belong to a guitarist who died
in a motorcycle accident.
Just reeks of you
screwing with people.
Your crash was 10 miles from the Orange
County Progressive Pain Clinic.
You live 10 miles
from Mary's Dress Shop.
And yet,
that's not even on my list of reasons
that I think you're
secretly a transvestite.
If you're going to another state
to get more narcotics...
He's on drugs?
I went to visit your ex-ex-ex wife
who lives in Thompson Ridge.
Let her know about the extra money
you're making on the lecture circuit,
so she'll be sure
to adjust your alimony.
You wouldn't do that.
Yeah, I wouldn't do that.
Would you?
You guys are friends?
Shouldn't we be entertaining
our patient?
I performed Euripides with sock puppets,
you just missed it.
House said we should.
The mind is like a muscle.
If you don't exercise it,
it'll atrophy, just like anything else.
Whoever's with him needs to talk,
keep his mind active.
And it'll show
House you still care.
Not sure if I do.
Jeez, you're my doctor.
Then why don't you just quit?
- Not sure I want to do that, either.
- Oh.
Maybe you should figure it out before
House figures it out for you.
Dude, maybe you should have your
midlife crisis after I'm better.
Kutner.
We'll be right back.
Wait. Wait,
what did you just see?
Do you drink?
He's a roofer, alcohol hardly
proves your theory.
Marchiafava-Bignami
disease fits.
LFT's are normal.
Speak English.
Is it fixable? What does that mean?
That hurts.
No tremors.
How much do you drink?
A six-pack a day?
I hate beer.
I don't even drink beer.
Could mean he drinks
more or less,
or maybe something else.
It may not be alcohol at all.
Street opiates could
also cause locked-in...
I don't get high.
MPPP.
Either we play 20,000 questions
with every street drug,
or instead of talking
to him, we talk to the lesion.
Talk to me.
We're going to
biopsy the brain stem?
For the record, that doesn't count
as your inspired idea.
It's sort of
where I was heading.
You're gonna cut
into my head? Why?
Stop treating me like
a piece of furniture!
I have a right to
know what's going on!
Where is that going?
Blood in your urine clogged up
your old catheter.
Peeing blood? That must be
what the insecure doctor saw.
Every clue gets us
closer to the answer.
Damn it!
The surgery will
get us more clues.
You have visitors.
No. No, Molly.
You can come in now.
- Daddy.
I told you not to bring them.
They wanted to
see their father.
I can't even hug them.
They can handle it.
It's gonna be all right.
You're not so sure
anymore, are you?
They must have told you that
it's dangerous, that I could die.
And that's why you
brought them in here.
I got an A plus on my test.
To see me before I die.
I love you, Daddy.
Daddy loves you, too.
I want to show my drawings.
Kids just want a dad.
Even if he's just a lump.
Maybe you should go now.
Oh no, they can stay.
Please, let them stay.
Bye, Daddy.
Sorry. You were crying.
Damn.
We're going to put you out,
just so we can drill the hole.
Oh, that's very
thoughtful of you.
Then we'll wake you back up.
We need you to answer some simple
"yes" or "no" questions
while we're cutting
to make sure
we're not cutting where we shouldn't.
Seems to be working.
Deep breaths. In about 10 seconds,
you will feel light headed.
By now, you should
be floating high...
How come I'm not better?
God's not supposed to
work in trial and error.
God's mistakes
are well documented.
If he'd done everything
right the first time,
there'd have been one plague
and zero great floods.
Those were because
of human mistakes.
You think your doctor
has an apartment on Mount Olympus?
God put me with
you for a reason.
I'm gonna be all
right still, right?
I don't know.
Lee? You with me now?
Easy questions.
You'll be done
before you know it.
Is this equation correct?
What? So if you make a mistake,
I'm not gonna
know that anymore?
Are these lines parallel?
Spatial relationship's intact.
Take a look at this circle.
Is more than half of it shaded?
Of course.
Don't forget to blink. Ls more than half
of the circle shaded?
Sorry. Yes.
Look at me, Lee.
Again. Ls more than half
of this circle shaded?
Blink. Come on, Lee. Blink.
Foreman, back out.
I can't blink. Cannot blink.
Why aren't his eyes moving?
Two options, my
neurologist screwed up,
or else something that
the hospital lawyer
is going to have to come up with
when you sue us.
Blinking and eye movements
are controlled
by a small cluster of nerves
just millimeters
from the biopsy site.
But he's still in there, right?
I mean, he just can't communicate?
It's possible.
Also possible is that the surgery caused
so much swelling in his brain stem
that he's just gone.
He had one way to communicate and now
that's gone. Well played.
Brain biopsy revealed severe
damage to the myelin sheath.
The question is why.
Epstein Barr.
Picornaviruses. Malaria.
He runs a business, meets a lot of
people, could have picked up rotavirus.
Did he report
having bloody diarrhea?
Wife's not sure.
Says he doesn't complain.
Did you ask him?
We prioritized.
He can only blink, a real history
would've taken weeks.
If he had Epstein-Barr,
he'd have belly pains.
If he had picornavirus,
he'd have headaches.
Five other "yes/no" questions,
and maybe we'd know
what treatment to give,
and what treatment
would kill him.
Unless he's already dead.
Maybe there's another way.
Brain-computer interface,
better known as BCI.
The goal is to get you to move
that cursor with your mind.
When you think "up",
the computer records the pattern.
Think "up" enough times, it eventually
learns what you're thinking.
So, start thinking "up."
You in there?
Are you trying?
I called the ex-ex-ex-wife.
She was at a sweat lodge
in New Mexico last week.
What were you
really doing in New York?
Know how you hate
it when I meddle in your lies?
I mean, your life?
Why are you being so evasive?
Unless you have
something to evade.
Interesting.
So it's nothing to do
with you, your ex-wife, or my pain.
I was heading to the Downstate
Correctional Facility in Fishkill.
One of your hookers
arrange a conjugal visit?
It's where Foreman's
brother is being held.
This is gonna mean
months of sleepless nights wondering
if I could've done
something differently.
Maybe it's not that
I'm sick of House,
it's that I'm sick
of being scared
out of my mind to
go to work every day.
Sorry.
Did that just...
Was that you?
Are you really in there?
I knew you were in there.
I was scared.
Thank God.
I am scared.
Molly, I love you so much.
Have you had any bloody diarrhea
in the last two weeks?
(BEEPING "No-q."
Rotavirus out.
Any recent joint pain?
(BEEPING "No-q"
Epstein-Barr's out.
Have you traveled out
of the country lately?
What about inside the country?
He was in St. Louis.
Good.
Could be Missouri malaria.
We'll start treatment.
(BEEPS "No-q."
He was there.
The machine must
not be working.
Hmm.
Either that or
he lied to you about it.
People do that sometimes.
For example, I just lied to him
about Missouri malaria.
Did you go to St. Louis?
I should've told you.
Why didn't I just tell you?
Down.
When you weren't in
St. Louis for two days,
I assume you were
getting some strange for two days.
So does she.
You have to tell her I wasn't.
Amazing.
A man who only has two blips
at his disposal can still lie.
I'm not lying.
If you were getting some
really strange strange,
you could have
contracted neurosyphilis.
Infection went to your
brain, froze you right up.
Good news is, it's treatable.
You'll be up and moving in time to sign
the divorce papers.
Why would I tell you the truth
about being in St. Louis
and then not tell you
the truth about this?
He just admitted he wasn't
in St. Louis in front of his wife.
And you think he's lying
when she's not even in here?
I'm liking this one more and more.
Don't fire him.
Were you out of the state?
I never left.
Were you within 20
miles of your house?
Yes.
Were you within five miles?
Within two miles?
Yes.
Did you stay at a hotel?
No.
You had to sleep
somewhere. Your car?
No.
A friend's house?
Yes.
That narrows it down,
depending on how popular you are.
Tell the wife to stop
crying, get in here.
He says that when he was supposed
to be in St. Louis,
he was staying at
a friend's house.
- Really?
- Yes.
Let's assume that
you believe him for the moment.
Name your friends
within two miles.
Martin and Kim's?
No.
Guess someone who
doesn't have a wife.
- Dave?
- Yes.
You got an address?
If this is where he got sick,
someone else here
should have symptoms.
Not if Lee was the
only one coming down to the basement.
Furnace is rusty
but no gas leaks.
Résumés and cover letters here.
Some are weeks old, he's been spending
time here for a while.
Business wasn't going good.
I didn't want you
and the kids to worry.
I was trying to protect you.
Molly...
I wish you could hear me.
I wish I could make
all of this better.
Looks like he
temped a few times.
As a janitor.
Factory out on Route 10.
The factory foreman says they make
rechargeable batteries,
mostly for cell phones.
Big step down from running your own
business to sweeping up.
Doing what I had to do.
Metal filings.
Judging by the color,
I'd say cadmium.
Which he'd aerosolize with the broom,
then right into his lungs.
Heavy metal poisoning
explains everything.
The chelation will scrub
the heavy metals out of your blood.
If we're right about the cause,
we should see some
movement in about a day or so.
Can you put
this thing on turbo?
Getting a little
anxious in here.
Somebody will be
here at all times
to irrigate your eyes,
keep you company.
Hopefully help make
the time go quicker.
My eyes still feel really dry.
Thank you for thinking "up".
For helping me
find you in there.
Man, when you
moved that cursor...
Bought my first girlfriend a necklace,
it was silver.
Cost 180 bucks.
Had to save for six months.
She hated it.
Really, seriously,
would you tell this story
to someone who could walk away?
Never bought
another girlfriend jewelry again.
Until Dr. Hadley.
You're dating her? You might want
to start all your stories with that.
Same thing. She didn't
even wear it.
The diamond thing?
She was wearing it the other day.
If she doesn't like it,
she doesn't like it.
Apparently, I suck at
picking out jewelry,
but at least have
the guts to tell me.
Okay, getting boring again.
How long till we know
if this treatment is working?
You lied to me.
I wasn't having an affair!
So, we needed money, who cares?
The last time business was slow,
you got migraines every day.
Why would you do that to me?
I'm sorry,
I was stupid, I was...
Don't go. Don't... Damn it! Somebody put.
"I'm sorry" on
this stupid computer.
My eye is killing me.
I want to keep my job.
Great. All you gotta
do is come up with a good idea.
How about we hook the guy's brain
to a computer so he can communicate?
That's a great idea.
For the guy who invented the computer
that can read minds.
Your idea was to use his idea.
You didn't come up
with it. No one else came up with it.
If I didn't re-establish communication,
we never would have found...
What's interesting is
why you're here now.
Not when I gave
you the ultimatum.
Was it something
the patient said?
I realized that what
we do here terrifies me.
And overcoming that
is the only way I can matter.
Kutner found
the battery factory,
Kutner came up with cadmium.
Maybe you don't matter.
I'm gonna close your eyes
so you can get some sleep.
Hopefully, when you wake up,
we'll see some improvement.
Hope that includes
my eye feeling better.
Hand me the fluorescein stain.
What does that mean?
Epithelium looks torn.
These drops sting.
I'm going to close your left eye
to keep it protected.
I'm gonna blink your eye a few times
to distribute the dye.
Ulcerative keratitis.
It means it's not
cadmium poisoning.
Which means you
don't know what's wrong.
Again.
When was the last time you changed
that dressing?
Judging by the smell
of it, I'd say never.
He's locked-in,
his kidneys blew a fuse,
and now his eye's oozing pus.
I assume you went
over all that with your team.
Also assume
they didn't have any brilliant ideas
or you wouldn't
still be muttering to yourself.
This is gonna hurt.
Ow!
The way he's losing his myelin
makes an infection most likely.
Could be varicella.
Road debris has come to the surface.
I'm gonna have to scrub it out.
And the initial
acyclovir would've treated that.
Which pushes me towards
an auto-immune disease.
Like Behcet's.
Here, this is gonna
hurt even more.
Take two now, two later.
Oops.
Of course, if the varicella
was resistant,
it wouldn't matter what they did
up in Middletown.
Do an LP.
You've been in the ER too long.
When the patient
had a head trauma,
white blood cells only
indicate that he had head trauma.
Or you could use the LP
for something useful.
If you find polys, it's varicella,
lymph's, Behcet's.
Why did I fire you again?
You didn't. I quit.
You weren't visiting
Foreman's brother either.
Busy. Kutner's doing
an LP so I have to focus.
I had prison security check
visitor logs, phone records,
you've never had any
contact with anyone at Fishkill.
So I ask again,
what were you
doing up in Middletown?
You know what's more interesting
than what I was doing?
The reason you are so obsessed
with what I was doing.
Stop deflecting, House.
Says the deflector.
The reason I was up there is the reason
you're scared I was up there.
I was checking out
your dirty little secret.
How long have you
been sleeping with her?
How did you know?
Your only secrets are
the girls you find embarrassing.
And the only
embarrassing girl you've met recently
is the one at your brother's
cuckoo facility.
We've only been
out a few times.
She's a caregiver.
Like all your other failed exes.
And someone who takes
care of your brother.
Who was the last
person that took care of your brother?
You think this is oedipal?
Actually I was
thinking masturbatory,
but I guess your mom
took care of him first.
So the safe course is to gouge
your eyes out.
LP stands for lumbar puncture.
We use this needle to collect fluid
from your spine.
That's a really big needle.
You're going to feel some extreme
pressure in your back.
I already feel pressure in my front.
My chest hurts.
Sort of a fetal position...
Something's wrong.
The best angle into your spine.
No, my chest.
Something's wrong. I think I'm...
Pull the needle out!
Oh, God, I'm flatlining.
Call a Code.
There is no God.
You don't know
what's wrong with me.
Doesn't seem that way.
So am I dead?
Not yet.
But you're about to be.
Okay.
Charging. Clear.
Again. Clear.
He's back.
No. No. Let me go.
You can't fix me.
I've been here for three days.
Everything hurts.
We need to get him
started on steroids.
It's okay. Just stop fighting.
She's gotta go
on with her life.
The kids don't need this.
I can't do nothing for them. I can't.
God, this foot.
Oh, that really, really itches.
So we put in a temporary pacer,
it's not gonna...
Shut up! Shut up!
He's trying to talk.
Something bothering you?
If there's still tightness
in your chest, it's expected.
Is it your eye?
Why's he saying "no" three times?
You only asked one question.
Maybe he's not saying "no".
Maybe he's saying "down"?
Are you saying that
the pain is lower?
How low? Your leg?
Your foot?
Left foot?
Check his... Let me see now.
Yeah. His right foot.
No bruises, no rashes, no cuts.
Then there should be no pain.
Is it a tingling sensation?
Is it itching?
Itchy foot means liver failure.
The liver's fine, his enzymes have
been normal since we admitted him.
I didn't say failing,
I said failure.
Just like you.
Liver's like a cruise
ship taking on water.
As it starts to sink,
it sends out an SOS.
Only instead of radio
waves, it uses enzymes.
The more enzymes in
the blood, the worse the liver is.
But once the ship has sunk,
there's no more SOS.
You think the liver's fine, but it's
already at the bottom of the sea.
So dying liver released toxins,
damaged the nerves,
led to locked-in syndrome.
Now we just need to know what's causing
the liver failure.
Liver plus eye plus kidney,
most likely sclerosing cholangitis.
Oh, God, if only
Taub had said that,
it would have
been a happy ending.
Do a biopsy to confirm.
I'm gonna numb up the area where
we'll go in for the punch biopsy.
Where's the new bracelet?
She was wearing the bracelet?
You didn't notice
that I was wearing it?
Because you weren't.
He noticed and you didn't?
If you don't like it,
it's fine, it's not a big deal.
I like it. That's the point.
I'd rather have it at home
in the jewelry box
than getting peed on at work.
You got the patient's
urine on that arm?
When I was putting
in the catheter. Why?
- You've got a rash.
- The bracelet's real.
I figured. So what if the rash
isn't just a rash,
what if it's an infection?
If there were rats
in that basement,
then the liver failure
could be caused by leptospirosis.
Transfers through urine.
Rat pee to him. His pee to you.
The infection would
need an entry point.
Look for any recent
scratches, cuts.
Look. Next to his fingernail.
The infection
destroyed your liver,
which released toxins that caused
the locked-in syndrome.
You were dying of a paper cut.
I hope you're right this time.
Let's start him on
high dose penicillin G.
We found rats in your
buddy Dave's basement.
Tested positive
for leptospirosis.
Means we're on
the right treatment.
So try moving a finger.
Your brain needs to get used
to doing its job again.
Try harder.
I'm sure you've lost hope.
I know we've told you several times
that we knew what this was,
but this time we're right.
Concentrate. Move
one finger for me.
Welcome back.
I did it.
Rat pee.
Very nice idea.
Who came up with it?
I did.
Good.
You okay with him
claiming the credit?
It was his idea,
he saw the rash, he...
If he did, he would have hung
a "Mission Accomplished"
banner in my outer office.
Don't toy with him, if you're going
to fire him...
Fact that he stole your
idea means that he cares enough to lie.
That's all I needed to know.
Rat pee. It's a very nice idea.
House, you left
this in my office.
No, I didn't.
So either I have
a hole in my pocket...
No, that's right.
I remember now. I stole it.
Because if you had gone up there
to check out my girlfriend,
you wouldn't have come
back here and lied to me about it.
You would have thrown
her right in my face.
You underestimate the
entertainment value of your obsessions.
And then there were all those calls
you weren't taking in front of me.
So I dialed the number of the calls
you weren't taking.
You're seeing a psychiatrist.
You had no right to
invade my privacy.
- Is that?
- Yeah, it's irony.
Hey.
God sent you.
Suddenly, you're not
so fascinating.
You're spying on your team?
Prioritize, Wilson.
Is that really what you want
to torture me about right now?
I don't want to torture
you at all.
I think this is a great thing,
not something you have to drive an hour
out of town to shroud in mystery.
Yeah, whining on
someone's couch
is an excellent use of my time.
Maybe I'll discover
that my childhood wasn't perfect.
So your attitude
about therapy clearly hasn't changed.
And yet you went.
Which leads me to believe that maybe
something else has changed.
Maybe you think you can change.
Credit Cuddy with that.
Not much credit to
take 'cause I'm not going back.
Oh, House, please.
I assume you went
because you're tired of screwing up
every chance you
get at happiness.
Delete contact.
Do not let the fact
that I found out about it...
Don't beat yourself up.
I'm not going back
because it doesn't work.
You'll end up alone.