You and Anastasia.
- I think he knows.
- He doesn't know.
You will suffer.
Just breathe.
So you're a pretend
policeman now?
Oh, God.
Who's there?
It's me.
It's okay.
It's okay. It's just me.
Fuck.
You're a mess.
You get used to it.
- They found Rabbit yet?
- Not yet.
- If he's not dead...
- I know.
What you did for Max...
I did it for you.
I know.
Gordon?
Yeah, he won't let me see them.
We can get through this.
I need to get my family back.
Ana will always
be a part of who I am.
But I stopped living
for her a long time ago.
Carrie Hopewell.
You really think
that's who you are?
I honestly don't know anymore.
But they're my children.
That hearing is coming up...
and God only knows where
all this is gonna land.
They know who I am now,
but you can't afford
to have your cover blown.
I think it's time
for you to disappear.
I disappeared for 15 years.
When you weren't in the house this
morning, I got worried.
I'm sorry.
You know, it would be so easy...
to just walk down there
and apologize.
And as long as I said
all the right things,
I could be back
in my bed tonight.
I thought you had made peace
with your decision to leave.
I killed that man, the mayor.
You didn't know he was in there,
and neither did I.
You really didn't know
he was in there?
I never lied to you, Rebecca,
and I'm not gonna start now.
You choose my world,
you have to know there
will be casualties.
If you can't deal
with that then...
maybe you do belong
back on the farm.
Okay.
Okay what?
Okay, let's go home.
Do you have any other speed
besides slow as shit?
Hey, I'm recovering
from a gunshot wound.
That's right, you got shot
because you slow as shit.
How many times can you
bury the same guy?
We wouldn't be out here
if your lazy ass...
had dug a deep enough
hole the first time.
Shut up and grab his feet.
Fucker doesn't even have feet.
Agent Racine?
Dean Xavier.
You made good time.
Not good enough.
What do you have for me here?
We got a couple of bodies that
don't add up.
We've got positive IDs
on these two.
Charles Randall
and Delmont Munson.
Should that mean
something to me?
No. They're local.
But there was a third
body that we found.
Teeth missing, fingers filed.
But two days
after we dug him up,
someone broke in here
and stole the body.
Sorry, you can't smoke in here.
Turns out we were able
to get some DNA samples
from the clothing
that he was buried in.
I've already sent the kit out.
You're showing this to me why?
Well, just thought
it might be pertinent.
These bodies date back, what,
about three or four months?
Coroner's got them
at 16, 17 weeks.
So long before Rabbit
showed up here...
and everyone started shooting.
Well, yes, but there's
other things going on here.
These two guys worked
for Kai Proctor.
I'm sorry, I forgot your name.
Xavier.
Dean Xavier.
Agent Xavier,
I didn't come out here
to clean up all your messes.
Just the one.
Deputy Emmett Yawners.
Deputy Brock Lotus.
Deputy Siobhan Kelly.
Lucas Hood.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'm Special Agent Jim Racine.
You all know Agent Xavier.
Let me tell you how
this is gonna work.
This is a closed federal hearing
in which you will be delivering
sworn testimony,
'cause everyone knows
swearing on a Bible...
keeps people honest.
You do have a right
to have an attorney present.
And I should inform you
that if you exercise that right,
you will earn my immediate
and eternal suspicion.
I'll call you in one by one
to answer questions.
If you answer
to my satisfaction,
this will probably be the last time
we see each other.
I understand your mayor
recently suffered...
the misfortune
of being blown up.
This town is something else.
I've asked Mr. Hopewell...
to serve as a witness
to these proceedings.
As he's married
to Mrs. Hopewell,
he's not exactly
an objective party here.
But since he will play no part in the
resolution of these findings
and since everyone in this town,
seems to be connected
in some way to everyone else,
I'm gonna let that slide.
Any questions?
No? Okay.
Come on, let's get started.
State your name for the record.
Lucas Hood.
You're the sheriff?
I am.
Okay, then, Sheriff Hood,
why don't you tell me
when you first came in contact
with Mr. Rabbit.
Well, Some of his men
shot up the Cadi.
And you didn't kill
the men who shot at you?
- Nope.
- So who did?
No idea.
And Rabbit was there?
What do you want, Rabbit?
To be the last face
you ever saw.
Yes.
Although, at that point,
I didn't know who he was.
So just to be clear,
at no point in your life
before the events of that month
had you met or spoken to
or had any kinds of dealings...
with the gangster
known as Rabbit?
Correct.
But he spent
about 1,000 bullets,
lost three men
trying to kill you.
- Any idea why?
- No idea.
You sticking with that story?
Yes.
Mrs. Hopewell,
how would you characterize...
your relationship
with the sheriff?
I don't know.
Cordial, I guess.
So not to put too fine
a point on it,
were you fucking him?
- Excuse me?
- Excuse my language.
Were you involved in a sexual
relationship with the sheriff?
Of course not.
It's been my experience
that when a man...
puts himself through
that kind of hell,
it's a pretty safe bet
that there's some sex...
somewhere in the equation.
So, just to clarify...
you weren't fucking him?
No.
She told me that
her father was a gangster,
that she had been hiding
from him for years,
and that now he'd found her.
In addition to asking
for your help,
- she asked you to keep it a secret?
- Yes.
Even from her husband?
- Which you did.
Yes.
Back in the day,
before you went AWOL,
there was a prevailing opinion
on the organized crime desk that...
you were an integral part
of the organization.
Is there a question in there?
No.
No question at all.
By your own account, he had you
down there for a few hours.
He must have said something.
He said a lot of things.
Sheriff Hood?
- Excuse me?
- I asked you
what some of those things were.
What did Rabbit talk about?
You took my only daughter
from me.
There are no words
to express the pain.
Sorry, I'm...
I'm not 100% yet.
He spoke mainly in Russian.
Ukrainian.
Yeah, well,
it's all Greek to me.
Moving on.
This business
with the metalworks.
What the hell was that about?
We knew they had Sheriff Hood.
And that he'd be killed
very quickly if we didn't act.
- I see. And who told you that?
- Mrs. Hopewell.
You just took her word for it?
She was very convincing.
She told us she had
a past with Rabbit...
which explained why he had
taken her son earlier...
and that Sheriff Hood had
traded himself for the boy.
You often go into battles
with civilians for backup?
There were mitigating factors.
We had to move immediately.
I don't know.
13, 14 guys.
I lost count.
They were all
using machine guns.
I couldn't hear myself think.
I'm out!
First two caught me in my vest.
Then I took one in the leg.
We had no idea they'd be
that heavily armed.
There was a guy up on
the stacks...
laying down cover
fire with a machine gun.
- Who took him out?
- Mrs. Hopewell.
Mrs. Hopewell.
Two shots...
one to the chest,
one somewhere around the neck.
That must have been hard...
for you to shoot
your own father.
Good-bye, Daddy.
Well, he kidnapped my son
and threatened my family.
My father was an evil
and twisted man.
No, he wasn't.
He is an evil and twisted man.
He's not dead.
I shot him point-blank.
Well, then I guess
it was his corpse...
that got up and walked
out of that building.
I saw him go down.
He couldn't have survived.
- And even if...
- He's not dead!
Normally we review testimony...
over a period of weeks.
But if I've learned anything
in my years of doing this,
it's that bullshit
will stay bullshit
no matter how long.
I think we've had our fill today.
And fortunately
after years of meetings,
I have been granted
the serenity to accept...
the things I cannot change.
I think we can all agree
that you all showed...
some monumentally bad judgment.
At the same time,
a group of hardened criminals was
setting up shop in your town.
Desperate times and so on.
The bottom line is...
this town needs
its sheriff's department.
Lucas Hood,
you were not on active duty
on the night in question.
You had surrendered
your firearm and badge...
and were for all
intents and purposes
an endangered civilian.
As far as I can tell, you weren't
doing any of the shooting.
As such, I've got
no book to throw at you.
Congratulations,
you're the sheriff again.
Deputy Lotus.
You were in charge that night.
As such, I'm gonna
throw you under the bus.
But you also got shot trying to
rescue one of your own.
That makes you
something of a hero.
So 18 months probation,
and a letter of censure
in your jacket.
Are you kidding me?
You cannot come in here...
You want to take this up the ladder,
you go right ahead.
The protocol breaches alone would be
grounds for a criminal hearing.
I don't know how the hell...
You won the fucking
lottery with me today!
And this is where a smart man
would shut the hell up.
Deputies Yawners and Kelly,
12 months probation.
Either of you does anything
that even raises an eyebrow...
in my office
and you're unemployed.
And the BSD will be
under federal oversight...
for the next two years.
Every arrest, every call,
every traffic ticket...
will be subject to my review.
So you had better make sure
you do it all by the book.
I've got to go.
I'm late.
How can you let them
all off like that?
There were two other civilians.
The bartender had priors.
You didn't even charge them.
Local criminal elements
are the sheriff's problem, not mine.
But why are they
any different than Mrs. Hopewell?
Because they are not the daughters
of a Ukrainian crime lord.
The US Attorney's office
authorized you
- to conduct a full-scale hearing...
- Oh, for fuck's sake.
Xavier, I've got
bigger fish to fry.
Your fish is dead.
You're so obsessed with finding this
Rabbit that you're losing sight...
He's not dead! You'd have another
body to show me.
Rabbit's got a fucking river
of blood on his hands...
and you want to waste my time
on small-town shenanigans?
How are you gonna explain what you
did in there to Washington?
- It won't hold up.
- It's Banshee, Pennsylvania.
No one gives a shit!
Let go of me.
Look, I'll be dead
pretty soon, Xavier.
My cancer has got cancer.
But I am going to spend some
small amount of time...
on this planet,
knowing that bastard
isn't on it.
And whatever his unresolved
issues are here,
I want them all...
right where they are
so he can find them...
when he's ready.
You're using them as bait?
That's what you do
with little fish.
This is my case.
No,
your case was Proctor,
who has somehow...
managed to be the only guy
in this town not involved...
in this shit show.
Seems to me, Agent Xavier,
your mishandling of things here...
has led to a lot of dead bodies,
and a pretty serious amount of
reckless endangerment.
What the hell
are you talking about?
You can go down for this,
or you can take a reassignment.
Oh, shit, I'm late.
Pack your bags.
You'll have new marching orders
by tonight.
Mrs. Hopewell.
As a civilian, you don't fall under
the same federal statutes
as the sworn members
of law enforcement,
so I'm turning your case
over to the DA's office.
You'll be charged with unlawful
possession of a firearm...
and obstruction of justice,
whatever other charges
they can drum up...
in regard to your involvement
on the night in question.
They took my son.
That is...
unless you can shed some light...
on where Daddy
might be holed up.
If you were to aid in my
investigation,
I might find a way
to make those charges disappear.
If I knew where he was,
don't you think I would tell you?
After everything
I heard in there,
I have no idea...
what you would or wouldn't do.
You're a bastard.
I'd lawyer up, then.
Good luck in court.
Gordon.
How's the leg?
It's getting there.
You believe this shit?
What, after everything else,
this is the part you find
hard to believe?
Hey, Gordon, I'm sorry.
I know your family's
been through a lot.
Listen, if there's
anything I can do...
Well, maybe there is.
I want you to keep
an eye on Hood for me.
Anything out of the ordinary,
I want to be the first
call you make.
- That's pretty much everything.
- Well, that's my point.
Now you got a place to come to.
You gonna put that badge
back on or what?
I didn't want to rub it in.
After what we went through
to bring you back...
damn well better wear it.
- Hey.
- Yeah?
Thank you.
Yeah, well,
let's see how long you can stay out
of trouble this time?
We dodge a federal probe
by the skin of our teeth...
and the first thing we do is go out
and rob an armored truck?
Quit your whining
and pop those doors.
Whoo!
Flip that bitch!
...floating high to deep
center field!
Come on, baby.
Okay, let's go.
- Time.
- Okay, I'll be right behind you.
- What the hell is going on?
- We're being jacked.
Grab him.
Oh, fuck me.
Motherfucker!
You hit 'em?
Ana, stay with them.
What? Oh, don't even
think about it, baby.
No, we don't have
fucking time. Fuck!
What is he doing?
God damn it!
Get back in here.
We're coming up on the split.
I'm turning in three,
two, one.
Hi.
Dude, I'm pretty sure
this is the ugliest color.
- You like these? No?
- You can do better.
I think these
would be hot, though.
- Oh, my God, they match your hair.
- They're perfect.
Uh, no, no.
You're crazy.
All the boys would love that.
My grandma would
seriously wear these.
Oh, I actually like these.
- Kind of cool.
- Those are hot.
- Yeah, I like these.
- You should get them.
I don't know. I don't think
I need them, right?
Yeah.
All right, I think we're good.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
Excuse me, girls.
- Come here.
- What? What?
- Can I see what's in your bag?
- What do you want?
Fuck my shit.
- Get down!
- Shit!
Who the fuck is that?
How the hell should I know?
- Well, will you shoot him already?
- Oh!
Drive! Drive!
Fuck.
Oh, shit.
- Let's go.
- God damn it!
That motherfucker can shoot.
Okay, let's go.
Go, go, go!
Let's go, let's go!
Go! Go, go!
Shit!
I love it when a plan
comes together.
Shut the fuck up and drive.
So you want the good news
or the bad news first?
What happened?
Who the hell was that?
I don't know.
I thought you said you had this
handled?
It was.
Maybe we should review
your definition of handled.
The guards weren't tipped off
or Job never would have made it past
dispatch this morning.
I don't know who that was,
but it wasn't Kinaho security
and it wasn't the cops.
We got well over 100 grand here.
It's not what we were going for,
but it's something.
All that planning, man,
and we got rolled...
like a bunch of
motherfucking amateurs.
Yeah, how?
Only the four of us knew.
Well, no one here
leaked anything, right?
Could you have been hacked?
First of all, fuck you.
Second of all,
I ain't the one shaking off...
fifteen years of mommy rust.
Okay, I'm out of here.
Call me when you've got
my cut ready.
- Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
- What?
What are you so pissed about?
I should have my head
examined for doing this with you.
Hey, you came to me.
Don't forget that.
We had this planned without you.
And who would have
done the driving?
- Come on, Ana.
- That's not my name.
- It's who you are.
- No, that's who you want me to be.
If that's true,
then why did you want in?
I got fired, okay?
By my best friend.
And no one else
is going to hire me,
especially if I get brought up
on criminal charges,
which seems to be
what Racine is aiming for.
I'm broke.
So this is pretty much
the only gig I've got.
I think now might be a good time
to remind you...
we need to get the fuck
out of this town.
Not yet.
Come on, man.
We came, we saw,
we got our asses whipped.
And if Rabbit is still out
there,
that's just one more
reason to get gone.
We risking our necks
out here for chump change.
We're still good.
Still got those diamonds, right?
Fuck me.
Look, every day,
you find a new way...
to get your damn head blown
off and mine along with it.
Those diamonds are an insurance
policy for the both of us.
- I was keeping them safe.
- I know.
I would never cut you out.
I know.
So let's get
the fuck out of here.
We can fence the stones
and set up shop in New York...
or anywhere else you want.
Not yet.
For fuck's sake, what the hell is
keeping you here, man?
Here's how this works.
You either give me your names...
so that I can call your parents
or I have to involve the police.
And I'm telling
you it was a mistake.
I meant to pay for them.
And I'm sure your parents
will believe you.
I'm trying to cut you a break here
by not calling the police.
- Call them.
- Okay.
And as soon as they get here,
I'll tell them how
you groped me...
when you
were taking us back here.
Don't be ridiculous.
He said he had to search me.
And then he started, like,
rubbing my breasts.
- I was so scared.
- Deva.
And you'll tell them
it never happened.
And I am sure...
your wife will believe you.
So, William...
can I call you William?
What's it gonna be?
Keep up the good work, William.
Come on, Beats.
They knew what they were doing.
Ever since they built
that new connector,
barely anyone uses
that highway anymore.
Least that much makes sense.
So someone else
ran them off the road...
and they left
all the cash behind?
- Not all of it.
- Someone got away with one bag.
100,000 and change.
Either the thieves
or whoever ran them down.
Yeah, but you
got off light considering.
Any idea who the shooter was?
Can't help you there.
This fake guard,
you catch any security video...
of him loading
the truck this morning?
The server went down
this morning.
So did our backup.
Some kind of virus.
We lost the last
24 hours of footage.
And the missing cash,
any way to trace that?
Serial numbers?
Markers?
It's unbanked cash
from the tables.
Yesterday it was
in someone's pocket.
Yeah, I figured as much.
There are some
on the reservation...
who would consider
$150,000 quite a bit.
A fortune, actually.
It is troubling,
this coming so soon after the
setback with the hotel.
Whether this was Proctor or not,
the fact remains
that the Kinaho Moon...
is having some serious problems.
George, we've been through this.
This entire renovation
and expansion...
was designed to be serviced
by that hotel,
which is now rubble.
I take it your insurance didn't cover
unexplained explosions.
You've been opposed to the hotel
project from the start.
My father...
Your father was a great man...
who lost his way
when he became ill.
Even you have to concede...
that since you've become chief,
our fortunes have suffered.
And the tribe
simply can't afford it.
The sooner you say
what you came to say,
the sooner you can leave.
You're out of your depth, Alex.
And the members of the tribal council
have serious concerns,
about your qualifications.
You've always wanted
this seat, George.
Everybody knows that.
And everybody knows
that you're too young for it.
Nola.
I know.
And they use
special effects for it.
But you can tell because
his hair is barely moving.
And if he was really flying,
his hair would be, like,
you know, flying around
his face and everything.
Yeah, you are totally right.
You okay?
Hey, where's your inhaler?
I got it.
Here.
Here, bud.
Deep breaths.
- You shouldn't be here.
- This is my home.
Look, your case...
is going to the grand jury.
I'm the district attorney.
Are you really gonna
let them charge me?
Racine wants a scapegoat.
I have no choice
but to recuse myself.
There's nothing I can do.
The assistant
district attorney...
Bullshit.
She works for you.
I'm sorry.
Are you innocent?
Is that what you're telling me?
I hurt you.
I know that.
No, Carrie.
Not me, all of us.
Max, Deva.
And you didn't hurt us.
You destroyed our family.
You scarred your kids.
And they will not heal.
And sending their mother to prison,
that's going to help?
Well, their mother
almost got them killed.
I'm drowning here, Gordon.
Yeah, well, join
the fucking club.
That's the last of it.
Thanks.
New beginnings.
It's just temporary.
I know.
So, we're back in business.
Kind of hard to believe
we got off so light?
Yeah, Racine's not
interested in us.
It's Rabbit he wants.
You really think...
Gordon's gonna let
Carrie go down for this?
Racine's pulling
all the strings.
He's just playing every angle.
Trying to flush out Rabbit.
Can I ask you something?
- Off the record.
- Sure.
You and Carrie Hopewell.
What?
I don't know.
You tell me.
There's nothing to tell.
I got in over my head.
That's all.
So there's nothing
between the two of you?
No.
I should probably go.
Let you get settled.
You've got secrets, boss.
Don't we all?
I'm just saying...
if they ever get to be too much or if
you want to talk...
All right.
What you did,
coming to check up on me every day
these past few weeks,
that...
that was a big help.
Good.
I'm just glad
you're back on your feet.
I'll see you tomorrow.
It's hard to know what to say
at a time like this.
You know, Banshee's a town
like any other town.
And like any other town,
we have our darkness.
Our secrets.
Danny was too young
to be mayor...
and he was definitely
too young to die.
But something in him
compelled him to...
fight for goodness and justice.
He was young enough...
or maybe naive enough
to think that...
that he could help to build us
something better than we had,
something better than...
maybe some of us deserved.
He hadn't seen enough
yet to know fear.
Or regret.
Or the relentless
nature of evil.
And the truth is,
we should have had
this service weeks ago,
but Dan's the one who always
arranged these kind of events.
We're all just playing
catch-up now,
trying to fill the void he left.
Janie, on behalf of myself,
my office, and all of Banshee,
we mourn his loss with you.
So, back to business as usual?
Whatever that is.
You know, Job may have a point.
Do you ever stop to wonder
if you be pushing your luck?
Maybe it's time for you to take your
show on the road.
Look here, even
at 20 cents on the dollar,
those diamonds are more than enough
to get you set up...
anywhere you choose.
Trying to get rid of me?
Yeah, maybe I am.
For your own good.
Come on, man.
You've taken this sheriff thing about
as far as it should have gone.
Sooner or later,
someone's gonna figure out
who you are.
Or at least who you are not.
The thing is...
she's all I had.
I leave here...
I don't know, I feel
like I'll disappear or something.
You start over.
It's what you do
after a stretch like yours.
- Not that simple.
- Maybe.
Maybe you just don't know
simple when you see it.
Seat taken?
No, it's all yours.
Haven't seen you before.
- You from around here?
- I don't get out much.
You got Chivas 25?
Sure do.
Rough day?
I've had better.
You live around here?
About 40 yards away.
Well, that's convenient.
You wouldn't say that
if you'd seen the place.
Well, then let's go
see the place.
Bless me, Father,
for I have sinned.
Agent Racine.
Back again so soon?
I have a lot of sins.
Your visits
are becoming tiresome.
I thought you enjoyed
our repartee.
As I get older,
I find there are...
far fewer things that I enjoy.
Jesus Christ, Father.
You're in a hell of a mood.
My brother is dead.
I am waiting for you
to find his body.
I fully expect
to find his body...
eating and shitting
and recovering from
two bullet wounds.
This obsession of yours,
it cannot be good...
for your already fragile health.
You can't kill a dead man.
Death is not the worst thing that
can happen to a man.
I don't know how you can
call yourself a man of God...
when you hide
that evil son of a bitch.
I have seen pain
and suffering...
you would not believe.
And I have found God
in corners of the world...
in which you wouldn't
stoop to take a piss.
So don't come into my church...
with your grade school
notions of morality.
Right and wrong, good and evil,
they're just words.
Words made up
by small frightened men...
such as yourself
who cannot fathom...
the chaos and the darkness
of a truly almighty being.
Okay.
Good talk.
I'm coming for him, priest.
And you...
along with him.
You hear me?
You hear me?!
There's no one there.
Tell that to them.