Uh-huh, Barbie.
Hey.
So how were you planning
on getting home
if I hadn't shown up?
How do you get anywhere from here?
Middle of nowhere.
Yeah, that's where they build them.
They give you a bus schedule.
Thanks for coming.
No problem.
You okay?
It doesn't feel like
you think it would.
Getting out?
Yeah.
But you would know.
Yeah, reentry's a bitch
under any circumstances.
You must be missing your kids.
Sometimes in bed
I'd pretend that they'd crawled
into my arms like they used to
when they were little
and they couldn't sleep.
Deva's going through some stuff.
She needs her mom.
And how's Max?
From what I can see,
he's all about his skateboard.
You'll see for yourself
soon enough.
Can we stop somewhere to eat?
I'm starving.
Good?
How much do you remember
about prison food?
You know,
there was this one time
it was the warden's birthday,
anniversary, something,
I don't know.
He decided he wanted to
give us a special meal, right?
So he has the cooks
make us these big steaks.
Pretty good.
With potatoes and pie for dessert.
It's funny... some guys,
they just inhaled it.
I mean, it had been so long since...
Other guys, they took it back
to their tables and sat,
looked at it, just started crying.
I get it.
Then there was these other guys
who took the steak and threw it
against the fucking wall.
Like telling the place
to go fuck itself, you know?
Sean, get back here.
- I got it!
- Give it back!
That's so not fair.
You're supposed
to be setting an example.
I told you this was a bad idea.
I got to tell you,
I'm with Sean on this one.
- He wasn't sharing.
- Sure, take the girl's side.
Yeah, that's what I'm doing.
This could be Banshee.
But it doesn't feel the same.
Oh, my God. I can't believe this.
Deva had one just like this.
She loved this thing.
She slept with it,
took it to school with her.
We read The Last Unicorn
together when she was little.
It was her favorite book.
"I would enter your sleep if I could
and guard you there..."
Something something.
"But I cannot enter
unless you dream of me."
There you go.
- You read The Last Unicorn?
- In prison.
It was a small library.
What is it?
Nothing.
Tell me.
I just...
The whole time I was away,
I thought I knew what I was missing.
Turns out,
I only knew the half of it.
You should buy it for her.
- This a Revell?
- Good eye.
You a modeler?
Once upon a time.
- How much?
- It's 10.
Thank you.
I wouldn't have pegged you
for the model airplane type.
When I was a kid,
about the only time
I spent with the old man...
building model planes.
In all the time I've known you,
you've never once
mentioned your father.
Really?
There's no reason to start now.
What is it?
It's nothing.
Nothing.
Security camera,
upper right-hand corner on a swivel.
Won't do them any good
if they get hit at night.
You've been away too long. See
that ring around the outside lens?
That's LED lighting.
Finds you in the dark.
But that Vicon
in the window display...
- That's a camera?
- Yeah, it's wireless.
It's no problem
throwing off the signal.
Totally Mickey Mouse.
Listen to you.
Well, it is.
You know, if the safe
is the same make,
this place would be child's play.
But if you get jammed up front...
There is an alley running
behind the whole block.
I'm sure they have a door to it.
Look at you.
What?
That car.
- A tail?
- I don't know.
- But you've tagged it before?
- Twice.
Where?
Next street up,
down a block to the right.
- The driver?
- Couldn't see. Tinted windows.
I'll bring the truck around front.
Right.
- Behind.
- I know.
Wait here.
Excuse me. Is everything okay?
Yeah, sorry. I thought this was
a friend of mine's car.
Would you mind
just giving me a hand?
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
Guess I got too much stuff.
Thanks.
Where are you going?
Turnpike's that way.
Yeah, I thought
we could take a little detour.
Something I want to show you.
What is it?
Won't take more than a couple hours.
Unless you're in a hurry to get home.
Home.
Wait.
I got you something.
It's where we're going.
It's our house.
It's the house.
I figured we could, I don't know,
disappear here.
Oh, my God, you own this?
Paid cash.
Set up a trust for the taxes.
Just wanted you to see it.
It was a good plan.
You know, I've been thinking.
It's probably time
for me to be moving on.
Ever since I got to Banshee,
things have...
well, I've made things worse for you,
your family.
I mean, that wasn't the plan,
but that's what happened.
You tried to tell me.
Anyway, I...
I can't play lawman forever, can I?
Yeah, but where would you go?
What would you do?
Just go.
Maybe come back here.
I don't know.
I just can't keep doing the things
I've been doing to people.
No more.
When I got out and I found you,
you had a home, a family.
You had all the things
you were supposed to have with me.
And that fucking killed me.
Then I saw Deva.
And the truth is
I just didn't want to go.
So I told myself
that by staying,
I was protecting you.
- From Rabbit.
- Yeah.
I mean, I believed it.
I really believed it.
But he was always really after me.
It was never you.
So...
best thing I can do
for you is to leave.
What is it?
Well, maybe nothing.
Stay there.
- Sheriff Hood.
- Agent Racine.
Let's go.
The FBI dropped in for a visit.
- So I see.
- Mrs. Hopewell.
Congratulations...
on your release from prison.
Sit anywhere.
You won't be needing that.
Maybe. You want to tell us
why you're here?
Heard you had a visitor
while you were inside.
Oh, you knew?
After the fact.
You don't know me well.
If you did, you'd know
that putting Rabbit down...
is pretty much it for me.
Why? What is it
between you and Rabbit?
When I was a young agent...
I worked a few angles.
Got Rabbit's case for myself.
I figured I'd grab a few headlines,
move up the ladder.
But I busted him too soon.
His lawyers shredded me.
Got my wiretaps thrown out.
A week later,
my confidential informant
was murdered in Astoria
along with his wife
and two daughters.
So the way I see it,
those little girls and anyone else
he's killed since then,
they're all on me.
You have an ashtray?
Never even tried to quit.
Loved it too much.
And now they tell me
I don't have too much time left.
Six months.
A year.
I don't know what happens
to us when we die,
but I don't want to go out
with all those deaths on my head.
Yeah, that's touching,
but it still doesn't explain
why you're following us.
Waiting for her to get out.
Figured Rabbit would be waiting, too.
I still think that.
So you're using us as bait?
- Exactly.
- But you're wrong.
He's not coming.
He's tired, worn out.
- He's given up.
- What about you, Sheriff?
You also believe
our Rabbit has decided to
- forgive and forget?
- No.
You think he knows
my father better than I do?
It's not about what he knows.
It's about what I know.
So when Rabbit shows up,
you plan to be there.
That's right.
Then deliver him to justice.
By which I mean
shoot him till he's dead.
And if we get killed in the process,
that's just too bad?
You don't have anyone
to blame but yourself.
You had him at point-blank range.
You think of it, you should
thank me for having your back.
Did you hear the man?
We should be thanking him.
- How about that?
- We should be working together.
- We can't.
- Why not?
- Because we don't trust you.
- You should.
You of all people.
Why?
For starters,
I know you're not Lucas Hood.
Hey, hey, hey.
My gun is in the large compartment.
I'm still waiting to hear
what you got to say.
Fifteen years ago,
Capital Diamond Company.
I'm sorry?
Two thieves broke in that night
and one got away.
He or she was never caught.
But you weren't so lucky, were you?
I was there watching
that cop Bonner interrogate you.
You didn't give him a thing.
Hell, we still don't know
your real name.
Then I show up in Banshee
and there you are.
Lucas Hood.
A sheriff, no less.
I think you must have me confused...
No, no, don't.
Don't waste my time.
Those bodies your people
dug up in the woods,
one of them was stolen.
Someone wanted that body gone
before any DNA trace samples
could be taken.
Turns out there was more
than enough DNA on the clothes
that poor sucker
was wearing when he died.
And the DNA belonged
to one Lucas Hood.
He had his blood profiled like
everyone else in law enforcement.
So that makes you something
of a mystery, doesn't it?
Would you mind
putting a little water in this?
He knows who you are.
You can't let him leave.
Enough people have died over this.
So...
can I count on your cooperation?
No more.
So we help you find Rabbit...
what happens next?
You do that, as far as I'm concerned,
I never even have to ask
the next question.
What question?
Just who the hell you really are.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Stay there.
On three.
Okay?
Hey!
Shit.
Rabbit.
He's never gonna stop coming.
Not until we're both dead.
Nope.
I'm here.
- Back from the hill.
- Yep.
So you back a day late, aren't you?
Yeah, we took a detour.
So how'd it go?
Someone tried to kill us.
Was it Rabbit's people?
He's still out there, huh?
What happened?
Okay.
Well, I guess
you won't be leaving just yet.
I can't.
I can't say I'm sorry
to have you around a bit longer.
What can I say?
You keep me young.
And you're very generous
with my whiskey.
Especially my good whiskey.
You know,
every time I think
I know the way forward...
something just kicks me
back on my ass, you know?
It's like, you know...
it's...
Fuck, I don't know.
Like you're still inside.
People like you and me,
we don't need bars.
We build our own cells.
When you live like we live,
it goes without saying.
We're gonna find ourselves
in places
we never imagined we'd be
looking back and wondering
how the hell we got there
and why the hell it seems
you can't leave.
There's something broken in us.
Something that we don't have
that other people do
that lets them settle down
and find peace
and dream of a better life.
People like you and me,
we can't afford those dreams.
Why not?
Because of what we have done.
There are ghosts
that just won't let us be.
Fuck that.