(SOPRANOS THEME SONG)
I want you
to count backwards from 10.
Ten, nine...
...eight, seven...
Mr. Soprano, there's someone
here to see you.
Even here, you hector me?
The director has authorized us
to make you an offer.
Give up your nephew Tony.
Help take him down.
- What do I get?
- Guaranteed cure.
- No more cancer?
- Not a single diseased cell.
(LIVIA) I'm happy for you.
I know you've waited a long time.
- I don't like it.
- (LIVIA) Don't let people take advantage.
(TONY) I'm kidding, you old fuck.
What's the matter with you?
Dr. Kennedy? It's Dr. Enloe. I have
the results for the frozen section.
Can we move this along?
I have a thyroid in OR six at 10:30.
Based on the preliminary results
and depending on the full report...
- Is it clean, Enloe, or not?
- Yes, it's clean.
- Miles, you close.
- Quickly.
I've got his BP up,
don't know for how long.
Watch and learn, Miles.
Watch and learn.
Well?
Your uncle is a very strong man.
He did very well. The news is good.
- Beautiful.
- So the cancer is?
Gone? You bet.
I took out a tumor the size of a fist.
Oh, Madonna.
So if you'll excuse me,
I have another patient waiting.
Cheryl, make sure Marty gets
that Goldman Sachs statement. Yes?
I just wanted to say thanks, you know?
My uncle thinks the world of you.
If there's anything I can do...
...a favor, anything, let me know.
I'll keep that in mind, Mr. Soprano.
Game three.
- That's $60.
- Good luck getting it.
I won, Paulie.
It's only right you pay.
- And for other things.
- Like what?
Fucking Dom Perignon for everybody
in the skybox at the Garden.
Check comes, you're MIA.
You're worried about what I give you.
Worry about what you give me.
- Blow me with your lectures.
- Kid, you wearing a wire?
You crazy?
- Pat him down.
- He fucking touches me...
Then make it easy on us all.
Take them off. Everything.
New York reopened the books, but
they laid down a probationary period.
When I was coming up,
this would never happen.
- But too many are doing a simulcast.
- Yeah, maybe you, you fuck.
Do me a favor
and don't take it personally.
- Everything.
- Go fuck yourself.
Before, I was breaking balls.
Now you're beginning to worry me.
I guess you could call that a dick.
You're going.
That's all there is to it.
- Jason Mangelli isn't going.
- Tony, you want to weigh in here?
Tony?
- What?
- The Washington trip?
You're gonna be
on that bus tomorrow.
You're all packed and paid for
and you're gonna learn.
We're going to FBI headquarters.
So?
(BEEPING)
Excuse me.
What did you do to this scarole?
It's delicious.
Balsamic.
That's all they have at King's these
days. Balsamic, balsamic, balsamic.
My mother never heard of balsamic.
- I gotta go. Problems at work.
- It's Sunday dinner, Tony.
I know. I gotta go.
All right, Hugh, see you later.
- Can I be excused too?
- No, you may not.
He's got homework to finish
before the trip. Go ahead, Anthony.
- That's a nice example he sets.
- Ma.
The man's got two speeds, moping
or yelling, when he's here.
- He's got an uncle sick with cancer.
- They didn't speak for a year.
Actually, if you must know,
Tony has been better.
We've been seeing
his therapist together.
- What?
- He's no Angelo Stamfa, that's all.
- What does that mean?
- Angelo was dying to marry you.
Stamfa's is a chain of drugstores.
He doesn't need therapy?
He prescribes his own pills?
Don't be so sensitive.
What's sensitive?
I gotta hear this Stamfa shit again?
- All I was saying was...
- I know what you're saying.
Hugh, bring your plate.
You are blowing this all out
of proportion. We worry, that's all.
Spare me your concern, all right?
Spare me your attitude too.
Did you forget? Dad's mall was zoned
residential until Tony made a call.
- Bullshit.
- Oh, really?
That contract at Sparta High? The
other builders were too busy to bid?
My heart bleeds. The waters don't
part for you wherever you go?
I earn it. You two get a free pass.
- What's up?
- Hey, Tony.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(PUSSY'S VOICE)
Anyway, $4 a pound.
- Who brought this in here?
- Georgie. It's wacky, huh?
- You think it's a playroom back there?
- What?
Fucking toys. This is a business.
That's an office.
- They were selling them at Rite Aid.
- What? What did you say?
I pay you a fucking salary!
(POP MUSIC PLAYING)
(DOOR OPENING)
Carmela.
You sounded tense on the phone.
Yeah, I...
I wanted to make sure
it was okay if I came alone.
I mean, because Tony couldn't make it.
(PHONE)
(ANSWERING MACHINE BEEPING)
I love the artwork you have.
Those country scenes.
Thank you.
That statue is not my favorite.
It's not like this when Tony's here.
You never give the silent treatment.
Is that what you think?
I'm giving you the silent treatment?
You could tell me why you came today.
I'm worried about my husband.
The mood swings.
I thought when his mother died,
maybe...
But... still half the time
he doesn't even talk to me.
You've seen him like that,
that day he sat here like a wall.
I know he's your patient
and I'm the patient's wife...
...but you try living with that,
see how you feel.
- I see.
- Oh, you do?
For your information,
I am not the only one.
Tony isn't under the weather.
He didn't feel like coming.
"Fuck that shit," he said.
Usually happens
when we touch on a nerve.
He was distressed about this young
man's death in the garbage compactor.
See, he didn't say
garbage compactor, did he?
See?
- What do you believe?
- You know his job.
He reports to a strip club.
Who knows how he spends his days?
I'm sorry. I'm just frustrated.
Tony has been out of sorts for so long
and there's nothing I can do to help.
I think coming to therapy with him
has stirred feelings in you...
...that you would like to address.
Oh, please. I'm just emotional today.
I would like to help you, but as you
pointed out, your husband's my patient.
I am not the one who needs
mental help. I just needed to vent.
In case you change your mind...
...here's the number of
a colleague in Livingston.
He was a teacher of mine.
That really won't be necessary,
but thank you anyway.
Thank you for your time.
- You took these yourself?
- That's a village I lived in.
You could send them in
to National Geographic.
So I got back your complete
surgical pathology and op reports.
- I feel 100%.
- That's good.
It's possible though that there may be
some malignant cells we didn't get.
When we operate...
...we have to decide how much healthy
tissue to cut around the tumor.
The margins weren't wide enough.
We took a small sampling of the tumor.
When we got back the complete results,
it showed nodal involvement.
Don't blame yourself, doc.
What do we do next?
- It's called amended surgery.
- Oh, Jesus. Cut me again?
(INTERCOM BUZZING)
- Mrs. Brody is here.
- Don't let me keep you.
I am kind of backed up.
Let's schedule you for Tuesday at 6.
We can admit and prep you Monday.
- Any questions?
- When can he eat regular food again?
I'd guess two weeks.
Let's fill out the consent forms.
One less thing you have to deal with.
- Take all the time you need.
- You say sign, I sign.
Tell me to crap on the Queen Mary...
...an hour later, they're hosing
it down. I owe you everything.
How do I know
what nodal involvement is?
Didn't you listen? A whole issue
of U.S. News on seniors and health.
"Take somebody to the doctor's,"
it said. Somebody to ask questions.
You ask one dumb fucking question
about my diet.
- Angie?
- Carmela, hi.
- What a surprise.
- I didn't know you shopped over here.
They're running a special on lams.
Every penny counts.
How are you doing, Angie,
with Pussy gone?
I tell you, shopping for one
is no picnic.
Why don't you come for dinner?
It's just me and Tony.
Who knows? Maybe we'll get lucky
and Tony won't show.
(LAUGHING)
- That's Cocoa's worst time of the day.
- That dog is not a substitute.
That French poodle is
all I got left of Sal.
He disappears one day
and I get a sick dog.
The vet says to put her down,
but I want another operation.
With Sal, there was nothing
too good for that dog.
But where am I gonna come up
with $1200?
Tony helps out and I am so grateful.
It covers the basics.
But anything extra, there's no way.
Angie, I'm sorry.
That must be so tough.
I told the wallpaper guy
that this was okay.
Well, why did you
do that?
Because I didn't want to deal with
your parents anymore.
Anybody around here love
the word "Jimmy Choo shoes"?
No way.
Oh, my gosh, they're gorgeous!
Or would the lady prefer
something in gold?
Say a nice, I don't know,
whatever the fuck that is.
They're all yours. They're from next
season. You can't even buy them yet.
- What size are these?
- Ten.
Ten? That's Sasquatch size.
I'm a 81/2.
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Where'd I get 10 from?
Yeah, where?
So now what happens?
I gotta give them all back?
Temporarily. I'll get you
81/2s tomorrow.
- All of them? You swear?
- More even.
Since you been, you know, "in,"
I just can't believe the stuff we get.
It's so great.
Except for that Paulie. Fuck him
and the Coupe DeVille he rode in on.
He's saying
you're holding back again?
Like I'm gonna give that prick
a full share? Come here.
What do you say?
- I love you, baby.
- Oh, you fucking better.
- You better.
- I do.
You could've called.
Now everything's cold.
That's why they invented microwaves.
For inconsiderate husbands.
Since we're alone, it'd be nice
to have dinner together.
Don't bust my chops.
I got a lot on my mind.
This is fucking delicious. Really.
Is this the pecorino?
Right.
The hell with heating it up,
it's good like this.
I'm glad something brings you joy.
You're amazing, your cooking.
I'm having lunch with our daughter's
dean. You won't be joining me?
All he wants is our money.
We already shell out 40 grand a year.
It's well spent. She's really
learning. If she passes us by...
If? She did that when she was 14.
Isn't that what you want
for your kids?
No. I want them
to be backwards and ignorant.
And I'm gonna make sure of that by
not going to lunch with some asshole.
Fine, Tony. Don't go.
Guess who I ran into
at the supermarket today?
Angie Bonpensiero.
Really?
How's she doing?
Her dog is sick.
What, that fluffy French Cocoa
piece of shit? What's wrong with him?
Her. Osteoporosis.
Angie needs money for an operation.
Take it up with Pussy.
If you can find the fuck,
wherever the Feds put him.
I'd look in Arizona. Stake out all the
T.G.I. Friday's. He loves their wings.
He left Angie holding the bag. And
those FBI "family values" cocksuckers.
- They let him go without his wife.
- Into the program?
That's right. He ratted us out.
Me and you. That's where he is.
I don't want to hear about him
or his cunt wife.
His what wife?
- Okay, who was your oldest?
- Easy. Chuckie Periccio's mother.
- You had sex with Beverly Periccio?
- Yeah. A whole summer's worth.
Okay, my turn.
Who was your most famous?
And Bobby DiTillio doesn't count.
He's only famous in New Jersey.
You know Penn and Teller,
the magicians?
You fucked them?
Penn. And I didn't fuck him,
I gave him head.
- Which one is he?
- The big one.
They were playing AC
and they're funny.
He followed me into the ladies' room...
You lowlife cunt whore!
Get out of my sight!
- You fucking shitbag motherfucker!
- In the fucking bathroom?
(KNOCKING)
- Who is it?
- The FBI. Come on, dickhead, open up.
Paulie, it's 2 in the morning.
- It's an outrage. Adriana, you there?
- Yeah?
Sorry for the intrusion.
Put something on and come out.
You can't fucking do this!
I can't? You must have not read up
on the latest rules.
And put that piece away.
What's all this?
The Berezovsky brothers jacked
a shipment from Milan off pier 87.
Nice goods. My broad wears a size 10.
Patsy, pack up some of these shoes.
You don't mind if I take my taste now?
He's not taking those.
Make yourselves comfortable.
We'll just have a look around.
- I'll still get more shoes, right?
- Don't know. I have to pay for them.
- This really sucks, Christopher!
- You see the shit I go through?
- Motherfucker.
- What?
Nothing.
(POP SONG SOFTLY PLAYING)
Leave it on. It's nice.
(DOOR SLAMMING)
Meadow?
- Didn't you hear me knocking?
- I thought it was Vanessa.
You don't answer the door
when friends knock?
They keep you from studying.
My first class isn't until 2.
I brought your laundry.
I made ziti with the sweet sausage.
Oh, I'm so starved.
It reeks of cigarettes in here.
Are you smoking?
Caitlin.
I hope you're taking advantage of
offers here. A boy handed this to me.
"A seminar on the CIA
and the cultural cold war."
Oh, this looks interesting.
- It's basic, we're way past that.
- I'm reading Barbara Kingsolver.
I so wish I had time for fiction.
So how is the drama queen
doing anyway?
- Fine. Can we not talk about this?
- If you want me to leave, I will.
I have an hour before my lunch
with Dean Ross.
- Lunch with the dean?
- Can we not talk about this?
- Mom!
- His secretary called and invited me.
- Come on, what about?
- Money, I'm sure.
- They probably want a donation.
- How corrupt.
I wanted to make sure
you're recovered from the Noah thing.
I'm worried it'll affect your grades.
You call losing a wonderful man
because of Dad, a "thing"?
Is that what happened?
You kept seeing him long after
that business with your father.
Don't drag me into whatever bullshit
accommodational pretense you've got.
Was that last night's
reading assignment?
All right.
Let's hear it. What's your big theory
about me and Daddy?
No way. I'm not touching that.
Fucking bitch!
(SOBBING)
Uncle Jun, what the hell
are you doing?
Those marshals see you coming in here?
Because I need being remanded
to a jail hospital like I need crabs.
There's no car out there. And I came
up through the cellar like always.
Where's Bacala?
He's supposed to help.
I sent him to the drugstore
for more Pepto.
You're getting better. That's the
important thing. You look better.
If you're gonna lie, tell me
there's a broad in the car.
You want that,
it's a phone call away.
- Still want this?
- I gotta get nutrition somehow.
Kennedy says eat only
what I can sip through a straw.
What's going on with you
and Ralphie Cifaretto?
You don't got enough on your plate?
Worry about your own problems.
When can you eat real food?
Who knows? Kennedy's putting me
under the knife again.
Back up. More surgery?
Shouldn't you get a second opinion?
Chemo? Forget it.
With Kennedy, it's cut, zip, over and
out. He has the hands of an angel.
Don't forget his name.
I have to be impressed
because his name's John Kennedy?
All the micks named their kids that
after the guy got killed.
I loved that man.
(DOOR SLAMMING)
He was older than me and now look.
How many White Castles did you have?
- I didn't, I swear.
- I can smell them!
Let me call Cusamano.
He knows doctors.
He sent Silvio's mother to one.
It can't hurt.
- People come from the city see Kennedy.
- Then we won't be fighting traffic.
Come on, Uncle Jun,
you know I'm right.
All right, you set it up.
You come with me.
To listen and ask questions.
Good, good. I'll let you know,
all right? All right.
(DOOR SLAMMING)
He thinks I need a second opinion.
He doesn't like that
I'm going back under the knife.
- Maybe there's something to that.
- Another expert. Think on this.
Anthony is a cunt-hair away from owning
all of Northern Jersey. I'm that hair.
Maybe he has something else on
his mind besides my speedy recovery.
Junior, all this cynicism,
this can't be good for you.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
- You speak Italian.
- Second generation.
- Really? Ross?
- Rosetti.
A thousand years of a proud name
undone at Ellis Island.
A paesan.
- Not far from you. New Brunswick.
- No, get out!
My success, I credit
to the Jersey public schools.
- Where did you go to college?
- Rutgers.
- I went to Montclair State.
- Good school. Your major?
Business administration.
To Meadow Soprano,
a valuable addition to Columbia.
- Really?
- Absolutely.
I've talked to her professors.
They say she does all her work
and makes insightful contributions.
I am glad to hear you say that.
I was worried about her adjusting.
Let's not tell her.
We don't want her overconfident.
- She sleeps an awful lot.
- They all do.
Tony, what the hell?
You know, driving over here, I was
thinking about how to handle this.
Been working on my anger lately, so I
figure it's good if I quietly say...
...any kind of problem you got,
you come directly to me.
Please. Leave Carmela
the fuck out of it.
- Of course.
- Then I saw the Cadillac.
The money I give you, you're driving
a Cadillac and you want more?
Shot the whole plan.
(GLASS SHATTERING)
So remember this:
You see my wife, you talk about oven
cleaner. Anything else, come to me.
But think twice before you do.
Think about your fat-fuck husband
and what he did to you. Him, not me.
Cocoa, please. Cocoa, down!
Hey, how are you?
I'm sorry, Tony.
Just push her away.
She's all right. Good girl, good girl.
(LAUGHING)
- She don't look sick.
- It comes and goes.
Your kids don't feel boxed in
by the city?
We're out all the time.
Felicia has us all into kayaking.
- You do it together?
- Yeah.
The kids love it.
They're better at it than I am.
- More wine?
- Why not?
Remember I said I spend half
my time with student affairs?
- This is how I spend the other half.
- At lunch?
Development.
Fancy word for fundraising.
New student center.
We break ground in the fall.
- See the marble wall by the entrance?
- Yes.
- That's where the donor names will go.
- Everybody who donates?
The wall is reserved for those
whose commitment begins at $50,000.
It's what we felt
you'd be comfortable with.
Based on your generosity
to the Verbum Dei School.
You know what
we gave to Verbum Dei?
I'm half-embarrassed to say it,
but it's my job.
All the information,
including tax benefits, is in here.
I will have to talk to my husband.
Fifty grand?
You gotta be kidding me.
He talked a lot about Meadow
having the best possible experience.
- Those Jews are holding her hostage.
- He's Italian.
Jews with better food.
They know from Verbum
we're big givers.
We gave 5 grand a year.
That's a long way from 50.
This is college, Tony.
Five thousand is a slap in the face.
Well, let them say no.
Here.
It's around 5 grand.
Run it through your household account.
And that's it. Not a penny more.
5-FU with cisplatin and doxorubicin.
This is what I would recommend.
Are you getting this?
Sort of. So the chemotherapy
would be instead of the surgery?
I can't guarantee it.
We'll evaluate the results.
I could end up having the chemo,
puking my guts out...
...having the six hairs I have left
fall out and still be cut.
It's possible.
With Kennedy,
you don't get these maybes.
- But you gotta have surgery.
- Kennedy's a great surgeon.
Can't you people agree?
- Sure. Convene a tumor board.
- What's that?
A meeting of the chief of oncology,
pathologists and specialists...
...who work together
to reach a consensus.
- Then you hear what they have to say.
- Your uncle will not be present.
They'll pass their decision to you.
What you do is still your decision.
- And Kennedy will be there?
- No surgeon would miss it.
Not much to him, if you ask me.
Oh, you mean he's not Kennedy?
You make life and death decisions
because of a man's name?
It's only Sloan-fucking-Kettering,
best cancer hospital in the world.
Excuse me.
Let me ask you something
about this JFK worship of yours.
What about Hoffa
and the Teamsters?
That was the brother.
(PHONE RINGING)
Dr. Krakower?
Hi. Thanks for calling me back.
I was referred by a Dr. Melfi.
Yes, I would.
Anytime that's good for you.
That's great. That's fine.
Grove Avenue, right. I gotta go. Bye.
Who was that?
The paving guy. I'm thinking
of having the driveway redone.
- You smoking?
- What is this, the third degree?
- This says "with pulp."
- You like it with pulp.
Not this much. I like the one
that says "some pulp."
- What the fuck was that for?
- I'll write you up a list.
Hi. Oh, honey, I missed you so much!
(HORN)
This is the longest we have ever
been away from each other.
- Did you miss me?
- Sure.
Did somebody drop this?
Well? How was it?
Good. They had PlayStation 2
in the hotel room.
And?
That was the total of your trip
to the nation's capital?
I guess.
I'm sorry. The orange juice is fine.
Whatever kind is fine.
- Fuck the orange juice.
- I give up. What then?
The money you give to Angie and other
widows you've got on your payroll...
It's a business expense!
But there's not enough to make sure
your daughter is protected?
I won't pay. I know too much
about extortion.
Big deal, he pats you down.
I could do that standing on my head.
It's everything else.
He came to my apartment and
embarrassed me in front of Adriana.
I heard he strip-searched you.
I'm not kidding. He's a sick fuck.
He was sniffing her panties.
- What?
- You heard me.
I don't deny that Paulie can be
a little quirky. He always has.
You're moving up fast.
Why do you think that is?
- Because I'm your nephew?
- So be a big boy and suck it up.
The patient: Soprano, Corrado.
Male, caucasian, 72 years old.
Presented with severe weight loss
and early satiety.
He was scoped and a mass in the
curvature of his stomach was detected.
A CT scan revealed no evidence of
metastasis. Kennedy was referred.
He recommended gastric resection
for cure.
There were no surprises.
I thought we had it.
I was told we had clean margins.
Often, too little healthy tissue is
taken around the site...
...which leaves the possibility
for a false negative.
You want the whole stomach?
If there's a problem, we'll take it
to the board. What do we do?
He's high-risk. His pressure fell
below 60 for eight minutes.
Incision's fresh.
I can do it in half the time.
- If we don't do surgery, we do 5-FU.
- Which works how well?
- Not very.
- Which is why we decided to go in.
- What do I tell Mehta?
- Mehta? Sloan-Kettering Mehta?
Your patient sought a second opinion.
Forget it then. I don't need that shit
looking over my shoulder.
I'll tell him.
Yes, I'll have him there. Thanks.
Don't sugarcoat it!
(GROANING)
If you concentrate on your breathing,
it'll be easier.
The girl said she'd page Dr. Kennedy.
Where is he?
Twenty minutes and I'll be back.
- You go too easy on him.
- Probably.
Hey, if my nephew Cubby wasn't dead,
I'd have a soft spot for him.
Did you sniff that girl's panties?
He told you that? Fucking baby!
- You got to apologize.
- I'm not apologizing to him.
You were out of line.
He's gonna marry the girl.
As of the wedding day, anything that
touches her pussy is off-limits.
Think it's all up?
Soon enough there'll be more
where that came from.
Sounds like you were going
at it in there.
My pain a source of entertainment?
You see me laughing? Brought you
a milk shake from 31 Flavors.
It's your fault. I've been throwing up
all day since I started the chemo.
Oh, right. I gave you cancer.
You don't know what this is like,
Anthony. I can't do it.
- Kennedy was right.
- What's he gotta say?
I can't get him.
They won't put me through.
Why not?
I leave messages at the hospital and
office. I sent him a box of cigars.
I couldn't get past reception.
- He didn't call?
- Do they even tell him?
The machine says
for an emergency, press 6.
I press 6. Still no callback
24 hours later. He must be busy.
Yeah, that must be it.
You got his number?
Three more weeks.
Three more fucking weeks.
Answering machine.
What are you gonna do?
These doctors, it's not like on TV.
Dr. Kennedy, this is Tony Soprano,
Corrado's nephew.
My cell phone is 917-555-0157.
Call me back anytime day or night.
It's important.
Batter up.
Bye.
- Now what?
- Get in.
You're not even married yet,
you're dipping into whores.
Didn't cost me a quarter.
I don't pay for it.
How'd you find me?
Better be careful. If I can do it,
so can your bride-to-be.
What is this? Some new rule about
who I fuck? You want more shoes?
No. They don't fit her. I don't know
why I thought she was a size 10.
- I don't know either.
- I'm here to tell you one thing.
You go whining to the Big Man again
about shit between us...
...we'll have a problem, my friend.
You seen these?
Fuck is that?
My godson got it for me.
They're all over the place.
We gotta bring one into the club.
(FISH SINGS SONG)
Watch and learn, Phil.
Watch and learn.
- What are you doing?
- It's me, Tony. Corrado's nephew.
You belong to this club?
- Me? No. I came here to see you.
- You'll have to call my office.
You need a new secretary.
You're not getting all your messages.
For you.
Titanium. I use one.
Added 10 yards to my drives.
- Thanks, but I can't accept it.
- For what you've done for my uncle.
I already got one
and Mr. Williams here, he don't play.
- Right?
- Stupid fucking game.
- What can I do with it?
- What is it, Jack?
He'll just be a minute!
- I could use a little extra distance.
- Who couldn't?
My uncle's not doing so well.
Bad reaction to the chemo.
That happens.
There's nothing that I can do.
There are worse things that
can happen to a person than cancer.
My uncle thinks he's gonna die.
You know how old people are
with their superstitions.
He thinks it's because
he went against you.
I was his surgeon, that's all.
You got a bee on your hat.
Show that man the respect he deserves.
Answer his phone calls.
Cheryl, make sure
Mr. Soprano is scheduled for...
Just remember it.
- Everybody's marriage has problems.
- Is he seeing another woman?
You can make that plural.
He sees other women.
I look the other way.
I want to help him.
Do you? Moments ago
you used the word "divorce."
I said I was considering divorce.
I may be overstepping my boundaries,
but aren't you Jewish?
Is that relevant?
Us Catholics place a great deal of
stock in the sanctity of the family.
- And I'm not sure that your people...
- I've been married for 31 years.
Well, then you know
how difficult it can be.
He's a good man, he's a good father.
You said he's a depressed criminal,
prone to anger, serially unfaithful.
Is that your definition
of a "good man"?
I thought psychiatrists
weren't judgmental.
Patients want to be excused
from their predicament...
...because of events
in their childhood.
That's what psychiatry
has become in America.
Visit any shopping mall or ethnic
pride parade to witness the results.
- What we say in here stays in here?
- By ethical code and by law.
His crimes...
...they are organized crime.
The Mafia?
Oh, Jesus.
Oh, so what? So what?
He betrays me every week
with these whores.
Probably the least of his misdeeds.
You can leave now or you can stay
and hear what I have to say.
- You'll charge the same.
- I won't take your money.
That's a new one.
You must trust your initial impulse
and consider leaving him.
You'll never be able to feel good.
You'll never be able to quell
the feelings of guilt and shame...
...as long as
you're his accomplice.
- You're wrong about the accomplice.
- Are you sure?
All I do is make sure
he's got clean clothes and dinner.
So "enabler" would be a more accurate
job description than "accomplice."
My apologies.
So you think I need to define
my boundaries more clearly...
...keep a certain distance,
not internalize my...
What did I just say?
Leave him.
Take only the children,
what's left of them, and go.
My priest said I should try
and help him to be better.
How's that going?
Have you read Crime and Punishment?
Dostoyevsky?
It's not an easy read,
it's about guilt and redemption.
And I think, were your husband
to turn himself in, read this book...
...reflect on his crimes for 7 years
in his cell, he might be redeemed.
I would have to get a lawyer...
...find an apartment,
arrange for child support...
You're not listening.
I'm not charging you
because I won't take blood money.
And you can't either.
One thing you can never say:
That you haven't been told.
I see.
You're right. I see.
You're poisoning me.
I don't know how much more I can take.
- You taking care of this young man?
- Dr. Kennedy!
How you doing?
I've been busy. You all right?
Don't bullshit a bullshitter.
Will this work? Or should we operate?
- You got a top guy here.
- Him?
- I'd see him if I needed to.
- Son of a bitch.
Stay strong and keep fighting.
That's my home number.
You start to feel punk, you call.
Thanks.
I'll check on you Wednesday.
Take care of this young fellow.
- Carm.
- What?
You sick?
Everybody else in this family sleeps
all day, I thought I'd try it.
You...
...depressed?
Or what?
I figure in the division of labor
around here, that's your job.
Because, you know, if you want to go
to therapy on your own or something...
I notice you been tense lately.
That's rich.
You suggesting I go to a shrink.
I don't have the time.
I'll still go to yours, if you want.
You know best.
- That dean called today.
- Well, that can't be good.
I told him to put us down
for the 50,000.
Carmela, I gave you 5.
Maybe I could go another 5.
Maybe 10, but that's enough.
Tony, you gotta do
something nice for me today.
And this is what I want.
You gotta do this.
All right, I'll go to 10.
That should be enough for them.
I already told him 50.
- 50 G's?
- Yes.
You look like you could use
a night off from cooking.
What do you say we go out?
(POP SONG PLAYING)