(OPENING CREDITS MUSIC)
JACKIE:
Goddamn Martha Stewart funeral.
MARIAN: What if, after you die,
part of you goes to heaven,
but part of you stays here?
JACKIE: Goddamn Mother of the Year.
MARIAN: Just to see
how things turn out...
JACKIE: And then she burned her.
MARIAN: For you... For Mama.
JACKIE: Cremated.
ADORA: Hello, darling. Sit down.
Have dinner with us.
Special occasion.
I set a place for you.
AMMA: "Occasion" means cake, Mama.
You promised.
Now that the Keene boy's
been arrested,
our little girl is finally safe.
(STUTTERS) I can't even say
the relief I feel.
ALAN: Yep. All is well at last.
ADORA: Mmm-hmm.
Is it?
I don't think John Keene is a killer.
ADORA: Of course you don't.
Camille, sit down.
Sit down.
I suppose this means you'll be
heading back to St. Louis shortly.
Story's over.
AMMA: I hope he gets
the death penalty.
Babykiller Keene.
Turns out, Missouri is
the fifth most productive state
in terms of carrying out executions.
We had to stop. It was, uh...
The fluid was controversial.
I think, um...
Yeah, I think it wasn't
killing people well enough.
-(MUMBLES INDISTINCTLY)
-Well, in any case, um...
I just read that
we import it from Romania.
AMMA: Fluid?
ADORA: For lethal injection, sweetie.
-Oh.
-ADORA: Hmm.
Needles. Like the needles
I get sometimes?
Very different.
Like putting a cat to sleep.
Hmm.
Well, I hope he gets the needle.
Guess which Greek goddess
I am, Camille.
I guess I'm not really
up on my goddesses.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
I'm Persephone.
Queen of the Underworld.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
She's married to that...
Big dude.
-Hades.
-(ADORA CHUCKLES)
AMMA: He runs Hell, but she's
in charge of punishment.
But I feel sorry for Persephone
because, even when
she's back with the living,
they're afraid of her
because of where she's been.
Kind of funny, huh?
How many stories they have
where princesses
need to get rescued from witches.
Wind Gap has one, even.
Little girls yanked from the woods
by the Woman in White.
I don't like that one.
-Too close to home?
AMMA: Mmm-hmm.
Would you be more sad
if John died or I died?
I don't want anybody to die.
ADORA: Wind Gap
has too much death as it is.
ALAN: Hear, hear.
ADORA: Camille, uh, that food's
not gonna eat itself.
Or aren't you feeling well?
Just a little off.
ADORA: Your editor must be excited
about getting his
intrepid girl reporter back.
What will you work on next?
Maybe something more upbeat
for a change. (CHUCKLING SOFTLY)
In any case,
I'm sure he's happy to have you
back where you belong.
(SNIFFLES)
Well, Mama...
I was thinking that with everything
going on in town, all the trouble,
it might be nice to have Amma
come stay with me
in St. Louis for a while.
Little change of pace
might do her good.
(SIGHS) Well...
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
That is a truly remarkable suggestion.
That's a wonderful offer, dear.
But impossible.
She's starting school soon.
I think it would be nice
to see that big old arch.
Did you two discuss this already?
No. I just thought that...
Amma.
Your color is high.
Are you feverish?
Oh, God. You're as hot as an oven.
-l want cake.
-ADORA: No, you have to lie down.
-I will bring you cake later.
-Please eat, Camille.
-(AMMA CRYING)
We'll say our goodbyes in the morning.
-l want cake.
-Come on, sweet.
Come on, sweet. Come on.
You can have cake.
ALAN: Dinner is not finished, Camille.
(GRUNTS) Ma.
-Mamal!
-ALAN: Adora!
Mama. Oh, God.
(BREATHING HEAVILY) Help me.
-What's going on, sweetheart?
-CAMILLE: I don't know.
-(GRUNTS) Okay, come on.
-Help her up.
-Mama's here. Hold on.
-What's going on?
I don't know. (BREATHING HEAVILY)
I don't know what happened.
(CAMILLE SNIFFLING
AND BREATHING HEAVILY)
ALAN: It's all right. It's okay.
It's all right, dear.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
ADORA: I got you.
CAMILLE: (SNIFFLES) Okay.
ADORA: You may come in, darling.
Take your clothes off.
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
Do you see how nice it is
not to have to worry or fight?
Just to let yourself be looked after?
Mmm. Yeah.
This will be good for both of us.
Don't you think?
Mmm, yes.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(SOFTLY) Open, darling.
Ahh...
Mmm.
You are such a good girl.
(SOFTLY) More, Mama.
Yes.
Now rest.
I'll fix your dosage for the night.
(FAN STOPS WHIRRING)
(FOOTSTEPS DEPARTING)
-(FAN STARTS WHIRRING)
-(DOOR SLAMS)
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
(EXHALES)
(VICKERY GRUNTS SOFTLY)
-VICKERY: How'd you sleep, son?
-Why am I even here, hmm?
(CLEARS THROAT)
Well, the thing is, John,
your girl, Ashley, she gave you up.
So, she... She said I did it,
or she thinks I did it?
RICHARD: She led us to evidence.
What do you think that was?
I got no idea.
She wasn't getting
what she wanted from me.
Sometimes you stay with somebody,
and the only reason is
because you don't have the energy
to go through ending it.
All the fights and the scenes.
And with Ashley,
it was gonna be a scene.
(SIGHS) And then
Natalie happened, and...
I don't know, I could barely, uh...
Ashley was there,
but I wasn't, really. You know?
Natalie "happened."
Yeah.
Yeah, somebody killed
my little sister.
Not me.
Do you want me to say it again?
Want me to fucking write it down?
So, you think Ashley made something up
to get back at you.
-Is that what you're saying?
-I don't know.
But she was mad at me,
and she had her reasons
to be, I guess.
How do you explain the blood we found
in the carriage house?
What?
Natalie's blood.
How do you explain it, John?
Really?
(SHUDDERING BREATHS)
It happened there?
Come on, John. Stop bullshitting us.
-You know it fucking happened...
-I don't know!
Okay? It doesn't make
any fucking sense!
(BREATHING HEAVILY) Look, I know
I need to get my head right
because what happened
to Natalie and Ann.
But you want me to say it's me.
And you could probably
get away with it.
But you'd be so wrong.
You'd be so fucking wrong.
VICKERY: What do you think?
(VICKERY SIGHS)
He gonna crack?
Almost everyone does
if you push them hard enough.
Even if they're innocent.
Well, we'll give him some time
to think about it.
Take another run at him
after his next shitty meal. (CHUCKLES)
Sorry about the Preaker girl.
No need to be sorry.
She got a lot of her mother in her.
Adora's not as dramatic about it,
but that woman loves her attention.
Then scolds you
if you give her too much.
Well, if you listen
to all the talk around here,
everyone's some kind of crazy or evil.
Only half of it's true.
RICHARD: That's what
I'm worried about. (SIGHS)
We're looking at the wrong half.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(BELL TOLLING)
VICKERY: News crew's coming down
from St. Louis today.
Jocelyn says the stubble...
How'd she put it?
-"Undermines my authority."
-(CLYDE CHUCKLES)
I think she just wants
to spare her chin.
(CLYDE LAUGHS)
-CLYDE: Oh, Alan.
-(ALAN SIGHS)
CLYDE: Uh, sorry,
this won't take long.
The chief here
is fixing to be on the news.
Oh. I guess, uh,
congratulations are in order.
I suppose they are.
Well, I'll just, uh,
come back in a while.
-How's Amma?
-Amma's fine, fine.
-VICKERY: I ran into her roller pals.
-Oh, yeah?
Said she wasn't feeling well. Sick.
Yeah. We've been passing
something around the house.
I hope you don't catch it.
How's that?
You're up there as much as I am.
Why don't you pull up a chair, Alan?
We'll talk this out like men.
(MUSIC PLAYING OVER STEREO)
(INAUDIBLE)
Get it out.
(RETCHES)
(COUGHING)
Mama? (BREATHING HEAVILY)
ADORA: Well, you're back early.
Clyde was, uh...
Wasn't feeling very well.
Neither is Camille.
She's already finished a bottle,
poor thing.
Don't go overboard.
ADORA: What?
I only mean...
(SIGHS) Let the girls rest.
The body's a miraculous thing.
Let's just let it do its work.
I will.
I'm just helping nature along.
This is your area.
Is there anything you want here?
Whatever.
AMMA: You took it, didn't you?
It's better if you don't try to stand.
Crawling's okay.
-How do you feel?
-Can you walk?
AMMA: Yeah, I'm not so bad right now.
She's got you to care for.
I need you to call, um...
No cell. Mama took it.
Then I need you to go get Richard.
-Um, what?
-Go and get him,
and tell him that I need him,
that we need help.
-And if anything...
-Mama.
...happens to me, you tell them
-that Mama took care of me.
-Mama.
You understand?
So you go. And you don't come back.
Go.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
ADORA: What's going on?
You girls better be in bed.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(AMMA GASPS)
ADORA: Camille. Camille.
-Oh, darling.
-Mama... (INHALES SHARPLY)
-Camille.
-Mama, am I gonna die?
-We're all gonna die, Camille.
-(CHUCKLING SOFTLY)
Let's get you clean.
You're just covered in sick.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER CONTINUES)
ADORA: I got you. Hold on.
ALAN: Feeling better, dear?
Here. Here.
Oh, it's not so bad.
-On the mend, I hope.
-Yeah.
-Hey, how about that cake, hmm?
-(SNIFFLES)
I could use a piece myself.
If we're gonna have cake,
we should tell Mama.
You go on upstairs to your room,
and I'll bring you your dessert.
Mmm-hmm.
This is not the time
to insert yourself,
you understand?
(SOFTLY) All right.
ADORA: Sit right here.
Right there, right there...
MAN: (OVER MIC) Check this, one, two.
One, two, three. One, two.
Okay, you ready? Here we go.
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING ON JUKEBOX)
WOMAN: (CHUCKLES) You know
I'm gonna be here all night.
MAN: Well, so am I. Mmm.
WOMAN: Yeah. (CHUCKLES)
All right. All right.
I have other people to take care of.
MAN: You know how to sing, Big City?
(GIGGLES)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER CONTINUES)
(RETCHING)
CAMILLE:
Mama, what's in the blue bottle?
Oh.
I've waited for this for so long,
for you to need me.
Of my three girls,
you're the one most like me.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Marian, she was a...
She was a good girl.
She just...
She needed constant attention.
Stuck to my side.
You killed her.
She was a very sick little girl.
(CHUCKLING SOFTLY) You're delirious.
-She died.
-You burned her.
Well, ashes to ashes, I say.
To even think of you or her
rotting in a box,
things eating away at you?
No, no, no. No, no.
Just tell me.
What?
-Tell me.
-You're asking me to lie.
I can't.
I can't do that, even for you.
My mother,
you never did know her like I did.
Once, Joya woke me
in the dead of night.
I was seven, eight.
She didn't say a word to me.
Just shook me awake,
walked me outside.
Barefoot, in my nightgown.
I knew better
than to open my mouth
when Joya was punishing me.
It was the same whether
I'd done something wrong or not.
She drove me to the woods,
walked me in deep,
sat me down and left me.
-(SNIFFLING)
-Took me hours to get home.
When I finally made it,
I walked in that door,
and my mother said,
"You're home."
I believe if you had asked her
she would have said
what she was doing was right.
We all have bad childhoods.
At some point,
you have to forget it, move on.
Anything else is just selfish.
(CAMILLE GROANING)
Time for more medicine.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(RETCHING)
I don't want any more. I can't.
It's good for you.
(GROANING)
Here. Take just a little more.
Right here.
I'll be right back.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
-It's okay.
-(SIGHS AND SNIFFLES)
(CAMILLE BREATHING HEAVILY)
(DOORBELL RINGS)
(GASPS AND COUGHS)
-(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
(MUSIC PLAYING ON RECORD)
RICHARD: Hello? Hello?
-(BREATHING HEAVILY)
-RICHARD: Hello?
CAMILLE: Hello? Hello...
-Evening, Detective.
-Good evening.
I didn't hear you right off.
I apologize.
Is Camille available?
Not at the moment, no.
She's out with those
girlfriends of hers.
Help me. (BREATHING HEAVILY)
-Tell her I stopped by?
-I certainly will.
You have a good evening, Detective.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(MUFFLED SONG CONTINUES PLAYING)
-(CONTINUES BREATHING HEAVILY)
-(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
(CAR DEPARTS)
CAMILLE: (BREATHING HEAVILY)
Amma, you said you were gonna go.
(CRYING) I'm sorry.
I need to stay her good girl.
(CRYING) I need to stay her good girl.
(CAMILLE WHIMPERS AND CRIES)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GROANS)
(CONTINUES BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CELL PHONE BUZZING)
CAMILLE: (OVER VOICEMAIL)
Preaker. Leave a message.
(LINE RINGING)
Preaker. Leave a...
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING ON RECORD)
(SIGHS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GROANS)
(INAUDIBLE)
(CONTINUES BREATHING HEAVILY)
(WEAKLY) Mama.
ADORA: Alan! Alan!
Alan! (BREATHING HEAVILY)
Alan!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(MUFFLED INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(CONTINUES BREATHING HEAVILY)
RICHARD: Camille. Camille. Camille.
Talk to me.
Camille. Camille, look at me.
Look at me.
We need an ambulance in here now!
Get one up here now!
-Camille!
-CAMILLE: Get Amma.
Get Amma.
Shh. It's okay, honey.
Amma.
It's gonna be okay, kiddo.
(CAMILLE CRYING)
-(SOBBING)
-It's all right.
Get you home. Home. Home. Home.
Yeah. Home. You're okay.
-RICHARD: Amma!
-You're okay now.
(CONTINUES SOBBING)
ADORA: What were you told
to warrant this kind of a violation?
You know me. You know who I am.
My God!
You know how sorry I am
it has to be this way,
but we have reason to believe...
ADORA: No. Get...
Alan, get Glen Morgan on the phone.
-Yeah, all right.
-ADORA: He's our lawyer.
I won't have this.
(STUTTERING) I don't... I don't care
what Camille told you.
-She is mentally ill.
-MAN: Detective?
ADORA: Do you understand?
-(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
-What do you got?
-ADORA: Do you understand?
-Adora, that's not the point.
She's mentally ill.
RICHARD:
Mrs. Crellin, you're gonna need
to come down to the station with me.
What?
Adora, put your hands
behind your back.
VICKERY: Adora, you have to do
what he says. Now.
No, no, no. No, I can't. I can't.
They're trying to make this
as respectful as possible.
-Put your hands behind your back.
-No, no, no, no.
RICHARD: You have the right
to remain silent.
Detective, is that necessary?
You have the right to an attorney.
If you can't afford an...
ALAN: Call me
as soon as you get there.
RICHARD: Do you understand
your rights, Mrs. Crellin?
-Come up. Please, gentlemen, hurry.
-MEDIC 1: Yes, sir.
Can you see that? Can you see it?
CAMILLE: Mmm-hmm.
MEDIC 1: Eyes are PEARL.
-Can you see it?
-FRANK: She gonna be okay?
MEDIC 1: Yeah. Eyes are PEARL, too.
-Good girl.
-MEDIC 2: Yeah.
MEDIC 1: Can you walk? Come on.
CAMILLE: Yeah.
MEDIC 1: Good, good, good. Okay.
CAMILLE: I'm walking out of here.
MEDIC 1: Take it easy.
Take it easy, now.
-It's gonna be all right.
-(SOBBING) Please don't.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
MAN: Check 'em.
MEDIC 1: I got you.
ADORA: Amma!
AMMA: Mama! Mama!
AMMA: Mama!
(SCREAMS) Mama!
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
I'm bleeding as fast as I can.
We found the pliers
that match the marks
on Ann and Natalie's gums,
so we're expecting to charge
your mom on the girls, too.
She pulled the teeth alone?
She might have had
an accomplice, maybe Alan.
We'll investigate.
And what about Marian?
We're hopeful that the levels
from you two will help us.
Thank you.
Usually Munchausen Moms, they, uh...
They tend to use the same poisons
once they find one they like.
We found a collection of medicine
Adora was hoarding.
Antifreeze, prescriptions.
Rat poison.
Amma built up a tolerance
for it over the years.
That's what the doctors think.
But, uh, not you, so...
Oh, Christ.
You have a good friend in your boss.
Vickery didn't want
to hear it from me,
but, uh, Curry nearly busted
the station door down.
I'm sorry for your...
I'm sorry, Camille.
For everything.
Yeah. Me, too.
I'm sorry.
AMMA: What a dick.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
(INAUDIBLE)
How do you plead?
ADORA: Not guilty.
(INAUDIBLE)
JACKIE: Well, look here.
I wasn't expecting
to see you beauties.
Don't you just look beautiful?
Did you get
the housewarming card I sent you?
Okay.
I know your place
isn't new to Camille,
but it is new to you.
It's a new lease.
You know, I might just come up
to St. Louis one day
for a visit.
CAMILLE: Yeah, you should do that.
Do not let that witch
come to St. Louis.
She tries. She's just not happy.
Not happy? She's a pig in shit
now that Mama's out of the way.
FRANK: "Men get to be warrior poets.
"What woman is described that way?
Not Adora.
"Prosecution says
my mother is a warrior martyr.
"If she was guilty, they argued,
"it was only of a very female
sort of rage.
"Overcare. Killing through kindness.
"It shouldn't have surprised me
"that Adora fell on that sword
spectacularly.
(SIGHS) "Of course,
she never did explain the teeth
"or that kind of naked rage a person,
"man or woman,
would need to do something like that.
"It didn't fit.
"So, as with everything
in my mother's world, it didn't exist,
"except perhaps in some dark place
only she knows about.
"My mother has many years
to consider what she's done.
"As for me,
"I've forgiven myself
for failing to save my sister
"and given myself over
to raising the other.
"Am I good at caring for Amma
because of kindness,
"or do I like caring for Amma
because I have Adora's sickness?
"I waver between the two.
"Especially at night,
when my skin begins to pulse.
"Lately, I've been...
"Leaning toward kindness."
-(FRANK CLEARS THROAT)
-(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Come on, what do you think?
Can't a person
be quiet for a second, or...
It's beautiful, Cubby.
(SMACKS LIPS) Really beautiful.
So, just file it?
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
File it.
(CLEARS THROAT) Um...
You noticed I finally stopped
asking if you were fine?
You noticed
I started asking if you were?
Yeah. It's annoying.
-Are you?
-Doing better. Stop it.
I owe you. You and Eileen, I do.
If you, uh...
If you ever need anything...
You certainly do not owe us.
Worrying about you was the only thing
that kept the missus
from nursing me to death.
(BOTH CHUCKLE SOFTLY)
(AMMA LAUGHING)
She seems like
she's gonna be just fine.
And I like her friend.
She might actually be
a good influence on her.
Amma's, uh... I don't know.
She doesn't sleep most nights
unless I'm with her.
-She misses Adora.
-What a thing.
Even when you win
the fucked-up family Olympics...
-EILEEN: Okay, guys, time to eat now.
-(GIRLS CHUCKLE)
CAMILLE: Oh.
(TAPS TABLE)
It's about damn time!
So, it turns out that
the mayor didn't want me to know
because the new head of Parks and Rec
was his appointment
-and his mistress.
-(AMMA LAUGHS)
And that, I believe,
has nothing to do with,
Mae, your question about
why the public pool closed.
Oh, but it was a good story. Juicy.
My husband will take the long route
to avoid a simple "I don't know."
MAE: I like your editorials,
Mr. Curry.
They make good points,
and they're not boring.
-FRANK: You read the editorials?
-Mmm-hmm.
-Call me Frank. I like this girl.
-(LAUGHTER)
I'm thinking about going into
either politics or journalism.
-FRANK: Mmm.
-You just say that to impress Camille.
-I do not.
-Kiss-ass. (SCOFFS)
MAE: I don't know what
I want to do yet, exactly.
-We have a lot of time, right?
-FRANK: Absolutely.
Well, I'm gonna be
an on-camera personality.
I have the gift of gab, that's what...
That's what people say.
Well, that's interesting.
How does one get into that field?
Well, you start with the gift of gab.
Then you go to college,
and Communications major.
EILEEN: Again, he has no idea.
-I have no idea.
-(LAUGHTER)
Let's just get you
through high school first, hmm?
Do you wish I was a writer like you?
All I wish is for you to be happy.
You make me happy.
I could eat you up.
(CHUCKLES)
-(LAUGHS)
-Okay.
All right, good night.
G'night.
(DOOR CLOSES)
-(KNOCK AT DOOR)
(MUSIC PLAYING ON RECORD)
Sorry to bother you,
but have you seen Mae?
Oh, uh, I think that she and Amma
went to the park
to not swim in the closed pool,
but, uh, they should be back soon.
Did Amma talk to you?
I think the girls had
their first little fight.
-Over what?
-Who knows?
-(CHUCKLES)
-A boy, nail polish,
-girl stuff.
-Yeah.
I envy the skin, but nothing else
about that age, you know?
Yeah. Well, um, when they get back,
I'll send her your way, all right?
-Thanks, hon.
-All right, no problem. Bye.
(SIGHS)
(DOOR OPENS)
(KEYS JINGLING)
(SOFTLY) Don't tell Mama.
(END CREDITS MUSIC)
(INAUDIBLE)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(SONG PLAYING)