Previously on Hannibal...
Four of the lures are made from
materials including human remains.
Kade Prurnell, Office of
the Inspector General, FBI Oversight.
I'm pleading innocent.
You'll be found guilty
and given the federal death penalty.
What defense do you think I have?
You had no control of what you were doing,
much less remember doing it.
Betrayal was
the only thing that felt real to me.
I trusted you.
Let me help you.
I need your help.
We investigated your claims
about Dr. Lecter.
We found nothing.
You stood over
Cassie Boyle's body in that field
and you described yourself to me.
No, I described Hannibal Lecter.
You think Will is innocent.
I don't know what I think.
I think he still wants to save lives.
That's what I think.
Mr. Graham, it's time.
Let me tell you the story
of a mild-mannered FBI instructor
who was asked to create
a psychological profile of a murderer,
Garret Jacob Hobbs, the Minnesota Shrike.
He killed young women
that looked just like his daughter.
He killed them
and he ate them.
Will Graham
understood the way Hobbs thought.
That's how he caught him.
He shot Hobbs dead
while he cut his daughter's throat.
So Will Graham
was able to save Abigail Hobbs' life.
But the profile that he created
of her father was so vivid
that he couldn't escape it.
See.
And in an unconscious state,
he killed four more women.
Cassie Boyle.
Marissa Schurr.
Georgia Madchen.
Abigail Hobbs.
He was able to save Abigail Hobbs
from her father,
but he wasn't able to save her from himself.
He killed her and he ate her.
At the very least, he ate her ear.
What happened to the rest of Abigail Hobbs
is locked away in the recesses
of Will Graham's traumatized mind,
or so he would have you believe.
Something else you should know
about Will Graham.
He has remarkable visual memory,
he's keenly insightful
to the human condition
and I would argue,
the smartest person in this room.
He's capable of creating
a psychological profile
of a completely different kind of murderer.
One that would become his alibi.
Moment of truth.
If I only knew what the truth was.
There's nothing wrong with your instincts.
My instincts have not yet
arrived at conviction.
Mine have,
with the benefit of no previous involvement
and no personal connections
to the accused.
Meaning I can't be impartial?
Of course, you can be impartial,
but right now you're not.
You have to believe something,
as long as there is reason
and evidence to believe.
You've got reason, you've got evidence.
Will Graham is playing a game.
I understand why
that might be hard for you to accept.
Do you?
It's easier to be a man
who missed his friend's suffering
than it is to be
the head of Behavioral Sciences at the FBI,
who missed a killer
standing right in front of him.
There's a reason that you're a witness
for the prosecution, Agent Crawford.
Remind me what that reason is.
If you can't represent your own beliefs,
represent the Bureau's.
Agent Crawford?
Let yourself off the hook, Jack.
How did you meet Will Graham?
I met him at the opening
of the Evil Minds Research Museum.
He didn't agree with what we called it.
He told me that the title
mythologized banal and cruel men
who didn't deserve
to be thought of as super-villains.
And what was your first impression?
He was intelligent and arrogant.
And very likely on the spectrum.
Which is why he wasn't real FBI.
He didn't pass the screening procedures.
Yes.
But you felt that he was qualified
to work in the field.
Under my supervision.
And you believed that he was valuable
because he could think like a killer.
He could think like anybody.
Sounds like a super-villain.
Five horrendous murders,
over 40 different pieces
of forensic and physical evidence
that tell us that Will Graham
can think like a killer because he is one.
Rather than feel tormented
by the work he did,
Will Graham enjoyed the cover
his role at the FBI gave him
to commit his terrible crimes.
I don't believe that to be true.
Agent Crawford?
Will hated every second of the work.
He hated it.
He didn't fake that.
He hated it and I kept making him do it.
Why then is it that when you offered him
an opportunity to quit, he refused?
Because he was saving lives.
I had been warned by more than one person
that if I pushed Will, I'd break him.
I put those checks and balances in place,
then ignored them.
And here we are.
COURT HOUSE
LEONARD BRAUER
PERSONAL & CONFIDENTIAL
What does Jack Crawford drink?
Whatever it is,
I need to send him a very expensive bottle.
He said I'm a killer
because he drove me insane.
- No, he paved the road for your defense.
- Well, he didn't say I'm innocent.
Innocence isn't a verdict, Mr. Graham,
but "not guilty" is.
This isn't law, it's advertising.
Advertising trivializes, it manipulates,
it's vulgar.
Boo-hoo. So is the law.
We had to create desire
to find you not guilty,
which is nonexistent
in this courtroom right now.
We're manipulating people
into buying something they don't need.
- Mr. Brauer?
- They don't want your innocence.
Thank you.
Unconsciousness in a pretty package,
that I can sell.
If I take the moral high ground with you,
I'll get you killed.
I think I opened your mail.
HANNIBAL
That was a good and brave thing
you did for Will today.
It may have cost me my job.
The prospect doesn't seem to trouble you
as much as I would have thought.
Haven't felt better in weeks.
Clarity will do that.
Tell me, Jack.
Was your testimony
meant to be a resignation?
There is something appealing
about walking away from all of the noise.
I'm content to let the chips fall.
The magic door is always attractive.
Step through
and leave all your burdens behind.
I've given my life to death.
And now death has followed you home,
come to live in your house.
Bella has kept our bedroom
from looking too much like a sickroom.
There are flowers, but not too many.
You know.
She insists that there are no pills in sight.
So, I've been thinking about
taking her to Italy where we met.
We could...
She could die there.
Jack.
You're not sick.
You don't have to go
into the ground with her.
When Bella's lost to you,
the FBI could still be there.
You're telling me
not to commit professional suicide?
As a friend,
I'm telling you not to force an issue
for the short-term emotional satisfaction
it can have.
Shrunken capillaries.
The ear was cut from a corpse
no more than 48 hours ago.
Before the trial started.
We fumed it all,
ear's clean,
no prints on either of the envelopes,
besides the courier, paralegal and lawyer.
We know Will Graham didn't do it.
- It wouldn't surprise me.
- The timing's deliberate.
It was choreographed to drop the ear
at the beginning of Will's trial.
Such a gift has great significance.
A gift from who?
Will claimed someone else
committed the crimes he's accused of.
He said that person was you.
Perhaps he was half right.
You've gotta be kidding me.
BALTIMORE STATE HOSPITAL
FOR THE CRIMINALLY INSANE
It seems you have an admirer.
You think someone sent me an ear
because they admire me?
The boundaries of what's considered normal
are getting narrower.
Outside those boundaries,
this may be intended as a helpful gesture.
How far would you go to help me?
It hadn't occurred to me to send you an ear.
But I'm grateful someone has.
Gratitude has a short half-life.
So can doubt.
I have new thoughts about who you are.
There may very well be another killer.
I want there to be.
Some part of you still suspects me.
I don't know what anyone
is capable of anymore,
least of all myself.
I know there is no evidence against you.
There never was.
And accusing you makes me look insane.
I'm not insane.
Not anymore.
And you may not be guilty.
This ear you were sent is an opportunity.
If someone else
is responsible for your crimes,
perhaps he now wants to be seen.
Why would he want to be seen now?
He cares what happens to you.
The prosecution calls
Freddie Lounds to the stand.
I swear to tell the truth, the whole truth,
nothing but the truth.
Could you please describe
your relationship with Abigail Hobbs?
We were very close.
I was helping her write a book
about surviving her father.
Did you ever discuss
Will Graham with Abigail?
Abigail told me
she believed Will Graham
wanted to kill her and cannibalize her
like her father wanted to do.
She was right.
I should've listened to her.
Do you blame yourself for her death?
I blame Will Graham.
Thank you.
Your witness.
Miss Lounds.
Could you please
remind me how many times
you've been sued for libel?
- Six.
- Sorry?
Six.
And how many times did you settle?
Thank you. Nothing further.
The defense calls Dr. Alana Bloom.
I believe Will's empathy disorder
combined with the effects
of viral encephalitis...
Do we have to do this like this?
I don't want the first time you do this
to be in court.
Dr. Bloom, weren't you and the accused
romantically involved?
- How is this relevant to the case?
- It's relevant to your testimony.
In that court, your feelings, your emotions,
your pro-everything Will Graham
will be on trial.
You get all starey and non-blinky like that,
it'll undermine you and me, but mainly him.
My testimony is based on my professional...
You are smitten with the accused,
Miss Bloom,
and it is adorable,
but not our brand of defense.
And Ms. Vega will smell it on you,
like you stepped in Young Adult
and tracked it into the courtroom.
Were you and Will Graham
involved romantically?
I have no romantic feelings for Will Graham.
I have a professional curiosity.
I like that. "Professional curiosity."
It seems so...
It seems so indifferent.
Unless you look like you're lying
when you say it.
But you didn't.
- You've identified the ear?
- We identified the knife that cut it off.
It's Will Graham's.
The blade matches the cuts
on Abigail Hobbs's ear and on this one.
It was presented in court as evidence,
then it was sent
to the courthouse evidence room
where it was checked out
by the bailiff in Will's trial, Andrew Sykes,
and it never went back.
Pretty good, right?
MILFORD MILL, MARYLAND
Go.
They wanted to give us a warm welcome
and to make sure we found something.
An arresting piece of theater.
Our bailiff was mounted on a stag's head.
A. SYKES
Glasgow smile.
Killer lopped off his ear and set him on fire.
Will Graham's greatest hits.
- Could we have been that wrong?
- About Will Graham? No.
We could not.
He practically takes selfies with his victims.
The evidence we found was immediate
and almost presentational.
May as well have been gift-wrapped.
That's what Will said about Cassie Boyle
when we found her in that field.
"Field Kabuki."
There was no evidence
before Will was apprehended
and there hasn't been any since.
He ate a girl's ear!
It was in his stomach.
God knows what else of her was in there.
We should've taken a stool sample.
Yes! We should have. Well, why didn't we?
I was the one that said we should have.
Knock it off.
What impact could this have on Will's trial?
This murder raises serious doubts
about the case against Will Graham.
Your team provided the evidence.
The overwhelming evidence.
So you understand the significance
of my questioning it.
Agent Crawford,
we all heard your testimony.
Are you sure you're not just trying
to assuage your own guilt?
- Yes, I'm sure.
- I'm not.
Andrew Sykes was mutilated
in the exact same manner
Will Graham allegedly mutilated his victims,
ways that have not been made public.
Will Graham isn't saying
he didn't kill those people.
His lawyer is running
an unconsciousness defense.
In effect, he's admitting the acts,
but just not the responsibility.
Will's maintained his innocence all along,
in spite of memory gaps.
Whatever Mr. Brauer's strategy is,
this will offer a new line of defense.
That's for Mr. Brauer to tell me,
Agent Crawford, not you.
Yes, Your Honor.
Will Graham manifests publicly
as an introverted personality.
He would like us to believe
he places on the spectrum
somewhere near Asperger's and autism.
Yet he also claims an empathy disorder.
You choose your words
very carefully, Dr. Chilton.
You chose the word "claims."
Will Graham has never been diagnosed.
He will not allow anyone to test him.
He has carefully constructed a persona
to hide his real nature from the world.
He wears it so well
even Jack Crawford could not see past it.
But you did?
Mr. Graham and I
had no personal relationship
for him to manipulate.
I have objectively examined him
and the crimes of which he is accused.
These murders were measured
and controlled.
The confused man
Will Graham presents to the world
could not commit those crimes,
because that man is a fiction.
So you discount the encephalitis
he was suffering as a cause?
He managed his illness
with the help of his neurologist,
whom he murdered for his trouble.
Is Will Graham an intelligent psychopath?
There is not yet a name
for whatever Will Graham is.
He kills methodically
and I believe would kill again,
given the opportunity.
Thank you, Dr. Chilton.
Your witness.
Dr. Chilton, Will Graham spent his time
catching murderers for the FBI.
You don't see a contradiction between that
and your description
of a coldblooded killer?
No, I do not.
Will Graham is driven by vanity
and his own whims.
He has a very high opinion
of his intelligence.
Ergo, he caught the other killers
simply to prove
he was smarter than all of them, too.
Saving lives
is just as arousing as ending them.
He likes to play God.
- My admirer?
- Yes.
The forensic report from the crime scene.
What do you see?
I shoot Mr. Sykes once, collapsing lungs,
tearing through his heart's aorta
and pulmonary arteries.
He will die believing we were friends.
It is his last thought.
His death isn't personal.
He is merely the ink
from which flows my poem.
My tribute.
This is my design.
It's not the same killer.
He murdered his victim first
and then mutilated him.
Cassie Boyle's lungs were removed
when she was still breathing.
Georgia Madchen was burned alive.
What I found of Abigail was cut off
while her heart was beating.
Then this is blunt reproduction?
You knew that already.
Would've liked to have been wrong.
Occam's broom.
You intentionally ignored facts
that refute your argument
hoping nobody'd notice.
You noticed.
I wanted to dispel your doubts
once and for all.
My doubts about what?
Me.
I want you to believe in the best of me,
just as I believe in the best of you.
This crime offered us both
reasonable doubt.
It offered us a distraction.
Maybe this acolyte
is giving you your path to freedom.
Even Jack is ready to believe, Will.
It would be a lie.
- I don't want you to be here.
- I don't want me to be here either.
Then you have a choice.
This killer wrote you a poem.
Are you going to let his love go to waste?
I'm confused.
You're going to abandon
your defense strategy,
the entire case you've built, mid-trial.
Exciting, isn't it?
And this seems reasonable to you?
It's not only reasonable,
it's fashionable.
There's a killer on the loose,
demonstrating all the hallmarks
of Will Graham's alleged murders.
Do you think this killer committed
the crimes that you're accused of?
Don't answer that, not in front of me.
It's inconsequential.
But is it true?
You're being awfully high and mighty,
Dr. Bloom.
Very ivory tower, very reductive.
Very far from the point,
which is the exoneration of your friend
Will Graham.
And the point you're trying to make
is reasonable doubt.
That's a win, yes.
The best you can hope for is mistrial.
That's also a win.
You won't be able to plead
unconsciousness again.
Your fast, triumphant diagnosis of
unconsciousness was the best play we had.
Now we have a better play.
Needless to say,
I won't be calling you to the witness stand.
Who's taking the stand in my place?
I swear to tell the truth, the whole truth
and nothing but the truth,
so help me God.
Good morning, Doctor.
Please describe your relationship
with Will Graham.
I was asked by Jack Crawford
to monitor Will's emotional well-being
while he worked on cases.
I was never officially his psychiatrist.
If you weren't his psychiatrist,
what were you?
I was meant to be his stability.
- I failed him in that.
- How did you fail him?
I was unable to determine if Will's condition
was due to mental illness
or stress from his work at the FBI.
My mistake was
never considering his innocence
until the murder of a bailiff
from this courthouse.
And how did you know about that,
Dr. Lecter?
I have been asked to consult
on the case by Jack Crawford.
He wanted a profile of the bailiff's killer.
So you believe the bailiff's murder
was committed by the same person
guilty of Will Graham's alleged crimes, yes?
Profiles aren't evidence, they're opinion.
This is hearsay.
I will allow it.
Thank you, Your Honor.
I believe there are alarming similarities
in the crimes, yes.
Will Graham accused you of the crimes
for which he now stands trial,
and yet here you are, testifying
on his behalf for the defense.
Will rightfully
couldn't accept these actions to be his.
A mind faced with the possibility
of committing such deeds
will find an alternative reality to believe in.
- You don't blame him for that?
- No.
Will Graham is and will always be my friend.
Your witness.
Dr. Lecter,
what was the cause of death
in the bailiff's murder?
A bullet to the heart.
And in Will Graham's victims,
or alleged victims,
what was their cause of death?
Mutilation.
That's very different from a bullet.
No two crimes of any killer
are going to be exactly the same.
The similarities...
Your Honor, the witness's personal beliefs
and biases are driving his conclusions.
There are clearly two different killers
and two different cases.
Your Honor, there are sufficient similarities
to consider this a defense.
I'm ruling this defense
inadmissible, Mr. Brauer.
Thank you, Your Honor.
All previous testimony on the matter
will be stricken from the record.
So, it appears that the judge
was murdered in his chambers
and then he was hauled out here
to be put on display.
Not only is justice blind,
it's mindless and heartless.
How did the killer get so close?
No sign of a struggle.
Mutilation was post-mortem.
He was shot in the chest just like the bailiff.
Can't see the entry wound
because he removed the heart.
But there is an exit wound.
No slug, must have taken it with him.
A trophy.
Doctor.
With this judge's death,
there will be no verdict.
No ending. It'll start again,
like the trial never happened.
But why?
Psychopathic violence
is predominantly goal oriented,
a means to a very particular end.
So the killer wanted a mistrial?
It's an elegant,
if rather unorthodox solution.
He spares Will a guilty verdict
and his life for the moment.
Yes.
The question is, is it the same killer?
Is Will still on trial in your mind?
The use of a gun, death first, mutilation last.
I feel like St. Peter
ready to deny Will for the third time.
I'm not sure this is the same killer, Jack.
Excuse me.
The killer exerted
careful control of the environment.
He left very little evidence behind.
Jeez, Jack.
The trial was supposed to put an end to this.
Instead, the circus
has just added another ring.
And we're the clowns.
Who's "we," Jack?
I got off track.
You have to force yourself
out of this train of thought.
The trial was going wrong
before this murder.
because you wanted to believe Will Graham.
Who is he to you that makes you
want to risk everything for him?
A very cogent reminder of the pitfalls of
having faith in one's fellow man, thank you.
Everyone, at one point or another,
has to leave somebody behind.
You've got to cut him loose.
Otherwise the someone being left behind,
today or tomorrow,
is gonna be you.
Will.
I was hoping the verdict would have
helped focus your mind to get better.
Make what happened to you
less terrifying and confusing.
I can't exactly blame your lawyer.
Faith in any sort of legal justice
has never been any more comforting
than a nightlight.
There are so many miscarriages of justice
when it comes to identifying a psychopath.
You could easily have been misdiagnosed.
I've already been misdiagnosed.
Not by the court.
No.
Not yet.
I walked out of that courtroom
and I could hear my blood,
like a hollow drumming of wings.
And I had the absurd feeling
that whoever this killer is,
he walked out of that courtroom with me.
He's gonna reach out to me.
What does he want?
He wants to know me.
What do you want?
I want to save you.