Previously on Hannibal...
I've given my life to death.
And now death has followed you home.
I don't think I want to do chemotherapy.
- Well, do I have any say in this?
- No.
I'm devoting a lot of time to this mural, Will.
Could use your help.
What was the cause of death
in the bailiff's murder?
A bullet.
And in Will Graham's victims?
Mutilation.
There are clearly two different killers
and two different cases.
Will claimed someone else
committed the crimes he's accused of.
He said that person was you.
Perhaps he was half right.
Wrap the leader around the tippet.
Four, five, six times.
Tuck the end between the lines.
Tighten.
And trim.
It's called a blood knot.
Your father taught you how to hunt.
I'm going to teach you how to fish.
Same thing, isn't it?
One you stalk, the other you lure.
One you catch, the other you shoot.
What are you trying to catch?
The one who caught you.
The one that got away.
Catch a fish once and it gets away,
it's a lot harder to catch again.
Everybody thinks you're lying
about the one that got away.
That's why I have to catch him.
Last thing before casting a line,
name the bait on your hook
after somebody you cherished.
To say goodbye?
The person you name it after cherished you,
as the superstition goes,
you will catch the fish.
And what did you name it?
Abigail.
You were right. Killer was in the mural.
Just where you said he'd be.
His name was James Gray.
We found his vehicle outside the farm.
Enough DNA on the bed of his truck
for us to be confident he's the Muralist.
You found as much evidence on him
as you did on me.
I'm glad you said it.
Who stitched him into the mural?
We don't know.
He may have had a partner. Another killer.
Maybe they had a suicide pact.
No. There was no partner.
This artist worked alone
until he was stitched into his own creation.
- No signs of a struggle.
- No.
So, this second killer, whoever he is,
understood the Muralist well enough
not just to find his canvas,
but well enough to convince him
to be part of it.
- You have an idea who that might be?
- I do.
- Don't say Hannibal Lecter.
- I'm saying Hannibal Lecter.
Didn't you stop ringing that bell?
I'm not asking you to believe
anything you can't prove.
I'm just asking you to prove it.
- Hannibal Lecter has no reason...
- That is exactly right.
He has no discernible reason
other than his own amusement
and curiosity.
That's hard to prove.
There will be a very clever detail
to find on James Gray.
He wouldn't be able to resist it.
Probably something that was overlooked.
Something hidden.
I'll look for clever details.
But I'm not looking for Hannibal.
Just as long as you're looking.
You look out there.
I'll look in here.
I'll give you the same deal
I gave Beverly Katz.
Oh, you know what it is.
You've been recording our conversations.
Or are we pretending you didn't?
What this are you offering
in exchange for my that?
I'm quite the topic of conversation
in psychiatric circles.
I shared my diagnosis of you
on the witness stand.
Your personality disorders,
neurosis, all forgeries.
Even if that were true,
I'd still be a psychopath of some interest.
Quite a manipulative one at that.
Poor, confused, wounded bird
for Agent Crawford
and Doctors Lecter and Bloom.
But for me, well,
I get the psychopath's triumvirate,
charm, focus and ruthlessness.
The charm being debatable, of course.
So either I'm a psychopath
or I am delusional.
Or I'm right about Hannibal Lecter.
Aren't you curious which one it is?
- Will you allow me to test you?
- Test me?
I'll take them all.
You will be the first and last word
in the mind of Will Graham.
God, you could dine out on that for years.
What about Dr. Lecter?
Shouldn't you be
my one and only psychiatrist, Dr. Chilton?
Ideally.
Well then, as to your that for my this.
Do not discuss me or my therapy
with Hannibal Lecter.
Tell him that you've decided
I am no longer any of his business.
I am now under your exclusive care.
Lazarus had it good.
My social circle doesn't include
a friend with power over death.
I suppose I should've embraced Facebook
while I had the chance.
I never should have let Jack
talk me into taking chemo.
He's trying to extend your life.
He's trying to extend the quality of life
that's not worth the effort.
Jack's efforts or yours?
I'm vomiting my stomach lining.
On a good day, I sleep 15 to 18 hours.
On a bad day, I don't sleep.
My best-case scenario
is prolonged pain management.
Jack will help you manage.
He loves you, Bella.
When you are gone,
he will feel your silence like a draft.
My silence is inevitable.
The war is over.
The cancer is an occupying force.
I want to surrender
while I still have my dignity.
You are considering ending your life?
Suicide seems like a valid solution
to my problem.
How does that make you feel?
Alive.
How does it make you feel?
I've always found
the idea of death comforting.
The thought that my life
could end at any moment
frees me to fully appreciate the beauty
and art
and horror of everything
this world has to offer.
A death benefit?
Upon taking his own life,
Socrates offered a rooster
to the god of healing, Asclepius,
to pay his debt.
What debt might that be?
To Socrates, death was not a defeat
but a cure.
Gentlemen.
Local police were supposed to
exterminate the bees
so we could work the crime scene.
Apparently, someone shut that down.
- I did.
- He did.
Jimmy?
Well, I love bees.
Did you know that the drone
is nature's
most talented suicidal swordsman?
When the drone mates with the queen,
his ejaculation is so explosive
it's audible to the human ear.
All right.
How long has he been out here?
From de-comp, I'd estimate two weeks.
Which makes sense
with how much honey is being produced.
Do bees naturally hive
in human carcasses like this?
No. The victim was purposely repurposed
as a human apiary.
Purposely.
Somebody removed the eyes
and part of the brain
to make room for the hive.
Zeller's out in the field,
otherwise I'd ask him to help me with this.
You were a surgeon, right?
I was a surgeon and a doctor, yes.
Have you found any evidence
on the Muralist's friend?
That's what I need your help with.
Might not have been a friend.
Might not have even been an acquaintance.
Whoever killed him, understood him.
So often you open your mouth
and I hear Will Graham's words come out.
I have an arrangement with Will.
He's agreed to consult with me on cases,
if I keep investigating
the murders he's accused of.
I'm happy to hear that.
- Will needs a champion now more than ever.
- He has you, doesn't he?
You think there's a chance
he could be innocent. I know you do.
I believe there is a possibility.
I'm just relieved he's not saying
the killer is you anymore.
At least not to me.
Who does Will believe killed the Muralist?
Doesn't know.
He thinks if James Gray's killer
hid him in the mural,
he may have hid something else.
A signature?
What kind of killer
seeks to depict the unconscious,
instinctual striving of his victim
by sewing him into his own human mural?
It wasn't just for appearances.
You have to get to the truth
beneath the appearances.
Only by going deep beneath the skin
will you understand
the nature of this killer's pathology.
Before I start asking you questions,
I need some confidence
that you will be telling the truth
when you answer.
- What's this?
- A consent form.
You're agreeing to a narcoanalytic interview.
You, me and our old friend, sodium amytal.
A little something to loosen my tongue?
Something lawfully used
in the evaluation of psychotic patients.
What would you use to induce memory loss
in a patient, psychotic or otherwise?
The protein synthesis that moves memories
from short-term to long-term
can be interrupted,
but that requires tools and skills.
And a certain level of unorthodoxy.
Does Hannibal Lecter
possess those tools and skills?
Dr. Lecter has indicated to me
that he is open to the unorthodox
when it comes to treating patients.
I wonder how that subject came up.
Sharing stories of the unorthodox?
Sign here.
I want you to draw a clock for me.
Did Dr. Lecter administer any drug therapies
during your sessions together?
The strobe causes neurons to fire en masse,
like striking many piano keys at once.
like striking many...
The dissonance might foster
a change in your mind.
Is something wrong?
Will?
He was inducing the seizures.
He was encouraging them,
blackouts, the lost time.
It was strategic. It was planned.
You would only see a seizure response
in a brain afflicted
with photosensitive epilepsy.
Or afflicted by something just as damaging.
Like encephalitis.
That would suggest
a radically unorthodox form of therapy.
Yes, it would.
Dr. Lecter.
I am so embarrassed.
You didn't get my message?
I canceled your appointment
with Will Graham.
Is everything all right?
I can explain. Shall we?
Will is at a delicate point in his therapy.
I don't want to confuse him
any more than he already is.
Confuse him?
Isn't it your opinion
he's an intelligent psychopath?
It was, but my opinion is evolving.
After administering
a narcoanalytic interview,
therapeutically vital information
has come to light.
What sort of information?
What Will Graham suffers from
may not be a single condition,
but a continuum of illnesses,
all with different neurological mechanisms.
Some naturally occurring,
others appear to have been induced.
Induced?
Induced by whom?
Did you ever use any kind of
light stimulation in your treatment?
Light stimulation
is a standard tool for neurotherapy.
Evidently, it was
overloading his visual cortex.
Creating seizures, time loss,
gaps in his memory.
Almost strategically, it seems.
You're suggesting it was intentional?
All our conversations about psychic driving,
you were so curious and eager
to hear what I had to say
while saying very little yourself.
I had very little to say.
I have been thinking about the possibility
that you may have been
psychic driving Will Graham all along.
A bold accusation, Frederick.
You are not the only psychiatrist
accused of making a patient kill.
We have to stick together.
Last time I did this, this isn't how I did this.
The young man at the dispensary
calls this Purple Kush.
He says all his cancer patients
love its "deep body stone."
Okay.
May I?
- Do you still get drug tested?
- Oh, come on, give me that thing.
I'm supporting my wife.
I filled out my advance directive today.
I added a DNR.
Oh, you are harshing my buzz right now.
I read an article the other day
about magnetic hyperthermia.
It's looking promising
as a treatment for lung cancer.
Come here.
I know what to expect from lung cancer.
I am my mother's daughter,
and I watched her go through
exactly what I am going through now.
I know.
Hey. I remember sitting by her bed
when she woke up in so much pain
that all she could do was scream my name.
I didn't know how to help her.
So I did nothing.
There was nothing you could do.
And there will be a time
when there is nothing you can do.
And I don't want you to remember me
pleading with you to make the pain go away.
Oh, I'm not going to remember you that way.
First of all, I'm going to remember you
walking along the quays of Italy
in the sunshine
with a trail of signori behind you
shouting, "Bella, Bella, Bella."
And I'm going to remember that your hands,
they smelled of thyme
when you came in from the garden,
and garlic and onions
every time you left the kitchen.
I'm going to remember you
as beautiful as you are right now.
Well, good.
Good.
Duncan Halloran, 52, divorced, bankrupt.
Reported missing six months ago.
And what do we know about his death?
Considering any post-mortem
morphological changes,
this guy's white blood cell count
was through the roof when he died.
You're telling me his killer was a fever
and/or a massive infection?
Lock them both up.
No family. No money. No reason to live.
Alive, dead or dying,
who put him under the tree?
It's possible we're dealing with
a highly motivated religious individual here.
- Explain.
- In Hinduism,
honey is one of the
five elixirs of immortality.
In Christianity, the bee is considered to be
an emblem of Christ,
his mildness and mercy on one side,
- his Old Testament justice on the other.
- Okay.
The orbital bone, his sphenoid,
behind where the eyeballs would usually be,
there's tiny punctures.
Something long and sharp
was pushed in his brain.
Jack, this guy was lobotomized.
- How are you feeling today?
- Not well.
My arthritis is killing me.
I can't take much more of it.
A course of bee venom therapy
would soothe the inflammation.
I can barely afford this treatment.
That's a problem for another day.
Now, you just quiet your mind.
Just live in the present.
- You feel that?
- No.
Good.
- You feel that?
- No.
Good.
Feel that?
I can't feel anything.
Good.
Then you won't feel this.
Mister, you're not supposed to
stare at the sun.
It'll hurt your eyes.
Multiple holes in this guy.
Over a dozen. Both eye sockets.
The lesions have severed
most of the nerve tract to the frontal lobe.
He's covered in bee stings
like he got swarmed.
Must be floating in apitoxin,
probably doesn't feel a thing.
Yeah, him not feeling anything
has got nothing to do with bee stings.
Welcome to the world of the living dead.
There's a pattern.
- Hey.
- Look what the cat's dragged in.
- What are you looking at?
- A pattern.
See, some of the bee stings
triggered an allergic reaction, others didn't.
The inflamed bee stings
were all in line with the body's meridian,
on acupuncture points.
The bee stings are hiding the needle marks.
What did you say?
The bee stings are hiding the needle marks?
The stitches are hiding stitches.
Only by going deep beneath the skin
will you understand
the nature of this killer's pathology.
He took his kidney.
I feel like I'm losing my mind.
Tell me if he's real.
- I don't see anyone.
- No, he's right there.
- There's no one there. We're alone.
- What are you talking about? You're lying.
You came here alone.
Do you remember coming here?
- Please don't lie to me.
- Garrett Jacob Hobbs is dead.
- You killed him. You watched him die.
- What's happening to me?
Will.
Will, you're having an episode.
I want you to hand me the gun.
Will, I want you to hand me your...
Will.
He's had a mild seizure.
That doesn't seem to bother you.
I said it was mild.
Are you the man who claimed
to be the Chesapeake Ripper?
Why do you say "claimed"?
Because you're not.
You know you're not,
and you don't know much more
about who you are beyond that.
Are you the Ripper?
A terrible thing.
To have your identity taken from you.
Whoever killed James Gray
didn't just take his leg.
Sutures hidden beneath the stitching
that wove him into the mural.
One crime made to look like another.
Like the copycat.
And the Chesapeake Ripper.
Now you're saying
Hannibal Lecter is the Chesapeake Ripper?
I'm saying also the Chesapeake Ripper.
- Were the kidneys surgically removed?
- Yes.
- Dr. Lecter was a surgeon.
- I know he was.
I asked him to consult
on James Gray's autopsy.
You what?
If you invited him with an actual agenda,
Hannibal would know it.
He pointed me to the evidence.
He pointed you to an absence of evidence.
He's baiting a hook, Beverly.
He's toying with you.
Go to Jack. Tell him everything.
I can't bring this to Jack
until I can back it up.
Stay away from Hannibal Lecter.
The Chesapeake Ripper
kept surgical trophies.
If Hannibal's the Ripper,
what's he doing with his trophies?
He's eating them.
- Katherine Pimms?
- Yes.
I'm Special Agent Jack Crawford
with the FBI.
This is Agent Zeller and Agent Price.
We'd like to speak with you
about two of your former patients.
Would you like to come in?
When was the last time
you saw Duncan Halloran or Lloyd Roat?
Whenever our last appointments were.
- I can check in my calendar, if you want.
- Sure.
- Have you found them?
- Yes, we have.
Mr. Halloran is deceased.
And Mr. Roat might as well be.
Poor Mr. Halloran.
What were you treating him for?
That man trudged from disease to disease.
He had severe combined immunodeficiency.
Life didn't seem to be going his way.
- Please.
- Thank you.
I find that people don't get their own way
because they often don't know themselves
where that way leads.
Mr. Halloran, he couldn't envision
a dignified end of life.
So it's much nicer to die,
well, for him, to die in a meadow,
a head full of bees.
- Have you tried the honey?
- No.
I couldn't bring myself to either.
It seemed too morbid.
So you left him in the field to die?
I brought him to the field to die.
I didn't kill him.
I quieted his mind
so that he could die in peace.
And Mr. Roat? You quieted his mind, too?
Oh, him.
He suffered crippling arthritis.
After he was quieted,
I saw him walk pain-free
for the very first time in his life.
I can't make pain go away,
but I can make it so that it doesn't matter.
I protected them.
I protected these people from hopelessness.
And that's beautiful.
Please come in.
It's a little unnerving,
not being able to walk across the floor.
Nothing can be so unnerving
for someone strong as being weak.
I was so weak after chemotherapy,
Jack had to physically pick me up.
It was the second time
he carried me across the threshold.
I brought you something.
A gift?
Paying my debt.
Coq Gaulois.
For helping me understand
that death is not a defeat
but a cure.
What have you taken, Bella?
My morphine.
Every bit of it.
I didn't want to die at home.
I didn't want Jack to find me.
I didn't want him to make that call,
be in the room with my body,
waiting.
For it to become some ceremonial object
apart from him,
separate from who I was.
Someone he can only
hold in his mind.
You denied him his goodbye.
I denied him
a painful goodbye
and allowed myself a peaceful one.
Tell Jack
I love him very much.
Yes.
Goodbye,
Dr. Lecter.
Goodbye, Bella.
No.
Hey. Have you seen Jack?
Oh. No, no, no,
there was some emergency with his wife.
Dr. Lecter called from the hospital,
asked him to come down.
- Is Mrs. Crawford okay?
- I don't know. He didn't say.
So Hannibal's at the hospital, too?
- Hi, baby.
- Hey.
I'm here.
What are you doing here?
I want to apologize.
I couldn't honor what you asked of me.
I'm sorry.
Get out.
Gotcha.
Oh, my God.