Previously on Hannibal...
The light from friendship won't reach us
for a million years.
That's how far away from friendship we are.
It would seem Jack Crawford
is less suspicious of me than you are.
Jack Crawford doesn't know
what you're capable of.
Neither do you.
You maintain an air of transparency,
while putting me
in the position to lie for you.
Someone went through a lot of trouble
to make sure that they were well preserved.
They've been coated in some kind of resin.
There are a lot of people missing.
You want to know
how he's choosing them, don't you?
Tell me what you see.
I've lost the plot.
I am the unreliable narrator of my own story.
You have an incomplete self.
There are pieces of you
you can't see.
I'm afraid to see.
I don't know who I am anymore.
And I'm afraid.
Without remembering,
you're seized by something imagined.
I don't know which is worse.
Believing I did it
or believing that you did it,
and did this to me.
Hannibal isn't responsible, Will.
And neither are you. We have to
get to the truth of what happened.
It's the only way you can move forward.
I felt so betrayed by you.
Betrayal was
the only thing that felt real to me.
I trusted you.
And I needed to trust you.
And you can trust me.
- I'm very confused.
- Of course you are.
Will, let us help you.
Let me help you.
I need your help.
What a pleasant surprise.
Please. Sit down.
I won't be staying long.
I'm curious,
what couldn't wait until our next session?
We don't have a next session.
I am no longer your therapist.
May I ask why?
I have reached the limit of my efficacy.
I don't believe I can help you.
Are you giving me a referral?
No.
I am simply ending
our patient-psychiatrist relationship.
You tried to end it before.
I am grateful for your persistence
in engaging me after my attack.
However, in light of everything
that has happened with Will Graham,
I have begun to question your actions.
Particularly your past actions
with regards to me and my attack.
Did you share these questions
with Jack Crawford?
No.
And nor will I.
I would look just as guilty as you.
But perhaps that is what you intended.
What exactly am I guilty of?
Exactly, I cannot say.
I've had to draw a conclusion
based on what I glimpsed through the
stitching of the person suit that you wear.
And the conclusion that I've drawn
is that you are dangerous.
I'm sorry you feel that way.
Please don't come to my home again.
I will see myself out.
I'm resuming Will Graham's therapy.
To what end?
Besides your own.
He asked for my help.
Then maybe you deserve each other.
His name is Roland Umber,
same profile as the other victims.
Lived alone, disappeared from home,
had a large dose of heroin in his system.
This victim wasn't unstrung,
he was ripped from his moorings.
Whatever his imperfection, it was enough
to aggravate the killer
into tearing him down.
He was discarded in a tributary
over 400 miles away from anything
that feeds into the dam
where the first victims were found.
Like dandelion seeds,
casting bodies
in every direction but his own.
Very poetic.
The buffeting in the current
causes so many postmortem injuries,
it's impossible to tell them
from the ones they got when they were alive.
Excuse me.
Doctor, join me over here.
There may be trace evidence
preserved in the craquelure.
What?
Craquelure. It's French.
For the cracks that appear
on an oil painting as it dries
and it becomes rigid with age.
Cracks are not always weaknesses.
A life lived accrues in the cracks.
Could be something in there,
fiber, debris.
Might help track where
the bodies were before they got dumped.
What do the victims have in common?
What if it isn't what they have in common?
What if it's what makes them different?
Each of these people
has a slightly different flesh tone.
It could be like a color palette.
The color of our skin is so often politicized.
It would almost be refreshing
to see someone revel
in the aesthetic for aesthetics' sake.
If it weren't so horrific.
We're supposed to see color, Jack.
That may be all
this killer has ever seen in his fellow man,
which is why it is so easy
for him to do what he does to his victims.
Which is why there'll be
a lot more bodies on his color palette.
A fascinating insight, Ms. Katz,
as if Will Graham himself
were here in the room.
Yes, it is.
How's Will Graham?
Shut your mouth.
Is there a reason you didn't come to me
before you decided to go talk to him?
- I figured you'd say no.
- You figured correctly.
But I knew you'd want to say yes.
You knew that?
You put me in an awkward position, Jack.
I had to go because I knew you wouldn't.
If you had gone like you wanted,
I wouldn't have had to.
Why didn't you?
Because Will Graham is either delusional
or he's a psychopath,
neither of which I can trust.
Fine, so don't trust him, just listen to him.
I'm listening. This is what I'm hearing.
If he's delusional,
it's because I made him that way.
If he's a psychopath,
it's because everything in my gut is wrong.
You think he's innocent.
I don't know what I think.
I think he still wants to save lives.
That's what I think.
I have bent the rules here
in the name of saving lives.
Now, there is an internal investigation.
I'm under the microscope.
The Office of the Inspector General
has ordered a psych eval
to determine
my competency to sit in this chair.
Well, what do you want me to do?
If you don't want me to go back, I won't.
We didn't have this conversation.
And since we didn't have this conversation,
I want you to go
and do whatever it is you believe
it is your job to do.
Do you know what your job is?
Yes, I do.
Then do it.
I've been advised
to stay on this side of the line.
Select patients
have taken to urinating on the therapists.
I would argue drawing a line
might encourage a pissing contest.
I'm not interested
in a pissing contest with you, Dr. Lecter.
Please, pull up your chair.
You said the light from friendship
won't reach us for a million years,
that's how far away we are.
I hope our friendship feels closer today.
Friends have a symmetrical relationship.
Psychiatrist and patient, that's unbalanced.
There is a power differential
between psychiatrist and patient,
one that I'm well aware of,
particularly with my own therapist.
But we're just having conversations.
- You threatened me with a reckoning.
- I did.
I can't claim unconsciousness on that one.
You were searching for something
in your head to incriminate me.
I can only assume you didn't find it.
There's not much in there I recognize.
Whatever you remember,
if you do remember,
will be a distortion of reality,
not the truth of events.
I'm realizing that.
Beverly Katz has come to see you?
Yes.
Wouldn't want Alana Bloom to worry
about you dwelling on anything morbid
in what's to be a time of recovery.
It's the only thing that feels normal.
The violence?
The structure of understanding the violence.
You're missing pieces of yourself.
Careful what you replace them with.
What did you see in the pictures?
This killer, he's not stringing his victims up,
he's stitching them together.
Each body is a brushstroke.
He's making a human mural.
Why does he do it?
He's missing pieces, too.
Dr. Lecter has advised me
against dwelling on anything morbid.
I know you want to stop
these murders as much as I do.
Reasons for stopping multiple murders
do readily occur to me,
but I'm going to need something in return.
There are things you don't have?
I can talk to the chief of staff.
- Chilton?
- He's being very cooperative.
Of course he is.
He loves when I have visitors.
He's recording every word.
He's gossipy that way.
What do you want, Will?
I'm wondering
if you can get me the thing I really want.
Try me.
I want you to ignore
all the evidence against me.
You're right. I can't get that.
How many colors
will this killer add to his box of crayons?
Say I ignore the evidence against you.
What then?
Strike it from your mental record.
Start over.
If I'm guilty, you'll find more evidence.
If I'm not guilty, you'll maybe find that, too.
All right.
I'll keep looking.
Good.
Give me the file, I'll tell you what I think.
Do you mind if I do this privately?
Yes.
The skin isn't as discolored
as the other victims'.
Looks fairly well preserved,
all things considered.
Why would I throw you away?
Did Roland Umber
have priors with substance abuse?
He was in an outpatient treatment program
for drug addiction.
Heroin?
Among others.
He had a high tolerance for opiates.
The overdose didn't kill him.
He survived what was done to him.
He tore himself free.
He ran.
- How did he end up in the water?
- Killer didn't put him there.
He'd have put him back
in the mural if he caught him.
Other bodies were dumped,
Roland Umber got away.
Got away from where?
This killer, he needs someplace private
to do what he does.
A warehouse, a farm, someplace abandoned,
upstream from where the body was found.
It'll be close to the water.
Thank you.
I'm curious.
What did Hannibal Lecter have to say
about Mr. Umber?
He thinks the killer tore him down,
dumped his body like the others.
That may be what he said,
it's not necessarily what he thinks.
Hello.
I love your work.
However did you find this place?
You and Will Graham are a good team.
You gave us the "what" we were looking for,
he gave us the "where."
Corn dust on the craquelure.
Yes, Will and I do make a good team.
Will didn't think
Roland Umber was discarded, he escaped.
We just went upstream from where
the body was found until we hit corn.
Hey, Beverly.
Dr. Lecter.
Follow me, please.
You might want to prepare yourself.
You've never seen anything like this.
I'm sure I haven't.
How could a human being go so bad?
When it comes to nature versus nurture,
I choose neither.
We are built from a DNA blueprint
and born into a world of
scenario and circumstance we don't control.
Praise the mutilated world, huh?
What did it look like from above?
Fascinating.
Ritual human sacrifice.
I'm not sure if it's an offering,
but it's certainly a gesture.
To whom?
The eye looks beyond this world
into the next,
and sees the reflection of man himself.
Is the killer looking at God?
Maybe it's some sick existential crisis.
If it were an existential crisis,
I would argue there wouldn't be
any reflection in the eye at all.
A person who could do this kind of thing,
would they be likely
to continue doing it?
This could be his beginning.
And/or his end.
He may never kill again.
You said he doesn't see people,
that he sees material.
Those in the world around him
are a means to an end.
He uses them to do what he's driven to do.
Will Graham was a means to an end.
I used him to do what I was driven to do,
to save lives at the expense of his.
I thought whatever I could put him through,
he would be strong enough
to fight his way back to himself,
and I was wrong.
Maybe he's still fighting.
Maybe he's not.
Point is, you don't know.
It's okay not to know.
You can't know everything.
You can't be certain of it all.
Knowing that Will descended
into such savage behavior
has changed the way that I see him,
the way that I see other people.
The world feels much darker.
It's not just
the guilt of what I did to Will Graham,
it's the guilt of watching all these other
lives fall apart based on what I did.
- What did you do?
- I pushed him.
When I was warned to back off,
I kept pushing him.
- You miscalculated.
- I failed.
I failed.
We all fail, Jack.
I look at my friend and I see a killer.
I'm failing to reconcile those two things.
Forty-seven bodies.
We've identified 19 of them,
- but not this one.
- No record of fingerprints.
He was never arrested or in any kind of a job
that required any type of security
clearance or background check.
Hopefully he's been to a dentist.
Why am I looking at this man?
Stitch patterns on John Doe 21
match Roland Umber.
John Doe 21
is Roland Umber's replacement in the mural.
What happened to his leg?
Maybe the killer had to cut off his leg
just so he'd fit.
He changed colors mid-brushstroke.
What did Dr. Lecter say?
"The eye looks beyond this world
into the next,
"and sees a reflection of man himself."
There was never supposed
to be a reflection.
The killer's
having an existential crisis after all.
The question is,
how did he find his faith?
Hello, Doctor.
What can I help you with?
Closure.
I think perhaps this should,
or may have to be, our last conversation.
At least on the subject of Hannibal Lecter.
Are you pleading the Fifth?
No.
I simply can't offer you any more insight
than I already have.
Not accounting for future insight?
I feel it would be irresponsible
if I continue to see Dr. Lecter.
Irresponsible?
For who?
For me.
I can only help Hannibal
if I'm feeling secure, emotionally.
I'm not feeling secure right now,
so I am recusing myself from the situation.
I hope you understand.
I'm not sure I do.
Hannibal and I were both traumatized
by dangerous patients.
Hannibal had his Will Graham,
and I had mine.
It has been a necessary,
albeit unpleasant, reminder
that I have unresolved issues.
Maybe Hannibal
can help you resolve these issues.
He is very good.
I am doing my best to avoid working
through my issues with Hannibal Lecter.
- Goodbye, Agent Crawford.
- Goodbye, Doctor.
Obviously, I cannot control
whether or not the FBI contacts me.
I can only tell you what I told Hannibal,
I prefer that you don't.
Now you're just taking advantage.
You're going to burn me out before my trial,
and then where will I be?
What would Jack say?
Jack's excellent administrative instincts
are not often tempered by mercy.
Clearly.
I'm devoting a lot of time to this mural, Will.
It's hard for me to focus on anything else
I've been tasked to do.
Could use your help.
In the 19th century, it was wrongly believed
that the last image seen
by the eyes of a dying person
would be fixed on the retina.
What would be the last image
fixed on this dying eye?
I made you pliable.
Molded you.
Set and sealed you where you lay.
This is my design.
A dead eye of vision
and consciousness.
I am fixed and unseeing.
Unless someone else sees me.
One of these things
is not like the others.
One of these things just doesn't belong.
Who are you?
Why are you so different
from everyone else?
I didn't put you here.
You are not my design.
Killing must feel good to God, too.
He does it all the time,
and are we not created in His image?
The killer is in the mural.
What do you mean? Literally?
I mean the man you're looking for
is sewn into his own mural, this man.
What happened to his leg?
Whoever sewed him in took a piece of him.
As a trophy.
He must have had a friend.
You're not alone, you know?
In The Resurrection,
Piero della Francesca
placed himself in the fresco.
Nothing flattering,
he depicted himself
as a simple guard asleep at his post.
Your placement
should be much more meaningful.
It's not finished.
I'm finishing it for you.
We'll finish it together.
When your great eye looked to the heavens,
what did it see?
Nothing.
Not anymore.
There is no God.
Certainly not with that attitude.
God gave you purpose,
not only to create art, but to become it.
Why are you helping me?
Your eye will now see God reflected back.
It will see you.
If God is looking down at you,
don't you want to be looking back at Him?
Will Graham.
Kade Prurnell, Office of
the Inspector General, FBI Oversight.
Am I still an FBI employee?
Or is that pending the outcome of my trial?
The point of the trial
isn't so much whether or not you did it,
it's whether or not you knew what
you were doing when you did it.
Sounds like I'm unemployed.
Dr. Bloom is hard at work
on your unconsciousness defense.
Yes, yes, the FBI made me do it.
The FBI made you a murderer.
Yes, that is Dr. Bloom's position.
As you can imagine, she's not popular.
What's your position?
Our point of view is that
you were already a murderer.
The prosecution will paint a picture of you
as an intelligent psychopath.
You conspired with your neurologist
to cultivate an illness
that would ultimately be your alibi.
And then I killed my neurologist
to broom the footprints behind me?
That's what everyone
in the courtroom will hear
when you take the stand,
regardless of what you say.
Well, what's to be done about that?
Let's discuss it.
If you plead guilty, you'll spare us all a trial.
And I personally will see to it
that you're comfortable here.
I'm pleading innocent.
You very publicly lost your mind,
some would argue theatrically.
The prosecution certainly will.
All part of the performance,
it's just not my performance
you're watching.
You'll be found guilty
and given the federal death penalty.
I'm trying to save your life.
I guess I'll have to save my own life.
I don't know you.
My name is Bedelia Du Maurier.
You're Hannibal Lecter's therapist.
What's that like?
I've heard so much about you,
I feel I almost know you.
You don't?
No, I don't.
But I understand you better than I thought.
I wanted to meet you before I withdraw.
What are you withdrawing from?
Social ties.
Well, you're a psychiatrist. Isn't our sense
of self a consequence of social ties?
They certainly are in your case.
It may be small comfort,
but I am convinced Hannibal has done
what he honestly believes is best for you.
No, that isn't small comfort,
that would be no comfort.
The traumatized are unpredictable
because we know we can survive.
You can survive this happening to you.
Happening to me.
Stay behind the white line, ma'am!
Ma'am!
Step away from the bars.
I believe you.
Come on, ma'am, let's go.
Step away.
And the conclusion that I've drawn
is that you are dangerous.