Previously on Hannibal...
Where were you last night?
I was with Hannibal all night, Jack.
- My name is Miriam Lass. I'm with the FBI.
- Come in.
The Chesapeake Ripper
recorded Miriam Lass two years ago.
Jack, I was so wrong.
You said yourself, there's no body.
Miriam Lass is dead!
Found something else in the lures.
Madrona bark.
Will didn't kill any of these people.
There's a small stand in Virginia.
Jack, it's Miriam.
I don't know where I am.
I can't see anything.
I was so wrong. I was so wrong.
Please, Jack. I don't want to die like this.
Jack, it's Miriam.
I don't know where I am.
I can't see anything.
I was so wrong. I was so wrong.
Thank you.
I knew you'd never stop looking.
Can I see him?
We haven't caught the Ripper.
He's still...
We need your help, Miriam.
You know who he is.
I don't know who he is.
You found him.
I don't remember finding him.
He got inside my head.
I remember a dream about drowning.
And then being awake.
And not awake.
Being myself, and not myself.
I'd wake up to the smell of fresh flowers
and the sting of a needle.
I wasn't afraid.
Fear and pain were so far away.
I was reckless with your life.
I was reckless with my life.
I saw what I needed in you, and I used you.
I let you break the rules on my behalf
while I hid behind deniability.
Agent Crawford, please do not
apologize to me for my mistakes.
He treated me very well,
until the end, until he put me in the ground.
Even when he took my arm.
He told me what he was going to do.
I went to sleep, woke up, it was gone.
He said he wanted to give it to you.
Can you identify him?
I could hear his voice.
I couldn't see his face.
All I could see
was light.
Why didn't he kill you, Miriam?
Why were you spared?
I wasn't spared.
He was saving me for last.
They found a witness.
A survivor.
The only victim of the Chesapeake Ripper,
who lived to tell.
Is this witness watching me now?
Yes.
It seems I am the usual suspect.
I keep having angry,
imaginary conversations
with Jack Crawford about that.
I wish I could tell you
why this is happening.
This witness must not be able
to identify the Ripper by sight.
Jack wants them to hear my voice,
otherwise, I'd be in here alone.
Right?
Still,
I appreciate your company.
It's not him.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
He's not the Ripper.
This is very sudden.
The federal prosecutor dropped all charges.
Since you were not convicted
of killing anyone,
the basis for your sentencing
to this institution is null and void.
The Chesapeake Ripper has set you free.
Mazel tov.
I would love nothing more
than to see you trade places with Dr. Lecter.
I have no intention
of ending up on his menu.
Well, then confess, Frederick.
Might be the only thing saves your life.
Confess to what?
Confess to bonding with Hannibal Lecter
over your shared practice
of unorthodox therapies.
Dr. Lecter with me, you with Abel Gideon.
Gideon is playing his own game,
was wheeled out of that hospital
by the Chesapeake Ripper.
Curious what bargain they struck.
No, there's no bargaining with smoke.
No, Gideon's dead.
You're next.
Unless I unburden myself?
Confession is good for the soul.
Shine a light on your relationship
with Hannibal Lecter.
He works in the shadows.
Deny them to him.
Tell Jack Crawford everything.
Are you suggesting I kill my career
before Hannibal can kill me?
I'm suggesting you convince
Jack Crawford however you can.
Like your life depends on it.
Why did Hannibal not just kill you?
Because he wants to be my friend.
You need a ride?
I was gonna call a cab.
We found Miriam Lass.
Alive.
You catch the Ripper?
How is she? Miriam.
Traumatized.
Miriam thanked me after we found her.
Thanked me for not giving up on her.
But I had.
I had given up on her.
And I gave up on you, too.
I thought she was dead.
I thought you were crazy.
And I gave up on trying
to find the both of you.
You didn't have to find me, Jack.
You just had to listen to me.
I put Miriam in a room with Hannibal Lecter.
She stated definitively he is not
the Chesapeake Ripper.
That definitive enough for you?
No.
It wasn't.
Where'd you find Miriam, Jack?
The property was condemned years ago.
Apparently, the Ripper
has been using it since that time.
Will.
In here.
It's Beverly Katz's blood.
He drained her before he froze her
before he cut into her.
Chesapeake Ripper's latest victim,
he was found in the other cistern.
The water in his lungs is what led us here.
We found Miriam down there.
She believed the Ripper
brought her here to kill her.
He was saving her to be his last victim.
He knows we're close to catching him.
He's been caught before.
Catch a fish once and it gets away.
It's a lot harder to catch a second time.
I sowed the seeds
and watched them grow.
I cultivated.
A long chain of events leading to this.
All of this
has been my design.
It's theater.
Every time the Ripper kills someone,
it's theater.
The Ripper didn't bring Miriam here
to kill her.
He brought her here for you to find.
But the Ripper's not self-destructive.
He doesn't want to get caught.
He wants you to catch someone.
Like he wanted you to catch me.
Somewhere, in all of this evidence,
you will find something that will
lead you away from Hannibal Lecter.
Miriam Lass has already done that.
Two years.
It's a long time
to have Hannibal in your head.
You can't trust her, Jack.
You can't trust any of this
to be what it seems.
Hey.
Welcome home.
Thank you.
Thank you for looking after them.
They seem happy.
Happy to see you.
Who's this?
Applesauce. She's mine.
She likes applesauce.
I rescued her.
Picking up some of my bad habits?
Picking up your good habits.
You challenged my whole framework
of assumptions about the way you are.
- The way I think you are.
- Well, the way you think I am
isn't always a reliable guide to who I am.
I was wrong about you.
Because you didn't believe me or in me?
Because you let me question my sanity,
my sense of reality?
Because you tried to kill Hannibal.
You're wrong about him, Will.
No, you're wrong about him, Alana.
You see the best in him.
I don't.
Hey?
What was done to you
doesn't excuse what you did.
Are you going to try to hurt Hannibal again?
Is he safe?
From me or for you?
He's dangerous, Alana.
I suggest you stay as far away
from Hannibal Lecter as you can.
Come on.
What can I do for you, Dr. Chilton?
It is what I can do for you.
I would like to offer my services
on the Ripper case, pro bono, of course.
I see.
You wish to be helpful expediting
Hannibal Lecter's arrest?
I have consulted with the FBI
on previous Ripper murders.
You have an agenda with this case, Doctor.
Yes, I have an agenda, living.
I should be assigned an FBI escort.
Everyone who believed Will Graham
about Hannibal Lecter is dead.
- Except you.
- Except me.
I would like to remain not dead
for the foreseeable future.
Do you have something substantial
to contribute or just an opinion?
- I have a witness.
- A witness?
If Will is not a suspect, then he is a witness.
To his own manipulation?
We have had remarkable success
recovering memory.
He remembers so much
of what was done to him.
Why hasn't Will told me this himself?
Because you told him
his memories were meaningless.
I imagine Hannibal Lecter used
the same coercive techniques
on Miriam Lass that he used on Will Graham.
He buried memories in both of them.
Jack, I dug those memories out of Will.
I can dig them out of Miriam.
Miriam Lass is not your patient, Doctor.
Over your shoulder...
Are you an FBI agent?
No.
I used to teach at the Academy.
And two days ago,
I was an inmate at the Baltimore State
Hospital for the Criminally Insane.
Courtesy of the Chesapeake Ripper.
Well, the Guru told me the only person
who had any practical understanding
of the Ripper was you,
but he didn't mention that you were a victim.
Guru?
Jack Crawford.
He has a peculiar cleverness.
The Guru tells me
that you don't remember much
about what the Ripper did to you.
I couldn't remember either.
Couldn't?
I remember now.
Not all of it. Pieces.
I was under his influence.
He used some kind of light
to induce a seizure response in my brain.
It created blackouts and lost time.
I remember the light.
He would stand in front of it
at a distance from me,
silhouetted, very still.
He would listen to chamber music.
I still hear that.
You're waking now.
And his voice, low and even,
would pull me to him.
Waking in a pleasant room, safe.
Like a current.
You're waking now. Waking, calm.
Waking in a pleasant room, safe.
You and I are part of his design.
He wanted you to be free.
He wanted me to be free too.
Neither of us are really free.
He's not done.
The same unfortunate aftershave.
Too long in the bottle.
Our last kitchen conversation
was interrupted by Jack Crawford.
I'd like to pick up where we left off.
If memory serves, you were asking me
if it would feel good to kill you.
You've given that some thought.
You wanted me
to embrace my nature, Doctor.
I'm just following the urges
I kept down for so long,
cultivating them as the inspirations they are.
You never answered my question.
How would killing me make you feel?
Righteous.
Aren't you curious, Will?
Why you?
Why Miriam Lass?
What does the Chesapeake Ripper want
with you?
No, you tell me.
How did Miriam Lass find you?
You made sure
no one could find you that way again.
If I'm not the Ripper,
you murder an innocent man.
You better than anyone know what it means
to be wrongly accused.
You were innocent, and no one saw it.
No, I'm not innocent. You saw to that.
If I am the Ripper, and you kill me,
who will answer your questions?
Don't you want to know how this ends?
My name is Miriam Lass. I'm with the FBI.
I would show you my credentials,
but I'm actually just a trainee.
Never just a trainee, an agent in training.
Please, come in.
I would have been happy
to come to your office, Jack.
I understand, but I wanted to do this here.
I'm sure you have your reasons.
The most-important aspect
of a successful recovery is
recognizing that life will never be the same.
Then I must be well on my way
to a successful recovery.
It's beautiful.
- Yours?
- Yes.
I enjoy portraiture.
A subject's mental process betrayed
only by the expression on their face.
Miriam, the Chesapeake Ripper
sent me a message from you.
It was recorded shortly after you were taken.
It's me? My voice?
Yes.
I want to hear it.
Very well.
Jack, it's Miriam. I don't know where I am.
I can't see anything.
I was so wrong. I was so wrong.
Please, Jack, I don't wanna die like this.
I don't remember.
Would you like to try?
You're waking now.
Waking, calm.
Waking in a pleasant room.
Safe.
Open your eyes.
Jack. Jack, it's Miriam.
Tell me where you are.
I don't know where I am.
What do you see?
I can't see anything.
I was so wrong.
Jack, please, I don't wanna die like this.
Miriam,
what was the last thing you remember
before making the call?
The Wound Man.
We found a fingerprint on a flower petal.
A partial, smudged.
Not enough points for a courtroom,
but it triggered a match in the system.
Hannibal Lecter.
After all these murders,
the Ripper's gonna leave a print now?
Will said whatever evidence we found,
it would lead us away from the Ripper.
We also found sodium amytal
and scopolamine in Miriam's blood.
Dr. Chilton used scopolamine
and sodium amytal
on both Gideon and Will
during their therapy.
One claimed to be the Chesapeake Ripper,
and the other accused Hannibal.
"You've got the right box,
but you're looking in the wrong corner."
Gideon pointed me at Chilton,
told me that he was the Ripper.
Wait. I'm confused. So, who are we saying
is the Chesapeake Ripper?
Dr. Lecter or Dr. Chilton?
Bring them both in.
Hello, Frederick.
Oh, my God.
That will be the FBI.
When you wake up,
your only choice will be to run.
One moment, please.
May I use your shower, please?
Gideon hasn't been dead for long,
no more than a couple of hours.
Chilton's been carving the steaks
off of him for days.
Chilton's shelves are filled
with a lot of old medical books.
The Wound Man.
This illustration shows up
in a lot of early texts.
It's the Ripper's sixth victim.
Chilton was consulting on the Ripper case
when Miriam disappeared.
She must've talked to him,
made the connection.
Beverly made a connection too.
Chilton's been a part of the Ripper case
since before Will Graham,
Hannibal Lecter, Miriam Lass.
He had access to case files.
He would know everything
the Ripper would need to know.
I have the same profile as Hannibal Lecter.
Same medical
and psychological background.
We are both doctors of note in our field.
Of course it would be me!
Hannibal was never going to kill me.
I'm his patsy.
I have to leave the country.
I am leaving the country.
No, if you run, you look guilty.
You did not run,
and you looked plenty guilty.
Abel Gideon was half-eaten
in my guest room.
I have corpses on my property.
You just threw up an ear.
There's an APB on you right now.
They've canceled credit cards.
They're tracing your phone.
I have cash, and I tossed my phone.
Jack Crawford thinks I killed
two agents, three agents.
You know what tends to happen
to people who do that? Shoot on sight.
I'm going to prove Hannibal Lecter
is the Chesapeake Ripper.
I know you will. And when you do,
I will read about it from a secure location,
and I will reintroduce myself
to society at that time.
Will, what have you done?
- I called Jack Crawford.
- No.
No. No.
No.
No! No! No, stay there!
You're not a killer, Frederick.
- Why'd you come alone, Jack?
- Where is he?
- Why'd you come alone?
Hey, I told you,
everything is not what it seems.
The Chesapeake Ripper
is still playing with us, all of us.
The Chesapeake Ripper is not playing
all of us, Will. He's playing you.
Jack, wait. I'll bring him out.
He's got a gun.
Good.
Chilton!
Chilton, stop where you are!
Please.
One navy blue sweater,
one pair of men's dress pants
in charcoal gray,
one black and red pea coat,
one black leather billfold containing
$443, various credit cards,
one set of car keys.
I need to speak to Will Graham.
I don't care what you need.
One Montblanc fountain pen
in silver and black.
Does it have to be you?
It seems like one final indignity.
Not like you to hide an achievement.
The achievement is not mine.
Whose is it? Hannibal Lecter's?
Those are just words
coming out of your mouth.
No weight to them.
No consideration they may be true.
They're not true.
You were using coercive therapies,
influencing Abel Gideon and Will Graham
to point the Ripper investigations
in false directions.
You cannot see it,
and you will not see it until it is too late.
Don't say I did not warn you, Dr. Bloom.
In fact, I believe,
these should be my last words
on the subject of the Ripper
until my lawyer arrives.
You're waking now.
Waking, calm.
Waking in a quiet room.
You're waking now.
Waking in a quiet room, safe.
It's him. It's him.
It's him. It...
It's all right.
Hello, Will.
May I come in?
Do you intend to point a gun at me?
Not tonight.
Are you expecting someone?
Only you.
Kept my standing appointment open?
And you're right on time.
I have to deal with you
and my feelings about you.
I think it's best if I do that directly.
First you have to grieve for what is lost
and what has changed.
I've changed. You changed me.
The friendship that we had is over.
The Chesapeake Ripper is over.
It had to be Miriam, didn't it?
She was compelled to take his life
so she could take her own back.
How will you take your life back?
I'd like to resume my therapy.
Where shall we begin?