Where's Nancy?
The food's getting cold.
- She's got a date.
- Oh.
A date?
With a boy?
Yes, dear, a date. Potatoes?
Don't try to distract
me with potatoes.
But you love potatoes.
I don't want
to talk about potatoes.
Okay. Carrots?
Carole, our daughter is 15.
- Danny...
- No dating till she's married.
Then her husband can
decide when she dates.
I wonder if he's going to
let her go to the dance.
Carole bought her a dress
and she cut the tags.
He's going to have to let
her go to the dance.
Boy, that Nancy is a handful.
Thank God we didn't have a girl.
Ignore Grandma, she's drunk.
Well, I think it's
plenty of space for a gathering.
I guess if I move the
dining room table out of here,
I could set up a punch bowl
station and...
There's that smell again.
Is it the drapes?
No, I don't think...
Anyhow, I'd really
like to be able
to give them dance lessons.
Every girl should know
how to do a proper...
Wait. Is it the carpet?
- I already sniffed down there.
- Where is it coming from?
- Follow me.
- What are you doing?
I'm gonna race him
down the hall.
I just want to see
if he can outrun me.
Well, of course
he can outrun you.
He's going to give himself
a heart attack.
Thank God we didn't have a girl.
They're the worst.
Ignore Grandma, honey.
And Grandpa. Ignore him, too.
It's the piano.
The piano smells like onions?
Just the black keys.
- Shirley?
- Yes?
The black keys on the piano
smell like onions.
- And?
- Why?
It's a used piano.
Danny, honestly,
is this really necessary?
You know he's going to be
on The Gordon Ford Show
tomorrow night.
- Danny Stevens? Really?
- Uh-huh.
Oh, my God. I love him.
There's nothing he can't do.
He sings, he dances.
He visits sick children.
Constantly.
- Can't stay away from them.
- The sicker the better.
You guys want to come to the
show tomorrow? Watch him live?
- Are you serious?
- We would love that.
How would we get tickets?
Well, lucky for you,
you've got someone
on the inside.
How fabulous. Who?
Me. I'm on the inside.
- I don't understand.
- I work on the show.
So, you know someone
who can get us tickets?
Yes. Me.
I can get you tickets.
Because I work on the show.
So I'm there.
I don't know
what she's saying.
If I air out that piano,
replace all the artwork,
lose the doilies
and the plastic,
add some flowers,
some pillows, paint, maybe...
- Shirley, I'll think about it.
- Think about what?
Oh, she wants a place
to throw a party
for those sad, lonely women
who pay her for a husband.
May I just say, thank God
we didn't have a girl.
We sure dodged
a bullet there, boy.
- Ignore Grandma, sweetie.
- Grandpa, too.
- Nancy.
- I know, Daddy.
Let's just make that
a blanket rule, shall we?
Thank you again.
You're welcome.
Miriam, have whoever's getting
us the tickets give us a call.
I'm getting you the tickets.
- So, they'll call?
- Yes, they'll call.
We're so excit...
So, what's the verdict?
Well, the bathrooms work,
and there's a roof.
You can always just have it
at our apartment.
Too small.
I hired a dance instructor.
- Where will he instruct?
- Then you'll have to rent a hall.
- With what money, Miriam?
- So, skip the dance instructor?
You know absolutely
nothing about love.
Cue the fan.
Close your eyes.
Picture "love."
Do you see a handsome,
academic husband?
Children? A modern apartment
with skyline views?
Or do you see
a successful orthodontist,
children, and a two-story
colonial somewhere suburban?
Perhaps it's a strapping,
strong, high-end contractor,
children,
in a renovated farmhouse
that makes your heart
skip a beat.
Whatever "love"
looks like to you,
I can help you find it.
Here at Rose Weissman's
"One Plus One Equals Love"
romance emporium...
...we cater to your every
romantic...
Every romantic...
Every... I don't know
what you're doing.
Cut.
I'm sorry,
but he's flapping his arms
like he's flying south
for the winter.
What?
So, Rose, you look wonderful.
- Thank you.
- Now, Kurt here
was just trying
to tell you to keep moving.
Remember? You got to keep moving
until you hit
this mark, here. You see?
Yes, but it just
feels so awkward,
and there are so many stairs.
Well, you look wonderful.
Can't I just do it
from up there?
That's not where
your end light is.
Well, maybe if
I didn't have to...
You do. But you
really look wonderful.
No.
Miriam?
Coming.
Hi. What's up? It's going great.
- It is?
- Yes.
There's a considerable amount
of groaning from the crew.
- That seems bad.
- Nope.
196 takes is
completely the norm.
This is ridiculous.
I need to lie down.
Mama, you wanted this,
remember? You wanted to take
the business regionally.
You wanted
to shoot a commercial.
Hey, everyone. We're doing
great here. Almost ready.
I am not an on-camera person.
Sure you are. Right, Eddie?
She looks wonderful.
He's very good.
I don't understand
why we can't get
someone else to play me.
- Like who?
- Doris Day.
Doris Day doesn't
scream "Rose Weissman."
You do it.
Your face still has
traces of my face in it,
so it's almost the same face.
That's a weird way of
saying "you've had work done."
I'm ruining it.
This whole thing
that you've put together,
I'm ruining it and making
a complete fool of myself
- in the process.
- I'll tell you what.
Forget about the walking.
You stand here, in your light.
I'll stand there,
next to the camera,
and you can just talk to me.
Stand there and tell me
all about love
and how to get a husband.
Okay, let's roll.
Quiet on set, please.
Mama...
...you really do look wonderful.
"One Plus One
Equals Love," take 197. Mark.
Close your eyes
and picture love...
Miriam?
What?
The stove won't light again.
Did you turn it on?
Of course I turned it on.
Sometimes
you don't turn it on.
One time, I didn't
turn it on. One time.
- Stand still.
- What?
Not you.
Miriam, why
am I standing still?
- Not you. Esther.
- Ah...
Hold still.
Papa, get
Ethan ready to go.
I'm busy with his piano lesson.
He needs
to get ready for school.
- I can't make tea.
- Stop it, Esther.
- Ow. Mama, stop.
- This is a good time
to learn how to tune out
everything in your life
but the music.
- Ow!
- Stand still.
I need some tea!
Have you ever seen
Vladimir Horowitz
hold a toy in one hand
while playing Rachmaninoff
with the other?
I'll answer for you.
You have not.
- Papa?
- Abe!
I don't like this.
Well, right now,
no one is enjoying it.
I need help with the stove.
I need help with her hair.
I'm busy with the boy.
Okay, stop.
I will play
the piece for you again.
Really listen, huh?
This is what
you are aspiring to.
See how nice it sounds
without the car?
Oh, thank God, Zelda.
This morning's been a nightmare.
- The pilot's out.
- What?
Miriam, the pilot's out.
Abe, the pilot's out.
It's fine. Easy to fix.
Miriam, it's easy to fix.
Abe, Zelda's here.
She says it's easy to fix.
- What?
- Zelda's gonna fix the stove.
Well, what's wrong
with the stove?
The pilot light is out,
Mr. Weissman.
Zelda?
What are you doing here?
She's fixing the stove.
Oh. Okay.
So, like I showed you last time,
all you have to do
is light a match, see?
Then you hold it here,
turn the knob,
and then it's lit.
My goodness. So complicated.
Not complicated at all.
I showed you before
many, many times.
- Did you look in the book?
- The book?
The book I made you, remember?
All labeled,
and there's pictures.
See, right here under
"No flame in stove for tea"
is "How to fix no flame
in stove for tea."
Very easy. A picture
of teacup and everything.
Yes, well, luckily
it's working now.
Maybe you could try
for next time?
Oh, please, if I did that,
I'd blow the entire building up.
Did she fix it yet?
She did. She's a genius.
Shoot, I wanted to see
her do it. For next time.
It's all in the book I made you.
- Where'd that come from?
- I have no idea.
It comes from me.
I made the book.
Oh, look, it has pictures. Fun.
I am double-parked, Zelda.
Oh, do you want
some tea, Janusz?
- We have flame.
- No, thank you.
- You want to come in, Janusz?
- No. I am fine here.
Just come in and sit.
I do not want
to come in and sit.
This will just take a minute.
You say that and then we spend
the whole day here.
Oh, my god, you have
to light a match?
If I did this, I'd blow
the entire building up.
You would not blow
She might blow
the entire building up.
Then let her.
Janusz.
You want some tea, Miriam?
No, I can't be late
for work today.
Danny Stevens is
on the show tonight,
and Gordon warned us to be
on time and bring our A game,
and I have to stop
by Ethan's school
- for this parent thing first.
- Hi, Zelda.
- Can you fix this?
- Of course I can.
- Zelda.
- What?
You have to stop helping
these people!
- You don't work here anymore.
- It's a little girl's hair.
They didn't know there was
a higher shelf
in the linen closet.
They forgot how to stack wood
in a fireplace.
A bird flew in
and they could not think...
...to just open a window
to let it out.
They are grown people.
They have to learn
to take care of themselves.
They can't!
Zelda...
Back in the old country...
...when a horse is lame,
it is useless, so you shoot it.
This is an entire house full of
extremely lame horses!
Zelda, could you get that?
No.
Do not answer the phone!
Mrs. Weissman, excuse me,
but I feel very confident
that you know how
to answer a phone.
Oh. Okay.
Excuse me,
but I know how to play.
Oh, that's
what a fireplace flue is.
I've always wondered.
- Once more, with feeling.
- Hello?
We have a fuse box?
What?
Stopper's out, I don't know
why it's not going down.
Something is wrong
with the drain.
Don't blame the drain.
The drain was fine
when it got here.
I'm not blaming drain.
It's never the fault
of the drain.
Well, water is pouring into
the Ronbauer's
apartment below us,
and the hallway runner's
officially a goner.
- Here, Zelda.
- Thank you, Miss Miriam.
Thank you,
Miss Miriam.
I really appreciate your help.
It's lucky you were here
when this happened, huh?
Yes, so lucky,
like being a leprechaun.
Uh-oh, hold the phone.
Here we go. I found it.
This is definitely not
supposed to be in the drain.
How did that get in there?
It looks like it
was hammered in.
Ethan!
What is this?
My boat.
And what is your boat doing
shoved down the drain
of my bathtub?
- It sank.
- Hello?
Ethan, what have I told you
about putting things
down drains?
- Nothing.
- Yes, I have.
When?
I mean...
wasn't there a thing
with a marble?
That was up my nose.
What about the playing cards
you cut up and did
something weird with?
That was a drain, wasn't it?
- No.
- Oh.
Well, I guarantee,
in the six years
you've been around,
we have discussed
shoving things
down the drain at least once.
Even if it was
in the abstract, theoretical,
"If you ever get
the chance to, don't"
sense of the question.
- Okay.
So...
That
was the Mendelson's
on the seventh floor.
It's coming through
their ceiling as well.
- Great.
- You should go apologize in person.
Their son just
graduated law school.
I will take care of it.
Remember, my event is Monday,
so this carpet must be
replaced by then.
I cannot expose unmarried
women to nude wood floors.
It would feel like a brothel.
And, of course,
the bathroom must be working.
If not, I'd have
to change my plans again.
- Do you understand?
- What time is it?
I need confirmation
that you understand.
Shit. I'm so late. What do I do?
I'm-I'm supposed to be
at Ethan's school.
- Mama, can you go?
- I have a million things to do, Miriam.
Ah...
Papa? You're not busy, right?
Well, I'm due at
the Voice in an hour.
So, not busy.
Can you take
Ethan to school
and then stick around
for the thing?
What's "the thing"?
The thing. Parents come
and stare at the kids.
The teachers
point out their seats,
you get a snack,
someone wets their pants.
You're a terrible salesman.
Please? I need to bribe
our neighbors not to unleash
their newly-minted
lawyer son on me.
All right, fine. I will go.
But I'm warning you, the first
person to wet their pants,
I'm out of there.
Unless it's a really good snack.
Deal.
You can write to him
"Care of The Gordon Ford Show."
I don't know how
long it will take
for him to write you back.
He's very busy.
Well, he does
a show every night.
That takes up some time.
Sorry.
My son shoved a toy boat
down the bathtub drain
and it flooded mine
and the two bathrooms below,
and 7 and 8C, especially,
are not enemies
I can afford to have.
My floors are warped,
my runner's ruined,
my mother's throwing
a matchmaking mixer on Monday
and she's panicked
the runner won't be replaced
and the bathroom
won't be working,
and for some reason
my in-laws' piano
smells like a bialy.
So, how about the tits
on Ursula Andress, huh?
Sorry, what were you discussing?
The tits on Raquel Welch.
- Anita Ekberg.
- Ann-Margaret.
Danny Stevens.
I mean, not his...
Anyhow, we're talking
Danny's spot tonight.
He's coming on
to plug his new book.
Ah, big gold star for you.
Now, as you know, Danny...
- Gave me my first job.
- First job.
- Great guy. - Great guy.
- In-laws love him.
Well, he did and he is.
So, I want him
set up to succeed.
His writers may be
working on material,
but be ready
in case it falls to us.
- I have a question.
- Yes, Mel.
How many minutes
do you think it will take
for Adam to give
Danny his screenplay?
- Ten?
- I say eight.
No longer than four.
Does anyone know
a good tile man?
Midge, we're mocking Adam here.
- Sorry.
- One of these days, you're gonna
have to decide,
are you in or are you out?
Uh, everyone
to the railings.
To the railings, people.
Great.
As many of you know,
I am now officially
the new producer
of The Gordon Ford Show.
Thank you.
I just wanted to take a moment
to say a few words as
we begin this transition.
Though the departure
of George Toledano
was abrupt and upsetting
to some of you,
I want to assure you
that I am fired up
and ready to assume the mantle.
Being a good leader
requires not just experience,
but empathy, instincts,
a cool head. And...
Gordon.
Hello.
Hey, Mike.
You look great up there.
New suit?
Ah...
just the coat.
Oh. Please, continue.
Oh, no. I'm-I'm done.
What? No.
You called us to the railings.
We're at the railings.
Last thing I heard
was, um, "cool head."
Well, I...
just wanted you
to know I'm ready,
and I'm, uh...
I'm here for anyone who
needs...
something.
Uh, my office
used to be down there,
but now it's up here.
It's actually still
a little bit down there, too,
since there was no place up here
to put the guest board.
So, if you need to look
at the board, it's down there,
but if you-you need me,
I'm up here.
Or down there, sometimes.
When I need
to look at the board.
So...
Thanks.
Oh, wait, official new producer,
I have a question.
Any plans to add
more ashtrays to the lobby?
Not that I'm aware of.
Aw, too bad.
I think we could use two more.
I can find out where
they sell them.
I saw a kid
lick the elevator
button this morning.
I'll tell maintenance.
I have this receipt
from dinner last night.
Do I give that to you?
Okay, I'm leaving now.
Wait,
official new producer,
can we leave, too?
Yes.
Boy.
First day on the job.
♪ Who's afraid of
the big bad wolf? ♪
♪ The big bad wolf,
the big bad wolf ♪
♪ Who's afraid of
the big bad wolf? ♪
♪ Tra-la-la-la-la...
We have the finest
school library in New York.
We're very proud of that.
This year, a very
esteemed alumnus
bequeathed us his entire
collection of first editions.
Yes?
This is a delicious snack.
I'm glad you like it.
Crunchy and creamy and nutty.
Just a terrific combination.
Do the children
get the same snack?
They do.
This is a very good school.
Okay, I want
to show you all something
we're very proud of here.
This is what we call
our "Free To Be" time.
A portion of each day
is set aside
for the students
to devote to one subject
they particularly excel in.
This is our engineering group.
They are building
a model of a hotel
that caters exclusively to pets.
Every room has a patio
and built-in water dishes.
Here's our math group.
They have one minute
to solve a problem.
The one who solves
the most equations wins a prize.
And, go!
Our reading
group reads a book a week,
then they write a play
dramatizing it,
and perform it at lunch
in the teachers' lounge.
The astronomy group
is over there.
They're selling candy bars
to buy a new telescope.
I've put on ten pounds,
all in the name of science.
Now, over here we have
our language group.
They are currently
reading Madeline in French.
Mrs. Moyers?
Yes, Mr. Weissman?
What is that group over there?
Oh, that's the happy group.
- I'm sorry, what?
- The happy group.
But what do they excel in?
They excel in being happy.
I don't understand.
They build a hotel,
they're buying telescopes,
they're basically
a fully-functioning
summer stock company,
and that table,
the one my grandson is at,
- is just...
- Happy.
They're just walking
in a circle.
Yes.
- Why?
- It makes them happy.
Oh, Mrs. Foster,
this is Mr. Weissman.
Ethan is his grandson.
Ethan's one of
the happiest kids we've got.
Ethan has a wand.
Is he the leader?
There are no leaders.
A hierarchy wouldn't
make them happy.
Who decided these groups?
The children take
an aptitude test
at the beginning of each year.
The test determines
their strengths,
and that determines
their groups.
I'm sorry,
there's been a mix-up.
- A clerical error.
- There's no reason to be upset.
He's walking in a circle.
That's it.
Mr. Weissman, Ethan is
a sweet, healthy young man
who also happens to be happy.
So, so happy.
Maybe the happiest child
in the whole school.
we've ever had.
In all my years of teaching,
I have never met a child
quite as happy as Ethan.
I insist he be tested again.
Well, next year.
No, not next year. Now.
- Mr. Weissman...
- I was a tenured professor
at Columbia University.
I worked at Bell Labs.
I have 12 patents pending.
That is my grandson.
He's a Weissman.
There is no possible way
he's happy.
The whole
network is there.
The cast, the crew,
Philip and Morris,
staring right at us.
I say the line. Big laughs.
Suddenly, a pisher
from the end of the table
pipes up and says,
"It's l'chaim,
not la-chaim, Mr. Stevens."
First job. First job, okay?
So, I look over
at this altar boy
sitting there in
his father's suit...
It was my father's suit.
...and I thought, "The kid's
got balls. He reminds me of me."
So, I fired him.
Well, hello.
- Ah, Midge.
- Sorry, just had to fix my face.
Danny, may I present
our resident lady writer,
Midge Maisel.
Hi. I'm a big fan.
I'm in your seat, aren't I?
Well, technically,
they're all owned by NBC.
Nope, I know the rules.
Taking an established seat
in a writers' room
is like correcting
a man's Hebrew
when you're from Nebraska.
- Wisconsin.
- There's room here, Mr. Stevens.
I'm fine. I actually
came in to ask a favor.
Anything you want, Mr. Stevens.
I wish you could see
yourself right now.
Tonight,
I appear on your show.
No one's surprised? Good.
You're professionals.
Now, normally
I'm plugging a gig,
I'm in Vegas,
there's a new season
of my TV show,
but this time, I wrote a book.
- Ah.
- That's the book.
I am an author.
Like Dickens, if he
grew up in Bensonhurst.
A Tale of Two Cities sold
over a hundred million copies,
so I got to sell
a hundred and one.
I must kill.
With that in mind,
I am going to read to you
the jokes handed to me
by my team of professional
comedy writers this morning.
I'd like your opinion.
We are here for you, Danny.
Right, boys?
- Midge?
- Hell no.
Bastard tried to steal my seat.
Funny.
Uh, "Kennedy just
established the Peace Corps.
Now boring kids
can be popular, too."
Next.
"Barbie gets a boyfriend. Ken.
I don't think it's gonna last.
He seems a little fake."
You still with me?
"The Apartment
won the Academy Award
for best picture.
Next year, The Sublet."
Okay, so, in your unbiased opinion,
do you think my writers hate me?
We can come up with new jokes.
You know, every time
you make an appearance
on a talk show, you do jokes.
I'm a comedian. If I came on
and pulled Gordon's
wisdom tooth, it'd be weird.
Yes, but,
now you want people to read
a book about your life.
Why not talk about your life?
Talk about your parents.
Sure. Where's the funny?
It's interesting. It's real.
If it's interesting and real,
you can find the funny.
Oh, great. Homework. Thanks.
Excuse me, Danny?
Gordon's ready for you.
Thank you, sweetheart.
Kids, find me some jokes.
Open your notebooks,
check under the couch cushions,
channel your drunk uncle Marvin.
Get me those laughs.
Take me to your leader.
No.
It's very
unusual that a student
actually does worse
the second time.
Across the board on the math,
English, science, logic.
But he did spell his name
correctly this time,
which is a big improvement
over the last test,
so that's exciting.
I just don't understand.
We threw this new test
at him out of the blue,
he probably panicked.
Plus, we took his wand away.
That couldn't have helped.
But he's a Weissman.
It's just one test.
It doesn't mean anything.
Except he's not good in math,
science, English, or logic.
Or days of the week.
I feel like I'm
in an alternate universe.
Like I'm in The Twilight Zone
without Rod Serling
here to guide me.
Look, Mr. Weissman,
unfortunately, taking
this test again now,
so soon after
he took the first one,
will mean this score
will replace
his old one on his record.
Grandpa, glitter
sticks to your face.
But rest assured,
he hasn't lost his spot
in the happy group.
Miriam.
- Hey, you made it.
- Yes, well, we were late.
We wanted to make
sure there were actual tickets
before we parked the car,
so I dropped her off.
So I was supposed
to come out and wave to him
if I had the tickets,
and he would park.
But it was raining.
So, I go out, if I didn't
see him, I'd go back in.
Meanwhile, I drive by,
I didn't see her,
so I drove around the block.
We kept missing each other.
She goes out, I'm not there.
she goes in, I drive by,
she's not there,
once more around the block.
Two hours, we did this.
Finally, I gave up and parked.
Thank God the tickets were
waiting for us
right where you said they'd be.
- I told you.
- Oh, listen, could you point out
the person that got them for us?
We want to thank them.
Hey, show's starting, Shirley.
Wait, here, wait.
I made Danny a sandwich.
Give it to him.
And we're back in five,
four, three...
And we're back, folks.
Our first guest is the star
of the very popular
The Danny Stevens Show.
He's a nightclub performer,
an award-winning producer,
but the title he thinks
describes him the best
is "America's sweetheart."
Ladies and gentleman,
Danny Stevens.
- Hey, there he is.
- I left out dancing.
- You did.
- I always leave out the dancing.
Ah.
Danny, Danny, Danny.
Gordy,
Gordy, Gordy.
- It's great to have you here.
- It's great to be back.
I love what you've
done with the place.
I've done absolutely
nothing with the place.
Well, it works.
"Absolutely nothing"
works for you.
You know,
I caught your show
at the Copa last month.
It was great.
Thank you.
And your show's
still going strong,
and now I hear
you've written a book.
I have.
Got to get that book.
I got to get that book.
How was it, writing a book?
Well, it was very
quiet, peaceful.
Uh, you don't need pants,
so that's a plus.
Just like you.
You don't wear pants.
But it's different writing
about your real life.
You have to remember things.
Names, dates.
Then you have to change
the names and dates
so you don't get sued.
Wow. Are these your parents?
- Yes, that is Mitta and Joseph.
- Aw...
And that's after
their number came in.
But, see,
my parents were immigrants.
Tough. Very tough people.
They had to be,
because life gave them nothing.
They didn't have a bed,
they had a rock.
They had to flee their village
when men in boots
on horses rode in saying,
"Hey, what's flammable here?"
That's terrible.
They strapped everything
they owned onto their backs
and took off
through forests and rivers,
over mountains, all on foot.
Snowstorms, bear attacks.
I can't imagine it.
If there's a line
at Barney Greengrass,
I have a nervous breakdown.
Well, if they run
out of that good sturgeon...
Exactly.
Finally, my parents
get to Ellis Island
where they were
immediately quarantined
for two months.
Why?
They were sick.
They had everything.
Typhoid, pneumonia, malaria.
They were so sick,
the immigration agent
changed their name to...
I can't go by that name
in show business.
Too Jewish.
Finally get out,
move to a tenement on Delancey,
- and proceed to have nine children.
- Ooh.
Because, as my mother said,
"Even if you
can't afford the movies,
Saturday night is
still going to happen.
You got to do something."
Interesting philosophy.
She was
an interesting woman.
Not a lot of hugs,
but a survivor.
She worked every
day of her life.
When I was in sixth grade,
she got a job
driving a laundry truck.
One day, she was coming home,
my father was
crossing the street,
he tripped, fell,
and she ran right over him.
Oh, my God. Was he okay?
Oh, sure.
I mean, he was dead,
but other than that...
Is that funny?
That is the worst story
I've ever heard.
Two of her kids died,
two others in jail.
What family she had left
was wiped out by the Nazis.
Yet, through all of that,
all the trials and tribulations,
the only time
I ever saw my mother cry
was the day I told her
I was going to be a comedian.
♪ Someday we'll
go places you...
The cigarette machine
is broken again.
It ate my money, so I cried,
and they opened it up,
and I took everything.
- Remind me to bring you to the bank sometime.
- Ah.
There she is.
Wonder Woman.
Is he talking about me?
I certainly hope so.
Midge, get over here.
Okay, but if this is
about someone stealing
all of Toots' cigarettes,
I know nothing about that.
You should ask Mel.
Hey, I heard that.
You sit right here next to me.
- You have to move, Alvin.
- Sorry.
She's not going
to sit on your lap.
I'm moving. I've moved.
Sorry, Alvin.
- Just find a spot, Alvin.
- Yup.
- Any spot.
- Okay.
A wall, a post,
- a sturdy waitress.
- I'm out of the way.
- Hello.
Good? Good.
I am buying you a drink.
Oh, I have a drink.
That is not a proper drink.
She will have whatever
Shirley Temple drank
right after Judy Garland
got The Wizard of Oz.
Tonight was a triumph.
It went very well.
You, you did this.
- No, you did this.
- Did what?
Gordon, this woman here
is like a brave explorer,
daring to find what
no one has found before.
A bit that works.
I think you're exaggerating.
You're Amerigo Vespucci,
Sir Walter Raleigh,
Amelia Earhart...
if she'd made it.
I'm sorry, how do you two
know each other?
We met in the writers' room.
Writers' room? My writers' room?
I went in there
a broken man
and came out a king.
You were in the writers' room?
She said,
"Tell your family's story."
When were you
in the writers' room?
She told me if it's interesting,
you'll find the funny.
They barely let me
in the writers' room.
Just doing my job.
Yes, your job.
Well, cheers.
Cheers.
Listen, I'd like
to throw something out there,
just a thought.
I have a couple of
new projects in the works
that I am producing, and
I think you would be perfect.
- For what?
- Do you know Loretta Young?
Only from temple.
I'm developing
a situation comedy for her.
Is Loretta Young funny?
With the right material,
she will be. Gene Tierney
also wants to do TV.
You know Gene Tierney?
- Sure I do.
- These are big stars.
They do a show,
people will watch.
I was wondering...
if you would like
to come work for me.
- What?
- You can pick your job.
Whatever show you want,
you choose.
Oh, I am not a script writer.
She's a joke writer.
- Very different.
- Night and day.
If it's interesting, you can
find the funny.
Who said that?
I was talking about you.
No, you were talking
about story. Character.
That is script writing.
Also, you're a woman.
These are shows starring women.
Who better to write for them?
Danny, what are you doing?
I'm offering her a job.
She already has a job.
And now she has a better one.
This is a good job.
She makes good money here.
She'll make better money
with me.
Oh, really? How do you know?
Because I'll ask her
how much she makes here,
and then I'll give her more.
You're poaching my writers
from me? Seriously?
Only this one.
You can keep the rest.
- Sorry, Alvin.
- No problem.
No, no, no, no.
No, no. I found her.
So, what, finders keepers?
- Okay, boys...
- This town is filled with great writers.
Why are you doing this?
This isn't personal, Gordon.
It's not? You put
your drinks on my tab.
Well, fine,
I'll pay for my drinks.
Look, there are rules.
What rules?
Just... rules of society.
Oh, please, fuck that.
I see talent, I go after it.
Talent?
I don't think
it's her talent you want.
- Gordon.
- What does that mean?
Oh, you know what that means.
I'm married, schmucko.
And I don't care
who the fuck's writing for her,
Loretta Young is not now
and never will be funny,
and only an idiot
would think so.
Should we compare bank accounts?
That's it. Get up.
Are you kidding me?
I was a boxer in the Army.
You were a boxer
in a movie about the Army.
At least I'm from Brooklyn.
You're Canadian.
We moved there when I was five.
Hey, guys. People are watching.
Hey, what's going on here?
Gordon, you starting shit again?
I'll throw you
right out of here.
Do it, Toots.
Last time, you threw
your back out for a month.
That was a pre-existing
condition, you son of a bitch.
All right.
It's back here somewhere.
Wait.
Ah! Got it.
You can't be too careful.
Herman from Icelandic studies
can sniff out a good brandy
a mile away.
Here we go.
We toast to your wedding
and to your wife.
- To Miriam.
Mmm.
Now, Joel,
I asked you
to meet me here today
because I have something very
important to discuss with you.
Okay.
My daughter is going
to want children.
Yes. Three before 30.
What?
It's just what she says.
Three before 30.
Three kids before she's 30,
so she'll spring back.
I'd like to just go past that,
if you don't mind.
- Fine with me.
- As I was saying,
you will have three children,
and, in all probability,
one will be a boy.
Hey, we'll name him Joel Jr.
You won't.
Now, you need to know
there are certain gifts
that are inevitably passed on
to the first-born male
of each Weissman branch
of the family.
Gifts? Like an inheritance?
Weissman boys are born
with immense intellect.
So great it will
stagger your mind.
It will happen slowly.
You won't notice it at first,
but then, by the age of six,
it will kick in. Quite suddenly.
- Six.
- You should've seen me when I was five.
Just a slow-witted embarrassment
to my entire family,
and then I turned six.
The rest is history.
Now, this is a record
of every generation
of first-born Weissman men
and their accomplishments.
And prepare yourself.
It's a barn-burner.
We've got doctors, lawyers,
scientists, kings,
at least one oboist,
five writers,
an archaeologist,
one very creative murderer...
Wait, my first-born
won't be a Weissman.
- What?
- He'll be a Maisel.
- I'm a Maisel.
- Doesn't matter.
Miriam's a Weissman.
Her genes will
overwhelm your genes.
Your first-born son
is going to be a genius,
and you are going
to have to deal with it.
I promise he will have
the best education possible.
Oh, schools don't matter.
What matters is
a total lack of input
from you to the child
before he turns six.
What?
Basically, ignore him
till he addresses you first.
I can't talk to my own kid?
Of course you can.
Once he turns six.
Before that, zip it.
How do I communicate with him?
Miriam can do it.
Or, if it's really important,
you can leave a note.
Abe, this sounds crazy.
Trust me, we did not
get a book like this
by talking to our sons.
- Wait...
- I completely ignored Noah
for five years.
The morning
of his sixth birthday,
he picked up a violin,
he was playing Mozart
in two weeks.
I've never heard Noah
play the violin.
He doesn't need to,
he's already done it.
Understand?
- Not at all.
- Good.
So, we have a plan.
Welcome to the family, Joel.
Now, drink up before
Herman sniffs us out.
We were going
to start in the fall,
but then I had a dream
that a snowman
was trying to stab me
with his carrot.
Quite a shock.
Papa, come sit down.
Having another baby.
It's so exciting.
Isn't it?
Trying to have
another baby. Trying.
I can't believe bathroom
appliances come in
so many pretty colors now.
Our lives are,
once again, nothing but
doctors and daily shots
and dirty magazines.
What about dirty magazines?
Nothing, Mama.
I'm just saying
it's stressful and expensive.
And hopefully a girl.
It will be worth it.
I naively thought,
second kid,
surely there's
some sort of discount,
like maybe they could reuse
a test tube or something.
You do not want a doctor
that reuses a test tube.
I'm okay with three to five
previously used test tubes.
Astrid, are you hearing this?
No, I haven't heard
anything he's said
for the last two months.
What color are you going to get?
I think a pink toilet
would be amazing.
- What's wrong with your toilet?
- Nothing.
Well, then, why would
you get a new toilet?
Because I have
to get a new bathtub.
- So?
- They won't match.
Does that matter?
Can you pass the lox?
Why didn't you ever mention
Ethan's aptitude test?
His what?
His aptitude test.
They give every child
in his school an aptitude test
at the beginning of the year.
- Oh, how'd he do?
- He failed.
They say he has the potential
for nothing but happiness.
Is that bad?
Ethan is a first-born
Weissman male.
A first-born Weissman male
is expected to excel.
They are not
expected to be happy.
I'm sorry,
just because he's happy
doesn't mean he won't excel.
Of course it does.
Not one person who has ever
accomplished anything
of worth in life
has ever been happy.
- That can't be true.
- Name me one
cheerful man of science.
One sunny artist of worth.
One giddy Founding Father.
Benjamin Franklin.
Didn't he get laid a lot?
- Miriam, in front of the baby?
- Yes, he did,
but given all his
great accomplishments,
I guarantee you,
he didn't enjoy it.
Why are you getting so upset?
Your son
flunked his aptitude test.
I saw the score. He basically
has no aptitude.
It seemed like, half the time,
he was trying to write
with the eraser side
of the pencil.
- He's just a little boy.
- A little boy
who marches
in a circle all day,
oblivious to what
the future holds.
And the only thing
his mother seems to care about
is a ridiculous pink toilet.
What's wrong with a pink toilet?
A toilet is not
supposed to be pink.
- Why not?
- Because a toilet is supposed to be white.
A pink toilet is still
a toilet, except it's fun.
Not everything
is supposed to be fun.
needs to make you smile.
Sometimes you just have
to use a toilet.
They call and you come running.
Like a well-trained Spaniel.
Stop it, Janusz.
We should get you a leash
and a chew toy.
Shut it!
That is a linen closet.
The linen closet is where
you keep the tablecloths.
And the sheets,
and the pillowcases,
and it's all in the book
I made you,
that sits untouched
in the kitchen.
Zelda, did you by any chance...
Yes, I brought
the baby-making herbs.
- Oh!
- I will now go into the kitchen
and I will cook you your tea
so you can give Chaim a sister.
- Thank you.
- And once I'm done,
we are going home
to call the phone company
to come take our phone.
We don't want it anymore!
This is why they always want
to kill the fancy folks.
I like her new uniform.
- Hello? I'm here.
- Hello, Joel.
Sorry I'm a little late.
I had to wait for a delivery.
What did you do to your son?
What are you talking about?
Have you been talking to him?
Papa,
you're acting crazy.
I assure you,
this is not an act.
- Tell me.
- Of course I've been talking to him.
You've seen me talk to him.
He's my son.
I told you specifically
the less said to him
before the age of six,
- the better, did I not?
- You were serious?
Of course I was serious.
Why wouldn't I be serious?
Because that's nuts.
I told you about the bloodlines.
- The Weissman gift.
- Abe, that's all bullshit.
There's no magic gift.
Oh, no, Joel, there is
absolutely a Weissman gift.
Did you see the Weissman
first-born male book?
Oh, wait. Was that the book
Zelda was talking about?
Why would Zelda talk about the
Weissman first-born male book?
I don't know, she just keeps
going on and on about a book.
There is nothing
wrong with Ethan.
Have you seen his group?
What group?
He is apparently in
a happy group in school.
What's wrong with that?
I can't believe it.
He's ruined the bloodline.
- Oh, no. Really?
- We don't know that.
Well, what's
the explanation, then, Rose?
What explains Ethan's happiness?
Maybe he's a late bloomer.
- Maybe he'll get miserable later.
- Six is the age.
But Pop, I thought there were
a few Weissman first-born males
that didn't kick in until seven.
Remember? That, uh,
really distant cousin
who helped pave the way
for the X-ray machine?
Well, yes, but there were
extenuating circumstances.
You had the Franco-Prussian
War going on.
But it kicked in
eventually, right?
Well, I hope so.
I was so counting
on Chaim being smart.
- He will be, honey.
- But what if he's not?
Oh, God, Noah, what if he's dumb
and we have to spend our
lives pretending he's smart
like the Kirchner's
down the street?
The chain has not been broken.
What if our daughter
is stupid, too,
and then we have two dummies
just running around the house?
Well, at least they can
be friends with Ethan.
- Hey.
- Yeah.
Can everyone stop talking
about how stupid my kid is?
This is an old wives' tale.
Ethan, get your sister
and let's go.
Now, this is the last time
I want to hear anybody
say anything bad about
my son's happiness. Am I clear?
Say, "Goodbye."
Goodbye.
Bye, bye, bye, bye, bye, bye.
Bye, bye, bye, bye.
♪ Well, all right, okay...
I love twins.
You are not supposed
to tell us what you have.
- I don't know. I don't know.
- I didn't tell you what I had.
"I love twins"
means you have a pair.
No, it means I love two things
that are identical
to each other.
Like douchebags and you.
Okay, I'm out,
while I can still send
at least one kid to college.
I'm in. It's just money, Pete.
Says the youngest executive
in talk show history.
Not the youngest.
One of the youngest.
- Call.
And to think
when I first met you,
you were
George Toledano's bitch.
It said so on my door
and everything.
Admit it, I've been
good luck for you, Mike.
You, not so much.
- Stop focusing on me.
- Sorry.
It's just that vampires
with expense accounts
are a real turn-on for me.
- Ten.
- I'll call.
Me, too.
I'm out.
All right, final card, people.
These are some great
sandwiches over here.
- What kind?
- This has bread, meat,
cheese, tomato...
So, basically, a sandwich.
It's a sandwich.
What's the move, Susie?
Ten.
- I'm out.
- Raise you ten.
I raise your raise.
Are you raising my raise
- just to raise my raise?
- Yes.
That's not how you play. Mike.
What do you think
he's going to do?
Fine. Call.
Pair of kings.
Hmm. Pair of threes.
Oh, and another three.
Fuck you.
I'm getting a sandwich.
They are delicious.
This one has mustard.
Everybody, take a break.
- Stretch your legs.
- Sounds good to me.
- Walk with me.
- Sure.
I didn't know you
had bad blood with Ken.
No bad blood, just hope
to hora on his grave.
Why?
He's Shy Baldwin's agent.
What do you think of Pete?
He is not Shy Baldwin's agent.
Pete books Jack Paar.
All you talent bookers
hang out together?
- You don't have any friends?
- No.
Listen, Paar wants new voices.
His show's number two,
he's hungry.
Pete's putting together
a showcase,
12 top up-and-comers,
ten minutes.
Midge is in.
- What?
- I talked to him.
He's really excited to see her.
You talked to him about Midge?
She's the only woman
in the showcase.
I got him to give her
a late slot.
She's gonna shine.
What's going on?
What? I thought you'd be happy.
Well, what about Gordon's show?
You know the rule...
That was George's rule.
George is gone.
It's not just George's rule.
It's also Gordon's.
But you're there now.
Get him to change the rule.
I've been there
all of five minutes.
I can't do anything
till he totally trusts me.
How long do you want to wait?
Shit. We were
counting on Gordon.
So count on Paar.
Come on. This is a gift.
Okay.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Hey, guys, I think Ken is
in the bathroom crying.
Seriously, thank you for this.
Of course.
I hope Midge kills.
What? Oh, yeah.
Thanks for that, too.
Pss, pss, pss, pss.
Are you sure
that's a good idea?
I don't think...
What's in the ceiling now?
We think it's a cat.
- You think?
- Well, it's fast.
And it's got a tail.
Hey, you. Get out here.
I want to talk.
Sure. We can talk in here.
Nope. Too much vag. Let's go.
Great. Sit.
I didn't know
you were coming tonight.
How long till you go on?
I got a couple minutes.
And I have some
very exciting news.
I love very exciting news.
It is not going to happen
with Gordon Ford.
That's exciting news?
- Miriam...
- Woo-hoo, it's my lucky day.
Stop it, that isn't
the exciting news.
The exciting news is that
I got you a showcase
for Jack Paar.
- A showcase?
- No.
Do not sigh.
This is different.
This is invitation only.
No cattle call.
It's very selective.
And Paar is going to be there.
This is real, this is big.
Jack Paar.
I talked to the booker, Pete,
after the poker game tonight.
Did you win?
Eh, I left with everything
but their dicks in my pocket.
Anyhow, he told me there's
only 12 comics on the bill,
and you are the only woman.
You get that whole
runway to yourself.
Who told you Gordon Ford's dead?
Doesn't matter. This is better.
The whole point of me
taking that writing job
was to get on his show.
Hey, look at me. Fuck Ford.
He's a child. Paar is a legend.
Let Paar break you.
Mm? Gordon'll look like
a fucking idiot 'cause
he had the next best thing
sitting in his office,
and he was too much of
a dickhead to put her on.
- I guess.
- You go on Paar first,
Gordon's going to be so pissed.
Yeah.
Think of how fun that'll be.
So, how about we shift
our gunboats to Paar?
Not a cat!
Definitely not a fucking cat.
♪ Walking down the street ♪
♪ And suddenly you meet ♪
♪ A pair of brown eyes
dancing along...
Why are you getting a raise?
Oh, hi. What?
You're getting a raise.
- Why?
- Am I?
- Yes.
- Says who?
The raise fairy.
Oh. Why?
- That's my question.
- Uh...
- You didn't know?
- I didn't know.
It's a big one, too.
You'll be making
as much as the men.
Jiminy Crickets.
- More than one of them.
- Ooh, Ralph?
- Is it Ralph?
- Oh, I'm not telling you that.
Yes, it's Ralph.
Well, this is very serious.
I mean, if this gets out,
every working woman
will want to get paid
just as much as a man
to do the exact same job,
and our entire civilization
will collapse.
Exactly.
Can't help you, Mike.
♪ And the show has begun ♪♪
Hi. Got a sec?
- No.
- Okay.
I guess I do.
I was just wondering,
why did I get raise?
You know why.
No, I don't.
Danny Stevens tried
to poach you,
so I had to bid
against him to keep you.
That's how business works.
Congratulations.
You feel very good
about it, I see.
I'm fine.
I was banned from
Toots Shor again.
Well, you did attack him
with his own garnish tray.
Midge, is there anything else
I can help you with?
Nope.
You know, I don't think
he was hitting on me.
I know when men
are hitting on me.
Oh, he was.
You are not a woman.
You are not a man.
No, but I get paid
like one now, apparently.
He's a smooth operator.
You probably didn't
pick up on it.
Right.
Probably because
it didn't happen.
It happened, okay?
It didn't, but sure.
Whatever you say.
Yes, Midge?
I'm going to do a showcase
for Jack Paar tonight.
Got a fancy dress on
and everything.
Shaved my whole leg,
front and back.
He's going to be there.
Jack Paar.
Twelve comics are performing.
I'm the only girl.
Gives me a little leg up,
hence the shaving.
Got a good spot.
Toward the end.
So...
Want to book me first?
Beat him to the punch?
No? Yes? Maybe?
Okay.
Well...
Going once...
going twice...
You're not supposed to back away
when you're counting down
like that.
You stand in front of a person,
you say "once, twice,"
and then go.
Okay, thanks for the tip.
I'll remember that.
I'm gonna get this.
You'll see.
Lost in Bermuda.
I love being a comedian,
because even though people
are judging me up here,
at least they've been drinking.
Jesus,
someone hand me a pillow.
I feel like I've been
watching the same blue suit
complain about blue balls
for three hours.
Because you have.
- Paar's still there, right?
- Yes.
He is loading a gun
to blow his brains out, though.
Make sure he saves me a bullet.
Midge Maisel?
There's only one chick
on the bill, one set of tits.
Why is it a question?
You could be Midge Maisel.
You've got tits.
I got to say, it's nice
someone finally noticed.
- I'm Midge.
- You're up next.
Well, here goes nothing.
How do I look?
For this crowd? Like the
eighth night of Hanukkah.
- But coming up next is a good friend of mine...
- Tits up.
- ...be kind. Mrs. Maisel.
Hello, hello,
ladies and gentlemen.
Wow. People, really,
did you all get bad news
at the same time?
Is it terminal?
How many puppies got clubbed
to land me this sea of faces?
It's like there are Germans
downstairs or something.
They live.
Great.
You're very funny.
Thank you.
You got any arsenic on you?
Oh, shoot. Other purse.
Just my luck.
Last smoke?
I'm guessing you weren't
happy with your set.
What was not to be happy about?
They coughed, they talked,
they ordered drinks.
It was like Sunday night bingo
without the door prize.
It wasn't that bad.
Yeah.
It wasn't that good, either.
You were, though.
I was okay.
"Okay."
Sure.
I'll see you around, Eugene.
...huge,
for her and you.
Okay,
easiest way to put it,
the parts just
don't add up, okay?
What are
you talking about?
I'm sorry, I just don't get it.
What do you mean,
you don't get it?
I mean, I don't get it.
She's a girl, but she's pretty.
She's got a nice dress
and she does what?
She's fucking funny.
I don't know what I'm selling.
You are selling a comic.
I just didn't get it.
- Jack was laughing.
- I talked to Jack.
He didn't flag her.
Don't think he got her, either.
Well, the audience sure got her.
Did you hear them?
They lost their shit
at every fucking thing she said.
Yeah, they were a nice crowd.
Fuck "nice." She killed.
She blew every guy away tonight.
Destroyed them. You know that.
Let's talk about
your other client.
- What other client?
- James Howard.
I hear that kid's hot.
Yeah, James is doing good.
Word is when that movie
comes out, he's a star.
I don't know.
Can we get back to Midge?
No on Midge.
I want to book James.
- What?
- I'd love to get him
on the show as soon as possible.
I can offer him great placement.
He can do six minutes,
then sit with Jack.
Let's get some excitement going
so when that movie hits...
But you've never
seen James work.
You don't even know
if he's funny.
I know people
are talking about him.
That's what I know.
Yeah, fuck that, Pete.
Tonight is about Midge.
- But...
- I am not discussing James.
I am discussing the woman
that went up there tonight
and wiped the fucking floor
with 11 other guys.
I want James.
Well, I'm not gonna...
You should book him.
James is great.
I've seen him work.
He'll be good for the show.
Look, Midge...
It's fine.
You don't have to get me.
Not everyone's gonna get me.
I don't get me sometimes.
There are mornings
when I wake up,
and I'm like,
"Who are you? What are you?
Why are you dressed
like that?" I understand.
- Miriam, let me handle this.
- No, Susie.
Don't hurt James.
Don't do that. I'm good.
Really.
You are a class act,
Midge Maisel.
I will give you that.
Well, that's something, right?
Thank you for the opportunity,
Pete. Really.
I hope to be able to say
"I told you so" one day.
Me, too.
Call you tomorrow.
Okay, let's talk dates, huh?
Sure.
Jack fucking Paar.
- Yep.
- My mother's gonna shit.
She gonna shit,
she gonna pass out,
she gonna wake up
and she gonna shit again.
Sounds like it's gonna be
a rough night for your mother.
Oh, man, I can't
believe this year.
Seven months ago, I was
working for wings and fries
at that chicken place,
and now I'm in a movie,
and I'm gonna be on Jack Paar.
Don't pinch me.
I don't want to wake up.
You are on a roll,
that's for sure.
So, what's the date?
When do they want me?
I want to talk
to you about that.
Hey, I don't care when it is.
I'll cancel whatever
I have going.
Jack want me,
Jack can have me.
I want you to turn it down.
What? Why?
It's not your turn.
What the hell does that mean?
You are on a great
path right now,
without Paar.
You don't need him.
Let's let the movie come out
and then you do Paar.
- Why?
- I told you.
It's just not your turn.
Uh-huh. Well, how about
you make it my turn, then?
- James...
- You book it, Susie.
I don't think we should.
You either give me
a better reason
than "It's not your turn,"
'cause, frankly,
that means fuck all
to me right now,
or you book the spot.
- James...
- Book me
or I'll find someone else
who will.
♪ Son of a gun ♪
♪ He walked in to the party...
This place is nuts.
Apparently Mama was so pleased
with the shoot today
that she wants
to come back tomorrow
to add some more angles.
So it looks more filmic.
She learned that term today.
"Filmic." And "copy that."
Midge, this commercial
has already cost triple
- what we had budgeted.
- What can I tell you?
Okay, I'd like to have
a "come to Jesus" talk
about this, if I could.
You want to have a
"come to Jesus" talk with a Jew?
This hobby of your mother's...
- Oops.
- Whoa, there.
Don't you ever let Mama
hear you call it that.
She will bite your nuts off
and make them into earrings.
This business of hers
has officially become
a huge financial drain on you.
- How huge?
- King Kong to Fay Wray.
Well, at least I get
to be an ingénue again.
The Madison Ave location
was bad enough,
but the fact that
she refused to rent
and you had to buy the building?
Why didn't you call me?
I was playing Tahoe.
The phones were sticky.
The business
is not making money.
We should really think
about closing the place.
We can negotiate severance
for the employees,
and we can try
to sell the building.
We'll take a loss,
but we should get it
off your books.
You can just pay
your mom a salary,
straight from you to her.
It'll be more
than she's making now. It...
Susie, back me up here.
He's not bullshitting you.
The numbers are bad.
Brian, I appreciate
what you're saying,
but this place is more
important to my mother
than her grandchildren,
her husband, her son or me,
so it will stay open as long
as she wants it to stay open.
I don't want her worrying or
feeling sad or like a failure.
We will continue to tell her
business is great,
and we will make as many
commercials as she wants,
because that's
all I can do for her
in the brief time
she's got left.
Book the Australian tour.
First thing tomorrow.
Miriam.
I just had a brilliant idea.
- Testimonials.
- Ah.
We film all
my great success stories
and do a series of
commercials with them.
I mean, it may affect
everything we just did today,
but, push come to shove,
we just do it again.
What do you think?
I think that's
a great idea, Mama.
The bathroom is not
gonna be fixed in time,
and the whole place
smells like mildew,
so I can't have my event here.
I'm going to have
to rent a hall,
to spend my own money,
and it's going
to cost a fortune.
I know you don't care.
You think what I do
is silly and frivolous.
That's fine. It only
means something to me.
Esther?
The Earth is exploding.
Did you hear?
No, it's not.
Something just fell.
It's okay. Go back to bed.
Miriam? Are you all right?
Miriam?
Not now, Papa.
Where's Nancy?
The food's getting cold.
- She's got a date.
- Oh.
A date?
With a boy?
Yes, dear, a date. Potatoes?
- Don't try to distract me with potatoes.
- But you love potatoes.
I don't want to talk
about potatoes.
Okay.
Carrots?
Carole, our daughter is 15.
- Danny...
- No dating till she's married.
Then her husband can
decide when she dates.
Can you get that, dear?
Fine, but when I get back,
we're going to have a long talk
about who's in charge
of this household.
Me. On second thought,
that was the talk.
Talk's done.
Oh, you're kidding me.
Is Nancy here?
No, she enlisted.
For how long?
What's your name, son?
Skippy.
Your parents named you Skippy?
- Yes.
- On purpose?
Yes.
Do they know you're not a puppy?
Danny, let the boy in.
He'll catch cold.
It's a hallway, not the tundra.
Okay, get in. Get in.
You sure do have
a nice home, Mr. Stevens.
What, are you casing the joint?
Aw, you brought Nancy flowers.
Let's see. When was
the last time I got flowers?
Oh, it was when the doorman
brought up a bouquet by mistake.
He had the wrong apartment.
Skippy, come.
Sit.
Good boy.
Now, Skippy...
I still cannot
get over that name.
I'm gonna ask you
a few questions.
- Do you date a lot, Skippy?
- No.
How come? Girls don't like you?
- What?
- Is there something wrong with you?
I don't think so.
Hi, Skippy.
Hi, Nancy. You look swell.
Oh, thanks. We should go.
Ah, excuse me, I'm not
done with Skippy yet.
- Follow me.
- What are you doing?
I'm gonna race him
down the hall.
What?
I just want to see
if he can outrun me.
Time to go, you two.
Have fun. Be home by 10:30.
10:30? What is this, Spain?
Home by 8:45.
But, Daddy...
Danny, may I see you
over here for a moment?
- Why?
- I just want to talk to you.
He started it.
Danny, your daughter
is about to go to her
very first dance
as a young lady.
Are you really going
to spoil it for her?
I really want to say "yes."
No.
That's the man I married.
Have fun, you two.
- Nancy.
- I know, Daddy.
Home by 10:30.
I was just going to say
you look beautiful.
Thank you, Daddy. I love you.
Bye.
Ay-ay-ay.
Very sweet.
Doesn't count.
♪ If I don't see her each day ♪
♪ I miss her ♪
Huh.
♪ Gee, what a thrill ♪
♪ Each time I kiss her ♪
♪ Believe me, I got a case ♪
♪ On Nancy ♪
♪ With the laughing face ♪
♪ Do you ever hear
mission bells ringing? ♪
♪ Well ♪
♪ She'll give you
the very same glow ♪
♪ When she speaks ♪
♪ You would think
it was singing ♪
♪ Just hear her say hello ♪
♪ I swear to goodness ♪
♪ You can't resist her ♪
♪ Sorry for you ♪
♪ She has no sister ♪
♪ No one could ever replace ♪
♪ My Nancy ♪
♪ With the laughing face ♪♪