♪ When we dance together ♪
♪ My world's in disguise ♪
♪ It's a fairyland tale ♪
♪ That's come true ♪
♪ And when you look at me ♪
♪ With those stars in your eyes ♪
♪ I could waltz across Texas with you ♪
♪ Waltz across Texas
With you in my arms ♪
Sorry about the hiccup, folks.
Won't be long.
♪ Waltz across Texas with you ♪
♪ Like a storybook ending
I'm lost in your charms ♪
You got five minutes.
♪ And I could waltz across Texas
With you ♪♪
Howdy, folks.
Could someone tell me if
Mrs. Alma May Urbano is on board.
Alma May Urbano.
There you are.
Hello, dear, very good to meet you.
My name is Jimmy. I tried to visit you at
Sandpiper, but they wouldn't allow me to.
Hey, you know what? It doesn't matter.
I saw your bus broken down,
here you are, lucky me.
Do you prefer to be called "Mrs. Urbano"
or "Alma May" or just plain "Alma"?
My last name is McGill,
but you can call me Jimmy.
Hey, everyone, my name
is Jimmy McGill. I'm an attorney at law.
But don't mind me,
just talk amongst yourselves.
Now, Alma May,
do you recall responding to a mailer...
...from my law firm, Davis & Main
of Santa Fe, New Mexico?
I don't know.
Well, we were looking
to help any Sandpiper residents...
...who may have been overcharged
for basic goods and services.
- Now, does that ring a bell?
- Oh. Maybe. Was it yellow?
It's canary yellow.
I picked that colour myself.
Well, ma'am, I'm here to make sure
you get your money back.
What are you talking about?
Who took Alma May's money?
Well, that's a very good question,
and thank you for asking, Mr...?
- Amos. Amos Lydecker.
- Mr. Lydecker, Jimmy McGill.
Now, nobody took
anybody's money exactly, okay?
It's not like the Sandpiper people,
you know, put on a ski mask...
...and mugged Alma May
here at gunpoint.
So I want you to put
that mental image out of your head.
See, what we're talking about here
is just a discrepancy.
It's a little thing. It's fairly innocent,
but we need to fix it.
You follow me?
Well, put it this way:
Alma May, let's say you're out
on a date with your boyfriend.
You do have a boyfriend, right?
Aha-ha-ha. You don't?
Come on, you--
Alma May is holding out on me.
- Do you have a nephew?
- Nephew? Oh. Yes. Steve.
- Okay, Steve. Is he a good guy?
- Yeah, very good.
Okay. So let's say you
and Steve go out to dinner at, uh....
Well, Birdie's. That's where
you're all headed today, right?
- Right.
- All right.
So, both of you have a great meal.
It's chicken-fried steak and green beans.
It's all perfect. Here comes the cheque.
"Hey, wait a doggone-- Twenty-four bucks
for a side of buttermilk biscuits."
- That doesn't sound right, now doesn't it?
- No.
No, it does not. It sounds
like something got added up wrong.
Well, naturally, you send your nephew
Steve to talk to the manager...
...and, naturally, the manager
corrects the mistake.
And what's more, he gives you a coupon
for a free meal next time you come in.
- How about that?
- Good.
Well, same kind of thing
is what happened at Sandpiper Crossing.
And nothing...
...makes me sadder than to see people
of the Greatest Generation...
...people like my own Nana
and Bobo...
...getting overcharged
by some great, big company...
...even if it was an accident.
Now, I know that the good people
at Sandpiper...
...wanna make this right,
sooner or later.
But you know what?
Well, sometimes it's just easier...
...if you get your nephew, Steve,
to go take care of it for you.
And that's how I want you
to think of me.
Georgiana. Hey, there, Georgie girl.
Thank you. Oh, it's all there,
everything I need.
Thank you so much. Enjoy your lunch.
Alma May, you did it.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
Thank you, Henry. All right.
Hey, Sue. Okay.
Beautiful penmanship, a lost art.
Schweikart & Cokely are pursuing
an aggressive strategy...
...but looking at the relevant case law,
it won't play with this magistrate judge.
I've read over a dozen of her rulings,
all of which have sided with the plaintiff...
...on cases like this.
I've included a memo to that effect,
which you can peruse at your leisure.
Thanks, Erin.
How about we move on
to client outreach.
Jimmy?
You still with us?
I'm gonna save you
from having to brag.
Over 200 new Sandpiper clients
signed over the past three weeks.
- Well done, Jimmy.
- Thank you. Thanks, Cliff.
Right now we're in the process
of mapping out the entire Southwest...
...targeting the largest
Sandpiper facilities first:
Phoenix, Colorado Springs,
Fort Worth, Provo.
That's just for starters. Ideally, my goal:
another 200 by the end of the month.
With this many folks...
...we have an excellent shot
at a solid batch of plaintiffs...
- ...for the classes in each district.
- Excellent.
Look forward to the next report.
On to a stickier wicket,
coordinating actions.
Sorry, before we move on, I'd like to go
back to client outreach just for a moment.
Looking over these numbers here,
really astonishing results, Jimmy.
Incredible.
Your last trip to Amarillo
you came back with 22 new clients.
- Twenty-four.
I'm confused.
How many people out there
actually responded to our direct mailer?
One.
Oh, right. Yeah.
A Mrs. Alma May Urbano.
But you got 24 new clients
from this one response?
That is.... Wow.
Well, you're welcome.
I mean, what, is there a problem?
Well, might not some parties,
the opposing counsel for example...
...see this differential and conclude...
...that there may have been
some solicitation involved?
- I did not solicit.
- I'm wondering...
...how you account for your success...
...because it will definitely raise eyebrows
over at Schweikart & Cokely.
I'm sorry, but it will.
Particularly in a case
involving seniors...
...for whom the ethical guidelines
on solicitation...
...were virtually created by the ABA.
Chuck, I'm sure that--
Jimmy, if you could clear this up,
that would be helpful.
I went to Amarillo to confer
with a client and to make sure...
...that we had a solid, good-faith basis
for our case there overall.
As many of you are aware, I've visited
more than my share of retirement homes.
These are close-knit communities.
Let me tell you,
word gets around real fast.
If Dorothy in Phase 2 gets
a new Rascal scooter, it's big news.
So these other 23 residents,
they approached you?
Cliff, they heard the scuttlebutt
before I crossed state lines.
And I certainly didn't have
to go knocking on any doors.
And is it any surprise
that they wanna speak with a guy...
...who's there to show them
they may have money coming their way?
I gotta tell you, with all that in mind...
...I should've done better.
Makes sense. Howard?
Chuck?
We good to move on?
Chuck, not incidentally,
it is absolutely vital...
...that we dot our I's and cross
our T's here. Invaluable. So, thank you.
Well, the price of excellence
is eternal vigilance.
Indeed.
Coordination.
I believe that's where we left off.
That's right. Brian, this is your thing,
so why don't you take this.
Sure. Ahem. Considering the dimensions
of these cases...
...taken together and individually,
it makes sense to designate someone...
...to handle the scheduling.
What I'm proposing is we create a small
team at D&M dedicated specifically...
...to coordinating all elements
of the individual actions.
- We'll loop in HHM on anything--
- I'm sorry. Excuse me for interrupting.
I just wanna say
that I take Chuck's point, I do.
I mean, this is like
a "wife of Caesar" type thing.
There can't even be a hint
of solicitation...
...so I'm gonna pull back.
All right, no more meet-and-greets
at Sandpiper facilities.
I'll find another way to proceed.
Jimmy, we'll leave that up to you.
You know,
client outreach is your department.
Uh.... Where was I?
Okay, right.
If we have a more consolidated nerve
centre here in New Mexico where the....
Hey, Kim, where can I get a copy
of that Niederman deposition?
I've got an extra Niederman, Jimmy.
You can have one of mine.
- Wow. Thanks, Erin.
- No worries.
- Oh, shoot, where did I put that?
- Thanks, that's....
Man, you believe Chuck in there?
Jesus, solicitation?
Let me tell you,
when we were building this case...
...I was chasing down 80-year-old
mall-walkers.
That was solicitation,
but did he say "boo"? Bullshit, he did.
What happened in Texas?
Nothing.
- I did my job.
- No song-and-dance in the day room...
- ...for the old-timers?
- No. No.
- Not in the day room.
- Solicitation can get you disbarred.
- This matters.
- Well, here's what I think matters:
Twenty-four senior citizens
now have representation.
Before, they didn't know
they were getting ripped off.
Now they have us in their corner.
How is that not a win?
You said in there
you'd find another way.
Did you mean it?
- Sure. Absolutely, I'll....
- Oh, it's just....
Look, I....
I need you to understand something
very critical here.
Shoot.
I put myself on the line
to get you this job.
Okay. I thought it was because
I'm sensational with old people.
Yeah, and who do you think
told them that?
- So, what, you threw me a bone?
- No, asshole.
You know I believe in you.
But then I made my beliefs known
to them.
And now everything you do
reflects back on me with Howard...
...because ultimately I talked him into
going out on a limb for you too.
Do you understand?
It's my word, it's my judgement.
Yeah.
You and I both know
you can do this job.
But, please, you just have to do it right.
Yeah, you wanna make sure you
put in the batteries the right way...
...or it won't work.
Then you close them up,
and I think--
I think you're good to go, young lady.
Why don't you give his foot
a squeeze.
He's funny.
Oh, darling.
I'm gonna name you...
...Mr. Snuggly.
Are you hungry?
I'm gonna get you some....
That should get you through
to next month.
Mike, thank you.
- But you shouldn't feel that you need to--
- Too late.
- Something up?
- Mm.
- Feels like something is up.
- No, it's....
- I didn't get much sleep. My head is....
- I'm sorry.
You tell me it's none of my business,
I'll drop it.
- I don't want you to worry.
- Not the worrying kind.
Last two nights I heard gunshots.
First night, they were maybe a block
or two over, woke me up.
My first thought was firecrackers.
That's what I assumed at the time.
But then last night,
there's no mistaking it.
There was three of them.
They were quick: Pop, pop, pop.
Closer, like they were
right outside the house.
- You call the cops?
- Yeah.
Took them over an hour to get here,
they looked around for two minutes...
...but by then
there was nothing to see.
- I'm staying here tonight.
- No. Mike, no, that's not necessary.
- It is not a problem. I'll take the couch.
- Mike, you asked, so I answered.
Please, don't make me sorry I told you.
Kaylee, come. Hm?
Get your supper.
What about Colorado Springs?
Um....
Two hundred eighty-three residents,
and we sent out 283 mailers.
Yeah, and how many response cards
came back?
- Zero.
- Zero?
Son of a bitch.
- Dana, Toni, have a good one.
- You too, Mr. Main.
Cliff, can I have a second?
- What's up?
- Yeah, it's the Sandpiper mailers.
We should be getting responses
of like 12 to 15 percent...
...but we're getting ones and twos,
in Colorado Springs: zero.
Wow. How can that be?
I'm thinking it's the staff.
They're tossing the mailers before they
can reach the residents.
Maybe they got told to do it
by the Sandpiper front office...
...which would be actionable as hell.
If we could prove it. Big "if."
And to do so would take
more manpower than I can spare.
Let's just stick with
getting those client numbers up.
- Guess you better think of another way.
- I think I got it.
TV commercial, highly targeted.
Let me tell you,
at Sandpiper the trains run on time.
Mussolini would be proud.
Everyone I've visited so far,
same exact schedule.
Ten a.m., water aerobics,
2 p.m., line dancing, so on and so forth.
They always leave 3 p.m. to 4 p.m.
free. Why? Murder She Wrote. Heh.
It's been in syndication
since like the 1850s.
Let me tell you,
when that thing comes on...
...it draws blue-hairs
like moths to a bug zapper.
Three-fourteen p.m.,
end of the first act cliffhanger...
...first commercial up: Davis & Main.
Guaranteed eyeballs, lots of them.
There's nothing Sandpiper
can do about that.
We ran a commercial a few years back,
another class-action case...
...kind of a new thing for us.
It's not exactly my go-to, but,
generally speaking, I'm open to it.
- We will talk next week.
- Great.
Safe travels.
If you or a family member...
...have been diagnosed
with mesothelioma...
...or related conditions, you may be
entitled to monetary damages.
Mesothelioma is a rare lung disease
usually associated...
...with exposure to asbestos,
a known human carcinogen.
Long-term inhalation of asbestos fibres
can cause serious or fatal illnesses...
...including malignant lung cancer,
mesothelioma and asbestosis.
Remember, they worked really hard
to get that just right.
- To get what just right?
- The swirl.
They wanted kind of nebulous,
but not too nebulous.
Then there was the issue of the speed.
I remember there were a lot
of meetings about that.
I'll bet.
For your free consultation
call Davis & Main at 505-242-7700.
That's 505-242-7700.
- Cliff signed off on this?
- The partners were very happy.
What do you think?
I think:
What ever happened to showmanship?
Yo, check it out. Ricola!
- Ricola!
- Hey.
Why don't you two ass-clowns act
like the professionals...
...your parents are paying
for you to become.
- This happens to be very valuable.
- Yeah? What is it?
This one is the Alpine shepherd boy.
It's for her nephew.
So come on, join me.
Production meeting, bring it in.
All right, now look,
teamwork makes the dream work.
Together we can make something,
dare I say it, bravura.
This is a golden opportunity,
especially for you.
This will play all around the Southwest,
so who knows what it can lead to.
Better lead to a hundred bucks each.
- What is it with you and money?
- Saving up for a VX2000.
Hey, pop quiz. What do we three have
in common with the greats?
Welles, Fellini, Bergman, the biggies.
What?
All three of them, to a man...
...worked in the highly lucrative,
creatively-rewarding field of advertising.
And tonight we join them.
This is heady stuff, right?
Okay, so pay attention.
We open on Granny
and she is rocking.
So, she's back and forth, just very--
Back and forth.
And then, very slowly and smoothly...
...the camera moves towards--
- Dolly.
- A dolly, good.
See a dolly here?
- You guys didn't bring a dolly?
- Nope, no dolly.
- You didn't ask for a dolly.
- Gotta ask. Dolly is extra.
- That's true.
- Okay, no dolly.
Um, heh.
We will improvise, then.
Stay with me.
She's rocking. She's shivering.
She's clutching...
...at a tattered shawl.
They turned the heat off on her,
these evil bastards.
She's cold and hungry,
she's friendless.
This is heart-rending stuff, man.
Okay, it's a oner
and it's shot in glorious black and white.
- We can do that, right?
- Yeah.
So, that's it, old lady in a chair?
That's your commercial?
Does anybody like you?
I'm ready for my close-up, Mr. McGill.
Makes the grab, two outs here.
He got underneath that one.
I think it's....
An easy, easy pop fly
out to dead centre.
That'll bring up....
Murphy's gone 13 for 29
over his last eight games...
...batting a blistering.343 overall.
And now Louis again
working quickly with the bench.
Murphy swings, it's a two-hopper
into the crowd, foul ball.
Have a good one.
Hey, honey, what's happening?
What's wrong?
What happened?
- Where's Kaylee?
- She's at school.
- She's fine, she doesn't know about it.
- Are you all right?
Let me show you.
It's up there.
You see it?
It's right up there.
You see that?
You see the shape of it?
- You do see it, right?
- Uh, I see it.
What time did you hear the shots?
2:13 this morning.
I looked at the clock.
It was three of them.
It was exactly like last time.
And you didn't call the police?
No, I.... What's the point?
Uh, I'm thinking outside the box, but....
You think maybe it's possible
that you dreamed it?
It happens sometimes.
I didn't dream it, Mike.
Because I didn't sleep a wink last night.
That came from a bullet.
I mean, it must have.
It wasn't there before last night.
I promise you.
- And I don't know--
- Okay.
Okay.
Jesus.
I mean, I was here.
I was here and you weren't.
I believe you.
All right.
That's it. We're getting you
and Kaylee out of this house.
End of story.
Do you ever wonder about these things?
- What things?
- This. Like what's the story with these?
Who was it who first said,
"Hey, I know, big bowl of balls"?
I don't know. They came with the place.
No shit. They're in
every corporate apartment in the world.
They're like the Gideon bible.
Hey. Don't be jealous of my
big bowl of balls. It's unbecoming.
Why do they all have
to have empty vases?
Well, it's the law. Plus it's a metaphor.
Gotta say, I will miss
the nail salon's vibrating chairs.
Well, for you I can make
any chair in this place vibrate.
You ready for this?
Okay. Here goes.
You're 86 years old, you're a resident
of Sandpiper, Colorado Springs.
You just finished your afternoon snack,
lime Jell-O.
- Lime. Got it.
- You're in the day room.
You're watching
your favourite TV programme.
What's this? There's been another
murder in Cabot Cove?
- No.
- Yes.
The sheriff is in over his head.
Jessica Fletcher has to put aside
the novel she's been writing...
...and assist law enforcement.
Shocker,
the killer left behind a cryptogram...
...and commercial.
My husband and
I scrimped and saved for so many years.
We did our best
to build a nest egg...
...so that we wouldn't be a burden
to our family.
After Ronald passed,
I moved to an assisted living facility.
A nice place. They told me
they'd take care of everything.
But, then one day
they said all my money was gone.
How could that be?
Where did it all go?
That's not a real tear?
If you or a loved one
is a resident...
- Visine.
- ...of the Sandpiper Crossing facility...
...or other
associated retirement community...
...you may be eligible
to receive compensation.
For a free consultation,
call the law offices of Davis & Main...
...at 505-242-7700.
That's 505-242-7700.
Well?
You made that,
with some film students?
I directed.
It looks professional.
- And?
- And if I were an 86-year-old...
...Sandpiper resident...
- ...I'd be dialling.
- Yes.
Up top.
And all made in accordance
with the rules and regulations...
...of the American Bar Association.
Good.
I can't believe
Davis & Main went for it.
Well...
- ...I'm in charge of the department.
- Yeah, but still, you know.
Cliff Main was fine with this.
Heh-heh.
Why wouldn't he be?
He.... No, it's....
It's fantastic.
Let's celebrate. I'm getting more wine.
You want some?
Absolutely.
Thursday at 11
in the Conference Room? Okay.
Very good. Thank you.
Colorado Springs, Colorado. Yeah.
I'd like the number
for KKTV channel 11.
Omar! What's the cut-off for FedEx?
I need to get a package out, tout de suite.
Oh. Yes, can you connect me
to your ad sales department?
Thanks.
Gums look good. No recession.
Tongue looks good too.
Eyes are clear.
This little lady's in fine fettle.
- One of the girls can trim her nails.
- No, some other time.
What do you got for me?
Bodyguard job, 200 bucks.
What else?
For you,
that's the best fit I've got.
I know a loan shark.
Always needs
enforcement and recovery.
Pays good and it's steady work.
Most of the time
we're just talking intimidation.
- Strictly verbal.
- Most of the time.
I'm not breaking legs. What else?
Look.
We discussed this.
You want next-level pay,
you gotta do next-level work.
I respect where you're coming from.
I do. But that's just how it goes.
All right.
She's gonna need a DHPP shot.
Six months.
We'll send you a reminder card.
Till then.
Give me the bodyguard job.
For 200?
Call you with the where and the when.
Yes, sir. He's expecting your call.
- So, everybody knows--
- They know.
Every line starting with 7700
has been rerouted to the bullpen.
Plus your office.
The assistants know to keep them open.
So if you're on a call
and another call comes in...
...it doesn't go to
an answering machine?
Very important. Old people
don't like talking to robots.
If I'm on a call and another call
comes in, it'll roll over to Maida.
After that, Iris will get the next one.
Then Julian and then Barbara
and Yvonne...
...right on down the line.
Good. Let's make that the plan then.
Oh, so, ahem....
What time do you have?
Quarter after.
It should be running now, right?
Is there anything else?
No. Thanks. It's--
I'll just be in my office.
Come on.
Come on, Colorado Springs, come on.
Good afternoon, Davis & Main,
attorneys at law, how may we help you?
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, ma'am, that is unfortunate.
Now, to get your case started...
...may I ask for a name and a number
for one of our attorneys to reach you?
Good afternoon,
Davis & Main, attorneys at law.
Can I help you? Yes, that is--
Good afternoon, Davis & Main.
Sandpiper hotline, how may I help you?
We'll get back to you.
Yes, ma'am. We'll be happy to send
an information packet to you.
May I ask...
...are you currently a resident
of the Sandpiper Crossing facility?
Good afternoon, Davis & Main.
- Bingo.
- Are you currently a resident at....
I'll just need a name
and a phone number.
Yeah.
Something came in this evening...
...and it's definitely next-level pay.
Yeah?
It's probably a long shot,
given your selectivity.
What's the job?
I asked. The guy wouldn't tell me.
But whatever it is, it's serious money.
And the guy?
He specifically asked for you.
And who's the guy?
- I can't hold it, sir.
- No control in the planes.
We're going down and fast.
"We're going down and fast."
Check this out. This is the good part.
- Anything?
- So do they all die? Tell me that much.
Does Rock Hudson run them
into an iceberg?
Is this before or after
he did McMillan & Wife?
Shut up, watch the movie.
What is this weird fascination
you have with stories...
...of men trapped on the North Pole?
Ice Station Zebra is on the North Pole.
The Thing takes place on the South Pole.
They could not be any more different.
- Aye, sir.
- My dad loves this one.
- Put it in the red.
- Yeah. Him and Howard Hughes.
I know, right?
Can't get two finer reviews than that.
How much pressure left in the air tanks?
Down to 800 pounds, sir.
- Secure aft to group below.
- Secure aft to group.
Unh-unh.
- It's the boss.
- At this hour?
Oh. It's never too late for congratulations.
Cliff, Jesus, you're still at the office.
You ran a commercial?
Yeah, and oh, my God, let me tell you:
The response has been--
You ran a commercial...
...without showing it to me
and consulting me and my partners.
Did you actually think
that was gonna fly?
I was planning on telling you
in the morning.
- The day after it aired?
- I only ran it once.
Just in one small market.
It was kind of an experiment, all right?
Kind of under the radar.
And in all fairness, you did tell me
client outreach was my department.
Don't be disingenuous.
This commercial,
I take it my firm's name is mentioned?
Yes. Yeah.
Jesus. Howard said
you were a little eccentric...
...he didn't tell me
you're a goddamn arsonist.
Cliff, to be fair, I don't think, uh....
I apologise if there was any misreading
of the situation on my part.
But there's
a very positive headline here.
We got 103 phone calls today...
...off a measly $700 ad buy.
Now that kind of return on investment...
- ...you can't--
- Tomorrow morning, 8:00, my office...
...with the partners.
We wanna see this thing.
Cliff, when you see this,
I know you'll--
Yeah, Cliff.
Thank you.
Yeah, you too.
Okay, see you.
Golden boy.
That's me.
So what did I miss?
Anything blow up yet?
Feeling cautious?
You gonna tell me
what we're doing here?
- I've got a problem.
- Okay.
This problem, I can't solve it myself.
This problem, is it a who or a what?
There's a guy.
I need him to go away.