♪ And I gotta catch a noon train ♪
♪ Gotta be there on time ♪
♪ Oh, it feels so good to know
She waits at the end of the night ♪
♪ Sweet, sweet city woman ♪
♪ I can see your face
I can hear your voice ♪
♪ I can almost touch you ♪♪
Jimmy?
How's that sweeping going?
Going good, Pop.
Hi, how are you?
Hello, sir. I was wondering if
maybe you could help me.
Yeah?
Well, I drove into the city this morning.
Usually I take the train,
but I was just in such a rush...
...to get some medicine
for my son, Freddie.
He has epilepsy.
He had an attack this morning.
But during his fit, he knocked the bottle
of medicine out of my wife's hand.
And just, bam, one huge puddle.
Oh, that's terrible.
Well, long story short, drove into town.
I bought the new medicine with
every last nickel in my pocket.
And then my car died.
- Oh, God. That's-- That's just--
- I know.
When it rains, it pours, right? Heh.
I tried the ignition.
Just nothing, not firing.
Anyway,
now I've convinced myself that...
...Freddie's gonna have another seizure
before I get back with the medicine.
So if you can help me,
I would be so grateful.
Well, I could come out
and check your car for you.
Maybe it's just a spark plug. I got
a box of plugs back in the stockroom.
Thanks, and I appreciate that.
But if you could possibly
just spare $5 instead?
I'd rather grab a cab than
take a chance with my old clunker.
Yeah, $5.
If you can spare it.
- Yeah, okay, sure.
- Psst.
Dad, come here.
Come here.
Dad, it's a rip-off,
just like that bum from last week.
Jimmy--
Every grifter in town knows that this
is the spot to come for an easy handout.
"Grifter"?
Where did you learn that word?
Dad, his story's baloney.
He probably doesn't even have a son.
He's conning you.
Jimmy, what if you're wrong?
You know what?
I'm sorry to bother you folks.
I'm gonna get out of here. I'm gonna--
- No, no, no.
- Dad--
No, no bother. Come on, now. Here.
Here's $10 for you.
Sir, you're--
That's-- That is so generous.
You know what?
I'm gonna go back in the stockroom.
Find those spark plugs.
We'll get your car started.
Come on, Jimmy.
Just man the till, okay?
And I'll just be back in a jiff, okay?
How much for a carton of Kools?
Four bucks.
Yeah, give me a carton.
Money first.
♪ Everybody here is out of sight ♪
♪ They don't bark and they don't bite ♪
Give me two cartons.
Spark plugs are here somewhere.
Just give me one more minute, okay?
♪ Dancing in the moonlight
Everybody's feeling warm and bright ♪
Come on.
♪ Everybody's dancing in the moonlight ♪
♪ We like our fun
And we never fight ♪
♪ You can't dance and stay uptight ♪
♪ It's a supernatural delight ♪
There are wolves and sheep
in this world, kid.
♪ Dancing in the moonlight ♪
Wolves and sheep.
Figure out which one you're gonna be.
♪ It's such a fine and natural sight ♪
♪ Everybody's dancing in the moonlight ♪
Okay, I found the, um--
Did he leave?
Did he just leave?
Sir?
♪ They don't bark and they don't bite ♪
♪ They keep things loose
They keep 'em tight ♪
♪ Everybody's dancing in the moonlight ♪
♪ Everybody's feeling warm and bright ♪
♪ It's such a fine and natural sight ♪
♪ Everybody's dancing in the moonlight ♪♪
- Don't let me interrupt.
- Oh, hey. Sorry. You ready?
Hey, come on. Let's get this over with.
Thank you for seeing us.
We don't wanna take up too much
of your time, so I'll get right to it.
Um, I regret to inform you that
with the benefit of hindsight...
...Mr. Ehrmantraut will be amending
his original statement a tad.
- "A tad"?
- A wee bit.
He's decided that he can no longer
in good conscience...
...claim that the gun found at the scene
belonged to Tuco Salamanca.
- So whose gun was it?
- Who's to say?
You know how many guns
there are in Albuquerque?
Somewhere between the number of
rattlesnakes and grains of sand, so a lot.
- Was it your gun, Mr. Ehrmantraut?
- No, he's not saying that.
Can we hear it from Mr. Ehrmantraut?
The gun wasn't Salamanca's.
That's all I can tell you.
You told us it was. You said
Salamanca pulled it and pointed it at you.
Well, he didn't.
- Why are you changing your story?
- Good citizenship.
Look, there was only one set of prints
on the gun. Salamanca's.
How's that gonna happen
if it wasn't his?
That's not really for
my client to say, now, is it?
He's not a forensics expert.
Who knows? Maybe it, uh,
fell from a passing bird's beak.
Mr. Salamanca caught it, tried to throw
it away. The possibilities are endless.
- Did Salamanca threaten you?
- Hey.
We wanna put this guy away for years.
The gun makes all the difference.
You gonna let this person
victimize you twice?
Forget about the gun, all right?
The gun was not Salamanca's.
If you introduce it, Mr. Ehrmantraut will
make himself available to the defence.
And he will set the record straight,
categorically and unequivocally.
Did he threaten you or pay you off?
Whoa, okay, that's it. We're done.
You're doing the right thing.
This Salamanca character? Maniac.
I had my own...
...thing with him.
I didn't wanna say before
because conflict of interest...
...yadda yadda, but yeah, he's nuts.
I'm talking
he had me hog-tied in the desert...
...with a gun to my head.
Broke two guys' legs
right in front of me.
If I hadn't
talked him down, he probably would've--
I'll spare you the gory details,
but it was a deal and a half.
Not something you forget.
And you're telling me this why?
Don't be too tough on yourself.
Like they say,
discretion is the better part of valour.
I would've done the same thing.
Hey, today, it's on me. No charge.
You take the next one.
And bill me.
Ingrate.
- Hey, Jimmy.
- Did you tell Howard yet?
- I can't really talk right now.
- You didn't tell him.
No, and I won't until it's rock solid.
Like, offer-letter-in-hand solid.
When you gonna get that offer letter?
I'm guessing next Thursday
after my interview with the partners.
- Yeah, but that's just a formality, right?
- Basically.
- I hope.
- What's the offer, you think?
I mean, brass tacks.
Well, it's not gonna be as
plush as your deal at Davis & Main.
But they'll make me
partner in two years.
As opposed to between
five years and never at HHM.
Not too shabby.
- Then there's my law school loans.
- What is that? A couple grand by now?
I wish. I had to finance the thing
only making mail room money.
I've got, like, 15,000 left.
Wow, Schweikart wants you bad, huh?
Jimmy, did you have something
you needed?
No, no, just checking in.
I'll see you later, okay?
If you play your cards right. Bye, heh.
Omar, where are you?
Omar, would you be so kind
as to take a letter for me?
"Dearest Clifford."
No, that's too much.
"Dear Cliff."
What do you think? "Clifford" or "Cliff"?
I don't, uh--
Depends on what the letter is.
That's fine. Treat yourself.
"Dear" whoever you put in.
Continuing. Uh....
"My heart is heavy as--"
No, that sounds like
a medical condition.
Let's go with, "It is with a heavy heart."
Okay?
"It is with a heavy heart that I tender
my resignation to Davis & Main."
"Tender" is better than "submit,"
yeah?
- "Resignation"?
- Yes, sir.
So "tender." Blah, blah, blah.
"To Davis & Main.
These have been some of the most...
...professionally
satisfying days of my life."
What's wrong?
You think I'm laying it on too thick?
No. Um....
I just didn't realise
how unhappy you were here.
Not unhappy, per se.
More like "not happy."
I had no idea.
It's not your fault, buddy.
You're top-notch.
Where were we?
You worked so hard to get here.
It's so much to give up.
I mean, the perks alone--
Yeah. The apartment is, uh....
Yeah. Heh. And the car.
For the most part,
the car is pretty sweet.
- And the bonus?
- Well...
...the bonus is a done deal. They cut me
the cheque. I get to keep the bonus.
Not if you quit.
Before a certain term--
I think yours is a year.
--you have to pay the money back.
Uh....
It's, um--
Yeah. Uh-- Um....
Yeah, yeah. It's, uh--
I think it's right here. Uh--
Yeah.
Omar...
...that whole, uh, letter of resignation
thing, that--
I didn't mean that.
Not a word. I--
I am so incredibly stressed out.
I'm stressed out the wazoo.
To be honest,
it has been more of an adjustment...
...than I expected
here at Davis & Main. So I just--
Don't repeat what I said to anyone.
I figured something had to be wrong,
really wrong.
Because you like it here, right?
I love it.
Call it a momentary lapse of reason.
But just-- Let's just rewind the tape
and, you know, forget this happened.
Mum's the word. No problem.
Yeah, I feel better already.
Sometimes you have to
say something out loud...
...to hear how crazy it sounds.
Thank you, Omar.
Hi. Jimmy McGill.
Jimmy, this is Al Newman
of Allied Funeral Homes.
- Great to meet you, Al.
- Nice tie.
Thanks.
All right. Let's get started, shall we?
- What are you doing?
- Hey, Doug. Got a juicer for the office.
- Jimmy, it's very loud.
- Brian, come on in.
- We have clients out there.
- Sure you can. Two coming right up.
Sometimes it gets a little jammed.
You just gotta force it.
- Aah.
- Oh. Oh, shit.
Oh. I'm spreading it around.
Did I get you?
And now I got you with this.
For chrissakes, Jimmy.
Backwards only.
Yeah? Because it's got suction that way.
Leverage and physics.
Don Clifford wants his floors clean.
Dude, I'm from Michigan.
So you don't understand
a word I've been saying?
Good night. No, you try. Backwards.
Excuse me.
Can I have everyone's attention, please?
Everyone can hear me? Good.
This is not a conversation
I ever thought I would have in my career.
But it's been brought to my attention...
...that we have an ongoing situation
in the washroom.
Someone is not flushing.
Once is an accident, maybe even twice.
Three times? That's a pattern.
- We're not talking about a number one.
- Yes. Thank you, Erin.
Now, I'm not here to shame anyone nor
do I even wanna know who did it. But--
Uh, Cliff, it was me.
- Jimmy, I just said I didn't wanna know.
- Hey, we need the water.
Now, I read somewhere
that the Santa Fe watershed...
...is down two full inches this year.
Every time you flush a toilet,
you waste a gallon of water.
A gallon.
What could be greener than this?
They're low-flow toilets, Jimmy.
From now on, flush.
Low-flow. That's good. Good thinking.
What is that?
I'm gonna call you back.
Jimmy, what's going on in there?
Jimmy.
Oh, you can hear this through the door?
I didn't realise. I'm sorry.
- What do you think you're doing?
- I took your advice. I'm blowing off steam.
"Blowing off steam"?
Yeah, yeah.
Like you and your guitar, you know?
I gotta say, you're right.
I mean, it really helps with stress.
I know I don't sound very good,
but I'm just learning.
I heard that the key is you have to
keep this bag inflated.
Enough. Put that down now.
I want you in my office.
You win.
- What do I win?
- You're fired.
What?
Cliff, if this is about the bagpipes--
It's not about the bagpipes.
Of course it's the bagpipes.
It's the bagpipes, the not flushing...
...and this optical migraine
you call a business suit. It's about--
It's about you keeping your bonus,
that's what this is about.
Been brushing up on
your contract law, haven't you?
You want out of here. But you can't up
and quit and expect to keep your bonus.
If I fire you for cause, like I should have
done for the TV commercial, no bonus.
However, if I fire you not for cause,
but for being an all-around jackass...
...yeah, hooray for you.
- If you think there's been malfeasance--
- Oh, save it.
I could fight you on this,
but you're not worth my time.
I'd rather just have you gone.
I'm sorry you feel that way.
I'll just, uh, pack up.
First, do me the favour of not
treating me like a fool for once.
Tell me,
how exactly did I mistreat you?
What did I do to
deserve this behaviour?
We gave you opportunities, encouraged
you, got you a car, an apartment.
Hell, that cocobolo desk.
Do you see a desk like that in here?
You never gave this a chance. Why?
I tried to make it work.
Really. I did. I'm just...
...a square peg.
If you knew that,
why did you take the job?
I'm sorry.
- How much was the desk?
- Seven thousand dollars.
I'll write you a cheque.
Fine, for whatever good that does.
Take your desk and get out.
Hey, Cliff, for what it's worth,
I think you're a good guy.
For what it's worth,
I think you're an asshole.
Hey!
Uh, yeah, it's open.
- Jimmy.
- Hey, can I talk to you for a minute?
- Does Howard know you're here?
- God, no. I snuck in.
Well, yeah, but make it quick.
Actually, can we talk
in the conference room?
- Why?
- It's just more appropriate.
No one's gonna need it until 4.
I checked.
Please? Ten minutes tops.
After you.
Have a seat.
What--? What is going on? Spill it.
Okay.
Schweikart & Cokely will pay
your debt to HHM...
...and make you a partner in two years,
correct?
Apparently.
That's the deal, yes. Why?
Would you entertain a better offer?
From who? HHM?
From me.
I'll make you partner tomorrow.
Consider that proof of concept.
Wexler-McGill, partners at law.
You and me. Together.
If Schweikart can pay your debt,
so can I.
And with my signing bonus,
you'll have a clean slate.
Sky's the limit.
Hey, we're good together. You know that.
So, what's stopping us?
Let's jump in with both feet.
Be our own bosses.
Build our own future.
Be our own bosses. Heh.
What about clients?
Mesa Verde signed with you,
didn't they?
It would be a hard sell to bring them.
So then, there'll be
another Mesa Verde.
That was all you, Kim.
You did it once, you can do it again.
- You make it sound easy.
- No.
You're talking to a guy who lived
in the back of a nail salon.
It'll be a lot of blood, sweat
and tears. At least at the start.
But in the end, we'll have a practice
that is 100 percent ours.
That's worth it.
Or we fail and we end up with nothing.
- You're right. It's a gamble.
- It's a big one.
Yeah, but you're betting on yourself.
And from where I sit, the odds are in
your favour. You're an amazing lawyer.
This is your chance
to show the world that.
So why not go to Schweikart?
They'll make me partner,
and they're a solid firm.
- You can't deny that.
- You deserve more than a lateral move.
Bottom line, that's what Schweikart
represents.
He's just Howard Hamlin
by a different name.
You keep talking about me.
What about Davis & Main?
It's over. I quit today.
Well, technically I got fired.
What happened?
It was mutual and a long time coming.
That job was never the right fit for me.
This is.
If we're gonna be law partners,
I need to know one thing:
What kind of lawyer are you gonna be?
I don't mean what kind of law
are you gonna practise. I mean...
...are you gonna play it straight,
or are you gonna...
...be colourful?
I'm gonna play it straight.
Right down the line.
I'm gonna dot every I,
and I'm gonna cross every....
There's no point in me doing this
if I can't be myself.
Every time I try to do things someone
else's way, it blows up in my face.
That's what happened at Davis & Main.
Look how that turned out.
I almost derailed your career.
Pissed everyone off.
I've been trying to be the person
someone else wants me to be for...
...I don't know how long.
At first it was Chuck...
...then it was you,
and that's not your fault.
That was my choice,
but if we're gonna do this...
...I gotta go into it as me.
So...
...yeah. Colourful, I guess.
What do you say?
I just--
I don't see why it's so important
to you that we work together.
I mean, we're already--
- Why do you need me for this?
- I don't need you.
I want you.
You've got me.
Just not as a law partner.
I have to get back to work.
- You okay?
- Yeah, no.
I'm fine.
Go on.
- See you later?
- Yeah.
It's move-in ready, as you can see.
And they've renovated within the past
three years. New floors and kitchen.
And it's a good amount of space.
- It's not too much house, you think?
- No, not at all.
And look at that backyard.
They're leaving the playhouse.
Isn't that amazing?
- Kaylee will go crazy for that.
- Heh-heh-heh.
- You'll never get her out of there.
- I know, right?
And most important, the schools
are good and the neighbourhood's great.
I called the local precinct
and asked about crime stats.
They're some of the lowest in the city.
Plus I got a good vibe from him.
- They sounded really responsive.
- Sounds perfect.
Yeah.
Do you like it?
If you're happy, I'm happy.
Yeah, I do.
- But I'm--
- But what?
It's a lot of money. I know,
I'm like a broken record, but it is.
Don't worry. We'll make it happen
whatever the cost.
- Mike....
- Hey, I'm serious. Not another thought.
If you want it, it's yours.
- How are we looking?
- Oh, it's perfect.
- Let's do it.
- Fantastic.
Do you have another hour?
We could go to the office,
get the pre-approval in order.
- Sounds good. We'll meet you there.
- Sure. See you in a few.
- Oh. I feel like I can finally breathe.
- Good. I'm glad.
- You wanna ride together?
- No, I'll follow you over.
The car looks good. Wouldn't know
you so much as scratched it.
Yeah. My guy knows his stuff.
Thank you, Pop. For everything.
- You go on, now. I'll see you there.
- Okay.
Right here.
- Sorry I almost lost you at that light.
- No problem.
Watch the fish tank.
To the left. My left, my left.
There.
What do you think?
Uh, yeah.
It's, um--
Yeah.
What should I do with this?
Dump it on the side of the road.
That's where I got it in the first place.
Hey, buddy.
- This is over and above.
- No, really.
How about a drink?
I know I could use one.
- Come on. I'm buying.
- No, I'm good. Long drive.
- Cucumber water for the road?
- I'm totally set. Thank you.
Gotta get home to my kids.
How about you?
What are you gonna do now?
Onward and upward.
Thanks, Omar. Drive safe.
Hello. You've reached the law offices...
...of James M. McGill, esquire.
Kindly leave--
Hi. You've reached
the law offices of Jimmy McGill.
Please leave a message and I'll get back
to you as soon as I can. Thanks.
Summary judgements?
Yes, I've handled six.
Actually, one recently
was quite complex.
It was a litigation.
The result of a nasty divorce.
My client sued her former company, which
she and her ex split in their settlement.
The issues involved had me chasing
case law for weeks.
- Who heard it?
- Judge Pittman.
Oh. Heh, heh.
- That guy, he's a handful, huh?
- Well, he can be a tough nut to crack.
- But he did rule in my favour.
- Mm-hm.
All right, enough about law, law, law.
We know you're good,
we know you know your stuff.
Tell us about Kim Wexler.
- You started in the mailroom, right?
- I did.
I was there almost, well,
10 years ago now.
Pulled yourself up by your boot straps.
I like that.
I see you went to UNM Law.
Are you from New Mexico?
Not originally.
I'm from the Midwest. Just a tiny little
town barely on the map.
Near the Kansas/Nebraska border.
You've never heard of it.
So, what brought you here?
I guess...
...one day I just looked around at my life,
at who I was...
...and realised if I kept going
the way I was--
Which way was that?
Best case, probably married to the guy
that ran the town gas station.
Maybe cashiering
down at the Hinky Dinky.
- The Hinky what?
- Hinky Dinky.
It was our supermarket. Um....
I just wanted something else.
What did you want?
More.
Well, thanks
for coming by. Always a pleasure.
- Great to put a face to the name.
- Thanks.
We're gonna put
our heads together and discuss...
...but I feel safe to say you can expect
to hear from us by tomorrow.
That's...
...fantastic. I look forward to it.
We liked you when you came in here.
We like you more now.
Well, thank you so much for taking
the time, and I will speak to you soon.
- Great to meet you, Lynne.
- You too.
- Perry.
- Pleasure, Kim.
- Howard.
- It's Rich, actually.
- Oh, my God. I'm so sorry.
- No, no.
I'm happy to be confused with Howard.
He's a good-looking man.
Don't worry about it.
Come on, I'll walk you out.
Hi, I'm here to see Jimmy.
- He's in a meeting.
- A meeting?
Have a seat.
And listen, I don't ever wanna hear
the word "permit" again, capiche?
It's your funeral, dude.
- Hey, what are you doing here?
- Just in the neighbourhood.
- Great. Oh, and I want a dolly this time.
- What kind?
- Western? Hustler? Pee Wee?
- Hey, watch your mouth around the lady.
How should I know?
You're the nerd. Just make it cheap.
Go on, get out of here.
See you got your old car back.
Yeah. The kidney people
wouldn't take it.
Sorry.
Wow, you finally got
your cocobolo desk.
Finally got my cocobolo desk.
Feel like it's a good omen
for what's next.
And what's that?
This. Solo practice.
Being my own man again.
So how'd it go with Schweikart?
It went well.
- Should be getting their offer tomorrow.
- That's fantastic.
- I'm really happy for you.
- Thanks.
You know what, we should celebrate.
Whataburger, on me.
I'm not taking the job.
Why not?
You were right. It's time for me
to be my own boss.
Solo practice.
What, you don't think
it's a good idea now?
- Don't tell me you've changed your mind.
- No, I--
I'm surprised, is all.
Hey, I-- I said all along you're
too good for those clowns.
This is-- Shit! Yeah!
Wow, it's great.
Good. To that end...
...I have a pitch for you.
Not Wexler-McGill, but...
...Wexler and McGill.
We find an office, share the housekeeping
costs, rent, electricity, everything.
But I am Kim Wexler, attorney at law,
and you are Jimmy McGill, attorney at law.
Both free to practise as we see fit.
Separate firms under one roof.
We're both headed uptown.
Why can't we share a taxi?
You do things your way,
and I do them mine.
We'll have freedom, but we aren't each
trying to go it alone.
Not partners.
Solo practitioners together.
What do you think?
I don't know what to say.
Say yes.