All the banks and trains around
here, and you choose to rob us?
I... I... I need to get to the train.
They've broken my father.
He's wildly unstable...
bouncing between old roles.
It looks like an immensely
complex encryption key.
Drive!
Whatever's in there,
they want to get it out of here.
Take this dog out back, put
him down with the rest.
Get out of here.
What is this place?
It's complicated.
Oh! We have to go!
We have to get out of here right now!
Shh!
Maling for you, sir.
Go ahead.
Dredging's almost at fifty percent.
Should have the rest of them
skimmed up by end of day.
We also started draining the valley.
You want all personal effects,
or just skin and bones?
Everything. Down to the last Stetson.
Fly the whole pile over.
We'll crack 'em open to see if
we can't reprogram these things
- to behave by our rules again.
- Copy that.
Sir, I have two teams out
looking for Abernathy.
Good.
When you find him, bring
him to me personally.
- So, what have we got?
- It's not good.
We're pulling what we can off the
recovered host control units.
But what's really unsettling
is what's in about a third of them.
- And what's that?
- Nothing.
- They've been wiped?
- More like they're virgin.
Like they never held data to begin with.
No user prints or anything.
And that's not the worst of it.
Have a look.
We've put the fires out,
but there's nothing we can
recover from the Cradle.
The hosts' backups have
all been destroyed.
So we've effectively lost a third
of our IP in a single sweep.
Well, that's quite a
story you gave them...
and one hell of an ending.
How did all these disparate threads
come together to create this nightmare?
If we figure that out, we'll
know how the story turns.
What the hell's that?
Looks like a dead man to me.
You know the old saying
about knives and gunfights?
Does the saying have a footnote
about fucking lassos, then?
All right, that's enough.
Lay down your sword.
Tell your associates to set us free.
We mean no harm.
See, darling?
Everything under control.
Beautiful way to watch the sunrise.
Glistening off the intestines
of the recently mutilated.
Oh, Jesus.
Ohh.
Judging by their weapons,
I'd say local police.
And given that he's got one now...
Captured by samurai cop-killers.
Fuck me!
Can't you... say something to them?
I'm from Hong Kong, asshole.
This is just the tip of
Shogun World's prick.
An experience expressly designed
for the guests who find
Westworld too tame.
We based this park on Japan's Edo period
for the true aficionado of artful gore.
This world will end badly,
but I'll make sure your end is worse!
You understand them?
You all do. Look, she's a Madam...
Consciously fluent in
dozens of languages,
including Japanese.
But you all have those com skills
buried somewhere in your code.
The point is, the fact
that these psychos
didn't flip to English as
soon as I opened my mouth
means that the same
malfunctioning shitshow
that's playing out in Westworld
has found its way here.
That's also why your vocal
voodoo didn't work on them...
You spoke the wrong language.
This all feels a little too familiar.
Is that a... a butterfly?
A mariposa.
I'll be damned.
It's us.
Yes, fine,
I may have cribbed a
little bit from Westworld.
Well, you trying writing 300
stories in three weeks.
W-W-We're human shields now?
Welcome to Shogun World.
Shit!
Can you watch it?!
Behind you!
Hell of a homecoming.
Sweetwater was never home
to begin with, Teddy.
You and I were born long before
this place even existed.
But it's the place I
return to again and again.
No matter how far I strayed,
somethin' always... carried me back.
Somethin' like that?
Looks like she's taken some
hits the past few days.
But who hasn't?
Make a thorough inspection
from the engine to the last axle.
Fix what's broke,
strip her for speed.
Teddy.
With me.
What do we need the train for, Dolores?
They've taken my daddy.
So we're gonna get him back.
Well, it ain't doin' any
good sittin' in that bottle.
Sorry, Maeve.
Didn't get much sleep last night.
Sometimes...
sometimes they're real bad.
Clementine?
You're new.
Not much of a rind on you.
That's enough.
Rejoin the others.
It's like I told you, Teddy...
this place was never home.
Let's ride. There's
some place I want to see.
When I asked for a
civilised conversation,
I meant the quickest way
out of here, not all this.
Just try and rein it in a bit, will you?
The narrative bones of this
place are just like Westworld.
Hospitality is the
foreplay to a new quest.
But in this world, if you
don't hear them out,
you've dishonoured them...
Sometimes homicidally so.
Fine. We'll listen.
But then we go and find my daughter.
And for the record,
it's not just the narrative
bones that are identical.
You've plagiarised our
stories, our identities...
It's not plagiarism.
It's supply and demand.
But if you're asking
can you trust Akane,
the real question is:
can you trust yourself?
You know who I don't trust?
Him.
Say the word and I'll
skin him like a rabbit.
What's the matter with you?
He's not supposed to be here.
Who knows how seeing
your own doppel-bot
is gonna fuck with your cognition?
Heightened aggression and suspicion.
Feedback loops. That.
Yet another reason to get out
of here tout fuckin' suite.
Our quest, I presume?
I recognise this one.
It's called "Army of Blood."
Madam Akane, a mere geisha,
has no choice but to give up Sakura.
That's not supposed to happen.
Looks like someone had
a choice after all.
Snow Lake is her cornerstone,
but it also has an access
point back to the tunnels.
It's our way out.
So you're not so useless after all.
Did you have something to do with this?
Both of you. Look.
Oy!
Shit! Ninjas!
Oh, fucking hell!
Ohh!
Aah!
Ahh!
We got three. The rest
vanished with Sakura.
This is insane.
Ninjas never show up in this story.
Oh, fuck!
The Shogun's army never comes into town.
You three, with me.
I don't need to know the language
to know a puckered asshole
of a man when I see one.
You and I spent a lot of time here.
Watchin' the herd...
talkin' about makin' a life together.
Someday.
I guess I just wanted to
see it one last time.
What if someday was right now?
What are you talkin' about, Teddy?
There's a fight comin', Dolores.
And it's gonna be one
that's gonna change us
in ways we can't even begin to predict.
And I'm still waking up to...
what I really am.
And if that means I'm
free, then we both are.
Free to walk away.
Now, you can't tell me that somewhere
out there in all that beauty...
there isn't a spot for us.
I ever tell you about the
year we almost lost the herd?
Bluetongue.
Quarantined the cows that had it, but...
it kept spreading all the same.
Daddy finally figured out that it
wasn't spreading from cow to cow,
it was the flies that carried it.
He worried over it all night.
How do you stop a sickness like that?
One with wings.
Say it was you.
What would you do, Teddy?
I'd give 'em shelter.
House the weakest in a barn, out
of the air, away from the flies...
until it passed.
You're a kind man.
Daddy burned 'em.
The weak and the infected.
Made a pyre that went on for days.
And it stank, but...
the flies hate smoke.
The herd lived.
I'll think about what you said.
I'd like to take this moment to
appeal to your sense of survival.
If the Shogun is awake enough
to play fast and loose with
his ninjas and his army,
then the odds of us surviving here
have dropped to approximately fuck-all.
But I say we ditch Akane and
make a run for Snow Lake.
Why should we all get killed
over a literal sex machine?
Present company excluded, of course.
That machine's name is Sakura.
You can't keep doing this to us,
giving us people to love and
then getting upset when we do.
- But it's just fucking code.
- You're wrong.
I'm coded to care about
nobody but myself,
and yet here I am, willing to
risk my life for someone else.
Well, so much for your
so-called daughter.
You want to go it alone, be my guest.
But mention my daughter one more time
and I will snap you like a matchstick.
Like you did that ninja?
He took one look at
you and self-impaled.
How did you do that?
I don't know.
That was no voice command.
I think I'm finding a new voice.
Our transportation is ready.
God damn it.
What have they done to the place?
Is that...?
The fucking cavalry.
Great. So much for our rescuers.
I'm gonna take a fuckin' moment.
Don't stop on my account.
If you've quite finished.
It's time to sell this ruse.
How many of them are there?
Between the camp and the town?
Hundreds.
Literally hundreds.
So Maeve's gonna freeze
all those assholes
and we're gonna make
off with that geisha?
We're gonna die.
Did you just make that up right now?
Damn convincing.
Not to the daimyos.
It's like they had no
idea what I was saying.
Shit.
That's cortical fluid.
The Shogun's not awake.
He's broken.
No fucking wonder the
daimyos didn't hear you.
We've gone completely
off the rails here,
and this loon is driving
the fucking train.
Train'll be ready by morning.
To go where?
Exactly where we thought.
I caught up with the men
who took your father.
Couldn't get him back,
but I got this one.
Took a while,
but he gave up their destination.
Tell them.
It's the Mesa.
We're goin' home, Teddy.
Load everything up on the train.
We'll leave at first light.
Let's find a spot for the night.
What you asked today,
about walking away,
making it on our own.
Would you want me to say yes
even if I was only going
to disappoint you?
I'm not some stranger, Dolores...
coming from outside,
looking for a pretty lie.
I've known you
my whole life.
Where we go...
we go eyes open...
together.
You're right.
Some things are too precious to lose...
even to be free.
There's something I need to show you.
For days now...
I've been questioning
my feelings for you.
How much is real,
how much is just some story
I was made to believe.
But tonight I know.
It was all true.
They built us to perform for them
and for each other.
That's over.
I saw you tonight, Dolores.
And you saw me.
I did see you, Teddy.
These past few days...
I've seen you so clearly.
Ohh.
And I've seen
you're not gonna make it.
Wh...
what is this, Dolores?
This is what
I don't want you to become.
There's a swarm descending.
Just like the bluetongue
when I was a girl.
And if we're gonna survive...
some of us will have to burn.
Hold him.
Dolores! Dolores!
I wish there was another way, Teddy.
But where we're about to go,
it's no place for a man like you.
I'm so sorry.
You sure you want this?
With changes this extreme,
without a full reset, it's...
I can't guarantee that
he'll hold together.
To grow...
we all need to suffer.
Arigato, Maeve.
Jesus. What do we do now?
I told you I found a new voice.
Now we use it.