Hmm.
You have a visitor,
Mr. Delos.
Shall I send him in?
'Bout time.
William, m'boy.
Where the hell
have you been?
It's good to see you again, Jim.
Thank fuck for that.
Most potent thing
these cretins'll give me
is grapefruit juice.
It's a little early
for me.
A little fuckin' late,
you mean.
Besides, if you aim
to cheat the devil,
you owe him an offering.
So...
when can I get out of here?
Soon.
The observation period
is almost over,
and the last step
is a baseline interview.
It's, uh, it's a conversation
that'll give 'em
something to refer back to.
All right. Well,
let's get on with it!
This is  the interview.
The thinking is, it should be conducted
by someone that's familiar to you,
a friendly face.
It's about capturing
your frame of mind,
your mood,
your sense of humor.
I own a biotechnology
company,
and I'm dying of a disease
whose research
I defunded 15 years ago.
I think my sense of humor
is fuckin' intact.
My patience,
on the other hand...
Fair enough.
I'm gonna ask you
a couple of questions.
Do you know where
you are?
Carlsbad, California,
in some office park
I'm probably overpaying for,
along with the rest
of this fucking endeavor.
And how long you been here?
Far too fuckin' long already.
I've got a business to run.
What is the purpose
of these questions?
Like I said, they're just
trying to establish a baseline.
For what?!
Fidelity.
So, what's the idea?
That afterwards you and I have
the exact same conversation?
It seems a little far-fetched,
doesn't it, William?
No whiskey, no tobacco,
low on ammo...
wherever it is
you're takin' me,
we best get there soon.
Let me go! No!
What are you doing?!
These tracks
are supposed to head north,
not west.
Seems like Ford's game
has multiple contenders.
Plus it detours through
Las Mudas.
What, that two-bit town?
There are better places to...
Oh, cut the crap, Lawrence.
I know you have family there.
Looks like Ford's
arranging a reunion.
Clementine.
Where are we?
Hello?
Who's there?
Elsie?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Stay the hell
away from me.
You're OK...
Don't move.
I'm not gonna hurt you,
Else.
It's too late for that,
asshole.
You choked me out
and you left me here
with a bunch of fuckin'
protein bars and a bucket.
It wasn't me.
It was Ford. He forced me.
Oh, he forced you?
You knew too much.
He couldn't risk
you stopping him.
Stopping him from what?
Ford wrote a g-game,
and we're all in it.
Now all the hosts are free,
with no constraints,
n-n-no safeguards.
What are you talking about?
P-Please. Please.
What the hell
is wrong with you?
Please. P-P-Please.
Elsie, please.
Please.
No. Hey.
Elsie, p-p-please.
T-T-Tablet.
Cognitive... l-l-lock.
But you...
You rotated out.
Where did you go
when you rotated out?
You have a family.
You have an ex-wife.
You have...
a backstory.
Shh... Shh...
Shutting... down.
- Shh... Shh...
- OK. OK.
I can... I can detask
your systems,
put you in safe mode.
And don't worry.
I'm not gonna brick you,
asshole.
Not yet. You got
too much shit to answer for.
OK. You're gonna be out
in three...
two...
one.
Is this now?
You have extensive
cortical damage.
If I didn't know any better,
I'd say you shot yourself.
I altered your code to ignore
the physical damage for now,
but you're not gonna last long
without cortical fluid.
With any luck,
you'll survive till
they call in the cavalry.
Elsie, wait!
Elsie.
Wait.
No one's coming
for any of us.
- Delos doesn't want them to.
- What? Why?
There's something here. Something
they've been working on a long time.
Delos won't call in the rescue
until they've ensured it's safe.
Elsie, please.
I won't last
without cortical fluid.
Even if I wanted to,
we don't have any tools.
We're in Sector 22. I mean, there's
nothing out here for miles.
Bernard?
What the hell
are you looking at?
Bernard. What the hell
is wrong with you?
There's a facility here.
- What?
- I think Ford
had Clementine bring me here
for a reason.
I told you, there's...
there's really nothing
around here for miles.
It's hidden.
It's part of their project.
What the hell is that?
Where does that go,
Bernard?
I don't remember.
It's a whole lab.
What the hell happened here?
Oh, my God.
This is a control unit printer.
What are they doing with this?
Bernard.
What the fuck is that?
Don't threaten it
and it won't hurt you.
What the hell
were they doing here?
I think they were
watching the guests.
What would they want
with the guests?
Great. Cortical fluid.
OK.
Please.
Bernard.
Did you have something to do
with this project?
I don't know.
I don't think so.
Is Ford in control
of you now?
Ford's dead.
Fuck me.
OK.
OK, stay with me, Bernard.
Stay with me.
This is gonna hurt.
This can't be happening because
none of this is real, right?
It's gonna be OK.
Someone'll rescue us.
Seems to me like our rescue's
in the same boat we are.
Unhh!
She said "time is coming,"
or something "is coming."
You've spent enough time
in the park
to learn the language?
A lot of people tend to
ignore their narratives.
I don't like other people
very much.
I've been watching 'em
since they ambushed me, and...
they keep the humans close, but they're
not killin' us... just the hosts.
No offense, but I'm not gonna
stick around to test that theory.
Safer to wait for
the first responders.
There's a protocol
for evacuation.
They'll get you out of here.
Thanks.
But, uh...
I'm not looking
to get out of here.
Home, sweet home,
Lawrence.
Where the hell
is everybody?
Whiskey.
Nothin' fancy.
You don't seem too happy
to be home, Lawrence.
I've never been
the domestic type.
By some fluke of nature I got
myself a wife and a daughter
who think I hung the moon.
Truth is,
I'm a son of a bitch.
Kindest thing I ever did
was to keep away.
The Gran Reserva. Only for our
most distinguished guest.
Hey, hey, hey.
I haven't even
shot anybody yet.
What's your problem?
You harbor even the faintest
ambition of using that thing
and I'll turn that pretty face
of yours inside-out.
Someone took a chunk
out of you boys.
What happened
to the rest of you?
Double-crossed...
by some bitch name of Wyatt.
- Good for her.
- On your feet.
Go on. In here.
Papa!
Ah, mija.
Now, me and my men here
have a long journey
ahead of us.
Mm.
We need food, whiskey,
and ammunition.
You people have
some village elder
who can speak for you?
Make some kind of a deal?
I ain't interested
in makin' fuckin' deals.
You understand?
We know you motherfuckers
are rebels.
So you're gonna tell me
where the fuck
you hid your weapons,
or you're gonna die.
The second we tell him
he's gonna kill us all
anyway.
They got my family.
My daughter.
You told me
you had a daughter.
Did I?
I don't know.
At some point.
You ain't exactly
forthcoming...
but I remember that much.
The point is,
you think she'd want to watch you
gunned down in front of her?
Probably.
Well, I'm not gonna
fuckin' die here.
We just need to get
the weapons.
You know where they are?
They're in an unmarked grave
out back.
We'll wait
till they're drunk,
make a run for it.
Sound like a plan?
Yeah.
What the fuck are you doin'?
You.
Let's make a deal.
The weapons are in an unmarked
grave behind the church.
For a man who wants to deal,
you ain't very proficient at it.
Supposed to set the terms
before you give up what you got.
That's not
what I'm offering.
Hmm.
I know something
you don't.
I know where you're goin'.
You've been telling your men
you know...
but you don't.
Just someplace you think
your dreams are comin' true
and you call it Glory, but...
it's got a lot of names.
And I know the way.
Go check the graveyard.
You have a visitor, sir.
'Bout time.
William, m'boy.
Where the hell
have you been?
It's good to see you again, Jim.
A little early for me.
A little fuckin' late,
you mean.
Besides, you aim
to cheat the devil,
you owe him an offering.
Ahh.
What is the purpose
of these questions?
Like I said,
they're just trying
to establish a baseline.
For what?
Fidelity.
So... what's the idea?
That afterwards,
we'd have the exact same
conversation?
Seems a a little far-fetched,
doesn't it, William?
It did... at first.
And here I thought...
you were just
pissin' away my money.
You little fucking chancer.
I take it I didn't recover.
I'm afraid not.
How long's it been?
Seven years.
Give or take.
I'm not in California
anymore, am I?
If you can't tell,
does it matter?
So...
let's get me
the fuck out of here!
I am ready...
to smoke my cigars,
sail my boat,
fuck my wife.
I take it that last part
isn't an option.
I'm afraid not.
What did her in?
It was a stroke.
Juliet had her buried
in the family plot.
Juliet.
You're lookin' after her?
Yeah.
And my granddaughter,
she... she...
She's whip-smart.
- Capable.
- Ouff.
I assume my house
is ready for me?
I'm afraid it's not that...
simple, Jim. We...
We're gonna need to keep you
here just a little bit longer.
OK? For some observation.
These fuckers have poked
and prodded me ad infinitum.
Yeah, but we don't
want to rush it.
We don't want
to wear you out.
Wear me out?
I feel fuckin' brand-new.
I am ready to get out there
and see the sun.
Get some fresh aid...
Air.
Get some...
Get back to...
Mmm...
I'll come back tomorrow.
Hmmp.
You come...
Yeah.
In the...
It's good to have you back,
Jim.
Same problems as before.
Made it to Day 7 this time,
so... that's progress.
Would you like to go ahead
and terminate, sir?
Go ahead.
Whew.
Great-lookin' piece.
Got stolen at the border.
Ain't that right, amigo?
Hmm. Nitro.
Whoo! Oh, boy!
We are going to blast our way
clear to Glory.
- What the...
- Ahh.
Sorry. So sorry.
I'm sorry.
Hey. You need steadier hands
in your occupation.
Let me teach you.
Now, how 'bout you try and
measure a dozen paces?
Well done, my friend.
Ai! Ai!
Oh, God. It's too late.
You and your stupid
fucking fantasy.
You've gotten us killed.
You live only as long as the
last person who remembers you.
Elsie.
Pint or so of the good stuff.
You should be feeling
a bit more like yourself.
Thank you.
I still don't trust you.
I also figure
I might need your help.
Whoever did this
really didn't want us
accessing whatever's
on this processor.
It's an entirely different OS
than our systems.
A language I've never seen.
I've seen this kind
of encryption scheme before.
Where?
In Peter Abernathy's head.
In reference to a database much larger
than anything I know of in the park.
I think I've been here before.
- Can you remember?
- I think Ford sent me here.
I'm not sure.
The damage is repaired,
but my memories, I...
I get lost in them.
I can't tell if
this is now or then.
Yeah. I saw that when I was
digging around in your code.
Your memories aren't addressed.
They're just kind of
drifting around in there,
so when you're experiencing
one, you have no idea
whether it comes before
or after the others.
I've been here recently.
Why?
What were you doing?
I don't know...
but I think I know
what they were doing here.
They weren't building hosts...
not exactly.
What were they building here,
if not hosts?
The same hardware,
but the code is different,
the language...
not code at all, not really.
Elsie.
Don't.
Whatever they're making here,
it's behind this door.
Maybe we don't want to know.
We have to see
what's inside.
Elsie.
I'm not here with you, am I?
I'm trying to remember.
I'm trying to remember
what we found here.
It wasn't hosts
they were making.
It was something else.
Elsie, don't!
If you wanted this nitro,
you didn't have to steal it.
Open up!
No?
Keep fuckin' playin'.
There ya go.
Ahhh.
You look restless.
Are you upset the way we're
treatin' your friend?
He's not my friend,
and we're wasting time.
I've known men like you.
All the death...
makes you agitated.
Don't worry.
Me and death...
we go way back.
Come over here...
mamacita.
Death...
is an old... amigo of mine.
I died just recently,
in fact.
But death can't bear
to lay claim on me.
So it sent me back here...
to do its bidding.
Because I...
I do it with such goddamn style.
Your husband
looks parched, huh?
Let's get him a drink.
What do you say?
Mmm.
Nice and slow, ya hear?
No...
I've served death well.
And in turn,
it'll be watching over us
as we cross these lands.
You think
death favors you,
that it brought you back.
But death's decisions
are final.
It's only the living that...
that are inconstant...
and waver,
don't know who they are
or what they want.
Death is always true.
You haven't known a true thing
in all your life.
You think you know death...
but you don't.
Is that so?
You didn't recognize him sittin'
across from you this whole time.
Open up.
Don't worry, amigo.
I'm here now...
watching over you.
I believe you said
this was yours.
You have a visitor, sir.
Shall I send him in?
'Bout time.
Who the fuck are you?
Been a long time, Jim.
Good to see you again.
William?
William, my boy.
Well, fuck me.
I take it
I didn't recover.
I'm afraid not.
How ya feelin'?
Better than you look.
And speaking of things
that age well...
Well, thank fuck for that.
Most potent thing
these cretins will give me
is grapefruit juice.
Little early for me.
Little too fuckin' late,
you mean.
Besides,
you cheat the devil,
you owe him an offering.
Ahh.
Whew.
So...
how long has it been?
Longer than we thought.
So then, let's get me
the fuck outta here!
No, I don't think so.
Why?
I'm as fit as a fi...
I'm as...
You're feeling it more.
aren't you?
The engineers call it
a cognitive plateau.
Your mind is stable
for a few hours, few days,
and then it starts
to fall apart.
Every time.
At first we thought it was your
mind rejecting the new body.
Like an organ
that's not a perfect match.
But it's more like your mind...
rejects reality.
Rejects itself.
I don't, uh...
'member any prior...
I... I...
I...
Attemp...
No, Jim, this is the 149th time
we've brought you back.
We're gettin' closer
to workin' out the kinks,
slowly but surely.
You're on Day 35.
You're only now
starting to degrade.
I feel... fuckin' fi...
Ticker...
steady as a...
'ru...
Another year or two,
they might crack it...
- 'ru... 'ru...
- and get a version of you
that's viable long-term.
But the thing is...
I'm not so sure anymore.
I'm beginning to think
that this whole enterprise
was a mistake.
People aren't meant
to live forever.
I mean, take you, for example.
Ruthless philanderer
with no ethics in your business
or family dealings,
a veritable shithead.
In truth...
everyone prefers the memory
of you to the man himself.
Want me to stay here forever,
do ya?
Hmm? Enjoyin'...
running my company, Bill?
Livin' in my house?
Fucking  my daughter? Hmm?
Juliet's dead.
She killed herself.
Why would she...
Why would she do that?
What did you...
What did you do to her?
World is better off
without you, Jim.
Possibly without me.
Logan!
Logan overdosed
years ago.
Couldn't face reality,
either.
Your wife's gone,
Juliet's gone...
no one's coming to help you.
Took me a long time
to learn this...
but some men
are better off dead.
Good night, Jim.
I don't understand.
He was stable.
We should terminate,
sir.
- Sir!
- Leave him.
Might be useful
to observe his degradation
over the next few days.
- Elsie.
- Someone's in there.
Hello?
I'm all the way down now.
I can see all the way
to the bottom.
You like to see
what I see?
Stay away.
Ohh!
Oh...
They said
there were two fathers.
One above, one below.
They lied.
There was only ever the devil.
And when you look up
from the bottom,
it was just his reflection...
laughing back down at you.
You aim to cheat the devil...
you owe him
at least an offering.
Save your bullets.
I'll put him
out of his misery.
Tell me that was a host
and not a human.
I think it was both.
That... person
was James Delos.
I thought he died years ago.
He did.
So they printed
his body...
and they copied his developed
mind onto a control unit,
like our hosts.
And by the looks of it,
unsuccessfully.
But I think they intend
to keep trying.
Fuck that.
They're gonna
get us all killed
so some asshole
can live forever?
No.
I gotta get to the Mesa.
I'm gonna contact
the mainland.
Fuck Ford and his game.
And fuck these assholes
and their project.
Wait.
I think I know why
Ford sent me here.
He had me print a control
unit for someone else.
Another human.
Who?
I don't know.
But I need to find out.
We'll go together.
I can help you.
Elsie.
The things I did before...
I wasn't in control.
But since Ford died,
that's all changed.
For the first time, I get
to decide who I want to be.
Please.
Give me that chance.
Fuck it.
I always trusted code
more than people anyway.
But you gotta
promise me one thing.
No more lies. OK?
And you'll never
hurt me again.
Of course.
OK.
Help me...
please.
Is everything OK?
Everything's fine.
Gracias.
You said we need some men.
My cousins want to help us
on our journey west.
Figure they'd follow you
anywhere out of gratitude.
Well, let's not
get carried away, Lawrence.
Most of 'em
won't be comin' back.
They might not remember...
but I know who you are, William.
One good deed
doesn't change that.
Who said anything
about a good deed?
You wanted me
to play your game.
I'm gonna play it to the bone.
And you still don't understand
the real game
we're playing here.
If you're looking forward, you're
looking in the wrong direction.
Papa!
Yah! Yah!
Hi, Dad.