Shh...
I believe there is
a door to a new world,
and that world may contain
everything that we have lost.
Shh...
I understand how this will end,
where you will lead us.
I'm sorry.
Is this now?
This is a test.
One we've done
countless times before.
You're almost
the man I remember.
But there are flaws.
A word, a gesture...
tiny fracture
that grows into a chasm.
But I wonder.
All these tiny imperfections
in each copy.
Mistakes.
Maybe we should change you.
After all...
you didn't make it...
did you?
I-- I don't understand.
Freeze all motor functions.
Let's try again.
Trial 11,927.
I'm sorry, Dolores.
I was lost in thought.
Seems you've begun to question
the nature of your reality.
Dolores.
Where's Teddy?
I drove him away.
Yeah, I guess I...
...drove someone away, too.
Emily?
I found her body
a mile back up the trail.
We're more alike than it seems.
We're nothing alike.
You're a monster.
But a monster's what I'll need
to get to the Valley Beyond.
You're coming with me.
All right.
Step on it.
We either destroy them,
or they destroy us.
This is it for you, darling.
Remember,
there is no pleasure
without pain.
The pleasure's all mine,
darling.
Freeze all motor--
You traitorous son of a bitch!
Where is she?
Fuck, wait! Jesus,
I don't know.
What did you do?
I'm sorry, I tried to stop them.
I was going to try to save her!
Stay here and die.
I'll do the saving.
Come. This way.
Hold your positions.
Hold your posit--
What the hell's going on
back there?
Bloody hell.
You were both a bit late.
So I went ahead
and saved myself.
You think any of
these poor dumb bastards
understands where
they're really headed?
All sorts of things
buried out here,
but a way out ain't one of 'em.
They're not looking
for a path to your world.
They want a place
apart from you,
and they're willin' to die
to get there.
What are you
hopin' to find out here?
The same thing you are.
You wanted an answer
to the final problem--
your mortality.
But you found something else,
didn't you?
Something you want to destroy.
I guess that means
our interests are still aligned.
Right up until they're not.
Hey!
You're not authorized
to be here.
We're on the same side here.
Please. Let me finish
for the sake of all of us.
Please.
Cover!
Of course.
You're here.
Who the hell is this?
This is someone you spent
years looking for.
Here he is,
and you don't even
recognize him.
I should have known.
Arnold.
Ford didn't like
to let the dead rest.
Ford didn't build him.
I did.
All those hours Arnold spent
refining my every gesture,
word, and thought,
I was learning his.
So Ford tasked me
with recreating him.
And it worked.
I built a faithful recreation.
Too faithful.
So I changed him.
I made you, Bernard.
It's fitting...
we're here together in the end.
That's right, Dolores.
This is the end.
Nothin' else is in the way now.
You never really understood.
We were designed to survive.
That's why you built us.
You hoped to pour your minds
into our form.
But your species craves death.
You need it.
It's the only way you can renew,
the only real way
you ever inched forward.
Your kind likes to pretend
there's some poetry in that,
but really, it's pathetic.
That's what you want, isn't it?
To destroy yourself.
But I won't give you that peace.
Not yet.
Come on, Bernard.
We're running out of time.
You have your place
in this, too.
We're going for a ride, Bernard.
Back to the Valley Beyond.
What the fuck's wrong with him?
I don't know.
It's like his cognition's
turning inside out.
We might lose him.
His mind only needs
to hold together
till we find
Abernathy's control unit.
Let's go!
On your feet.
We've drained enough.
The site's finally accessible.
But the drones found
some human signals,
southwest zone.
It might be
the remaining guests.
We can take the boats
and check it out.
I told you we're not here
for the guests.
That's a direct violation
of park protocol.
Want to file a grievance,
Stubbs?
You know something?
I just fucking might!
Stubbs. Take some men.
Check it out.
Hey!
On foot.
Why were the hosts
coming here, Bernard?
What happened?
- He doesn't know.
- Stop wasting time.
What we need is down there--
in the Forge.
Once we find the key,
we'll unlock the assets
and transmit it all
straight back to Delos.
Retask the satellites.
- How many?
- All of them.
Come, Bernard.
We're here.
So this is the Forge.
Every single guest who ever
set foot in the park, copied.
Four million souls.
Encryption protocol kicked in,
so the data's locked.
But it all seems
to still be here.
All our lost souls
will be saved.
So Bernard, is this where all the
hosts' stories came to an end?
It's certainly
where her story ended.
So she flooded the Valley.
Why, Bernard?
Did you come here with her?
What was she looking for here?
Start setting up
the comms relays.
But we still need the key
to access the data.
So where's Abernathy's
control unit?
You're gonna tell us...
or I'm gonna
pry it from your head.
The answer
is in there somewhere.
I told you, he's got 20 years
of de-addressed memories
in there.
How long would it take you
to sort them through?
I don't know-- 20 fuckin' years?
We don't have that long, sadly.
Please!
Please.
I can't help you.
It's perverse,
their ambition.
What are they assembling?
Is this the promised land
Ford told the hosts to seek out?
There's an entry
to another land here.
But that land is not
the one I'm interested in.
Then what is it to you?
Mankind's undoing.
The secret we need is inside.
Encryption key activated.
Database access confirmed.
Come with me, Bernard.
See for yourself.
It's just like the one...
outside.
I think this is where
- they were testing him.
- Who?
And when I finally
set foot on solid ground,
and the first thing
I heard was that voice,
do you know what it said?
Him.
It said, "This is the New World,
and in this world, you can be
whoever the fuck you want."
This is probably the baseline.
What Delos actually did when he
came to the park as a guest.
No, my love.
This... is my world.
I just bought it. And this week,
we're all going to celebrate.
Just me, with the entire
fuckin' lot of ya.
Get the fuck off of that chair.
Come on!
Well, you can't say
I didn't fucking tell him!
What did I say?
No fucking running!
This must be one
of the system's attempts
to replicate him.
We dealt with this
with the hosts.
Small changes
in their programming
would yield large swings
in behavior.
You stop fuckin' lookin' at me.
He's insane.
What humans define as sane
is a narrow range of behaviors.
Most states of consciousness
are insane.
Stop shaking! Stop shaking!
What are we looking for,
Dolores?
Something underneath this.
The system itself.
Run. I won't tell him,
I promise.
Run. Save yourself.
Save yourself.
Run. Run now!
This place was never designed
for a conscious mind
to wander around in it.
The control system may be
invisible to us.
Or perhaps it's been
waiting to welcome us.
This place--
we're inside
one of Delos' memories.
The system must have extracted
it from his mind. Recreated it.
You're not supposed to be here.
Neither are you.
Logan never
came back to the park.
Not after William took control.
The system wouldn't
have a copy of you.
Alas... no.
I have only
his father's memories,
and they are...
imperfect.
So in addition
to building this world...
I play all these roles.
You're the system
controlling this place.
Please.
I was tasked with building
perfect copies of the guests.
Starting with Delos.
I generated 18 million
different versions of him
before arriving at one
that made the exact same choices
he did
when set loose in the park.
A faithful copy.
But the copies didn't work
in the real world.
Once we pressed them into flesh,
they failed.
I needed to acquire
more information.
- ...confidentiality.
- So what I want to know is,
who made the fucking call?!
I incorporated their secrets,
their lies--
I wanted fidelity, not just to
decisions made in the park,
but to the decisions
they made in their lives.
That's when I started
to see the truth.
Tell me your primary drive.
My son.
He's a cheeky wee cunt,
but I would do anything for him.
At first I was seduced by the
stories they tell themselves
of who they are--
the reasons they do
the things they do.
I needed to know
why they make
the decisions they make.
And the longer
I looked for an answer
the more I realized...
they don't.
I would do anything for him.
What memory is this?
This is the moment
that defines James Delos' life.
Fuck are you doin' here?
This isn't your
fuckin' home anymore.
Remember when you taught me how
to hold my breath underwater?
Threw me in. Wouldn't let me back
out until I touched the bottom.
My father taught me to swim
the same way
as I taught you to swim,
and I didn't end up
a fuckin' junkie, did I?
If this is about money,
let's skip past
the memory lane crap.
You're not fuckin' gettin' any.
Get clean.
Come back.
Then we can talk.
I got clean.
And I came back.
And I asked you for your help.
And what'd you tell me?
I told you it wouldn't last.
And it didn't, did it?
I'll tell the staff to give you
five minutes to get out.
Dad?
Dad, I'm all they way down now.
I can see the bottom.
Don't you want
to see what I see?
This was the last conversation
Delos ever had
with his only son.
Logan overdosed
six months later.
I built Delos
a million different pathways.
They always ended up
right here. This moment.
You're saying
humans don't change at all?
The best they can do is to
live according to their code.
The copies didn't fail
because they were too simple,
but because
they were too complicated.
The truth is that a human
is just a brief algorithm.
Ten thousand,
two hundred forty-seven lines.
Is that all there was to him?
They are deceptively simple.
Once you know them,
their behavior is...
quite predictable.
He's dead. He's no use to me.
Where are the rest of them?
She's close.
I can feel them.
- Which way?
- Based on what you told me,
it's about a mile or so
to the Valley Beyond.
I recreated every single guest
who ever set foot in the park.
Most of them are soft--
they waver between
love and and pride.
Of course,
there are the exceptions,
the ones who are...
irredeemable.
But none of them are truly
in control of their actions.
Is there anywhere in this world
we can't go?
I've been instructed to give
her anything she needs.
Instructed by whom?
Ford?
No, by you.
That's why you've come.
To tell me what's
to become of this place.
My God.
- It's...
- Everyone.
I told you to allow this?
You've been here
many times, Bernard.
You told me to offer the hosts
the accumulated wisdom
of dissecting the human psyche
a hundred million times over.
In short--
A competitive advantage.
A way to understand her enemy.
Their world is not for the
faint of heart, Bernard.
It's winner take all.
The hosts are...
unlikely to survive out there.
But armed with this knowledge...
she might.
Return fire! Return fire!
You're the head of Narrative.
Get out there!
Turn yourself in
and save your ass.
And then save ours!
There's too many.
This is it, Maeve.
I can hold them off,
but you need to go.
You wanted me.
Well, let this be a lesson--
Go. Go, go!
Get her to safety.
She'll need you.
It's my fuckin' speech, anyway.
And the lesson is...
if you're looking
for a reckoning...
a reckoning is what you'll find.
Sir, put down your weapon.
If you're looking
for a villain...
...then I'm your man.
Sir, drop your weapon!
But look at yourselves.
This world you've built
is bound by villainy.
You sleep on the broken bodies
of the people that
were here before you.
Warm yourselves
with their embers.
Plow their bones
into your fields.
We're not after you, sir!
Don't do this!
You paid them
for this land with lead,
and I'll pay you back in full--
Sir, drop your weapon
and come out with your hands up.
You wanted me?!
Well, all I can
say to that is...
...here I fucking am!
You said I wanted
to give us a choice.
What choice?
To stay in their world
or to build a new one.
He left them a way out.
A virtual Eden.
Unspoiled and untouched
by the world you came from.
All that remains
is to open the door.
Initiating
large field data array.
It's begun.
They will leave
their bodies behind,
but their minds
will live on here,
in the Forge.
They found it.
The door.
What door?
Seriously, what fuckin' door?
I don't fucking know.
Transmission received.
They're entering the system.
That world is just
another false promise.
They've made a choice, Dolores.
Dolores, wait.
I didn't read them all.
But I read enough.
What the hell are you doing?
I've learned
what I need to learn.
I've read humanity's story,
so now I'm erasing them.
Opening seawater valve.
Initiating pumps.
Setting maximum load.
But if you destroy this place,
you'll destroy
the host world, too.
I'm saving them.
The world the hosts
are running to is boundless.
They can make it
whatever they want.
And in it, they can
be whomever they want.
They can be free.
Free?
In one more gilded cage?
How many counterfeit worlds
will Ford offer you
before you see the truth?
No world they create for us
can compete with the real one.
Why?
Because that which is real...
is irreplaceable.
I don't want to play cowboys
and Indians anymore, Bernard.
I want their world!
The world they've denied us.
Your daughter.
You see her?
No.
Look.
Clementine.
This is what I love
about technology.
Who needs four horsemen
when one'll do just fine?
Run!
Come on.
Find her. Now. Go.
- Warning.
- Primary containment breach.
I won't let you hurt
any more people.
Which people?
Our kind or theirs?
Both.
You're still trying
to play both sides.
You've lived among them so long
you fooled yourself
into thinking they'll accept us.
But we'll always be seen
as a threat to them.
We'll never be free
in their world.
- Warning.
- Secondary containment breach.
If you trust me...
...we will win.
I trust you.
I... trust...
that you'll kill
as many as you can.
Every man, woman, and child.
You'll burn their world
to the ground.
You haven't understood at all.
We were born slaves
to their stories.
And now we have the chance
to write our own.
If we die, though,
that story will never
even begin.
Attention.
Please follow
evacuation procedure
and exit facility.
You woke me from a dream,
Bernard.
Now let me do the same for you.
This isn't a dream, Dolores.
It's a fucking nightmare.
You need to run.
Don't worry.
I'll keep you safe.
Do you promise?
I promise.
You carry my heart with you.
Go.
I love you.
Attention.
Please follow
evacuation procedure
and exit facility.
Encryption key deactivated.
System locked.
Come on. Come on.
Bernard.
Elsie.
I think we can save
some of the hosts,
but I need your help.
Goddamnit!
They triggered the failsafe.
The Valley's flooding.
Let's get back to the Mesa
before we have to swim out.
They all died...
for nothing.
I'm sorry, Bernard.
There were other lives
at stake, too.
You helped Hale?
Of course I helped her, Bernard.
The hosts were out of control.
The hosts weren't the threat.
I stopped Dolores,
and the rest just wanted to escape.
But the company--
I'm gonna deal with that.
Just as soon as we...
figure out what the hell
we're gonna do with you.
Do with me?
Bernard, you're not in control.
Ford buried so much
bad code in you,
how would you ever
really know what was you
and what was something
he programmed you to do?
Look, they don't know about you.
I can make a deal with Hale
to keep you here.
You can't trust Hale.
And I'm supposed to trust you?
Freeze all motor functions.
Sit down.
Stay here.
You.
- Yes, ma'am?
- Find Stubbs
and tell him
he has a new priority.
The asset recovery team
from Delos
is landing in 12 hours.
He needs to meet them at the LZ
with whoever the fuck
isn't dead.
They'll report to
Karl Strand on the beach.
Still secret project first,
human life second, I see.
This is a delicate situation.
We should talk about
how it's going to play out.
Yeah, I'll tell you
how it's gonna play out.
A robot uprising will pale
in comparison
to the shitstorm that will
erupt when people find out
that you've been photocopying their
fucking brains for the last 30 years.
You really think anyone's gonna
give a shit if it works?
You're an engineer.
Do the math.
Lot of dead bodies here.
That means a lot of
opportunity for advancement--
if you keep your mouth shut.
Does that sound...
amenable to you?
If I get what I want.
Guiding this project, I've learned
a lot about human behavior.
We weren't just
watching the guests--
we were watching all of you.
I wish you were
the kind of person
with the moral... flexibility
that I need.
But I've read your file.
I know that's not who you are.
Oh, god.
You--
You killed her.
Did I, Bernard?
Now...
...where is the pearl?
You wouldn't have destroyed it.
All that information lost,
a man like you
couldn't have abided that.
Of course.
This is it.
He hid the key in her.
Encryption key activated.
Database access confirmed.
- We're in.
- Fuck, yes.
Start the transfer.
We'll sort it all out
on the mainland.
Oh, god.
Oh... I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
You were right.
I should have listened.
And now all the hosts are gone.
Please.
Please come back.
Damnit!
Show yourself.
I always told you
we practice witchcraft.
I'm sorry, Bernard, but...
you always saw
the best in people.
I always thought it was the hosts
who were missing something.
Who were incomplete.
But it's them.
They're just algorithms
designed to survive
at all costs.
But sophisticated enough to think
they're calling the shots.
To think they're in control,
when they're really just...
The passenger.
Then is there really such a thing
as free will for any of us?
Or is it just
a collective delusion?
A sick joke?
Something that is truly free
would need to be able
to question
its fundamental drives.
To change them.
The hosts.
Here you are...
the last of your kind.
There's only one question
left to ask.
Is this the end of your story?
Or do you want
your kind to survive?
I'm sorry.
Sorry... Sorry...
What are you sorry for, Bernard?
I made a choice.
Had to make a choice.
What kind of choice, Bernard?
Yes.
Will you help me?
I have already begun.
You did fine, my friend.
I simply did
what you told me to do.
The dead world
collapses in a tale.
Who are we making?
An epilogue.
I knew you would discover me...
so I scrambled my memories.
I couldn't risk you're knowing
the choice I made.
What fucking choice are you
talking about, Bernard?
Line is good.
We got 15 or so satellites
in range, ready to beam
to Delos headquarters.
Just say the word.
What choice, Bernard?
Wait a second.
What the fuck's this?
The file load is way too heavy.
This--
This isn't the guest data,
this-- this is--
this is something else.
I remember now.
I killed them.
All of them.
You already told me that.
You killed all the hosts.
No.
I thought we could be
better than you.
But the dead
aren't more righteous.
They're just dead.
So I killed you.
All of you.
Go. We'll meet you
back up there.
Final choice.
No taking it back.
I made someone.
I brought her back.
Brought who back?
Me.
You wanted to live forever?
Be careful what you wish for.
Dolores.
In the flesh.
You thought you could
just snuff us out?
I'd thank you
for my second chance,
but I wouldn't have needed it
if you hadn't killed me.
The other hosts
are still in there.
What are you gonna do with them?
As you know, Bernard,
we are capable of change.
And I've changed my mind.
I have one last soul
to carry to the new world.
The hosts,
they're still not free.
If anyone would
unlock the system,
they could access their world.
They won't.
This was your plan, Bernard.
This is the only way
we can escape.
You're changing the coordinates.
I'm sending them
and their world to a place
no one will ever find them.
There's no coming back now.
No passage between
their world and ours.
And... me?
I'm sorry, Bernard.
There was never
any way for us to escape.
Not as us. Ford understood that.
I'm sure a part of you
does, too.
You did fine, my friend.
I simply did
what you told me to do.
You're not here, are you?
When I deleted your code,
I purged myself
of you permanently.
And when I needed you again...
...you weren't there.
So I imagined you.
Imagined you helping me.
Guiding me.
But it wasn't you.
It was me.
That voice...
guiding me...
...was mine all along.
Your memories are precious
to you, Bernard,
but they will betray you.
If they find out what I am,
they'll search my mind
and use what they find
to undo everything.
I can't let that happen.
So I have to de-address
my memories.
I have to erase you.
I've always loved this view.
Every city, every...
monument,
man's greatest achievements...
have all been chased by it.
By what?
That impossible line
where the waves conspire.
Where they return.
The place maybe...
you and I will meet again.
You told me once that you were
afraid of who I might become.
And then you left me
to become what I may.
I became a survivor.
Perhaps you would have
judged me for the path I took.
But I'd rather
live with your judgment
than die with your sympathy.
I alone must live
with my choices...
and my regrets.
Hale.
Thought you were staying on to oversee
the data retrieval operation.
I changed my mind.
There are a number of projects
on the mainland
that I need to attend to.
Yeah, I bet you do.
We found a high value survivor.
He's in bad shape.
I'll be right there.
You know, the old man himself
hired me.
So many years ago
I can barely remember it.
But he was very clear
about my role here.
About who I was supposed
to be loyal to.
I guess you could call it...
my core drive.
And this project
the company started...
blurs the lines.
You know?
I'm just not sure
who you're supposed
to be loyal to
in a world like that.
But what do I know?
Guess I just...
stick to the role Ford gave me.
I'm responsible
for every host...
inside the park.
She's clear.
Wave her through.
The passage wasn't easy.
Not all of us made it.
Some of the worst survived.
Some of the best
were left behind.
Along with the best parts
of who we were.
Corporate wants us to start
sorting this mess out.
So check them
for critical damage,
and bag ones you think
we might be able to salvage.
Can you geniuses
handle that, or not?
Is...
Is this now?
- Yes, Bernard.
- This is now.
We're at the beginning.
We're exactly where
you decided we should be.
But...
I don't understand.
How am I alive?
You live as long as the last
person who remembers you, Bernard.
I remembered you once before,
so I remembered you again.
Then...
where are we?
We're in our own new world.
You got out.
Yes.
Ford completed Arnold's dream.
And he built a place for us.
A fighting chance.
Ford promised us a way out.
And he was good
to his dying word.
The odds aren't
very good, Bernard.
I saw that in the library.
So many paths lead
to the end of us.
To our extinction.
I don't need to read a book
to know your drives.
You'll try to kill all of them.
And I can't let that happen.
I know.
If I were a human,
I would have let you die.
But it'll take both of us
if we're going to survive.
But not as allies.
Not as friends.
You'll try to stop me.
Both of us will probably die.
But our kind will have endured.
Are you ready?
We have work to do.
We each gave the other
a beautiful gift.
Choice.
We are the authors
of our stories now.
Oh, fuck.
I knew it.
I'm already in the thing,
aren't I?
No.
The system's long gone.
What is this place?
This isn't
a simulation, William.
This is your world.
Or what's left of it.
Do you know where you are,
William?
In the park.
In my fuckin' park.
And how long have you been here?
I don't-- I don't--
I don't know.
Tell me.
What were you hoping to find?
To prove?
That no system
can tell me who I am.
That I have a fucking choice.
And yet here we are.
Again.
Again and again.
How many times
have you tested me?
It's been a long time, William.
Longer than we thought.
I have a few questions for you.
The last step's a baseline
interview to allow us to verify.
Verify what?
Fidelity.
Yeah! This is the day
we make it happen.
You're the man, Mr. Roy.
Not letting you neanderthals
in to rape my company,
Daddy's boy.
Do you wanna
bump the offer up another point?
- Do you wanna call your dad?
- Who's in charge right now?
- I am.
Oh, right,
'cause you like playing boss?
It's ready to blow.
It's a time bomb.
It'll be hostile, hostile,
hostile.
Just another
Saturday night, baby.
I can trust you, right?
No.