You are due to hang at
9:00 tomorrow morning...
...22 hours from now.
Do you wish to make
a new statement
about the murder
of David Blakely,
one that may materially
affect your legal situation?
Yes.
I had been ill for two weeks.
The miscarriage?
David had been so sorry.
Are you watching me sleep?
Listening to you snore.
I don't snore.
I want to be woken up by your
snoring the rest of my life.
Soppy little fool.
Is your stomach still painful?
It's fine. Doctor says
it's healing well.
Good.
'Cause I'm taking
you out tonight.
- Mm.
- Clean slate.
No more fighting. No more...
Cinema cleaning girls?
She was an usherette.
I do have some self-respect.
Neither one of us
has been perfect.
But from now on,
we're going to be a
boring old married couple,
you in a housecoat,
me in slippers.
And occasionally we'll
talk of how young,
foolish we used to be.
Promise?
Yes.
See you tonight.
Be ready at 8:00.
Findlaters' residence.
Is David there?
No.
Hello?
And who was that girl?
Look. David isn't
here, all right?
I got Desmond to drive
me to the Findlaters'.
Wait here.
- I want to speak to David.
- He's not here.
His car's outside.
I know he's in there
with some girl.
- That's our nanny.
- You did this, didn't you?
You threw her at him.
- David! David!
- He's left you, Ruth.
- You won't see him ever again.
- You're lying.
I have only ever
told you the truth.
You've never wanted to hear it.
He can't just walk away...
with everything in ruins.
I know you need someone to blame
for the way your
life has turned out.
You know, I had you down as
a dangerous sort of woman,
a predator who set a
trap for a naive boy.
But I was wrong.
You're just... a mess.
A wretched, ungovernable,
emotionally incontinent mess.
A whirlwind of
shabby destruction
bringing everyone
else down with you.
My job.
My savings.
My daughter.
My unborn child.
All gone because of him.
He does not get to walk
away without saying a word.
He doesn't! I have
to speak to him!
- David!
- There's nothing to say.
Then I want my key back
for Egerton Gardens.
- I want my key back.
- I'll have it sent to you.
You cannot do this!
You can't do this!
David!
David, I know
you're in... David!
I felt I had to do something...
...anything... to
make him listen.
Ruth? Ruth!
- David!
- That's enough.
- That's enough!
- He's in there with a girl.
He's laughing at me!
Does he have a key
to Egerton Gardens,
the place I rented for
you, your new start?!
Has he been there all along?
What are you looking at?
- David! David!
- Get in the car, Ruth!
In the car, Ruth!
I had to go back the next day.
I was determined to
make David speak to me.
Their plan, what they
had wanted all along...
to get David away from
me, without looking back,
without acknowledging what he
had done to me... it'd worked.
Are you all in? Are you all in?
All night I sat there
and thought about
the last two years.
When I had first met David, I
was managing a successful club.
I had two beautiful children.
I had money in the
bank, admirers...
...a lovely flat.
And now all I had was
a bedsitting room.
No money. No job.
And a man who swore
he loved me one day
and then beat and
abused me the next.
A man who was relieved when
I lost the child he fathered.
I thought, and I thought.
All the things he
had said to me,
all the things he
had done to me.
And I just felt pure rage.
I don't know what to do.
- I'll make you some coffee.
- I don't want any coffee.
Well, tea, then!
I don't want any fucking tea!
I just... wish he was dead.
I wish he was dead.
I wish he would jump
in the lake and drown
and I could just be free.
We could be free.
I just want to be
done with all of it.
Do you?
Whose idea was it
to get the gun?
I wouldn't know how to use it.
I wouldn't know how to aim it.
I'll show you.
I need the permanent
undersecretary of state.
He's at Ascot.
Well, get him bloody
back from Ascot.
What message should I give?
Tell him Ruth Ellis isn't
going to hang tomorrow.
Mrs Ellis is accusing
Desmond Cussen
of conspiracy to murder?
Yes.
The execution will
have to be postponed
while he's interviewed.
If charges are
brought against him,
Ruth Ellis will be
the principal witness.
She will be needed
to give evidence.
And that's to say nothing
of her own conviction,
which can now be
regarded as unsafe.
She was drunk. She was
influenced by this man.
I anticipate a retrial
at the very least.
You are not in fact a...
criminal lawyer, Mr Mishcon.
You are a divorce solicitor?
Yes.
Well, the undersecretary is
on his way back from Ascot.
I will brief him,
and doubtless he will wish to
speak to the home secretary.
But the execution
will be postponed
while all this is investigated?
I can give no such assurance.
Not on the strength
of this alone.
Then what would you need?
We can do nothing until
Cussen is interviewed
at the very least.
We must have some
corroborating evidence.
Until then, I'm afraid...
these are just words.
Then call Scotland Yard and
instruct them to find him now.
As I say, I will
inform my superiors.
We have 16 hours until
she is due to die.
You're right. I know
little of criminal law.
But I know how long it
takes to divorce someone.
Six months minimum
between the decrees
nisi and absolute
to ensure the
grounds are correct,
that the marriage is
truly unsalvageable.
Because a divorce is an
absolute that cannot be undone.
Your government passed that law.
And you give this woman, between
conviction and killing her,
22 days.
Call the bloody police.
Cussen left his
office 20 minutes ago.
He's on his way home.
You said it yourself, sir.
She pulled the trigger.
Doesn't matter where
she got the gun.
You did everything right.
Let's go.
Thank you for coming back.
I know I wasn't the most
gracious hostess last time.
I deserved it.
You're many things...
but you are no coward.
I wasn't when there was no hope.
Now I'm bloody petrified.
Do you remember
when you and Vicki came
to visit me in hospital
and you brought gin
and a gramophone?
Matron told us not to turn
the place into a bordello,
but by midnight, she
was absolutely smashed
and dancing with us.
I remember Vicki flashing
the geriatric ward.
And three of them
proposing to her.
We sat up on the roof and
watched the sun come up.
I wish we could do
that tomorrow morning.
Before Mr Pierrepoint.
Well, the hangman can
sod off back to his pub.
Your statement
changed everything.
You do know what
his pub is called?
- Mm?
- Help the Poor Struggler.
No!
Joy told me.
Listen.
I can try to find Desmond...
get a confession and
take it to the police.
We don't have to.
DCI Davies has been
at the Home Office
getting a rocket up his arse.
They're going to
find Desmond, Jackie.
He's going to be arrested
and charged... tonight.
So, you want to know
if I have anything else
that might help you.
As you can see, I am in no
fit state to help anyone.
But you knew.
You clearly knew about the gun.
I made certain suppositions
which have proved to be true.
And you told her to stay quiet?
You advised her to lie, to
perjure herself in Crown Court?
I was bound by client
confidentiality,
as I still am.
Mrs Ellis made me swear
not to say anything.
You may say I made the wrong
decision, and perhaps I did.
My aim was to show
that she was provoked,
not that she'd
conspired with anyone,
premeditated the whole thing.
Well, that was very
convenient for Desmond Cussen
that you took that route.
Did you make a deal with him?
Certainly not, my friend.
I suppose my problem is
that I'm not brave enough
to stand up to all of them
all, to s... to stand up to it.
- It?
- The English machine.
The whole... thundering
weight of it.
Are you talking
about a conspiracy?
Nothing so vulgar.
The machine is bigger
than any one man.
It's bigger than any...
gentlemen's club or
courtroom or police station.
It is concerned with
self-preservation above all.
And it is ruthless, you may
say, to the point of savagery,
to anyone who threatens it.
And Ruth threatens it
in every possible way.
And that is why the machine
is determined to get her.
It has been from the start.
Oh, you're drunk, man.
And this is dangerous nonsense.
This is the law,
the justice system,
the finest in the world.
And you say I'm
talking nonsense?
I was like you, you know.
I thought I was one
of the good ones,
fighting the machine.
Until I realised I'm just
a cog being ground in it.
If you know something
that could help her,
we have hours to save her life.
It's too late.
- That's Pierrepoint!
- That's the hangman!
- Murderer!
- How do you sleep at night?
Where's all your shame at?
Pierrepoint! Come back!
You bastard!
Why didn't you say anything
about Desmond Cussen before?
It seemed traitorous.
Until I realised he'd
betrayed me worse.
He promised to look after Andre?
Nothing. Not a visit.
Not a single penny.
What does Andre know?
He's been told you're in
Italy modelling swimsuits.
The MP, Mr Rogers, and his
wife, they've been very kind.
Offered to take him to the
country for a few days.
Get him away from all this.
But now we might not need to.
They tannoyed the undersecretary
of state at Ascot.
The press heard it.
Reporters camped
out at the house...
one from bloody New Zealand.
Evening papers all
saying the same thing...
a last-minute reprieve.
And there's been money
sent in by well-wishers.
Enough for you and Andre
to get away somewhere.
A new life!
Well, you'll never
need to work again.
Talk shows,
after-dinner speeches.
You're a flaming celebrity.
Evans! Bentley! Ellis!
There's hundreds of them!
Hundreds of people have
gathered this evening
outside Holloway Prison in
support of Mrs Ruth Ellis,
who is due to hang
tomorrow morning
for the murder of her
lover, David Blakely.
A nightclub hostess, Mrs
Ellis was sentenced to death
at the Old Bailey on the
21st of June this year
for killing Mr Blakely.
Lawyers for Mrs Ellis claim
that new evidence has surfaced
Implicating an unnamed person
and placing them at
the scene of the crime.
Her newly appointed
solicitor, Mr Victor Mishcon,
has submitted new evidence
to the Home Off...
This heat, it's hellish.
Let's get out of London.
Pack some things.
It's 9:00. Twelve
hours until she hangs.
Why aren't you out looking
for Desmond Cussen?
She shot him in the back, right?
Point-blank range.
An innocent bloke.
Could've been any one of us.
She deserves to
bloody swing for it.
Oh, shut up, Peter.
We looked for him, all right?
There's no answer
at Cussen's flat,
and we've driven round
the West End for hours.
I've been given two
men and half a day
to search the whole
of bloody London.
Does it really seem like
anyone wants him to be found?
Lucia, where is he?
Upstairs.
Thanks.
Desmond... Do you know
how I can find him?
You know me, Jackie.
I'm no grass.
No police. They've given up.
Please tell me, Morris.
Is he with one of your girls?
She should have asked me.
To take care of him... Blakely.
I'd have taken pleasure in it.
Ruth is in there,
waiting to die...
while you're here,
enjoying yourself.
Towel.
Hurry up!
Got reporters chasing
me night and day.
Customers deserting me.
And you want me to grass up one
of the only punters I got left?
Ruthie wanted
everything... the big job,
big, posh bloke, big
rock on her finger.
She went too far.
Took too much.
She ruined all of us.
I know you're not a bad man.
But you've done
some bad things...
to Ruth...
...to me.
This is your chance
to fix it, all of it.
Help me find him. Please.
Open the door, Desmond.
There's no police here.
You've been here all along.
I've come here as a friend to
ask you to do the right thing.
The police know you
helped kill Blakely.
You may not have
pulled the trigger,
but he is dead because of you.
She's lying... to
save her own skin.
I don't blame her, but I...
had nothing to do
with any of it.
You have one chance to
save the woman you loved.
She never loved me.
Is that why you did it?
To punish Ruth and
David together?
You knew she would be arrested.
She came to you when
she was desperate.
You could have helped her.
You should have helped her!
But instead you gave a
broken woman a loaded gun.
You know they haven't
even told Andre yet
about what is happening
to his mother?
But soon they will have to.
They will have to tell him
that she isn't in Italy,
modelling swimsuits...
...but that she's dead.
Hanged.
And he won't even be
able to visit her grave
because she will be buried with
murderers in the prison pit.
What you have done to that
child is unforgivable.
I told Ruth he should have
been at her mother's that day.
Was Andre there?
Did... Did he see something?
Make sure he gets this.
We're leaving.
Wait.
Hey! W...
Don't.
He's gone.
Of course he has.
I told the police, but he
could be anywhere by now.
He talked about Andre.
Was Andre there when
Desmond gave you the gun?
Did he see Desmond
give it to you?
Right hand on first,
left hand supporting.
Legs shoulder-width apart.
Elbows straight, not locked.
Now, this little
blade is the sight.
Get that on your target,
then squeeze the trigger.
Most importantly,
don't hold your breath
or you'll tense up... and
you won't hit the target.
Breathe.
In and out.
Nice and calm.
I can't do it.
Yes, you can.
You see?
I told you to wait in
the car. Go back! Now!
How much does he know?
He knows enough.
He's a witness.
The police need evidence
to support your statement.
We thought only Desmond
could give that.
- But Andre could.
- No. I won't.
I will not use him like that.
I will not ask that of him.
I think he knows you are here.
Of course he does.
He's a smart boy.
He doesn't believe that nonsense
about swimsuits in Italy.
Then let him talk to the police.
If he gives a statement to
the police and it fails...
...he will blame himself.
But you still have a chance...
if you ask him to do this.
He needs to tell them and the
police what he knows tonight.
I won't be long.
You will look after
him? You promise?
Whatever happens?
I swear it.
Are you quite well there, dear?
Yes, she's quite all
right, thank you.
Are you all right?
I don't know.
I'm here. I'm with you.
I love you.
I know.
I don't think I can.
Of course you can.
Four bottles of
light ale, please.
Oh, and two packets
of cigarettes.
- Come on.
- Because we're having a party
- round the corner.
- Leave the poor girl alone
It would've been rude
not to invite her.
Leave the poor girl alone.
David.
David!
Jesus C... Ruth, what are y...
No.
Christ. She's got a fucking...
Go and get help!
She killed him!
I won't be long.
Why did you have to kill him?!
Yes?
I took down your
statement this morning.
It appears that another
version was recorded, too,
by the, er, the... the prison
officer who sat with us.
In his version, you
ask Cussen for the gun.
I didn't say that.
I'm asking myself... w-why
they're focused on this version,
why they might be favouring it.
'Cause they want it
all to be over...
the protests, the
noise, the fuss,
the newspapers, the petitions,
all these people talking
about what a mess it is.
It's an embarrassment, and they
want it over and done with.
They were looking for a reason
to ignore what I told them,
to say that Desmond's
part doesn't matter.
And they found it.
They can't ignore it.
There are legal procedures.
Mr Bickford was right all along.
He said they wouldn't let me get
away with it, and they won't.
Right.
No matter what anyone
says or does now...
it won't do anything.
They are determined to put an
end to this, and they will,
tomorrow at 9:00 a.m.
I want you to call my parents
and say that Andre is to go away
with the MP, Mr Rogers,
and his wife, as planned.
You don't want him to make
a statement to police?
No. I want him out of London
and away from here immediately!
Please do it now.
Pray with us!
Our Father, Who art in heaven...
...hallowed be Thy
name, Thy kingdom come,
Thy will be done on
earth as it is in heaven.
Give us today our daily bread...
...as we forgive those...
Mrs. Ellis?
Make them stop. Quiet.
I just... want it to be over.
- Ruth, come with me.
- For thine is the kingdom...
Up we get. Up we get.
- Up we get.
- ...forever and ever.
Amen.
I thought you might like
to finally take your
beer privileges.
Is this allowed out here?
No. But what can
they do to you?
Thanks.
Not done much.
You might not believe this,
but the last few weeks have been
some of the best of my life.
You've all been so kind to me.
Calling me Mrs Ellis,
three square meals a day.
All those jam puddings.
No screaming, no fighting,
no men knocking on my door
in the middle of the night.
I've really rather
liked it here.
Can you put me through to the
governor of Holloway Prison?
Mrs Ellis.
You've come to tell me there's
not going to be a reprieve.
It's quite all right.
It's quite all right. Promise.
What time is it?
2 a.m.
Seven hours, then.
Would you like to
sit up together?
I have some brandy in my office.
Actually, I'd quite
like to get some sleep,
if you don't mind.
Thank you.
Philip Allen.
I want to speak to
the home secretary.
I insist on speaking
to him personally.
The home secretary has made
his position very clear.
And what is that position?
He says if she isn't hanged
tomorrow, she never will be.
I have practised
law for 20 years.
And until today, I would
not have thought it possible
that it should be used by
Englishmen in this way.
As a fig leaf for an
act of pure savagery!
No more prison smocks, then.
Can't say I'm sorry.
Hardy Amies.
Spent my entire first
wage from Carroll's on it.
It's lovely.
My mother was horrified.
Said I should've made do with
rayon like everybody else.
Probably should've made
do with a lot of things.
Little house in Basingstoke,
job in a typing pool,
week in Bognor with a
fat husband once a year.
I couldn't.
I wanted everything I could get
out of this life, every drop.
And I don't regret it.
Not a single moment.
Jacqueline?
I'm sorry. I tried.
They won't let me run the
story in the newspaper.
You need evidence
of what Cussen did?
I need something.
When all this is over, you
talk to Andre, her son.
How lovely.
Thank you, Joy.
Sorry.
It will calm you.
No, thank you.
Charity Taylor.
I'm so sorry, Mrs Ellis.
I just need a moment
with the undersheriff.
There's been a call
from a Miss Holmes,
claiming to be the home
secretary's office.
A reprieve. I've
tried to verify it.
No one there knows
anything about it.
A hoax?
It must be. Mustn't it?
This Miss Holmes...
I've tried two
private secretaries.
No one's heard of her.
Thank you.
I won't be needing
these any more.
One minute to, ma'am.
We can't make her
wait. It's torture.
I mean, it... it's
got to be a hoax.
Proceed.
It's all right, lass.
It's all right.
Follow me.
Don't worry, lass.
I won't hurt you.