Previously, on
"Good Girls"...
You're not supposed
to be here.
Yeah, neither are you.
This is the only way
we're gonna turn this around.
How does helping him
help me?
Saving up to run.
I'd rather have a lawyer.
We've never made you smile
like all this just did.
Because I told you,
this is what gets us out.
No, that's
what gets you off.
This whole time,
I thought he was the problem.
He's just the excuse.
Anyone who wears
a cardigan
shouldn't be doing
what he does.
- What are you, a priest?
- Just trying to help.
You got my wife shot.
I got you
your money.
Last party, I had to be
the damn go-between
for my husband
and my best friend.
I want you
out of her life.
You get us in that club,
and she'll never see me again.
- What's going on with you?
- My wife was laundering
a gang's money
through my business.
- What happened to her?
- Not a damn thing.
- You still coming to the game?
- Dude, I wouldn't miss it.
So he's back in?
- What do you want from me?
I caved.
- That Washington?
- The Queen.
I hate Canadians.
You said all we had
to do was print it.
And then drop it.
I assumed that you meant
in our country.
Mai Ian's "Dial My Number"...
♪ I'ma stop
being so gentle ♪
♪ Fill my head
with blood and anger ♪
♪ It's been two months,
I die for an answer ♪
♪ Take your phone,
dial my number ♪
♪ I'm still
and I'm waiting, sugar ♪
♪ This is more
than I can handle ♪
♪ Told you
not gon' wait no longer ♪
♪ Wish-wish-wish
I had you closer ♪
♪ If I meet you
at the corner ♪
♪ You'll see
I can be much meaner ♪
Seven's a winner.
♪ Take it, do it,
take your phone ♪
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
♪ And take your finger,
do it ♪
Okay, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Try it this way.
Okay, ready?
Ready? Ready?
♪ Dial my number
Oh, my God!
Why do you keep winning?
I'm trying not to.
I swear.
I swear to God.
I'm usually never,
ever, ever this lucky.
- All right.
- Whoo!
Give me those.
♪ I'll cut off
every single finger ♪
Bets in, ladies.
What do you think?
Hard ten.
♪ Take the phone, take
the phone, take, take, take ♪
♪ Take, take, take, take,
take, take, take, take, take ♪
take the phone ♪
♪ Take the phone,
take, take, take the phone ♪
take, take ♪
♪ Do it, do it
♪ Do, do, do it, do it
♪ Do it, take the phone,
take the phone ♪
♪ Take, take, take the phone,
♪ Take, take, dial it,
dial it, it, it, dial it ♪
♪ Dial it, it, it,
take the phone ♪
♪ Take the phone, take, take,
do it, do it ♪
♪ Take it, do it,
take it, do it ♪
♪ Take your phone,
take your phone ♪
♪ Dial my number,
dial my number ♪
*GOOD GIRLS*
Season 04  Episode 11
Episode Title: "Put It All on Two"
How would we train
thousands of pigeons?
You only need one.
One pigeon's gonna carry all
that cash across the border?
Well, not all at once.
- Thank you, ladies.
- Y'all killed it tonight.
Uh, the launch sequence
was all messed up.
- What are you talking about?
That was the best part.
And then it felt like
no one got
the crawling on the ground
part.
Hello?
Obviously an homage to Sandy B
at the end of "Gravity."
Ah, love you, guys.
- Bye.
- Bye!
Hey, what about drones?
Like the ones they use
in Guadalajara for heroin?
Well, it's easier
than training a pigeon.
Yeah. And way less range.
Plus, you better pray
for perfect weather.
They have 'em
at Hobby Lobby.
But you know,
it can fly in a storm.
Let's go tomorrow.
I'm busy.
Okay, and we can look
into your bird too.
- No, no, I... I really am busy.
I... I have plans.
- Doing what?
- Jobbie Nooner, baby.
Aren't you a little old
for that?
Can you really put an age on
the Mardi Gras of the Midwest?
That's tomorrow?
Taking a "me" day,
so sue me.
No, no, no, no, no.
You're going to a party
on a boat...
that is literally
on the border of Canada?
Yeah, my buddy Tim just got
out of rehab, and we always go.
Where you don't have to go
through customs
and there's millions of boats
filled with tons
of drunk people
who aren't paying attention
to what anyone else is doing?
Okay. Okay.
Yes, I see where you're going
with this.
And it could work.
What was your friend
in rehab for?
Meth.
But they let him
keep the boat license.
- When do we set sail?
- You going on a boat?
- Uh, yeah, yeah.
For a girls' trip.
Where?
- Detroit River.
- Why?
Girl stuff.
- Pedicures.
- Waxing.
It's like
a day spa/sunset cruise.
Sounds shady.
I think it's how they dodge
all those health
department codes.
Yeah, is this one of those
"spa days" that
ends up with a bullet
in her other knee?
I'm just looking out
for my wife.
A little self-care
never hurt anybody.
I would never let anything
happen to my maid of honor.
That a promise?
Oh, we have a deal.
Mm-hmm.
Well, I think y'all look great.
Well, tell that to the alpaca
sitting on my crotch.
Well, it got him out of here,
didn't it?
- Hey.
What... what's all this?
I thought we can
all eat together.
- Why?
- For a change.
- Ah.
Well, Ben's at his dad's.
Well,
then it's dinner a deux.
Okay.
It's a pretty fancy setup
for tortillas and soy sauce.
- Not what we're having.
- That's all I have.
Lemon chicken piccata.
- What?
You made this?
Well, it's not Olive Garden,
but it's the best
with what I could find.
Jeez.
What the hell is this?
A white carrot?
Parsnip, and...
- Mmm.
- A few other root veggies.
- It's so good.
- Thanks, man.
- No, thank you, man.
- No, no.
Thank you for letting me crash.
No, thank you
for picking all this up.
NBD.
I mean,
must have been expensive.
Not at all.
I mean, last I checked,
food was not free.
Well, maybe you're just not
looking in the right place.
- Kevin...
- Mm.
I went a little heavy
on the rosemary.
Where did you get this food?
- Kroger.
- Oh, thank Jesus.
Yeah, they throw out
the best stuff.
Like even before it goes bad.
Eww.
What is wrong with you?
It's fine.
It's trash food.
- You never would have known.
- Mm, except I do.
So if I paid,
would it taste better?
I mean, I guess not.
- Then what's the difference?
- The amount of E. coli.
- I washed it.
- Where, in the toilet?
I thought you were
cooler than this.
Why, because I'm not down
with gourmet dumpster diving?
No, because you think money
makes everything better.
- Doesn't it?
- All right. Yeah, sure.
If you want to live
for what you don't have.
- Oh, boy, here we go.
- This treadmill you're on...
- Excuse me for wanting more.
- Won't get you anywhere.
It's called
the American dream, baby.
Okay, well,
while you're dreaming,
you're also sleeping through a
pretty choice piece of chicken.
At least I won't
have hepatitis A, B, or C.
Whatever.
I won't tell you
where I got that.
Hey, guys. I thought we were
meeting down at the park.
Oh, guys can wait.
You're not going anywhere
with that derailer.
Let me see that.
Hey, look.
Sorry, I'm doing everything
I can with that night cream.
Oh, I get it.
Guys don't really like stuff
on their face before bed.
Right?
Gets stuff all over your pillow and...
Not why we're here.
Oh.
The other night
at the meeting...
- Yeah, I overshared.
- It was beautiful, Dean.
You're going through
a lot right now, you know?
You got a lawyer?
Not one that's gonna
keep me out of jail?
Well, you do now.
Oh.
Oh, that's so cool.
Never lost a case.
Which is
why
I definitely
can't afford him.
Don't worry about it.
Dean,
you're family now.
That bitch has
done enough to you.
Hi, boys.
Pulled them
out of the freezer
so they got that
big ice cube you like.
Thanks.
Do you guys want a refill?
- No, we're fine.
- Good.
Don't forget to wear
the reflective stuff.
We'll look out for him.
Oh, Danny's hockey game
got rescheduled.
I got him a ride
with the Simpson kid.
You just need
to pick him up.
Sure.
Saddle up, cowboy.
Take a bunch
so you can layer.
All right, here.
We're not here to party.
So you'd rather stick out?
I just want to make a run
for the border.
Yeah, well,
that's why you gotta blend.
Where is your friend?
He's probably just
gassing up the boat.
Sure this is the right place?
It's where we park
every year.
What if I have to pee
on the water?
Well, get it all out now.
Where?
It's also where we pee
every year.
Is that your guy?
Oh, here we go.
Mm-mm.
Nope.
- What are you doing?
- It's an open container.
We have a cooler full
of Canadian counterfeit.
Will you please
just act chill?
- He's coming.
- Okay, music on or off?
- On, on.
- ♪ Where my stash at?
- Off, off, off.
- ♪ Taking big time...
- Mike?
- Hey, Ruby.
What's going on?
What's in that?
A whole lot of fun.
Yeah,
it's her first Jobbie Nooner,
so, we went all out.
Open it on up.
You know, if this is about
the parking or something,
we could pull up...
What's in the cooler?
You put your boy on me?
You're welcome.
He gave Beth a ticket.
- Yeah.
Lucky that's all she got.
We could have just
slipped over.
Not on the weekend,
where they triple
border patrol.
We were gonna bury it
and go back tomorrow.
This is brilliant.
Drive right through customs
and pick it up.
'Cause nobody's ever thought
of doing that on Gull Island.
Yeah, smugglers.
Not a bunch of moms.
Was that her angle?
I need it back.
What else you got?
I don't know.
Hmm.
Come see me when you do.
Who are you, my dad?
No, you know,
I'm just worried
that's she's gonna come up
with something even dumber.
I'm not some kid you caught
with a case of beer.
This isn't just beer, Ruby.
I need to make that drop.
And I need to keep you
out of jail.
He's ready for you.
Now you don't look like
you're here
for the Sewer Expansion
meeting.
I'm not sure
I'd have a lot to offer.
Come on.
You know, they're actually
really interesting.
- Really?
- No.
Not at all.
So what can I do for you,
Elizabeth?
It's really stupid.
Oh, I've heard it all.
And it might be
crossing a line.
I'm okay with that.
It's kind of
more of a favor.
Is it a parking ticket?
- No.
- Okay, 'cause, you know,
people hit me up with that
all the time.
It's a trespassing ticket.
Oh.
Okay.
So what's next?
Burning Man?
It's a long story.
Try me.
I got time.
It's more of a thing for,
you know,
your brother cousin.
Him.
Which I can't explain
to a judge, so...
They're waiting for you
in the conference room.
You know what?
You're busy.
Look, it's just, um,
I don't... I don't like
to get involved with his... "things."
I never should have asked.
Just puts me in a bad place,
you know?
Go to your meeting.
This never happened.
I'm an idiot.
Wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no. No.
Hold on. Hold on.
I'll do it.
You really don't have to.
I really want to.
Come on.
- Thank you.
- But...
you're gonna have
to do something for me.
Yeah, what?
I wanna put you
to work.
- Please, no.
- Just try it.
I don't wanna release
whatever's trapped under there.
Don't you want to add rabies
to your hep A, B, and C?
I guess.
I'm scared.
What is this?
I'm no Shakespeare,
but I am sorry.
Let me take you out.
Why?
To make up
for the other night.
- Where?
- Restaurant.
A real one?
You like French?
Oui.
Ma'am.
This place is,
like, legit fancy.
- Oh, I know.
- Hey, Kev.
Hey, Ange.
You come here often?
All the time.
You have like a special table
or something?
Sort of.
Right this way, madame.
What is this?
This is dinner.
What are you doing?
Oh!
- Are you high?
- Little bit.
Oh, this three-course meal
right here.
- No way.
- One bite of each.
No, never.
- Not in hell.
- No.
I'll cook for you
for a month.
No, no, I don't want to be
eating your trash food.
Your food,
from whatever grocery store
you waste your money at.
No, bye!
Ben too.
Ben is not ever hungry.
Well, he eats
at his friend's house
so he doesn't have to at home.
One bite.
Well, I started
as a prep chef.
- Mm-hmm.
- And became a line cook.
And... and now
I just sort of sub in
whenever I need cash.
Wow.
Oh, forgot to ask.
What was the... it was like
a little brown chewy,
sausage-y, garlicy, butter
thing on the... on the toothpick.
Ah, yes, yes, yes, yeah.
That... that was a escargot.
Ah, escargot to you,
monsieur.
- Snails.
- What?
Yeah, see,
even from the garbage,
they're pretty great, right?
Ew! I never would have eaten
those, even inside.
That, my friend,
is exactly the point.
It doesn't matter.
Ugh.
Mmm!
Mm-mm.
Mm-hmm.
- Stop, stop, stop.
- What?
- What are you doing?
- I don't... I don't know.
You can't... you can't do that.
- Why not?
- Just...
Because it's... it's...
Because we're roommates.
So?
So it's not...
It's just...
It's too easy.
That wasn't in your rules.
We just... we can't, okay?
- All right.
- Um.
- I have to... I have to go.
- I'll walk you.
No, no, no. It's fine.
Just stay and enjoy the...
Well, I'll see you at home.
We get a PO Box.
Or whatever they
call it up there.
And just overnight it.
- Customs.
- Let 'em open it.
All they'll see is lots
and lots of Huggies.
Disguising, of course,
the cash.
Why would anybody want
to overnight diapers to Canada?
They use those cloth ones
up there.
I'm out.
You didn't want us involved
in the transport.
- Next.
- This is so low risk.
Yeah, until you're surrounded
by a bunch of Mounties
asking you why your Pampers
are so absorbent.
Huggies.
Hear me out.
There's a mini-submarine
called the Dolphin...
I thought we weren't
going to pitch this one.
No, you weren't gonna
pitch this one.
It's like 20 grand, Annie.
It's a lifelong
investment, Ruby.
You wanted one
way before we started all this.
Look, it's just so simple,
you know, we blend in
with the marine life,
we pop up,
we ditch the cash, we...
- This is ridiculous.
- Agreed.
Why do we have
to answer to you?
Oh.
How about my bag business,
my dancers, my club,
and what, my wife?
He makes some good points.
Are you ever gonna give us
our money back?
Well, not with these ideas.
Well, let's just sell
some bags then.
That's not gonna be necessary
this evening.
Why is that?
'Cause you're gonna need
these guys
to help you with your drop.
Hey.
How's it going?
Canadian dudes are
the most respectful.
Yeah?
My nipple popped out
too early,
and they all looked away.
- So we good?
- Oh, yeah.
They're not gonna ask
any questions.
That's it.
You better...
Yeah!
- Yeah.
Work all of that.
Our girls also dance
in Windsor.
- And?
- Fully nude, twice the money.
How does that help us?
They're real tight
with the border guards.
Ugh, Canadians.
Hey, how's it going?
IDs please.
Have we met?
I don't think so.
Oh, wait, no, you're... you're
Krystal's friend, right?
- That's it.
- Oh, yeah, Krystal.
You know, Krystal?
What's her real name?
She's actually right behind us.
- How do you guys know her?
- We met at the gym.
She teaches the most amazing
Zumba class.
She's so flexible, you know?
Yeah, well... yeah, I wouldn't
exactly call us friends.
Totally get it.
Um, where you guys
headed today?
We're gonna go see her dance.
#WomenSupportingWomen.
You should stop by.
Tell your wife you got
front row tickets
to the Windsor Ballet.
Well, I wish I could.
I... I got my kid's
violin concert, so...
Next time then.
All right,
you guys bringing anything in?
- Nope.
- Just us.
Great, then just pull over
right over there
and pop the trunk.
- But it's empty.
- Should be quick then.
Enjoy the show.
All right.
Good to go.
It's, like, no biggie at all.
Well,
we really appreciate it.
Anything to help a friend.
But we're gonna need
our expenses covered.
Thought this was a favor.
And what expenses?
You know, the cooler's super heavy,
so it uses more gas.
- Okay.
Can we just do this already?
Okay. How much?
5%.
Of what?
Um, just, like,
whatever's in the cooler.
- That's not our money.
- It's not our problem.
Okay, okay.
5%.
How are we gonna give them
5% of a cut we don't even have?
How are we gonna drop
a cooler that we don't have?
I don't like this SUV.
Why?
'Cause it's silver?
- 'Cause it hasn't moved.
- It is a parking lot.
Let's roll, bitches.
How bad is it?
Remember Payne Stewart?
- Wasn't he a golfer?
- Try U.S. Open champion.
- Okay.
- He's up in his private jet,
right, on top of the world.
Tower loses communication.
So they scramble some F-16s
to check it out.
Turns out,
the hull was breached.
Everyone inside was
sound asleep from no oxygen.
So what'd they do?
Plane's on autopilot,
just cruising.
All they gotta do
is wake up.
And what happened?
After 3 1/2 hours,
it runs out of fuel
and they crash into a cornfield
in South Dakota.
Jesus.
But that's not gonna be you.
- I already pled guilty.
- I know.
And they wanna move
the trial date up.
Yeah.
So how do I not end up
in the cornfield?
Her.
It's not an option.
So are you the one
printing fake money?
I already know where
you're going with this.
Cooking the books?
Committing wire fraud?
I'm not gonna turn
on my wife.
She did it.
- I have kids.
- So?
They need their mother.
Oh.
Okay.
So what's Plan B?
Who taught them
how to ride their bikes?
I mean, I did.
Who taught your son
how to do a slapshot?
Worked on that for months.
Who built the treehouse
in your backyard?
I bet they'd say all that stuff
is pretty important too.
- There's no Plan B, man.
- Come on, you guys.
She didn't leave you
a parachute.
What am I supposed
to do here?
Wake up.
Prepare to turn left.
This left or next left?
Mm, looks like next left.
Oh.
Uh, no.
What's "uh, no"?
- It was the other left.
- Recalculating.
Where do I go now?
I don't know.
It's... it's recalculating.
Where is this stupid place?
Here, here, here.
Next left.
It's cool.
We got it.
We're not there yet.
You must admit, Stanimal did
deliver on this one.
Yeah.
Except for the shakedown part.
That wasn't his plan.
It wasn't our plan either.
Better than taking a jet ski.
Okay, I get that you need
to defend him.
I'm not defending him.
But he has not made
our life easier.
Aren't we in Canada
with the money?
That's defending him.
In 400 feet,
take the next left.
I thought you were
cool with him?
I am.
'Cause I know
he's cool with you.
Recalculating.
Would you please
tell me where to go?
- God, that is so weird.
- What?
It's just this guy...
Every time we make a move,
he does too.
- Oh, God.
- What?
- Silver SUV?
- Silver-ish.
That's the car
from the parking lot.
- Okay.
You don't know that.
Same plate.
In 100 feet,
please make a U-turn.
take the next left.
- What do we do?
- Just... just drive.
- Where?
- Just go, go.
- Please make the next left.
- Just turn that off.
- I'm trying.
- Please make a left turn.
God, she's persistent.
What about the drop?
- We can't stop.
- Recalculating.
The second we do, we'll be
surrounded by Mounties.
- Mounties ride horses.
- Not when they're undercover.
We don't know
that they're Mounties.
- Okay, border patrol.
As if that's better?
Maybe Krystal sold us out.
Stan wouldn't
let that happen.
- Stop defending him.
- Let's just dump it.
It's gang-friend's money!
You want to explain that
to the Mounties?
Either way,
we can't make the drop.
Well, at least, my way,
we don't end up
in an Ontario gulag.
- Okay, how do we dump it?
- Roll down the windows.
So what, we can make it rain
all over their windshield?
- Here. Turn, turn.
- Annie!
Jesus!
We can lose them in here.
- Pull in somewhere.
- Where are they?
Can you see them?
Just do something!
- Slow down! Slow down!
- Stop yelling at me!
Oh, my God!
Come on.
- Do you think they're gone?
- Coast is clear.
- Where'd you learn all that?
- YouTube.
And they're back.
Grab the money.
- Why?
- Come on. Just do it.
No, no, no, just take it out
and divide it up.
What are we doing?
Getting rid of it.
Where?
Mai Ian's "Dial My Number"...
♪ Take the phone, take the
phone, take, take, do it ♪
♪ Do it, do, do,
do it, do it ♪
♪ Do it, take the phone,
take the phone ♪
♪ Take, take, take the phone,
♪ Take, take, dial it,
dial it, it, it, dial it ♪
♪ Dial it, it, it, take the
phone, take the phone ♪
Where's the bathroom at?
- Now, Annie?
- To flush the money, Beth.
- There's eyes in the sky.
They see everything.
So how do we dump it?
We don't.
Well, we can't go back
outside with it.
They'll be waiting.
♪ Dial my number,
dial my number ♪
We lose it.
Winner!
Where are we at?
- We're twice what we started.
- Jesus!
Why didn't we try craps
before crime?
I got to take this.
Hang on, what are we
supposed to do here?
Just be a loser.
Hey, I've called you
50 times.
Is everything okay?
- Danny's in the hospital.
- What?
Some kid checked him into
the board, he had the puck...
- Oh, my God.
- He even got the shot off.
What happened?
He got slammed
really hard, Beth.
- Is he okay?
- I don't know.
The coach thinks it's
his wrist, probably broken.
Can you go be with him?
Coach had to go home.
Nurse says
he's sitting there alone.
Can you?
Not unless I want
to get arrested.
Hello?
Yeah, it's gonna be a while.
Why?
Because I...
'Cause I'm not very close.
Well, where the hell are you?
I'm... sort of
out of the country.
Of course you are.
Next time,
just lie to me.
Wait.
Can't we just keep it?
I mean...
- We need to sign for it.
- So?
You want your name
on record here
if they find all our Queens?
Put it all on two.
You sure you don't want
to spread it around?
Two.
No more bets.
Oh, thank God.
Yes!
Oh, my God.
Whew.
- Chips fall where they may.
- Yeah, right.
To the unluckiest number.
2/2/2002.
Oh, honey.
Let's go home.
Am I supposed to know
what that means?
- You were there.
- Oh, the dot-com crash?
Her wedding.
Right, yes.
I knew that.
I'm gonna go
to the grocery store
and make him French toast
in the morning.
He didn't even ask for you.
Don't worry.
I paid for it.
Smells amazing.
It should
for how much it costs.
Is this
an Olive Garden special?
Yes, complete with
unlimited breadsticks.
Mmm!
Mm-hmm.
Uh, so,
um,
last night, uh...
I made things weird,
didn't I?
- No, no, no.
Seriously, not at all.
It's... it's fine.
It'll never happen again.
Cross my heart, hope to...
- Please.
Let's not go that far.
Sweet.
- Right?
- Can I have cheese?
- Absolutely, Benjamin.
- Mmm, so good.
- There you are, sir.
- Thank you.
- Where's yours?
- Oh, I'm eating out tonight.
Why?
That's for me.
- Hello.
- Hey.
You look great.
Thanks.
I love you in that shirt.
I don't think you've ever
seen me in another one.
You remember Angela.
- Hi. Yes, of course.
- Hey.
Just having some dinner
with my son.
You guys should go have
some fun.
Not too much fun.
But, you know, just kidding.
I'm kidding.
Better hurry up.
It's trash night.
Bon appétit.
You should put cheese on it.
You're looping it
the wrong way.
I got these sausage fingers.
Look.
Okay, but you're just making
a knot now. That's not...
- Friendship knot.
- That's not a thing.
- That's totally a thing.
It's better.
You can't undo it.
- Uh-huh. Okay.
- It's tight.
- Make me one?
- Yeah, sure.
In your room.
All right.
How'd it go?
Why are you helping us?
What do you mean?
Why'd you let us print
at the club?
You needed a space.
Why'd you make Krystal
do the drop?
Didn't want you to drown
on a jet ski.
Remember our wedding?
Um, well, not much.
Before my mom
made you do shots.
What, like, the ceremony?
The part where we promised
to treat
each other's family
like our own.
Yeah, why do you think
I did the shots?
I'm not talking about my mom.
What'd you say to her, Stanley?
Oh.
We made a deal.
Well, we kinda made a deal.
I told her that I'd give you
guys the place...
Lady Luck ain't on your side
tonight, huh?
There was a problem.
- Always is.
- And I had to get rid of it.
Never a solution.
Well, I didn't have
a lot of options.
Oh, yeah?
Or did the dice
just not roll your way?
- We were being followed.
- Yeah, by my people.
Well, that would have been
really nice to know.
They don't like
to make a scene.
But I don't mind so much.
Well, someone else will.
Hmm.
You got a guardian angel
I don't know about?
Maybe.
Everyone, meet Beth.
- Let's... yes.
- Hi.
Hi, Beth.
She's gonna be
running things around here.
- No, I'm helping.
- Just so we don't kill
whatever we plant.
Yeah.
They're all yours.
- Okay.
Well, I'm the new kid.
So maybe you guys
can help me out a little bit.
Show me what
you've already started.
Are you okay, man?
I'm fine.
You don't look so good.
I just woke up.
About time.
♪ S-s-sitting on my own
♪ Looking for
anything serious ♪
♪ Won't you give us
a chance? ♪
♪ Won't you give us a chance
♪ It's the time for me