‐ Don't y'all know
the drill by now?
‐ What if we ordered for him?
‐ He'll be here.
‐ I'm gonna go get that food.
And when I come back,
that seat better be occupied.
‐ Anything?
‐ Can't pick up the tab
if he doesn't show.
‐ You told him here, right?
‐ He's coming.
‐ Just like
your strip‐club guy
was moving all that
funny money.
‐ And the stuff
from the councilman's office
was all we would need.
‐ We're trying.
‐ It sounds like you're
trying to go to jail.
‐ Come here.
Yo.
‐ Yo.
‐ You hungry?
‐ No, I'm good.
‐ Watching your figure?
‐ Yeah, it's hard
looking this beautiful.
‐ Or you're meeting
someone more important?
‐
What's up then?
‐ Get in.
‐ Excuse me.
Are you Beth Boland?
‐ Yes, I am.
‐ I just voted for you.
Good luck today.
‐ Thank you for your support.
‐
‐ You guys,
just don't leave yet.
‐ You know...
I think I finally
figured it out.
‐ What's that?
‐ Why she's got you
by the jewels.
‐ Oh, yeah?
‐ Yeah, it's always
the spicy ones.
‐ My kind of girl.
‐ Yeah, well, makes me nervous.
‐ Don't be.
‐ Well, 'cause when
it all goes south,
I need you to be clearheaded.
‐ No, she's just
some bitch, bro.
‐ Oh, she's more than that.
Hmm?
Come on.
‐
You know me.
Do I?
‐ I'll do what I got to do.
All right?
‐ Let's see how far
we can take her, yeah?
‐ Drag that bitch
till she drops.
‐ That's right.
Forget lunch.
I think you need a boba.
What, you too cool
for boba now?
Put your seat belt on.
‐ Okay, okay, we're going.
‐ Yo, is that him?
‐ Nope, nothing. Oh.
‐ What's it say?
‐ I won.
‐ Oh, boy.
‐ She won.
‐ Seriously?
‐ Whiskey for the councilwoman.
‐ Where were you?
‐ Something came up.
‐ I looked like an idiot.
‐ To getting tough on crime.
‐ How am I supposed to do that
if I've got nothing
to give them?
‐ Change of plans.
‐ Why?
‐ Too much heat.
‐ Yeah, but the heat's
in charge.
‐ Yeah, that don't mean
we have to do it their way.
To keep your hands clean.
‐ What is it?
‐ Your acceptance speech.
Break a leg.
‐ Dinner!
Huh?
We have steak portobello
with a five‐cheese
mushroom risotto.
Well...
is there a problem, sir?
‐ There's ice in the middle.
‐ Oh, I'll just
toss it back on the grill.
‐ I'm also cool
with just PB on Ritz.
‐ Oh, well...
I just didn't want you
to go into...
food shock, since, you know...
‐ I'll survive.
‐ I don't know‐‐
you guys were just, uh...
pretty close.
‐ We still are.
‐ What do you mean?
‐ He's been helping out
at my practices.
‐ He has?
‐ Yeah, he and my coach
found out they used to play
against each other in college.
‐ Does he ever...
you know, like just...
ask about me, or is it...
‐ Mom.
‐ Hmm?
‐ You'll survive, too.
‐
‐ The mushrooms all exploded.
‐ Congratulations.
They didn't have
any patriotic options.
‐ Tastes the same.
‐ Hmm.
So do you want
to run your speech?
‐ Ah, I'm still working on it.
‐ Well,
if you change your mind,
I will be in...
the garage.
‐ What are you doing
in the garage?
‐ Cleaning up.
‐ Hey, ladies.
We got a family meeting
or lovers' quarrel?
What have we got?
‐ No, man,
we just want to talk.
‐ Shoot.
‐ I need you to leave
my wife out of this.
‐ Why?
‐ What do you mean why?
‐ Well, isn't she the problem?
‐ Not yours.
‐ Well, she's the reason
that you two are such losers.
‐ No, no, no, no, man,
you're not gonna do that
Harry Potter mind spell on us.
‐ All right, look,
everyone benefits from it.
She's gonna help
grow the company.
‐ Yeah, I don't‐‐I don't
think you're hearing me.
‐ All right.
‐ Leave my wife out of this.
‐ No, I got that part, yeah.
‐ Then don't be stupid.
‐ Or what?
‐ You don't want me
to make you understand.
‐ You think a guy my size
hasn't taken a few punches?
‐ Ain't nobody talking
about punches.
‐ I've been stuffed
into lockers, dumpsters.
At camp, I was lit on fire.
‐ Yeah, you ever seen a dog
rag‐doll a stuffed animal?
You ever seen that?
‐
‐ What, you think that's funny?
There you go.
Take it.
‐ What for?
‐ 'Cause the only way
you're gonna shut me up
is to kill me.
♪
‐ I am honored
to have this opportunity.
Uh, thank you
to my husband, Dean,
for his tireless support.
And thank you
to all my supporters
and my volunteers.
I made a promise to this city
to reduce crime
in our community,
and I do plan to deliver.
But I can't do it alone.
I'm gonna need your help.
We're all gonna
have to do our part.
And together,
we can heal our city
of this disease.
‐ Councilwoman, can you speak
to the corruption
in your own backyard?
‐ Uh, I don't‐‐I'm sorry.
I don't understand
the question.
‐ Can you comment
on the allegations
that Councilman Martín
uses city projects for
kickbacks and money laundering?
‐ I have only known
the councilman
to be honest and loyal
to the people of Ashfield.
But if there is
any impropriety here,
I will exhaust every resource
to maintain
the community's trust.
‐ You can turn it off now.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Got "Detroit News"
on line one.
‐ Tell 'em no comment.
‐ Uh, what about
"Oakland Press," "Freep,"
Action News 7,
WDIV, and FOX 2?
They're all on hold, too.
Hello?
‐ I'll let the councilman
speak for himself.
Thank you.
No more questions.
‐ I think there's been
a little misunderstanding.
‐ That's why we're here.
‐ Well, ask away.
I'm an open book.
‐ You sure
you don't want a lawyer?
‐ I've got nothing to hide.
‐ All right.
Explain to us
how we got it all wrong.
‐ Are you guys close
to your families?
‐ Only on holidays.
‐ I talk to my mom twice a day.
‐ Forget you, but you get it.
You grow up with someone,
you got your blinders on.
You want to believe
they can do no wrong.
‐ So this is all on him?
‐ Look, did I know
that he was running
with the wrong crowd? Sure.
Did I know that he was
gonna use my position
to line his pockets?
Absolutely not.
‐ But his name
isn't on any of this.
‐ Hey, you're welcome
to take a look.
‐ We know yours isn't either.
‐ Then aren't you sitting in
front of the wrong person?
‐ Okay.
Maybe you can help us, then.
‐ Why is all the money
in question
held up in companies
run by your grandmother?
‐ He, um...
He must have
set it up this way.
‐ Then you should really get
her a lawyer.
‐ 'Cause this is either
on you or Grandma.
‐ Your choice.
‐ Good news is she won't
serve that much time.
‐ Why?
‐ What is she, like, 100?
She'll croak long before
the sentence is done.
‐ Um...
Why can't it be him?
‐ 'Cause he's got something
you don't.
‐ What's that?
‐ Can you talk to my landlord?
‐ About what?
‐ You know, lowering my rent.
‐ What do you think?
‐ What about a disabled
parking permit?
‐ Are you disabled?
‐ She has one.
‐ I was shot.
‐ Being a ding‐dong
doesn't count.
‐ What‐‐what's the point
of all your new power
if we can't get something
out of it?
‐ How about not drawing
any more attention to ourselves
before we get out of here?
‐ Where we at?
‐ Okay.
Now I've lost my place.
‐ Just ballpark it.
‐ Well...
between the club,
the trips to Canada,
and what's left
from the purses...
It looks, um...
Good.
‐ How good?
‐ Good enough.
‐ Fine, who's yours?
‐ Evel Knievel.
‐ No way, dude.
‐ Come on, man, do the math.
‐ Anybody can hurl themselves
over a bunch of cars
and break every bone
in their body.
‐ But they didn't.
‐ 'Cause it wasn't a sport.
‐ Till he invented it.
Anyone can box.
‐
Where is he?
‐ I don't know, but I never
known this guy to be late.
‐ Know where Vance is?
‐ No, man.
‐ Hey, guys!
Sorry about that.
But something big
just rolled in
from corporate.
‐ Sweet.
‐ We are getting in
to haircare.
‐ Yes!
‐ Huh?
Now, we need someone smart
to spearhead this.
‐ I'll do it.
‐ Okay, now, we got
a lot of capital
we got to raise,
but I think the payoff's
gonna be pretty huge.
‐ Okay, dude, we‐‐we can
pool our funds.
‐ Actually, I was thinking
about going to, uh...
Stan and Dean for this one.
You guys up for it?
‐ Why not?
‐ Strong hearts, strong sales.
‐ No.
‐ The rest is in the car.
‐ We already have
a garage full of it.
‐ That's skincare.
‐ It's like a Sephora
out there.
‐ This is grooming.
‐ Stop being his bitch.
‐ How am I supposed to do that?
‐ We run.
‐ Now?
‐ Drop everything.
‐ What about the house?
‐ We sell it later.
‐ Kids?
‐ Put 'em in new schools.
‐ We just vanish?
‐ Like we were never here.
‐ And who's gonna pay for that?
‐ Hello.
Um, hi, there.
I‐I'm looking for Kevin.
‐ Use the bell.
‐ Oh, my God.
Kevin?
‐ Don't know him.
‐ Okay. Uh...
Hey.
Hey, is‐‐is he here?
‐ Doesn't want to see you.
‐ Please, I really need
to talk to him.
Thank you.
♪
Hey.
‐ You're supposed
to ring the bell.
‐
What is up with the bells?
‐ Basic etiquette.
‐ This place is sick.
‐ A friend of mine's
on spring break.
‐ Hmm.
Where'd they go?
‐ I don't know.
Just...
hopped a train south.
‐ We should do that.
‐ You want to go
on spring break?
‐ Except maybe...
we don't come back.
‐ You bought it.
‐ Yeah, well, they wouldn't
give me the deposit back, so...
Hmm.
‐ How many bedrooms?
‐ Two.
‐ And what about Benjamin?
‐ He gets the other one.
‐ I can't.
‐ But I don't want to go
with anyone else.
‐ Yeah, well, you don't
need a roomie.
‐ No, I don't need any guy.
‐ Then why are you here?
‐ I'm choosing to be.
‐ Does that thing have cable?
‐ Yeah, I think there's
probably a dish
on there somewhere.
‐ All right.
‐ That's why you're coming?
‐ Uh, well, the new season
of "The Bachelorette"
just started, so, yeah.
‐ Mm.
‐ That was a quick ride.
‐ He hasn't left yet.
‐ The girls already made
the drop this week.
‐ It's not about that.
♪
‐ Hey, Beth?
Bethie?
Beth!
‐ What is this?
‐ Beth, open the door!
‐ Consequences.
‐ Bethie!
♪
‐ My children are upstairs.
‐ Beth!
Beth!
‐ Thanks.
‐ Open up!
♪
‐ What do you want?
‐ Open the door!
You want a hot tub?
You want a better one?
You want money?
You‐‐
‐ Beth!
♪
‐ ♪ Rain, rain
♪ Go away
♪ I couldn't take you
♪ One more day
♪ There's broken glass here
♪ On the floor
♪ And I can't take this
♪ Anymore
♪
♪ Stay, stay
♪ Don't leave now
♪ I'll do anything
♪ But let you go
♪ My hands are cold
♪ My eyes can't see
♪ You can't do this
♪ Not to me
♪
♪ I can't stand this
♪ Rain
♪
‐ Hey.
‐ We got to move.
‐ Why?
‐ Guy's rig is, like,
right up against our porch.
‐ Okay, well, so ask him
to scoot over.
‐ No, he's a total dick.
‐ What happened?
‐ He made fun of my beard.
‐ Oh, honey.
‐  You know, I hear
there's a nice park in Reno.
‐ We can't go to Reno.
‐ Oh, we can go anywhere.
‐ Actually, baby, we can't.
‐ That's the perk of having
a house on wheels.
‐ What about Ben?
‐ He can play lacrosse
somewhere else.
‐ This is the only free school
in Nevada with a program.
And we're parked in the only
free spot in Nevada.
‐ Jesus.
Suburbia sucks.
‐ Mm.
Oh, what‐‐what are you‐‐
what are you doing?
‐ I'm wrecking his view.
‐ Uh...
Morning.
‐ Morning.
‐ A little snack for you.
‐ I might be late.
I have practice.
‐ Oh.
When's the first game?
‐ Mm, we haven't gotten
a schedule yet.
‐ Why not?
‐ Uh, I guess they start
later out here, so...
‐ Okay, all right.
well, just let me know,
because, you know,
I want to brag about you
with all the other
trailer‐trash mommies.
I love you.
‐ Love you, Mom.
‐ Bye.
‐ What are you doing?
‐ Just catching some rays, BM.
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ Just catching some rays.
both: ♪ Them hills
♪ Jump on it,
jump on it, jump on it ♪
♪
‐ ♪ Mani‐pedi
both: ♪ Jump on it
♪ Jump on it, jump on it
‐ Ooh, hold on.
‐ What is it?
‐ We got a lot to offer.
♪ Paraffin
‐ Oh!
‐ ♪ Jump on it,
jump on it, jump on it ♪
‐ Hey!
‐
‐ ♪ Open on Sundays
‐ ♪ Open Sundays
both: ♪ Get on it
♪ Get on it, get on it
‐ What do you think, baby girl?
‐ Well?
‐ It makes me want to
get my nails done.
‐ Boom! That is what
I thought it would do.
‐ That's what I'm talking
about right there.
‐ What if you guys
don't get customers?
‐ We will.
‐ But what if you don't?
‐ Oh, don't you have
to go to school?
‐ Hey, hey, hey.
What about your breakfast?
‐ Not hungry.
‐ You barely ate dinner.
‐ You need me to drive you?
‐ Uh, Someone from
the dance team's picking me up.
‐ She's a Vegas girl now.
They have dancing
in their blood.
‐ Oh, damn.
2,000 miles away
from that club.
‐ Still got to worry
about the pole.
‐ Hey, hey, hey.
Don't throw that away.
‐ What if we don't get
any customers?
‐ Then we'll have
to take a little money
out that boarding school.
‐  We'll have to do
more than that.
‐ Then we'll have
to put him to work.
‐ He's nine.
‐ He's short.
‐
He can do the feet.
Hey.
What is on, uh, tap
for you today?
‐ Something crazy.
‐ Should I be worried?
‐ Yoga.
‐
Seriously?
‐ Yeah, some mom
in the neighborhood
said there's an online class
that changed her life.
‐ Get over here.
Whoa! Welcome back.
I never thought you
could be you again.
‐ Thank you.
‐ Bye, babe.
♪
‐ Everyone on the floor!
Facedown!
Get on the floor!
Open the drawer!
Open it!
‐ Don't bother.
‐ I said floor, bitch!
‐ They always
empty out the drawer
in the morning shift change.
♪
‐ Give me your purse.
‐ I'm not gonna do that.
Because the manager over there
has already hit
the panic button.
So, when you try to grab this,
I'm obviously gonna stall.
Cops will already be here.
♪
‐ Do you want to die?
‐ Kind of.
‐ So, how was practice?
‐ It was fine.
‐ Yeah?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Yeah, I was thinking
maybe I could come
to the game on Saturday.
‐ Oh, you got a schedule?
‐ Yeah, it was online.
‐ Well, the coach
might not put me in.
‐ Maybe 'cause you...
never actually joined the team.
I went by there today.
‐ It's just not
the same out here.
‐ Well, why not?
‐ I don't know.
‐ Is it because of the heat?
‐ Because of everything.
‐ I mean, the sport's been
around for 300 years.
It's not like it can be‐‐
‐ Well, it's not that.
‐ It can't be that different.
‐ It's not the sport.
They won't let me change
in their locker room.
‐ They said that?
‐ They just put my uniform
in the other one.
Best teams are
in Reno anyway, so...
So get this.
Reggie said there's a way
to hook both of our trailers
together
to make one big giant one.
Huh?
‐ So Monique said
she didn't show up
because she had some bad tuna.
‐ Maybe she did.
‐ Sara, dinner!
Yeah, but when
I asked her about it today,
she said she had period cramps.
‐ Well, which one was it?
‐ Neither.
‐ How do you know?
‐ 'Cause you only get one,
Stanley.
Either you had some bad tuna,
or you got your period.
Sara!
No such thing as tuna‐period.
‐
I mean‐‐I mean, really.
The girl just has to
answer a damn phone.
‐ Hey, young lady!
Enough with the TikTok!
Time to eat!
Sara?
Sara, open up.
‐ Sara?
Sara?
‐ Sara!
‐ Hey.
Baby.
‐ Sara, open the door!
‐ Sara?
‐ She was fine at home.
‐ So was Ben.
‐ We'll get through it.
‐ She's rejecting the kidney.
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ We'll get through it.
‐ Our insurance
hasn't kicked in.
‐ Oh, my God!
‐ We'll get through it.
‐ Will you stop saying that?
‐ How?
‐ I've been knitting.
‐
‐ All right.
Hands where I can see 'em!
Nobody move.
Just be cool,
and nobody gets hurt.
‐ All right, you, come on.
Let's go, open it up.
‐ All right, ladies,
open it up.
‐ Put it in nice and easy.
‐ Come on, hurry up.
You know what to do.
‐ Nice and easy.
‐ More, more, more, quick!
‐ That's right.
Open those up.
‐ All right.
‐ Look down, please.
Do not look at me.
‐ You next, come on.
Open up that drawer.
‐ That's right.
Get it in there, come on.
‐ Time?
‐ All right,
where's the manager at?
‐ Three minutes.
‐ Get the video feed.
Look away.
‐ I said where's
the manager at!
‐ Pretty sure
it's this guy right here.
‐ All right, come on. Let's go.
‐ Let's go!
‐ Let's go to the back, you!
‐ Bro, what's going on?
‐ Let's go to the back.
Come on.
‐ Bro, let's go!
‐ Guys, what is going on?
Beth!
Are you okay?
Beth, do something!
Beth, are you all right?
Beth!
Call an ambulance.
Someone do something!
Wake up! Wake up!
Somebody!
No!
Please, help!
Beth, stay with me!
Beth!
Do something!
♪
Beth! No!
‐ What did you think
was gonna happen?
‐ Beth, please, come on!
Wake up!
‐ Can't run
from who you are, Beth.
How many times
have I told you that?
How many?
‐ How many?
How many, Beth?
How many fingers
am I holding up?
‐ Two.
Where are the kids?
‐ Neighbor's.
They're okay.
Hey, you're gonna be okay.
‐ Can you tell us who shot you?
‐ Go ahead.
‐ Uh...
‐ Beth.
‐ It, um...
It happened so fast.
‐ Tell him.
‐ Who did this, ma'am?
♪
‐ I don't know.
‐
‐ What?
‐ Do you not like the flowers?
‐ They were on sale.
‐ I'm not going to Nevada.
‐ We can get you other flowers.
‐ Nothing'll be different.
‐ Except you won't
be a criminal.
‐ Exactly.
‐ But what about the part
where you don't have to live
in fear for your life?
‐ 'Cause that's
pretty enticing.
‐ He just grazed me.
‐ You got shot.
‐ You are extremely lucky
that he missed.
‐ What if it wasn't luck?
You guys,
he left his gun behind.
‐ Must feel like a boss.
‐ Nah.
Nah, man, it just feels right.
‐ You know none
of it's gonna stick.
‐ Not without me.
‐ You know,
the crazy thing is...
I don't blame you.
‐ Look, man, it don't matter
who you try to put this on.
You're gonna leave her be.
‐
Yeah?
‐ Yeah.
And don't be using my people
for your dirty work.
‐ He's on my payroll.
‐ Not anymore.
‐
‐ Ah, there's nothing more
I can do to her anyway.
‐ Yeah?
You should've finished the job.
‐ I did.
‐ How so?
‐ I‐I took your advice...
hit her where it hurts.
Remember?
♪
‐ What if it's that gun?
‐ Except why shoot me
with a gun
with my prints on it?
♪
‐ Her prints are all over it.
‐ Sibling rivalry?
‐ Way more than that.
Not the only time it was used.
‐ Jesus.
‐ So what do we do?
‐ It's not our case.
♪
‐ You bought an RV?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Does Dad know?
‐ Not yet.
‐ Benjamin was freaking out
about school.
‐ But then I was like,
"Why don't we go
cross‐country for summer,
"and I could be
with Dad for school
and then fly back
for Thanksgiving?"
‐ Ooh, we should do
a college tour on the way.
‐ I want to see Oberlin.
‐ Fork that.
You're going to Maryland.
‐ Guys.
Um...
I may not be able to go.
‐ What?
‐ Why?
‐ Uh, I'm actually
in a little bit of trouble.
‐ Hey. Hey, hey, hey,
check this out.
Uh, three bedrooms, two baths,
central air‐‐'cause we're gonna
need that out there.
‐ Stanley.
‐ Let me guess.
‐ I can't leave her like this.
‐ This was your idea.
‐ Maybe we can...
go once everything blows over.
‐
Maybe you can just join us.
‐ What do you mean?
‐ When you decide.
‐ Decide what?
‐ Which family
you want to be with.
‐ Don't do this.
‐ I already put
the application in.
‐ Why can't we just wait?
‐ The longer we wait,
the worse it gets.
‐ We just can't do it anymore.
‐ I know.
♪
‐ ♪ Three, oh,
it's the magic number ♪
♪ Yeah, it is
♪ It's the magic number
♪ Somewhere in that ancient
mystic trinity ♪
♪ You'll get three
♪ It's the magic number
♪ And the past and the present
and the future ♪
♪ And faith and hope
and charity ♪
♪ And the heart and
the brain and the body ♪
♪ Will give you three
♪ It's the magic number
♪ It takes three legs
to make a tripod ♪
♪ Or to make a table stand
♪ And it takes three wheels
♪ To make a vehicle
called the tricycle ♪
‐ Yeah.
‐ ♪ And every triangle
has three corners ♪
♪ Every triangle
has three sides ♪
♪ No more, no less,
you won't have to guess ♪
♪ Now there's three
♪ Can't you see
that it's the magic number? ♪
♪
‐ ♪ Three times two is six
♪ And three times one
‐ What is it?
‐ Three!
‐ Yeah.
‐ ♪ A man and a woman
had a little baby ♪
♪ There were three
in the family ♪
♪ And that's
the magic number ♪
‐ Mommy, I want to do
the swing!
‐ Wait your turn, okay?
He'll share.
‐
‐ You know the best part
about all this?
‐ What, not the city salary?
‐ You work for me now.
‐
‐ ♪ Three, oh,
it's the magic number ♪
♪ Yeah, it is
♪ It's the magic number
‐ You got it, boss.
♪ Somewhere in that ancient
mystic trinity ♪
♪ It's the magic number
♪ And the past and the present
and the future ♪
♪ Faith and hope and charity
♪ And the heart and the brain
and the body ♪
♪ Will give you three
♪ Three, six, nine, uh‐huh
♪ 12, 15, 18
♪ 21, 24, 27
♪ 30, oh
‐ ♪ It's the magic number
♪ Three, six, nine, uh‐huh
♪ 12, 15, 18
♪ 21, 24, 27
♪ 30
♪ Three, six, nine, oh, yeah
♪ 12, 15, 18
♪ 21, 24, 27
♪ 30
♪
‐ Now multiply backwards
from 3 times 10 ♪
♪ 3 times 10 is 30
♪ And 3 times 9 is 27