.
- Previously on
"Good Girls"...
- You ever heard of The System?
- That's like a pyramid thing,
right?
- A multi-level opportunity.
- I want to pull Ben out of
St. Anne's.
- I am asking you for a favor
here.
- I don't want to be your favor
anymore.
- What am I being arrested for?
- Trafficking a class one
controlled substance.
- How'd you guys get the
wholesale hook-up?
- He would be upset
if I told you.
- How'd we do?
- You mean how did I do?
- Well, it looks like you did
just fine on your own.
- Beth can't be a part of this.
She does whatever she wants
whenever she wants.
- We're gonna give them
the broken toy.
- So, what you're saying is
we're framing someone?
- Who the hell's that?
- D.C. is not gonna keep
the tab going much longer.
- Remember when I asked you
to get a juice?
- You want to get a juice,
let's go get a damn juice.
- Just pick a side.
- You need us,
you need all of us.
- Not all of you.
- Ringside seats, huh?
How'd you get these?
- Called in a favor.
- You don't find it
coincidental?
- What's that?
- That both the bullets
in Lucy's head
match the ones
in the other bodies.
- I don't know any Lucy.
- We got him.
- Where is he?
- He walked.
- So what do we do about her?
- That's why you got me,
brother.
♪
- ♪ God is playing marbles
♪ With His planets
and His stars ♪
♪ Creating havoc
through my life ♪
♪ With His influence on Mars
♪ That's why I'm rolling down
the sky way ♪
♪ On my cosmic wheels
- Another bad dream?
- Banana or blueberry?
- Just plain.
- Boring.
- Which one was it?
- Want juice?
- Zombies?
Tornados?
- I made coffee too.
- Kidnappers?
- They came in
through the basement.
- I lock the door every night.
- They kicked it in.
- I'd wake up.
- But you don't
when that's out.
- Nothing's gonna happen
to you, okay?
- How do you know?
- 'Cause I'm your dad.
- Can we get an alarm?
- Don't need to.
- Jenny got one.
- Her dad's an accountant.
Hey.
Don't burn my pancakes.
- ♪ Instead of stumbling
down this highway ♪
♪ On my boots of steel
♪ Cosmic wheels
♪
- Councilman.
Got a minute?
- Always, please.
- Order up.
Could we get some more
of these wasabi things?
- There's a charge for refills.
- Oh--no, no, no.
There's still some dust left.
- Is everyone a criminal
in this city?
- Maybe you should slow down.
- You can't get drunk
off these things.
- We're not on vacation.
- Not anymore.
Mm.
Don't look.
Why did you look?
- To see what I wasn't supposed
to look at.
- What happened to our meeting?
- Would you like one?
Uncle Sam is treating.
- I want to know
what's going on.
- D.C. pulled the plug.
- Why?
- Clearly, he's got someone
on the inside.
- I can still get him.
- First night I get here,
I'm about to hit the hay,
right?
I see a spider
in the bed.
Damn thing runs away under the
sheets before I can get him.
I get my phone out, I rip
the place apart--nothing.
But that little bastard,
he's under there, somewhere,
hiding, waiting.
You think I'm ever gonna get
back into that bed again?
- Where have you been sleeping?
- Bathtub.
- It's just not safe.
- What about my deal?
- Drink.
- What about my husband?
- What about our money?
- Drink.
- There goes Ben's school.
- Stan's out of work.
- Since when?
- Since we put away his boss.
- Well, what happened
to the girls?
- Heaven and Cinnamon went back
to Arby's.
- Oy.
- Dean's gonna go to jail.
- They can't do that.
- Can't they?
- We have to get to Nevada.
- How?
- They bailed on us.
- Then we have to get there
ourselves.
- Are we talking about
Nevada, Nevada?
- It's a metaphor.
- Just because
I'm not remembering
Nevada's exact
extradition laws,
but if this is about Deansie--
- Mexico, Thailand, wherever.
- Who's gonna foot
those moving costs?
- You still have those bags?
- What you doing?
- I'm getting these babies
ready for market.
- Why?
- What do you mean why?
- We don't owe Gene anymore.
- We still got bills.
- Oh, some of the girls
were talking about doing
private parties.
- Can't make a living
being a freelance heavy.
- Hmm.
Yeah, all right, I hear you.
I guess we can move
a few of these.
- Gotta move
a more than a few.
- It's only two of us.
- Not necessarily.
- No.
- We need help.
- She helped you.
- No.
- Luck didn't lock Gene up.
- We owe her, Stanley.
- Hey.
How was the game?
- Do we have any razor blades?
- That bad, huh?
- DIY screen repair.
Step two, scrape off excess.
- Did you score?
- I didn't play.
- What? Who did they put in?
Brad?
- Don't know.
- Ugh.
The coach is, like,
so in love with him.
- I'm gonna quit.
- What?
- I want to sell all my gear.
- Why?
- To pay for karate.
- What are you talking about?
- I know I have to go back
to my old school.
- I'm so sorry, Bubba.
- It's okay.
- Promise?
- I still follow some friends
from there.
- Okay.
- And it's closer. I can bike.
- Yeah, that's true.
- Classes are way easier, too.
- You'll, like,
totally be valedictorian.
But don't sell all your gear
just yet, okay?
- They don't have lacrosse.
- I know but we could...
find you a club team.
- I'm gonna need the karate
anyway.
- Why?
- Last time I was there,
I wasn't...Ben.
- So Vance says
it's all about your base.
I build up enough contacts
here,
we'll have a little wiggle room
to grow my business
once we get to Nevada.
- That sounds like a plan.
- Yeah, so I had Carlene
send me
all our old contacts from
Boland Motors and Bubbles.
- That's smart.
- Yeah.
- What?
- Well...
I don't want to jinx it.
- Oh, come on.
- Just feel like this time,
we got a real chance.
- Mom.
Mom, I gotta poop.
I'll run her home.
- Oh, wait.
Are you sure
you didn't want to just
hot bag it in the bushes?
- Yes, I'm positive.
Come on, kid.
- Not a great time.
- I'll make it quick then.
- Can we do this
someplace else?
- Oh, you haven't told him
my good news?
- I don't think
he'll take it that way.
I need you to run
a little errand for me.
- They are never little.
- Get me my funny money back.
- How am I supposed to do that?
- Ask nicely.
- The cops?
Not them.
They're your crew.
- They're leaving.
- Never a good time, is it?
.
- I was just thinking,
before you leave,
we could, um,
finally get that green juice.
I could even bring it to
the hotel if that's easier.
I don't know if you got
my text, but, um...
call me.
Okay, bye.
- How do you even know
the money's there?
- I don't.
- So, wait,
you're just gonna get her
hopped up on green juice?
- Could always roofie her.
- Just to loosen her up,
get her talking.
- You know what
a little errand is?
Picking up the dry cleaning,
dropping off a dog
at the groomer,
getting milk.
Breaking into a hotel room
to steal federal evidence
is a kamikaze mission.
- It's suicide.
- That is what kamikaze is.
- That's exactly why we have to
get out of this town.
- Y'all ready?
- Squad up, bitches.
- It's just something we say.
- Mm-hmm.
- Oop--
- Oh, no.
- Go ahead.
- You take it.
- It's your house.
- It's my bags.
- Oh, boy.
- So, last time--
- I was thinking--
- Last time
we hit the third grade,
now we do fourth.
- This way,
we don't repeat parents.
- Also,
let's use a different house,
because we got new prospects.
- Oh.
What about Irish twins?
- What about them?
- Same parent could have
a kid in third grade
and in fourth grade.
- Not an issue.
- Making sure.
- So I figured that we'd...
break this down into shifts,
maybe over a few days.
- And would that be
the most bang for our buck?
- Um, I guess we could
double up in one day.
- I mean the whole school
thing.
I mean, if it ain't broke...
- Okay.
- I mean,
if you see a problem--
- No, no, no.
This should work.
- She sees a problem.
- No, not necessarily.
- Phew. Real big one.
- Just a little snag.
- Hey,
I'm all ears.
- It's kind of risky.
- Here we go.
- Why?
- Well, who's on your mom chain
right now?
- Bunch of people.
- And how many fourth grade
moms are on there?
- Um...
Not a lot.
- What's your point?
- Moms talk, a lot.
- Mm-hmm.
- And it only takes one
to smell a knock-off.
- Or it's safer.
- How's that?
- If someone finds out,
then we can get ahead of it
because we're on
that mom chain.
- Or...
they start another mom chain,
so they can talk about you
behind your back.
- How many mom chains
are you on, babe?
- Not a lot.
- And then Harry gets kicked
out of school.
- Come on now.
- And we're all in cuffs.
- That's never gonna happen.
- Why take the chance?
- You know what?
I'm just gonna shut up.
- Stan.
- You got a better idea?
- It's whatever you want to do.
- She's got a better idea.
- ♪ I've never seen a diamond
in the flesh ♪
♪ And I'm not proud
of my address ♪
♪
♪ In a torn up town
♪ No post code envy
♪ But every song's like
♪ Gold teeth, Grey Goose
♪ Tripping in the bathroom
♪ Blood stains, ball gowns,
trashing the hotel room ♪
♪ We don't care
♪ We aren't caught up
in your love affair ♪
♪ And we'll never be royals
♪ Royals
♪ It don't run in our blood
♪ The kind of luxe
just ain't for us ♪
♪ We crave a different kind
of buzz ♪
♪ Let me be your ruler
♪ Ruler
♪ You can call me queen bee
♪ And baby, I'll rule
♪ I'll rule, I'll rule,
I'll rule ♪
♪ Let me live that--
- Hey!
- What the hell?
- Who are you?
- We are your halftime show.
- Jesus.
- Yeah, uh,
I think we'll stick
with the main event.
- If you want to see
their goods,
you're gonna have to buy ours.
We got all the brands
right here.
- So bust out
that tip money, gentlemen.
- We already paid
for this party.
- Yeah.
- No, you paid
to get this party started.
- You can't do this.
- Oh, but we are.
- What are we gonna do
with a bunch of purses?
- Give them to your wives.
Or your mistresses,
or your girlfriends.
We really don't care.
- All right, how much?
- Start at two grand.
- What?
- Who carries that kind
of cash?
- Well, you guys always manage
to find it
for the champagne room,
don't you?
- We all accept
all major credit cards,
including Venmo and Apple Pay.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold up--no.
- Come on over.
Grab them while they're hot.
- No, no--what are you doing?
- I need to see those goods.
- Guys, put your money away.
- Girls, put your clothes on.
- Whoa, come on.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Hey, it's pay to play, man.
- The only thing
we're paying for
is some high class ass.
- Um...
- Sorry.
- Okay, thanks.
Maybe next time
there won't be a cop.
- Fourth grade moms would have
been way riskier.
- Are you kidding me? -
Yeah, come on man.
It's not that great.
- Seriously, how many cars
do you sell in a month?
- 300?
- 300.
- That's more than we'd sell
in a quarter.
- Well,
I learned from the best.
- Aw.
You always had the it factor.
- Nobody would have ever
noticed
if you hadn't pulled me up
to the big leagues.
- Best porter we ever had.
Okay, you ready?
Hydrator, toner, tightener.
This stuff right here.
It's great for the circles--
the dark circles
under your eyes.
- I'll take one of each, man.
- Wait.
You don't want me to do
the rest of my spiel?
- Nah, no need to.
- Yeah, I mean, you'll see,
I mean, it's--
It's really--
it's really solid stuff.
- If you say so, I am in.
- And,
when you respond
the way I know you will,
we can even talk about
other opportunities.
- I'm pretty busy right now.
- No, I know, I know--
I'm just saying, like,
in the slow months,
it's an easy way
to put a little extra cash
in your pocket.
- Pyramid schemes aren't really
my thing.
- It's more of a--
you know, community of men
supporting each other.
- You ever think about
coming back on the lot?
- Uh...
Nah, it's not--
it's not my bag anymore.
- Friend of mine
over at, um,
Southfield Volvo
said they're losing one of
their best sales guys.
- Southfield, huh?
- Mm-hmm.
I can put in a word.
- I'm my own boss now.
- Just get lunch with the guy,
feel it out.
- You know what?
Um, actually, I can just
do all this for you.
You don't--
you don't need to be--
- That your phone?
- Yeah, I think it's--
I think it's, uh--
Out of batteries.
I should really get going.
- Also need a copy
of the arrest file.
- Should be there.
- It's not.
- Hang on.
- Don't see it.
- Well, maybe they threw it out
when they threw out my case.
- No, nope, here we go.
- Hm.
- Sign the release.
- That it?
- Why'd they throw out
your case?
- Well, if I knew that,
I wouldn't be going home.
Pays to have friends
in high places, huh?
- Hey, Shel.
- I'm not sharing this.
- I need something
from evidence.
She was someone's daughter.
- Rather give you
half my sandwich.
- You're the best.
.
- Order up.
- This is a little
embarrassing.
- Hit me.
- Got kids?
- Mm-mm.
Married to the city.
- Ah.
My daughter, she's nine.
She's a big MMA fan.
- Mm.
Who's her favorite?
Anyone who kicks ass.
- The whole girl power thing.
- Right. Right, right, right.
- Yeah.
- So what can I do for you?
- There you go.
- Mm.
- Heard you're the ticket guy.
- How's that?
- Word is you got the hook-up
for all the best fights.
Says who?
- Can't be humble on Instagram.
- Office seats.
- Hook a guy up?
- Those are usually reserved
for donors,
Make-A-Wish kids, you know.
- What about murderers?
- I don't know anything
about this.
- How'd they end up with a
gang banger tied to a homicide?
- I guess,
maybe they scalped them.
- One of the cancer kids?
- Mm.
- Sorry,
what was your precinct?
- Fourteen.
- Mm.
Let me see what I can do
for your daughter.
- Appreciate that.
- Yeah.
Have a good day, officer.
- You too.
- And I've been using the same
shampoo bottle for, like,
a year.
Just add water and shake.
And I've never bought ketchup
or soy sauce,
I have a whole drawer
dedicated to freebies.
And I always order
off the kid's menu.
- No doubt about it.
You're poor.
- Yes.
- Maybe the poorest
I've ever seen.
- Thank you.
- But we can't grant you
financial aid.
- Have you gotten to
the part yet
where we lived off a deer
for an entire winter?
- The problem is
your drug charge.
- I can explain.
That was because
a man tried to rape me,
and when I wouldn't let him
rape me, he tr--
- It's just school policy.
- The thing is,
Ben loves this school.
- We love Ben.
- Ben loves this school
so much that he's, like--
one of those kids
that you see on a brochure,
that you're sure has to be an
actor because they're so happy.
But actually,
Ben is so happy at school.
- What about Ben's father?
- Isn't there any other way?
- Do you have a boyfriend?
Domestic partner?
- Okay, well, now you're just
rubbing it in.
- Is there anyone you get naked
with regularly?
- That counts?
- If they share your address.
- Ooh.
Jesus.
- I brought bagels.
- Man, DWP was jackhammering
all night.
- You want everything
or poppy?
I gave you a house key?
- Oh, I used the spare.
It's been a while.
- Yeah, I got--
sorry, so busy--
- Could have called.
- I lost my phone.
- Still liked my TikToks.
- Hey, question--
you don't have
any kind of like--
record or anything like that,
right?
- Huh?
- You know, like,
drug charges or felonies...
What do you want?
- Nothing.
- You only come over
when you need something.
- Excuse me
for trying to have
a nice breakfast moment
with...my...boyfriend.
- Wow.
All right, seriously,
why are you here?
- Just--
here.
Fill these out, and for the
address, just use mine.
- Well, if I do this,
you gotta do something for me.
- Yeah, I'm not really ready
for the tattoo thing.
- Never come here again.
- Okay.
- And leave the bagels.
- It's like my uniform,
you know?
I don't even work out.
- Neither do I.
- But I still put them on
every morning like it's my job.
- That's why I focus
on my accessories.
- Because I may not feel great
in my jeans, but my bags?
They always look hot.
- I wish I could afford it.
- Convince your husband
that you need one.
- He just sent me
on a girls trip to Chicago.
- Ooh, fun.
- Go, go, go, come on.
Get your snack. Move it.
- Stop running.
We're not gonna be late,
all right?
- Hey, hun.
This is Beth.
Her oldest did Ladybug
with Olivia.
I feel so bad
I didn't remember that.
- Please, it was forever ago.
- She's selling
these cute bags.
Kim just bought one.
- How do you know Kim?
- Friend of a friend.
- Mom, where are the nuggets?
- In the freezer,
where they always are.
- No, they're not.
- Excuse me.
- What is this?
- Never use your real info
when booking strippers.
- Do you want to get arrested?
- I want you and your friends
to all buy your wives a bag.
- Or maybe you're just dumb.
- No, dumb would be
thinking that
I didn't record everything
the other night.
- Hey, babe,
we're out of nuggets.
- Ooh, I wanted to show you
one more thing
because I forgot to bring
the snakeskin.
- Oh, that might be
a bit much for me.
- Come on, you just have to
channel your inner stripper.
Here it is.
So this is from a trunk show
that we did the other night.
- Let's just get it.
- Babe, these are expensive.
- Call it an early birthday
present, huh?
- Wow.
Someone won the husband
lottery, huh?
- I so did.
- Uh, maybe the other guys
wives would dig them, huh?
- Are you kidding?
They would love them.
- I would appreciate
the referrals.
.
- What are all these emojis?
- That's everybody paying
everybody.
- That's confusing.
- Okay, click there.
So that's everyone paying you.
See? One emoji.
- Is that a middle finger?
- You did blackmail him.
- Well...
- Happy hour?
- Very happy.
- She got the money.
- Well, not all of it.
A few guys want to pay in cash
'cause they don't want it
on record.
- Cool.
-  Cool.
- Can somebody read
my Bio report?
- What's it on?
- Cellular organelles.
- Yeah, that's all you.
- Okay.
You know I was the queen of
cellular organelles,
back in the day.
- Is your account @ThemHills?
- Yep.
- And...
that is your cut.
- Must feel good
proving me wrong.
- Feels better
to get the money.
- Like that's why you did it.
- What's your problem?
- You.
- Okay, I'm sorry that I--
- You could have waited
for the next party.
- I saved our asses.
- No, you went back over there
because your ego
couldn't take the hit.
- Okay, let's not talk
about ego.
- Got ignored for so long
in your own home--
- Mister "my bags."
- Now all you want to do
is matter.
- Excuse me?
- You use whoever you can
to get whatever you want.
- I got you your money.
- You got my wife shot.
And that's the least of it.
- If you think that I would
ever do anything to hurt her--
- I think that you don't think
about anyone
but yourself, Beth.
- Ready to go?
- Yeah, let me grab my jacket.
- What are you doing here?
- Do you want to have
that green juice?
- I'm kind of over it.
- Good.
'Cause that's why
I brought this.
- I got work to do.
- Is that your version of
"gotta pick up the kids?"
- Only mine's real.
- I'm not a total bitch.
- I only do shots.
- Hey.
All right,
let me ask you something.
- You got a glass?
- Uh...your choice.
Mug or sippy cup?
- Never mind.
- Okay.
What do you know about cars?
- I know what I like.
- No, like,
how they work--
like, why is a Cadillac good
for one guy,
but a BMW is great
for someone else?
I was really good at that.
- You're a natural.
- At cars.
- Think I see
where this is going.
- You guys have been
so incredible to me--
- When you were little,
what did you want to be?
- Easy, astronaut.
- Stuntman.
- Okay, so?
- You didn't know anything
about cars.
I didn't know anything about
men's skincare.
- I got a better chance
at being an astronaut--
- But you have something
down here
that you wouldn't have
in outer space.
- What's that?
- This guy.
- It's just not for me.
And look, I really hope
that I can still bike
with you and the guys.
- Dude.
You're my ride or die.
Come on.
- 'Cause you're mine, so--
- You just write me a check
for the product, we're good.
- Oh, okay--um,
so I knew this was coming,
so I boxed it up.
- These are just the samples.
- That's all you gave me.
- When you sign up, you commit
to product for the year.
- How much product?
- I got a whole garage full
for you.
- Maybe I'll give it
another shot.
- You just gotta get
your groove.
- What's the deal with local
news these days, anyways?
It's like, what's the point?
Unless you don't have a phone,
because I'm pretty sure
by the time you get home
and it's 11:00 p.m.,
you've been reading
all about everything
that's been happening all day.
It's kind of like, uh,
when parents send you a meme
after six months,
and you're like, "Um, that's
not funny anymore guys."
She was smoking in home room.
I know, but why did you care
so much?
- It's the principle
of the thing.
- That's why you're so good
at your job.
- Secondhand smoke
causes lung cancer.
- You've always been
a professional narc.
- Mm.
And then she told
the whole school
that I got genital warts
from my dad.
I told her that in confidence.
Last part was a joke.
- Oh.
- Oh, come on,
you would have done
the same thing
to somebody like me.
- I honestly probably wouldn't
have even known you.
- Well, definitely wasn't
homecoming queen.
- Me either.
- Or on prom committee.
- Or cheer squad.
- Okay, I was cheer squad.
- A-ha.
- But I was kicked out.
- Partying?
- Um...
manic depressive mom.
- Sucks.
- If it makes you feel
any better,
I didn't make it to
any of the dances either.
- Oh, I went to prom
with my dad.
- And do not even
get me started
on how useless
the weather people are.
- My husband hates
my best friend.
- So what I'm learning
here is,
you're basically
a better person than me.
- I'm not so sure about that.
.
♪
- Don't forget the hook.
Ooh!
Oh.
There it is.
- What's up?
Now you the coach?
- Used to beat your ass.
When was that?
When we were in diapers?
♪
Well, what's up?
Come teach me something.
♪
- It could get ugly.
- Good.
Let's see what you got, man.
♪
You good?
- Yeah.
♪
- Hands like this, right?
- Yeah.
- Oh.
♪
- Damn.
- You pick up some moves
at that Ochoa fight?
- Kid kept dropping his hands.
- That could get you
into trouble.
- Or draws them in.
♪
Hey,
what was that knockout like?
- Boy got whooped.
- Nothing like ringside seats,
huh?
- Yeah, I could hear
his whole nose explode.
- How's that?
- Come on.
Whoo.
♪
- Kid got cracked.
Yeah.
Thing is,
you weren't at that fight,
right?
♪
Too busy putting a bullet
in that girl's face.
♪
- Sometimes I work weekends,
bro.
♪
- So...
you were just gonna--
What?
Keep it to yourself?
- It don't concern you, dude.
- No, no--it does.
When a cop ruins my breakfast
over it.
- I'll buy you some eggs,
come on.
- Did you do it for her?
Huh?
- Don't worry about it.
- Oh...
Gangster Rio
had to whip it out.
- I got it covered.
- Show the soccer mom
how big it is.
- She knows.
- Aw, what's up?
Wore you out already?
♪
- No, cousin.
Round two.
- All right, come on--
Yo?
♪
What's that for?
- Doctor.
♪
- That was quick.
- So there was this
electrical line.
- Uh-huh.
- For the street lights.
- Cool.
- And it fell.
- Can I have that back?
- On my house.
- On your car.
- I was fine, because of
the whole rubber tire thing,
but long story short,
it ignited the gas tank.
- And you're telling me this,
because?
Hey.
- Hey.
- You want the good news
or the bad news?
- Good.
- You can stay at St. Anne's.
- How?
- Well--
- Yo, you're out of Q-Tips.
- That's my toothbrush.
- I'll get you back.
Roomie.
- In case it wasn't clear,
that's the bad news.
- So how'd you get it?
- Just being myself.
- Sometimes it's worth it.
- What are you gonna buy?
- Something special for you.
- How'd you get that?
Just being myself.
♪
- Monkey?
I thought Mom
was picking you up.
♪
- You awake?
- Mm-hmm.
♪
- Never did it for her.
- Okay.
- I did it for me.
♪
- Okay.
- What smells so good?
♪
- Chef Boyardee.
- That Washington?
- The Queen.
- Ugh.
I hate Canadians.
.
♪