‐ Previously
on "Good Girls"...
‐ Dear, Dean,
I'm going to tell you
exactly what to do
and how to do it.
‐ I know how we're going
to wash that money.
We're robbing it, Stan.
‐ It's an armored truck.
‐ Swap fake for real.
‐ Yo, Neil!
‐ I can't stop thinking
about you.
‐ He wants more than dinner.
‐ DL Dave, you know, he and I
were, like, all over.
I mean, like, everywhere.
‐ You want it to be her?
‐ Yes.
‐ Get something
to convince a DA.
‐ Selling hot tubs
in my class?
‐ Kahuna Spas would love
to be part of the ride.
‐ He's walking right into it.
‐ That's 'cause he has no idea
what's going on.
‐ I got the account.
‐ That's great!
‐ I also had to give him
the books.
‐ Dean Boland,
you're under arrest.
‐ Dean,
I'll explain everything.
‐ What am I under arrest for?
‐ Can I help you?
♪ ♪
‐ Yeah, I'm gonna
need a refill.
‐ We don't do that.
‐ You do for Mountain Dew.
‐ It's not the same.
‐ Haven't I seen you
at our games before?
‐ Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Yeah, suck it!
You serious with that?
‐ Hey!
‐ Yeah, you're a cheerleader,
right?
‐ Can you do something
about your friends?
‐ Hey, ass face!
‐ Hey, you dick!
‐ There you go!
‐ Oh, bull's‐eye!
‐ Yeah, that's right!
You better keep running!
‐ Hurry!
‐ Go, go, go!
♪ ♪
‐ ♪ I want you, aah, aah ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ I wanna wake up ♪
‐ Pigs.
‐ Smarter than dogs, right?
‐ Still gross.
‐ Yeah, well,
so are my friends.
Oh, no.
♪ ♪
‐ What?
‐ Every time I hear this song,
just really weird
things happen.
Look, I just,
I can't be responsible
for anything I might do, okay?
‐
‐ ♪ I want a girl
with extensions in her hair ♪
♪ Bamboo earrings,
at least two pair ♪
♪ A Fendi bag ♪
‐
Okay, stop, I need that back.
‐ No, it's okay,
don't worry about it.
I got, I got it, look.
♪ I need an around ♪
‐
‐ ♪ An around the way girl ♪
‐ ♪ She's the only one for me ♪
‐ ♪ I need an around
the way girl ♪
‐ It was Elizabeth, right?
‐ Beth.
‐ Kay, well, I'm Dean.
‐ I know.
‐ You do?
‐
You're the quarterback.
‐ Yeah, I know.
‐
‐ And don't worry about this.
I got it, okay?
♪ ♪
‐ Can you hear me?
How'd you sleep?
‐ I didn't.
‐ This was this morning.
Jane went to school full Elsa.
Kenny's in Kalamazoo
at his tournament.
‐ Do they know?
‐ Not yet.
And the accounts are frozen,
so...
you might be here a minute.
‐ Tell me one thing.
Was he part of it?
Beth.
The whole time?
‐ I love you.
‐ We're finished here.
‐ I'm gonna fix this, okay?
I promise.
‐ How?
‐ That from the minibar?
‐ Mm‐hmm.
Is he talking?
‐ So it's just a coincidence
that you're eating corn nuts
which are now gone
from the corn nuts slot.
‐ You can take it from my room.
Did you get anything
out of him?
‐ Not a word.
‐ Get me in there.
‐ What's the point?
You're already getting
a new office.
‐ I am?
‐ Out of the basement.
‐ With a window?
‐ Pack your bags.
‐ Five minutes.
‐ Take the W
and call it a day.
‐ He's protecting her.
‐ Why would he do that?
‐ 'Cause he has no idea
what she's gotten into.
‐ They've been married
for 20 years.
‐ So have you.
‐ What's that?
‐ Your wife has no idea
who you've gotten into.
But I do.
Because he's a real
chatty Kathy.
‐ Are you really doing this?
‐ Just give me
five minutes alone.
‐ I didn't know
you had it in you.
‐ But I know
everything that's‐‐
‐ All right, all right,
all right, enough.
You got your five minutes.
Leave the money for the corn
nuts on top of the minibar.
‐
‐ So I'm sure you all have
a lot of questions,
and I'm going to do
my very best
to answer each
and every one of them.
‐ Where's Dean at?
‐ He is a hot tub conference.
‐ A very important one.
‐ Are we in trouble?
‐ No, no, no, no.
Just a little
misunderstanding...
With our taxes.
‐ Can we FaceTime him?
‐ Ooh.
‐ There's not real good
reception in, um...
‐ Uh, North Pole.
‐ Yeah.
‐ He's with Santa?
‐ So if you all
just hang tight,
we will have
this all cleared up,
and we'll get back to work
in a jiff.
‐ Does this count
as vacation days?
‐ Think of it like
a snow day.
Just enjoy yourself.
Take a little me time.
‐ But you're still paying us,
right?
♪ ♪
I miss Gayle.
‐ When's he coming back?
‐ Uh, as soon as it's over.
‐ When's that?
‐ When he's done.
‐ Who wants another slice?
‐ He really screwed the pooch,
huh?
Anything I can do
to help my homie,
let me know.
‐
‐ Where is our mom?
‐ She's, um, helping your dad.
‐ I need a loan.
‐ For what?
‐ Bail.
‐ Yeah, that's not my thing.
‐ I need to get him out.
‐ Nah.
You need fall guy
if you're ever trying
to make money again.
‐ It's not his fault.
‐ I told you to be smart,
right?
‐ I was.
‐ Then how'd they
get your books?
‐ He didn't know.
‐ Why he's
the perfect fall guy.
‐ He didn't do anything!
‐ That's what
makes it beautiful.
Got nothing to say.
Look, they'll cut a deal.
Three years, club Fed.
‐ What about my kids?
‐ Visitation.
‐ What about me?
‐ Your boy will come back
in better shape
than when he went in.
Might even want
to hit it again.
‐ There's gotta be a way
to get him out!
‐ Do the crime, do the time.
‐ But nothing ever sticks
to you.
‐ Yeah, I got luck on my side.
Maybe you do too.
‐ What's that mean?
‐ Sink that eight ball.
Corner pocket,
I'll cover his bail.
‐
I don't play pool.
‐ And I don't do loans.
‐
♪ ♪
Like that?
‐ Yeah, just like that.
Just hit it straight, okay?
‐ Ha!
I did it!
‐ Lucky shot.
‐ No, a deal is a deal.
‐ Yeah, you're right.
Take it out of the cut
you owe me.
‐ The place is swarming
with secret service agents.
‐ So?
‐ So I can't wash,
and I definitely can't print.
We're shut down.
‐
That's why you need a fall guy.
‐ Mom bootcamp.
‐ That's what you get
for exercising.
‐ The bitch made me
do her nails.
‐ Don't they have to tell you
if they're cops?
‐ Only if you ask.
‐ That's not a real thing,
and she's secret service.
‐ How's Deansie holding up?
‐ He doesn't have
his mouth guard
or his sleep apnea machine,
and his cellmate is in
for trying to set
a guy on fire.
‐ That good, huh?
‐ Ugh, pink flavor.
‐ He can't be my fall guy.
‐ Well, it can't be you.
‐ It should.
‐ You have four kids.
‐ So does he.
‐ Ugh, orange flavor.
‐ Stop biting
into all of them.
‐ What kinda psycho
gets somebody fruit chocolates?
‐ A hitman.
‐ The man is sending you
chocolate now?
‐ I mean, kinda.
‐ He wants me to go
on a job with him.
‐ Where?
‐ Fiji.
‐
Maybe if these were caramels.
‐ I wish he'd just
put a bullet in me.
‐ At this point
I think you're looking
at a little pickle tickle.
‐ What am I gonna do?
‐ Over the pants, real fast.
‐ About Dean.
‐ We'll figure something out.
‐ It's either him or me.
‐ Is it?
‐ Isn't it?
‐ On "First 48"
people call in all the time
to confess to crimes
they didn't commit.
‐ Why would anyone do that?
‐ I don't know, weirdo loners
with nothing to lose.
Maybe being convicted
gives them some purpose.
‐ Huh.
‐ Swimming, tennis,
art classes.
What kinda resort is this?
‐ Not a resort exactly.
‐ Damn it!
‐ Can you take that upstairs?
‐ I mixed the trapezoid up
with the rectangle again.
‐ I'm conducting business.
‐ Your aunt's just gonna
send me right back down.
‐ She's napping.
You're allowed in the parlor
till 4:30.
‐
It's my room too.
‐ So what's the dillio?
‐ Well, think of it
as a fresh start.
‐ We would pay off
all your credit card debt
and throw in 100 grand
for your trouble.
‐ Paid in installments.
‐ Why would you do that for me?
‐ Well, you'd actually
be doing it for me.
‐ It's a jail?
‐ With benefits!
‐ Except for the part
where you can't leave.
‐ Bu‐but I hear the library
is exquisite.
‐ I know this is a huge ask,
but you're the one who said
you wanted to help out
your homie.
‐ You wanna pay me more money
than I've ever made
in my entire life
to have my own room,
unlimited TV privileges,
and vegan‐friendly meals
on an all male campus?
What's the shower situation?
‐ Um, probably group.
‐ Well, how do we get
this party started?
‐ Um, just confess I guess,
right?
‐
‐ Well, I‐‐
I think might actually need
to do more than that.
‐ Wait.
What do you mean?
‐ Well, they have Dean's name
on all the accounts,
so he may need to
get caught with something
way worse,
you know, just to make sure.
‐ Damn it!
‐ Chillax, man!
You're gonna wake my aunt!
‐ Remember when calculators
used to double A?
‐ Remember when our calculators
were our brain?
‐
This is supposed to be
the smart school, right?
‐ Maybe they're doing
bigger math.
‐ Yeah, but who just has
a lithium ion 2032
just laying around?
A physicist?
Cyborg?
‐ Can I ask you something?
‐ Yeah.
‐ I need to borrow some money.
‐
Okay.
‐ It's more than
you got on you.
‐ What's going on?
‐ And I'm gonna need it
in 1s.
‐ I'm not stealing
from the club.
‐ It's for Dean.
‐ Why do you need all 1s?
‐ To get him out of it.
‐ Beth put you up to this.
‐ I offered.
‐ Why?
‐ Because when you were in
jail, she did the same for you.
‐
Think there's one of those
batteries in my watch.
‐ Stan, toss me the aloe.
‐ Okay.
♪ ♪
Oh, I think Mindy
used it all.
‐ I got pole burn bad.
‐ How 'bout some ice?
‐
That's my song.
‐ Eesh, take it easy out there.
‐ Thanks, Stanimal.
‐
♪ ♪
‐ Hey, buddy.
‐ Yo, Gene.
‐ Got a sec?
‐ Uh, yeah, man,
I was just about to head back
out to the floor.
‐ George'll cover you.
Have a seat.
‐ All right, can always make
time for the boss.
‐ So what that wife of yours
make you for lunch today, huh?
‐
Uh, what was it today?
Penne pasta
with those little green balls.
‐ Peas?
‐ No, not those.
The other ones, uh...
‐ Capers?
‐ Yep, there it is,
those things.
‐ She treats you pretty good,
huh?
‐ Yeah, man.
She's the best.
‐ We treat you okay?
‐ Uh, yeah.
‐ You happy here?
‐ Hey, man, listen.
I'm glad to have the job,
you know?
‐ Good to hear, buddy.
‐ Yeah.
‐ So there's no reason
you'd be upset with me.
‐ What?
‐ You'd tell me if you were
having any problems.
‐ For sure.
‐ I got your back.
‐ 100%.
‐ You got mine?
'Cause something's
not adding up here, you know?
A few weeks ago, that thing
with the bank truck burning up.
‐ Oh, yeah, that was crazy.
‐ Yeah, crazy.
Crazy how much it cost me.
‐ But, uh, doesn't insurance
cover that stuff for‐‐
‐ I have to keep them in the
champagne room a little longer.
‐
Yeah, that's why
you the king, man.
‐ Can't have it happen again
though.
‐ Not on my watch.
I hear you loud and clear.
All right.
‐ Oh, and whenever's
good for you,
I would love to hear
about them private parties
you've been running
behind my back with my girls.
‐ Now's good.
‐ This is currency.
Like, top dollar.
You could trade it
for anything:
supplies, TV time,
protection.
‐ Who are you?
‐ I know your wife.
‐
I want a lawyer here.
‐ Chill, I just gave you
a bunch of ramen.
I had this friend
in high school.
Super cool.
Captain of
the cheerleading squad.
‐ Hmm.
‐ Always had the newest jeans.
The most expensive makeup.
Everyone wanted to be her,
including me.
She threw the best parties,
and I would bring
the wine coolers.
I was, like, in.
We'd go to the movies,
the mall.
We were besties before people
used the word "besties."
And then my parents
took away my fake ID,
and she stopped
calling me back.
‐ What's your point?
‐ Women like your wife,
they use people,
and when they're done,
they throw them in the trash.
‐ So you don't know my wife.
‐ I know the wrong person
is sitting across
from me right now.
‐ So what?
‐ I just need something on her.
Without it, you're gonna need
a lot more of these.
So what's gonna be, Mr. Boland?
‐ Hey.
Is your sister home?
‐ Doesn't wanna see you.
‐ Did you give her
any of my messages?
‐ Hates your guts.
‐ She said that?
‐ Thinks you're a total loser,
regrets ever looking
at your ugly face,
and wishes you'd just die.
‐ Hmm.
‐ Brutal.
‐ Yeah, so can I
just go talk to her?
‐ What's it worth to you?
‐ Wow.
Okay.
All right, fine.
‐ 4 bucks?
‐ That's all I got.
‐ You can owe me.
Deansie's here!
‐ No one calls me that.
‐ Annie.
Mom needs you.
What are you doing here?
‐ I called you
like five times.
‐
I've been busy.
‐ You haven't been
at any of the games.
‐ I got a lot going on.
‐ I thought we were cool.
‐ We are.
‐ 'Cause if I'm way off,
it's totally okay.
‐ It's not that.
‐ I don't wanna look like
a dick, you know?
‐ I can't find her meds.
‐ Be right there.
‐
It's not you.
‐ Gotcha.
So it's definitely me then.
‐ It's not either of us.
‐ It's okay.
Don't worry about it.
I was gonna ask you to prom,
but it's all good.
‐ You were?
‐ I don't wanna put
any pressure on you.
‐ I'd love to go.
‐ Uh, okay.
Cool.
‐ Yeah.
‐
‐ Mrs. Boland?
He doesn't wanna see you.
‐
Turns out if you
make a fart noise
with every math problem
he gets right, he can focus.
‐ Got your bills.
‐ How'd it go?
‐
Piece of cake.
‐ I'm gonna pay you back.
It's just gonna take a second.
‐ No rush.
‐ Really?
You good?
‐
Just thirsty.
‐ At a certain point,
you don't really
need the glass, do you?
‐ Had a day.
‐ He'll get over it.
‐ What if he doesn't?
‐ You've done way worse.
‐ I'm a monster.
‐ I mean, he stuck around
after you bone surfed
the guy who shot him.
‐ The kind
that climbs skyscrapers
and destroys cities.
‐ Yeah, well,
at least your kids
are still talking to you.
‐ Because they don't know.
‐ Ben won't even look at me.
‐ Maybe they've all
just had enough of us.
‐
God, we are monsters.
‐ Incoming.
Last dance, ladies.
‐ Let's make it a good one.
‐ Not too good.
♪ ♪
‐ You sure about this?
‐ It'll work.
‐ Looks legit.
‐ It's not.
‐ Our worst batch yet.
‐ Your one way ticket
to Shangri‐La.
‐ All right.
See you hotties
on the other side.
I'd like to open
a new account.
‐ Certainly, sir.
I'm just gonna need you
to fill out a few forms
and a valid ID.
Thank you.
Um, just to let you know,
we do require
a minimum balance of $50.
‐ Oh, that won't be a problem.
‐ Uh, w‐what are you doing?
‐ Giving you 100,000 smackaroos
to babysit.
‐ Um, anything over 10 grand
we have to report to the IRS.
‐ Ooh.
That'll be a problem.
‐ Thought it might be.
‐ So how 'bout we do 10 grand
in ten different accounts?
‐ Um, we don't do that here,
sir.
‐ Okay, okay.
9 grand
in nine different accounts,
and uh,
you keep this for yourself.
‐ Is there a problem here?
‐ Uh, yes, there is.
I'm being profiled.
‐ Excuse me?
‐ She won't take
my hard‐earned money.
‐ How is that profiling?
‐ Mustache.
‐  That's not a thing.
‐ Sir, we're
a family‐owned bank.
‐ Then take my money,
it's good.
‐ We really don't want
any trouble.
‐ Go ahead.
Test it yourself.
‐ Why would we need
to do that?
‐ Been in there a while.
‐ Can we please just go?
‐ No, I wanna watch.
‐ Well, I don't.
I feel bad enough as it is.
‐ Shh.
Listen.
‐ Here we go.
‐ Kay, show 'em the money.
‐ Ooh, ooh.
It is on.
‐ Oh, boy,
he is getting worked.
‐
‐ Was that really necessary?
‐ Fell for the honeypot.
‐ Okay, what are
they doing now?
‐ All right.
What?
‐ Uh‐oh.
‐ I go in the back.
Hey, I go in the back.
Hey.
Guys.
‐ What the hell?
‐ What happened?
‐ I think I got robbed.
‐ By cops?
.
‐ She's stable now.
We had to sedate her
to pump her stomach.
She'll be out for a while.
Any other family
I should notify?
‐ It's just me and my sister.
‐ Your mom's gonna be okay.
‐ I went to pick you up.
‐ Oh, God.
What'd she say?
‐ That you didn't wanna go.
At least not with me,
'cause...
I'm the dumbest, ugliest
tool that's ever lived.
‐ I'm gonna kill her.
‐ But 40 bucks later,
and here I am.
‐ You didn't have to come.
‐ Got you something.
You look great by the way.
‐ So do you.
‐
Yeah, I know.
♪ ♪
‐ Um, do you want anything
from the vending machine?
‐ No.
‐ Okay, good, 'cause...
your little sister
took all my money.
‐
‐ Here's a thought.
‐ Oh, boy.
‐ I go right back in there,
grab that guard's gun,
shoot up the place.
‐ Why?
‐ Get their attention.
‐ So then they put you in jail
with Dean
and not instead of.
‐ Oh.
Plan C‐‐
‐ Please no.
‐ Try a different bank.
‐ And deposit what?
Those crooked cops
took everything we made.
‐ Hey, maybe
they'll realize it's fake,
and they'll come back
and nab him.
‐ No, they didn't even
look at my ID.
‐ Okay.
What's plan C?
‐ Track those guys down.
‐ The cops?
‐ We pull in front of their
cruiser, jam on the brakes.
And they slam into us.
Bam!
Airbags go off.
Pssh!
We hop out,
shatter their window.
Cchh!
Get the keys to the trunk.
‐ Make it stop.
‐ How can it possibly be this
difficult to get you arrested?
‐ 'Cause I'm invisible.
‐ What do you mean?
‐ I've been that way
my whole life.
Smack in the middle
of nine kids,
you get used to being left
in a hot car.
‐ That's terrible.
‐ It all kinda changed for me
when the D‐man got hired.
Brought me to lunch
with the rest of the crew.
Called me Eric.
‐ What'd everybody else
call you?
‐ Scott.
‐ I see that.
He's got a Scott vibe.
‐ Anyway, lunch becomes
work drinks,
and next thing you know,
I'm finally a real person.
Oh, they don't make them
like Dean Boland anymore.
But I don't need
to tell you that.
‐ I know.
‐ Plan D‐‐
‐ No more plans, Eric.
‐ Thank Jesus.
‐ What do you want me to do?
‐ Nothing.
Hey.
I made breakfast for dinner.
‐ I'm not hungry.
What are you doing?
‐ You are gonna eat this.
‐ Can I go to the bathroom?
‐ You love breakfast
for dinner.
‐ I ate at Mark's house!
‐ Oh, a lacrosse buddy?
‐ What do you want?
‐ I want you to talk me
like a normal person.
‐ You're not a normal person.
‐ Then talk to me like you want
me to be your mom again, like‐‐
‐ I don't even know
what that means.
‐ Like you don't hate me
so much.
'Cause, you know,
if you...
if you're unhappy here...
you could always stay
at your dad's more.
‐ You think I hate you?
‐ You haven't talked to me
in, like, three days.
‐ It doesn't mean I hate you.
‐ Kay.
‐ I love breakfast for dinner.
‐ Me too.
‐ Makes sense though.
‐ Hmm?
‐ Just for, like, practice
and school and stuff.
‐ What?
‐ Staying with Dad more.
‐ Oh, yeah?
‐ Nancy would never
go for it though.
She's, like,
so OCD with Dakota.
‐ I could talk to her.
‐ Really?
‐ Why not?
‐ I can just come back
for some of the weekends.
‐ If that's what you want,
yeah.
‐ Not that I want it.
It would just save a lot
of time going back and forth.
‐ Cool.
‐ I still gotta pee.
‐ Yes.
‐ No classes today?
‐ I don't really
teach boot camp.
‐ I don't really sell hot tubs.
‐ Yeah, I know.
‐ Mommy!
Look how high I'm going!
‐ Wow!
Like an astronaut!
It all started
about a year ago.
I robbed a grocery store.
It was supposed to be
one and done.
Don't you want to record this
or something?
‐ It doesn't matter.
‐ Why?
‐ Your husband
pled guilty today.
‐ Mommy!
Mommy, watch me!
‐ Jesus!
‐ Your elderly neighbor
was getting curious
the longer I stood
at your door.
‐ Why does everyone think
they can just let themselves
in to my house?
‐ These things are
extremely easy to find
once you know
what you're looking for.
‐ I'd offer you a drink, but...
‐ All set.
‐ I can't go to Fiji with you.
‐ Why not?
Huts over the water,
looking at the fish
while you sip your cocktail,
nothing but privacy.
‐ I'm in a little bit
of trouble right now.
‐ Perfect time for an escape.
‐ And I have kids.
‐ Happy to make arrangements
for them as well.
I hear your husband's gonna
be tied up for a while.
‐ Put down your tea.
‐ Pardon me?
‐ Get naked, come on.
‐ What?
‐ Let's go!
‐ Now?
‐ Why, you need a pill?
'Cause I've gotta pick up
my kids soon.
‐ I think there's been
a misunderstanding.
‐ Really?
Because you have made it
very clear
that this is exactly
what I need to do.
‐ Not like this.
‐ Oh, I'm sorry.
Was I supposed to enjoy it?
Maybe fall in love with you?
End up on some remote island
so you can live out
your twisted mid‐life crisis?
‐ I thought you wanted...
more.
‐ From you?
‐ From your life.
‐ Oh, and I need a man
to do that?
‐ What do you want?
‐ To be nothing like you.
‐ A little late for that.
‐ Why?
‐ You hired me, remember?
‐ Then why don't you pull up
your pants like a big boy
and do your job?
‐ Well.
Seems I read this all wrong.
I'll fulfill our contract
when I get back.
‐ Thank you.
‐ Hide this under a real rock.
♪ ♪
‐ 'Sup, Hill?
‐ Hey, can you grab me
some of that lemon pepper
on your way home?
‐ Mmm, might be
a little late tonight, baby.
‐ Aren't you lunch shift today?
‐ Yeah, boss got me
doing some extra.
‐ Okay.
Should I do Cajun?
‐ That sounds good.
‐ All right, I'll throw
your plate in the oven.
‐ Hug those animals for me.
‐ Everything okay?
‐ Yeah, just in the middle
of something.
‐ All right, boo.
‐ Okay, see you later, baby.
‐ What's for dinner?
‐
Chicken.
‐ Nice.
This won't take long.
‐ So what's this cat
look like, man?
‐ He's a little bitch.
‐ He alone?
‐ Nah, he lives
with his brother.
‐ And what's he look like?
‐ Big bitch.
‐
What if they don't
give me the money?
‐ Don't come out till they do.
‐
I got a family, man.
‐ Should've thought about that
before you messed with mine.
‐ Car on or off?
‐ Put on
my Yacht Rock playlist.
♪ ♪
‐ ♪ Girl, girl,
you're so hard on me ♪
♪ Girl, girl, you're
so hard on me ♪
♪ Girl, girl,
when you talk to me ♪
♪ ♪
♪ You tell me lies
and you set me free ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Turned my home
into your castle ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Oh oh oh ♪
‐ I miss Daddy.
‐ Me too.
‐ Does he miss us?
‐ Always.
‐ Why won't he call us back?
‐ Dad is not at a conference.
‐ Where is he?
♪ ♪
‐ Hi!
‐ I love your pigtails!
Did you do them yourself?
‐ No, Mommy did them.
‐ Is there a fence, and if you
touch it, will it zap you?
♪ ♪
‐ What's it like in there?
‐ Are they nice?
‐ I've made some
pretty good friends.
I get my own room.
‐ Do you get ice cream
when you're done?
‐ As much ice cream
as you could ever possibly eat.
‐ ♪ Girl, girl,
you're so hard on me ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Girl, girl,
you're so hard on me ♪
when you talk to me ♪
♪ You tell me lies
and you set me free ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Take me by the hand ♪
♪ Then try to understand ♪
♪ ♪
♪ You can't make it alone ♪
♪ No no ♪
♪ Oh oh oh ♪
‐ ♪ Come to the dark
with your fate ♪
♪ ♪
♪ All at once,
you're in another place ♪
♪ ♪
♪ You can't make it alone ♪
♪ No no ♪