.
- Previously
on "Good Girls"...
- A few weeks ago
that thing with
the bank truck burning up,
crazy how much it cost me.
- Can't do another one.
I have a wife.
- Oh, the bitch
who stole my money?
- Convince women
these are real,
you get ten times the money.
He didn't know any women
who could afford a real one.
- And we do?
- We might have to find them.
- We could send him to private
school, St. Anne's.
- Did you see the game?
- Dude, you were so good.
You scored, like, 20 goals.
- I at least want
my husband out.
- Not until we know
where the money goes.
- I made a deal to get you out.
[gate buzzes]
- What did he make
you do this time?
- It's not him.
- Do you want this over or not?
- What if he finds it?
- Improvise.
- Grandma loves Grisham.
- Let me ask you all something.
What are we doing here?
- Like, right now?
- I mean this operation.
- Yes, you.
- Trying to
get the bad guy.
- Ah, how?
- Yes, yes, go ahead.
- By following the money.
- And what would get
in the way of that?
- Um...
- If you don't...
what?
- We don't...
- If you don't--
- Show up on time.
- 'Cause today we got here
before you did.
- No, no, uh-uh.
If you don't
tell us...
that you're
screwing the target.
- [gasps]
Yeah!
Why didn't you tell us?
- Um, because I'm not?
- Your wire would disagree.
- Okay.
I'm not screwing anyone,
all right?
- Except your friends
if you want to keep this deal.
- You did it
with him again, dude?
- Not it.
- Then what?
- You know, the other thing.
- Did it involve your vagina?
- Sort of.
- And his penis?
- No.
- So his hm?
- So his huh.
- Okay, I was trying to
distract him.
- By trapping his fingers?
- Because he was going
to see your wire.
- Unbelievable.
- In his abuelita'shouse.
- I really don't care
how many bases you rounded.
- They just call her grandma.
- Oh, the boss, right?
- How was I supposed to know?
- Now we're right back
where we started.
- None of this is my fault.
- Okay, just what are we
supposed to do now?
- 'Cause, like,
we really need this deal.
- You are back on the bench.
One of you two
will have to pinch-hit.
- Now I'm getting confused
because the baseball stuff
is blurring with
the sexy stuff and...
- No part of that man
is getting any of this.
- Her wire's still hot.
- Anything good?
- Well, Grandma loves
"Two and a Half Men."
She's totally sick of CPK,
and her foot doctor
appointment's on Tuesday.
- What about our guy?
- Oh, he's gonna need her.
- Just don't ask me
to wear a wire again.
- What were you
guys talking about?
- Hey.
Little Money wants me to cut
the crusts off now.
- You thought about how we're
gonna sell these things?
- Ask me, it's the best part.
- All right. Check this.
- Hm, that's swank.
- Four bedrooms,
open floor plan,
mad curb appeal.
- Yeah, who's staying there?
- We are.
It's right by Harry's school.
- Mm-hmm.
- With all those rich moms,
it's the kind of place
you buy a top-notch purse.
- Yeah, if you got
two Gs a night.
- One of the girls
at the salons
cleans these pads
in-between guests.
- Well, won't they know that
we don't live there?
- Not if we say we do.
- Nah, I can't fake
that kind of money.
- All these bitches
care about are their houses,
their charities,
and what everyone else has.
- Exactly.
- Okay, you can
just be my arm candy.
Hey, it's your ass on the line.
- Beth can't be a part of this.
- Okay.
- I mean, she makes everything
about her.
- You're right.
- No, I don't think you're
hearing what I'm saying.
- I am.
- She does whatever she wants,
whenever she wants.
- I know.
- And the rules don't
ever apply.
- You're right.
- Next thing you know,
you got a bullet in your other
knee, I'm back in jail--
- And she's living large.
- Yes.
She can't even hear about this.
- I agree.
- You know I'm talking about
Beth Boland, right?
- Yup.
- Your homie.
- Got it.
- Really?
- She doesn't tell me
everything she does.
- Huh.
Okay.
Good.
- They were out of Windex.
- That boy's onto something.
That's good as hell.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, yeah.
- Mugs?
- Sit down.
- I was really hoping
for more of
a to-go kind of
coffee situation.
[sighs]
Just, uh,
just lay it on me, bruh.
- You were right.
- Hm, exciting.
About what?
- I want to pull Ben out
of St. Anne's.
- Wait, what?
- I don't want him to
turn into a rich dick.
- But you wanted him to
go in the first place.
- Well, I changed
my mind, okay?
- What, now that he
has friends?
- This place is evil.
- He has teachers
that love him.
- His teachers will love
him in public school.
- But what about lacrosse?
- He can play
lacrosse anywhere.
- They just got
into the playoffs.
- It's fine, all right, fine,
but you deal with all
the birthday stuff.
- What does that have to do
with anything?
- You remember Keeley Shukert's
birthday last weekend?
- The Swifty karaoke?
- Mm-hmm, yeah.
Well, it turns out that it
wasn't a themed party.
Taylor Swift
actually showed up.
- Taylor Swift came to
a 14-year-old's birthday party?
- Yeah, and she played
the whole "1989" album.
- Did she do
"Out of the Woods?"
- The whole album.
- What about "Clean"?
- The whole "1989" album, okay?
All of it.
Every single song.
And then she stayed
and ate cake.
- My God.
- Yeah. Yeah.
So, you know, what's Ben gonna
expect for his birthday?
Selena Gomez?
- I think she charges
by the song
or by, like, the hour, or by--
- Who cares?
That's not the point.
The point is
Ben can't think this is
what birthday parties are.
- I mean, he can't be a dick.
- No, so we gotta pull him out.
- Right.
- Stat.
- What's faster than stat?
- I don't know.
Maybe you'll figure it out.
- Hang on.
- Well, you gotta tell him.
- Why me?
- 'Cause I'm eating
the tuition.
- Jesus.
- This sucks.
- Yeah.
- Think they forgot to put
the cinnamon in it.
I think that's what it is.
Hold on.
- Hey, I fed the kids
fish sticks,
but I told them
it was mozzarella.
We should get Kenny to cut
his fingernails.
- Why?
He looks like a wizard.
- Are you going out?
- Yeah, I'm gonna
run some errands.
- Like...
like errands?
- Why are you whispering?
- It's just your hair
and your makeup,
and you smell good, you know.
- No, I don't.
- Is this, like, an op?
- [whispering]
Okay, between us--
- Yeah.
- You can't tell.
- I won't.
- Swear on Emma's life.
- Can I swear on Kenny's?
- Seriously.
- I'm sorry. Yes.
I won't tell, I promise.
- I'm going to
the grocery store.
- [chuckles]
[mellow rock music playing]
♪
- What are you drinking?
- Something strong.
- Nah, come on now.
So dinner was, uh...
fun,
yeah?
- Parts of it.
- Got a problem, though.
- What's that?
- Grandma's pissed
we missed dessert.
- What'd you tell her?
- That you're a fan, too.
- Tell her thank you.
- One more thing though, yeah?
- Never mind,
I'll just write her a note.
- I need a bank.
- Maybe try your
mattress this time.
- Safety deposit box
would be even better.
- Not when your husband's
under house arrest
for laundering money.
- That's why it can't be you.
- What about the other girls?
- Nah.
Same kind of heat.
- Okay, who's
it supposed to be?
- It don't matter.
As long as
they're in mom jeans,
no one will think twice.
- Why jeans?
- 'Cause a dress
like that draws
the wrong kind of attention.
.
- She's not a mom.
- She just needs to get him
to talk about his money.
- She doesn't look like a mom.
- They record that and boom.
- She doesn't even
walk like a mom.
- Racketeering, tax evasion--
- 'Cause she's not a mom.
- She has a mom.
- No gummy bears before
night-night, little fella.
Don't run
with scissors, tiger.
Just getting my mom on.
[chuckles]
Hmm?
- We're so gonna die.
- How hard can it be?
- Literally nothing
gets past this guy.
- So teach me.
[retro synth music]
- How many kids?
- Two.
- Names.
- Tom and Sally.
[horn blares]
- 'Cause it's 1958.
- Bryar and Julian.
- Okay.
- Bryar with a Y.
- How old's Julian?
- Um...
- Quick!
- One and a half.
[horn blares]
- In months.
- Always in months.
- What?
- Everything under two years
is in months.
- Everything over two years
is in years.
- Why?
- Never ask why.
- Only kids ask why.
- Let's go again.
Start from the top.
♪
- Now it's a mom bag.
- When's bedtime?
- Seven.
[horn blares]
Eight.
I go to bed at nine.
- It's a trick question.
- There's no point
in setting one
'cause they'll never listen.
♪
Do you want to live?
- It's so gross.
- It's 2:15.
What are you late for?
- School pickup.
- Just pickup.
- How many times are we gonna
go around this mountain?
- No one says school.
- Okay, just...
- Oh, no, don't give him that.
It's too much sugar.
Yeah, the bad kind.
Not the good kind.
You know what? Give him the
sweet potatoes in the fridge.
I puréed them myself.
Don't use the pouch.
I started adding tarragon
to introduce spice.
Sorry I'm late.
Marty doesn't know what
to feed the kids.
- Okay, yeah, just do bath time
and then I'll be back
in time for stories, okay?
All right. Love you. Bye.
[exhales]
- So?
Julian has a temp.
102.
And a rash,
which I was freaking out
because I thought
it was measles
'cause he just had his MMR,
but no.
Turns out it's roseola,
which Bryar never had,
but she did have
foot and mouth,
so I thought maybe
it was that at first,
but I was wrong.
Poor little monkey.
Hmm.
Anyway, I forgot to write down
what the pharmacist
told me to get.
Where is that pen?
- Oh, shoot.
Here it is.
- She's ready.
Did you fix it?
- It wasn't broken.
- Danny said he couldn't
do his book report.
- Well, all he had to do was
replace the ink cartridge.
- What is the Aqua Joy 2000?
- It's the most powerful
home spa on the market.
- Yeah, I know, but why does
it say that we bought it?
- Because we did.
And we need it.
- You said that
no one needs a hot tub.
- That was before
my wife decided to go
all Donnie Brasco on us.
- What are you talking about?
This is money
that we don't have.
- For starters, it's very loud.
Right, so in case you
and the girls ever need
to get into a conversation
that you don't want other
people to hear--
- No one is listening.
- How do you know?
- Because I'm the informant.
- Well, I can't risk it, okay?
- You?
- Yeah, me.
- I'm taking all the risk.
- Well, I have
the most to lose.
- Well, we don't need this.
- I need Nevada.
- There she is.
- Hey.
- Morning, ladies.
- Good morning.
- I added the chunky necklace.
It's great, right?
- No.
- It's not. It's bad.
- Beep twice if you
can hear me.
[car honks twice]
Showtime.
- Is it in the salt
and pepper shaker?
- All of it.
- Can he hear when I'm
talking to the condiments?
- All of it.
- Beep three times
in you can hear me.
[car honks three times]
Oh, my God. Damn.
- Up, ladies.
- What?
- Can't seat you 'til
your whole party's here.
- He's parking.
- Actually, I spoke to
the manager yesterday
about reserving this table.
- Well, he ain't here today.
- We really need this table.
- So do those folks.
- But there's, like,
150 other tables in here.
- This is their favorite.
- What if we ordered for him?
- Don't count.
- Why doesn't that count?
- Because we don't
seat tuna melts.
We seat people.
- Okay, we're not actually
here to have lunch.
- Well, what the heck
you doing then?
[door opens]
- Ladies.
Round of Arnold Palmers.
Thank you.
- And you can just leave out
the iced tea
for mine, thanks.
- So, lemonade.
- This is my friend.
- I'm Carolyn with a Y.
- So how do you all
know each other?
- Pick up.
- Garden class.
- I mean, well,
I knew her first from school.
- Yeah, she was
the only other mom
who would rosé all
day with me, so.
- And then she did wonders
with my perennials.
- Stop.
- You did.
- You should see what this girl
can do with a topiary.
- You'd be like, a-poosh!
- I run a small
landscaping business
when I'm not shlepping
Bryar and Julian
off to play dates,
and Gymboree, and
toddler tunes, and--
- And then we've all
been great friends ever since.
- Yes.
- Cool.
- Way cool.
- So she's trying
to grow her business,
which makes her sort of perfect
for our arrangement.
- So what do you want
me to do?
- Well, I don't know
about you guys, but um...
I can't talk shop
on an empty stomach.
- Oh.
- Y'all ready?
- Ready if you guys are.
- Sure.
- Yep.
- Okay.
- I could be ready.
Let me just--
- I'll do a BLT,
bacon extra crispy, please.
- White or wheat?
- Surprise me.
- I'll just take a Cobb salad.
In fact, do you guys all just
want Cobb salads?
- Mm, yummy.
- Yeah, that's delicious.
- Read my mind.
- Love Cobb.
- Thank you.
- So...
what do you wanna
just have her
stash a bunch of cash...
- Oh, uh, miss.
Could you wrap all that
up to-go for us?
Thank you.
- Where are we going?
- To her house.
- Why?
- You know, you never know
who's listening around here.
- Well, we could go
to my house.
- Way closer.
- It's like, right--
- Yeah.
- It's good.
- Nah.
I want to see her place.
.
- How much further?
- Uh, just ahead.
- And then?
- Just a few blocks.
- Hey, why don't
we just talk in here?
- Yeah, I mean,
it's just us.
- Super private.
- We close?
- We're here.
They're in here somewhere.
- Could just knock.
- My husband's sleeping.
- At noon?
- Yeah, he's not feeling well.
Yeah, he got it from the kids.
- Yeah, went through
the whole soccer team.
- Must've left them inside.
- Ah, that's a shame.
- Why don't we go to the park?
- Dine El Fresco?
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah, they have those,
you know, picnic tables.
[footfalls approaching]
- He's up.
- Ah, again?
- I know. Sorry, babe.
- You're gonna have to
put them on one of those
big wooden sticks,
like at Starbucks.
- So when did you move?
- Recently, yeah.
- Oh.
Ruby didn't mention it
at the recital.
- No, well yes,
it's real recent.
- Oh?
- Mm-hmm.
- Where is she anyway?
- Oh, she's on her way.
Try some cheese.
It's real good.
Can I get you a refill?
- How'd you guys get
the wholesale hookup?
- Uh,
he would be upset
if I told you.
- You know Louis Vuitton?
- Try some cheese.
Mm-hmm.
- Hmm.
- Some more?
- Is that real?
- The ten point buck.
- Oh, my God.
- He never felt a thing.
- Ruby offered to volunteer
at my animal rescue.
- Yeah, poor guy.
He got hit by a gravel truck
on I-75.
- Oh, my God.
- Yeah, yeah.
We thought this was
the best way to
kind of honor his life.
Yeah.
- What about the other ones?
- I'm sorry?
Truck killed
the whole damn family.
- [gasps] Oh.
- Try some cheese.
[phone buzzes]
- Sorry, I didn't
expect company.
- You got a glass?
- Next to the fridge.
- Right or left?
- Right.
I mean, um, I meant my right.
Not yours.
That's--
[both chuckle]
- Hmm.
[uneasy music]
♪
So how does this work?
- I'll bring you a duffel.
You keep what's inside
till I need it.
- What do I get?
- Holding fee.
- Sounds fair.
- I'mma need a key
to the box, too.
- Okay.
- Tomorrow.
Noon. Your bank.
Send all the details.
I wouldn't drink that,
by the way.
- Why not?
- It expired a week ago.
- That's it.
It's over.
- We got him, right?
- No, he got us.
- He just laid it all out.
- That was practically
a confession.
- I found this place
ten minutes
before you guys got here.
- You didn't have
time to wire it?
- I barely had time
to text you.
- [sighs]
Oh, God.
- So it's not over.
- Excuse me.
- Is it safe?
- Oh, yes, I am so
sorry about that.
Everyone, meet Irene and Phil.
Your country thanks you
for your service.
[phone buzzing]
You have a very lovely home.
My aunt in Nantucket--
.
- Dang,
it's archway after archway.
Are you kidding me?
It's like the damn Taj Mahal
if it had two ovens.
Turkey in one,
mac and cheese in the other.
Change the whole
Thanksgiving game.
How'd we do?
- You mean how did I do?
- I had a situation.
- Do you know how hard it is
to pretend you're
someone you're not?
- Every day.
- Yeah, well, I'm not
used to having two ovens
two sinks, two dishwashers--
- They got two dishwashers?
- Two fridges, too.
- Dang.
- Your pal, Michelle,
she was asking me who our
interior designer was.
- What did you say?
- Jovann.
- Who the hell's that?
- That cologne you
gave me for Christmas.
You threw me to the wolves.
- It was a situation.
- So, what,
yours is worse than mine?
- The life and death kind.
- Or is it because
she always comes first?
- Well, it looks like you
did just fine on your own.
- Well, I'm short.
- How?
- Didn't sell enough.
Priced them too high.
- Well,
we'll have another party.
- Well, then what am
I supposed to tell Gene?
- That it's coming.
- Well, and that might
put me in a situation.
Life and death kind.
- Is that caribou?
- Two of everything.
[door opens]
- Hey. Soft serve.
- So not fair.
- Well, pardonnez moi,
we are out of foie gras.
- It's about school.
- Oh, you know,
it's funny.
I actually wanted to
talk to you about that.
Um...
- Dad won't let me go to D.C.
- Why?
- He says you don't
actually learn anything.
It's just a giant party.
- Well, duh, yeah.
That's, like,
why field trips were invented.
- I will literally
be the only one
in my grade not going.
- Okay, and?
- And I want to be
with my friends.
- Well, maybe
this is a chance to, like,
make some new friends.
- What are you talking about?
- Just take a breath, okay?
Have some pâté d'Annie
- Mom, tell me.
- I will talk to your dad
about D.C.
- Really?
- I mean, it's D.C.
We can't be letting down
our founding fathers, can we?
- It's kind of your
constitutional duty.
- Mm.
Mm.
Sick nails.
Nancy did 'em.
- You mean her fancy person.
- She doesn't come any more.
- What, she's slumming it
at the salon?
- She's doing it herself.
- You mean like at home?
- Bought me cosmic blue
on Amazon.
- Why does the cheap stuff
always taste the best?
- They're having
money problems.
- Shh.
The kids.
- She's doing her own nails,
hasn't been to
Whole Foods in months,
and she's picking up
her own takeout.
- Who?
- The Duchess of Winchester.
- Who's that?
- Nancy, Gregg, hello?
Otherwise,
why would I be so excited?
- Wow, imagine how
excited you're gonna be
when you drive by
their tent under the freeway.
- Ugh, amen to that.
- Um, how are you all doing?
You know, moneywise.
- Well, I'm not in a tent.
- Yet.
- Can you spare any this month?
- What's going on?
- I got some extra bills.
- How much?
- Six grand.
- Jesus!
- What did you buy?
- Another jazzy?
- We're hustling
these janky-ass purses
for Stan's boss,
and I'm short.
Okay?
What?
- How many scams
are you running?
- Why does it matter?
- Because it's kind of weird
that you didn't tell us.
- It doesn't involve you.
- It kind of does
if you're doing
something sketch.
- We do sketch stuff every day.
- Yeah, because that's
part of our deal.
- We do so much sketch stuff,
I don't even know
what's sketch anymore.
- Which we won't have
if they find out that
you're doing something sketch.
- She does kind of
have a point.
- I mean, excuse me,
but what about your sex tape?
- Not the same.
- It's exactly the same.
- I did that to protect us.
- 'Cause the rules
don't ever apply when it's you.
- You think I wanted
to do that?
- Way to take a finger
for the team.
- You know, I can kind of see
it from that perspective.
- Would you please
take a side already!
So what happens
if you don't get it.
- That'd be bad.
- How bad?
- Like, gang friend level.
- You're really
gonna do this, huh?
- What do you mean?
- Noticed how things are
different now, that's all.
- If Carolyn makes you f--
I know she can be a lot,
so I've got other friends--
- Is she FBI or Secret Service?
- She's a mom
in my gardening group.
- Found the wire.
Behind "Pelican Brief."
Don't.
Don't do that.
Open the glove.
Hand it to me.
[Bobby Vinton's
"Over and Over"]
♪
- ♪ If
♪ I had my life
♪ To live over
♪ Again
♪ I
♪ Would truly take you
♪ For my love
♪ Again
♪ Oh how I'd love you
♪ Over and over
♪ Over again
♪ Yes I would love you
♪ Over and over
♪ Over again
♪ One lifetime
♪ Isn't long enough
♪ To be
♪ With you
♪ I need more time
♪ To give this love of mine
♪ That I have
♪ For you
♪ And then I would love you
♪ Over and over
♪ Over again
♪ Yes I would love you
♪ Over and over
♪ Yes over again
♪ Over again
- You blew it, Carolyn.
.
- And so now whenever
I plug my phone in,
it's "I'll Make Love To You."
- Boyz II Men.
- Yeah, I played
the damn thing one time
for this bitch who can't
get going without it
and now it's all I hear.
- Had that happen with
"Mambo No. 5."
- Yeah, you stuck
with it forever.
- Song herpes, am I right?
- How we do?
- Well,
I hate to say it,
but I'm afraid you crushed it.
- Good.
- It wasn't easy.
- Should make you guys
partners in the club, too.
- Hey, that would be awesome.
- I said I should,
not that I would.
But what I am gonna do...
- Appreciate it.
- ...is invest it
back into the company.
- What company?
- Our fake handbag company.
- We'd just rather
take our cut.
- It's gonna be big, though.
- Yeah, we're all set.
- Like Apple or...
- Our loss.
- Facebook.
- Hey, that's all you, man.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
Real sure.
- So you don't want to
be the next Google?
- We'll take our chances.
- You know what?
I care about you guys too much
to let you do that.
- I mean, we don't have any
real investments.
- That fool's going down.
- Yeah, right.
[engine starts]
- Oh, no.
- Sit down.
- Mugs, huh?
- You loved that eighth grade
field trip to D.C.
You had that insane hookup
with Melissa Thomas
at the Smithsonian.
- Yeah, right by Lincoln's hat.
- [laughs]
- There's only one reason
why you wouldn't let him go.
- Is this drip?
- Get used to it.
- Nancy tried to grow
the business too fast.
- What's the damage?
- We're totaled.
- Want some cream?
It's free.
- What about school?
- It'd be nice if he could
finish out the school year.
- He loves his dick friends.
- And those dick parents.
- Maybe,
maybe I can try to
help with the tuition.
- It's not cheap.
- Really?
'Cause I thought a school
named after a saint
would be free to all.
- You make minimum wage.
- It's more than you now.
- I am never going to
live this down.
- No you are not.
I am just getting started.
- [groans]
- Bad day?
Wanna turn it around?
Hop in.
Tell me all about your bad day.
'Cause they...
won't hear a thing.
Come on!
Yes, ma'am
Oh!
Ah.
So what happened?
- It's complicated.
[dreamy music]
♪
I didn't have a choice.
- You got one now.
The way I see it, you got
the angel on one shoulder
and the devil on the other.
- Damned either way.
- So what's it gonna be?
♪