‐ Previously
on "Good Girls"...
‐ We get to start over,
and then they'll move us
anywhere in the country.
‐ Assuming we can even
deliver gang friend.
‐ We need to know
what he does with the money.
‐ He'll kill me.
‐ You have something
you want to tell me?
‐ It's not gonna
do that, is it?
‐ Another double.
What's this man got you doing?
‐ Who do you think's
paying off all your debt?
‐ You had pizza
with your therapist?
‐ And a couple beers.
So what?
‐ She's really into you, okay?
‐ I proposed to Lila.
You're quitting?
‐ You can't make
someone like you.
♪ ♪
‐ Annie, what are you doing?
‐ Tyler, please, there has
to be something that you want.
‐ I'll see you in 30 years.
‐ It might not take that long.
♪ ♪
‐ How did you do it?
‐ I can't keep doing this.
‐ Don't have much of a choice.
‐ Why?
‐ Because I also have
people to answer to.
They're gonna want
to meet you.
‐ He's got a boss.
♪ ♪
‐ Make peace with yourself.
Make peace
with the amazing person
that you truly are.
♪ ♪
Your mind
is your greatest asset.
♪ ♪
You are your own best tool.
‐ ♪ He said, "Baby,
what's wrong with you? ♪
♪ Why don't you
use your imagination?" ♪
♪ Oh, no, oh, no ♪
♪ Standing in the half‐light ♪
♪ You're almost like her ♪
♪ Take it slow
like your daddy told you ♪
♪ Strut, pout, put it out ♪
♪ That's what
you want from women ♪
♪ Come on, baby ♪
♪ What you taking me for? ♪
♪ Strut, pout, cut it out ♪
♪ All taking and no giving ♪
♪ Watch me, baby,
while I walk out your door ♪
♪ ♪
‐ I am my own best tool.
‐ ♪ Strut, pout, put it out ♪
♪ That's what
you want from women ♪
♪ Come on‐‐ ♪
‐ Be cool.
‐ Why are you in clothes?
‐ Why are you awake?
‐ I have practice.
‐ Before school?
‐ Can't do it in school.
‐ But it's extracurricular.
‐ Yeah, extra.
‐ Hmm.
What's your excuse?
‐ Work.
‐ You got home,
like, 3 hours ago.
‐ I forgot to lock up.
‐ The store is open 24 hours.
What's in the backpack?
‐ Mostly tampons.
‐ Can I see?
‐ You know what's so weird?
‐ Guns?
‐ You didn't go to bed a cop...
‐ Drugs?
‐ But you woke up one.
‐ Body parts?
‐ Remind me never
to get up early again.
‐ All right.
Be on your way.
‐ I will bring you a Slurpee.
‐ If only
you were going to work.
‐
‐ You're not dumb.
You just weren't prepared,
so let's try again.
If you can open up
your textbooks
to chapter 6, page 89.
‐ Will you take me
to Annabelle's?
‐ Can your mom take you?
‐ I want you.
‐ Could she come over here?
‐ She has better dolls.
‐ What about FaceTime?
‐ Not the same.
‐ What if you rode your scooter
over to her house?
‐ I can't cross
the street by myself.
‐
Well, maybe it's time.
‐ Hey, go get
your shoes, sweetie.
‐ But I want Dad.
‐ Go.
How long does that take?
‐ When it beeps.
‐ Do you want
a pillow or something?
‐ How did you get it?
‐ What?
‐ The bail.
I mean, we were drowning
before they even took the shop.
‐ Come here, sit up.
‐ What'd he
make you do this time?
‐ It's not him.
‐ Who is it?
‐ Does it matter?
‐
Yeah, kind of.
‐ Would you rather
just go back?
‐
‐ I'll take Jane.
♪ ♪
‐ We out of peanut butter?
‐ We are.
‐ We out of bread, too?
‐ Do you see any bread?
‐ No.
‐ Then you have your answer.
‐ Can you go to the store?
‐ Sure, as soon
as we stop showering,
stop watching TV,
and stop cooking.
‐
Got it.
How bad?
‐ As long as you don't
need to see the food
that we can't buy or cook,
we can probably keep
the TV going.
‐ Well, it's okay,
'cause I got a craving
for saltines and mustard.
‐ You cannot be serious.
‐ I could do Cheerios
and barbecue sauce.
‐ Her meds went up again.
‐ They just upped them.
‐ And they upped the up.
‐ How much?
What are we going to do?
‐ I know
this is kind of my fault.
‐ All your fault.
‐ And I don't want
to make things any worse
than I already have.
‐ But you just
can't help yourself.
‐ What's going on
with the bags?
‐ What do you mean?
‐ Maybe you can ask
for some kind of commission
or something.
‐ This isn't Herbalife, babe.
‐ But you made the deal.
‐ To stay alive.
‐ Well, are they selling?
‐ I don't know, Ruby.
He's got 'em in some car washes
around town.
‐ Car washes?
‐ Some gas stations too.
‐ They're fake CELINEs,
not Slim Jims.
‐ Looks like it's gonna be
a condiment kind of month.
‐ Got to do better than that.
‐ Well, get it from your guy.
‐ He just
won't wash right now.
‐ And we can't live
without our cut.
‐ How is that my problem?
‐ This takes up
all of our time.
‐ I can barely work.
‐ And it's not like
we're ratting out
some pencil pushers.
‐ There's crime,
undercover crime.
‐ These fools are packing, yo.
‐ None of it pays anymore.
‐ We're not
your financial planners.
‐ So could we get, like,
an advance or something?
‐ On what?
‐ On our salary.
‐ What salary?
‐ The one we're gonna get
in our new lives.
‐ You don't have new lives yet.
‐ But we can't afford
our old ones.
‐ I can't even pay my rent.
‐ Hey, guess where
you won't have to.
When do you meet the boss?
‐ Oh, I'm still waiting
on my e‐vite.
‐ I like your eyes.
‐ Excuse me?
‐ The smoky stuff.
‐ My makeup?
‐ What's it called?
‐ Eye shadow.
‐ Would you say
it's, like, slate
or more of, like, a smoky gray?
‐ She'll text you a link.
‐ Mm.
♪ ♪
‐ Hey, mama.
I can trust you, right?
♪ ♪
‐ Follow the money.
‐ What color lip gloss is that?
♪ ♪
‐ Boss will know where it goes.
‐ My people
want to check you out.
♪ ♪
‐ You've got this, girl.
‐ We're counting on you.
‐ Don't let me down,
all right?
♪ ♪
‐ Do you have a USB cable?
This thing is flashing,
and I need to charge it.
‐ Yeah, it's in my purse.
‐ Okay.
‐ What happens
when his boss has a boss?
‐ And that boss has a boss?
‐ We work harder and harder.
‐ And get poorer and poorer.
‐ And still end up
deader and deader.
‐ And deader.
'Cause there's three of us.
Hello?
‐ Yo, Holly Hobby.
‐ Anything at all
to contribute?
‐ What do we do?
‐ Green or orange
around the mouth?
‐ Hey, will you give me
that blue AUX?
Do you feel that?
‐ Hm?
‐ Oh...
The rush.
‐ From the fumes?
‐ Here, you try.
This one goes right there.
‐ Okay.
‐ How awesome is it
being in the field?
‐ Hmm, food's better
than the cafeteria.
‐ How about no D‐bag suits
to report to?
‐ Sounds nice.
‐ Right?
‐ For you.
‐ Point is,
if we deliver on this,
everything changes.
‐ Really?
‐ Yeah, yeah.
Could mean division chief.
‐ For me too?
‐ Yeah, if you
play your cards right.
‐ Hm.
‐ What'd you do to your face?
‐ Nothing.
‐ Oh.
Is that eye shadow?
‐ No.
‐ Oh.
Listen, I‐‐I worked
with this CI once.
Great guy.
Loved Kenny Chesney.
We'd go out.
We'd get sauced.
‐ Fun.
‐ He even taught me
how to line dance.
‐ Got to make him trust you.
‐ Problem was, I trusted him.
‐ I'm not going dancing
with her.
‐ They're not your friends.
‐ I just had to find my way in.
‐ The only reason
she's even talking to you
is because we caught her.
‐ What happened
with your Chesney pal?
‐ He played me
like a steel guitar.
They shut down the whole op.
‐ I get it.
‐
It took 15 years
to dig out of that hole.
‐ I'm gonna make her
my bitch, okay?
‐ Just don't forget
what's pretend and what's real.
Not your color, by the way.
‐ Your place is really nice.
‐ Oh, thanks.
You've been here before, right?
‐ Just to help you
move your couch.
‐ What about
my Super Bowl party?
‐ I wasn't invited.
‐ To any of them?
‐ Wait, there was
more than one?
‐ Let's talk a little bit more
about you, Baby T.
What's new?
‐ I rescued a cat.
‐ Aw.
‐ Then he drowned himself.
‐ Oh.
So tell me a little bit more
about this exciting
new job of yours.
‐ Well, it's not really
that exciting.
‐ What if it could be?
♪ ♪
It's a new place
in Grosse Pointe.
‐ It's a lot of eyes.
‐ It's only one exit.
‐ And a police station
right down the road.
‐ Hey, ladies.
Hey, have you seen
my Allen wrenches?
‐ No.
♪ ♪
‐ Different key for each case.
‐ It'll take forever.
‐ Suicide mission.
♪ ♪
‐ Perfect.
‐ ♪ I heard what you said ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I heard how you said it ♪
♪ You heard what I said ♪
♪ ♪
♪ You heard how I said it ♪
♪ I'm not afraid ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Just tangled in your wires ♪
♪ It's not heavy enough ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Unless you open your eyes ♪
♪ I've been crashing ♪
♪ Almost every night ♪
♪ But it pains me to say ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I'm not even bruised ♪
♪ My skin is teared up ♪
♪ To the touch ♪
♪ I radiate heat ♪
♪ Too much ♪
♪ Must give
quick, quick, quick, quick ♪
‐ All right, everybody be cool,
and nobody gets hurt!
‐ Time.
‐ One minute.
‐ Miss, that one
is not locked.
‐ Oh, terrific.
Thank you.
‐ Time.
‐ Come on, pick up the pace!
Ten seconds.
‐ Where is this fool?
‐  He's coming.
‐ It's time.
‐ Everything's insured.
You can go.
‐ Um, we will...
After you open something else.
‐ You took everything.
‐ ♪ I want to know ♪
‐ Well, don't look at us.
‐ I haven't called
the cops yet.
‐ Get on the ground.
Go on.
Get down there.
‐ Okay.
‐ ♪ If you ever go ♪
‐ Where is he?
‐ ♪ How do I ever,
ever survive? ♪
‐ You stay down there.
‐ ♪ How do I ♪
♪ How do I live? ♪
‐ Be cool.
‐ ♪ There would be
no sun in the sky ♪
♪ There would be
no love in my life ♪
♪ ♪
♪ There would be
no world left for me ♪
♪ And I ♪
♪ Baby, I don't know ♪
‐ Turn around.
‐ ♪ What I would do ♪
‐ That way.
‐ ♪ If I lost you ♪
♪ ♪
♪ If you ever leave ♪
‐ Donuts?
‐ I thought it was tomorrow.
♪ ♪
‐ Really?
‐ What the hell is going on?
‐ Just trying to make a living.
‐ Armed robbery is 5 to 10.
‐ For squirt guns?
‐ Doesn't matter, actually.
‐ It does when you
pull the trigger.
‐ You think this is funny?
‐ At least here
we get three square meals.
‐ And a roof over our head.
‐ Cute jumpers.
‐ Oh, I love orange.
‐ They do blue here.
‐ Oh, even better.
‐ Fine.
You could all rot.
‐ We'll round up
your husband too.
‐ But how
will we finish the job?
‐ You didn't really
give us anything anyway.
‐ Can you just ask
the security guard
for my phone?
I hate when people
don't respond to an e‐vite.
‐ Did gang friend
actually send a e‐vite?
‐ Paperless post.
‐ When's the meeting?
‐ Does it matter?
‐ You know, I think
it actually kind of does
'cause if they bail us out,
which it feels like
they're leaning towards,
then we could hit
that credit union
before it closes.
‐ Oh.
It's right next to Walmart.
‐ Twofer.
‐ Might want to hang tight
in the parking lot.
We'll probably be back here
before that meeting.
‐ We'll put you on payroll.
‐ Same amount as our cut.
‐ Not happening.
‐ Hmm.
Never knocked over a casino.
‐ Open all night.
‐ Loaded with cash.
‐ And on every corner.
‐ How did we not think
of this before?
‐ I just did.
‐
‐ Come here.
‐ Your guy came through?
‐ You tell me.
‐ Hm?
‐ Real or fake?
‐ As long as it pays the bills.
‐ Come on.
‐ Real.
Fake?
I can't tell the difference.
‐ That's the point.
‐ What's that
got to do with it?
‐ You want a cut or not?
‐ You know it.
‐ Then we gotta show your guy
how valuable you are.
‐ It's missing
the engraved logo...
right here in the corner.
Can't sleep on the stitching‐‐
at least ten stitches per inch.
Got to be symmetrical
on all sides.
And the real ones...
come with a dust bag.
‐ What's that?
‐ It's like a bag for your bag.
‐ Seems like a waste.
‐ Ladies love it.
‐ Why are you telling me
all this, Stan?
‐ 'Cause, Gene,
you're selling fake for fake.
‐ So?
‐ Convince women
these are real,
you get ten times the money.
‐ All this time,
I thought I hired a badass.
Lucky for me,
I got a prissy fashionista.
‐
‐ I really need to pass.
It's not just for me.
It's for my son.
Look, I know
this might not seem
like the most important thing
in the world to someone else,
but I literally cannot move on
with my life without it,
so...if there is...
anything else...that I can do.
‐ There's one thing you can do.
‐ Name it.
‐ Take your seat.
‐
How many times?
Yeah, same here.
‐ You have 7 hours
to complete the test.
The first section
has a limit of 75 minutes.
I'll notify you when there's
5 minutes remaining.
When the time is up,
please place your pencils down.
Are there any questions?
♪ ♪
‐ Get 'em curry.
‐ Curry?
‐ Yeah,
Jane's learning cultures.
‐ Okay.
‐ She likes India.
‐ Is the store
paying you in cash now?
‐ Remember when you first
went to work for your dad,
and you said, "It's only
gonna be for the summer"?
‐ Yeah, stuck for life.
‐ Me too.
Just leave it.
‐ I got it.
‐ Leave it.
‐ You okay?
‐ Kenny likes the naan.
It's just flatbread.
What if he checks me?
‐ Improvise.
‐ What if he finds it?
‐ He'd have to get you naked.
♪ ♪
‐ Hey, now.
Come on.
‐ Do you need to frisk me
or something?
‐ Nah, you're good.
Don't sweat it,
all right?
♪ ♪
This is my boss.
‐ I'm just his grandmother.
‐
‐ Come on, creepy guy in 4A.
Why is your Wi‐Fi so weak?
Yes!
No!
‐ This is not my house.
‐ What are you doing here?
‐ I just left my stag night.
‐ That doesn't help me.
‐ Your people
call it a bachelor party.
‐ That would explain
the boob glitter on your face.
‐ It got really weird.
‐ With the strippers?
‐ With a mini horse.
‐ I don't even know
who to feel sorry for there.
‐ I can't get married tomorrow.
‐
You should go home.
‐ I don't want to.
‐ Then go somewhere else.
‐ Can I just please come in?
‐ Find yourself
a good therapist.
‐ Please, I really need‐‐
‐ Josh.
‐ Sorry, I really need to‐‐
‐ Josh, you have to trust me.
‐ I think
I'm gonna crap myself.
‐ It's around the corner.
‐ Okay.
‐ Oh, no, that's too much.
Thank you.
‐ Don't worry.
She'll tell you
when you've had enough.
‐ How do you know my uncle?
‐ She's just
a work friend, bud.
‐ What's she do?
‐ Um, she helps me out.
That right?
‐ We're partners.
‐ That all?
‐ I'm married.
‐ How many children?
‐ Four.
‐ She's married.
‐ Where's the ring?
‐ Let the girl eat.
‐ Come on.
I'm just playing.
‐ My cousin.
‐ Brother.
‐ Cousin.
‐ Heard a lot
about you, Elizabeth.
‐ It's just Beth.
‐ Okay, Elizabeth.
‐ Got to watch out
for that one.
‐ You've got to watch out
for both of these guys.
‐ Like you're some peach.
‐
‐ Is there a bathroom?
‐ Oh, yeah, inside, sweetie,
off the den.
‐ Thank you.
‐ I'd avoid going in there.
‐ How long?
‐ A week to be safe.
‐ Feeling better?
‐ Not really.
‐ Well, pre‐wedding jitters
are totally normal.
‐ I've never gone
number two at Lila's.
‐ Huh?
‐ Never.
‐ But‐‐but what do you do?
‐ There's a café
down the street.
They know me.
They key's waiting
when I come in.
‐ Why?
‐ Because her bathroom
is so fresh and girly.
It smells like gardenias.
‐ Yeah, 'cause she's trying
to mask her own dumps.
‐ No, she doesn't do that.
‐ So she also goes to the café?
‐ No, she just doesn't do it.
‐ Are you kidding me?
‐ She never has to go.
‐ That's just
physically impossible.
‐ She eats so clean
there's very little waste.
‐ Jesus.
‐ Yeah.
‐ She really is perfect.
‐ Just not for me.
You destroyed
my office bathroom
after our first session.
‐ I thought I sprayed.
‐ Not enough.
‐
‐ Can I ask you something?
‐ Okay.
‐ Do you really want
to be with me...
Or do you just
not want to be with her?
‐ ♪ Half of my whole life ♪
♪ Is gone ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Let it drift ♪
♪ And wash away ♪
♪ ♪
♪ It was just ♪
♪ A dream I had ♪
♪ ♪
‐ What are you doing?
‐ I don't‐‐
I don't know.
‐ Don't know?
Don't want to say?
‐ I'm just curious.
‐ Oh, yeah?
You figure it out yet?
‐ What's that?
‐ Grandma loves Grisham.
‐
What is all this?
‐ Family.
‐ I thought this was business.
‐ Same thing.
‐ Why do they care about me?
‐ Got to know
you're good enough.
‐ For you?
‐ For business.
‐ What if I'm not?
‐ Then you don't
get invited back.
‐ That doesn't seem fair.
‐ Hm.
♪ ♪
‐ ♪ Half of my whole life ♪
♪ Is done ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Heather gathers ♪
♪ In its place ♪
♪ ♪
♪ It was just ♪
♪ A dream I had ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Mm ♪
♪ It was just a dream ♪
♪ ♪
♪ The mark where he left me ♪
♪ A clip on my wing ♪
♪ Oh, let it soften ♪
♪ I forgive everything ♪
♪ I once hummed the seasons ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Now I'm whistling ♪
‐ What's going on?
‐ She improvised.
‐ Hey.
They like you.
‐ Morning.
‐ What time is it?
‐ You're good.
You're good.
But...
it's approaching go time.
‐ Oh, God.
‐ So what are you gonna do?
‐ Not how this works, remember?
‐ Oh, we're back to that now?
‐ You never really needed me.
‐ Hi, Ben.
‐ You've got to be kidding me.
‐ Well, good luck.
‐ You, too.
‐ Hey, it's not that!
‐ It looks like that.
‐ It's a different kind
of that.
‐ That is that.
‐ It's that without the that.
‐ Why should I believe anything
that comes out of your mouth?
‐ Because I'm not lying.
‐ I called
the mini‐mart after you left.
‐ What?
‐ Where were you?
‐ Not where you think.
‐ 'Cause I think
you were humping your shrink.
‐ Jesus.
I was at
a GED prep class, okay?
‐ For real?
‐ Yeah.
I just‐‐
I didn't want to tell you.
‐ Why?
‐ In case I failed again.
‐ How'd you do?
Come on, creeper in 4A.
‐ Ugh, he has really
got to upgrade.
‐ It's loading.
‐ Oh, my God.
I can't look.
‐ I got this.
Oh, no.
Now we both
have to pay for college.
‐ Ah!
‐ Hey.
Rise and shine.
‐ You just getting home?
‐ Mm‐hmm.
Got my cut.
‐ For real?
‐ Did everything you said.
‐ How much?
‐ Even more than I asked for.
‐ Depends on how many I sell.
‐ Why you?
‐ He didn't know any women
who could afford a real one.
‐ And we do?
‐
We're gonna have
to find 'em.
‐ They look legit though.
‐ You see the hardware?
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ Sorry about this,
my gaily colored
beach ball of rapture.
‐ Actually, this look
is very popular...
‐ You guys,
please turn that down.
You're gonna go deaf.
‐ Earthworm Jim!
‐ Dean?
‐ Prepare to be unsuited‐‐
‐ Earth to Dean.
‐ Oh, sorry.
I was just spaced.
‐ Weren't you gonna go
on a bike ride?
‐ Can't.
‐ Didn't you fix the tires?
‐
I have a radius of three blocks
with this thing.
‐ Well, why don't you
just go up and down
the driveway like Jane?
It was a joke.
You guys, TV.
‐ Might as well
just throw me back in.
‐ Because you can't go
on a bike ride?
‐ Because you gave 'em
enough evidence to put me away
for as long as they want.
‐ I'll ask him
to increase the radius.
‐ There is gonna be a trial.
‐ There's not gonna be a trial.
‐ They're not
gonna cut me a deal.
‐ You won't need one.
‐ Well, how do you know that?
‐ Danny, turn the TV up.
‐ ♪ Through the soil
he did crawl ♪
♪ Earthworm Jim ♪
‐ Come on, even louder.
‐ ♪ Jim was just
a dirt‐eating ♪
♪ Chewing length
of worm flesh ♪
♪ But all that
came to a crash ♪
‐
‐ ♪ Earthworm Jim ♪
‐ ♪ He's such a groovy guy ♪
‐ ♪ He rockets
through the sky ♪
♪ Cruising through
the universe ♪
♪ Having lots of fun ♪
♪ Here comes Earthworm Jim ♪
♪ You know
that he's a mighty one ♪
Look out!
♪ ♪
‐ ♪ Earthworm Jim ♪
‐ ♪ A hero for all time ♪
♪ Earthworm, Earthworm,
Earthworm, Earthworm Jim ♪
‐ ♪ Despite
his great big muscles ♪
♪ And his really big ray gun ♪
♪ Jim is still an earthworm ♪
♪ But then
he's the only one ♪
♪ With a super suit to make
him really super strong ♪
♪ Jim can be a winner
if we only sing along ♪
‐ ♪ Earthworm Jim ♪
‐ ♪ We think
he's mighty fine ♪
‐ ♪ Earthworm Jim ♪
‐ ♪ A hero for all time ♪
‐ ♪ The soil he did crawl ♪
‐ ♪ Earthworm, Earthworm,
Earthworm, Earthworm Jim ♪
♪ Hooray for Jim ♪
‐ G‐roovy!