.
- Previously
on "Good Girls"...
- I was at a GED prep class.
- How'd you do?
- Aah!
- Now we both have
to pay for college.
- What's he got you into?
- Whatever Gene needs.
There's 300 more coming
right behind it.
- Maybe you can ask
for some kind
of commission or something.
- You crushed it.
What I am gonna do
is invest it back
into the company.
- We'd just rather
take our cut.
- I care about you guys
too much
to let you do that.
- Weren't you're gonna go
on a bike ride?
- Can't.
I have a radius
of three blocks
with this thing.
- I'll ask him
to increase the radius.
- What are we doing here?
- Following the money.
- I can't keep doing this.
- Don't have much of a choice.
'Cause I also have people
to answer to.
They're gonna wanna meet you.
- I'm just his grandmother.
- Heard a lot
about you, Elizabeth.
- Just Beth.
- My cousin.
- Brother.
- Cousin.
- He was going to see
your wire.
- Now we're right back
where we started.
- Her wire's still hot.
- I need a bank.
Can't be you.
- This is my friend.
- She FBI or Secret Service?
Found the wire.
- I didn't have a choice.
- Well, you got one now.
So what's it gonna be?
[video game sound effects]
- I can't do the eyes.
Dope.
- You'll get it, brother.
[oven dings]
- Cousin.
- [sighs]
Ohh.
For the love of God.
What's older, me or this oven?
Don't answer that.
Nice and hot.
Here ya go.
[chuckles]
What's that face?
- Tastes nasty.
- Mm.
Bad eggs.
- Try it.
- Hell, no.
- Rotten one can ruin
the whole bunch.
- Just put it in?
- Mm-hmm.
If they sink, they're good.
- Better to catch it now.
Okay.
Now we have to start all over.
Now, where is that
baking powder?
Here we go.
Vanilla, brown sugar.
Flour.
Who wants to help?
[mid-tempo music]
♪
- You and me, we got
a real opportunity here.
♪
- What am I supposed
to tell them?
- Just keep 'em busy.
- The people who live
in a surveillance van
outside of my house?
- Yeah, them.
They don't trust you?
- I've given them nothing.
- Well, you better
give 'em something.
♪
- They're gonna
see right through it.
- Not if you play it smart.
♪
- I'll end up in jail.
- I'm not asking you.
- Well, I'm not doing it.
♪
- [laughs]
You know, there's worse
places to end up, right?
♪
- I thought you needed me.
- I do.
- Well, there you go.
- But not your family.
♪
You feel me?
Keep your head up, champ.
We're playing
the long game here.
♪
[door slams]
- You guys.
Say something.
Anything.
- Who exactly do
we work for now?
[loud slice]
- You mean, who don't
we work for?
- See, that's the part
I'm having a problem with.
- Why does he have us printing?
- I don't know.
- What's it for?
- It didn't come up.
- [chuckles]
How are we supposed
to keep it secret
from the Secret Service?
[suspenseful music]
♪
- [exhales]
Let's just pack it up.
- Yeah, right.
- Did you figure out
where his money goes?
- Not Mediterranean Avenue.
- Not anywhere.
D.C. is not gonna keep the tab
going much longer.
♪
- They'll take our deal away.
- You know what
he'll take away?
- Like we have anything
left to lose.
- Our kids.
♪
- What if
she's protecting him?
- She can't think
we're that stupid.
- She's not thinking
with her brain.
- He is pretty hot.
- Stupid hot.
♪
- So, we're back
to where we started?
- The man's like IBS.
- Ain't no cure.
- Never know when
it's gonna strike.
♪
- Well, now she thinks another
baby is gonna fix everything.
- First three didn't.
- I got four.
- I told her--I said,
"Honey, the time I spend
in the saddle,
the sack is cashed."
- Wait, is that a--
is that really a thing?
- [chuckles]
It's a perk.
[laughter]
- What was it like?
- Oh...
This?
- Big house.
- Yeah.
It was kind of a party.
- Come on, man.
- No, seriously.
Food wasn't that bad.
I got to work out all the time.
Plus I had my own cell, so...
- How'd you swing that?
- My first cellie
tried to steal my ramen,
so I beat him
within an inch of his life.
- Over ramen?
- Took his nose off.
With my teeth.
[laughs]
- Jesus.
- I'm just busting
your cashed sack, bro.
[laughter]
- You want to know
what it's really like?
- Yes.
- It's kind of like being
in an elephant exhibit
at the zoo.
- Dude.
- And all the other elephants
think that you are their wife.
- Dude.
- And it's your honeymoon.
- And they won't stop
until they put a baby in ya.
I'm kidding!
- Okay, I'm not believing
a word that comes out
of this guy's mouth.
- I mean, look,
I did sell cars.
- Yeah, he could sell
bottled water to fish.
- I also sold hot tubs.
- Dean, how do you feel
about men's skin care?
- Uh...neutral.
- Mm, well,
we're about to change that
for you, buddy.
- You ever heard
of "The System"?
- That's, like,
a pyramid thing, right?
- No, more like a multilevel
opportunity.
- I mean, skin care
is not really my jam.
- It's not really about that.
- And there's a good chance
I'm probably going back
to the elephant exhibit
anyway, so...
- That's exactly why
you need "The System."
- Right, and you don't just
get a bunch of products.
You get a support network.
[soft music]
- Well, that's sounds good.
Cool.
Just, you know,
let me put
a think on it, you know.
♪
- All the time you need.
- Hey, we're not just into you
for your skin.
♪
[cell phone chimes]
Tina's ovulating.
- Let's get back on the road.
Yeah.
- It's go time.
- When you get out of bed
in the morning
and throw your uniform on,
what do you expect
out of your day?
I mean, a living wage, maybe.
A reasonable amount of breaks.
Okay.
But what does any of that
mean if you don't have respect?
- Like, when the customers
get handsy?
- Sure.
I mean, yeah,
that's a part of that.
- But we get tipped way more
when we let that happen.
- Yeah, I'm thinking more about
how you're valued
as an employee.
You guys got a health plan?
Dental?
- No.
- What about paid sick leave?
How about daycare?
- You know we got none of that.
- Okay, well these are
the investments
that an employer should make.
- Why?
- 'Cause you are crucial
to the success of this company.
Right?
I mean, picture a McDonald's
without a Ronald.
Imagine green beans
without the Jolly Green Giant.
- Charles Schwab
without Mr. Schwab.
- Exactly, okay?
You are the face
of this business.
- No one's looking
at our faces.
- And what does Gene
give you in return?
- 10% of our tips.
- That's not daycare.
- Well, we can take home
the extra food
from the private parties.
- Not paid sick leave.
Not dental.
- He's not wrong.
- And definitely not respect.
- Yeah.
Stan's right.
- We deserve it.
- Screw that guy.
- He lies.
He cheats.
He takes better care of these
poles than he does any of you.
- He's right.
That is so messed up!
- We deserve better.
- Enough is enough.
- So what do you want us
to do, Stanimal?
- How do you strip without
taking any clothes off?
- You don't.
- But people come
to see the booty.
- That's my point.
- [laughs]
So they won't come.
- Now you're getting it.
- Okay, well,
that's one of the dumbest
things I've ever heard.
- [laughs]
Okay.
Hold up.
Gene doesn't have a club
without the girls, right?
So eventually, he's gonna have
to come to me to negotiate--
- Or he just sacks all of you
and starts over.
- Then we do a sit-in.
Old school-style, right?
Handcuff ourselves
to the stage.
- I take it back.
- Force his hand.
- That's the dumbest thing
I've ever heard.
- Yeah, that's what
the girls said too.
- Hey, that's mine.
Let it go!
- I had it first!
- You can't just go in my room.
- Well, Mom says
you have to share.
- Hey, hey, hey.
Let Danny have it.
- He only wants it
'cause I was playing with it.
- Give it to your sister.
- You gave it to me
for my birthday.
- Yeah, like, three years ago.
- Ow!
- A little help here
would be nice.
- This one's better.
The legs bend.
- Let me see.
- That one's busted.
- It'll keep her busy.
- Should we be mad
or impressed?
[soft music]
♪
- How do you always lose
your key?
- What do you care?
It's never locked.
- It's always locked.
- It hasn't been like the
last ten times we've come here.
- Because I always have my key.
- Yo, I thought
we finished his run.
- This one's not for him.
- You know what time I have to
be at the salon tomorrow?
- So, he's the toy
they want, right?
- You're gonna be late.
- But we can't give 'em
the toy that they want.
- I should text my boss.
- So we're gonna give 'em
the broken toy.
- The hell are
you talking about?
- I literally just told you.
- Not in English.
- Okay.
The broken toy's gonna
keep them busy over here,
while the good toy can go off
and do God knows what.
- I'll just call in sick.
- I would.
So what you're saying is we're
basically framing someone.
- Yes.
- But who?
- Oh, my God,
that is the best part.
Because it's--
.
[muffled rap music]
- There it is.
There it is.
Fast hands.
Come on.
Jab.
[loud music continues
over speakers]
Keep your chin down.
Jab.
- [sighs]
Son of a gun.
Oh.
That's good.
- My buddy might disagree.
- Now he won't.
- Good, good.
Another hook.
Go again.
Come on, come on.
One more.
All right.
Good work.
[phone ringing]
- Yo, champ.
Cousin.
[rap music continues
over speakers]
♪
Hurry up.
He doesn't seem happy.
♪
- Don't be pissed.
- Can't keep covering
for you, champ.
- Nick.
- This--this is too much.
- For making me look good.
- Played a great round, sir.
- Thanks to you.
- You got your head
in the wrong game.
[car engine turns]
[machine beeps]
[knocking]
- Look familiar?
- Wondered where I left that.
- Yeah.
I was gonna keep it, but--
- It's not your style.
- You look better in it.
- Thank you.
- Um...
do you have a minute?
- I have this coconut milk.
I had a coupon,
so I thought I'd try it.
Or just...
- So what's the deal?
- Plain cream.
- With you and him?
- What do you mean?
[bottles clanking in fridge]
- Well, you're just not his
typical colleague.
- Well, maybe
we're more friends.
- Not his typical friend.
- You don't even know me.
- [exhales]
I just think that you should
be careful.
Hey, anyone who wears
a cardigan shouldn't be
doing what he does.
- What are you, a priest?
- [chuckles]
Just trying to help.
- I'm fine.
- Ah--look.
Tell your neighbors.
And hold on to that.
- You could have just given it
to your brother,
cousin, or whatever.
- Why?
Do you wish it was him?
- No.
- Good.
- Which is it, by the way?
Brother or cousin?
- Family.
And thanks for the coffee.
I kind of like coconut milk.
[door clicks]
[dance music in background]
- [scoffs]
What's this?
- An offer.
♪
- How tall are you?
- 5'2"-ish.
- With or without or heels?
- Uh--
- You ever compete?
- For what?
- Well, she looks
like a gymnast.
You know Gabby Douglas?
♪
Flying Squirrel?
- Yeah.
- Does she work here?
- No.
Uneven bars.
She won.
- Can you touch your toes?
- Yeah.
- How about the splits?
- Okay, we're trying to do
some business here.
♪
- I want to pay off
Stan's debt.
♪
- Mercedes.
Throw this in
the microwave, would you?
- How long?
- Baked potato, 30 seconds.
♪
Looks like a fair amount.
- Twice as much
as he owes you.
- Must really be worth it.
- He's the best.
- The greatest.
- I agree.
- Great.
We have a deal.
♪
- No.
You can't replace the greatest.
♪
- Fine.
What's your number?
- It's not possible.
- Triple?
- Serious flex.
- Like your Flying Squirrel.
- Quadruple?
- Got dolla, dolla bills.
- Where do a bunch of bitches
like you get a bunch of money
like this, though?
Huh?
- Oh, now you've got
a moral code?
- I just don't do business
with bitches.
That's all.
I'll take it upstairs,
baby doll.
Auditions are Sunday.
♪
- That guy's a giant turd.
What?
- Nothing.
I just have never heard you say
the word "turd" before.
- Well, he is.
- Way more than that.
- He's a giant piece of--
- Do you think he knew
the money was fake?
- That turd just gets off
on keeping a good man down.
- Okay.
So we break into his car
and we load up the trunk.
- How's that get it
in the club?
- Well, he parks it
right outside, in his spot.
- Then Rizzoli and Isles
know it's a setup,
because of lojack or whatever.
- Ladies.
- What if we just mailed a box
of fake dough to the club?
- Ladies?
- No, because then we're gonna
get busted for mail fraud
on top of everything else.
- Ladies!
Occam's razor.
- What?
- The problem-solving principle
that says that entities
should not multiplied
without necessity?
Come on.
- She gets her GED, and now
she's Stephen Hawking?
- Sometimes the simplest way
is the right way.
[upbeat music]
♪
- [singing in French]
[rapid whispering in French]
♪
[mid-tempo club music]
- What is going on here?
♪
- Eggs and legs.
- Carving station's legit.
♪
- You said you wanted to know
where it goes.
- Where what goes?
[whirring]
[cheering]
♪
- It's not enough to sell a DA.
- Mm.
Can we grab another
round of mimosas?
- Can I have some change?
Thank you.
Is that enough?
♪
- [sighs]
.
- Mr. Varna needs help
with his clubs.
- You want to handle it
from the trunk.
That way, you don't
disturb this right here.
This is called a root ball.
- Tree's got a sack.
- Fine, yes, it's a sack,
which is why you should
protect it more.
Okay?
- What do you use for backfill?
- Peat moss.
- Hmm.
- Hey, we're open
to suggestions.
- I mean, I like
bone meal, personally.
- That sounds nasty.
- Makes them grow.
- Like, human bones?
- You should see my tulips.
- Damn.
- Ohh.
You do know that these
are at-risk kids, right?
- Yeah, amazing.
- Yeah, but you just sent him
on a murder spree
in the name of gardening,
so...
- But the city's
gonna look great, so...
- [laughs]
Okay.
I--I didn't think you'd come.
- I didn't think councilmen
actually did anything.
- Oh, we try not to.
No, this is more
of a campaign promise.
You know how that goes.
- What's your brother think?
- Cousin.
- Whatever.
- I'm not him.
It's just a choice, right?
- Not always.
- Why are you here, Elizabeth?
- I just want to plant a tree.
- Now you're stuck here.
- Yo, Councilman!
- Coming.
- Hi.
Thank you.
- Sure.
- Ready when you are.
- I don't even know
why I'm here.
- Is it Bring a Total Stranger
to Work Day?
- Next week.
- Then you must have broken
the law.
- That's cute.
- How'd it start?
- Huh?
What's this?
- It's not money.
- Don't know anything
about that, my friend.
- Oh, really?
'Cause your club's
got more of it
than toilet paper.
- It's n--
it's not my club.
- It's his, right?
- That's why he should
be here and not you.
- He's not a bad guy.
- What kind of guy is he?
[guitar music]
- Liquor.
Cigarettes.
Whatever the kids would buy.
Then we got into gift cards.
Applebee's, Chili's, Michael's,
Bed Bath & Beyond.
Man, we hit a Triple-B
so hard once,
they had to stop
giving out all those coupons.
♪
Then his doctor bills
kept coming in and coming in.
Heart medications.
All these boner pills.
And that's--that's when
we started knocking off
the pharmacies.
You know, xanny bars, those
patches with the fentanyl?
♪
Yeah.
[crying]
Nursing homes ain't cheap.
And that man treated me
like his own grandson.
[crying]
If it wasn't for him,
I'd still be in Philly
selling fireworks
out of my damn trunk.
[crying]
Did I dabble in hillbilly
heroin, and some other things?
Oh, yeah.
Guilty as charged.
[crying]
- You haven't been charged.
- Then lock me up.
- Actually, for anything
you confessed.
- [sniffs]
That's why this
country's great.
People care about people.
♪
[crying]
Who the hell is that?
- Wedding?
- Bris.
- Mm, quite a turnout.
- It's apparently
quite a penis.
- Thanks for getting us
that guy, by the way.
- Oh, yeah.
Anything good?
- Oh, my God.
Tons.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
Confessed to pretty
much every crime.
- Wow.
- Except for anything
having to do
with your gang buddy.
- Well, those guys
all protect each other.
- This guy pretty much gave up
everyone he's ever worked with.
- Well...
he's lying.
- Remember after boot camp,
when I asked you
to get a juice?
- Mm-hmm.
- And you said you had
to pick up the kids?
- Right.
- Did you really have to?
- You want to get a juice?
Let's go get a damn juice.
- They're rounding you
all up tomorrow.
- It's not over yet.
- Dave wants to go home.
- What do you want?
- Just pick a side.
[crickets chirping]
[car engine approaches]
- [chuckles]
Look who got her head
in the game.
- I didn't do it for you.
- Aww.
That hurts.
Hmm.
Be for real with me.
Who's more fun?
- It's all there.
- Me?
Or your van people?
- What do you think?
[police siren in distance]
[dramatic music]
[police sirens blaring]
- That's a wrap.
♪
.
- Hey, I'm not
gonna make weight.
- You got me this new stove.
I gotta try all the burners.
- Don't make me regret it.
- The old one worked fine.
- Yeah, if you didn't need
to use the oven.
[chuckles]
- Taste that.
- All right, it's going back.
- [gasps]
Don't you--don't you dare.
- [laughs]
[police scanner chatter]
- That's him.
[muffled chatter]
- Come on, man.
- Ten years.
- Dude, if this is a bar,
I'd card you.
- Stop.
- You want to lock it in
with R-Cubed.
- Uh-huh.
- Rejuvenate, refresh, rewind.
- Hey, baby.
- Buzzkill.
- Beth?
- You look so young, she
probably didn't recognize you.
- Right.
- Come here.
- Excuse me, boys.
They're leaving soon,
I promise.
Ride got a late start, 'cause
Vance was at some conference.
Is that--
is that okay?
- We got him.
- Him him?
[exhales]
- I call dibs.
- You can't do that.
- Just did.
- Well, then I call rank.
- I got a better angle on him.
- What's that?
- These.
- [laughs]
Means nothing.
- To that guy?
- It'll get you about
as much as this.
- I think he's more
into these than that.
- Trust me.
You never know.
- Okay, rock-paper-scissors.
- Fine.
- Still using these.
- Sure.
If you can find 'em.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Private meeting.
No one's allowed in.
- We are.
- 'Cause of this.
- Under orders.
- So are we.
- Mine are from above.
- Ours are above your above.
- Uh, you can't--
you can't go in.
You--
- Where is he?
- He walked.
- What?
- That's impossible.
- DA didn't charge him.
Guess there's someone
above all of us.
[mid-tempo music]
♪
- You owe me.
- Add it to the list.
♪
So, what do we do about her?
- Well, not what
you want to do.
- Don't see any other way.
- That's why you got
me, brother.
- Cousin.
- [laughs]
Right.
- Right.
- You hungry?
[car engine turns]
♪
Put on your seatbelt.
.
- [blows]
What you know about mail fraud?
- It's bad.
- Mm-hmm.
Get you five years bad.
How about tax evasion?
- Real bad.
- 10 to 20.
What about inappropriate
behavior with an exotic animal?
Swear to God,
something with a hedgehog.
- Why are you asking me this?
- 'Cause you add all that up,
that's how long Gene
is out of our lives.
- Ding, dong.
- You know what this means?
- Yeah.
The witch is dead.
That's why I said,
"Ding, dong."
- We're free, baby.
- How's it feel, boo?
- [sighs]
I feel like the luckiest
sonofabitch alive.
What?
- The hedgehog
might have you beat.
- Yeah.
Not alive anymore.
- Left or right?
- Left.
- What?
- I'm sorry.
Right?
I mean right.
- It's the right side.
It has way less lines.
- You look great.
- It's only 'cause
"The System" works.
And I can do it anywhere.
Like, I could do it in Nevada.
- How much does all this cost?
- I mean, you--
I think you have to think
of it as an investment, right?
'Cause we're getting in
at the ground floor,
but who knows where
this thing could go.
- Only up.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Now that you're a part of it.
- Thanks.
Um, all right,
I'm gonna go see Vance.
He wants to go over
the products one more time
before I meet corporate.
- Okay.
- All right.
Obviously the right side.
- Go.
Go.
- I won't be late.
- [screams]
- Shh.
You'll wake the kids.
- I didn't have a choice.
- Yeah, you did.
- No, they were gonna--
- You just didn't choose me.
- Please don't hurt my kids.
- I ain't gonna hurt nobody.
- But I turned you in.
[soft dramatic music]
♪
- Got you something.
- New gig?
- Promotion.
- More like reward.
- [chuckles]
They're all the same.
♪
- Could have had my back.
- I did.
- How?
I'm the one who ended up
doing the six-month stretch,
cousin.
- Brother.
- Got banned from the gym.
- Don't need it.
- Trainer dropped me.
- You don't need that either.
- Oh, yeah?
What do I need?
- Stolen clubs.
Liquor from the bar.
Register at the pro shop.
♪
- Why?
- Now they trust me.
- Now they'll believe
anything you tell them.
We can do whatever we want.
♪
- They'll never see us coming.
[mid-tempo music]
♪