‐ Previously
on "Good Girls"...
You didn't want
your cool, fancy new friends
to know about
your broke‐ass mom, right?
‐ You called them douchebags
and date rapers.
You make fun of everyone,
but no one's life is
a bigger joke than yours.
‐ Where are you going?
‐ Dad's.
‐ Something's
not adding up here.
A few weeks ago, that thing
with the bank truck
burning up?
Crazy how much it cost me.
‐ So you steal from me?
‐ It wasn't really from you.
‐ It's still my ass
on the line.
I got a family, man.
‐ Should have thought
about that
before you messed with mine.
‐ What if they don't
give me the money?
‐ Don't come out till they do.
‐ Big Kahuna.
They want to meet with us.
‐ Kahuna Spas would love
to be part of the ride.
‐ I got the account.
‐ That's great!
‐ I also had
to give them the books.
‐ Dean Boland,
you are under arrest.
‐ Your husband
pled guilty today.
He's protecting her.
‐ Tell me one thing.
Was he part of it?
‐ There's got to be a way
to get him out.
‐ He's the perfect fall guy.
‐ Is Dean okay?
‐ That depends on you.
‐ He'll kill me.
‐ We'll protect you.
‐ What could I even get on him?
‐ Looks like plenty.
‐ Looks legit.
Who made it?
‐ We both know how hard it is
to find a good artist,
so I'm not gonna tell you.
‐ Fair enough.
‐ So you approve?
‐ Yeah.
♪ ♪
‐ ♪ Louie, Louie ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Me voy, me voy ♪
♪ Ay‐yi‐yi, yi‐yi‐yi ♪
♪ Louie Louie ♪
♪ Ooh, me voy ♪
‐ All you have to do
is make the exchange.
‐ Unique New York,
unique New York...
‐ And what if
he figures it out?
‐ We'll protect you.
‐ Red leather, yellow leather.
Red leather, yellow leather.
‐ His gun's the size of my arm.
‐ We're Secret Service.
‐ So?
‐ Ever seen
"In the Line of Fire"?
‐ You'll take a bullet for me?
‐ He will.
‐ Betty Botter bought a bit
of bitter butter,
but the bit of butter was
too bitter for the batter.
♪ ♪
‐ ♪ Ay que me va hacer ♪
♪ En caso me hacer despacio ♪
‐ And what if he goes crazy or
something, like kidnaps me?
‐ Already tagged his car.
You just do what
you've always done.
‐ It's not gonna do that,
is it?
‐
Let's hope not.
‐ ♪ Me voy, me voy ♪
‐ He knows.
‐ He doesn't.
‐ Yeah, he does!
‐ He might.
‐
Seriously?
‐ Tracker just went dead.
‐ I want a cop
outside my house.
‐ That'll just draw attention.
‐ So will my dead body
in the Detroit River.
‐ Let's not
lose our heads here.
‐ I at least want
my husband out.
‐ Not till we know
where the money goes.
‐ I did everything you said!
‐ Except the only part
that matters.
‐ That's not on me!
‐ It kind of is.
‐ Trackers sometimes glitch.
‐ Wait, what is
"a pet emergency"?
Because this is
an actual emergency.
‐ Nanny flaked.
‐ Where's Dad?
‐ Chicago.
Some zit cream convention.
‐ Yes!
Samples.
Why do none of
these freaking things work?
‐
‐ Well, how does tomorrow help
me when the meeting is today?
Okay, okay, okay.
Why don't you just let me know
about Gizmo's MRI?
Okay?
Bye.
‐ Why don't you just get
somebody to cover for you?
‐ Because it's not like
your mini‐mart.
I own the company.
‐ So reschedule the meeting.
‐ It's a whole thing
with the bank.
‐ I could take him.
‐ Really?
‐ You have school.
‐ Well, can't he skip?
‐ It's one day.
‐ You always did, right?
‐ Not happening, my friend.
‐ Mom, what is she
supposed to do?
‐ Uh, I don't know.
Find literally anyone else.
‐ There's no one else.
‐
What about the retired guy
who sleeps on his front porch?
‐ He's not allowed around kids.
‐ Your pool guy's like family.
‐ Smokes weed all day
in his truck.
‐ Come on.
Alex'll bring me my homework.
‐ I'll do it.
‐ But Alex will be at school.
‐ No, no, I...
I mean I will watch Dakota.
‐
‐ Sorry.
Why can't I do it?
‐ You can't even take care
of the turtle.
‐ How was I supposed to know
that that green stuff was mold?
‐ You can't even
change a light bulb.
‐ Those are all duds.
Obviously, I...
tried that.
Look, I raised you.
‐ Barely.
‐ Excusez‐moi?
‐ Auntie Beth took me
every day.
‐ Yeah, because
I was finishing 11th grade.
‐ You know, it's fine.
I'm just gonna figure it out.
‐ Drop the kid.
‐ It's very sweet of you
to offer‐‐
‐ Do you remember when
they found that toddler
wandering alone in the woods?
He made it for three days
on his own.
I'm only one day.
‐ If anything happens‐‐
‐ Nothing's gonna happen.
‐ Something's gonna happen.
‐ Come on.
‐ Okay.
All right.
The wipes are
under the diapers.
‐ Check.
‐ The butt rash stuff
is in the side pocket.
‐ Check.
‐ The binky is in a Ziploc
with the snacks.
‐ Checkity‐check‐check.
‐ And Mommy will always,
always love you.
So, so much.
‐ I think that's enough.
Go, go.
Go.
‐
‐ Go!
‐ Okay.
‐
‐ Guess I got school.
‐ Hey, baby.
‐ I forgot the sauce.
‐ What are you talking about?
‐ The chimichurri
for your lunch.
‐ Ooh.
Doesn't need it.
‐ Meatloaf, and no chimichurri?
‐
Don't worry about it.
‐ I'll just drop it off.
‐ Nah.
‐ I'm in the neighborhood.
‐ No, no, no, no, no.
It's crazy here.
You know how it is
on Wing Wednesday.
‐ I'm not getting
on the pole, Stan.
I'll just put it in the fridge.
‐ I already ate it.
‐ You did?
‐ Well, I'm eating now.
‐ Not too dry?
‐ Mm‐mm.
Mmm, it's just as good
sans sauce.
Mmm.
Yep.
‐ I find that hard to believe.
‐ You want me to lie to you?
‐ Just want to make sure
you're taken care of.
‐ Always, baby.
‐ Cool.
Later, Hill.
‐
♪ ♪
‐ Psst.
I'll take that sauce,
if you offering.
‐ Dean hides junk food.
Where were you last night?
What are you doing?
‐ You better watch your back.
‐ Maybe he doesn't know.
‐ At a minimum,
he suspects.
I read about this lady
who turned on her drug dealer
in Florida.
‐ Stop reading those.
‐ Wired up.
Surveillance helicopter
tracked her.
The whole shebang.
‐ That doesn't mean
it's gonna be us.
‐ They found her stuffed
in a suitcase.
‐ I can't.
‐ She was shot
with the gun that
the cops sent her to buy.
‐ I cannot.
‐ At the airport.
‐ How is this helping?
‐ She was his carry‐on.
‐
‐ It's like...
I give him the baba, 'cause
he acts like he wants it,
but then he doesn't want it.
And then, when I take it away,
he wants it again.
Like, what?
‐ Why'd you bring him here?
‐
I've tried everything.
‐ Excuse me?
‐ I mean,
there's heavy machinery.
‐ I mean, I've gone all Harvey
Karp on his ass at this point.
I mean, with the shushing and
the swaddling and the shaking.
‐ Shaking's not one of 'em.
‐ This is exactly
why I need you.
Oh‐‐oh, now you want it.
‐ We have bigger problems here.
‐ Will you just give it to him,
please?
‐ No way, this is a sick,
twisted little game
he's playing,
and I'm not gonna give in.
‐ Give me that.
‐ What?
‐ What's up your butt?
‐ I'll tell you what isn't.
‐ Oh...huh.
‐ What?
‐ I don't know.
It's just not what I imagined.
‐ What did you imagine?
‐ I don't know.
Something sleeker.
This is kind of giving me,
like, '90s pager vibes.
‐ She's not wrong.
‐ I mean, not something
to track a car.
‐
‐ God.
‐ Kid's hungry.
You got a bottle?
‐
I...
It's...
‐ Seconds count.
Shh.
Got a lovey?
‐ What is‐‐what's a‐‐
oh, that.
‐ Shh.
You're not gonna need those.
‐ He doesn't want the drop?
‐ It's not drop day.
‐ What day is it?
‐ Hey, just go get in the car.
‐ Um, she‐‐she can't.
‐ I can't.
‐ And why is that?
‐ The baby.
‐ What about it?
‐ I can't be left alone
with him.
‐ And what about you?
‐ My kids are grown.
‐ Then this won't be fun.
‐ "Seafare Pool and Patio."
Hmm.
That sounds nice.
‐ Back on the horse.
‐ Do what you love, you
don't work a day in your life.
‐ Too bad my boss
is such a D‐I‐C‐K.
‐ You can swear in here.
‐
She's the worst.
‐ She can't be worse
than Gayle.
Are you kidding me?
‐ Who else would hire me?
‐
Bet she loves that I'm in here.
‐ Well, made any friends?
‐ It's not a frat.
‐ At least you get to work out.
‐ Mm‐mm.
You have to be in the Blood
Lords to use the equipment.
‐ Well, what about classes,
you know, like art?
You know, pass the time?
‐ We can't use paintbrushes
anymore.
‐ Why?
‐ This lifer.
He plucked the guard's eyeball
out with one.
‐ Ooh...that's raw, dawg.
‐ I gotta get out of here, man.
‐ Well, how's Beth doing
with the bail?
‐
I think she wants me in here.
King me.
‐ Why would she want that?
‐ So she can hump the tats
off her boyfriend.
‐ Hmm.
I'm gonna get you out.
‐ How are you gonna score
100 grand?
‐ Let me worry about that.
‐ You live in a basement.
‐ You're my best friend.
‐ With a roommate.
‐ Your move.
‐ Are you letting me win?
‐ Don't get too comfy in here.
‐ Oh, no, no.
No, I'm good, man.
‐ Come on.
Join me.
‐ Ah, you know,
it's the middle of the day.
‐ That's why
I don't wear a watch.
Come on.
‐ Yeah.
‐ You're a good guy, Stan.
Thanks.
‐ You're funny.
You know how to talk to people.
Not too bad on the eyes,
either.
‐ What's that?
‐ You work out?
‐ Uh, yeah.
You know, I hit the gym
when I can.
‐ Bet those girls at the club
can't keep their hands off you,
huh?
Stanimal!
Huh?
‐ Hey, man, there's no touching
in the champagne room.
‐ Don't gotta worry about me.
‐ Who I gotta worry about?
Jane?
‐ Someone I want to be
in business with.
‐ Why me?
‐ I can't seem to close her.
‐ I have a wife.
‐ Oh.
Oh, the bitch
who stole my money.
‐ Come on now.
‐ I'd be happy
to put her to work,
if you're not up to it.
She's in room 216.
‐ What's the deal?
‐
‐ It's easier
if you put it on the side.
‐ What, are you on crack?
‐ She is not.
‐ The middle's the safest spot
in the vehicle.
‐ Whatever works.
‐ Let's roll.
‐ Y'all realize we're using
a baby as a human shield.
‐
‐ You're gonna need this...
and this.
‐ Why can't he do it?
‐ Boss is laying low.
‐ And why can't you do it?
‐ You're the banker.
‐ Maybe it'll be okay.
‐ How so?
‐ You can't kill the banker.
‐ Unless...
whoever's waiting behind that
door is gonna take you out.
‐ Not every thought
in that head has to come out.
‐ Oh, plus
he took the tracker,
so they have no idea
where we are.
‐ There's another one.
♪ ♪
‐
‐ Hello?
♪ ♪
Hello?
‐ Is anybody here?
♪ ♪
‐ Nobody move!
Give me the '52 Mantle rookie.
♪ ♪
‐ Can I help you?
‐ Uh...
I'm the banker?
‐ Is she alive?
‐ No.
‐ What?
‐ No, it's Nancy.
She wants proof of life.
Oi...okay.
‐ Could have used one of those
from Stan.
‐ Why?
Where's he at?
‐ Not anywhere he says he is.
‐ I thought he, like,
lived at work.
‐ That's what he says.
‐ Where's the man work?
‐ Um, Sweet P.'s.
‐
The place with the shaved ham?
‐ Oh, whoa!
We prefer "gentleman's club."
‐ Why?
‐ I mean, you gonna say it
or am I?
‐ Come on.
‐ Say what?
‐ He's a bouncer.
‐ And I bet those chicks know
how to show their appreciation.
‐ Okay, you know what?
This is a family matter, so‐‐
‐ Um, you don't know
my husband.
‐ You're right.
Man's got lady gardens
in his face all day.
I bet he can't wait
to get home.
‐ No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
‐ He is always tired.
‐ 'Cause he's always working.
‐ In lady gardens.
‐ I'm the banker.
♪ ♪
Excuse me.
‐ Yeah.
Give me a minute.
‐ I'm the banker.
‐ I'll be right back.
♪ ♪
‐ ♪ I don't wanna be here ♪
♪ I don't wanna be here,
I don't wanna be here ♪
‐ I'm the banker.
‐ ♪ Why'd you bring me here? ♪
♪ Giving me bad dreams ♪
♪ Can't scream, bad dream ♪
♪ How did I wake up
surrounded by walls? ♪
♪ How did I break
all my bones? ♪
♪ Keep banging the concrete ♪
‐ I'm the banker.
I'm the banker.
Heard of me?
Yeah.
The banker.
♪ ♪
‐ ♪ Mommy, wake up,
I can't sleep ♪
♪ I need some comfort
from my dreams ♪
♪ I swear I saw you dancing ♪
♪ With some specters ♪
‐ I'm the banker, bitch.
‐ What did you just call me?
‐ I'm sorry.
I'm the banker.
‐ The what?
‐ Who's the owner here?
‐ My mom.
‐ Is she available?
‐ She's, uh‐‐she's sick.
‐ Well, did she happen
to leave any cash around?
‐ Let me see here.
I got gold bars.
Bunch of diamonds.
Nope.
No cash.
‐ Okay.
Your mother pays my employer
monthly.
‐ For what?
‐ Well, I guess you could say
for protection.
‐ From who?
‐ From him.
‐ Get out of here.
‐ I'm sorry
if this is a hard time‐‐
‐ What do you want me to do?
‐ Maybe shoot her a quick call?
‐ Sure.
Yeah, I'll just have the nurse
hold up the phone
to her dialysis machine,
and you can shake it down.
‐ Okay. I feel terrible‐‐
‐ It'll just magically turn
into an ATM.
‐ Is there anyone else here
I could talk to?
‐ What is wrong with you?
‐ I just need my money.
‐ Or what?
‐
Text you back yet?
You know, the nipples,
the G‐strings.
It's just what he does.
It's not who he is.
Are you gonna finish that?
‐ Oh, my God.
Will you turn the heat down?
It's like Arizona in here.
‐ Little guy sleeps better
when it's warm.
‐ He hasn't woken up yet.
No!
My God.
‐ Just get it already.
‐ She's trying to FaceTime me.
‐ I'll get it.
‐ Oh, yeah, sure.
Because the complete stranger
with the‐‐
this whole message is really
gonna calm her down.
Oh, Jesus.
She finished early.
We...
‐ You got it?
‐ Yep, all there.
‐ You sure?
‐ Positive.
‐ 'Cause if not,
you'll have a situation.
‐ Do you want to count it?
‐ It won't be on me.
‐ Let me guess.
‐ He trusts you.
‐ I hate to make this
about me,
but, uh, any chance we could
get this show on the road?
‐ ♪ Do you remember
when you were quite small? ♪
♪ Your cotton pigtail
and school in the fall? ♪
♪ Autumn leaves
blanket the earth ♪
♪ A new season
was given birth ♪
♪ To feeling
that warms the soul ♪
♪ Another rescue
for the cold ♪
♪ Feel good, feel good ♪
♪ Feel fine ♪
♪ For such a lovely day ♪
♪ Feel good, feel good ♪
♪ Feel fine ♪
♪ Oh, years gone by ♪
♪ Can you remember? ♪
♪ So cold that Christmas
brings a warm December ♪
♪ Think of the many years
gone by ♪
♪ Turn the pages
and give it a try ♪
♪ Feel good, feel good ♪
♪ Feel fine ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Such a ♪
♪ Lovely day ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Fantasy ♪
♪ Is sometimes real ♪
♪ Can you understand? ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Life is hard,
and you felt what I feel ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Someone takes your hand ♪
‐ Mommy.
Can I play a game
on your phone?
‐ Yeah.
Just be careful with it.
‐ Y'all open?
‐ Told you to get out.
‐ What about with
one of these in your face?
It's just
your basic Glock, right?
Front and rear sights.
Polymer grip.
Extractor.
Slide.
Slide release.
Blah‐blah‐blah.
‐ What am I supposed to do
with it?
‐ Pick it up.
‐ No, I don't want it.
‐ Yeah.
And my daughter doesn't want
to wear a helmet
when she rides her scooter,
but you know what?
Bad things happen.
I'm sure your mom would agree.
‐ I'm gonna call the cops.
‐ Go ahead.
He'll just send someone else.
‐ It's not fair.
‐ That's what the gun's for.
‐ All right.
‐ Oh!
I almost forgot.
Better watch your back.
‐ "Sleep tight, goose.
Sleep tight, moose.
Sleep tight, bear
with the fuzzy, fuzzy hair."
‐ I meant to be here sooner.
‐ Hey.
‐ There were, like,
a million documents to sign.
‐ It's fine.
We just got out of the bath.
‐ Oh, how's my little man?
Hello.
‐ Still breathing.
‐ Hello.
‐
‐ When did you last change him?
‐ Oh, just now.
‐ Mm‐mm.
Okay, okay.
‐
What is that?
‐ His ding‐a‐lingy.
‐ It's a rash.
Did you use the cream?
‐ Yeah, of course.
‐ Which one?
‐ The one that said
"diaper cream."
‐ There are two.
I told you to use the one
in the side pocket.
‐ What's the difference?
‐ One works, and one does not.
‐ Then why do you have
the other one?
‐ In case of emergency.
‐ That makes no sense.
‐ Well, now he's got a rug burn
on his crotch.
‐ Well, he didn't tell me
that he was‐‐
‐ Because he can't speak.
‐ No, I mean he didn't indicate
that he was uncomfortable.
‐ You know what?
Just get me a new diaper,
please.
Okay.
Yes, we're gonna fix this.
‐ I'm sorry.
I‐‐
‐ No, no, you know what?
It's my fault.
‐ Why?
‐ Because I left a child
with a child.
Okay.
Almost.
All right.
What do I owe you?
‐ Nothing.
‐ Fine.
Okay.
‐ I, um...
Really, really, really wanted
to get this one right.
‐ Why?
‐ I don't know.
I guess just to know I could.
Sorry.
‐ Tell it to his little sack.
‐
‐ Jesus!
‐ Rough day?
‐ Uh, not what I planned.
‐ You got something
you want to tell me?
♪ ♪
‐ 'Cause I'd really love
to hear from you.
♪ ♪
Straight from
the banker's mouth.
♪ ♪
‐ I'm sorry.
What?
‐ Books didn't balance.
‐ Oh, um...
One of your customers needed
a little bit more persuading.
That's this month and next.
‐ Well, good.
I'm glad it didn't have
to get messy.
‐ Glad it's done.
‐ What's that?
Oh, darling, no, no.
We're just getting started.
‐ Why?
‐ 'Cause I gotta sit tight.
‐ Why me?
‐ You're my girl.
Unless...
you're not.
‐ It just, you know,
feels a little risky.
‐ How's that?
‐ Shaking down
all these people
when maybe someone
is still watching.
‐ Yeah, but all they'll see
is you.
So...
‐ Whoa.
‐ Hmm?
‐ You still going, huh?
‐ Is that a problem?
‐ Can you take Harry
to quiz bowl tomorrow?
‐ Let me check.
You like mama's new purse?
‐ Yeah.
‐ You think I'm worth it?
‐ Of course you are.
‐ Who is she?
‐ Who are you?
‐ It's so obvious.
I can't even believe it.
‐ You're going
through my car now?
What's next, my email?
‐ Oh, I already did that.
‐ Oh, so what, you think
I'm some kind of player?
‐ Exhausted all the time.
Coming home all late‐‐
‐ He had me making
a business deal.
‐ Body glitter?
‐ I mean, listen.
Don't get me wrong.
She would've‐‐
‐ Smelling like
all kinds of wrong.
‐ Excuse me.
That's part of the job.
‐ What about the lying
straight to my damn face?
‐ I am not sleeping around.
‐ Is that part of the job too?
‐ It is when
you put me in this.
‐ What does that mean?
‐ Who you think's
paying off your debt?
‐ You said insurance
covered it.
‐ It's not about money.
‐ What's it about then?
‐
You can't just take
from a guy like him.
‐ Jesus.
‐ Yeah.
‐ What's he got you into?
‐ Whatever Gene needs.
‐ For how long?
‐ How long you into it
with your guy?
Nah, keep it.
It looks real, right?
‐ Perfect.
I mean, close.
‐ Mm‐hmm.
There's 300 more
coming right behind it.
‐ Are you okay?
‐ Yeah.
Why?
‐ I just never knew
you had a floor.
‐ It's wood.
‐ Who knew?
‐ Oh, hey, by the way,
the kitch is fully stocked.
You got
your sour gummy candies,
your sweet gummy candies,
and then a bunch
of the really sour‐sweet ones.
‐ Is this 'cause
of the baby thing?
‐ What baby thing?
‐ What Nancy said about Dakota.
‐ What'd she say?
‐ That he loved you,
and you did really awesome.
‐ Cool.
‐ Mom?
‐ Yeah?
‐ Why'd you take
the turtle out?
‐ I didn't.
♪ ♪
‐ How'd you do it?
‐ Look, I'm not
some big, dirty thug.
I can't keep doing this.
‐ You don't have much
of a choice.
‐ Well, can't we just
sit tight?
‐ Like I said,
don't have much of a choice.
‐ Why?
‐ 'Cause I also have people
that I answer to.
Oh, and, uh,
they're gonna want to meet you.
‐ He's got a boss.
♪ ♪