Previously, on
"Good Girls"...
Stop, stop.
You can't do that.
- Why not?
- Because we're roommates.
You remember Angela.
You look great.
Why'd they throw
out your case?
Well, if I knew that,
I wouldn't be going home.
Hey, Shel.
Need something from evidence.
- So what can I do for you?
- Heard you're the ticket guy.
Sorry.
What was your precinct?
14th.
Hmm.
Get your coat.
- Why?
- 'Cause you'll be cold.
- Gonna wonder where I am.
- Yeah.
That's kind of the point.
I want my sister back!
Finish the job then.
- See you at school.
- Your bags are fake.
- What's this?
- Our offer.
- This is way less than I paid.
- Plumbing.
Electrical.
It's all gotta go.
- We're back in the club.
- Whose name is it in?
I need career advice.
You gonna sell out
your own wife?
It's not like she ever
had my back.
She's not the only
one in this.
I will protect Ruby.
What if that's not up to you?
That's why I have to make
sure it all sticks to Beth.
What do you think, man?
I think I got
something on her.
Here's the rest of it.
- Weird, right?
- What's that?
Being reduced to a box.
- Where's his daughter?
- With the ex.
- How's she doing?
- Never been better.
Really?
Mm-hmm. Random robbery.
Dad gets slaughtered.
She can't wait for Christmas.
None of it's right.
Any leads?
Just every dirtbag
with a prior.
What are you gonna do?
I have, like, a month
of banked vacay.
Aren't you suspended for,
like, three?
So I'll get a Peloton after.
Do that before the vacation.
Don't let this die, okay?
Nothing can survive here.
I grabbed your mail, too.
Why didn't I leave Detroit
when you did?
'Cause you're not
smart enough
to know it's all pointless.
Hey, did Dave say anything
about our last night there?
He, like, made this noise
I've actually never heard
a man make.
It was, like, high-pitched.
I think we're gonna go
on vacation,
like, Playa del Carmen.
They like gays, in Puerto Rico.
I think he'll like that.
How could his wife not know?
She knows?
*GOOD GIRLS*
Season 04  Episode 13
Episode Title: "You"
Aired on: July 08, 2021.
What's that gonna do?
We'd be protected.
You'll be protected.
I think the question is
how does you being
on city council protect us?
Because I'd finally have
some real leverage.
You kind of already do.
How?
I mean, he's not gonna mess
with somebody he wants to...
- Don't.
- Fingerpaint.
- That's gross.
- Pick your lock?
Somehow worse.
Give you the double gopher.
I think you see
where we're going with this.
I mean some real leverage,
like if he wants to throw you
in a freezer again.
I would have the city
on my side.
What happened to Nevada?
- Nothing.
- 'Cause we wouldn't have
to worry about the freezer
in Nevada, right?
Yeah, but I'd like
to get us there in one piece.
- That's a pretty big detour.
- Yeah.
You don't really stop in Miami
on your way to Vegas.
Okay. Chill.
Gosh.
It wasn't even my idea.
Whose idea was it?
- Brother cousin.
- Hmm.
What?
Okay.
That is not
why he suggested it.
I mean, isn't it?
- He said he could use me.
- Oh, I bet he could.
A mom like me.
And I'm guessing
he also has fingers.
All right. Forget it.
I'll tell him
to ask someone else.
Sheesh.
There's no one else.
No. We don't have to fill
his seat right away,
so why don't you just
take a minute
and, you know,
realize why I'm right?
Okay.
Take longer than a minute.
Yeah, but I'm not gonna
give in easy.
All right.
Talk to you later. Bye.
Maybe she's just not that
into you, bro.
Mm.
She'll come around.
Chicks like that don't need
to be romanced.
Oh, yeah?
What does she need?
Someone to yank her
by that ponytail.
That's not my style,
brother.
You want her in that
seat, right?
What would you do?
I'd give her
what she needs.
I know what you need.
What's that?
You need to stop
eating this burger.
Yo!
Gotta make weight.
Always want what I already
have, huh?
Always get it too.
Mmm!
Ah!
Ow, hey, stop, stop.
Annie!
- What are you doing?
I thought you were
breaking in.
- My key didn't work.
- Yeah.
Well, yeah,
because the lock is broken.
Is that why your entire
kitchen's on the floor?
It's my alarm system.
It worked.
Where have you been?
Angela's.
Well, you missed
all the action.
I did all right.
I meant here.
Wait,
where are you going now?
- Gotta get back.
- Angela could stay here.
I wouldn't want
to break your rules.
I'll make an exception.
We might order food.
I could also order food.
We could all three watch
a movie or...
She asked me to move
in with her.
Already?
This my avocado knife?
It's not.
- Can I have it?
- Uh...
Don't you just think
it might be a little soon?
Dude, it's better
than couch-surfing.
Okay. Well, then you can
sleep in my bed.
I mean I'll stay in Ben's room.
Why would you do that?
Because we had a deal.
Just... tell the school
I still live here.
Wait. Please, I...
I don't want to be alone.
Neither do I.
What's all this?
Need to get 'em out of here.
What about our money?
Well, you should have thought
about that before you
and your bestie told Eli's mom
that she bought a fake.
- It just came out.
- Yeah.
Well, it's all over
the parent chain.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, yeah.
They threatened
to call the cops.
- What did you say?
- It was a mistake.
- That's good.
- And I refunded all her money.
Not good.
Well, what else
was I supposed to do?
- This was our way out.
- It was.
And not just for us.
Do you feel that?
- What?
- The déjà vu.
- This isn't Beth's fault.
- Yeah.
You go out with your girl
for one night,
and then you come back with
problems that last you forever.
So we'll find
another way out.
She'll screw that up too.
Goodwill will be here
in the morning.
- Stan?
- This one was mine.
It's just like what is
he even doing in there?
Well, he's probably built up
more filth,
because he's been homeless
for so long.
He might as well be showering
in Cristal,
for what it's costing me.
- What if he took baths?
- He moved out.
Problem solved.
Still can't pay
the water bill.
We need another purse party.
Oh, okay.
Check with the girls,
would you?
Totally.
Get something on the books.
It might...
not be right away.
How come?
Just, you know,
some issues.
What kind of issues?
Inventory.
♪ They don't even want
a pic ♪
♪ Wanna lick up on the
yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I done made a couple hits ♪
♪ Goin' hammer with the Bic ♪
♪ God handed me the gift ♪
So a dealership?
Never really my thing.
Spas?
What are those even for?
But this?
This is how
we make dreams come true.
Not "we."
Public record, darling.
- This is ours.
- A little Lysol. Lot of love.
- This is just where we print.
- Clean this place right up.
Not a place to wash.
It is now.
We know nothing about
running a strip club.
Didn't know much about cars
or hot tubs either.
How much?
How much what?
Our cut.
Why would I do that?
You know how this goes.
How clean do you
want your money?
Oh, I want it to sparkle.
Then you get
what you pay for.
What are you doing?
Maybe we could work
something out.
- Don't be mad.
- I'm not mad.
- She's mad.
- We were out.
- Not exactly.
- We were more out than in.
You know how you protect us?
By doing exactly what he says.
At least now
we're getting paid.
That's what the purses
are for.
The purses are gone.
Can't we just make more?
Not without getting Harry
kicked out of school.
Oh, no.
- What happened?
- I said a thing.
- She said a thing.
- Oh, no.
So without this it is
bye-bye Nevada.
- Hey, bitches.
- Hey.
I'm starving.
Yo, hey, let me get
a Reuben sandwich, okay,
Extra Russian dressing.
What kind of fries you got?
Steak. Skinny. Curly.
Okay.
- Which one?
- All three.
Okay, so we have two parties
coming up,
and we can stick these guys
with at least ten purses.
- Change of plans.
- Okay.
Need you back at the club.
- What do you mean?
- It's opening back up.
That's not gonna happen.
Why not?
The girls have moved on.
Can't we get 'em back?
Oh, no.
Jean treated us like garbage.
Oh, well,
there's new management.
Who?
Low Pros' "Who Wanna Play"
plays...
♪ Hundred band jewel,
now who wanna play ♪
♪ Fifty shots in the K,
♪ We could take it outside
if you wanna play ♪
♪ Got some... down to die,
now who wanna play ♪
♪ Who wanna play ♪
♪ Who wanna play,
who wanna play ♪
♪ Who wanna play ♪
♪ Who wanna play
who wanna play ♪
♪ Who wanna play ♪
♪ Hundred band jewel,
now who wanna play ♪
♪ Fifty shots in the K,
♪ We could take it outside
if you wanna play ♪
♪ Got some... down to die,
now who wanna play ♪
♪ Who wanna play ♪
♪ Who wanna play,
who wanna play ♪
♪ Who wanna play ♪
♪ Play, play, play, play
play, play, play, play ♪
♪ Play, play, play,
play play, play, play, play ♪
♪ Play, play, play, play
play, play, play, play ♪
♪ Who wanna play ♪
♪ Hundred band jewel,
now who wanna play ♪
All of us.
We'll treat it
like a partnership.
We'll split the costs
and the profits.
So instead of just dancing
on the table...
You'll finally have
a seat at it.
So what do you guys think?
Whoo!
Babe, the geraniums don't go
with the snapdragons.
I'm just planting everything
that's in the flats, babe.
Now we've got purple
on top of lavender.
- So?
- They clash, babe.
It's the exact same color.
You are such a dude.
Cowboy.
Sorry.
The gate was open.
Babe, this is Agent Donnegan.
She was
with me in Detroit.
Thanks for keeping him
in line.
He's a pretty
straight shooter.
Well, my trainer's
on her way.
Babe, just make it look pretty.
I tried to sway the director.
It's not your fault.
Yeah, but it was
under my watch.
I'm the one lost the money.
You didn't lose it.
You just got played.
I'll be okay.
I wish there was something
more I could do.
There is.
Can you help me water here?
Come with me.
Where you going?
Detroit.
- You're off the clock.
- It's my vacation.
They'll never authorize this.
- They will for you.
- We lost, kid.
That's 'cause
we didn't connect the dots.
This is for someone else.
It's not just about money.
It's not even our
jurisdiction there.
He's got the entire city
in his pocket,
and you're just
gonna plant petunias?
- Geraniums.
- Well, they're beautiful.
Thank you.
With a garden like that,
who cares that he slaughtered
a cop, card store girl,
and a team of federal agents?
You need a real vacation.
And you need to separate
the purple ones, babe.
I found this...
in my underwear a while ago.
Wow.
Look at the quality.
I didn't touch it,
so those are all her prints.
- Sweet.
- Yeah, I...
I got this
from my wife's cell.
They're just talking about
going to a book club.
No. It's code.
Yeah. Nobody was doing
any reading.
So we made a whole list,
right,
with timestamps, you know.
See, it correlates with
when she left
in the middle of the night.
- Making her drops.
- Maybe we can use the towers.
You know, however they do that.
They use the towers.
Maybe that's how you
track the money.
I mean is that enough?
It's up to the DA.
Wait.
What's gonna happen to her?
Everything that never should
have happened to you.
It's the right thing, D.
It's easy for you to say.
It's not your wife.
She brought it
on herself.
Listen to this guy.
He knows what's up.
I mean I'm just trying
to help out a friend.
You're gonna fit in great
with the team.
How's that?
You got your territory
all set.
Yeah.
You can work under Dean,
till you get
the program down.
I'm not looking
for a career change.
No, no. That's the wrong way
to think about it.
Yeah.
No disrespect.
The night renewal cream is
really flying off the shelves.
Let's not talk shop
in front of tourists.
No disrespect.
It's all good.
Ahh
When are you gonna get
that lock fixed?
- Why are you home?
- I live here.
But you have the tournament.
- Yeah.
- Oh.
So you guys need, like,
a chaperone or...
- Dad's doing it.
- Oh.
What about a water girl?
What's going on?
What? Nothing.
Ever get the feeling
you're gonna be
kidnapped and murdered?
I'm gonna skip
the tournament.
- No, no, no.
- It's one game.
It's the semifinals.
Why don't you stay
with Aunt Beth?
Ugh. 'Cause those kids
wake up at, like, 8:00.
Rather get murdered.
Where'd Kevin go?
His girlfriend.
Well, where's
Martha gonna go?
Who?
His friend with the green
shopping cart.
- How do you know her?
- Martha and Tom come over
to do laundry
when you're at work.
Of course they do.
Rollerblade Roy just chills
and watches Maddow sometimes.
The rest of 'em crash behind
the food court, at the mall.
They throw out
everything there.
Panda Express.
Steak Escape.
Wetzel's Pretzels.
Hot Dog on a Stick.
I think I finally figured
out this bedtime thing.
Only took four kids.
Promise 'em anything
they want,
and they go to sleep
with a smile on their face.
And what happens
when they wake up?
They've forgotten everything.
So you lie.
- I'm open to suggestions.
- Maybe try holding a pillow
over their cute little face,
till they pass out.
Wow.
Let me know how that goes.
I'm on mornings, so...
Well, I might be working
more nights, from now on.
Why?
He's just throwing a lot
at us, these days.
All right.
You gotta do
what you gotta do.
Thanks.
Don't miss too many bedtimes.
You never know
how many you got left.
They don't grow up that fast.
Reservation?
Angela, right?
Sorry. Annie.
I'm Kevin's old roommate.
Oh, my God. Hi.
Hey. I'm sorry
to bother you at work.
I just... I couldn't get
a hold of him.
Oh, he's probably
at my place.
Oh, yeah. Of course.
Makes sense.
It's just, you know, with his
phone number always changing,
'cause the prepaid phones
and all that.
- He uses those?
- Yeah.
That or the payphone
at the bus station
which he swears
still works, but...
- Gross.
- Yeah. Oh, speaking of, here.
Yeah. He left this behind.
- What is that?
- His bathroom.
- He poops in there?
- Oh, yeah.
Poops. Showers.
Shaves. The works.
- He can use my bathroom.
- You know Kev.
Creature of habit.
Oh, he also forgot
to take these.
Condiments?
I have all this stuff.
In my experience,
you're gonna want to double up.
Why?
Well, you know he doesn't
believe in silverware,
so when you combine that
with the bucket
it just gets a little dicey.
Why are you doing this?
Just... to help you prepare.
Or maybe you're jealous,
or, like, lonely,
or just, like, psycho.
Okay. I'm cool with Kevin.
- That's great.
- I like that he's different.
Hey, he's all yours.
Thanks.
- ATM.
- Check.
- Liquor vendors.
- Dry cleaning.
- Jean put in coin-op machines.
We'll set up an account.
- Trash removal.
- Underway.
How are you on diapers?
This one just had
a major blowout.
Okay.
I'll make sure you're stocked.
- Health insurance forms.
- Yeah.
Make sure all the girls
get one of those.
Some ladies outside want
to talk to the managers.
Can we help you?
We're here about the dancing.
Oh. Auditions are Tuesday.
Fully nude?
We leave that up
to the performer.
Do you know how many kids
ride their bikes past here
every single day?
We're fully zoned
and licensed.
Not anymore.
There's enough there
to keep you from opening.
It's your turn
in the freezer.
Don't need a turndown.
Thanks.
Haven't left my bed
since the last turndown.
Not housekeeping.
Took me
three flights to get here.
- Why?
- I use miles.
- We're both on vacation.
You better give me
money for that.
It's mine too.
How?
We're roommates.
Department chief can't spring
for his own room?
I'm kind of in
the middle of something.
My funds are limited.
My wife left me.
This is all you got, huh?
What happened?
We're still gonna have
to track a motive.
No. Why did she leave?
I told her that I like
a more diverse garden.
So what now?
We get him.
I fart in my sleep.
I watch an unhealthy
amount of porn.
We're gonna be just fine.
What is Family
First Alliance?
Not a group you want
on your bad side.
Women have been naked
in that dump for over a decade.
Yeah. Well, when
ownership transfers...
But it's the same place.
The community has a say
about it.
- I don't even want to do this.
- Then don't.
Oh, sure, so your brother can
come for the rest of my family.
Not my brother.
What is he exactly?
Blood.
Well, you are
my elected official.
So?
So you're supposed
to be helpful.
You want this problem
to go away?
Yes, please.
Then run for city council.
I'm just a mom.
I was just a caddie.
Well, what's a plain,
old mom supposed to do?
- Fight.
- How?
Studies show crime goes up
around a strip club.
Assault, random victimization,
drunk driving,
and public indecency.
This is what we live in fear of
when we take our dog for a walk
or our kids to a school that is
right around the corner.
What crawled up her butt?
We ask you tonight to restore
family values to our community
and to finally shut down
this lawless den of sin.
Thank you.
Anyone else like to speak
on this matter?
Okay.
If there are no objections,
- we'll move to vote...
- Just a second.
Someone still has the floor.
Yes. I'd like to read
a statement I've prepared.
Oh, boy.
From the oldest of times,
people danced
for a number of reasons.
They danced in prayer,
or so that their crops
would be plentiful,
or so that their hunt...
- Is she doing "Footloose"?
- Would be good.
I couldn't talk her
out of it.
It worked for Bacon.
They danced to stay
physically fit and show
their community spirit,
and they danced...
Okay. Thank you. Thank you.
I would also like to respond
to what the woman
from Families First said.
I respect that you're a mother.
I am also a mother.
In fact, we're all mothers,
right, Krystal?
I drop my first-grader
off at that school
right around the corner,
before I go to the club.
My little girl's
in third grade there.
My son's in college.
Boy, she looks incredible.
We are all just trying
to make a living.
There's a lot of other ways
to do that.
Fine, but...
do they all benefit
our economy the way ours does?
Is Mr. Samborski here?
- Right here.
- This is Mr. Samborski.
He owns the 24-hour donut shop
right next to the club.
My sales between 2:00
and 5:00 a.m.
have gone way down,
since Sweet P's closed.
That's one business.
I own a jewelry store.
When Sweet P's was open,
we did so much better.
Husbands are way more generous
with their wives
when they feel guilty.
The guys always pre-game
at my sports bar.
We need to get those girls
to take their
clothes off again.
See? Whether they're
dancing in a club,
or speaking in a board room,
or baking in a kitchen,
these women are making
a difference in our community.
And aren't those values just as
important to show our children?
Well, thank you for listening.
Whoo!
How'd I do?
You brought home the Bacon.
Next up, after the vote,
ordinance 0.682.
The length of retractable
dog leashes.
Ooh, I gotta hear this.
Open for business.
- Congrats. So exciting.
- Thanks, baby.
- Thank you.
- Yes. Whoo!
Huh, so what
should we toast to?
To our new venture.
Most of which we give to the
man who put you in a freezer.
Why are we even celebrating?
Hey, guys.
Miss us?
What's all that?
Redemption.
Huh?
We are ice cream
social chairs,
running a car wash thing,
a holiday boutique,
concert committee.
Is that enough to keep
the cops away?
Well, it's enough
to keep him in that school.
- The car wash is all you.
- Yeah.
What's all that?
Putting in a spice rack.
Hell no.
Oh, I'm not getting on it.
But who... hell to the no.
I think it's fun!
For you.
My own private
champagne room.
So what am I?
A piece of meat?
Tonight, no.
Tonight...
- you're a fireman.
- Oh.
Wait,
where'd you even get this?
We replaced the old ones.
What's going on, baby?
We're opening the club
back up.
- Who's "we?"
- All of us.
Me, the girls,
even the dancers.
Okay yeah.
You can't do that.
Before you get weird,
I'm just as much an owner
as Beth is.
- Ruby.
- This is our new way out.
We don't even need the bags.
Is this a done deal?
We're legit.
There might even be
a job in it for you.
For me?
Chiiild's "Back To Life"
Who's next? Dennis.
Tyler.
What do we look for?
We look for weaknesses, right?
Let's go!
There you go. No retreat.
No surrender, Tyler.
He's bigger,
but you might be better.
Tyler, don't back up.
Get in there.
Dennis, attack!
Good.
All right.
Let's take a break.
Dennis, help Tyler up.
Caleb, that's enough crying.
We're not giving out
crying patches.
Come on. Join the group.
Let's go.
Today.
Let's go!
This one's trying to get
his fitness patch here.
Yeah. Well, this is
important.
Make it quick.
So it turns out that Beth's
not the only one
that's going down.
- So?
- So my wife's in it too.
More the merrier.
You can't give that stuff
to the DA.
- Putting me in a tough spot.
- I know.
I mean, I'm Team Dean
all the way.
I just need you to drag
your feet a little bit.
Why would I do that?
- Come on, man.
- No, it'd be
a different story if you were
one of us, but...
Dennis, stop whipping Tyler.
If I'm gonna have your back
I'd want to know
that you'd have mine.
I'll do whatever it takes.
Let's talk at
the next meeting.
All right. See you there.
Yeah you will.
Let's go. Line up.
I fixed the lock.
What are you doing?
- Hungry?
- I mean, yeah, always, but...
We're having citrus-braised
lamb shanks.
What...
happened with Angela?
I mean, she's not
really roommate material.
Oh.
What is she, like,
a clean freak or something?
You ever see that episode
of "Hoarders"
with the woman
who kept dead cats?
Of course.
That's Angela?
Yeah, but instead
of dead cats,
it was rotisserie chickens.
She would eat off them
for weeks.
They were all over the place.
You like mint jelly
with lamb?
- No.
- Good.
So, why did you leave?
Isn't that what you wanted?
I mean, why else would you
do something this crazy.
Are you mad?
I was, at first.
But then I thought about it,
and...
no one's ever
really needed me before.
No one's ever
needed me either.
- Oh. You got any cumin?
- Uhh...
Does taco seasoning count?
It's close enough.
Also, it's so nice to have
my bucket back.
Thank you.
This is older than me.
Well, I figure it's what
fancy politicians drink.
Thank you.
So how does it
feel being tax ID#49-3451299?
- Overwhelming.
- Why's that?
There's a lot more people
to answer to.
Based on the other night,
I think you handled
it pretty well.
What was the vote?
4-3.
Close.
There's always
someone to convince.
- Not if you had my vote.
- Serious?
You think a strip club owner
has a shot?
You're of the people.
I'll need lots of advice.
What changed your mind?
Jonathan Bree's
"Until We're Done" plays...
♪ Take it ♪
♪ Show me how you move girl ♪
♪ Back it up
all night until we're done ♪
♪ All night,
keep it moving ♪
♪ All night, we work it ♪
You.
Wait, Beth.
Let's crack this open.
Oh, I haven't earned it yet.
You're gonna win.
Share it with someone
who already has.
Pour that out.
♪ Keep moving all night ♪
♪ Keep working ♪
Sync corrections by srjanapala