Previously on "Good Girls"...
You can stay at St. Anne's.
- How?
- Well...
Yo, you're out of Q-tips.
- That's my toothbrush.
- Roomie.
You ever heard of The System?
That's like a
pyramid thing, right?
A multilevel opportunity.
Does feel like this time
we got a real chance.
Or you haven't told
him our good news?
I don't think he'll
take it that way.
I want to know what's going on.
- D.C. pulled the plug.
- Why?
Clearly he's got
someone on the inside.
I wore you out already?
- No, cousin.
- Yo.
- Dean's gonna go to jail.
- They can't do that.
- Can't they?
- We have to get to Nevada.
Who's gonna foot
those moving costs?
You still have those bags?
I guess we could
move a few of these.
- We need help.
- No.
- She helped you.
- No!
You use whoever you can
to get whatever you want.
I got you your money.
You got my wife shot.
What time is it?
Time to sleep in.
Are the kids up?
I got it.
You da best.
Breakfast time!
Dut-dut-dut-dut-dut-
dut-dut-dut-dut-duh!
Wake up, maggots!
- Ah!
- I'm up!
- Okay, man.
If you're not up in five,
I'm coming back with the
fire extinguisher again.
And music camp was
so great to have,
and learning to play the
guitar and song-writing...
Oh. Hey.
Look at what I got. Mint.
I got Maple Creme.
I got Birthday Cake.
And I got Double Stuf.
Trade amongst yourselves,
mix and match,
but do not tell your mother.
Wait, wait. Where
is she, by the way?
Work.
We're... we're supposed to
load up the minivan, right?
I don't know.
When is she coming home?
But she said no snacks.
Ink, chemicals, paper.
- The hologram's polymer.
- One-stop shop.
Everything you need.
And why you making it so easy?
'Cause you bitches
made it so messy.
And what happens
when I gotta wash it?
Don't worry about it.
Where am I supposed to do it?
Duty-free?
Tim Horton's downtown?
They take Canadian?
You don't have to.
What about my cut?
What about it?
Does it come in loonies?
Elizabeth.
All you have to do
is print and drop.
Your husband's here.
- Just need to...
Trade cars.
Now?
Thought we would hit the
road early for, you know.
Oh. Kenny's game, yeah.
You're not supposed to be here.
Yeah. Neither are you.
No, man, I mean,
it's not gonna be good for
anybody when the cops come.
- I'm within range.
- It's low battery.
Please, just go.
How you feel about baby blue?
- Eh.
- Okay.
How about... ostrich?
Better.
Okay, okay.
What if...
We combine the two?
- That the new one?
- Yep.
She said we could
swap whatever we want.
Awesome.
Yeah. Lowers our cost like 8%.
Good for you.
This is good for sales.
Next party is gonna
be pure profit, baby.
Oh, I'm not going.
Hey, what, now?
I can't.
I didn't even tell
you when it is.
Doesn't matter.
Wait, baby, you're the one
that wanted to keep
this train running.
Not if you two are gonna
keep clapping at each other.
Oh, my God. Ruby.
No one is clapping at anyone.
No, it's worse.
Last party, you didn't
even speak to her.
What? I got nothing to say.
I had to be the damn
go-between for my husband
- and my best friend.
- Then don't be.
You don't have to love her.
- I don't.
- Don't even have to like her.
- Oh, I don't.
- Just take the high road.
What for?
Me.
You say all this to her?
She could take the high road.
Our first family meeting.
Just meeting.
One sec.
Okay, first up, let's go
over the bathroom rules.
I know, I know. Off-limits.
No. We're cool if you use it.
But I got the bucket.
Yeah, we'd, uh
we'd actually like you
to get rid of that.
Mm.
Number two, do not wash your
underwear in the kitchen sink.
Mm, let me guess. Bathroom.
Washer. It's in the basement.
And it's free.
Whaaaat?
Okay. Um...
Where do you guys
stand on parties?
- Anti.
- We're also anti-your music
and the shopping cart
that's parked in the hallway
with all of the cans in it.
- My bank account?
- Gotta go.
Which, I believe, brings
us to the timeline.
How long are we talking here?
For what?
For the length of stay.
I don't understand the question.
When will you be leaving?
Well, when's graduation?
Uh...
Is his name Chris or Kevin?
It is way too late to ask.
Car is packed.
They hit the ice at 7:00.
Okay.
Next year, he'll
be bantamweight,
so you won't have to get
up at the crack of dawn.
Dean.
I mean, I really wish
I could take him.
No one knew this would happen.
Could you FaceTime
me when he plays?
- Not me.
- Not the Secret Service.
Don't.
I'm trying to
explain what you saw.
I didn't see anything.
All right.
Just FaceTime me, please.
Yeah.
How are you doing, dear?
Good.
I'll have them to
you in an hour.
What happened with
the Klein bat mitzvah?
Oh, the one with
the pop-up Torahs?
- They were a week late.
- Yeah, but she loved them.
She didn't really have
a choice, did she?
Is everything okay?
We need to talk about Megan.
Oh, God. That wasn't on her.
- I'm gonna make some changes.
- No, no, no.
I was just going through
some personal stuff.
That was totally my fault.
She's getting promoted.
Oh. To what?
Shift manager.
Isn't that my job?
- You're a wonderful mother.
- Spend more time at home.
They grow up so fast.
- My husband's out of work.
- I really need this job.
I need someone I can rely on.
- Megan's in 11th grade.
Sweetie, it's just a job.
Oh, Dorothy.
It is so much more than that.
I'm gonna need you to
clean out your craft cubby.
.
I still don't get it.
What's there to get?
Well, how are they supposed
to know who they want to marry
if they can't see each other?
- That's literally the point.
- But they're blind.
For four episodes, she
thought this show was
about blind people dating?
- It's not?
- Thank you.
What is wrong with y'all?
We have bigger issues right
now than Amber and Barnett.
Yeah. Jessica won't hump Mark.
You know, I don't see why.
- She can't see anything.
- Excuse me.
We don't have anywhere
to print, guys.
- Can't we just sneak in?
- Yeah.
Middle of the night,
do one big run.
Because it's never one.
- He always wants more.
- So we'll go back.
And she'll change the alarm.
Why don't we just
steal the whole thing?
Hey. Now you're talking.
Okay, and then what do we do
with a two-ton printing press?
Well, we put it in your garage.
So Mrs. Karpinski
can just drop in and
borrow the leaf blower?
What's she
gonna do, call a Mountie?
Or my kids walk in, and
Mom's printing cash.
Yeah, I can see that
that could be a problem.
I got a place.
Let's just get another
storage unit, you know?
Electricity,
drainage, ventilation.
- Calm down.
- Guys.
Not to mention space. Privacy.
It's called a
brainstorming sesh.
I know where we can do it.
Where?
- Strip club.
- It's still shut down.
Can Stan get us in?
What do we have to
do to convince him?
Not "we."
What?
We have a Philly
cheesesteak special.
That'll come on an onion roll.
Choice of side.
Fries or coleslaw.
I think we need
a couple minutes.
I'll set you up
with some waters.
- Want to share something?
- The answer's no.
Or just get your own.
I'm not putting my neck
out on the line for you.
It's not just for me.
I don't want my wife in
anything else you got going.
Well, it's a little
late for that.
Ready to order?
- She's on her own.
- Couple more minutes.
This guy doesn't care
about what you want.
- Find some place else, okay?
- There is nowhere else.
Beth.
The less you and I gotta deal
with each other, the better.
You think he's just gonna
let us off the hook,
'cause you're pissed at me?
I think you gotta worry
about your family,
and I gotta worry about mine.
I'm sorry.
Is that what you want to hear?
What for?
What you sorry for?
I am sorry...
That you feel that I have...
Somehow put your family in a
not-ideal situation.
Okay. All right.
Let me... let me
try this one on.
So, you're sorry that I
feel you should be sorry?
- What else do you want?
- I want you to mean it.
Okay.
I am sorry.
Better.
I'm sorry that what I got your
wife into makes her happy.
Oh, that's how you
gonna play this?
Not to mention, pays your bills.
You know what I want?
Please.
I want you out of her life.
Okay.
Okay?
You get us in that club, and
she'll never see me again.
Maid of honor.
Oh, I know.
You just gonna give all that up?
Dean's facing 20 to 30.
Can't stick around for a trial.
What looks good, folks?
We'll share the chili fries.
And Sea Kelp
Moisturizer is up 50%.
- All right!
- Nice.
All right, now,
guys, we got to push
the Spot Fading Serums
though, all right?
Maybe they'd sell if they
didn't smell like ass.
Active ingredients.
Smell means what?
It's working.
Right. It's a joke.
I like jokes.
You know what else is a joke?
Your numbers.
- It's just one month.
- Till it's two.
Then three. Then four.
Then you're flat on your face.
I'm on it.
What happens if he
isn't on it, fellas?
All: We pick him up!
What's holding you back?
Uh... thing with
Jules' mom again.
How long she want
to stay this time?
She bought a one-way ticket.
- Ugh.
- Boy.
- What's he gotta do, fellas?
- All: Stand up!
Evolution has given us
the ability to stand up.
We stand up for our families.
Stand up for our community.
Stand up when we pee.
- It's not that easy.
Then let's do it together.
- Yeah.
- Attaboy, Cory!
Now you go home
- and you stand up to Jules.
- Yeah.
- Strong sales.
- All: Strong hearts.
There we go.
Dean.
You put up some solid
numbers this week.
Thanks.
Let's keep it that way.
What's going on with you?
- I'm fine.
- You don't get slapped
with an ankle bracelet
by being fine.
Look, I love selling
the products.
They're great. It's just
you know, all this, it's
just not really my thing.
- All right.
- Let's wrap it up, fellas.
Strong sales. All:
Strong hearts.
Hey, Dean?
- No pressure.
- Cool.
Do you really want
to make it here?
I mean, yeah.
You're gonna need all
the help you can get.
Hi.
Excuse me.
Any idea where,
uh, your friend is?
Who, Kevin?
Kevin. Thank you.
- Oh, hey.
- You're all out of shampoo.
That was a brand-new bottle.
Yeah, you know, we
were all pretty gnarly.
Can I speak with you
outside for a moment?
Yeah.
- I thought I said no parties.
- I know.
Well, then, what
the hell is that?
It's laundry club.
That is not a thing.
Well, not for the homed.
- Okay, you know what?
- This is not gonna work.
- It's only once a month.
- No, no.
This, this. You here, with us.
Well, I have no
place else to go.
Can't you bunk
with that old man?
- Oh, no.
- Murphy's super private.
It's just... it's too weird.
- Just give it a chance.
- It's too weird for my son.
Well, I'm his guardian.
On paper.
Yeah. Fine.
I'll, uh...
Yeah, I'll go get my stuff.
Thank you.
And, yeah, I'll let
the school know.
Whoa, whoa.
Let the school know what?
I'm no longer your
domestic partner.
- You can't do that.
- Well, I can't lie.
I mean, you can.
But I'm not gonna.
- It's for my kid.
- Sorry.
It's just too weird.
That woman could only
own a paper store.
Mm, I don't know.
Name literally anything else.
- Christmas tree farm.
- Same diff.
Or like a jam store in Vermont.
I mean something
that wouldn't be
in a Lifetime movie.
- Okay, then I don't know.
- Mm.
Okay. Let's go.
Kind of have a weird thing
going on with the neighbors.
- Yeah.
- So, the quicker, the better.
And quieter.
We'd do it during
business hours,
but the new model arrives in
the morning, you know, so.
And we really gotta hit
the ground running, right?
'Cause Mother's Day, graduation,
I mean, they're all
right around the corner.
- Oh, Father's Day.
- Can't leave out the dads.
Gonna stop you right there.
- We have cash.
- We're not doing this.
A lot of cash.
It's not the money.
Okay, you know what?
I'm just gonna be real with you.
We are straight-up
stealing this thing.
You don't need to know
the why, but just know
that our life kind
of depends on it.
And you can waste time
with morality, that's fine.
But just know that
you are looking at
three mostly good moms
who really need your help.
We don't have a problem
with any of that.
Thing just won't fit.
It's too big. It won't
go through the door.
But if you got anything
smaller you want to steal,
we cool with that.
.
- How'd it get in here?
- Maybe they built
the building around it.
This ancient machine from
Germany was just sitting here.
Maybe.
In a field.
- Maybe.
- Until Dorothy
stumbles upon it and decides...
Card shop.
Maybe.
Someone must have put it
together piece by piece.
Well, can't we find that guy?
How?
Well, who services it?
- Repair guy.
- Okay.
So, we find that guy, and...
Who knows Dorothy.
Then can we just get
somebody who's, like, handy?
- At this hour?
- There are apps.
What, TaskRabbit?
There are others.
- What's it like inside there?
- Guys.
- The Earth still round?
- Is the sky even blue?
Dean.
You think he could do it?
He took apart our
dishwasher last week.
I guess this is kind
of like an appliance.
Would he?
So, how do we convince him?
Not "we."
Honey, wake up. Come on.
- What's going on?
- Come on, I need your help.
- Now?
- Yeah, it can't wait.
I'm sorry.
- Is it the kids?
- No.
Is it my mom?
No. I need your toolbox.
- Oh, it's the toilet again.
- No.
Well, what is it?
Dean.
No.
Listen.
This is the only way we're
gonna turn this around.
How does helping him help me?
Because if I keep
him in business,
he won't notice what
I'm doing on the side.
What are you doing
on the side now?
I am saving up.
- For my lawyer?
- To run.
- Where?
- I don't care,
as long as they can't find us.
- I'd rather have a lawyer.
- You would need
the entire bar association
to save you now.
I'll get my tools.
What?
Um.
Could you guys give us a minute?
But my pulp's gonna dry.
Let's check out the pole.
How's it going?
Almost there.
Thank you.
I never realized what
went into all of this.
Yeah.
I mean, it took a second
for us to find our groove.
It's impressive.
Yeah?
And... terrifying.
Why?
When we get to
where we're going,
how do I know he won't be there?
I'm not gonna forward our mail.
Like, how... how do I know
he's not gonna be in your head?
Because
he never belonged there
in the first place.
And what about all of this?
What about it?
What's gonna replace it?
You. And the kids.
Where are you going?
We've never made you smile
like all this just did.
You have to finish.
- Why?
- Because I told you,
this is what gets us out.
No, that's what gets you off.
This whole time, I thought
he was the problem.
He's just the excuse.
.
- What does it look like?
- Even if we find it,
how are we gonna
put it together?
We can figure out five pieces.
- It's not like it's 50.
- Okay, does it look like this?
- Kind of.
- Okay, or more like this?
- Just get both.
Uh.
Mm. It's in Germany.
You gotta talk to him.
What's there to say anymore?
What'd you say to Stan?
I just told him what
he wanted to hear.
Then do the same.
Mm.
Really, really sucks
to be you this week.
Hey, hey, hey.
- What are you doing?
- Yo, this is super fly.
- That is not yours.
- Like, the Tesla
- of lacrosse sticks.
- Give it back.
Oh, oh, oh!
- Score!
- Stop.
Okay, that is enough.
That's enough, that's enough.
I can't take it anymore, okay?
I'm relocating you.
- Huh?
- Yeah.
I'm gonna lease you a house.
- For real?
- Yep.
On wheels.
See?
It's got a shower
and a fold-out bed,
and it gets 14
miles to the gallon,
and there's a stove.
- How can you afford that?
- I can't.
But I also can't
afford to have my son
be kicked out of his school.
Oh. You want me out that bad.
I never wanted you in.
Well, uh...
Yeah, if we're being honest...
Please.
I kind of just assumed
he was a little dick.
My son?
You know, he goes to
some fancy-ass school.
He has a bathroom.
But now that I've hung with him,
he's, like, a regular dude.
Thanks, I think.
Yeah, that school
could probably use
someone dope like him.
That's why I gotta
do whatever it takes.
You know what, just, uh
yeah, you can forget
about the home on wheels.
What are you gonna want instead?
Oh, just keep him in lacrosse.
You know, don't let him
become some theater kid.
Where are you gonna live?
With Murphy.
I thought he was too private.
I snagged him a refrigerator box
from Best Boy, so he owes me.
Gotcha.
Uh...
Can I put on Maddow
while I pack?
Sure.
It's real, people...
The stain-fighting
power of OxiClean.
It's how I did the towels.
Looks like the
stain is coming out.
When the OxiClean started to...
Corporate has given us an extra
3% margin on all of these.
- Mm, cha-ching.
- Yep.
So let's get them out there
as fast as possible, huh?
Rosehips!
Pair it with the
Restorative Night Cream.
- Great add-on.
- Yeah, but do we
use it before or
after the Face Wash?
- I don't know, Cory.
- You're gonna wash off
$90 face cream right
after you put it on?
I robbed a greeting card store.
What's that, Dean?
I stole a printing press.
Is that how you
got the bracelet?
That's
because my wife was
laundering a gang's money
through my business.
Yeah, but what'd you
need the press for?
She uses it to make counterfeit.
What happened to her?
Not a damn thing.
And you're the one
in the bracelet.
I owed her.
That's a big-time debt.
I messed up big time.
Girl at work?
More than just one of them.
- Still going on?
- God, no, it was forever ago.
What's manslaughter get you, Z?
Good behavior?
A few years, tops.
- I didn't murder anyone.
- Exactly.
You just put your
penis in some strange.
- Human nature, bro.
- People make mistakes.
She doesn't feel that way.
Then you gotta let it go.
I don't know that I can.
Johnny, give me the key.
- Whoo! All right.
Come on. Come with me.
Gotta get up, buddy.
Come on, buddy.
Come on.
Right over here. Right here.
Stay right here.
Come on, Dean.
Don't let her keep
you behind those bars.
Come on, buddy.
There you go. Come on.
That's right.
It's okay, it's okay.
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
You're free.
Free.
.
- Dad!
- I'm in here, bud.
I got one goal and one assist.
What? Nice!
That's amazing.
Come on, go get in the bath.
Tried to FaceTime you.
Eh, I was busy.
I can't promise you
that I won't get bored.
Or.
Think it might be fun to
hit a grocery store again.
But at least we'll have a shot.
'Cause if we stay here,
nothing's gonna change.
You can print.
I finished it.
Why?
I just let it go.
D-Man! Give me the recap.
- Braid emergency.
So you're just
gonna take my job?
- You weren't home.
- I got 'em.
Work emergency trumps
braid emergency.
All right, let me see.
- It's not bad, right?
- Eh,
I don't think Alicia Keys
will be calling you, but...
- Snoop might, though.
- Oh, so now you do LOCS?
Oh, well, you want
to give it a go?
I'm all good.
How'd it go?
A couple of speed bumps,
but pulled it off.
- Okay.
- How long is it gonna take?
Till we find somewhere
else, I guess.
All right, now, the city's
gonna put that place
up for auction soon.
- What's soon?
- I don't know.
You'll know when the
sticker's on the door.
Thanks for making that work.
Pssh. I just gave you a key.
I meant with her.
Hmm.
Well, she's your girl.
What'd she say to you?
- Everything I wanted to hear.
What? What's funny?
She said the exact
same thing to me.
Hmm.
Hey. Where is he?
- He's in the shower.
- Oh, good.
Got us all-new peanut butter,
mayo, mustard, and soy sauce.
Where is he gonna go?
To a lovely DIY duplex.
I used his move today.
What do you mean?
- Rusty gate.
- Eww.
It's this really tough check,
'cause if you do it wrong,
you get a penalty.
- Wait, hang on.
- He taught you a lacrosse move?
He was All-American.
What?
Played for Maryland.
Hey, I just need five
more minutes, and I'm out.
Oh, and hey, if you ever want
to work on more defense stuff,
just come by the dumpster
behind the Kroger.
- You still coming to the game?
- Dude, I wouldn't miss it.
Unless I can't find
someone to watch my cart.
Check. Ooh!
Benjamin, nice reflexes.
All right.
So, he's back in?
- What do you want from me?
- I caved.
What about that bucket?
He held strong.
- Dude.
- Yeah.
What's up, ladies?
Just business.
You know, you still got it.
It wasn't easy.
That maple leaf is like
four different colors.
Cool.
When do you want the rest of it?
I don't.
Why?
My guys can't clean
the Queen here.
You said all we had
to do was print it.
Yeah. And then drop it.
I assumed that you
meant in our country.
Jesus, not again.
Why can't it ever be Mexico?
When?
When I'm ready.
- Avoided it for so long.
- Don't.
But I think we all knew
this day would come.
It's like you want it to happen.
I'm just saying.
Stay in the game long enough,
something's bound to
wind up in your ass.