(GIGGLING)
Hey. You ready?
Hm?
Ah, all right.
All right.
Secret sign.
Hey. Ryan?
Very good.
Excellent, excellent.
DWIGHT:
Michael.
MICHAEL:
Today, at lunchtime,
we are going to be playing
the warehouse staff
in a friendly little game
of basketball.
My idea.
The last time I was
down there, I noticed
they'd put up
a couple of hoops.
And I play basketball
every weekend,
so I thought, pfff,
this might be kinda fun.
And so I start messin' around.
And, uh, I'm sinkin' a few.
You know?
Swish, swish, swish.
Nothin' but net.
And, uh, their jaws
just drop to the floor.
African-Americans. Um...
But, you know, it's really just,
uh, a good friendly game.
A reason for everybody
to get together.
Pam-Pam,
thank you ma'am!
Messages, please.
Thank you.
Michael, can I talk to you
for a second, please, privately?
Uh...
In your office?
I think I should be
on the team.
No.
(CLEARS THROAT)
And that's not me
being mean, Dwight.
That is based
on your past behavior.
Oh, please.
When I let him, uh,
come to my pick-up game.
I apologized for that.
I vouched for you.
Michael--
I vouched for you in front
of Todd Packard, Dwight.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(TOY PLAYS JINGLE)
All right,
here's what I'm gonna do.
The hand strikes
and gives a flower.
You are not going
to play basketball.
Oh.
But...
I need somebody to come in
and take over the holiday
and weekend work calendar.
I can handle that.
Good.
Excellent.
It'll be fun.
Yeah.
Because corporate, uh,
wants somebody to be here
on Saturday, and so we're gonna
have to have a couple of people
come in on the weekends.
And I know nobody's
gonna wanna do it.
And everybody's
gonna complain and bitch,
and I don't wanna have
to deal with it.
And that's why you have
an Assistant Regional Manager.
Yes, it is.
Assistant to
the Regional Manager.
Same thing.
No, it's not.
It's lower, so...
It's close.
So we need someone
to work this Saturday.
And I think
that that should be...
Jim.
God, this is so sad.
This is the smallest
amount of power
I've ever seen go
to someone's head.
Phyllis, can you
believe this?
Keep me out of it.
My fiance has plans
for us this Saturday,
so I really hope Dwight
doesn't make me work.
Maybe I should
sleep with him.
I'm kidding.
(LAUGHS) Kidding.
Totally kidding.
MICHAEL:
All right.
Managing...by walkin' around!
This is our warehouse,
or, as I like to call it,
the "whoorehouse."
But don't you call it that.
I've earned the right.
Fine.
Don't worry about that.
And here we have
Mitta Roger's neighborhood.
Come on over here.
Hey!
This is Ryan.
He's tempin' upstairs.
What's up?
And this is the foreman,
Mitta Rogers.
That's not my real name.
No.
It's Darryl.
Darryl is Mitta Rogers.
Darryl Rogers?
Darryl Philbin.
Then Regis.
Then Rege. Then Roger.
Then Mitta Rogers...
Then Mitta Rogers.
(LAUGHS)
And that is Lonny.
And this is Roy.
Roy dates Pam.
You know, the, uh,
the best-lookin' one upstairs.
RYAN:
Yeah, yeah.
You still gettin'
it regular, man?
Huh? I mean, I can tell her
it's part of the job.
Rapport.
No, n-n-no, I know that
the warranty's expired,
but isn't it supposed
to last longer than two years
if it isn't defective?
Okay, fine, three years.
JIM:
Pam gets a little down.
Her toaster oven broke.
Um, which she got
at her engagement shower,
um, for a wedding that
still has yet to be set.
And that was three years ago.
So! Um, 1:00 sharp
and we've got a game on.
We're loadin' at 1:00.
Oh, I see.
You're, uh,
you're chickenin' out.
You're bailin' on me.
No, we got a truck
goin' out at 1:15, so...
Uh-huh.
That's the busy time.
Oh, well, I'm glad that
some time is a busy time,
because whenever I'm down here,
doesn't seem too busy to me.
(GIGGLING)
(MICHAEL LAUGHING)
Ha huh. Oh.
Oh. You can dish it out,
but you can't take it.
Okay, fine.
Have it your way.
(CLUCKING LIKE CHICKEN)
All right, fine.
You know what?
Huh?
1:00.
(GASPS)
All right.
See you at 1:00.
MICHAEL:
Are we ready for the game?
Yeah.
(GROANING)
(IMITATING GROANS)
Yeah, I know, grumble, grumble.
But you would follow me
to the ends of the earth,
grumblin' all the way.
Like that, uh, dwarf
from Lord of the Rings.
Gimli.
Nerd. That is why
you're not on the team.
Just tryin'
to be helpful.
(MOCKING)
I'll help. I'm a dragon slayer.
Uh, ten-point power sword.
Voom! Voom!
That's him.
MICHAEL:
Okay, so let's put together
a starting lineup,
shall we?
Stanley, of course.
I'm sorry?
Um...
What do you play, center?
Why "of course"?
Uh...
What's that supposed
to mean?
I don't know.
I--I don't remember saying that.
Uh, I heard it.
Well, people hear
a lot of things, man.
Um...
Other starters...
Me, of course.
I heard it that time.
I'd like to play.
If it's just for fun.
I played basketball in school.
Um... Yeah, who else?
We have Jim.
We have Ryan,
the new guy.
All right, untested, willing
to prove himself right now.
A lot of passion,
A lot of heart.
But I'm getting paid
to skip lunch, right?
Yes.
Okay.
Yes, this is business.
The, uh, the business
of team building
and morale boosting.
Ah, who else?
I can help out
if you need me.
I will use your talents
come baseball season, my friend.
Or if we box.
I have a hoop
in my driveway.
No.
I have a sports bra.
No, no! Ridiculous!
Michael, look.
Hoo, hoo, hoo.
(EXHALES)
Close.
All right, uh, me,
Stan the man,
Jim, Ryan, and Dwight.
Yes!
Sorry, Phyllis.
Can I be team captain?
No, I'm team captain.
Can I be team manager?
No, I am the team manager!
You can be assistant
to the team manager.
Assistant team manager?
No.
Okay, we'll see who's working
this weekend then.
Jim, you're in charge
of the vacation schedule now.
Oh, my God.
Threat neutralized.
MICHAEL:
Off the backboard!
Ho-ho-ho-ho.
Please don't throw
garbage at me.
Oh, Pam with a zinger.
(LAUGHS)
Hey, Pam, how would you like
to be our cheerleader today?
You know?
Some, uh, pigtails.
Little, uh, halter top.
You could tie that up.
And, you know, somethin'
a little just youthful,
for a change,
just this once.
I don't think so, Michael.
Besides, I can't cheer
against my fiance.
JIM:
I'll do it.
Wear a little flouncy skirt
if you want, and...
Yeah, I bet you would.
Just try not to be
too gay on the court.
And by gay,
I mean, um...
you know, not in
the homosexual way at all.
I mean the, uh,
you know,
like the bad at sports way.
I think that goes
without saying.
PAM:
Maybe Angela would cheerlead.
MICHAEL:
Oh, yeah, right.
I'll do it.
Oh, yuck!
That's worse than you playing.
(MICHAEL SIGHS)
'Cause you know what,
we need you
as an alternate, in case
somebody gets hurt.
That's where we need you.
Blessed be those
who sit and wait.
You made it!
Suit up.
You're on the team!
All right.
Cool!
Very good.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
It's a spy
from the warehouse.
Tryin' to figure
out our plays, huh, man?
Just gettin' a tea bag.
(LAUGHS)
Ooh.
He's runnin'.
He's runnin'!
He's runnin', but he can't hide,
because you know what?
1:00, you better bring
your "A" game.
Because me and my posse guys
are gonna be in your face.
Right in your face!
Why don't we make
it more interesting?
Loser buys dinner
at Farley's.
Oh-ho, I like
the way you think.
Yeah.
You know what, I'm gonna
take that one step further.
Loser works on Saturday.
No...
That's not as much fun.
(CLUCKING)
You know what?
Oh! What?
You on.
Okay.
Cool!
You're on.
(CLUCKING)
Don't screw this up.
Classic beginner's mistake,
eating before a game. Tck!
(MICHAEL CLEARS THROAT)
Has anyone seen
the first aid kit?
How many times
have I told you?
I'm the safety officer.
Not you.
Basketball was kinda my thing
in high school.
And I'm--Yeah.
I'm looking forward to playing.
You know, I think I'm gonna
impress a few people in here.
JIM:
You comin' down?
Yeah, I'm just
forwarding the phones.
You gonna wish me luck?
Yeah, you're gonna need it.
Whoa.
Is that trash talk
from Pam?
I'm just saying,
Roy is very competitive.
Oh.
And he wants to take
the waverunners
to the lake
this Saturday, so...
Wow.
Well, I'm goin' to
the outlet mall on Saturday.
So if you wanna save
big on brand names
and Roy has to work,
which he will,
because I'm also competitive,
you should feel free
to come along.
Um, I think I'm gonna be
up at the lake.
I think I'll see
you at the mall.
Yeah.
(LAUGHS)
(DOOR OPENS)
Hey.
There he is.
Secret weapon!
(CLAPPING)
MICHAEL:
All right, you guys.
Come on.
Let's bring it in.
Here we go.
Okay.
Listen, this is just going
to be a friendly game, right?
We are all
on the same team here.
The Dunder Mifflin team.
Of course, if you
beat us, you're fired.
That's a joke.
(MICHAEL LAUGHS)
Okay!
Let's do it!
Have a good game, man.
Yeah, you too.
Should be fun.
All right, everybody,
stretch out a little bit.
Stretch it.
Full stretch.
Ryan, you want to stretch?
I stretched
before I came.
Okay, Ryan, you have Darryl.
I have Roy.
Really?
I thought
I'd take Roy.
No, actually,
I think Roy's
their best player,
not Lonny.
So Dwight,
you have
the East German gal.
Um, okay.
All right, you guys?
Okay, we'll be skins.
Oh, come on, Dwight.
What?
Shirts, on or off?
On. Just put it on.
You sure?
Yes.
Pam, you kind of have
your foot in both camps here.
Why don't you do
the jump ball, okay?
Don't listen
to him, Pam.
Trust me. Tip it my way
or you're sleeping in the car.
Stanley!
What?
You gotta be kidding me!
Here we go!
Who's on him?
Somebody get him!
That's what
I'm talking about.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah.
Over here!
Three!
Let's go to zone.
Let's go in the zone!
Defense!
TEAM:
Defense. (clapping)
MICHAEL:
Who's got him?
Who's on Roy?
Whoo!
Oh, come on!
What is wrong with me today?
Usually hit those.
Dwight, I was open.
All right, let's go.
Oh.
Okay, foul.
Charging. Charging.
That's a foul.
MICHAEL:
Okay, I'll take it.
When I am playing hoops,
all of the stress
and responsibility
of my job here
just melts away.
It's gone.
Three!
I'm in the zone.
What's with me today?
Who am I?
Am I Michael Scott?
I don't know.
I might just be
a basketball machine.
What's Dunder Mifflin?
I've never heard of it.
Filing, paperwork?
Who cares?
Possible downsizing.
Um...
Well, that's--that's probably
going to happen, actually.
Jim! Jim! Jim!
Right here!
Jim, give me the ball.
Ryan, cut.
My bad.
Here we go.
They don't want
none of that.
There you go.
Uh, uh, uh.
Where you at?
Where you at? Where you at?
Uh. Oh.
You over there?
I'm over here.
Yeah. Mm.
Here. Uh.
That is cool.
Is that like the robot?
(CHEERS)
Come here.
There's no free throws.
Can we just do one?
That's cool. That's fine.
All right, let's go.
MICHAEL:
Don't get hurt.
Back off, man!
Come on!
Hey, Dwight. Dwight.
Yeah!
In your face!
Yeah, like that counted.
Hey! Hey, you know what?
Dwight. Dwight.
Football is like
rock and roll.
It's just * buh buh boo
And basketball
is like Jazz, you know?
You're kind of
* doop be doo
It's all down beat.
It's in the pocket.
It's like * blee dee dee
bloo doo doo blah da da *
("SWEET GEORGIA BROWN")
* Do do do do do do do
* Do do do do do
Harlem Globetrotter.
(HUMMING TO HIMSELF)
* Doot doo doo doo doo doo
Your ball.
MICHAEL:
All right, time.
Time out.
Come on, sales.
Over here.
Bring it in!
Come on!
What's goin' on?
What is goin' on?
You guys are playing
like a bunch of girls.
You know what,
let me take Roy.
All right, we'll switch.
Take it up a notch.
Come on.
DWIGHT:
Shoot it. Shoot it.
(SMACK)
MICHAEL:
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Foul. Naked aggression.
Oh, that is...
You all right, Jim?
Suck it up.
He's afraid of you now.
MICHAEL:
Ouch!
Oh, how much
does it hurt?
How much
MICHAEL:
Yes!
What the hell, man?
Take it easy.
No, you take it easy.
Watch the long passes,
you guys.
Same team, Dwight.
MICHAEL:
Dwight.
Yes!
MICHAEL:
Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah!
In your face!
Hazel,
what's the score?
You're ahead.
Yeah, baby!
Here we go!
Jim. Jim.
Right here.
Ow, God!
Okay! Foul! Foul!
I'm sorry.
You all right?
God!
Oh, that hurts.
I'm sorry, I didn't--
What's your problem, man?
I didn't mean to do--
God!
Just clocking me
for no reason.
ROGER:
Take your shot, man.
No, no, no, no.
That was a flagrant
personal intentional foul.
Right there.
No, it wasn't.
Yes, it was. You know what,
I'm just being fair.
No, really, you were
bearing down on me.
No, no, no, no.
I just put my arm up--
Game over! Game over!
Game over!
MICHAEL:
That is it.
I'm sorry, you know?
I hate to do it this way,
but, you know,
that's just--
We were having
a friendly game.
It's a shame.
This is a damn shame.
But, you know,
we're like a family here
and that's just--
that won't fly.
This is a cold pack.
Here, give me that.
You have to break
the interior bag.
Thanks, Dwight.
Wait, what does that mean?
What is it, a tie?
What's going on?
Well, let's just say
whoever was ahead won.
That was you.
That was us, really?
I didn't--I didn't know.
Great. I mean, I guess
you guys working Saturday.
Your face.
No, no, no.
I'm not coming in on Saturday.
Yeah,
this isn't happening.
Uh...
Well, guys, you know...
I am the boss.
So what--what's that?
We--we coming in
on Monday, right?
Monday?
You guys believed me?
Come on.
Dawgs, you know,
you should know me
better than that.
Do you think that would've
been good for morale?
No. No. No.
Exactly. No.
I'm embarrassed
it was even that close.
No, of course,
we're coming in Saturday.
ROY:
Good game.
Word.
So I talked to this gal.
Looks good.
I haven't signed anything.
Hey, baby.
Hey.
Look at Larry Bird.
Larry legend.
Yeah, he's, uh,
he's pretty good, huh?
Let's get you into a tub.
Yeah, let's get you
in a tub.
(PAM LAUGHING)
Hey!
What a game, huh?
What a game.
What time
do we have to come in?
Come on.
Let's not be gloomy here, man.
We're all in this together.
We're a team.
You know what?
Screw corporate.
Nobody's coming in tomorrow.
You have the day off.
Like coming in an extra day
is going to prevent us
from being downsized.
Have a good weekend.
The great thing
about sports
is that it is all
about character.
And you can learn lessons
about life
even if you don't win.
But we did because
we were ahead.