Michael.
D'oh! God!
Dwight, come on!
I wanted to talk to you
about the downsizing--
There's no downsizing.
Ai'ight.
But if there were,
I'd be protected
as Assistant
Regional Manager?
Assistant to the Regional
Manager, Dwight.
Yeah, so I don't
have to worry, right?
Look, look, look--
I talked to corporate
about protecting
the sales staff,
and they said they
couldn't guarantee it
if there's
downsizing, okay?
But, there's no downsizing,
so just don't--
Bottom line--
do I need to be worried?
Mm mm mm...maybe.
MICHAEL:
It looks like there's gonna
be downsizing.
And it's part of my job,
but...blech.
I hate it.
I think the main difference
between me and Donald Trump
is that, uh, I get no pleasure
out of saying the words,
"you're fired."
[AS TRUMP]
"You're fired."
"Uh, you're fired."
He just makes people sad,
and an office
can't function that way.
No way.
"You're fired."
I think if I had
a catchphrase,
it would be,
"You're hired.
And you can work here
as long as you want."
But, that's
unrealistic, so...
DWIGHT:
It's a real shame.
Because studies have shown
that more information
gets passed through
water cooler gossip
than through
official memos.
Which puts me
at a disadvantage because...
I bring
my own water to work.
Why'd you do this?
DWIGHT:
I didn't do it.
What do you mean?
Oh, the water cooler
was brought over here
for...maintenance.
So, what do you guys hear?
What's the scuttlebutt?
Get set for Operation
Morale Improvement--
starring Michael Scott.
Now, I think I've had
a little stroke of genius,
in that I have had
my assistant Pam--
Smile, Pam.
I have had her go out
and find out whose birthday
is coming up,
so we can have a little
celebration for them.
Not bad!
Not bad at all!
All right!
And the birthday
person is...
drum roll please...
Who is it?
Whose birthday is it?
Um, actually,
we don't have any staff
birthdays coming up.
Next person
on the...calendar.
Okay, um...
that would be Meredith.
Yes! All right!
Come on down, Meredith!
But it's not until
next month.
Um...uh, okay.
Well, great.
Well, you know,
it'll be a surprise.
You still want
to have a party?
Yeah. Why not?
Sure. Go ahead.
Live a little.
C'mon, Pam.
C'mon. Shake it up.
Shake it up.
Shake it up!
Bdddrrrooop...
Uh, Spock, are there any signs
of life down there?
Well, let me check,
Captain.
[MAKES SCANNING NOISE]
[SCANNING NOISE]
No Captain,
no signs of life down here.
Just a wet blanket
named Pam.
[LAUGHS]
Bddddddrrrrooooop.
Star Trek...
Well, for decorations,
maybe we could...
it's stupid, forget it.
What?
Well, I was
just gonna say
maybe we could
have streamers,
but that's dumb,
everybody has streamers.
Never mind.
No, yeah, I think
that's a good idea.
What color
do you guys think?
Well, there's green...
uh, blue...
yellow...red...
How about green?
I think green
is kind of whoreish.
PAM:
This was tough.
I suggested
we flip a coin,
but Angela said
she doesn't like to gamble.
Of course, by saying that,
she was gambling
that I wouldn't smack her.
These are my party-planning
bee-otches.
Pulled off an amazing
'80s party last year.
Off the hook!
MICHAEL:
So I was thinking,
if you haven't already gotten
a cake, um, maybe go in
for one of those ice cream
cakes from Baskin Robbins.
They're very good.
Very delicious.
Meredith's allergic
to dairy, so...
She's not the only one
that's going
to be eating it, right?
And I think everybody
likes ice cream cake.
It's not, uh...
not just about her, so...
It is her birthday--
Mint chocolate chip!
would be good.
How about some...
mint chocolate chip?
Hey.
So, listen, I was thinking
that it might be a good idea
if you and I
formed an alliance.
'Cause of the downsizing...
I think an alliance
might be a good idea.
You know,
help each other out.
Do you want to form
an alliance...with me?
Absolutely I do.
Good, good, excellent.
Okay, now we need
to figure out
who's vulnerable
and who is protected...
There may be--
JIM:
At that moment,
I was just so happy.
I mean, everything
Dwight does annoys me.
Did you get your tickets?
To what?
The gun show.
[LAUGHS QUIETLY]
And I spend...hours
thinking of ways
to get back at him,
but only in ways
that would get me arrested.
And then here he comes
and he says,
"No, Jim, here's a way."
And there's one other thing,
and this is important:
let's keep this alliance
totally a secret.
[WHISPERS]
Yeah.
Don't tell anyone.
An alliance?
JIM:
Oh, yeah.
What does that even mean?
I think it has something
to do with Survivor,
but I'm not sure.
Um...
[LAUGHS]
I know that it involves
spying on people,
and we may build a fort
in accounting--
Jim.
Hey.
Hey. Hi, Pam.
Listen, could I talk
to you for a second
about the...
paper products?
Did you tell Pam
about the Alliance?
What? No--
Just now!
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Dwight, no.
I'm using her,
for the alliance.
JIM:
Who knows the most information
about this office?
Pam.
Right. That's good.
Good. Pursue this.
Well, I'm trying to.
Mm-hmm.
Do you see
what I'm doing?
Mm-hmm.
But listen, I'm gonna have
to talk to her a lot.
All right?
And there may be chatting
and giggling.
And you gotta just
pretend to ignore it.
Wipe it away.
Done.
All right.
Can you get her?
She's right there.
That is Meredith.
The birthday girl.
And this...
is Meredith's card.
"Happy Bird-Day."
[LAUGHS]
Um, let's see...Jim.
JIM WROTE: "Meredith,
I heard you're turning 46.
"But, come on,
you're an accountant,
just fudge the numbers."
Not bad. Pretty funny.
I don't appreciate condoning
corporate fraud, though.
Uh, here's the thing.
Whatever I write here
has to be really,
really funny.
Because people out there
are expecting it.
I've already set
the bar really high.
MICHAEL:
And they're all worried
about their jobs, you know?
It's kinda dark out there.
Can you imagine if I wrote
something like, uh,
"Oh, Meredith.
Um, Happy Birthday.
You're great.
Love, Michael."
[SCOFFS]
[GAGS]
[LAUGHS]
They seem awfully chummy,
don't you think?
Yeah.
What do you think
that's about?
Only one way
to find out.
I'm on it.
You are not going
to believe this.
What? I believe it.
Well, tensions were
high in the kitchen.
I could tell
from the body language.
Hey, that looks good.
What is that, turkey?
Italian.
Oh, Italian.
Nice. Wow.
You got the works there.
Red onion, provolone.
Yeah.
JIM:
Toby and Kevin,
they're trying
to get Angela kicked off.
Good. Let 'em.
That's fine.
It helps our cause.
Well, I don't know.
Because if Kevin's
in accounting,
Yeah...
and Toby's
in human resources,
and they're talking?
Oh...they're forming
an alliance.
I love their sandwiches.
I love their
sandwiches too.
Yeah, their bread's
really good.
Their bread
is very good.
Damn it! God!
Rrrrrrr!
[CAR ALARM]
Okay, listen.
We need to assume
that everyone in the office
is forming an alliance,
and is therefore trying
to get us kicked off.
God damn it!
Why us?
Because we're strong, Dwight.
Because we're strong.
Meredith, Meredith.
Mary...Mary had
a little lamb.
Mary...Meredith
had a little lamb.
Don't bring
that lamb to work,
or it'll poop
on the floor--
[DOOR KNOCKS]
Hey! Oscar.
C'mon in, what's up?
Uh, I'm sorry
to bother you.
Oh, not at all.
Come on in.
What's goin' on?
My nephew is involved
with, um, a charity
for cerebral palsy.
And I was wondering
if maybe
you'd like to...
you know...
What?
Uh, donate
to the charity.
Oh, God.
Of course I would.
Pshhh. Get it over here!
Get that over here.
Thank you.
You know, I'm always good
for some serious buckage.
Wow. Two dollars?
Three dollars?
People out here
do not care
about...diseases.
I'm going to give you $25.
That's...that's...
That's very generous.
Oh, my gosh.
Well, listen, Oscar.
Generosity,
and togetherness,
and community,
all convalescences
into...morale.
That's what I say, so...
[CLICKS TONGUE]
PAM:
Hey, Jim.
Can I talk to you
for a second?
Sure. What's up?
Um, I don't know.
I'm just, like,
going a little crazy.
'Cause I keep overhearing
all of these conversations
between Michael
and corporate
about, like...
staff issues.
Oh, no.
Yeah.
He's making me take notes
on these meetings,
and I'm like,
"These people
are my friends,"
Right.
but he's all like,
"This is confidential,
you can't tell anybody."
But I don't know,
I just feel like I wanna--
Just promise me
you're not gonna
say anything?
I will not...
I'm not gonna
tell anybody.
Okay.
This is between
you and me.
Yeah.
Jackpot.
JIM:
That was beautiful.
All her idea, too.
Awesome.
She's so great.
Meredith. Bad breath.
Meredith has bad breath.
[DOOR OPENING]
Hey.
You wanted to see me?
Uh, yeah.
What do you know
about Meredith?
I don't think
she'd be missed.
There's not going to be
downsizing, Dwight, okay?
I just--I need to know
a little bit more about...
my friend.
NAME: Meredith Palmer.
UH, PERSONAL INFORMATION:
divorced twice, two kids.
UH, EMPLOYER:
Dunder Mifflin Paper, Inc.
AWARDS: multiple Dundies--
I know all that.
I-I know all that.
I just--I need something
kind of embarrassing,
you know?
Kinda fun, inside...
She had a hysterectomy.
Which one is that again?
It's where they remove
the uterus.
Oh, God, Dwight, no!
I'm trying to write
something funny here, okay?
What am I gonna do
with a removed uterus?
It could be
kind of funny.
You know what?
I am on a deadline here.
And, just--okay.
Thanks,
thanks for your help.
I'll work it out.
Thank you, Dwight.
That wasn't
a waste of time.
Okay, here's the deal.
All right.
Pam says that one
of the alliances
is meeting
in the warehouse
during Meredith's
birthday party.
Oh, my God,
we have to be there.
I know.
But it's gonna be
a little tough,
because there's no good place
to hide down there.
No, no, yes there is.
Behind the shelves--
oh, my God.
What, what, what?
I know. I know.
I know exactly
what to do.
Great.
DWIGHT:
I'm a deer hunter.
I go all the time
with my dad.
One thing about deer,
they have very
good vision.
One thing about me,
I'm better at hiding
than they are...at vision.
This is gonna
be perfect, okay?
Centrally located.
Perfect cover.
I can hear
and see everything.
Good.
[DOOR KNOCKING]
Michael.
Just a sec.
Are you done yet?
Almost there.
Just a...second.
It is perfect.
Thank you. Excellent.
Here we go. It is time.
Thank you.
Okay! C'mon, let's go!
Get the cake! Here we go.
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon!
Shh! Be quiet!
Wait, this isn't gonna work.
The lid's open.
So, tape it down.
I can't do that.
Then you won't be able
to breathe.
Look, I can breathe
just fine, okay,
but if it makes you
feel better,
I'll poke holes
in the box.
Thank you.
Thank you. Okay.
[DOOR OPENING]
Surprise!
Oh! Surprise!
No, it's a--
It's surprise, Meredith!
MICHAEL:
One, two,
* Happy Birthday to you *
Find the key...
* Happy Birthday *
So, you want me
to stay here
and, you know,
stand next to the box, or--
No!
You need to go upstairs
to the party
so people don't notice
that we're both gone.
Right. That's good.
Can I trust Jim?
I don't know.
Do I have a choice?
No. Frankly, I don't.
Will I trust Jim? Yes.
Should I trust Jim?
You tell me.
* Happy Birthday,
dear Meredith *
* Happy Birthday to you
* And many more *
You were surprised,
weren't you?
Yes.
You looked freaked, man.
We said, "Surprise,"
and you were, like, "What?
What the hell's
goin' on here?"
Good cake.
Why don't you have some?
I...I can't, um.
C'mon. A little bit.
A little bit.
No, no, I can't eat dairy.
Oh, right. Oh, God.
Too bad, it's so good.
Yeah, it makes me sick.
You know what?
If I were
allergic to dairy,
I think I'd kill myself.
'Cause this is way,
way too good.
PAM:
He's in a box?
JIM:
Pam, he's in a box.
He's downstairs
in a box
on the floor
near the shelves.
[LAUGHS]
I'm serious.
Go down there.
And work your magic...
PAM:
Hey, where are you?
Yeah, we were supposed
to meet here.
What?
Oh, my gosh!
That ties in perfectly
with something that Michael
was telling me earlier.
I just don't know
what some of the people in,
like, accounting,
are gonna do.
It said specifically that...
Oof...
Oh...
Hey, Jim.
Good party, huh?
Just a little something
I...whipped up, you know,
a little morale boost.
Yeah?
No big deal.
Speaking of which,
I meant to tell you.
Very impressive.
The, uh, donation you gave
to Oscar's charity.
Oh.
What was that, 25 bucks?
Yeah, well, you know,
money isn't everything, Jim.
It's not the key
to happiness.
You know what is?
Joy.
You should remember that.
Maybe you'd give
more than $3.00 next time.
Yeah, well, $3.00 a mile
is going to end up
being, like, 50 bucks.
So...
God, I can't even calculate
what you're gonna
have to give.
Is Oscar around?
I just thought
it was a,
kind of a flat,
you know, $25
one-time donation.
I didn't think it was
a per-mile kinda deal,
you know, so...
Well...that's what
a walk-a-thon is.
I know--
It says it right
on the sheet.
Look, look at the sheet.
It says it's however
many dollars per mile.
Right. Got it.
Yes. So, it does.
Um...
I just think
it's kind of cheap
to "undonate" money
to a charity.
No.
No, no, no, no, no.
I-I wasn't--that wasn't
what I was...no.
I-I-It's not about
the money.
It's just...
it's the ethics
of the thing, Oscar.
How's your nephew?
Is he in good shape?
Yeah.
How many miles
did he do last year?
Last year,
he walked 18 miles.
Son of a bitch.
That is impressive!
Good for him.
Happy birthday,
Meredith.
MICHAEL:
Read it out loud.
And say who
wrote everything,
so we know
whose is the best.
"Happy Bird-Day."
"MEREDITH, GOOD NEWS:
you're not actually
a year older,
because you work here,
where time stands still."
[LAUGHTER]
I don't know about that--
MEREDITH:
That was Stanley.
"Meredith,
Happy Birthday.
You're the best,
Love, Pam."
ALL:
Aw.
Blech!
Thanks, downer.
[SCOFFS]
MEREDITH:
This is from Michael.
"MEREDITH: Let's hope
the only downsizing
that happens to you
is that someone
downsizes your age."
MICHAEL:
Because of the downsizing.
Rumors.
And because
you're gettin' old.
No, I get it--
it's funny.
You didn't get the joke.
So...that's cool.
That's--you know what?
Actually, I have
a bunch of these...
good ones
that I didn't use.
Um...oh, where's that, uh--
oh, okay,
here's a good one.
Um, "Hey, Meredith,
Liz Taylor called.
She wants her age back
and her divorces back."
'Cause Meredith's
been divorced,
like, twice?
Is that right?
Uh, you're right.
MICHAEL:
Did I get that right?
Okay.
Right. Yes.
Divorce...
um...oh, okay.
"Meredith is so old."
How old is she?
Well, if everybody...
could do it.
"Meredith is so old..."
(EVERYBODY)
How old is she?
"She's so old,
"she went into
an antique store
and they kept her."
MICHAEL:
Well, that wasn't even mine.
I got that off
the internet...website...
so, don't
get mad at me...
Uh...
Nice party, Michael.
This isn't my fault.
Um, ladies,
not your best effort.
The streamers?
I think we could have
done better than that,
don't you think?
Phyllis wanted red.
I didn't.
Oh, boy, you...
Okay, wait--
all right, people,
hold on, hold on,
hold on just a second, okay?
I think we're losing sight
of what is really
important here.
And, that is
that we are a group of people
who work together.
I was--I really wasn't
gonna flaunt this.
I have made
a very sizeable donation
to Oscar's nephew's...
Walk-A-Thon.
$25.
Per mile.
Per mile, yes.
When I retire,
I-I-I don't want to just
disappear
to an island somewhere.
I want to be the guy
who gives everything back.
A check for the kids.
And for the team.
MICHAEL:
I want it to be like,
"Hey, who donated
that hospital wing...
that is saving
so many lives?"
"Uh, well, I don't-
I don't know.
It was anonymous."
"Well, guess what?
That was Michael Scott."
"But, ah...
it was anonymous,
how do you know?"
"Because I'm him."
Thank you, Michael.
MICHAEL:
Come here.
Don't cash that
until Friday, okay?
Really? Today?
Yeah.
Oh. Happy Birthday.
Thanks.
I could say something--
Don't do that.
Okay.
Okay, okay--
I have something
that totally
tops the box!
Oh, tell me!
Tell me!
Okay.
I have just
convinced Dwight
that he needs
to go to Stamford,
and spy on
our other branch.
No, no, no.
JIM:
But before he does so,
I told him that he should
dye his hair
to go undercover.
[LAUGHTER]
If we can get him
to drive to Connecticut
and put peroxide
in his hair--
[DOOR SLAMS]
What the hell is this?
What, are you trying
to cop a feel
or somethin', Halpert?
No, dude, no--
Dude, no, I was just--
listen--whoa--
God, I don't even--
I don't even know
how to explain this.
Um, uh...
Dwight asked me
to be in an alliance.
[LAUGHS]
And, then, um,
um, we were--
we've just been
messing with him,
uh, because of the whole
alliance thing.
Um...
It's just office pranks.
It's stupid.
An alliance?
What the hell's
he talking about?
I have absolutely no idea.
C'mon.
DWIGHT:
Do I feel bad
about betraying Jim?
Not. At. All.
That's the game.
Convince him we're
in an alliance,
get some information,
throw him to the wolves.
That's politics, baby.
Get what you can
out of someone,
then crush them.
I think Jim
might have learned
a very valuable lesson.