(THEME MUSIC)
Pam!
Pamela, Pame-lama ding-dong.
Making copies.
(PHONE RINGING)
I'm not making any copies.
Let's go!
Messages, stat!
Lots to do, lots to do.
Information superhighway.
-Nothing new.
-Lay them on moi.
What?
-There's nothing new.
That's not what
you said earlier.
Oh, do you want me to
repeat the messages that
I gave you before for the--
The most sacred thing
I do is care and provide
for my workers-- my family.
I give them money.
I give them food.
(PHONE RINGING)
Not directly but through
the money-- I heal them.
Today, I am in charge--
(TAPS BOOKS)
--of picking a great new
health care plan, right?
(TAPS BOOK)
That's what this is all about.
Does that make me their doctor?
Yes, in a way.
Yeah, like a specialist.
(ADDING MACHINE SOUNDS)
So which health plan
have you decided on?
I am going to go
with the best, Jan.
I am going to go with the
one with the acupuncture,
therapeutic massage--
you know, the works.
JAN: Wait, acupuncture?
-Mm-hmm.
None of the plans
have acupuncture.
Have you looked at
them closely, Michael?
Oh, I think it was you
who didn't look closely
enough at the gold plan.
The gold plan?
MICHAEL: Yeah.
I'm not even on that plan.
Well, I'd recommend it.
JAN: Michael--
It's very good.
You gotta crack
these things open.
JAN: You know, the
whole reason that we're
doing this is to save money.
So you just need
to pick a provider
and then choose
the cheapest plan.
Well, that is a-- kind
of a tough assignment.
Um-- it's not gonna be
a popular decision--
JAN: It's your job.
- --around the old orifice.
JAN: So.
I-- well, it's a
suicide mission.
You know?
(LAUGHS)
JAN: Michael--
I-- I don't--
JAN: Maybe, I mean--
They're-- They're--
JAN: You know,
sometimes a manager,
like yourself, has to deliver
the bad news to the employees.
I do it all the time.
Oh, yeah.
When have you ever done that?
I'm doing it right now to you.
(SIGHS)
Last night on
"Trading Spouses"--
(PHONE RINGING)
--there's-- have you seen it?
PAM: No, I have a life.
-Interesting.
What's that like?
PAM: You should try it sometime.
Wow.
But then who would watch my TV?
(LAUGHS)
- JIM: Sort of like a (INAUDIBLE).
- MICHAEL: Jimbo.
PAM: --your problem.
(AWKWARD LAUGH)
There's a decision
that needs to be made,
and I'm having an
unbelievably busy day so I'm
going to let you pick a health
care plan for our office
and then explain it
to your coworkers.
Gosh.
MICHAEL: Yeah.
That is a great offer.
Thank you.
I really think I should
be concentrating on sales.
Really.
JIM: Yeah.
I just don't think that
this is the kind of task
that I-- I'm going to do.
You know who would
be great for this?
Any time Michael asks
me to do anything,
I just tell him that
Dwight should do it.
Yes.
I can do it.
I'm your man.
Right now, this is just a job.
If I advance any higher
in this company then
this would be my career.
(LAUGHS)
And, uh, well, if
this were my career,
I'd have to throw myself
in front of a train.
OK.
First, let's go over
some parameters.
How many people can I fire?
Uh, none.
You're picking a
health care plan.
OK.
We'll table that
for the time being.
Two, I'm gonna need an office.
I think the conference
room should be fine.
You can use the conference
room as a temporary workspace.
Yes!
I have an office--
(QUIETLY) bigger than his.
Nope.
You cannot use it.
OK.
I take it back--
it's a workspace.
--temporary workspace.
You can use it.
Thank you.
If Dwight fails then
that is strike two
and good for me for, uh,
giving him a second chance.
And if he succeeds,
then, you know,
no one will be
prouder than I am.
I groomed him.
I made him what he is
today-- unless he fails
and, uh-- talked
about that already.
(PHONES RINGING)
DWIGHT: What did I do?
I did my job.
I slashed benefits to the bone.
I saved this company money.
Was I too harsh?
Maybe.
I don't believe in
coddling people.
In the wild, there
is no health care.
In the wild, health care
is, ow, I hurt my leg.
I can't run.
A lion eats me and I'm dead.
Wow.
I'm not dead.
I'm the lion.
You're dead.
(COPY MACHINE RUNNING)
STANLEY: There's no
dental, there's no vision.
There's a $1,200 deductible.
(PHONE RINGING)
Dunder Mifflin, this is Pam.
MICHAEL (ON PHONE):
Pam, Michael Scott.
How's tricks?
Where are you?
(SIGHS)
MICHAEL (ON PHONE):
I am in my office.
I am swamped.
I have work up to my ears.
I'm busy, busy, busy,
busy-- can't step away.
I just wanted to check in and
see how everybody's doing.
Everybody cool out there?
PAM: Um, actually, people
are really unhappy.
Um, Dwight sent around
this memo and people
are freaking out because the--
MICHAEL (ON PHONE):
Pam, you know--
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa--
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I--
I-- I gotta go.
I'm getting a call.
No, you're not.
I have to make a call
after I finish-- my work.
You know what?
Um, just don't let anybody in
my office under any conditions
today.
I'm just too busy--
too swamped, you know?
I am unreachable.
- I am incommunicado, capisce?
- PAM (ON PHONE): OK.
Thank you.
Oh, god.
Here we go again.
Gotta go.
I have to take this.
PAM (ON PHONE):
Still no one calling.
PAM: Dwight, what is this--
DWIGHT: Uh, knock please.
Please, knock.
This is an office.
It says workspace.
Same thing.
If it's the same thing, then
why'd you write workspace?
Just knock, please?
OK-- as a sign of a
respect for your superior?
You are not my superior.
Oh, gee, then why
do I have an office?
Thought it was a
workspace, Dwight.
OK.
Dwight, are you really
in charge of picking
the health care plan?
Yes, and my decision is final.
This is a
ridiculously awful plan
because you cut everything.
DWIGHT: (SARCASTICALLY)
Oh, times are tough, Pam.
Deal with it--
You cut more than you
had to, didn't you?
DWIGHT: Sure.
-Well, why did you do that?
You work here, don't
you want good insurance?
Don't need it.
Never been sick--
perfect immune system.
OK.
Well, if you've
never been sick then
you don't have any antibodies.
I don't need them--
superior genes.
I'm a Schrute-- and
superior brain power.
Through concentration,
I can raise and lower
my cholesterol at will.
Why would you wanna
raise your cholesterol?
So I can lower it.
(PHONE RINGING)
OSCAR: He literally won't
come out of his office.
He's gotta come out sometime--
to got to the bathroom.
ANGELA: Kevin,
that's inappropriate.
(WATER RUNNING)
Michael, can I talk to you?
Uh, uh, I would love
to but I am really busy.
Rain check?
OSCAR: Well--
MEREDITH: Uh, Michael?
Michael, please, can we
talk to you about this memo?
MICHAEL: Uh, what--
which a-- which memo?
Dwight's health care memo.
I told you about it.
-It a good plan?
It's a great plan-- saves
the company a fortune.
OSCAR: It's like a pay decrease.
Michael, he made huge cuts.
Cuts-- what-- wow,
Dwight, did you make cuts?
Yeah, you said to
go ahead and trim--
No, no no, no no,
no, you know what?
I said nothing specific
because I was so busy.
Why don't you go
in there, Dwight,
and find these people a plan
that'll work for them, OK?
DWIGHT: I can handle it.
MICHAEL: OK?
All right.
We feel good?
Good.
Plus, there's some
other good news.
Today, at the end of the
day, I will have, for all
of you, a big surprise, OK?
So hang in there and I will
see you at the end of the day,
all right?
OSCAR: This is not good.
It's ridiculous.
Did you talk to him?
What was that?
--You let him walk all over you.
It's just pathetic.
KEVIN: What are you
guys talking about?
ANGELA: Nothing, Kevin.
Do I know what the surprise is?
Hell, no.
It doesn't matter.
The point is, they're
not unhappy anymore.
They're out there thinking, wow,
my boss really cares about me.
He has a surprise.
He's cool.
Why-- what a great guy.
I love him.
OK, everyone.
Gather round.
Step forward.
It has been brought to my
attention that some of you
are unhappy with my plan.
So what I'd like you to do is
to fill this out and write down
any diseases you have that
you might want covered,
and I'll see what I can do.
OK.
You know what, Dwight?
We can't write our
diseases down for you
because that's confidential.
-OK.
Well, I didn't say to write
your name down, did I?
Fill it out, leave
it anonymous or don't
write any disease down at
all, and it won't be covered.
Sound fair?
Good.
All right, I'll be in my office.
JIM: Workspace.
You know what, come with me.
We are going on a little
mission-- operation surprise.
(PHONE RINGING)
PAM: Where are you going?
Um, headed out-- part of my
busy day, you know-- meetings.
(LAUGHS)
Couldn't find the knob.
So basically, I
want to do something
nice for my employees.
Atlantic City, OK?
They have this thing where they
send a bus, right-- for free.
It picks everybody up.
You head down there, get to
the hotel, room is comped,
and they give you a
big pile of chips,
and your food-- everything
just kind of all inclusive,
free, kind of, weekend.
I don't know of
anything like that.
But, um, you know
what you might want
to do is just call those
casinos directly, uh, maybe?
MICHAEL: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, I did so--
(PHONE RINGING)
Wait, what are you writing?
Don't write Ebola or mad
cow disease, all right?
'Cause I'm suffering
from both of them.
(LAUGHS)
I'm inventing new diseases.
Oh, great.
So, like, let's say that
my teeth turned to liquid
and then they drip down
the back of my throat.
What would you call that?
I thought you said you
were inventing diseases?
That's spontaneous
dento hydropolosion.
Nice.
JIM: Thank you.
MICHAEL: Callin' to ask you a
little favoroonie, my friend.
Um, trying to give
the troops around here
a little bit of a boost,
and I was thinking
that maybe we could
take 'em down to take
a spin on your big ride.
MALE (ON PHONE): You mean
the elevator that takes
you down into the mine shaft?
It's not really a ride.
It says here that
it's a 300 foot drop.
MALE (ON PHONE): Well, it
goes 300 feet into the earth
but it moves really slowly.
So it's not a free fall.
MALE (ON PHONE): It's an
industrial coal elevator.
MICHAEL: Uh, all right.
Well, once you get down
into the mine, what do you--
you got laser tag or something?
OK.
So I don't know what
the surprise is.
Am I worried?
No.
No way.
And see, I thrive on this.
This is my world.
This is improv.
This is "Whose
Line Is It Anyway."
(ANGRY GRUNTS)
(ANGRY) Jim!
All right, who did this?
I'm not mad.
I just want to know who did
it so I can punish them.
What are you talking about?
Uh, Someone-- uh-- forged
medical information and that
is a felony.
-OK.
Whoa.
All right-- 'cause that's a
pretty intense accusation.
How do you know
that they're fake?
Uh, leprosy, flesh eating
bacteria, hot dog fingers--
(LAUGHTER)
--government created killer,
nano-robot infection.
(LAUGHTER)
You did this, didn't you?
-Absolutely not.
DWIGHT: Yes you did.
-No, I didn't.
I know it was you.
OK, fine.
You know what?
I'm going to have to interview
each and every one of you
until the perpetrator
makes him or herself known.
And until that time,
there will be no health
care coverage for anyone!
Killer, nano-robots?
It's an epidemic.
(ADDING MACHINE SOUNDS)
The problem, Jim--
JIM: Mm-hmm.
--is that people who are
really suffering from a medical
condition won't receive
the care they need
because someone in this
office is coming up
with all this ridiculous stuff.
Count Choculitus?
(WHISTLES)
Sounds tough.
Why did you write
that down, Jim?
Is it because you know
I love Count Chocula?
Do you?
I think you need to confess--
JIM: Mm-hmm.
--the fact--
JIM: Yep.
DWIGHT: --that--
What are you doing?
- (KEYS RATTLING)
- JIM: What?
Those are my keys.
JIM: Good luck.
DWIGHT: Jim!
Damnit!
No!
Jim, let me out!
Jim, let--
(KEYS LAND LOUDLY)
The light green--
the green and the--
(PHONE RINGING)
Jim Halpert.
DWIGHT (ON PHONE): Let me out.
Who is this?
DWIGHT (ON PHONE): Let
me out or you're fired.
No, you can't fire me.
DWIGHT (ON PHONE): Yes, I can.
I'm manager for the day.
-Mm-hmm.
DWIGHT (ON PHONE):
Clean out your desk.
(PHONE RINGING)
-OK.
Can you hold on one second?
I'm getting the, uh, beep.
- Jim Halpert.
- PAM (ON PHONE): Hey, Jim.
It's Pam.
-Hey, Pam.
How are ya?
DWIGHT (IN LOCKED OFFICE):
Jim, open the door!
PAM (ON PHONE):
Good, how are you?
You busy?
-I'm doin' OK.
Gettin' excited for
the weekend though.
PAM (ON PHONE): Yeah.
-Yeah, what are you up to?
DWIGHT (IN LOCKED OFFICE): Jim!
PAM (ON PHONE): Um, I'm
not bothering you, am I?
No, not at all.
(BANGING ON WINDOW)
PAM (ON PHONE): You don't
have anything you're doing?
- I have nothing to do.
- PAM (ON PHONE): Oh, great.
DWIGHT (IN LOCKED OFFICE): Jim!
PAM (ON PHONE): Um, yeah,
no, this weekend-- nothing.
I'm not really doing anything.
JIM: Oh, yeah?
-Jim!
PAM (ON PHONE): I
might go to the mall.
- The mall?
- DWIGHT (IN LOCKED OFFICE): Jim!
PAM (ON PHONE):
I need new shoes.
(BANGING ON WINDOW)
Oh, interesting.
What kind of shoes?
(PHONE RINGING)
JAN (ON PHONE): Hello?
Hello, uh, this
is Dwight Schrute
calling for Jan Levinson-Gould.
JAN (ON PHONE): This is Jan.
Hi, Dwight Schrute
calling-- acting
manager, Scranton branch.
Listen, I needed your
permission to fire Jim Halpert.
JAN (ON PHONE): Who is this?
Dwight Schrute.
JAN (ON PHONE): From sales?
-Well--
JAN (ON PHONE):
Where's Michael Scott?
Uh, he is not here right now.
He put me in charge
of the office.
(PHONE RINGING)
JAN (ON PHONE): Dwight,
listen to me very carefully.
You are not a manager
of anything, understand?
That's not entirely
true because he
put me in charge of picking
the health care plan.
JAN (ON PHONE):
(SHOCKED) Really?
- DWIGHT: Yeah.
- JAN (ON PHONE): OK.
When Michael gets back, you
tell him to call me immediately.
Call you immediately, good.
JAN (ON PHONE): Yes.
Oh, hey, listen, um, since
I have you on the phone, um,
can I fire Jim?
JAN (ON PHONE): No.
And please, don't use
my cellphone ever again.
Oh, this is your ce-- I
thought this was your--
(DIAL TONE)
(OFFICE CHATTER)
(DOOR OPENING)
MICHAEL: Hey, hey, everybody!
Ice cream Sandwiches-- aaahhh!
(LAUGHS)
Here you go-- take
one, take one.
It's all good.
Phyllis, think fast.
Ya-boom!
Oh, oh, I see Angela, right?
Angela, aaahhh!
(LAUGHS)
Hey, Tim, why don't you take
two because you don't get health
care and uh, faster metabolism.
Did you get the kind with
the cookies instead of the--
Why don't you just eat it, OK?
And here you go,
Stanley the manley.
STANLEY: Ah, thanks.
-There you go.
STANLEY: This isn't the
big surprise, is it?
Because we've been having
a pretty horrible day.
Uh, nope.
Nope.
This isn't the surprise.
It's surprising because you
didn't expect it but you will--
you'll know it when you see it.
(THUD)
(BANGING ON WINDOW)
DWIGHT (IN LOCKED
OFFICE): Michael!
Michael!
Oh, for Christ's sake.
I tried being rational, OK?
And what happened?
The employees went crazy.
I got no help from corporate so
that leaves me with no options.
I'm now going to read aloud your
submitted medical conditions.
When you hear yours read,
please raise your hand
to indicate that it is real.
If you do not raise your
hand, it will not be covered.
What about confidentiality?
DWIGHT: You know what?
You have forfeited
that privilege.
I have tried to treat
you all as adults
but, obviously, I am
the only adult here.
Number one, inverted penis.
Could you mean vagina?
Because if you do,
I want that covered.
I thought your
vagina was removed
during your hysterectomy?
A uterus is different
from a vagina.
I still have a vagina.
MICHAEL: Ugh.
(SIGHS)
-OK.
Great.
Dermatitis.
Thank you, Angela.
I'll make sure that's covered.
OK, now, who wrote this--
this hysterical one?
Anal fissures?
That's a real thing.
DWIGHT: Yeah, but
no one here has it.
Someone has it.
STANLEY: Do you
think we should go?
OSCAR: I don't know but I
mean-- if this is important I
don't want-- there he is.
STANLEY: What is he doing?
OSCAR: I don't know.
- (SIGHS)
- OSCAR: Well-- well?
Well, what?
You could be
referring to anything.
OSCAR: OK-- the
health care plan.
Why did you put Dwight
in charge of that?
He did a horrible job.
Uh, Dwight?
Did you raise benefits?
-I most certainly did not.
-Oh, come on!
That's horrible!
Duh!
Thanks, Dwight,
for a crappy plan.
(DISINGENUOUS) Ugh, damn!
Oh, mm, I wish I had
time to change it but--
(SIGHS)
--Jan needs it by five
and-- what time is it?
What time is it? (RELIEVED)
Oh, it's after five.
Uh, ugh.
(DISINGENUOUS) It's awful!
So, well, OK.
See you guys on Monday.
What about the surprise?
Oh, yes.
Exactly-- thank you,
Angela, for reminding me.
Terrific.
Um, before I tell everybody
what the big surprise is,
would you like to tell me what
you think the big surprise is?
STANLEY: We all think you
don't have a surprise.
MICHAEL: All right, I
have some news for ya.
There is a big surprise.
And here it is!
Here we go!
And the big surprise
is-- brrrrrrrrr,
drum roll, brrrrrrrr.
(SIGHS)
(BREATHES NERVOUSLY)
When I am backed into a corner
that is when I come alive.
See I learned improv
from the greats
like, um, Drew Carey
and Ryan Stiles.
Ah, this--
(SIGHS)
Robin Williams.
Oh, man, would I love to
go head-to-head with him.
Oh!
That would be exciting.
(IMITATING ROBIN WILLIAMS)
I'm Mork from Ork.
Well, I'm-- I'm Bork from Smork.
Nanoo, nanoo.
Jibilee, Balubalu.
(DOOR CLOSING)
Oh, uh, Jan wants
you to call her.
(TRUMPET SOUNDS)
(NBC JINGLE)