Hey. Ready?
Come on! Show me excited.
Yes!
Yeah. I'm pretty excited too.
Today I'm headed
over to the job fair
at valley view high school
to find some new interns.
Wanna get some fresh blood,
uh, euthanize this place.
Hey, we doin' this thing? Yeah.
Oh, my god, Darryl.
You look like Barack Obama.
Everybody, I'm
dating Barack Obama.
Why are you dressed like that?
Like what?
Like you're applying for a loan.
Maybe he's going to church.
Or court.
Figured I'd look presentable.
You...went a different way.
I think you look nice.
Thank you. Thank you.
Okay. Here's what
we're going to do.
I'm going to instruct the kids
about management and sales.
Oscar will be in
charge of accounting.
Pam will be eye candy.
No, and also because
that is your Alma mater.
Darryl will hire some
kids for the warehouse.
We don't have to worry
about internships with them
because they definitely
ain't goin' to college.
What college did
you go to, Mike?
Let's go!
*
Today I am meeting
a potential client
on the golf course
because Ryan put
me on probation.
You remember Ryan.
He was the temp here.
Yeah. And, uh...
It is not a good time
for me to lose my job
since I have some pretty
big long-term plans
in my personal life with Pam
that I'd like her parents
to be psyched about.
So I am about to do something
very bold at this job
that I've never done before--
try.
Whoa!
Mr. Maguire.
It's been a couple of years.
Hey, Jim, how are ya?
Nice to see you, man.
Oh, no!
No, no, no, no, no.
My grandfather would
be spinning in his urn
if he knew that I was out
here with a dartmouth boy.
You take that shirt
off right now,
or I will take it
off for you, sir.
I am totally
and completely kidding!
Andy Bernard.
Cornell. '95.
Phil Maguire, dartmouth, '74.
Oop. Got some blisties.
Yeah, you do.
Hit about 1,200 balls last night
in preparation for today, so
hands are a little tender.
It's actually not funny at all.
It's incredibly painful.
Let's make it interesting.
Say, uh...10 bucks a hole.
Great.
What are we talkin'? Skins?
Acey deucy? Bingo bango bongo?
Sandies, barkies, arnies?
Wolf? What?
I'm gonna take
this petty cash that
I got from Oscar
and turn it into
next month's rent.
So many memories
in this old gym.
Pretending I have pms
so I didn't have
to play volleyball.
Pretending I have pms
so I didn't have
to play basketball.
Those were the days.
Little over the top,
don't you think?
Show 'em what you brought, Mike.
Um...
That's all we brought.
This is all we need. We'll see.
Yes, we will see, Oscar.
We will see,
because a blank sheet of paper
equals endless possibilities.
Conceptual. All right.
We are...
Open for business.
Hello.
Andy, you're up. Let's go.
Giddy-up. Let's do this.
People assume I'm great at golf,
but like everybody,
I hated golf lessons
when I was a kid.
So I used to just hang out
with the sailing club instead.
Got my knot on.
Damn it!
Guys, do we have
to stay all day?
I mean, Michael's gone.
Can't we just go?
Yeah. And I finished
my work months ago.
Excuse me, people.
It has come to my attention
that some of you have forgotten
who is in charge here.
When Michael is gone,
Jim is in charge.
When Jim is gone, Andy
and I are in charge.
When Andy is gone, you
answer to me, okay?
Excuse me, where do
you think you're going?
Oh, no, no, no.
You're not leaving.
No! Stanley.
Do not walk out that door!
If you walk out that
door, so help me,
I will--
he left.
Last time I checked,
the American workday
ends at 5:00 P.M.
You will all stay at your desks
until that time
or you will suffer
the consequences.
What consequences?
I will tell on you.
There's some filing,
restocking the supply shelves,
replacing the water jug,
which nobody likes to do.
Um...
We, uh,
eat a lot of cake.
Cool.
Yeah, and, uh, you know,
you basically, you learn
how an office runs.
Hello. So...
Hi. Can I talk to you for a sec?
Excuse me. This is
Michael, my boss.
Yeah. Justin.
Hey, remember what
we talked about
in the car on the way out?
"Only the best and
the brightest"?
He's nice, and he
seems interested.
He's totally wrong, Pam.
Hey...
Hi. How you doin'?
Listen, I don't think
that a handsome, funny, smart,
funny-looking kid like you
should limit himself.
You could do whatever
you wanna do.
You could be a classy janitor
or a cashier with
dignity or a...
Migraine worker.
Maybe for you, paper
should be more of a hobby.
Sorry for wasting your time.
Oh, no problem.
And he signed!
He put his name
on the piece of--
okay, that...
Was supposed to
be a blank canvas
on which to put their
hopes and dreams,
and he just...
Made it into a stupid
piece of paper.
We need another one immediately.
Yeah. The booth is
lame without it.
I only brought the one.
Are you mental?
Michael, do you remember
you specifically told me
to only bring one
sheet of paper?
You said it only takes one
sheet to make a difference.
And I said, "are
you sure, Michael?"
And you said, "Pam, Pam, Pam."
And then you sneezed in my tea.
And then you said, "don't worry.
It's just allergies."
Do you remember that?
I...don't.
Okay. I'll go look
for another one.
And that...Is why
I need a smart intern.
Hey, so, uh, how's the
direct mail business going?
I can't complain. People
love their junk mail.
Now, are you gettin' all
your paper from ppc, or...
You know what, Jim?
I'm not really looking to
change things up right now.
I just came out here to get
out of the office a little bit,
so why don't we just play, okay?
Absolutely. Will do.
So I guess I'll just
work on my short game.
Hello, there.
What is this company?
Well, it's funny
that you should ask,
because it's really...
More than a company.
Dunder Mifflin. Paper.
Thanks.
It--okay.
Damn it, Oscar!
Yeah, I'm trying to lure
these kids into my booth.
But, uh, kids are very wary
of being lured these days.
Thank you, dateline.
Thank you.
Extension 128.
Hiya, pumpkin. It's creed.
Say we're gonna ditch
this bitch--you in?
No. You out?
Pumpkin's out! Let's go, gang.
My old art room.
Oh! Maybe it's still here.
No. No, they must
have taken it down.
Never mind.
What do you want?
Michael, I know you're swamped.
I just thought you should know
that everyone in
the office has left
except for Angela and I.
Do not worry, though.
I have taken down their names,
and I have docked
them a personal day.
Who cares? I'm not
there, Jim's not there.
Why should they
have to be there?
So...what else is up?
Mich--
Thank you!
Whoa--what is this?
Piece of paper.
This isn't dunder Mifflin paper.
It's some sort of
Pendleton crap.
Well, I think they'll
get the spirit of it.
Pam, Pam, Pam, Pam, Pam, Pam!
We're dying here.
I want you to go
back to the office,
and I want you to
get the real stuff.
I want you to get
ultra white card stock.
Are you serious?
Yes. And don't call me Shirley.
Okay.
Oh!
Ah, damn it!
You know, you could
just pick it up,
take the triple bogey.
Yeah, i-- I'll get it out.
Thank you.
Yep.
Ah!
Come on, tuna!
Hey. Can't really talk now.
What's up?
Just checkin' in.
How's it going?
Uh...you know.
We'll see. We'll see.
I just drove 20 miles round
trip back to the office
to get Michael a single
sheet of white paper.
So...i could have just had
them fax it to me, I guess.
Oh, I like you.
Talk to you later?
Yeah. All right. Bye.
All right.
I'm sorry, I got to
annoy you one more time.
What if I bring
down shipping costs?
You can try.
But I've looked at your prices.
Even with free shipping...
Doesn't work.
It's just--it's not
in the stars, Jim.
Six.
Yeah.
All right, race
to the next hole!
Ooh. Winner gets ten bucks.
Wait--wait for me! Andy!
Shortcut! Shortcut!
Oh!
I fell in the sand trap.
All of these jobs suck.
I would rather live jobless
on a beach somewhere
off the money from
a large inheritance
than to have to work in
any one of these crapholes.
They suck.
Hey.
Game over.
Justin time.
Hi.
Justin case.
What's your last name?
Polznik.
"This...just in:
Justin polznik."
Huh?
Justin is the ugly
girl in the movie
who takes off her
glasses, and she's hot.
And you realize that
she was always hot,
she was just wearing glasses,
and that you were the blind one.
He's the most...
Important thing in
my life right now.
I want you... To meet my family.
Come on.
Oscar Martinez,
accountant extraordinaire.
This is Justin.
Hey. Hi.
This is Darryl philbin.
Isn't he big?
And you already met her,
Pam beesly, office hottie.
She will do you.
No. No.
But she has already dated
two guys in the office
that we know of, so...
This could be number
three, you never...
Excuse me.
Come here.
I would never say
this to her face,
but she is a wonderful
person and a gifted artist.
Why--why wouldn't you
say that to her face?
So...what do you think?
Think these guys are nice?
Guys I didn't bring
are even better.
Justin...
I'm willing to commit right now.
Would you do me the honor...
Of spending the summer with us
at dunder Mifflin?
I think--i think you
are very special.
You didn't want me before.
That's what you said.
No, I didn't.
You were--you were
kind of a jerk to me.
I...
And I'm-- I'm gonna go now.
Why don't--hey.
Ah-choo!
Bless you.
Thank you.
Okay, Jim, you owe me 120.
And Phil, you owe me 230.
Let's open a tab,
because you and me are
gonna be playin' more often.
Count me in. No.
All right.
Okay.
You had some fun and,
uh, and got paid for it.
So let me just get my
last shot in there.
Is there anything
you can do for me?
I'll tell you what.
My fiscal year
ends in two months.
Let's talk then.
Sound good? Absolutely.
Good playing with you guys.
Right on.
You know, it's a tough thing
seeing a grown
man take six shots
to get out of a sand trap.
But I had to give Phil
credit for not quitting.
Which is what I told him.
I also told him that
I don't quit either...
And I'd call him
every single day
until he gave me his business.
Which he then did...
After...15 minutes of
me blocking his car.
So I am now his paper supplier.
And I shot a 102 today, so
I'm feelin' pretty good.
The job fair will be
closing in five minutes.
Eighth period will
commence as scheduled.
Hold down the fort.
I have to do something.
Excuse me.
If you can hear me,
I would like you to look
around at all these companies
and know that none of them
are good enough for you.
H&r block?
Come on!
I mean, I don't even
know what they do.
"Frank Regan funeral home"?
Too much formaldehyde.
The air force?
Air force is cool.
The refreshments?
Bush league, you know?
That's not what you want.
Dunder--
that--okay.
I see security is coming,
so I just wanted to say
come to dunder Mifflin.
Dunder Mifflin,
a great place to work.
Anybody? Show of hands?
Anybody wanna intern
at dunder Mifflin?
We do not offer college credit.
We cannot give you
any sort of pay,
but it is a really
fun work environment.
Anybody? Show of hands?
Damn it. Okay.
I'm gonna wrap it up here.
Thank you...For your time.
And drive safe.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Beers?
You closed it?
I closed it.
Yes! Oh!
Um...congratulations to you, sir.
Thank you.
Oh, thank you very much.
Appreciate it.
Well done. Nice job. Thank you.
You know what? Screw this.
Oh!
Ooh.
* bow wow wow
* do do do do do do do do *
Today I did something stupid.
I questioned myself,
and I will never do that again.
'Cause I look at somebody
like Jim Halpert,
and I think that guy can
do anything he wants to do.
He could...Do anything,
and he chooses to work
here selling paper.
Just like me.
Yeah. Kiss her.
Kiss her good.
Hi. Hello.
I was just wondering
what kind of jobs
do you guys have?
Are you interested
in graphic design?
Yeah. Um...
Can I fill out an application?
Oh, absolutely. Here.
Take a seat.
I should let you know right away
this is just an entry level job.
It's really basic.
We're looking for
like a self-starter,
someone who can meet deadlines
and just pretty much just
go the extra mile, I guess.
I can do that. Great.
And, uh, obviously,
we're looking for someone
who knows Photoshop
and Dreamweaver,
Corel painter, Illustrator,
After Effects--all the basics.
I don't know any of those.
It's actually not
super-complicated.
I mean, I'm sure there's
some sort of, like,
adult education
classes in the area.
But if you're really serious
about graphic design,
one thing about New
York or Philadelphia--
they've got amazing programs
out there for design.
New York or Philadelphia.
Yeah.
All right.
Cool. Well, thanks.
And I'll look into those.
You should.
New York or Philadelphia.
Absolutely. That's
where the action is.
Thanks.