‐ Previously
on "Good Girls"...
‐ Electrical companies,
plumbing, construction,
the shell companies
build whatever projects
Gang‐Fairy Godfather
could get approved.
‐ Which is why he needs you
in that seat.
‐ So all your projects
and whatever,
they're all above board.
‐ Wow, this is, like,
kind of amazing.
‐ So is he.
I'm really happy for you.
‐ Oh, it's not like that.
♪
‐ You got another zit?
‐ Beth's not the only one
that's going down.
My wife's in it too.
‐ The more the merrier.
‐ You can't give that stuff
to the DA.
‐ Vance, what are you guys
waiting for?
‐ Ask your friend.
‐ I just need you
to answer something.
How do you make it through
your day being such a moron?
♪
‐ All right, turn it off.
‐ No.
‐ Your guy died.
‐ I'm not going.
‐ What do you mean?
‐ I told him he could skip.
‐ Why?
‐ It's a special day.
‐ Yeah, he has a math test.
‐ It's his half birthday.
‐ You got pwned!
‐ I just wish
you'd ask me first
before you make any promises.
‐ Can you cut those
a little smaller?
‐ You know, no other parents
celebrate half birthdays.
‐ Do I get a present?
‐ No.
‐ Sure.
‐ I'll text you guys my list.
‐ Just get him half a present.
‐ Here.
‐ Who's Vanessa?
‐ Just take it.
‐ I asked for almond milk.
‐ They were out.
‐ So what is this?
‐ Milk.
‐ I'm lactose intolerant.
‐ Don't be such a woman.
♪
‐ ♪ You can't hear it,
but I do ♪
♪
♪ You can't hear it,
but I do ♪
‐ Excuse me.
Can I download my own ringtone?
My grandson
plays clarinet and‐‐
excuse me, sir.
‐ Vance Madison.
Employee ID number 53802.
Thank you.
Yeah, I need to track
a stolen phone.
Boland, Elizabeth.
‐ It kind of burns.
‐ That's how you know
it's working.
See?
‐ Ow.
‐ Oops.
‐ Okay, that's enough.
Go get ready for school.
‐ It's supposed
to remove age spots.
‐ Who got you into this?
‐
‐ Hey, Ruby.
‐ Here you go.
What's up, man?
‐ Well, I need you
to do something for me.
‐ Name it.
Share, brother.
‐
‐ I didn't know
what else to do.
‐ You could have told me.
‐ They were gonna
take Ruby down too, Dean.
‐ I've known you for 30 years.
‐ I'm not the bad guy
here, man.
‐ They're all I got.
‐ Oh, let's do it
in the bathtub next.
‐ Mm, that never works.
‐ Why not?
‐ Unless you have, like,
one of those super fancy tubs,
It's like you're in a bobsled.
‐ No, but we'd be
facing each other.
‐ Then we're, like,
in weird rowboat sitch
where everyone's freezing.
‐ Fine, okay.
What about...the closet?
‐ It's kind of limited.
‐ I like a challenge.
‐ ♪ I need a sign
‐ Sorry,
it must be on shuffle.
‐ Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This is a banger.
‐ ♪ Over the atmosphere
♪ I need to know
‐ It's Train.
‐ Whatever, I know.
They are easy to hate on.
‐ I love everything about them.
Which closet?
‐ Broom.
‐ Hot.
‐ ♪ When there is no safe
place to put my head ♪
‐
‐ You know, I never thought
that I'd date someone
who loves Train
as much as me.
‐ ♪ And I'm
‐ Are we?
‐ ♪ Calling all angels
‐ What?
‐ Dating?
♪
‐ ♪ And I'm
‐ Aren't we?
‐ Uh, I mean, uh, maybe.
‐ ♪ All you angels
‐
Um, what do you wanna call it?
♪
‐ Why do we
have to call it anything?
‐ Because we've been
doing the other "it" now
for, like, three days straight,
so I'm just kind of curious.
‐ ♪ 'Cause my TV set
just keeps it all ♪
♪ From being clear
‐ I don't know.
‐ Really?
‐ Come on.
Isn't this something
that we could settle
in the broom closet?
‐ No, I'm kind of tired.
‐ Hey, come on.
‐ ♪ All angels
‐ My junk needs to recharge.
‐ But...
‐ ♪ So they don't disappear
♪ While private eyes
solve marriage lies ♪
‐ The song
isn't even done yet.
‐ ♪ 'Cause we don't talk
for years ♪
‐ Your supporters
are highly loyal
with 60% being completely
or very certain
of their choice.
Hispanic support
with some college
to college grad is also solid,
with an overwhelming majority
in strong favor
of your
"clean up the streets" message.
Polls also show 83% of voters
want a visionary
as opposed to a politician.
‐ Is that part good?
‐ Are you a politician?
‐
No.
‐ Then it's not bad.
‐ Okay.
‐ And women like you in red.
‐ Thank you, Scott.
‐ Seriously?
‐ It's a power color.
‐ I hate red.
‐ You gotta play by the rules.
‐ Why?
‐ 'Cause then we get
to do things our way.
Urban garden,
basketball courts, ice arena,
nature trails all over.
Olympic‐sized swimming pool.
Café, lounge, amphitheater.
‐ Money laundering, bribery,
extortion all wrapped up
in your friendly
neighborhood rec center.
‐ Okay.
‐ That's it?
‐ What more did you want?
‐ Need a warrant.
‐ Great, get one.
‐ We need someone
to sign off on that.
‐ Can you do that?
‐ And you can't do that.
‐ No, need access to a judge...
‐ Need my old job back.
‐ To even get access.
‐ My hands are tied.
‐ We're on vacation.
‐ What are you gonna do?
‐ Not us.
‐ How would we get it?
‐ Isn't that what you guys do?
‐ Sorry, are asking us
to break the law?
‐ Does that
make you uncomfortable?
‐ Consider it a favor.
‐ But the clock's ticking
because we used miles
for our room,
and they're almost gone.
‐ Then we're even.
♪
‐
‐ Time.
‐ 5 minutes, 40 seconds.
‐ I can do better.
‐ I love that she needs
the whole look
to get into character.
‐ Okay, what about
dinner Thursday?
‐ Won't it be weird?
‐ Stan loves Deansie.
‐ Not the problem.
‐ It'll make you guys better.
‐ Or it'll make us worse.
‐ We'll just talk about
their stupid skincare business.
‐ How's that gonna help?
‐ When was the last time
we all got boozed up
and it didn't end
in a hug fest?
‐ When was the last time
we got all boozed up?
‐ Exactly.
‐ Time.
‐ It was faster.
‐ You didn't even time it,
did you?
‐ How are we gonna even
get into the building?
‐ Why don't we just go
during the day?
‐ Because he'll be there.
‐ So distract him.
‐ How?
‐ You know how.
‐ No, I don't.
‐ Why did Watergate fail?
‐ 'Cause they got caught.
‐ 'Cause they were men.
‐ She means use your hoo‐ha.
‐ Just stop.
‐ Worked with the wire.
‐ You use your hoo‐ha.
‐ I'm just saying,
take the Brousin
to lunch or something.
‐ I thought we agreed
on "Gang‐Fairy Godfather."
‐ "Brousin" makes more sense.
‐ I'm not doing anything
with the Brousin.
‐ Why not?
‐ Because then
he'll know it's me.
‐ Okay, you guys,
we obviously go at night.
‐ What about the
security guard?
‐ We'll use my hoo‐ha.
‐ Can I help you?
‐ May I use your bathroom?
‐ Okay, so...
‐ What took you so long?
‐ I actually had to pee.
‐ I'm, like, covered in thorns.
‐ Okay, here we go.
‐ The penguin is in the igloo.
‐ Huh?
‐ The horse is in the barn.
‐ Then where's
the security guard?
‐ He's still at his desk.
‐ Can you just say that
from now on?
‐ 10‐4.
‐ Bye.
‐ Over and out.
‐ Ugh.
‐ Just trying to make it fun.
‐ Give me the L15.
Wait, the L16.
‐ They don't have names
on them.
‐ The crocodile teeth ones.
‐ They all have teeth.
‐ Oh, my God.
Crocodile, you amateur.
‐ Where is he?
‐  What's his 20?
‐ Huh?
‐ Where is he?
‐ Uh, he's eating a Kit Kat.
‐ But we heard a door.
‐ Yeah, he's got a whole stash
in the closet.
‐ He was just getting a snack.
‐ Okay, well, hurry up.
‐ Come on, come on.
Bada bing!
Bada boom!
‐ Okay.
What's going on?
‐ It won't open.
Look, it's unlocked.
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ What?
‐ Do you have a tool
for one of those?
‐ Oh.
That is a whole different set
of YouTube videos.
‐ Okay.
Maybe his assistant has,
like, a spare or something.
‐ Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, he's kind of cute.
‐ Got it.
‐ Sick.
‐ He has a card for everything.
‐ Talk to me, baby.
‐ We okay?
‐ He's on the move.
You got this.
‐ Come on, ladies,
give me a sign.
Well?
‐ I tore my jeans on the way
back out the window.
‐ No.
‐ Yeah, my favorite pair.
‐ Where we at?
You guys want in on this?
‐ What are we gonna do?
‐ 10% off at Chili's.
‐ I could do a marg.
‐ Hill, you up?
‐ Nope.
‐ Guess where I went.
‐ You smell like a cantina.
‐ I only had one.
‐ I didn't ask how many.
‐ Fine. Three.
‐ All right, where did you go?
‐ When's the last time
you had Southwestern egg rolls?
‐ I bought some
from Kroger's last week.
‐ No, at Chili's.
‐ I don't know, Ruby.
‐ Remember that time someone
pulled the fire alarm
and we all had to go outside?
‐ And we sat at the wrong booth
when they let us back in.
‐ You got halfway through
that guy's black bean burger
before you even realized.
‐ Yeah, we were pretty bombed.
‐ We haven't had fun
like that in forever.
‐ We need more like it.
‐ How about Thursday?
‐ They still got
that Texas lemonade?
‐ They do.
‐ In.
‐ So are the Bolands.
‐ What do you mean?
‐ We all used to
have fun together.
‐ Babe, I'm not going
to Chili's
with no damn Bolands.
‐ Fine.
‐ Good.
‐ They can come here.
‐ What is wrong with you?
‐ I don't want a situation.
‐ It's just dinner.
‐ It's gonna be weird.
‐ Don't worry.
I got you covered.
‐ How?
‐ Dean will be there.
‐
Mmm, something smells good.
What you working on over there?
‐ Spanish omelet.
‐ Mmm!
‐ Little chorizo.
‐ Red peppers, fried potatoes,
and a pinch of salt.
‐ Mmm!
Just like we are
in Barcelona.
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ Mmm.
Oh, whoa, whoa, sir.
‐ What?
‐ Well, where's mine?
‐ Everything you need
is on the counter.
‐ Well, it's just that,
you know,
you usually make me one.
‐ Well that's when
we were roomies.
‐ Well, what are we now?
‐ You tell me.
‐ Oh, come on.
‐ I mean, we're definitely
not dating, right?
‐ We really can't
just move past this?
‐ Oh, I have.
‐ What is that?
‐ Hinge.
Wait, no, this is Tinder.
‐ You're back on the apps?
‐ I mean, how else
am I supposed
to put myself out there?
‐ Why do you need
to put yourself anywhere?
‐
'Cause you don't
wanna do this, right?
‐ I don't...
I don't wanna
not do this, okay?
And I definitely don't want you
doing this with anyone else.
‐ So you don't wanna date?
‐ Right.
‐ But you don't wanna not date?
‐ Essentially,
you wanna not not date?
‐ I think so.
‐ But do you wanna
not not date anyone else?
‐ No.
‐ I mean...
I'm down with that.
‐ Cool.
‐ You want cheese in yours?
‐ Duh.
‐ You can just turn that off.
‐ Yeah, I think I will.
Jesus, how did you get
so many matches on this?
‐ I'm a catch.
‐ Obviously.
‐ No, you wanna know my secret?
‐ Yes, please.
‐ I just...I think
about the kind of tail
I wanna land, right?
And then I just sort of cater
my profile to the customer.
‐ Sorry,
like, you make stuff up or?
‐ I mean, it's more like
I just sort of tell them
what they wanna hear,
and then they come to you.
Have I ever volunteered
at an animal shelter?
I mean, no, but I don't
want 'em gassed either.
Yeah,
once you figure it out,
it's like shooting fish
in a barrel.
And I'm no, like, coder,
but I'm don't want
some algorithm
telling me
who I should be with.
‐ Ooh, Oaxacan street corn.
‐ Dad hates that cheese.
‐ She is not wrong.
‐ I'll make coleslaw.
‐ Then after dinner,
you and Stan
can be on the same team.
‐ For what?
‐ Scattergories.
‐ Wait, now we're doing
a game night?
‐ We just need to be normal
around each other.
‐ We've never played
Scattergories.
‐ Twister?
‐ You guys,
I can get us into that office.
We've been using
my hoo‐ha all wrong.
Hey, Sara, how are you?
It's a little late
for you to be up, isn't it?
‐ My bedtime's
not for another two hours.
‐ Go to your room.
‐ What?
‐ I can't believe I finally
met a girl who butt chugs.
‐ Well, how else are you
gonna pound a White Claw?
‐ Cheers.
‐
So what did you
major in at Michigan?
‐ Oh, science.
‐ How did you get
through organic chem?
‐ I just really love
organic stuff.
It's actually pretty easy
at Whole Foods.
‐ Well, uh...
‐
‐ You know, most girls
are turned off by my profile.
‐ You're kidding me.
Why?
‐ They get all uptight
about the hating kids stuff.
‐ Ugh, I mean, kids suck.
‐ Right?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Oh, hell yeah.
Jell‐O shots.
‐ Our fave.
‐ To not remembering
anything tomorrow morning.
‐ I will drink to that.
‐ Mmm.
‐ Whew.
‐ They go down easier
the more you do 'em.
‐ Oh, no, I'm just‐‐I'm cold.
‐ You should've
brought a jacket.
‐ I need you
to have the full picture.
‐ Appreciate it.
‐ Now that you had a preview...
Can I borrow yours?
‐ Seriously?
‐ The next round will be on me.
‐ Fine.
‐ You're sweet.
‐ My mom always says that.
‐
She's right.
Mmm.
‐ Ready when you are.
‐ Uh, ready for what?
‐ That shot.
‐ Right, yes.
Okay.
‐ Let's just get the waitress.
‐ But then
you'd see me roofie it.
‐ Will you marry me?
‐
♪
‐ You gotta be kidding me.
‐ Please, Clark,
I'm gonna burst.
‐ You should see a doctor.
♪
‐ Showtime.
‐ ♪ She's fed up with seeing
♪ The same dead people
over and over ♪
♪ Hanging out in the streets
♪
♪ She screams
♪ Hang on a crucifix
♪ Open hands on the IVs
♪
♪ Low, afraid,
and pissed off ♪
♪
♪ In quivering voice
♪ She says
♪
♪ Au revoir
‐ What took you so long?
‐ Oh.
These are, like,
really complicated.
Mmm.
‐ Just tastes like tequila.
‐ Really?
No, they‐‐they‐‐
first, they light 'em on fire.
‐ I came in and looked for you.
‐ Well, they‐‐
they wouldn't do it inside.
‐ What's going on?
‐ Okay.
I'm gonna level with you.
‐ That's never a good sign.
‐ I went outside
to ask the valet
if I could leave
my car here overnight.
‐ Or maybe it's a great sign.
‐ Yeah, maybe.
‐ Uh, hey.
‐ Beat it, bro.
We don't have any money.
‐ No, no, it's okay.
I know him.
‐ How?
‐ He's my...
Roommate.
‐ Oh, we're back
to that now, huh?
‐ Clark is on the prowl.
I repeat, Clark is a‐prowlin'.
‐ Who is that guy?
‐ He's just a‐‐he's a coworker.
‐ You work at a mini‐mart.
‐ Yeah, he's the boss.
‐ So now you wear
your boss's jacket?
‐ No, he was thinking about
adding a jacket to the uniform,
and he wanted feedback,
so obviously I'm gonna
tell him smaller sizes.
‐ Hey, you know what?
I'm sorry.
‐ Kevin, please.
‐ This is my fault.
‐ Can we please just talk about
this later when we get home?
‐ See, I really thought things
would be different now.
‐ I promise you.
It's not what it looks like.
Okay, but I can't talk
about it here, so please‐‐
‐ Is everything cool?
‐ Yeah, it's fine.
‐ Listen, I don't wanna get
in the way of anything here.
‐ No, it's fine,
I was just leaving.
‐ No.
‐ No, I feel like I should go.
‐ No to me or no to him?
‐ We literally just met, so...
‐ How'd you meet?
‐ Bumble, Hinge,
I don't even remember.
‐ All right,
she's all yours man.
‐ You wanna go do another shot?
‐ Yes.
‐ I got phone records,
bank accounts, names, numbers‐‐
‐ Quite a haul.
‐ He knows everything.
‐ Gotta say,
none of this looks good for
a lady who's tough on crime.
‐ What do you want?
‐ Let me buy you guys a drink.
‐ Why?
‐ Talk strategy.
What's good around here?
‐ There's a Chili's.
‐ Perfect.
Can I throw my bike
in the back?
Could you take
the child lock off?
‐ That doctor dude sounds
way more messed up than you.
‐ Therapist.
‐ Textbook.
‐ Mm, textbook what?
‐ Gay.
‐ He's just British.
‐ Your ex‐husband, super gay.
‐ Don't tell me‐‐Noah?
‐ Everyone
in law enforcement's gay.
‐ And why is it
that I'm listening to you
about any of this again?
‐ 'Cause I'm the only one
who calls it like it is.
‐ But you just have
the one call?
‐ Okay, you know
who couldn't be
more straight and into you?
‐ Let me guess.
‐ Your hobo friend.
‐ He's
experiencing homelessness.
‐ Whatever.
That dude's all sac.
‐ I just don't think I should
be with anybody right now.
‐ Why is that?
‐ Because I have issues.
‐ Everyone does.
‐ Well, mine could be studied.
‐ Well, at least
you're not in denial.
‐ Thanks.
‐ I'm serious.
Being aware of it
means you can't
be that messed up.
‐ How can a bro like you
be such a good listener?
‐ I'm not really a bro.
‐ Sorry, bruh.
‐ I'm gay.
‐ Funny.
‐ Everything on my profile
is made up.
‐ But what about
the picture of you
in Jamaica with the cheetah?
‐ Photoshop.
‐ But you had on
a backwards hat?
‐ To convince my dad.
‐ Well, okay then.
‐ Mm.
‐ Mm‐hmm, mm‐hmm, mm‐hmm.
‐ You know, this is actually
one of the best dates
I've ever had with a girl.
‐ And you, my friend,
make very convincing
human garbage.
‐ Could I get a selfie
for my dad?
‐ Why not?
‐ I'm sorry.
‐ Why?
‐ For what I'm about to do.
‐
Hey.
Have you seen this bit
where the guy,
that dude from "SNL,"
he recaps TV shows?
‐ Nope.
‐ It's genius.
He does this thing
where he tries to guess
what the show is
based on the title,
but he has no idea.
‐ How could you?
‐ How are those housewives
in the ATL?
‐ Didn't watch.
‐ Uh‐huh, what'd you guys do?
‐ We went out for drinks.
‐ Twice in one week?
‐ We ran into
a friend of yours.
‐ Yeah?
‐ What, were you trying
to show off
in front of your bike dads?
‐ No.
‐ You must've felt
like a real big shot.
‐ It's not like that.
‐ What's it like then?
‐ You put me in jail.
‐ Not on purpose.
‐ What's the difference?
‐ You would still be in there.
‐ Well, this guy is trying
to make sure I don't go back.
‐ Oh, the grown man in tights.
‐ He's got my back, okay?
‐ You are such an idiot.
‐ Yeah, for trusting you.
‐ He's not your friend.
‐ At least he's trying to help.
‐ To get to me.
‐ What are you talking about?
‐ I have to get the city
to plug his stupid face creams
for, like, conventions
or hotels or whatever.
‐ Wait, he said that?
‐ He was never in it for you.
I really did want Nevada.
‐ She could lose everything.
‐ So could we.
‐ She has kids, Stanley.
‐ Who's sleeping down
that hall?
‐ Since when do you get
to decide to put a woman away?
‐ It's not just about her.
‐ 'Cause I don't remember
marrying a judge.
‐ You can't even
see it anymore.
‐ I can see
we're not in a courtroom.
‐ You could dress it up,
talk around it.
‐ At least in court,
you get a jury.
‐ But we're just criminals now.
You remember our old Nissan?
‐ Rust bucket?
‐ Mm‐hmm, mm‐hmm.
It started out with
a little patch on the door...
but, eventually,
I took over the whole car.
‐ Come on.
‐ When's the last time
we've been to church?
‐ It bought our daughter
a kidney.
‐ Or volunteered
at the food bank?
‐ It pays for Harry's school.
‐ And the crazy thing
is that I don't
even feel guilty anymore.
‐ 'Cause we deserve it.
‐ Justify it all you want...
but, eventually,
it rots out the floorboards.
‐ I guess we should
cancel dinner with the Bolands.
‐ Yeah, probably.
‐ No, dude, dude,
she practically broke my jock.
‐ Sounds like
a wild night, buddy.
‐ I was like‐‐
I was like, "Chill.
I know you can't get enough,
but Papa has got to sleep."
‐
Hey, where's the file key?
‐ Top right.
‐ Yeah, that's where I left it.
Are you gonna see her again?
‐ Hell, no.
‐ I cannot keep up
with your women.
‐ Oh, here.
‐ That's weird.
‐ You must have moved it.
‐ I didn't.
‐ It wasn't me.
‐ Can you grab
the night logins from security?
‐ Yeah.
‐
‐ Who is she?
‐ That's your boy's girl.
‐ You think this is funny?
‐
What'd she get?
‐ What do you think?
‐ I think
you got played, brother.
‐ Yes, suck it!
‐ All right, chief,
time for homework.
‐ One more level.
‐ You got a book report, buddy.
‐ I'll do it later.
‐ It's late.
‐ Mom said I could stay up.
‐ Did you get almond milk?
‐ I got oat milk.
It's better for you.
‐ Where'd you get this?
‐ It was on my car
in the parking lot.
She's your buddy's wife, right?
I like her.
‐ Why?
‐ I don't know.
She seems like a leader.
I hope she wins.
‐ You know what?
Me too.
‐ Die!
Hey.
‐ Turn it off.
‐ I can't see.
‐ Mom,
tell your husband to move.
‐ Just let him finish, honey.
‐ Mom!
‐ Vance!
What the hell are you doing?
‐ Book report, now!
‐ Hey, you're here.
I know you're not allowed
to endorse one way
or the other,
but I thought you could
wear one while you work out.
‐ Just take a seat.
‐ Uh‐oh, am I falling behind
with working women
ages 18 to 34
who like to eat food?
‐ No, I have something
that's gonna help you.
‐ I thought you weren't
allowed to do that?
‐ Well,
I don't mean the election.
‐ What's this?
‐ Everything you
were looking for last night.
‐ I don't know what
you're talking about.
‐ Well, you or your sister
or someone else
that you're working for
swiped in at 9:38
with my assistant's ID,
so when you're done,
I am gonna need 'em back.
‐ What happens now?
‐ I don't understand.
‐ I wake up
with a gun to my face
in the middle of the night?
‐ You have a campaign to win.
‐ And then when we're done,
you roll me up
in a carpet for trash day?
‐ Relax, jeez.
No, that's not my style.
I'm more the guy
that makes things difficult.
I know people, right?
You got a husband
that's facing a long stretch.
Sister's got a record.
I mean, those two are
low‐hanging fruit,
and there's no way that
that friend of yours
can pay
for her son's private school.
That's just
a quick call to state,
get her tax returns,
you know how that goes.
Yeah, can't let you off
that easy, Beth.
You have a lot of work to do.
‐ Oh, wait, wait, wait, stop.
Right there.
Zug Island Holdings.
‐ Where's it go?
♪
‐ Romeo Pipe Fitters
and B and J Construction.
♪
Could make a case
from the numbers
that it's padded for kickbacks.
‐ But none of it
goes back to him.
♪
‐ ♪ How deep's the water?
♪ You say it's not
♪
♪ How long is it flowing?
♪ You say, "It's gone"
♪
♪ I guess
I dreamt ♪
♪
♪ Slow‐traveling times
‐ Just leave it
on the table, man.
‐ Beth wanted to, you know,
make sure
you guys still had it, so...
♪
‐ That's a lotta slaw, bro.
‐ It's half of what she made.
‐
♪
‐ Listen, man,
I'm sorry that...
‐ We're in a cult, dude.
‐ Yeah, they got us good.
‐ You wanna...
you want to take
the brotherhood down?
‐ Now you're knocking?
‐ You said to.
‐ When have you
ever listened to me?
‐ Nah, don't be like that.
‐ What do you want?
‐ I'll take an apology.
‐ What did I do now?
‐ You hurt my feelings.
‐ How's that?
‐ If you
need something, darling,
all you gotta do is ask.
‐ He's your brother.
‐ Cousin.
‐ Family.
‐ He's in our way.
♪
‐ ♪ Oh, lover
♪ You seem to
be hiding ♪
♪
♪ Something from me,
and ♪
♪ I'll find it
♪
♪ Silver shining across the
♪ Deep end
♪
♪ But we're swimming...