.
- Previously,
on "Good Girls"...
- Is all that from one night?
- I would love to hear
about them private parties
you've been
running behind my back.
- Ben threw a rager
at our house.
- You didn't want your cool,
fancy new friends
to know about
your broke-ass mom, right?
- You called them douchebags
and date rapers.
- If you're unhappy here,
you can always stay
at your dad's.
- Big Kahuna,
they want to meet with us.
- Kahuna Spas would love
to be part of the ride.
- I got the account.
- That's great!
- I also had to give them
the books.
- Dean Boland?
- Tell me one thing:
was he part of it?
- There's gotta be a way
to get him out.
- He's the perfect fall guy.
- It all started
about a year ago.
- Doesn't matter.
Your husband
pled guilty today.
- We pop gang friend.
All of this goes away.
- You're gonna need a sniper.
I know a guy.
- What do you want?
- Pull up your pants
like a big boy and do your job.
Dear Dean,
I'm gonna tell you
exactly what to do
and how to do it.
[dramatic music]
.
[Yes' "Leave It" plays]
[vocalization]
- ♪ One down, one to go
♪ Another town,
and one more show ♪
♪ Downtown,
they're giving away ♪
♪ But she never came back
♪ Do do do do
♪ No phone
can take your place ♪
♪ Do you know what I mean?
do do ♪
♪ Two down, there ya go
♪ MacArthur Park
in the driving snow ♪
♪ Uptown,
they're digging it out ♪
♪ Better lay your claim,
dum dum dum ♪
- What's it gonna be?
- Pop-Tarts.
- We don't have Pop-Tarts.
- Yes, we do.
- Dad has them at the top.
- ♪ No illusions
as we take ♪
♪ Refuge
in young man's pleasure ♪
♪ Breaking down
the dreams we make ♪
- Wash them down with some OJ.
- Dad lets us have soda.
- ♪ Ah leave it
♪ Goodbye, goodbye
♪ Goodbye bad
♪ Leave it,
hello, hello ♪
♪ Heaven
♪ Goodbye, goodbye,
one down, one to go ♪
[knocking on door]
♪ Another town...
♪ Leave it
- Hi.
We haven't actually met.
- Aren't you the Big Kahuna?
- Just Dave.
- Is Dean okay?
- That depends on you.
- ♪ Goodbye, goodbye
♪ Goodbye
- I only see whole milk.
- He'll kill me.
- You have any almond or soy?
- We'll protect you.
- He has people everywhere.
- No one will know
you're with us.
- Except for your
entire department.
- It'll just be me.
- And me.
- This boat--airtight.
No holes.
- What could I even get on him?
- Looks like plenty.
- We need to know what
he does with the money.
- Okay. Well, I'll just
text him and ask, then.
- Seriously?
- I can't do this.
- Okay.
- Okay...
- Just might wanna give the
rest of your posse a heads-up.
- Why?
- Because now, we have
to round up everyone.
- Okay, I'm a mom.
Who's gonna believe
that I wrote that?
- That's the gamble.
Right?
Oh...
I used to do hearts
over the Is.
[somber electronic music]
♪
[no sound]
[somber music continues]
♪
- Hi. Fuel up.
- Ooh, early bird over here.
- Yeah. Gotta drink.
- Ah...I gotta go to bed.
- Got Harry's assembly
this morning.
- Well, why can't you go?
- I am. They want us both.
- [sighs]
Do private school parents
have jobs? I mean...
- None that start
before noon, apparently.
- Babe, I'm supposed to be
on the clock in an hour.
- Another double.
- Gene needs me.
- What's this man
got you doing?
- You know, just taking care
of business.
- Excuse me.
- What?
- Your hand!
What the hell is happening
in the champagne room?
- You should see the other guy.
- I hope
he's paying you overtime.
- I'm just trying to...
keep on his good side.
- Please shower.
- [groans]
Ah...
- Key's taped to the side.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
- I made a frittata.
- Gutsy.
- Yeah.
I don't have to wake up
at the crack anymore.
You know why?
- Why?
- No child to get off
to school.
Yeah, I got all the time
in the world.
- Sounds like
you're adjusting well.
- Mm-hmm. It's almost
as if I never gave birth.
- What's in a frittata?
- You know...eggs.
- Well, how's it different
from an omelet?
- I wanted to make
a frigging frittata, okay?
I actually did.
But we don't get cell reception
in my apartment,
and the internet was down,
and only Ben knows
how to reset the box.
And I have this ringing
in my ear,
so I wanted to look that up,
but I couldn't,
because the internet
and the resetting.
- Tinnitus.
- Sure. Whatever.
The point is
is that if Ben was here,
I wouldn't have even
had to look it up,
because he's so much smarter
than me and better than me,
and everything in my life
is just a lot better
whenever he's with me.
- You don't have tinnitus.
- So, I, uh, purchased
some concert tickets.
- When I was a young chap...
- I need him to come back.
- Dad and I used
to collect butterflies.
- And I know you're gonna say
that I'm bribing him,
but I'm telling you it works.
- I would run around the field,
scooping up as many as I could,
and the net would snap
their little wings.
- Jesus. No wonder
you became a therapist.
- Dad would just stand
perfectly still,
so they'd land on him.
- And then what,
you'd take them home
and let them fly around
your house like a weird pet?
- Mount them in decorative
shadow boxes.
The point is, you can't use
a net to get what you want.
- That's really
an elaborate metaphor.
- You can't make someone
like you.
- You know, I think Dahmer
was a collector too.
- See you next week, Annie.
- I know.
- Do you?
- I do.
- Because he's gonna--
- I know.
- Like, for real.
- We're dead.
- Okay, let's focus
on the positive.
- They'll never find
our bodies.
- We get to start over,
which is a good thing.
- Assuming we can even deliver
gang friend.
- And then they'll move us
anywhere in the country.
- Do Alaska and Hawaii count?
- Probably.
- To do what?
- Whatever we want.
- What about Puerto Rico?
- I mean, if it's under
their jurisdiction,
I don't see why not.
- They'll fully set us up.
- House, car, job.
- American Samoa?
- Do you want to live
in American Samoa?
- I wanna know that I could.
- It'll be like
we never existed.
- Like we never
put on those masks.
- Ooh, one thing.
Not a big deal. Real minor.
- All the territories count,
Annie.
- Even Guam.
- Okay!
The hitman.
I mean, wouldn't
this whole deal go away
if your boy gets whacked?
One other thing.
- Where the hell'd he go?
- Son of a bitch!
.
- He changed his number, he
pulled his child out of school.
I mean, this man
has completely disappeared.
- Yeah. That's what
we do before we, uh,
get to work, so to speak.
- But we don't want him
to get to work.
- I can't just call
off your hit.
- Why not?
- There's a code.
- Like an assassin's creed?
- I vouched for you guys,
all right?
- We'll still pay him.
- It just makes me look bad.
- Well, what if we pay you too?
- Yeah.
Like a restocking fee.
- I don't need your money.
- Just give us a phone number.
- Email.
- Insta.
- Come on. We'll do anything.
- Anything?
- Yes.
- There's something
I haven't been able to do
for myself lately.
- Uh-huh.
- I got needs.
- Oh, no.
- Seems like something
you girls would be good at.
Yeah, I mean, sure,
all of you.
- Sweet Jesus.
- Okay.
Let me just
stop you right there.
- You. Bathroom. Five minutes.
- Seriously?
- Yeah. Your car. Whatever.
I don't care.
- I'm married.
- Oh.
- Well, why don't you just
tell us what it is?
- I'll text you.
[mellow pop music
in background]
♪
[buzzer]
[metallic clang]
[click]
- Where are the kids?
- They're with your mom.
Wait. Wait. Wait. Just wait.
The kids showed me where you've
been hiding the Pop-Tarts.
And they're actually fortified.
Who knew?
Maybe you did.
- What is this?
- Henderson, Nevada.
Second safest city in America.
- Okay.
- 16.1 miles from The Strip.
And it has this wonderful
big cat sanctuary
called the Lion Habitat Ranch.
- What's going on?
- You said you wanted to
move to Las Vegas.
- Have fun.
- I mean all of us.
- I'm sure Jane
will love the lions.
- Dean.
- I'll see you in 30 years.
- It might not take that long.
- And then what? I just pretend
like this never happened?
- Just don't give up
on me, okay?
[buzzer]
- What's going on?
- Taking measurements.
- We get a new one?
- That one's never been big
enough for Thanksgiving.
And people want
to grill these days.
- But these people's
just find with a griddle.
What's wrong with the fridge?
- It's janky.
- Janky?
It's not janky.
It still gets cold.
- People like all those gadgets
in the doors.
- Who are all these people?
- I don't know.
Potential buyers.
- You selling the house now?
- Someday.
- Your mama's house.
- Why not?
- The one you made me promise
to bury you in.
- Would getting out of here
be the worst thing?
- [laughing]
Oh, you're serious.
- You hate your job.
- What would you do?
- I don't know.
Something with nails.
- And what would I do?
- [huffs] Anything else.
- Take the kids?
- Probably.
[both chuckle]
- Can we lay away the layaway?
- Why?
- That's the only way we'd be
able to upgrade all of this.
- Well...
doesn't hurt to dream.
Grab two boxes
of those mothballs.
- One. Two. Five. Six.
- I don't think
Go-Gurt's on his list.
- Well, it's on my list,
okay?
Why does he want us
to go shopping for him, anyway?
- How's that guy gonna pick up
a 24-pack of Charmin?
- There are people to help him.
- I'm just glad we're on
the outside of his pants.
- What's next?
- Duct tape.
- Excuse me.
God forbid I get my Go-Gurt,
but you can have Pop-Tarts?
- My kids
are really missing Dean.
- You're just as fun.
- He burps
their names good night.
- I mean--psshh--that's easy.
Anybody could do that.
- It's harder than you'd think.
- Is it?.
[belching]
Good night,
Kenneeee...
[loud belch]
- Is that everything?
- Uh, let's see.
We've got the garden hose.
The roofing nails,
hydrogen peroxide,
Sun Chips,
moth balls, duct tape.
Yeah.
And five bags of fertilizer.
What?
- These aren't groceries.
- I know.
It's a mix of sundries.
- [mouthing]
It's a bomb.
- What?
- [mouthing]
A bomb.
- Jesus, just say it.
- There are people here.
- Can you fill me in?
- Okay. Okay. Okay.
Remember when we did karaoke
and you sang "Lovely Day"?
- Yeah.
- How did you do?
- I crushed it.
- Not that time.
The time at my birthday.
- I blew the roof
off the place.
- Not that birthday.
The other birthday.
When you had
a little cold coming on.
- Oh, God.
- How'd you do?
- I bom--
.
- Yeah.
Hmm.
- What's it say?
- That we have enough here
to blow up a church choir.
- God.
- Then again, I don't
understand metric proportions,
so could be more like
a...jury?
- Oh my God.
- Maybe a bus.
- What are the nails for?
- Shredding flesh.
- We can't give this to him.
- I don't see how we don't.
- You want to be responsible
for a bus full of choir jurors?
'Cause I'll never sleep again.
- You know where you're really
never gonna sleep again?
Curled up with Deansie
in his cell.
- All right.
- Yeah. 'Cause that's where
we're all going
if gang friend gets whacked.
- It's not coed, Annie.
- Well, newsflash, sis.
The women's ones are worse.
- She's right.
I saw this thing on MSNBC.
- Okay.
- The guard's make them,
you know,
do sex stuff to each other.
- No!
- While they watch.
- Thank you. Got it.
- So, I mean,
if we're on the same block,
it's just a matter of time
before we'd have to--
- Can I have a juice box?
- Of course, honey.
- I want Daddy.
- There was one where
the warden got in on it too.
Taped it and everything.
- Let's do this.
- Ow.
- Oh, you know what?
On second thought,
mind putting them up top?
- Did you find him?
- Yeah.
- So it's taken care of?
- Kinda.
- What's kinda? Either he's
murdering a man or he's not.
- He wants to talk to her.
- Well, can you
patch me through?
- You know, we're not doing
any more errands for you.
- All right, everyone, chill.
He'll call you.
- And for your information, the
store has a delivery service.
Not to mention
there's an entire industry.
- I'm on a million watchlists,
butt cheeks.
- Yeah, well, whoever it's for,
I really hope they deserve it.
- Believe me.
Mom has it coming.
- Mom?
- Yeah.
And at 75, I gotta do it
while she's still around.
- Jesus.
- I'm just glad the chemo
didn't take her out
before I got the chance.
- Okay, you know what?
That's it. We're done here.
Okay? We good?
- She'll really
appreciate this.
- Getting blown to bits?
- Her garden.
- Huh?
- This is a prize
for beating cancer. Twice.
You bitches are sick.
- Yeah, well...
- How about some tunes?
[Jay Ferguson's
"Thunder Island" plays]
♪
- ♪ Ooh, yeah
♪ Da da da da
da da da ♪
♪ Da da da
da da da da doo ♪
♪ Da da da da
da da da ♪
♪ Da da da
da da da da doo ♪
♪
♪ Sha la la la la la my lady
♪ In the sun
with your hair undone ♪
♪ Can you hear me now
calling your name ♪
♪ From across the bay
♪
♪ A summer's day laughing
and a-hidin' ♪
♪ Chasing love
out on Thunder Island ♪
♪ Da da da
da da da doo ♪
♪
♪ Da da da da
da da da ♪
♪ Da da da
da da da doo ♪
♪ Yeah-eah-eah
♪ Da da da
da da da da da ♪
♪ Da da da da doo
♪
♪ She was the color of
the Indian summer ♪
♪ And we shared the hours
without number ♪
♪ Until one day
when the sky turned dark ♪
♪ And the winds grew wild
♪
♪ I'll remember the nights
in the cool sand ♪
♪ Making love
out on Thunder Island ♪
♪ Da da da da
da da da ♪
♪ Da da da
da da da da doo ♪
♪ Goodbye Thunder Island,
da da da--♪
- Don't have all day, man.
Let's go.
- I can't.
- You can't?
You, uh, put it in drive,
and you-you press the pedal.
- I can't do another one.
- We'll go to my restaurant,
put some food in you.
- No, man. I'm done.
- Okay.
Then drop me at the club.
We'll get an early start
in the morning.
- I gotta be paid up by now.
- Fair enough.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I need us all on the same page.
- So can I have
my old job back?
- You get some rest.
Come by tomorrow.
I'll see what I can do.
- Appreciate that.
- Hello?
- In the kitchen.
[light clattering]
So, what's a better closer?
Turkey pinwheels
or pigs in a blanket?
- Both classics.
- So is this place, right?
You want one?
- What am I doing here?
- Either you are in the market
for a three-bedroom
fixer-upper,
or you want out of
the contract.
- You have your money.
- This is why
I don't do jilted lovers.
- Why do you care?
- Unless I go through with it,
you're a liability.
- I'm not gonna tell anyone.
- Cross your heart?
- Yes. Whatever.
- I'd feel a lot better
if you were an accomplice.
- You don't have to do it.
- Just can't live
without him, huh?
- Believe me, that has nothing
to do with this.
- You're not his only
side dish, you know.
- I just need him alive, okay?
- You cut a deal.
- It's complicated.
- Where are they putting you?
- I don't know.
- Usually it's Indiana or Iowa.
- I haven't put
a lot of thought into it.
- Nevada.
- Why does it matter?
- You could have had Fiji.
You traded in
for a cul-de-sac.
- I have a family.
- I thought you were special.
- I'm a mom.
- Just what the world needs.
[footsteps approach]
- Excuse me.
Is-is this the open house?
- Let me give you the tour.
- What are you gonna do?
- My job.
Why don't we begin upstairs?
[light music]
♪
- Thanks, bro.
- Know what I used to do
before I met you?
- Heroin and hookers.
- So obvious.
Carpools sucked.
Class parent is excruciating,
and don't even get me started
on the cookies.
- Minute in the sack,
never take it back, huh?
- They want you.
- Feds?
- Secret Service.
- Mm. [small laugh]
Yeah, I figured one
of 'em was coming.
- Yeah.
- They're taking care of you?
- Full package.
- Good.
I'm worth it.
Quite a situation we got.
- Always.
Well, what's it gonna be?
- If I have to make
one more cookie, I will die.
He runs the whole thing.
- Don't look it.
- Trust me.
He's the Big Kahuna.
- Who else knows about this?
- It's off the books.
- What's his name?
- Dave.
You sure about this?
- Only way it goes away.
- Give her the bottle.
[mellow music continues
in background]
♪
.
- Hey.
- What's up?
- Who are you?
- Security.
- Is that my lasagna?
- I don't know.
- That's my Tupperware.
- How would I know that?
- Is your name Stan Hill?
- What's your problem, man?
- What?
- Hey, can I ask you
some questions?
- Uh, yeah. Sure.
Is everything okay?
- Got a tip about a guy
robbing a dry cleaner
over in Hazel Park.
- Oh, yeah, I wouldn't know
anything about that.
- You fit the description.
- What, a brother
with a tight fade
with some gray in his beard?
Come on, now.
[laughs]
- Oh good,
you found each other.
- Gene, help me out here, man.
I'm being profiled over here.
- Can I see your hands,
please, sir?
- Now why is that?
- They said the guy went
all aggro on the register.
- You know anything
about this, Stan?
- No.
It's some kind of tip.
- Well, show him.
- Why are you doing this?
- Can I see your hands,
please, sir?
- When did you say this was?
- Two nights ago.
- Was that, uh, Thursday?
- Yeah.
- Hey, you know what?
You got the wrong guy.
We had a bachelor party
that night. Right?
- Yeah. Yeah.
I was working the back room.
- You got video of it?
- I'm sure I could
dig something up.
- I'd sure like to see it.
- My guy'll send it over.
We good?
- I appreciate your assistance.
- In the car in ten.
We got a long night.
- Mom? Mom.
I can see you.
- Hey. What are you doing here?
- It's my school.
Did you see the game?
- Dude, you were so good.
You scored like 20 goals.
- Three.
- Yeah, but last time
you only scored two.
- One.
- Well, penalty shot
should have counted.
- How many games
have you been to?
- You know, like, one or two,
or a couple, a bunch.
All of them.
- You could have told me.
- I just love high school
sporting events, you know?
I didn't even realize
it was your team, frankly.
- Mom.
- I just--I didn't
want you to feel like
you had to acknowledge
your number one fan, you know?
- Yo, Marks.
both: Yeah?
- He means me.
- Tight.
- We're going for ice cream.
- All right,
well, does Dad know?
Cool. Have fun.
- Do you want to come?
Some of the other parents
will be there.
- You know, I'd love to,
but I-I have a--
it's like a thing.
- Next time?
- For sure.
- Later, loser.
- So long, sucker.
- ♪ Do do do do do
♪ Do do do
do do ♪
♪ Do do--
- Eew!
- Okay, dinner.
- Dad lets us eat here.
- We eat at the table.
- We don't have a table.
- Got a counter.
Jane, put that down.
Come eat.
Don't...you dare.
[Echo and the Bunnymen's
"Ocean Rain"]
- ♪ At sea again
♪ And now my hurricanes
♪ Have brought down
this ocean rain ♪
♪ To bathe me again
♪
♪ My ship's a-sail
♪ Can you hear
its tender frame ♪
♪ Screaming
from beneath the waves ♪
♪ Screaming from beneath
the waves ♪
♪
[Beth inaudible]
♪ All hands on deck at dawn
♪ Sailing to sadder shores
♪ Your port
in my heavy storms ♪
♪ Harbors the blackest
thoughts ♪
♪
♪ My ship's a-sail
♪ Can you hear
its tender frame ♪
♪ Screaming
from beneath the waves ♪
♪ Screaming from beneath
the waves ♪
♪ From beneath the waves
[inaudible]
♪ All hands on deck at dawn
♪ Sailing to sadder shores
♪ Your port
in my heavy storm ♪
♪ Harbors
the blackest thoughts ♪
- How you wanna do this?
Ha. Y'all don't
mess around, huh?
- Just business.
- Mm-hmm.
- May I?
I didn't think
she had it in her.
Gotta be careful with
a woman like her.
You never know
what they're thinking.
- Don't. Don't do that.
Later, Dave.
- Dave?
[gunshot]
- When's Daddy coming home?
- Soon.
.
- And, funny enough, he
actually invited me this time.
But--
- Okay. That's good.
- But I-I let him
go by himself.
- Maybe you'll go next time.
- Yeah, maybe.
I actually got you something.
- What?
- Here.
It's just a little...
little gift.
- Is that--
- It's a monarch.
I got him with my wiper.
- Lovely.
- It's for your collection.
- Very thoughtful.
- And kind of a goodbye.
- Okay.
- Like a toodle-oo.
- See you next week.
- It's more of a forever
toodle-oo.
- You're quitting?
- I'm cured.
- Just like that?
- Yeah, well, you're that good.
- Annie.
- You can't make someone
like you.
- I know where we can move.
- We still dreaming?
- Wyoming.
- Like, the place with cowboys
and rodeos and stuff?
- And a super low tax rate,
hardly any crime.
One of the few places that
can boast unspoiled nature.
- And no black folks.
- Not true.
- Really?
- Kanye.
- He's up in Wyoming?
- The ranch.
- Psshh...
Ahh...
- What's your problem?
- I gotta get up
in a few hours.
- Can't humor me a little?
- You know what?
I'd rather stay here.
- For the rest of our lives?
- At least I know
what I'm up against.
- Looks legit.
- So you approve?
- Who made it?
- Alexander Hamilton.
- You dug up an old white guy?
- No, but we both know how hard
it is to find a good artist,
so I'm not gonna tell you.
- Fair enough.
- And I obviously
can't wash it anymore.
- Spa business
ain't what it used to be?
- They seized everything.
- All of it?
- Yes, even yours.
- Bummer.
- I'll take a smaller cut.
- Nah. We're cool.
- Really?
- Yeah. You earned it.
Oh, one thing, though.
- What's that?
- Your kahuna?
He wasn't looking
to put me away.
- What do you mean?
- He was looking
to put me down.
- They--must have been out
of options, or--
- Hmm.
I must have been
all they had.
- Yeah, maybe.
[Harden Trio's
"Tippy Toeing"]
♪
- ♪ Well, mama come
a-tippy tippy toein' ♪
♪ Through the house
♪ Gotta see what's the matter
with the baby ♪
♪ It's been a-bawlin'
and a-squalin' ♪
♪ And kickin' on the wall
♪ I know what's the matter
with the baby ♪
♪ We know what's
the matter with the baby ♪
♪ Well I hear the clock
a-ringin' ♪
♪ Just a-dongin'
and a-dingin' ♪
♪ Daddy go and make
a little money maybe ♪
- ♪ Mama sleep
a little longer ♪
♪ But remember
while I'm gone ♪
♪ Please take good care
of the baby ♪
♪ After all, he's just
a little bitty baby ♪
♪