.
- Previously on
"Good Girls"...
- All you have to do
is print and drop.
Your husband's here.
- My wife was laundering
a gang's money
through my business.
Danny's in the hospital.
Can you go be with him?
- Sort of out of the country.
- I just woke up.
- About time.
- I want you out of her life.
- You get us in that club,
and she'll never see me again.
- What'd you say to her,
Stanley?
- We made a deal.
- I'm a building inspector
with Wayne County.
You folks got yourself
a load of violations.
- We came up
with some creative solutions.
What do you think?
-
- You said all we had to do
was print it.
- And then drop it.
- I assumed that you meant
in our country.
- I don't like this SUV.
- Every time we make a move,
he does too.
- Turn, turn!
- Annie!
- Grab the money.
- What are we doing?
- Getting rid of it.
- Put it all on two.
- Oh, thank God.
- Lady Luck ain't on your side
tonight, huh?
You got a guardian angel
I don't know about?
- Maybe.
- At the Women in IT Awards
in 2017,
which fictional character
did the head of MI-6
reveal is actually female?
- Mm, Q.
- Mark from Ohio,
let's see what you said.
- Come on.
- M.
- Oi, you idiot.
It's Q.
- Austin in consumer
marketing, you said Q.
- Yes.
You're the man, Austin.
- Okay, here comes
another question.
- Hey.
- Do you still have
my mini blender?
- What mini blender?
- The one that you borrowed
to make piña coladas
with your Wi-Fi neighbor.
- No, I gave that back to you.
- Well, I can't find it.
- Maybe you loaned it
to someone else.
- No one else
borrows a blender.
- So maybe you lost it.
- Where would I lose it, Annie?
- I guess if you knew that,
it wouldn't be lost,
would it, Beth?
- Can you please just look?
- Chillax, I'm looking.
I'm looking.
Okay, let's see.
Looking and I'm looking.
Nope, don't see it.
- It's red with a black lid.
- Silver button?
- Yep.
- White cord?
- Yeah, I think so.
- Dishwasher-safe?
- Do you have it?
- I'll keep looking.
- All right, well,
if you find it,
can you bring it
by here tomorrow?
- What time?
- Early.
- I have work.
- Before that.
- Why do you need it?
- It doesn't matter.
It's mine!
- Yeah, except that when I
borrow something from you,
I have to bring it back,
but when you borrow something
from me,
I still have to bring it back.
- I just have a lot going on
tomorrow, okay?
- I have a job.
- So do I.
- Since when?
- It's called
raising four children.
Okay.
You know what?
That's fine.
I just won't take Ben to school
or have money
to give him for lunch,
because I'll have to skip work
so your husband
who is on house arrest
can have his nutritious
morning smoothie.
- I thought you didn't have it.
- That's if I have it.
Jesus.
I thought it was trash day.
Excuse me,
I mean date night with Angela.
- Who's Angela?
Get your coat.
- Why?
- 'Cause you'll be cold.
- Cold 'cause I'm dead?
- Your shoes too.
- My son's gonna be home
any minute.
- Mm-hmm.
We should probably hustle then,
huh?
- Gonna wonder where I am.
- Yeah, that's kinda the point.
No.
Don't do that.
- And time
for another question.
For Canada's centennial,
what gift did Elizabeth II
give Ottawa six pairs of
from the Rideau river?
- Swans.
After you.
- Tom from Boise.
- Swans?
- Tell me when.
It's gonna be all chocolate.
- Okay, when, when.
How about some OJ?
- How about a Coke?
- Okay, one Coke.
- Can I have one?
- Not for breakfast, honey.
- That's not fair.
- Just be grateful
you have two working wrists.
- Okay.
- Yes!
- Don't break anything.
- Dad, look what I got.
- Nice.
- Hey, have you seen my phone?
- Yeah, you left it
in the bathroom.
- Oh.
- Hey, where is
the mini blender?
- Annie has it, which is why
she won't text me back.
- Oh, great.
What's on tap for you today?
- Carpool.
- Is that what
they're calling it now?
- What's that mean?
- Hmm.
You gonna drop off kids
or cash?
- Kids.
- Hmm, then what?
- Some laundry.
- Hmm, are you gonna
wash clothes or cash?
- Clothes.
- Hmm, just wondering
what to expect today.
- Just some errands.
- In what country?
- What are you doing?
Daddy's just kidding.
Okay, you guys.
Go brush your teeth.
- But I'm not done.
- You can take it with you.
- Let's go.
Vámonos.
- Nothing's going on right now,
okay?
- That's what you said
when you were overseas.
- It was just Canada.
- While our son
was in the E.R. alone.
- That won't happen again.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hey.
I got nothing.
- Did you go through her phone?
- Yeah, she deletes them all.
- Well, that's not gonna help.
- Well, what about the fact
that she ran a crime ring
through my hot tub store?
- That's the problem.
It was yours.
- Yeah, you need something
that's hers.
- What about the fake
Canadian money she's printing?
- On the press that you built.
- Look, I read her emails.
I tore through her car.
I even dug around
in her underwear drawer.
There's nothing.
- Does she keep a journal?
- Can't you find some kind
of legal loophole?
- Not with a case like yours.
- I thought you were the best.
- He'll keep you out of prison.
- Great.
- But the day they cut
that thing off your ankle,
who's gonna be celebrating?
- Me.
- Her.
- 'Cause she got away
with using you
like one of those period cups.
- Oh, Jesus.
- Don't put a stop to it now.
She's gonna be using you
again and again and again.
- This isn't about your case,
man.
- Then what's it about?
- It's about sewing
your sack back on.
- Right now, you don't even
need that seat on your bike.
- He's right.
Here.
Just sit on the post.
- Guys.
- There you go.
- Yeah, sit on the post.
- Give me my bike seat.
- Nah, you don't need it, Dean.
- I hear you, okay?
- Then give us something
we can use.
- Come on, Dean.
Mmm.
Hey, bud.
- Have you seen my mom?
- Did you try homeless guy?
- He's at his girlfriend's
all the time.
- What about the therapist?
- She's over him.
- I'm gonna call your dad.
- He wouldn't know.
They're in Minnesota
visiting Nancy's parents.
- I'm sure she's fine.
- Hey, Aunt Beth.
- She left her phone?
- It was just in the kitchen.
- Was there anything missing?
- There's nothing to take.
Maybe you should call
the police.
- You know...
I think I might know
who she's with.
- Don't forget to subtract
the cost of goods.
- And what's that?
- It's the cost of everything
that goes into
selling the bags.
- Okay.
- Hey.
What are y'all doing?
- Business.
- Teaching baby girl
accounting.
- Um, so this is
Aunt Beth's pile,
this Annie's, and this is ours.
- Mm-hmm.
Had a good week.
You wanna do the deliveries?
- I'm gonna need all of it.
- That an expense or a loan?
- Just straight-up theft, baby.
- What's this?
- First installment.
- We'll get the rest.
- Oh, I know you will.
- Give her back.
- Okay.
- Where should I send
the first installment?
- What do you want?
- You know how much of my money
you left in that casino?
All of it.
- All of it.
I guess we'll call it even.
- I don't want to be even.
- She ain't worth much more
than that.
Not sure how we'll use her.
We'll think of something.
- Oh, Jesus.
- I want my sister back!
- Do you?
Finish the job then.
.
Don't forget me
when I'm gone
- Regular or double stuff?
- What?
- Which one?
- I don't know.
I have loved you
for so long
- You can try.
Everyone tries.
- Double stuff.
- You want Chex Mix or Cheetos?
- Chex Mix.
- Uh, grab some Skittles,
would you?
- I don't like Skittles.
- They're not for you.
There's so much
for me to do
- I'll go grab water.
Sparkling or regular?
- Sparkling.
when I'm gone
Hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
See that guy I'm with?
Don't look.
He's kidnapping me.
- These are two for one.
- I'm good.
Except for the fact that
I'm being kidnapped by him.
So make an excuse;
go call the cops, please.
Run.
Quick.
- Hey, bro.
- What's up?
How's your Moms?
- You always worry.
You should stop by.
- Yeah, I definitely will.
Um, let me get a couple
of those Slurpee cups.
- I don't want a Slurpee.
- It's not for that.
- Huh?
- Yeah, we got a long ride
ahead of us.
- Ma'am.
Ma'am, he's not available.
- I want you to look into...
- This is how you serve
your community?
- I'm in a meeting here.
- By looking the other way?
- I didn't think
it was something
we could discuss over texts--
- "Of the people" my ass.
Okay.
Can we have the room, please?
Thank you.
What do you want me to do?
- I want you to help me
get her back!
- Not so easy.
- Why not?
- I can't be anywhere
near that.
- Oh, so now he's not
your brother or whatever?
- It's political suicide, Beth.
- What he will do to my sister
is far worse, trust me.
- Detroit Police.
- Councilman Martín
for the Chief.
- One moment.
- I can't.
- Why not?
- You know why.
- Not so easy, is it?
- It's not my job;
that's the problem.
- Tell that to your sister.
- It's him.
- I--I got Chief Gorski
on line one.
- Tell him "false alarm."
- See, it's not only
for your face.
It's also a whole-body oil.
- What's this have to do
with fantasy football?
- Well, yeah,
but first things first.
Look.
- Can we just talk
about our picks?
- Yeah, as soon as we talk
about your dermis.
- Listen, I got my own system.
- But you're using
Brawn and Beauty?
- Brother,
this is soap and water.
- Oof.
That is a dangerous road,
my friend.
- Yeah, so are these dudes
that you're in with.
- Nah, it's not like that.
- No?
What's it like?
- It's like a brotherhood.
- The kind with the Nikes
and the aliens?
- Look, they're just--
they're just trying to keep me
out of jail, that's all.
- How?
- You know, legal advice,
and they know how to work
the courts or whatever.
- And what's their angle?
- Beth.
- Wait, you're gonna sell out
your own wife?
- I mean...
it's not like she ever
had my back.
- Whoa, no, no, no, no.
Hold on.
- What, she just gets
to destroy my family?
Why, 'cause she's the mom?
- She's not the only one
in this.
- Look, I will protect Ruby.
I promise.
- What if that's not up to you?
- That's why I have to make
sure it all sticks to Beth.
That's heavy, man.
- That's why I need your help.
- Uh, what can I do?
- You got eyes and ears.
If something doesn't, you know,
look or sound right,
just pass it along.
- Uh, even if I could--
- I know how close
you guys are.
- It's not that.
- But you don't do anything,
you're gonna be wearing
one of these things too.
- No, that's not my kinda look.
- Good thing is, I've...
got something
for the chafing.
- Can we please
pick our teams now?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- Who's gonna do the holograms?
- I don't know.
- 'Cause I don't do that.
- I'll do it.
- You do the color.
- I can do both.
- It'll take twice as long.
- We'll figure it out.
- I just talked to her
last night.
- You talk to her every night.
- I accused her of stealing
my blender, which she denied,
and so I thought
she really did it,
and then she got defensive,
so then it turned into this
whole passive-aggressive thing,
which it is always does,
that had nothing to do with
the blender in the first place.
- You're gonna get
your blender back.
- Just maybe not right away.
.
- It went back to the city.
- How?
- It says he owes
a bunch of property taxes.
- Sounds like Gene.
- He's gonna lose a whole club
over, like,
9 grand?
- Sounds like Gene.
All you gotta do
is pay his back taxes.
- What, like, first dibs?
- Yeah, city doesn't want
to get stuck with that dump.
- Well, we don't have enough
anyway.
- Family first, right?
- Hey.
Whatcha doing?
- Couldn't sleep.
- You want a snack?
- I already housed
all your chips.
- I can get more tomorrow.
- Thanks.
- Okay.
Good night.
- Aunt Beth?
- Yeah?
- Was she always like this?
What do you mean?
- Just, like, drops everything
to run off to Mackinac
with some rando.
- Well, I don't know
how rando he is.
- I've never met him.
- Maybe she didn't want
to bring him around
until it was serious, you know?
- I mean, she just does
whatever she wants
whenever she wants.
- Well,
that's totally your mom.
- So not cool.
- She's very impulsive...
- Yeah.
- Not the most responsible.
- Like, at all.
- She's a train wreck.
- Yeah.
- But you know that's what
makes her so great, right?
- Huh?
- When we were little,
life was kind of a bummer,
but she found a way
to make it all fun.
- Like how?
- Like, a million
different ways, but...
so we never went anywhere
for spring break, right?
And one year she decided
that we should spend the night
in the camping section
at Target.
- Did you get caught?
- Yes, we got caught.
But she also convinced
the security guard
to order us a pizza
and let us watch
"Fried Green Tomatoes"
in the home theater section.
- She makes me watch that
every spring break.
- She can turn anything
into a party.
- Literally.
- She just doesn't know
when to leave.
I wish I was more like her,
honestly.
- Is this new guy cool?
He thinks he is.
- At least she's having fun.
- Yeah.
Get some sleep, bud.
Almost heaven,
West Jamaica
- Hit me.
- I think you've had enough.
- One more.
- I'm not doing nothing again.
- I can't do it.
- Try.
- It's too dangerous
while I'm driving.
- It's upsetting.
- Don't make me pull over.
How much longer?
- Stop asking.
- Then tell me.
- You'll know
when we get there.
- You know, you are making
a big mistake.
- Look, you think
I wanna be here?
- It's your job.
- It's my day off.
- Well, whatever.
Then your boss
is making a huge mistake.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
'Cause good luck making money
without me.
My my lady, swingin'
through the water, water
painted on the sky
tears gone from my eyes
- What makes you so important?
- I basically do everything.
I'm, like, the brains
behind the operation.
- He doesn't see it that way.
- Well,
then he's sorely mistaken,
because I basically do it all.
I--I do.
I'm the one who--
I do the blender thing,
and I do the holograph,
the shiny part.
That's me as well.
I'm the one cuts
the sheets into bills.
- That doesn't sound hard.
- Oh, it doesn't?
Well, it is hard.
Do you think people are buying
sheets of money?
No, because it wouldn't fit
into their wallet!
It has to be cut!
here we go
come on
- You know who the really
important people are?
- The ones who
don't have to tell you
how important they are.
- Sidwell number
09-875-688-4.
14-unit apartment building.
Back taxes of $21,800.
Do I have any bids?
- Okay, moving on.
Sidwell number
02-467-8895-3.
Banquet hall,
back taxes of $12,482.
- Right here.
- Any other bids?
Pick up your title at the table
and pay the cashier.
- Oh, my God.
Ruby, hi.
I didn't know
you were in real estate.
- I'm not.
We, uh--
- We're paying a tax bill.
- Yeah.
- What do you guys do?
- Hey, great bag.
- Oh, she's the one
with the hookup.
- Her son's a mathlete
with Harry.
- Oh.
- By the way, how did Barnaby
Prep kill us at semifinals?
- I keep telling Harry,
"You can't win
until you learn how to lose."
- Well, they're gonna learn
real fast
if they keep getting
those quadratic equations.
- Sidwell number
82-667-823-09.
Crap.
- Adult entertainment center,
back taxes of $9,172.
Do I have a--
- Here.
- Any other bids?
- $9,200.
I didn't see this one.
- $9,300?
- Yes.
- $9,400.
That's all we have.
- Do I hear $9,500?
- You already have one!
- It's just such a steal.
- Yeah, from us.
- Well, you can't win
until you learn how to lose.
- Anyone else?
Anyone?
Pay the cashier.
- See you at school.
- Your bag's a fake.
- Okay, moving on.
Sidwell number...
.
- Morning, sunshine.
What are we doing here?
- Paying our respects.
- To who?
The cast of "Cocoon"?
- Skittles.
- Oh, my God.
- He helps old people?
- I don't know about that,
but he won't steal from them
no more.
Now can I please
have my Skittles?
Sit tight.
- Hey, where is he?
- Out back.
- Hey, big-time.
- Hard at work, huh?
- Love what you do,
never work a day in your life.
- You're not making things
easy for me.
- Nope.
- What are you thinking?
- Had to do what I had to do.
- Oh.
Oh, that's playing
it smart?
- Ball.
See, while y'all
are over there planting trees
or doing
whatever the hell you're doing,
I'm losing money.
- What about the position
you put me in?
- Aw, you have a lovers' spat?
- I was making progress.
- My money can't wait.
See that's always
been your problem.
You never were
a big-picture guy.
- 'Cause I don't see it
your way, right?
No.
You never did.
It's like they say....
- What's that?
- Keep your eye on the ball.
- You know what else they say?
- I feel like
you're gonna tell me.
- Hit them where it hurts.
- I hope you're right.
- Ball.
- Later, brother.
-
- You hear that?
- The motorcycle?
- No, not that.
- I don't hear anything.
- Exactly.
Because Annie's not
in the back seat
asking us if we'd rather die
of a 1,000 bee stings
or be mauled by a bear.
- That one's her fave.
- Yeah, 'cause she thinks
there's a right answer.
- Bees.
- The bear.
'Cause eventually you go numb,
and you don't feel it anymore.
- The bear's way faster.
- Not if starts at your feet
and works its way up.
- What if the bees decide
to sting you one at a time?
- Like they're waiting in line
at the DMV?
- If she was here,
she would settle it.
- No, she'd tell us
we were both wrong.
- It's just weird
not having her around.
- It'd be weird
not having you around either.
- He told you?
- You should never have had
to make that deal.
- Come on.
- Seriously.
- No boy's gonna break us up.
- Say you were allergic
to bees...
- Fine.
Bees.
Now let's go get Annie back.
- Okay.
- She's here right now.
Yep, replace the floors,
a little paint,
this place will be up
and running in 30 days.
Gotta call you back.
- How's it all looking?
- Better than my knockoff bag.
- Mm.
- 'Cause we don't think this
is the right place for you.
- I'm gonna need a refund
by the way.
- You know how they say
a space chooses you?
- This one chose us.
- You're not a right fit.
What's this?
- Our offer.
- To take it off your hands.
- Well, this is way less
than I paid.
- Yeah, we're trying to get it
for a steal.
- All set in here.
- I can't do this right now.
My inspector's here.
- Quite a place you got here.
- Right?
- I used to get my groove on
back in the day.
- Right?
Well, now it's gonna be
a dog hotel.
- Aw, might be cheaper to house
them at the Four Seasons.
- Excuse me?
- Plumbing, electrical, ADA,
I gotta dock you for all of it.
- What?
That's ridiculous.
- Oh, yeah,
I'm just getting started.
Fire suppression, asbestos,
and I don't know
what you got going on
with that tinkler back there.
It's all gotta go.
- Excuse me, ma'am.
You dropped this.
- Oh.
Sweet of you, hon.
- Mm-hmm.
- My mom found me this morning
in our driveway.
- I've never seen this guy
in my life.
- You bashed my face in.
- I don't know
what he's talking about.
- Look at his hand.
- I cut it shaving.
- Your knuckles?
- She knows,
she was in his car.
She saw the whole thing.
- Ma'am, do you know this guy?
- Yeah.
.
- Were you with him last night?
Did you witness anything?
- Yeah.
First-degree murder.
- Pardon?
- Of my vagina.
- What's that now?
- Kinda like Lizzie Borden
with the hatchet,
except the hatchet it his--
- So he didn't assault
this man?
Trust me, officer, he wouldn't
have had the energy.
- Oh, my God.
She's lying.
- We haven't even left
our motel room in days.
- You sure you don't have
the wrong guy?
- Who else would look like him?
- A lot of people say I look
like the guy
from "Lord of the Rings."
Baby, I'm starving.
Let's go get
our electrolytes up.
Are we free to go or what?
- How'd she do?
- Well, Megan Thee Stallion
called,
and she's
her new backup dancer.
- Um, no, she's gonna be
my backup dancer.
- Ah, okay.
- Go wash up.
It's taco night.
- How'd it go?
- We're back in the club.
- I knew you'd get it.
- I gotta go print.
Make sure Harry doesn't eat
all the taco shells.
So, uh, whose name is it in?
Ah, she's not going anywhere
is she?
- Nuh-uh.
- Mm, family first, huh?
- Now you're getting it, Hill.
Okay.
- Good to see you.
- Bye.
- Bye, babe.
I knew it.
No, thanks.
- For back there.
- Oh.
- Running would've
made more sense.
- Well...
we couldn't have you
getting arrested
in front of your grandpa,
could we?
- Not my grandpa.
- Well, then who is he?
- We called him the janitor.
- Oh, no.
- Did cleanup.
- Cleanup?
- Anything that needed
to be dissolved...
- Okay.
- Then flushed.
- Got it.
- But he was like a grandpa.
- That's sweet.
- The kinda guy you want
to do things for.
Like that sister of yours.
- It's not the same thing.
- Mm.
How can one bitch have
such a hold on so many people?
- She's not all that.
- Then why are we both here?
- Let's call the ladies.
- He should've taken me.
- He never will.
- I need career advice.
- No, no, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, okay.
What about--
what about, uh, uh, lip balm?
- Oh, forget lip balm.
- No, lip balm sells.
- You, dude.
- Yeah?
- Yes.
- You gotta have lip balms.
- What do you think, man?
- I think I got something
on her.
.