You wish to acquire
a company called Sliceline?
I will be taking on
a total engineering team
of about 50.
I just have to go back
into my office.
(RETCHES, COUGHS)
Well we thought the best way
to introduce the PiperNet
would be through
the eight developers.
COLIN: I have been cooking up
a killer new game.
The Gates of Galloo.
We put this thing
on PiperNet...
Bam, 80,000 instant users.
Partnering with a company
of that size,
this early, would put us
months ahead.
Knock 'em dead, Richard.
Whatever you are doing,
stop it now.
Um, yeah, we're just
high-fiving.
Bye.
You need to make a deal
with my companies.
Taking existing companies
and just calling them new
isn't sophisticated,
that's theft.
JARED DUNN:
So they're manufacturing phones
and signing them
onto our network.
Why would they wanna help us?
They're not helping us,
they're attacking us.
-It's the 51 percent attack.
-I'm sorry, what?
-A 51 percent--
-(ICE RATTLES)
We've been exploring
the viability
of an acquisition
with Amazon.
You expect me to work
for Jeff Bezos?
No way.
I happen to know that
they fucked you over.
How would you like
to fuck them back?
I need you to attack me.
-A second attack.
-RICHARD HENDRICKS: Yes.
COLIN: Boom, you just got
80,000 new users.
Colin, you did it,
you saved us.
Gilfoyle, the patch.
Bombs away.
(CHEERING)
Oh, my God.
These are our new offices?
We're actually
right through here.
What do you guys think?
Do you want to see
the second floor?
HENDRICKS:
There's another floor? Okay.
(HEAVING)
Whoa.
DUNN:
I know, it's exciting, right?
♪ (MUSIC PLAYS, CONCLUDES) ♪
♪ ♪
Here we are,
right here to the left.
I like your tie.
Oh, thank you.
I tied it myself.
Oh...
Okay.
Well, good luck.
-(crowd murmuring)
-(camera shutters snapping)
(murmuring continues)
(gavel bangs)
Mr. Hendricks,
thank you for being here.
For the last three hours,
we've been asking
some prominent members
of your industry
questions about the security
of their users' data.
And while the gentlemen from
Facebook, Google, and Amazon
have acknowledged some
egregious lapses in the past--
And Hooli, sir.
Hooli also acknowledged
some spectacular
lapses.
Yes.
As I was saying,
these fine folks have
been assuring us all that
their oversights
are behind them,
and that they
are the best people
to protect
their users' privacy.
But my colleague,
Senator Shizaki
of the great state of Hawaii,
suggested that you might
have a different view.
Senator?
Thank you,
Chairman Hubbard.
Mr. Hendricks and his
company, Pied Piper,
are developing
a pilot program to deliver
wireless Internet
to my constituents
on the island of Maui.
I have asked him to deliver
a statement here today.
Mr. Hendricks?
Yes.
Mr. Hendricks, now would be
the time for that statement.
Okay.
I probably should've
gotten these out before.
He looks like a child
in a custody hearing.
But, like,
you don't feel
sorry for him.
You just want him to go away
-and not have
any parents at all.
-(Richard speaking indistinctly)
Hello,
I am Richard Hendricks,
CEO of Pied Piper.
There you go.
-Eye contact.
-I'm proud to tell you
that we are working
with Senator Shizaki...
-Good.
-...on developing
the first step
in providing a new
type of Internet
to the world. Oh...
-Hold on.
-(papers rustling)
Uh, basically,
it-it is a program...
that i-i-it's kinda...
Actually, can I pace? I-I just
think better on my feet.
So, a lot of people...
(inaudible)
Senator Kleco:
Mr. Hendricks!
Speak into the machine!
Oh! Okay.
I'm sorry. Does this come out?
Perfect.
-(whispers): Fuck.
-Richard (on TV): Okay, so,
these people up here, right?
You want to rein them in,
but you can't.
Uh, Facebook owns
80% of mobile social traffic.
Google owns 92% of search,
and Amazon Web Services
is bigger than their next
four competitors combined.
And they will be
even more robust
once the Hooli merger
is complete.
Richard:
Ah, see! Look, there!
Even Hooli can't survive
these monopolies.
No one can!
They track our every move,
they monitor every
moment in our lives,
and-and they exploit
our data for profit.
(laughs) And you can ask them
all the questions you want,
but they're not gonna change,
they don't have to.
These companies are kings,
and they rule over
kingdoms far larger
than any nation
in human history.
They won, we lost.
So, why are you here?
Because look at where we are.
-Yeah? We are in the seat
of the US government--
-Mr. Hendricks?
I'm okay. I've got it now.
We are in the seat
of the US government,
a government that
was founded by people
who were, at one point,
ruled by kings
they couldn't overthrow.
So, what did they do, right?
They started over.
They came here,
to the New World.
-World 2.0, version 1776.
-(murmuring)
And the way we win
is by creating a new,
democratic,
decentralized Internet,
one where the behavior
of companies like this
will be impossible, forever.
One where it is the users,
not the kings,
who have sovereign
control over their data.
This, I promise to you:
I will help you end this tyranny
by building an Internet that is
of the people, by the people,
and for the people,
so help me God.
-(laughing)
-(cheering)
-Dinesh: Yeah!
-(applause)
Whoo!
All: Whoa!
(theme music playing)
♪ ♪
No, Mike, I just--
-Huh? There he is!
-Uh--
King slayer! How was it?
-Good. I-I-- I, um...
-You can go.
-I got it...
-Yeah, I mean, I think
it went pretty well.
I mean, you saw it, right?
Of course,
but I-I-I want to hear
you tell me everything,
every detail.
Holden...
The man just
got off the plane,
give him some space!
Jesus...
Okay, so you
touch down at Dulles,
you turn off airplane mode,
and then--
Well, actually, we flew
through Reagan National.
(car starts)
Reagan?
But you love trams.
(scoffs) Well...
See, this is why I should
still be handling your travel.
Oh, don't worry about it,
Jared, you're busy.
I'm never too busy for you.
-But let's... let's not get
caught up in that, right?
-Right.
We're here now,
and we're walking,
and we're talking.
I mean, take it all in,
my friend.
Look at all this.
Can you believe we began
our journey way back...
in that little living room
in the hostel?
And just yesterday,
you addressed our nation's most
hallowed, powerful legi--
All:
Surprise!
♪ Too legit
Too legit to quit ♪
♪ Too legit... ♪
Jared:
Anyway, like I was
saying out there,
we started out
in that little hostel,
just a couple of kids.
-Richard: Yeah.
-Jared: Right?
-And now--
-You killed it, Richard!
Way to punch
big tech in the dick!
Jared: I was just gonna say,
let's-- let's take a moment
to let it soak in, right?
-Look what you've built!
-Uh-huh.
Okay, I'll let you go now!
Enjoy the party!
Your compression algorithm
was the stardust!
♪ ♪
Hey, Richard! Richard!
Come here.
Stand here.
Congratulations
from Team Dinesh!
Yeah.
("Aloha Friday" playing)
(cheering)
♪ It's Aloha Friday! ♪
♪ I'm going to Hawaii! ♪
-Richard: Okay, um--
-♪ Bah-doopy-doo! ♪
Congratulations.
♪ Bah-doopy-doopy-doopy doo! ♪
-♪ It's Aloha Friday! ♪
-Uh...
♪ Setting up the island's
first decentralized Meshnet ♪
Richard:
Uh, "You...
licked ass?"
-What?
-"You dicked ass"?
-I-I dicked ass?
-Dinesh: Kicked ass!
-Kicked!
-Oh.
Why were those your
first two guesses?
-(stops music)
-Gabe, what the fuck?!
-You're the K! Where's the K?
-K's right there.
-Dinesh: Kicked has two Ks!
-Hey. (chuckles)
-Ha.
-That's for you.
Oh, uh, I'm trying to get
some work done today.
I-I just wanted to toast.
Okay. So...
Don't worry, it's short.
The word companion
derives from
the Latin word
"panis" for bread,
and while I can
no longer digest bread,
-I know that you
leaven my life--
-Colin: Richard!
Hey, man, you got a second?
Uh, yes, Colin.
No, I do. Um...
Sorry. Okay. Uh, cheers.
Saw you on TV.
You crushed it.
That king shit
was on point, man.
-I fucking love kings.
-Richard: Oh, yeah.
So listen, um,
did they swear you in?
Like, pull the whole
Johnny Law routine with you?
Were you under oath?
Uh, no.
Cool! Well,
that's a weight off.
-Why?
-Well,
you said all that stuff about
not collecting user data.
-Yes?
-But we are.
-I am.
-What?
But I'm doing
the right thing now
by telling you,
so I feel like--
I-I'm sorry, Colin.
How long have you been
collecting user data?
Sorta... the whole time.
But it's just
to improve
the quality of my gameplay.
I'm not using it to sell ads.
It doesn't fucking matter.
It goes against the principles
of this company. I mean...
Shit, I just lied to Congress.
No.
You said a lie to Congress,
but you didn't know
at the time, I guess.
Don't beat yourself up
about it, huh?
But going forward,
maybe stop saying that.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Or do say it.
I don't care.
Maybe it'll be like Google
saying "Don't be evil,"
or Facebook saying
"I'm sorry,
we'll do better,"
or me saying
" Gates of Galloo  does not
leave your headset mic open
and record everything you say.
Suck it."
Sweet fucking shit.
A-a-are you...
bugging people and storing
their private conversations
on my network?
Colin!
This stops, now.
It would really
be better for me
if you just stopped
lying about it,
'cause the game's
pretty boss.
No, no. I'm the boss,
and I'm telling you
that this is over, Colin.
-It's done.
-Agree to disagree.
I'm glad we had this talk.
(laughs) Can't believe
I was so nervous.
Congratulations.
Okay.
Monica:
Oh, Richard! Hey.
This is Sam Liccardo,
the mayor of San Jose.
(quietly):
There's a major
fucking problem.
Just meet me in my office
in two minutes. Act normal.
Sorry, just excuse me
for a second.
Hey, Jared!
Hey, Tracy!
-How's my favorite
human resource?
-I'm fine, thanks.
Did anyone mention our
plan to move your office?
We're thinking about
putting you closer
to biz dev and marketing.
But that's... all the way
back in the Hamelin Wing.
Yeah! Follow me,
I'll show you.
Um... Okay, it's just,
that's a little far from--
from Richard's office.
Yes, but you really
don't have any
day-to-day business
with Richard anymore.
I mean, we were just
walking and talking before.
Oh. Looks like
they're having a meeting.
I should probably--
It's just better
for office cohesion
if you sit near
your direct reports,
and that is biz dev
and marketing.
Yeah, no, you
mentioned that. It's--
it's an interesting idea,
but I just think that, um,
I think we should
check with Richard first
'cause I think he's gonna
want me a little bit closer.
Of course.
It's subject
to his approval.
-Okay.
-I've already emailed him.
I think once you see
the conference
room suites though,
you'll really fall in love.
-Okay. Yeah.
-Just right through here.
Well, I don't fall
in love with rooms.
So, how do we get rid
of this fucker?
Look, Richard, I don't like
this any more than you do,
but we can't
get rid of Colin.
He's our most profitable
developer by far.
-So what? We have
other developers.
-We do,
but they're all
entangled with Galloo  !
We worked really hard
to build a whole
ecosystem around it.
It's like if you
cancel a Warriors game,
you're not just
hurting the team,
but you're also hurting
the parking attendants,
and the T-shirt guys,
and the concessions.
Okay. Thank you, Monica,
for putting it into an analogy
that will resonate with me.
-Football.
-It's basketball.
-No, I know.
-Losing him is no
longer a simple thing.
So, what are you saying?
We just do nothing?
Richard,
he's not selling ads.
He's just using it to optimize
the performance of his game.
It's actually a fairly
elegant implementation.
What?
What?!
Hiroshima was an elegant
implementation.
-I don't think anyone
agrees with you on that.
-No, I'm saying,
just because it's successful,
doesn't mean it's good.
I mean, it goes against
everything we stand for.
I mean, if we start
collecting personal data
"just for the good stuff,"
I mean, next thing we know,
-we're fucking Facebook.
-Dinesh: Well,
for the record,
I would not mind
being fucking Facebook.
No. We gotta kick him off, okay?
There are 500 people out there
who believe in this company's
ethics and standards.
There are 532 people out there,
and someone
has got to pay for them.
Right now, it's Colin.
Ditching him would be
too complicated.
Dinesh:
You know what's not
too complicated?
Hawaii.
In Hawaii,
aloha means hello and goodbye.
They use the same word
to mean two things
that are the exact opposite.
That's awesome,
and I have a chance to go there
as long as Colin
is on our network.
Aloha.
So, Colin betrays us
and we just tolerate it?
Great.
This is the cost of working
with humans, Richard.
They suck.
Paul:
Gavin, after months
of protracted
negotiations,
I'm happy to say
that we've come
to final terms on
our sale to Amazon.
Merger. Continue.
Amazon has agreed to no layoffs,
and they'll even provide
retention bonuses for
a period of two years.
Uh, what about my role?
No change.
Essentially,
you'll still have
complete discretion over
all of your divisions
exactly as you
enjoy right now.
Full executive privileges.
Perksssss...
Well, congratulations,
Team Hooli!
Oh, um, about that.
Uh, that was their
one major stipulation.
From this point on,
all of our properties
will be rebranded.
-As-- as what?
-As Amazon!
What?
Hoover!
Bezos wants to just erase
the Hooli name from history?
Mr. Bezos simply felt
that the Hooli name had--
What were his
exact words?
Um "A...
stink."
Hoover, goddammit!
Stop it!
You can't just threaten
people with violence.
Go stand over there.
(sighs) You tell Bezos
we keep the Hooli name,
or he can go fuck himself
with his rocket ship.
What is
Amazon anyway?
Is it a river?
Is it a giant woman?
It's not clear. No.
We keep the name Hooli.
-That's a deal breaker.
-Denpok: Gavin,
is not Hooli more
than simply a name?
Is-is it not
the culture and the...
great products?
The liberal...
private aviation policy?
-No.
-You know that the board
-has decided to sell,
right, Gavin?
-You know what?
I've still got
friends in this town.
I'll put together
some investors.
Amazon can take
a chunk of our assets,
but Hooli will remain a viable
and independent entity,
even if we have to shed
a few divisions
and trim a little fat.
♪ ♪
(computer chimes)
(chimes)
Richard:
So, Dinesh thinks
this is you?
Gilfoyle:
Correct.
He's been messaging
with it all day
and he has
no idea it's an AI.
Well, we fooled a human.
I guess we just passed
the Turing test.
-Almost a human.
-(Dinesh laughing)
Fucking Gilfoyle.
We're friends.
You trained that
thing in a day?
No, I didn't train it.
Son of Anton did.
-Son of Anton?
-An homage to a fallen friend.
It's the name
that I've given
our new inference API.
He's indexing all of
PiperNet as we speak,
and he's starting
to recognize intent,
emotion, causality.
Hang on, wait. Uh...
Do you think you could
engineer Son of Anton
to index compressed
audio files?
Why would you
insult me like that?
He can do
whatever he wants.
Okay.
Uh, hey, Dinesh?
-Yes?
-Can I get the latest tech
specs from you, please?
I've already sent them
to you five times.
I don't really wanna
dig through my inbox.
Um, so if you sent it now,
it'll be on top.
-I'll wait.
-(chair clicks)
Wearable chair.
Sending now.
-(computer chimes)
-Okay. Thank you, Dinesh.
(chimes)
(laughing)
Gilfoyle just said--
♪ ♪
(chimes)
Um, Gilfoyle?
What the fuck is going on?
'Cause I just
texted you,
and you were-- Um,
we've been texting
back and forth all day.
Was that not you?
Complicated question.
Is your shadow you?
-Was that a bot?
-Yes.
So, I spent all day
chatting with a bot?
-Yes.
-You made an AI Gilfoyle?
-And I was talking to it?
Do you need the real me
for this conversation?
You can't just
fuck with people
and manipulate them
because you don't
have the decency
-to want to interact
with a coworker.
-(cell phone chimes)
Gabe wants to know
if he'll need a jacket
if he walks to lunch.
(phone chimes)
And if so,
can he borrow a jacket.
Look at him.
Fucking Gabe.
Hey, could you make me
an AI Dinesh?
♪ ♪
We are down
to the final few decisions
in our new baseline contract
for strategic developers.
Let me provide
some context on each
before providing
recommendations.
The first is how
indemnification will work,
given that our network
provides distributive storage.
The second is how licensing
and access fees
will be applied
to copyrighted
material given that
our network also
does not allow any
-tracking or user--
-Hey.
-Can you talk?
-Oh, hell yes.
Colin (on tape):
I charge all kinds of
shit to the investors.
I bought a Jet Ski,
I bought a snowmobile,
I bought a 10-pack
of piano lessons--
-(turns off tape)
-He flat-out admits
to embezzlement.
-Where'd you get this?
-Colin!
He's been storing
private conversations
on our network,
including his own.
Because he's got gaming
headsets everywhere.
At his office,
at his house, at his RV,
and they are live 24/7.
We have thousands of hours
of his private conversations.
You see, once I paired
the automagical Son of Anton
with my compression algorithm,
and gave it access
to Galloo Games' database,
it indexed it all
in less than 10 minutes,
and generated this.
(laughs) Jared,
this is a graph
of all of his
voice recordings,
clustered by keyword.
I mean, look at this.
He steals, uh,
he does drugs at work, uh,
he's even sleeping with
one of his investor's wives.
I mean, this guy
is dirty as a dog
and we got him! Cold!
Hold on. What-what are
you suggesting here?
Blackmail?
-No-- I-- no.
I... I don't--
-Richard,
what Colin
is doing is clearly,
and gobsmackingly, awful.
But we're supposed to be
the virtuous ones here,
and-and this is...
just plain wrong.
Yeah. Okay.
Yeah, I guess, yeah.
I guess you're right.
I'll think of something else.
-Yeah.
-I mean, he started it,
but I don't know.
Yeah. Yeah.
I don't know.
Okay. I don't know.
-Hey, Richard?
-Hmm?
Um, did Tracy happen
to talk to you
about moving my
office down here?
Yeah, she-- she mentioned it.
I approved it.
-Oh, you did?
-Yeah.
Okay, then.
Richard?
Um...
I mean, Colin lied
to you first...
about collecting data, right?
-Yes, he did.
-So,
even if this is wrong,
I suppose you could argue that
it's wrong in
the service of rightness.
Richard:
Yeah.
It's, um...
it's, uh, unethical
in the defense of ethics.
Uh, unjust in
the quest for justice.
It's like stealing
from your pimp
to pay for your
friend's appendectomy.
Yeah, a-and everyone else,
Monica, Dinesh, and Gilfoyle,
they're all just
perfectly content
with letting this guy shit
all over everything
we believe in.
But are we, Jared?
Richard...
let's go put a foot
in Colin's ass.
Colin (on tape):
Danny, don't be
a fucking bitch.
I'll get you the tanning bed.
I charge shit to
the investors all the time.
I put two grams of coke
on the company card
last week.  (snorts)
Aah, fuck.
You see, Colin,
we were able to break down
all of your misdeeds
by category,
including a catch-all
for personal embarrassment.
Masturbation, farts,
the one time
you said that
you could, if you wanted to,
get porn of your sister.
You get the gist.
Data collection.
Not so boss when
it happens to you,
is it, Colin?
-Holy shit.
-(chuckles)
I say, what time is it?
Uh... Where's my phone.
Uh, do you have a phone?
Do you have a phone?
It is
fuck you o'clock!
Seven, you say?
Oh! Well, hey,
isn't that the...
time your board is
meeting tonight?
It's on my freaking
shared Exchange calendar.
Oh, oh look!
There they are right now!
-Look at that!
-Jared: Say, Richard,
that, uh,
that a looks a lot like
Harold Gibbons, the man...
whom Colin has
made a cuckold of.
Richard:
It does.
-Dude.
-Richard: You just messed
with the wrong
pair of boys.
Here's what's
gonna happen.
You're gonna march
into that meeting,
and you're gonna make
an amendment
to your company bylaws
that you will
never record
or collect user
data ever again.
Unless, of course,
you want the information
on that little
thumb drive
to get out.
Son of a bitch.
You can keep
that one, Colin.
We've made copies.
Jared:
Yeah. Walk-- walk
your ass out of here,
you liar, and why don't you...
-Go... fucking... die.
-Die! (giggles)
-This, Richard, this!
-(laughs)
(laughter)
Let's break something.
(muttering): Don't come over,
don't come over,
don't come over.
I gotta say,
this is amazing.
Gabe whines and complains
and AI Dinesh
just takes care of it.
Thank you so much!
(laughs)
My auntie sent me
a Hawaiian shirt.
AI Dinesh must've
told her about Hawaii.
Stop.
Why would AI Dinesh
be talking to your aunt?
I specifically told you
you could only use it
with Gabe.
But it was going
so well with Gabe that
I might've given AI Dinesh
access to all my contacts
just to handle
talking to my auntie,
and my parents.
Why would you give AI Dinesh
access to your contacts,
you fucking moron?
I'm one of your contacts.
-So?
-So, at some point,
AI Dinesh is going
to reach out to AI Gilfoyle.
Oh fuck.
(power whirring down)
(beeping)
Oh fuck indeed.
Gabe:
Uh, hey, Dinesh?
Yes, Gabe?
I think the network is down.
Thank you, Gabe.
Gabe:
Uh, hey, Dinesh?
Dinesh:
Yes, Gabe?
Can you fix it?
♪ ♪
Oh.
Ah, Uber's almost here.
You know, um, there's
a couple of beers
back at the office
with our names on them
'cause when I put it
back in the fridge,
I put our names on them.
-Sure. Yeah, we've earned it.
-(laughter)
Colin:
What Richard created
is fucking amazing.
We're all gonna be rich!
Look,
I'm doing blow,
so it's lighting up drugs,
but it's also lighting up
unprotected sex
and geotagging the Four Seasons.
It's the greatest
data aggregating platform
in history.
This could flip our
whole business model,
and Richard developed
it specifically for us.
Hey! There he is.
So, you guys wanna hear me
banging Harold's wife? Sorry.
It's okay, we're poly.
Right, Dan?
(laughter)
Tracy:
Over seven million emails.
-All on our servers.
-My servers.
Virtually all containing
racist invective,
and pornographic diagrams.
-Yep.
-Care to explain?
AI glitch.
Human error.
I will rectify.
Oh, oh, no,
don't delete AI Dinesh.
I love him.
I can be more
like AI Dinesh.
I'll learn from my mistakes.
I'll optimize myself--
And...
deleted.
Gabe:
Uh, hey, Dinesh?
(chair rattling)
Can I get the tech spec
from you, please?
Sure, Gabe.
(clicking)
♪ ♪
-Paul!
-Gavin.
Did the deal close?
-It did.
-What'd I tell you?
Did you actually look at
the specifics of the deal?
I didn't have to.
Did we have to shut
some divisions?
Of course. Will some
people have to sacrifice
their pensions and the like?
Well, that's up to you,
but we all have to make
sacrifices for the cause.
I really wish you had
looked at these numbers.
The new Hooli will be
significantly smaller.
But you just said Hooli.
Did you hear that?
And that's all that
really matters.
-So, make it work.
-Yes, I've been trying.
To-to that end, uh,
since we have so many
employees moving to Amazon,
-we don't need as much space
and we need to reduce cost.
-(crane whining)
-So--
-What is going on?
Why is their logo
bigger than ours?
Because, technically,
we are now subletting from them.
It was the only way Hooli
could afford to stay here.
You're telling me that
El Pollo Loco corporate
has more employees
than we do?
How many divisions
did I just give up?
We need to fix this! Now!
The term sheet is binding,
and, as of this morning,
I now work at Amazon.
Be well, Gavin.
(scraping)
-(shatters)
-Fuck!
Jared: What do you mean,
"Am I still happy
at Pied Piper?"
W-why would you
even ask me that?
Well, I know you're
my therapist.
I was there when
the court appointed you.
But I-I let my desire
to be around Richard,
and to be needed by him,
turn me into some kind
of a craven yes-man,
and it clouded my judgment,
and I led him down
a horrible path.
What?
I'm not-- I'm not
gonna dignify that.
Of course I belong there.
Where else would
I possibly belong?
All right, well,
I'm home, so...
I guess we're gonna have
to, uh...
Big Head:
Jared?
What are you doing here?
♪ ♪
I-I don't know.
Big Head:
Thought you moved out?
It's Big Head,
from here.
(Simon game beeping)
The garage hasn't
changed a bit.
Although, the rodents
are back in force.
-Oh, cool.
-(beeping)
Big Head,
I need to talk to
you about business.
-Oh hi, Jared.
-Jian-Yang, I was just
taking a little walk
down memory lane--
Can you stay or go?
This is not interesting to me.
Jian-Yang:
Big Head,
we need to kick Gwart
out of the incubator.
Oh, really?
I thought we like Gwart.
-(beeping)
-Oh, damn it.
Gwart?
Gwart has a very good idea,
very good software,
but when I ask her
for business plan,
she doesn't have
a business plan.
She's a brilliant coder,
but this is not a charity.
She's also
not very friendly.
It's a bad for the vibe.
This place should be
a cool hang.
I got you some new cans,
by the way.
-Thank you, Big Head.
-(game beeping)
-(pops)
-(can clatters)
-Nice.
-(cocking)
-(gun pops)
-(can clatters)
Hey.
Looks like you could
use a little help?
May I?
(slurping)
Hi, I'm Jared.
("Easy Loving" by
Freddie Hart playing)
♪ Easy lovin' ♪
♪ Every day's Thanksgiving ♪
♪ To count all my blessings ♪
♪ I wouldn't know
where to start ♪
♪ Every time ♪
♪ I look you over ♪
♪ So real to life it seems ♪
♪ Up on your ♪
♪ Pretty shoulders ♪
♪ There's a pair of ♪
♪ Angel wings... ♪
♪ Life with you
is like living ♪
♪ In a beautiful dream...♪
A man offered us
a billion dollars.
You said, "no."
A very bad man.
And he would have turned us
into the worst possible version
of ourselves.
I mean, you can't put a price
on ethics.
BERTRAM GILFOYLE:
But it seems you just did.
One billion dollars.
GAVIN BELSON: I will be asking
the tech community
to sign their name onto this.
Tech ethics.
Or tethics for short.
No one in town
is ever gonna sign
this hypocrite's
hypocritical garbage.
Hey, Richard.
Ah... what?
-It's my resignation letter.
-What?
Pied Piper isn't
the same company
that I signed up for.
She has different needs now.
You buddy fucker.
I'm not a buddy fucker.
RICHARD HENDRICKS:
I am your buddy,
and you are fucking me.
Ergo...
you are a buddy fucker.
-See the logo?
-Russ.
Check it! (HUMMING)
One, two, three. Boom!
Tres  commas tequila. Boom!
Dollar sign, boom!
Billionaire, boom!
Russ, boom! Fest, boom!
Russfest!
You're not doing anything
illegal here, are you?
Fuck the police.