Facebook, Google, and Amazon
exploit our data for profit.
I will help you by building
an internet of the people
by the people
and for the people,
so help me God.
(CHEERING)
You said all that stuff
about not collecting user data.
-But I am.
-I just lied to Congress.
Hooli will remain
an independent entity,
even if we have to shed
a few divisions
and trim a little fat.
Gwart has a really good idea,
but she doesn't have
a business plan.
Hi, I'm Jared.
We were able to break down
all of your misdeeds.
This guy is dirty as a dog,
and we got him.
Oh, hell yes.
It's the greatest
data aggregating platform.
And Richard developed it
specifically for us.
Dinesh:
So this morning,
Colin cut a new build
of  Gates of Galloo
to his staging server.
Okay, um, this
is Baldereach,
capital city of Galloonia.
Those are some ghoul knights,
wearing gelatinous armor.
This is just the game,
pretty standard stuff.
Well, until I...
turn on the microphone.
How are you doing, Richard?
Are you hungry?
-Would you like some pizza?
-(game chimes)
What the fuck?
He's using our API to run ads
directly in the game engine?
Gilfoyle:
Crazy, right?
Domino's Pizza
in a fantasy medieval universe.
Why, it's enough to make
you wanna go on vacation.
Gilfoyle: And he's even using
our ability to track sentiment.
Yeah. Even if I say
nonsense words,
it assigns them
an emotional value.
La-la-la-la-la-la-la!
Richard:
Fuck me. So,
unless we get rid of Colin,
which we can't,
he is going to put
this on our network.
Money just perverts everything.
At this point, I could stand
to be a little perverted.
Yeah, I wanna be
a lot perverted.
I wanna blow money while it
talks to its wife on the phone.
-I wanna suck money-- Oh.
-All right.
-Microphone.
-Dinesh: Oh! Uh...
Kittens, puppies,
United Nations!
(theme music playing)
Richard,
is this an okay time?
It's a great time, Jared.
I'm surrounded on all sides
by people who turn on me.
-I can come back.
-No. No, no, it's fine.
What do you got?
(sighs) What is this?
It's my resignation letter.
I'm leaving.
What?
One gaff with Colin,
and you're just gonna walk away?
It's about so much more
than that, Richard.
I've been agonizing
over this.
Not sleeping,
not eating...
I completely forgot
my godson's 40th birthday.
Richard,
Pied Piper isn't the same
company that I signed up for.
She has different
needs now,
and so do you,
and, it turns out,
so do I.
Okay, Jared...
we are in the middle
of a shit storm here.
I'm trying to handle this
as honestly as possible.
There's a founder
at the hacker hostel,
and she needs my help, and...
once I'm free of encumbrances--
Encumbrances?! Oh! Well,
fuck me, Jared.
I don't want to encumber you.
(chuckling)
Okay.
Go to your new boss.
I hope she's not a...
big of a fuck-up
as I am, you...
buddy-fucker.
-I'm not a buddy-fucker.
-Oh, yes, you are, Jared.
You are a buddy-fucker.
I am your buddy,
and you are
fucking me. Ergo,
you are a buddy-fucker.
Goodbye.
-Richard, I'm not--
-Goodbye, Jared. Thank you.
I like it how it is.
But it's too warm.
I want it warm.
(quietly):
Okay.
(inhales)
Gentlemen, and lady,
a short time ago,
I reached out to you
and asked you
to invest, sight unseen,
in a newer,
leaner, and more focused Hooli.
And invest you did,
guided not by
traditional spreadsheets
or actuarial tables,
but by your own highly
attuned financial--
Gavin, cut the bullshit.
What do we still own?
Mr. Skelton.
As candid and as
forthright as ever.
-Age has not dulled
one iota of--
-Gavin.
Of course. I had
prepared a presentation,
but I suppose I can
just skip to the end.
Hopefully, I won't
lose you. (chuckles)
Okay...
Confucius, John Lennon,
Nietzsche, Ayn Rand,
Steve Wonder,
and here we go!
As you can see,
among the many jewels
still in Hooli's crown
are our exciting
suite of office--
Where is web services?
Well, Mr. Bezos felt it would
fold nicely into his AWS,
so he insisted--
Smart speaker and in-home?
-He took that, too?
-HooliHome was,
indeed, subsumed
-by the Amazon Alexa--
-Targeted search?
Ironically, also missing.
But we maintain rights
to the HooliPhone
and its proprietary apps,
the patent for
the Hooli Puck Mouse.
We also maintain our
web-based marketplaces,
including our up-and-coming
lifestyle networking platform,
-Foxhole.
-What the fuck is that?!
Well, Foxhole is
a very exciting
web-based exchange,
catering to those
in the military,
-who are interested in
having extramarital affairs.
-Skelton: Gavin,
when do you expect
the eight of us will
recoup our investment?
Ah, yes!
That's my very next slide.
-After this one.
-(clicks)
Well, with a little luck,
we'll be profitable and up 5X
inside three years.
You got three months,
or you're out.
So, Melanie will take on
all of Jared's
marketing duties,
Gwen will cover biz dev,
and that should
take care of it.
Does this
scan to you?
-I can see it.
-Okay, great.
-Richard: Okay, back to work.
-Tracy: Uh, Bertram,
while I have you...
You don't have me.
Richard's just tasked me
with streamlining productivity
and balancing headcount.
Can you explain
to me why you have
no one working under you?
It just seems odd considering
that the agile board is showing
that you have a massive backlog.
You're new here,
so I'll forgive
the patronizing tone.
I'm more concerned
with being right
than being fast,
and I don't like dealing
with people. To wit,
-are we done?
-Oh,
you're "that guy."
What "guy" exactly?
The brooding, arrogant guy
who refuses to take orders?
Self-taught coder
who looks down on
anyone who's
taken a class.
You're probably
an atheist
or something
more contrarian.
You claim to be
an anarcho-capitalist,
but you work here
and pay taxes.
You've probably read half
of Neal Stephenson's
Cryptonomicon,
and it's about 50/50
whether you own a snake.
(whispers):
His girlfriend
owns a snake.
I finished Cryptonomicon,
and you easily could've
just looked in my file.
I didn't need to.
-I'm assigning you five coders.
-Inadvisable.
Noted.
I'll send them over
first thing tomorrow.
If you're going to throw
five randoms under me,
at least let me pick my team.
-Fair enough.
-Good.
-Denpok: Georgia?
-Mm.
You want to move the entire
company to Georgia?
-Why?
-Well, the Valley's become
prohibitively expensive.
Look at these numbers.
If we move to Georgia,
we can save a fortune
and get a further investment.
It's the only way.
Well, I have heard
good things about
the food scene
in the Dirty South.
Stankonia. Freaknik.
-Might be nice to be around
more people of color.
-Gavin: What?
Not Atlanta.
Tbilisi. The country of
Georgia, not the state.
What?
-Denpok: Gavin?
-Hmm?
Tbilisi is no doubt
a wonderfully rustic place,
but do you not fear losing
a local presence,
a connection with
the beating heart of
the technology industry?
Hoover:
Boots on the ground,
so to speak.
I think it's wise, sir.
Shit. You're right.
I need to be here
to maintain my relevance.
All right then. Plan B.
You two and the team
will move to Belarus.
If we can get close enough
to the Chernobyl exclusion zone,
it's a buyer's market,
and with the money
we save from substantially
downgrading from Tbilisi,
plus the bigger Belarusian
investment we've been offered,
I'll maintain
a pied-à-terre here in town.
Now, I'll need to rely
much more heavily on you
because you probably
won't see me much.
I'll need you
to guide the troops
and bridge the language gap,
but...
God damn,
I respect the hell
out of you both.
♪ ♪
-Monica: Are you
sure about this?
-(clears throat) Uh...
Yeah. Yeah, no.
We can't have that atrocious
game anywhere on our network.
-We have to do a raise.
-Well,
it's a terrible time
to do it, but...
I mean,
it's your call.
It's gonna have to be
a big number though.
Yeah, good.
I guess we should set up
some meetings, yeah?
Monica:
Too time-consuming.
Let's jump-start the process.
Are you feeling charitable?
Just 39 cents
a day can literally
feed an entire
family like this.
Think about it,
then ask yourself...
-  (noisy chattering)
-  (mellow jazz playing)
All right, so this place
is the who's who of VCs,
so let's do a lap,
take inventory,
and we'll start
with the biggest firm,
work our way down to--
-Laurie!
-Monica. Richard.
What are you doing here?
The same as you, I suppose.
Eating caviar and...
hacking famine.
-No, I thought you
moved to China.
-Mm.
The interesting thing
about moving, Monica,
is that you can do it
more than once. I am back.
You may be
intrigued to know
that I have severed ties
with Yao and YaoNet.
So, you're going
back to VC?
Oh, no.
You misunderstand.
I have severed ties
between Yao and YaoNet.
Yao has been exited,
and I have made myself
the CEO of the company,
which I am moving
back to the US,
and in order to make it
sound more American,
I am renaming it
"YaoNetUS."
Wait. So, you're
launching here?
Yes, and with those
Chinese out of the way,
I can finally be more
ruthlessly efficient.
Speaking of,
excuse me.
-What? Are you
fucking kidding me?
-Richard,
relax, okay,
she's got inferior tech,
she's got no developers.
You remember when
she tried to run Eklow?
She's gonna last a week as CEO.
I mean, look at her.
She's desperate.
She's already
in total flirt mode.
I do believe with
proper management...
Monica:
She needs money just like we do.
Let's just worry
about us, okay?
I will introduce you,
and just...
let me do
the talking, okay?
Don't speak until--
Richard Hendricks
from Pied Piper.
-Eric Rivera, Graves Partners.
-Richard: Oh.
I saw your
congressional testimony,
and I thought, man,
I really need
to talk to that guy.
Oh, you did? Huh, cool.
Yeah. I mean,
you committed
to a really bad business model,
on national TV.
I guess I just wanted to know,
what the hell were you thinking?
I mean, picking a fight
with Facebook is one thing,
but shitting on Google
and Amazon at the same time,
in front of TV cameras?
What was going on in your brain?
And-and Hooli. I-I shit
on them, too, so...
I mean, we're all sitting in
front of the TV in our office,
thinking this is
the dumbest man in tech.
And then we talked about it,
and we realized, hang on,
-that is totally unfair.
-Yeah, you did? Good.
Yeah, because, I mean,
you were subpoenaed, right?
You were under oath?
-What were you supposed to do?
-Technically, I don't...
You weren't...
you weren't under oath?
Mm, I don't think so.
Are you kidding me?
Wait. Karl, Ben!
Come over here.
You gotta hear this.
We were wrong, man!
Tell them what you just told me.
(chattering)
Hey, um--
Richard Hendricks,
from Pied Piper, yes?
Uh, no.
Maximo Reyes.
I am an investor from Chile.
Wow, I gotta tell you,
it is an honor
to meet you, man.
Truly, I am such a big fan
of your technology.
Wow.
-What, like, really, or...
-Of course. Hi.
We are shaking hands.
Correct?
But I'm sure you have more
important people to talk to,
you know, and, you have
made it painfully clear
that you do not want
me as an investor, so--
No, h-hold on.
Wait, I-I-I made it clear?
When did I--
Oh no, not you personally,
but I spoke with somebody
from your company many times.
Uh, Yarez?
Yarez?
Y-Yarez Dun...
Yarez-- Oh!
-Jared.
-Yes!
-Whatever...
-Potatoes, potatoes.
Well, uh, Yared doesn't really
work with us anymore, so...
-Oh, wow. Well, then.
-Yeah.
Look at you and me.
-We are talking.
-(laughs)
Have you ever had
a Chilean terremoto  ?
-Hoover: Denpok, got a minute?
-Denpok: Yes.
I may have a way
to keep us here in the US.
Talk.
Are you familiar with CIFIUS?
Yes.
No.
The Committee on Foreign
Investment in the US,
or CIFIUS,
is a federal agency
that has wide latitude
to prevent American companies
-from doing business
with foreigners,
if there's a national
security threat.
Are you familiar with
the dating app Grindr?
No.
Yes.
Last year,
CIFIUS reversed the sale
of Grindr to Chinese investors.
They ruled that the sexual
and HIV status of US citizens
was something
they needed to keep
out of the hands
of foreign interests.
-I understand.
-This morning,
I was on the user
database of Foxhole,
when I happened upon
a familiar face.
(clicks)
Four-star General Hanley Barris.
That is not his face.
No, it is not.
But as a four-star general,
he could anonymously
compel CIFIUS
to prevent Foxhole
or its ownership
from moving to foreign soil.
No more Belarus?
I think General Barris would
be very keen to keep
this type of material
out of the hands of
foreign interests,
and by that,
I mean his wife, Yekatarina.
♪ ♪
Hey! What happened
to you last night?
Oh my God,
you reek of booze.
Were you out all night?
Monica...
-I got lucky.
-Didn't need to know that.
No, no, I got even
luckier than that.
Tell me, did you know that
the national tree of Chile
is the piñoner  ?
Also this,
-do you know who
Maximo Reyes is?
-Yeah.
The richest man in Chile.
Well, I saw that very tree
in the middle of
his living room,
and he let me climb it.
You met
Maximo Reyes
and you went
to his house?
Yeah, and he showed me
his art collection,
and we drank a number
of terremotos,
which are...
fucking disgusting.
Anyway, I may
have convinced him
to give us enough money
to get rid of Colin.
Wait, what?
I casually floated
50 million,
and he didn't
even bat an eye.
-(chuckling)
-Monica: Richard...
There's a reason Jared
tried to ditch this guy.
-We cannot take his money.
-Why not?
Did he tell you
where he gets it from?
How his grandfather was
the chief of secret police
under Pinochet?
About how they ran
their mines?
They were basically
slave traders.
He can't really be
all that bad.
I mean, he really,
really likes Pied Piper.
Look, we cannot
take blood money.
You thought selling
ads were bad?
These guys executed
people in soccer stadiums.
I was open
to it at first,
but Jared was adamant
and he's right.
Fifty million sounds great,
but it's an awfully low price
to pay for your integrity.
Fuck.
Look,
I know Colin
is a sleazebag,
but at least
he's temporary.
Okay, Maximo is
a thousand times worse,
and he would be permanent.
(phone chimes)
(scoffs) Of course.
He just e-mailed me
the term sheet.
I don't even
wanna look at him.
Just forward it to me.
-I'll take care of it.
-Thanks.
I know that this sucks,
but I promise you,
you're doing the right...
Fifty million?
Do you remember
when I was offered 10?
-(laughs)
-Richard.
Hmm?
It's not $50 million.
Is it more?
It's a billion, Richard.
A what?
He just offered us
a billion dollars for 10%.
Fuck.
-(exhales)
-You're already
holding a cigarette.
♪ ♪
Tracy:
Mr. Gilfoyle!
-Gilfoyle: Yes, ma'am?
-Is this your new team?
It is.
Five people, as you requested.
-That man over there?
-Gilfoyle: Ken.
-Isn't he the coffee guy?
-Barista. Yes.
And Joyce was
watering the plants.
Mona was working security.
Dan and George,
they were painting the lobby.
Until today.
Which reminds me,
they all need to change
their LinkedIn
status to...
"placaters of
middle management."
I'll be honest,
this is sort of a first.
And here you thought
I was just...
"that guy."
You know, Mr. Gilfoyle,
you're right.
You're not "that guy,"
because at the seven companies
I've helped take public,
every other "that guy"
accepted their limitations,
took on a team, and managed
to get their work done.
Some of them are
now billionaires.
None of them
would've gotten into
a dick-measuring
contest with HR
when they were
two weeks behind.
So, lucky us,
I guess you're unique.
♪ ♪
You know, Gilfoyle,
when I first heard the phrase
"dick-measuring contest,"
I thought it was a contest
to see who could
measure the most dicks.
But it isn't,
is it, Gilfoyle?
Is it a typo?
Maybe it's a typo.
It's not a typo, Richard.
It's spelled out in the offer.
One billion dollars,
in one lump sum.
Okay, what do I do?
-I don't know.
-Oh. Okay, well,
Jared had you pretty convinced
that this was evil money.
It's a billion fucking
dollars, Richard!
Okay, so does that make
this less evil or, like,
-way more evil?
-Ack!
Do not touch.
It's an e-sign.
You touch that button,
it's over.
Tell me what to do.
Monica, this is your job!
Look, when my sister
got pregnant her
freshman year of college,
I said get an abortion.
Well, now my niece, Dakota,
who is very much with us,
calls me "Aunt Abortion."
I'm sorry.
You are the CEO,
this is on you.
Well, I gotta talk
to Dinesh and Gilfoyle.
No, you can't talk
to those animals!
You say a word
to anyone out there,
and this whole company turns
into Lord of the Flies
in five seconds.
It's a billion
dollars, Richard.
I'm sorry. You're on your own.
Monica...
Richard, there is
a major emergency.
Gilfoyle is using
the barista as
one of the coders,
so I tried to use
the cappuccino
machine on my own,
and I don't know if, like,
the frother knob is, like,
jammed or something,
but it's, like,
not working.
So, there is no froth,
at all,
for anybody.
So, can you get on that?
-Yeah.
-Okay, great.
-He's on it!
-(sighs)
It's really
a shit sandwich.
They've been in there
for a while.
-Wonder how it's going.
-(door opens)
General Barris. Is it done?
-Wonderful.
-Say hello
to your wife for me.
Gavin! How was the meeting?
-(shouts)
-(clatters)
♪ ♪
Gavin:
Aah! Fuck!
Richard?
Huh? Yeah.
What are you doing here?
(clears throat)
Do you have a second?
Yeah, yeah. Come on in.
I know you tried to keep
Maximo away from me,
but one thing lead to another
and-and now this.
-That is quite an offer.
-Yeah.
So, what do I do?
Look, Richard, I know you said
Monica's checked out on this,
but... this is kind of
a monumental Pied Piper matter.
I think you should get
advice from somebody
within the company.
That's why I'm here, Jared.
That's you.
You gotta come back.
-Richard--
-I-I know
your job changed over time,
but we can undo that.
You know, restructure your role,
move you upstairs
so you're closer to me.
Whatever it takes
to make it work.
Come on, think about it.
We'll be...
a pair of boys,
back in business.
Richard, it's too late.
I mean,
you know, you let me go,
so I took the job here
-with Gwart, and--
-So?
Go inside and tell
Gwart you're leaving.
Well, that's not
how loyalty works.
I mean, that
wouldn't be fair.
Fair?
Years ago,
you came to this house,
begging me for a job,
and I gave you one.
In fact, I made you COO.
And now,
when I need you the most,
you stab me in the back,
and you have the balls
to lecture me about loyalty?
Are you fucking
kidding me?
I was right.
You are a buddy-fucker.
-Please stop saying that.
-Buddy-fucker.
Stop saying that.
And-and-and please
just leave this house,
-or I can't be held
responsible for my behavior.
-Oh yeah?
What are you gonna do,
Jared? Huh?
You gonna buddy-fuck me?
'Cause that's what you do
-to your buddies
now, isn't it?
-Get out.
(buzzing)
Oh, Gwart. No, no, no!
That's too much sun.
-(buzzing stops)
-Oh my God.
This is Gwart?
-Richard...
-(scoffs)
-This is who you're
walking away for?
-Richard, do not.
She's your new little
code girlfriend?
-Don't.
-This, uh--
-This googly-eyed...
-No, no, no, no...
-Yoo-hoo drinking--
-No!
-Oh my God.
Oh, okay, okay,
okay, look, I'm sorry!
-No.
-All right.
I oughta knock your teeth,
you bitch-made motherfucker.
-I-I-I... I didn't mean it.
-(glass shatters)
I was state-raised!
You think I'm scared
to catch a case
-of some bullshit?!
-I-I'm sorry, Jared!
I didn't mean it, okay?
I'm sorry, Gwart.
-I didn't mean it!
-You keep her name out of
your skanky little mouth,
you little,
little bitch!
Hey! Hey! Hey! This is
a place of business--
Oh my God. Don't shoot me!
-Jared!
-(BB clinks)
-Jared! Aah!
-Dope-led, peckerwood
motherfucker!
-Richard: Jared! Jared, no!
-Get checked in, hoe!
(banging)
Oh, Jesus!
Jared:
You wanna dance on
the blacktop, homie?!
You did this, Richard!
-(BB thwacks)
-Aah!
Ow, what the fuck?
♪ ♪
Mr. Gilfoyle! You wanted
to see me before I left?
Yes, Tracy, I did.
I wanted you to be here
when I push my entire
backlog of code.
You finished all of it?
In just 24 hours?
I did, all by myself.
(clicks)
I'll take that apology now.
Mr. Gilfoyle, you said
that I had to choose.
You said I could have it fast
or I could have it right,
but I just got it
fast and right,
and all I had to do was
threaten your manhood
by assigning you
other coders.
It worked at seven
other companies,
and it obviously
worked here.
We're back on schedule!
Now, why would I be
sorry about that.
♪ ♪
I respect your skills.
Thank you.
See you in the morning.
Maximo:
And now, we are both holding
-a whiskey.
-Yes.
Um, Maximo,
I wanna apologize
for coming over
here unannounced.
And I wanna do
this deal with you,
but... Jesus--
Richard, you have some
concerns because of my family.
I mean... yeah.
Richard, do you see
these photographs?
Now, these people,
a lot of them children,
used to work for my father
in my family's mines.
Now, I keep them
here as a reminder
of the many, many
mistakes my father made.
I want to fix those
mistakes, Richard.
By investing in you
and your company,
I'll be able
to start doing that.
Do you really believe that?
Richard, we are going to change
the world, you and I.
-(thuds)
-Shit! What was that?
Ah, the birds. You know,
they're attracted to the tree,
so sometimes, you know,
kapffft!
(laughs)
What are you gonna do?
-To rectifying
the mistakes of my father.
-Sure. Yeah.
The fool who allowed
the workers to unionize
and ask for
higher wages
and more expensive
hospitals.
-We--
-Uh, sorry.
What was that?
Yes. My grandfather,
he built a great fortune,
but then my idiot father
almost gave it all away.
But not now, though.
Oh no.
Now, I mine copper,
cobalt and diamonds,
and now, thanks to you,
data. Gracias.
Uh, no. No, what?
-No, we do not--
-(bird clunks)
Oh my God!
Uh...
No, we...
We will not mine user data.
I was very clear about that.
-But you do.
-(thuds)
Richard, did you not tell me
when we were sitting
on my tree, bonding,
that there is a man in
your network right now,
using a tool, that you built,
in order to mine user data?
No. That is coming to an end.
That doesn't happen anymore.
-(bird clunks)
-Richard, please. Cheers.
To our future
endeavors together.
Maximo...
we will never collect
and monetize user data.
Ever.
Then why would I give you
one billion dollars, Richard?
Look at me. I am not
a fool like my father.
(bird clunks)
You are turning this into
a dick-measuring contest.
Please don't,
because I assure you,
it will be I
who measures the most.
Are-are you threatening me?
Take my money, Richard.
It'll be very good
for you,
and very good for me.
But if you do not take
my money, Richard...
oh, it will be very bad for you.
(bird clunks, splashes)
("She Got the Devil in Her"
by Buddy Guy playing)
♪ ♪
♪ You know I talk
to my baby ♪
♪ Like a mother
talk to her kid ♪
♪ You know
I love
that woman ♪
♪ But I just can't
keep it hid ♪
♪ She got
the devil in her ♪
♪ Yes  ♪
♪ That woman got
the devil in her... ♪
Richard, it's Maximo.
(CHUCKLES)
We are on the phone.
Let me tell you what is going
to happen to you next.
(RETCHES)
All I wanted to do
was be a golden millionaire.
A millionaire
that gets peed on?
I could see you making half
that happen.
Can I be honest with you
for once?
For once?
You're my attorney.
You're out of options.
-DINESH CHUGTAI: Holy shit.
-MONICA HALL:
We could buy Hooli.
Take your marks.
(GUNSHOT)
I still got it, Hoover.