Quit it.
Make me.
Make me, man.
I'll make you.
Knock it off.
Hey.
I got something for him,
if he's still interested.
What's so funny?
- Ah, you wouldn't get it.
- Okay.
Okay, here's what you're gonna do.
You're gonna take 25 South to Las Cruces.
You can pick up 10 West from there.
Hey, write this down, man, es complicado.
Ten West at Las Cruces.
A little past Deming
there's a state road. It's 146.
Follow the signs to Antelope Wells
until Mile Marker 223.
Turn off at the dirt road
and take it 30 miles south.
- Thirty miles down a dirt road?
- Fewer eyes out in the desert, you know?
Actually, it's 31.6.
So make sure that you use the little,
you know,
trip metre thing on the odometer,
whatever.
Anyway, once you get there,
you're gonna see a well.
It's really old.
You know, broken down.
What does this well look like?
It looks like a well.
It's the only one out there.
- Can you see it from the road?
- You'll see it. Don't worry about it.
My cousins are gonna meet you there
with the money, 9 a.m.
- You'll like them. They're good boys.
- I'll bet.
Hey, I have an idea.
Why not have these cousins of yours
bring the money just all the way here?
Cut out the middleman.
Yeah, see, the thing is,
this whole thing has
to be very low-profile, you know?
There are people,
let's say competitors of mine,
people who wanna keep me in here.
And so, you know,
my cousins come into town,
those people will notice.
What about Nacho Varga, right?
Would your competitors notice him?
He seems like he's got
a pretty good head on his shoulders.
You mean Ignacio?
Yeah, sure, I mean,
he's good for a lot of things.
But with 7 million?
A guy like that could get real dumb
real fast, you know?
Hey, you're the right guy for this.
You're nobody.
I mean, no offence,
but nobody's gonna look twice at you.
Yeah, sure...
Hey, look, maybe this isn't your thing,
you know? I mean, that's okay. I get it.
You did good in court.
We'll leave it at that.
Well, thanks, that's...
I appreciate that.
Don't worry about it.
I'll find somebody else, you know?
Yeah. So I guess we're done here.
Guess so.
All right.
I will... I'm gonna shred these.
And...
if there's anything else you need,
any legal services...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I got your number. See you.
This stupid thing.
Hundred thousand?
Dollars?
- Yeah.
- That's a lot of money.
To bring back 7 mil?
And I'm the best guy to do it?
That's actually less than
2 percent commission. I think it's right.
So 100K for a little drive
through the desert, huh?
That's the price.
Done.
Hey, I'm home.
Great. I'll be out in a sec.
Evening shower, huh?
Yeah. Got an early day tomorrow.
Hey, I hope you're hungry.
I'm making fajitas.
- You're cooking?
- Yeah, why not?
I picked up some strip steak
on the way home,
and it's been marinating
for a couple hours
in a secret blend of herbs and spices.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Something I like to call Old El Paso.
It sounds exotic.
It'll be delicious, you'll see.
I... I have some business news.
You're a friend of the cartel?
Is that it?
Not exactly.
Maybe.
You got him bail?
Some evidence fell into my lap.
I was kind of obligated to use it.
You know, for my client.
When you said you couldn't do it,
I knew you'd find a way.
There's a complication.
Remember that time you had a PD case
with the kid whose parents kicked him out
because he got caught with a joint?
Yeah.
And you had to drive all the way out
to the uncle's house,
I think it was in Moriarty,
to pick up the bail? Well...
Wait, what? So, what, you're saying
you're gonna pick up Salamanca's bail?
Yeah, only it's a little further
than Moriarty and a little more money.
- How much?
- Seven.
- Seven thousand?
- Million.
- Seven million?
- Yeah.
You're going to pick up $7 million
of cartel money?
I know what you're thinking,
but it's safe. Completely.
A quick drive down by the border,
- I'll be back.
- The border?
Jimmy, you are an attorney,
not a bagman.
There's no amount of money
that is worth this.
- Can't his people do it?
- He trusts me.
I'm his attorney, that's it.
You're making a bigger deal out of this
than you need to.
- What?
- I will pick it up in the morning,
I will be done
and I'll be home before you will.
Okay. Then I'm going with you.
Well, they're only expecting me.
You know, one guy?
I mean, that's kind of the whole point.
You know, security through obscurity.
- Jimmy, this is insane, I...
- No, listen, it's just little old me
in my little old Suzuki Esteem.
And there has never been
more than 50 bucks in an Esteem
in the history of Esteems.
So no one's gonna look at me twice.
You sound like you are talking yourself
into this.
I will be okay. I swear.
If I smell even the faintest whiff
of anything wrong,
I'll be out of there like a shot.
I don't like this.
I don't want you to do it.
Kim, listen.
I swear, okay? I'll be fine.
L... Lawyer.
From Lalo. Eduardo sent me
to pick up the dinero.
I'll just take these back to Lalo.
You guys are just gonna... Just go?
Well, that'll work.
All right.
Seven million dollars
of cash in the trunk
Seven million dollars of cash
Take one dollar, pass it a rollar
Six million
nine hundred ninety-nine thousand
Crappy service
Six million
nine hundred ninety-nine thousand
Ninety-nine dollars of cash
in the truck
Take a buck, pass it for luck
Six million, nine hundred
ninety-nine thousand, nine...
Nine hundred ninety-nine...
Go by.
Oh, shit, shit, shit.
Oh, nuts.
Okay, yeah.
Coming out. Slowly.
I think... I think I have a sense
of what you want here. It's in the trunk.
Yeah, good. Take those.
What? No, no.
That's not what he meant.
No, this is a mistake.
It's a big...
No!
You hit?
- Hit?
- Are you shot?
Get up.
Shot?
You're in shock.
You stay here and breathe.
Hey.
You're alive. Focus on that.
You'll be okay.
Get out. The alternator's shot.
Literally.
All right. I'm gonna need you
to put your back into this.
Push!
Wait! Wait, wait, wait!
What is it?
Where is it?
Did you know all this was gonna happen?
If I did, I would've brought more guys.
Let's get that to where it belongs.
This way.
Well, home is that way.
One of those guys got away in a car.
On the road. This road.
We gotta get off it.
Big mistake...
discontinuing...
thousand dollar bill.
Big.
These would've been so much lighter.
Hey.
How about we take turns
with these bad boys, you know?
So we both stay fresh?
Fine.
- I got an idea. Let's dig a hole.
- A hole?
Yeah. Walk out of here,
get to civilisation,
drive back, pick it up.
Work smarter, not harder.
You'll never find it.
Oh, I will because
I'll memorise the landmarks.
Like this tree? You can't miss it.
That hill, that's distinctive.
It's got a hill shape.
Yeah, very different
from the couple dozen trees we've seen
on hillsides that we walked past.
I will remember. I will find this tree.
That's hard pack.
If you manage to dig a hole big enough
for those two bags,
you might as well dig one for yourself.
Oh, come on. That's not gonna work.
You are wasting energy.
I'm almost there.
It's working.
Stop.
Put that away. They'll see it.
You take off anything
that'll catch the light.
- Is it him?
- Oh, yeah.
It looks like they're doing a grid search.
Meaning?
Meaning they found your car.
I'd go easy on that.
Hey, why are we camping?
I mean, shouldn't we keep walking?
It's cooler at night.
You go out there in the dark,
you're gonna break your leg
in a prairie-dog hole.
Hey, we gotta be halfway there, right?
Almost.
I should have been home hours ago.
This will be tearing her up.
Oh, she's just gonna think
you're out catting around.
No, she won't.
She's gonna think I'm chopped to pieces,
dead in some ditch.
And why is she gonna think that?
Are you saying she knows
what you're doing?
Not, you know, the details.
She knows I'm picking up money
down by the border, that's all.
You told your girlfriend
what you're doing?
My wife.
- Wife?
- Yeah, wife.
Congratulations.
And what's your wife gonna do
with this information, do you think?
- Call the cops?
- No.
No? People get scared, call the cops.
Pretty standard.
No, she's not calling any cops.
Her mother. Girls at the book club.
Gonna call her boss,
tell her about her missing husband.
No, she's not doing any of that, okay?
She knows better.
She's just gonna be scared
out of her mind, is all.
Well, let's hope you're right.
She knows.
She's in the game now.
What? No.
She's not in the game, all right?
She's not even game-adjacent.
I just told her the truth.
A little slice of the truth. That's all.
- She's not in the game.
- Yeah.
Well, I can't make a fire.
Our guy may still be out there.
I got two of these, you want one?
No, thanks.
- Gets cold fast.
- I'm fine. Thanks.
You suit yourself.
- Ma'am, do you want me to...?
- Yes, please.
Thank you.
I know I misrepresented myself
as a member of your legal team,
I apologise for that.
I wouldn't be here right now
if I didn't absolutely have to be.
I know who are.
Who you actually are.
We have something in common.
You wanna know where your money is,
I wanna find Saul Goodman.
If you tell me where you sent him,
I won't alert the authorities,
I won't tell anyone.
I will find him and you'll get your money.
Mr. Salamanca...
Who the hell are you
that he tells you my business?
He didn't betray your confidence.
We're married,
which means I have spousal privilege.
Anything he says to me stays with me.
No one can make me discuss it.
It's as bulletproof
as lawyer-client privilege.
So you're his wife?
Yes.
So you're his wife and you love him,
and he didn't come home last night,
and you got scared enough
to come down here and talk to me.
What makes you think
he didn't run off with my money, huh?
He did not run off with your money.
Yeah, maybe not.
Not without you.
Just tell me where you sent him.
That's all I need.
I don't think so.
Your man, he's...
He's like la cucaracha, you know?
Born survivor.
If trouble found him, give it a day.
If he's alive, he'll show.
And if he's...?
Well, then a day's not gonna make
a difference, is it?
All right. Well, nice to meet you,
Mrs. Goodman.
Wait, Mr. Salamanca...
Done!
Hey. I wouldn't waste that.
Waste what?
I don't have enough of this
for the both of us.
Just a lonely soul
Slowly dying
I was smiling hard
But I was lying
Then you sailed along
With your sweet dream
When you stole my heart
I was livid
Morning come
Sun don't shine
I'll get by without you
I was lost, but now I'm found
Tell me, love, it was you
More.
- No.
- More.
No. You want more...
All right.
Come on. Let's go.
Hold it. I have an idea.
- That's not gonna work.
- This is gonna work.
You gonna get that?
Get what?
Got it.
Oh, crap.
Hey. Shit!
That's it. I'm done.
Done!
Quiet.
Why? I'm quiet, I'm loud,
I'm gonna die in this dirt
one way or the other.
Let's get it over with.
- Get up.
- No.
I'm not going.
I'm done.
Everything hurts.
God, I'm so thirsty.
You need to drink.
What's the point?
So they can find a corpse
with a mouth full of piss?
That's not gonna happen.
Now get up.
Come on.
Oh, God. Oh, no. How...?
How the hell are you still going?
Because I know why I'm out here.
That's how.
I know what it's for.
And I can't drag that money
out of here by myself.
So you...
You get up, and you get up now.
What it's for? What is it for?
I have people.
I have people waiting for me.
They don't know what I do,
they never will.
They're protected.
But I do what I do
so they can have a better life.
And if I live or if I die,
it really doesn't make a difference to me
as long as they have what they need.
So when it's my time to go,
I will go knowing I did everything
I could for them.
Now, you ask me how I keep going?
That's how.
Stay down. He's back.
Lie low.
We're gonna have to wait him out.
Hey, get that thing ready.
Come on, you asshole.
You want this 7 mil?
Come on, I'm just walking here
like a goddamn idiot!
Come and get some, you dickhead.
You son of a bitch. Look at me!
Yeah, there you go.
Come on. Come on.