How about a special discount?
For the next two weeks,
non-violent felonies,
50 percent off. Yeah.
- Okay.
- I'll take one.
Yeah. That's for you. Fifty percent off.
Yeah, all right. Now we got some takers.
There you are. Oh, yeah. Who else?
Fifty percent off. There you are.
- Fifty percent off.
- Dude, that's almost half.
Hey! You bastards!
Fifty percent off!
Money, money, money!
Money, money, money.
Yeah!
Yeah! I got my money! Yeah!
Yeah.
Get back here, you little bitch!
I'm okay!
Fifty percent off!
Yeah!
- Yo.
- What?
- Dude.
What day is it?
Tuesday?
- What?
- You know what that means?
Fifty percent off!
And have you smoke-free
in just seven days.
It's all-natural and nicotine-free.
Best of all, it's guaranteed to work
or your money back.
Order now to get Smoke Away's
new oral spray free, Spray Away.
It can stop your cravings instantly.
Call now.
Thousands have already quit smoking
using Smoke Away.
Baby, what's happening?
What's happening, baby?
Get off of me, man.
It's okay.
Come on, man.
What do you want from me?
I switched the stuff.
I played it all like he told me.
No.
What are we doing?
Come on, man. Don't.
You got five people in there.
Too bad.
Hey, wait! Wait. Wait.
Hey! Hey, wait! Wait. Hey, wait!
Why is he doing this?
Hey, why is he doing this?
I did everything.
Wait.
Please, man.
Please, man, please, no. Please, no.
Please. Man, please.
Please, man.
Okay.
I get it.
Just tell me what you want me to do.
Lalo Salamanca.
I need to know where he is going.
What he is thinking.
What he's planning.
I need to know what he's going to do
before he does it.
I've been trying, okay?
He doesn't tell me shit.
He's just keeps talking about some guy
named Werner Ziegler.
And some gringo Michael.
That's it.
Gain his confidence.
Make him rely on you.
How?
Find a way.
My father has nothing to do with this.
I'll find a way. I'll make him trust me.
Okay?
Your pop's a nice guy.
Yeah. Sure.
Let me see if I have this right.
A Mr. Bertram Moran, aka B-Mo,
claims that you solicited him
for the purchase of narcotics
when, in fact, you were simply enjoying
a Big Gulp in the park
when he approached
and attempted to sell to you.
I got a live one.
Yes, PJ. Go ahead.
Kim, sorry. My side is too full.
I'm gonna take some of those
back to Mrs. Nguyen's.
Yeah, uh-huh.
Well, I think I got the specifics.
I'll call you later.
Geez. A chatty one.
So, hey, how's it going with Cold Finger,
the mini-fridge mastermind?
Did you get a trial date yet?
No. He took the deal.
He took the five months?
Yup.
You were right, as usual.
Saul Goodman, speedy justice for you.
Yes, miss. I...
Oh, no. Well, that's not right.
Yeah. Go on.
Can you hold for a moment?
Kim, how about dinner and a movie tonight?
I'm... Scampi and Scorsese because they got
After Hours on the Classic Movie Channel.
I love that one,
but we'll have to see.
I might need to stay late.
Okay. Just let me know.
Yeah. I'll see you.
Yes, go ahead.
There's something about a minivan?
- Kim.
- Jimmy, what are you...?
There's something I gotta show you.
It's just three blocks from here.
Look, I... Sorry.
I know you gotta get to work. This will
only take a couple of minutes, please.
Drive. If we go right now,
it will be over like that.
- Which way?
- Take a right.
There. Right there.
- The white one?
- Yeah. That one. Right there.
Jimmy, we're not buying a house.
Maybe not today,
but doesn't hurt to look, does it?
I drove by this place like a week ago,
and I'm curious.
Aren't you, just a little?
Look at all that space.
Hey, you're doing great. I'm gonna
be doing great. I got 45 clients.
Forty-five?
How are you gonna handle all that?
I got a system, but can we just look?
They're not even open yet.
Yeah, well. They want to sell this house.
They'll let us in.
All right.
Hey, folks. Do you mind signing in?
There's a guestbook right over here.
You know what?
Could we do that on our way out?
Sure.
Just take your time. Have a look around.
Let me know if you have any questions.
- You got it.
- Thanks.
Man, look at all this wall space.
Imagine a plasma TV mounted right there.
One of the huge new ones.
Hey, this would be a big change,
but we could make it our own.
We could host movie nights.
Some comfy chairs
and smell of popcorn in the air, and...
And check out these countertops.
Yeah.
Blue. Is this quartz?
I read somewhere
that it's good for healing.
So good for healing.
Hey. You know that...
50 percent off thing I said
I wouldn't do?
Well, I did it.
I told a few potential clients.
It just kind of slipped out.
Don't worry. I know these people.
They're not gonna do anything
because of some stupid discount.
But it was a bonehead move
and I shouldn't have done it.
Okay.
Jimmy, I know you were trying to help,
but I don't want to lie to my clients.
Are you talking about the fridge guy?
That was a dumb idea.
I mean all my clients.
Of course. Absolutely. Never again.
Oh, my God.
- This is the closet of your dreams.
- Our dreams.
Sure.
Where are my Louboutins?
Louboutins? Louboutins?
Hey, check this out.
- Oh, there's jets.
- Yeah, it's like a mini spa.
That would be so nice
after a long day on our feet.
Yeah. And two sinks.
So plenty of room for brushing.
And spitting.
Hey, you gotta see this.
I mean, look at all the nozzles.
- Yeah.
- Is that what I think it is?
Steam?
But how do you get it going?
Maybe the water's shut off.
Maybe.
Hey...
Quit it.
You're... Very mature. Very mature.
Thanks again.
Nice house, huh?
Yeah. Maybe someday.
My turn.
Hang on, Tio.
Excuse me, Mr. Salamanca.
Would you give your uncle some of this?
It's Fizzy K. He needs to hydrate.
Fizzy K?
It's just a vitamin solution.
It's very berry, his favourite.
Right, Hector?
- Thanks. I'll make sure he drinks it.
- Thank you.
Look, Tio.
What's he doing?
He's building something.
A tunnel...
A lab... maybe a vault?
He's preparing for something big.
He lies to me with this shit
about the Germans.
Maybe Eladio and Bolsa
believe it but I don't.
But what can I do?
They don't give a shit.
As long as he makes them cash.
What?
You mean the money?
Right...
The money.
As long as he brings in the money,
he's protected.
Gross, Tio.
This is shit.
Let's see. Better, no?
Yeah?
Mike, hi. I'm sorry to bother you.
No, no bother, honey. What's up?
I don't know what your work schedule
is like these days.
I'm still making my own hours.
Well, I just got called in.
- Emily's busy, and...
- No problem.
Are you sure?
Positive. I'll be happy to watch her.
- What time do you need me there?
- How about now?
Now.
On the way.
Oh, thanks, Mike. You're a lifesaver.
Yeah.
- Hey!
- Hey.
I thought we'd finish fixing the ladder
on the treehouse.
- Pop-Pop!
- Hey, kid.
She needs to finish her homework first.
Don't let her sweet-talk you.
No, not a chance of that.
She gotta learn her times tables.
She's on the sevens.
Sevens?
There's lasagne in the oven
and I should be back before bedtime.
- Sounds good.
- Okay.
- See you later, sweetie!
- Bye, Mom!
Bye.
What do we got?
Sevens are the worst.
I bet you know
more than you think you know.
I do?
You remember when we watched
the Super Bowl?
Seven times three?
- Twenty-one.
- Right. Seven times four?
Four touchdowns equals 28.
Plus another one makes 35.
Go, Eagles! Kick ass.
You don't talk like that.
Who taught you to talk like that?
You did.
Come on. Seven times eight?
- That's a lot of touchdowns.
- It's a lot of touchdowns.
It's a big game. Where are we at?
Fifty-five?
So you think the kicker
missed the extra point?
Oh, no. It's 56.
Seven times eight is 56.
You got it.
My dad liked the Eagles, right?
Yeah. He sure did.
Was he good at math?
- Thank you.
- Yeah, he...
Your daddy was a smart kid.
A good student like you.
Did he want to be a policeman
when he was my age?
When he was your age...
You know, I think he went back and forth
between an astronaut, deep sea explorer
like Jacques Cousteau.
Who?
You don't know Jacques Cousteau?
Well, we'll fix that.
So instead,
my dad decided to be a policeman.
Like you.
Yeah.
Hey, make sure those are nice and even.
And he was a really good policeman, right?
Yes.
And you taught him.
But...
the bad guys got him?
- I told you to make those even.
- I am.
No, you're not!
You're making a mess.
You either do it right,
or you don't do it.
But I wanna do it.
You're done. You are done!
Hey.
- Where's Kaylee?
- She's in her room. She won't come out.
- She didn't eat dinner.
- Why? What happened?
Mike!
And they expect me to glow,
so I gotta be cold
Like a baseball, shawty,
I gotta be pro
Yeah.
So? Two?
It's gonna be a 10 tonight.
- Ten?
- Yeah.
I don't care what they were saying,
I ain't wanting to know
I know hating's real bad,
for your arteries though
Every party, we go,
everybody we know
Hey! Why you doing that?
- Where's the cookie?
- I sent it down.
Well, it ain't here.
- Yeah, it is.
- What up?
- No stuff.
- No stuff?
It's there.
No, it ain't!
Quit that, fool!
Who you calling fool, fool?
Don't make me come down there.
Stop playing!
- Oh, you better come down here!
- Shut up!
You shut up!
- You shut up!
Shut up!
Call.
Fairground spot's doing really good.
Lots of traffic.
Hey.
Shut up while I'm in a hand.
You know what?
Two hundred.
Oh, man.
It's too deep for me.
And did I get you?
Let me see what you had.
You had a set?
You had three eights on the turn,
and you don't raise?
And then you fold at the river?
It's too bad.
Ocho Loco this guy, huh?
All right, guys, give me your cards.
Sorry.
Yeah?
Hold on.
Problem on Fifth Street.
Some skells say
they didn't get their stuff.
It's your crew.
Off you go, Ocho Loco.
Okay.
Yo.
Maybe we could shoot the pipe.
Like with a gun.
Hey, we ain't shooting nothing.
Oh, okay. Well, we paid for our shit,
so we're getting our shit.
Yeah.
Where's our glass?
We're gonna kick your ass
Yo, give me the mic.
- Mic.
- So I can rap about this pipe.
Yo, my name is Mr. Sticky,
I'm pretty fricking tricky
Gonna kick you in the thicky
What does that even mean?
'Cause I'm Mr. Picky
and I'm so tricky
Yeah, yeah, you're thicky.
- Oh, shit!
- Hey, we still get our glass, right?
Domingo!
Hey!
This your vehicle?
No, sir.
Wanna come down here?
No problem, officer.
What you doing up there?
Just fixing a drainpipe.
Some kind of block.
Guess you fixed it.
- Only Domingo got picked up?
- Yeah.
The rest of us bounced,
but he was stuck up there.
Shit, whole block's crawling.
You got the stuff?
- You got it?
- Nah.
I had to leave it.
They were on my ass.
Hey! Right here.
Shit's gone now.
These assholes will turn
the whole place upside-down.
How much is in there?
Almost a full load.
Wait, where you going?
What the hell are you doing?
Stupid idiot,
they're going to catch your ass.
Where'd he go?
There he is.
He's on the roof!
This is gonna be good.
No.
You're kidding me. You're kidding me!
Look at that!
He's a fool, right?
Here they come.
Bye-bye, Nachito.
Police! Open up!
We got a fortified door.
Need to breach.
Police!
Clear!
What's happening?
Did they get him?
They must've got...
Ignacio Varga...
You are a badass.
Suzanne...
Oh, Suzanne!
Suzanne,
I think we have something in common.
I think we have something
in common.
Suzanne,
I think we have something in common.
Bill!
- Bill...
- What?
Am I on Candid Camera again?
No, but by the way, you look great.
We gotta talk Bruno Leder.
Leder? Lost cause.
- I beg to differ.
- He assaulted a minor.
That oaf? You call him a minor,
I call him a menace.
Hey, my featherweight was simply
defending himself
against your raging bull.
No sale.
Leder's doing the full freight.
Welcome back to the law, McGill.
It's Goodman. And you'll be back.
- Hannah-Banana.
- Hi!
Hey. What's the word
on moving Tripp to Thursday?
It works on the calendar,
just have to check...
Consider them checked!
Veronica.
- She's finally clear. Go ahead.
- Hey, you got something for me?
Muchas gracias.
All right, let's see.
Long sleeves, covering the tats,
that's excellent.
Pull your hair back and lose the hardware.
Her Honour doth protest a chin pillar.
- But it's gonna close up.
- Into every life, a little rain must fall.
Meet me outside Courtroom 103 at 2:15.
Mitch! What say you
to moving Tripp to Thursday?
- Thursday works.
- Great. Thursday.
- What did you do?
- I don't know. What did I do?
Suddenly, Leder has witnesses?
What can I say? People step up.
From the sewer?
Life's rich pageant, who are we to judge?
Anyway, they saw what they saw.
Your beefy if youthful hooligan
cold-cocked my small potato.
So, what do you say,
sentence suspended,
six months' probation,
70 hours community service?
Yeah, I guess.
That's the spirit.
Suzanne,
I think we have something
in common.
Suzanne,
I think we have something in common.
- Suzanne, I...
- Jimmy!
- Howard, hey.
- Congratulations.
- You're back in the saddle.
- Yeah.
So...
Saul Goodman?
Yeah, that's me.
How's business?
It's good. It's very good. You?
Actually, it looks like it's gonna be
one of our best years ever.
I was wondering, any chance
you're available for lunch some time?
Lunch? Lunch? Really?
Yeah. Have Julie call my people.
I'm in the book. See you, Howard.
Suzanne,
I think we have a few things in common.
- Oh, I hope not.
- Oh, we do.
To the tune of 16 cases.
So you're busy, I'm busy.
How about we do a lightning round,
we'll settle these puppies, 20 minutes?
Don't you already have
an appointment with me?
Yeah, next Tuesday.
But, you know,
let's get it done right now.
How about we wait till next Tuesday?
My clients need answers.
Look, you've got a problem with me,
that's fine.
Don't take it out on my clients.
This isn't about your clients.
This is about your wallet.
- Okay, slow down...
- You're looking for turnover.
You wanna churn through more clients,
make more money.
That's your problem, not mine.
Suzanne, I'm outraged.
They say it's clear out there.
Should I tell the guys to move out?
Ignacio, it's your call.
Okay.
Hey!
Grab two Modelos.
Sit.
Your friend...
Krazy-8...
Yeah. Domingo.
I know him a long time.
How?
My family knows his family.
Has he ever been inside before?
No.
You worried about him?
No, man, he'll keep his mouth shut.
You want me to take care of it?
No.
I got something much better for him.
Come on.
I need you to call Beau Bindler
and set a meeting for tomorrow a.m.
so we can prep him for the deposition.
- Got it.
- And maybe bring bagels.
The guy eats his feelings.
Bagels, check.
- So yeah. See you tomorrow.
- All right.
Okay, let's review.
Your sister, Nancy, attacked
your girlfriend, also named Nancy,
with a curling iron?
I'm gonna need a face-to-face
so I know who I'm representing.
Look, I'm in an elevator.
Now I'm gonna lose you.
Hello? Okay.
Oh, no.
No, no, no.
No!
Hey! Hello?
Hi, this is ADA Ericsen.
We're in the south bank of the elevator...
- Goddamn it!
- Please!
Sorry, we're stuck between
floors two and three.
Yeah. How long?
Thanks.
And?
They're sending someone.
It's gonna be a minute.
I can't believe this.
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury,
I ask you,
what is this trial really about?
The state may call it vandalism,
but I call my client's brave act
of social justice
constitutionally-protected free speech.
- Really?
- That...
I gotta use my time.
Can you do it silently?
Yeah, sure.
My client is a young man
of deep moral fortitude...
Moral fortitude.
With a passion for progress.
A solid citizen.
No, no, no.
A dedicated citizen
with a voice that needs to ring out!
Name one.
I'm sorry?
One of the cases.
One of our cases?
Oh, let me think. Veronica Nix.
Motor vehicle theft?
With mitigating circumstances.
Such as...?
It was her aunt's minivan.
That's already baked in.
It was parked in the driveway.
The old lady was berating her, so...
So what?
So, you know,
good luck finding a jury
that's never been reamed out
by a relative.
- One year probation.
- Sold.
- Just like that?
- Yup.
What do you say we look at...
Jerome Sheehan?
So full year supervised for Drew Kirkman?
- How about 18 months?
- Eighteen it is.
Next up, we got...
Tanika Berman.
Four months jail?
The vampire stunt?
That was negligent arson.
Well, it was more of a prank gone wrong.
The knife was real.
Yeah, but it was used as a prop.
Was the fire a prop?
The blood was fake.
- How is that relevant?
- Petty misdemeanour.
Plus fourth-degree felony.
But drop the property damage?
Keep the weapons charge.
Fourteen months jail?
Sixteen.
Plus fines, TBD.
All right.
Oh, hey, look at that.
Oh, finally.
Twenty minutes.
Pleasure doing business with you.
Sure.
See you next week. For the last three!
Legal services for the other half?
So my brother's little problem?
His record will be cleaner
than Doris Day's Greatest Hits.
Catch you on the flip-flop.
Seventy hours is a breeze, trust me.
Think of all the good that you'll do.
Bruno, good talking to you.
I gotta jump.
Saul Goodman, speedy justice for you.
Miss Hower!
Hey, have I got good news.
I had to strap on the old armour
and do some jousting, but...
It's what knights used to do
back in olden times...
You know what? I'll call you back.
Mr. Varga, long time no see.
Get in.
Your timing isn't perfect.
I'm a little swamped right now.
We're just going for a ride, or...?