Where is this place?
Where am I?
I don't speak English.
Sit down, please.
Phone?
No, local calls only.
Please, be careful.
You should not be moving around.
The doctor will come soon.
Who brought me here?
Did Fring do this?
Gustavo Fring.
Sit down.
I will get you a glass of water.
HIGHWAY 2.5 MILES
Look what you've done to all my fine work.
What am I doing here?
You were meant to be recovering.
What's he want with me?
He's asked me to keep you alive.
Will you allow this?
Okay, listen up.
If Acker doesn't leave on his own by
quarter after, the sheriff's gonna evict.
Once that's done,
utilities will drop and cut their lines
while we take down the north fence.
Anything inside the place gets loaded up
and sent to storage.
Debris goes in the side dumpster.
Concrete's staying.
Disposal company's coming for it.
- We good so far?
- I think I might be seeing a hitch here.
Wait, who are you?
I'm Saul Goodman, attorney-at-law.
Glad to meet you.
- A better question might be, where are we?
- What's that supposed to mean?
Well, you know what?
It's coming up on the hour,
so a word to the wise,
if you let everyone go right now, you
might save half a day's salary in fringes.
What the hell are you talking about?
Deputies, great. Perfect timing.
- What's going on?
- He's a lawyer, says he has a hitch.
I'm Everett Acker's attorney, I'm just
dotting the I's in due diligence.
Well, I'm sorry, sir.
The eviction order's signed by a judge.
I'm sure it is.
Can I have a peek at that?
It's all correct, sir.
Sir, since you represent Mr. Acker, can you
make sure he cooperates with the eviction?
Can you make out the address on that?
1130 Arroyo Vista. Is there a problem?
Well, I mean, is that where we are?
There were house numbers on that mailbox,
plain as day. Eleven-thirty.
I don't see any.
Do you, deputy?
No. I don't.
Well, somebody messed with them.
This is 1130 Arroyo Vista.
This here's 1240 Arroyo Vista.
It's always been 1240 Arroyo Vista.
- Twelve-forty?
- Twelve-forty.
My client says it's 1240.
I got a plat map,
says we can straighten this out.
Well, all due respect
to whoever drew that map,
but Mr. Acker's been living here
for 30 years.
I think he knows his own address.
Sir, you got something
with an address on it?
Thank you.
1240 Arroyo Vista.
It's 1130. Anybody can print out
something like that.
You've got an order signed by a judge.
You know, we could get a surveyor up here
this afternoon. He'll clear everything up.
- That would lose us a full day.
- Listen, officer.
Before you go forcing an elderly veteran
from his home
and take everything he's got,
demolish a half century of hard work,
wouldn't you like to know
you got the right place?
Come on, all we're talking about
are some missing house numbers.
I have to make a call.
Everybody take 10!
After a year of running every
which way, now the guy gets a lawyer?
The lawyer comes in, the crazy comes out.
We had it straightened out
in a matter of hours.
It was a gimmick,
and not a particularly effective one.
It's costing us a day.
I call that plenty effective.
But we're past that. Tomorrow they're
finally tearing the place down, right?
That's the plan.
There's more?
Unfortunately,
there is another complication.
The lawyer Acker hired, it's Jimmy.
Jimmy? Your Jimmy?
Yes.
How did that happen?
Jimmy's been doing
some very aggressive marketing.
Looks like Acker picked up on it.
Okay, so, what now?
In fairness to you, I'll withdraw
from everything having to do
with the Tucumcari project.
Stef will step in for me.
She and Paige can see it through.
Kim's brought us this far.
I think Stef will do a fine job for us.
Of course, this is just Tucumcari
we're talking about.
I'll continue to handle everything else
as usual.
You know what?
I smell a rat.
Acker hiring Jimmy, that's no coincidence.
And I heard about the talking-to
you gave that guy.
Sounds like you tore him a new one.
- I... I wouldn't say that I...
- Here's what I think.
This fella saw you for the killer you are,
and he went and hired Jimmy specifically
to take you away from us.
Kevin, I...
I have to say,
I think that's very unlikely.
Trust me on this, Kim.
I know a scam when I see one, okay?
No disrespect. I'm sure
your associate's more than capable.
But I am not gonna let this guy deprive me
of the best in the business.
I think what Kim's trying to say is that
going home to the attorney
on the other side of this matter
could get awkward for her.
Is that right, Kim?
This gonna be tough on you at home?
It's not the personal side
that concerns me.
I just wouldn't want there to be
any question of conflict of interest.
Well, I'm not worried about that.
If you're willing to stick with it,
I say, why change horses midstream?
Kevin, are they waiting for you?
Oh, yeah.
Listen. I need that call centre.
We gotta get this thing moving now.
We got a lot of competitors out there,
and none of them
are waiting on some
crabby, old son of a bitch
to get their damn call centres built.
- Got it?
- Got it.
I know you do.
That an MRI machine
I saw back there?
It is.
And Fring paid for all this.
And all those
nice little houses out there,
I'm guessing there
are bales of meth inside.
There are no drugs here.
None, save the ones that I prescribe.
No men with guns either.
And if I wanna get back to where I belong?
You're welcome to leave.
You'd go back to the road
where I found you.
Five kilometres from here, there's a gate
that leads to the main road.
There are men at that gate.
Those men have guns, I'm guessing.
Perhaps.
I've never seen any weapons.
In any case, they will not stop you.
Twelve kilometres up the highway,
there's a small town.
Bigger than this place, but small.
There is a bus stop.
Once you're on that bus...
you're perhaps a day from El Paso.
However...
as you are now,
you would not survive the journey.
My advice is to rest.
Enjoy some of Señora Cortazar's
excellent cooking.
And take in some clean air.
Fring carts me all the way down here.
Why?
That I do not know.
You would have to ask him.
So you're just his on-call quack?
I am the quack who saved your life.
This is for infection.
Two every four hours for the next week.
This is for the pain.
Take it when you need it.
I'll be back to check on you
in three days.
Then, in a week or so,
perhaps you will be able to travel.
I can get a message to your family.
They're fine.
DEDICATED TO MAX
Hello, Howard.
Hi, Jimmy. This a bad time?
I'm a bit busy, to be honest, but...
what's up?
Just thinking about you.
How are you doing?
Fine.
Glad to hear it.
So, what's up?
Just touching base,
to see if you had any thoughts
on what we talked about.
What we talked about...
Oh, the job!
Oh, yeah, no, I mean, hey, I've been
thinking of nothing else, really.
Glad to hear it.
Any conclusions?
No. I'm just...
I'm mulling it over.
You know, reflecting, trying to give it
the consideration that it deserves.
Fair enough. I'm ready
to discuss the details when you are.
- Sounds good.
- And Jimmy...
Hey.
Smells interesting.
Oh, yeah, that's the curry.
I think it's our unlikely hero.
I'm gonna have to soak it overnight,
but it'll be ready first thing.
- So how'd it go with Kevin?
- Well, I'm still on the case.
No shit. That's great!
What happened?
You know, the more I wanted to go,
the more he wanted me to stay.
- Yeah, but he was pissed, right?
- A little bit.
Right, so where were you?
We were at his country club.
Cutting it close to tee time.
Pressure. That's excellent.
- He had to move his game actually.
- I love it!
Right. Now what?
You were sitting?
You were standing? I mean...
Paint a picture. Set the scene.
Come on.
Okay...
Paige and I meet him
outside the clubhouse.
And the three of us are at a table, and
he's over here like this, and he says...
Wait.
He sits like that?
- Yeah, he sits to the side.
- He's a side sitter?
I guess so.
Okay, well, you never told me
that he was a side sitter.
And that is gold.
Now, go on.
Okay, so he's sitting here,
and he says...
- I'm not gonna let him deprive...
- Wait, do the voice.
- I'm not gonna imitate him.
- Yes. Come on. Give me a nibble.
I mean, he's a good old boy, right?
So do he talk like this?
- No. No.
- Ding, dang, doo?
It's...
It's more like...
Lawyer comes in, crazy comes out.
I need that call centre real bad.
Of course, Kevin.
- Wait, are you being me?
- Yes, this is you.
Yes. Go on. Go on.
Okay. I'm not gonna
let him deprive me. No, sirree.
Kim,
I need it sooner than yesterday, got it?
- But, Kevin...
- No, you do whatever it takes.
I don't like waiting one bit.
Never have, never will.
Bottom line, breaking ground.
More statues.
Kim, you get him now.
Blah, blah, blah.
What?
Kevin?
Yes, Kim?
Would you care to take a shower with me?
Well, shoot.
I believe I would.
The international call cannot be placed.
Gracias.
- Hello.
- You know who this is?
How are you feeling?
Better, I trust?
You don't do anything without a reason.
Why am I here?
Now is not a good time.
What's going on here?
Sir, sir, please watch your step.
Stop right there!
- What the hell?
- Please stay out of the grid.
The what?
The area marked by the stakes.
Step out of it, please.
So, what about it, doctor?
Well, at a glance, I'd say
these pieces are likely contemporary.
I'll bet they are.
But we need to do
a systematic property search to be sure.
Really? Is that necessary?
- I'm afraid so.
- How long is this gonna take?
- A day or two. A week at the most.
- A week?
Come on.
You know this guy planted that stuff here.
This is the same thing
with the house numbers, all over!
No, that was an honest mistake.
This is the law!
Says who?
Says the New Mexico
Cultural Properties Act.
No.
You're not going along
with this. Seriously?
I have to make a call.
Sorry to interrupt.
He's suing on
behalf of the water district.
The water district?
Stef, you're good with regulatory law.
He's claiming there's a flaw
in the original land grant from 1846.
That's ridiculous.
Pat, you better drop everything else.
He's claiming our prime contractor
is an escaped felon.
You can't be serious.
Evan, I'm gonna give this one to you.
- I can see the Little Dipper.
- That's the Big Dipper.
Yeah.
Ah, right over here.
Is that Orion over there?
No. That's a satellite.
Officer, radiation's borderline.
We gotta get soil samples.
Do I have to ask?
I'm gonna have to...
You know.
Better safe than sorry.
Yes. Got it.
We have a problem.
I've always enjoyed your radio programme.
And I never thought I'd see a miracle
with my very own eyes.
That's right. Tucumcari.
Right off 54.
There's plenty of parking.
Well, thank you!
I'm a long-time listener
and a first-time caller.
Oh, I see it.
Hello, there.
What's your name, honey?
Goddamn it.
The crowd's already thinning out.
The image on the side of the house
has started to fade.
Tomorrow, we're bringing in additional
security and blocking off parking.
Answer me this.
If they're saying it's radioactive
over there,
how the hell is Acker still in that house?
That was really more of an OSHA situation.
The concern was for the construction crew.
Turns out,
the radiation level was completely safe.
We should be cleared
to resume construction on Thursday.
Assuming nothing else comes up.
Kim, bottom-line me here.
Clearly, this is all designed
to force us back to the table
and put us at a disadvantage
when we get there.
We gotta get back in the driver's seat
on this thing.
I say we sue them right back.
Sue Acker, sue Goodman.
Take the fight back to them.
Going down that road could take years.
They know this is costing Mesa Verde.
Time is on their side.
You got that right.
Rich, do you have anything to add?
Possibly.
What if there were a way
to turn this around on them?
What if you don't build the call centre?
Or not at that location, at least.
Suddenly, you're holding all the cards,
there's nothing to delay.
The other side's the one spending money
with no hope of recovering their expenses.
Wait, so...
What?
I understand
there's a viable alternative site.
You make the switch, and you've won.
Wait, hold up.
Didn't we let the other site go?
Lot 2375 is available,
and our permits still apply.
We'd still hit our target for
getting the call centre up and running.
We took the liberty
of running the numbers for you.
The financial hit would be negligible.
My dad did not raise me
to run from a fight.
Kevin, we're not saying...
I'm not gonna roll over and let some
low-life shyster bully me off my land.
No offence, Kim.
He's got one lawyer.
I got a room full of the best there is.
Here's what we're gonna do.
You're gonna figure out a way
to get them off my property.
That call centre's not moving
one goddamn inch!
You gave it your best shot.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
You went the distance for the old S.O.B.
Above and beyond.
- You should feel good about that.
- You think so.
You gave Acker more than he deserved.
And let's be real.
Putting me on this, that was bad.
I mean, if anyone found out...
You risked a lot for this guy.
Look, this time next week,
Acker will be living somewhere else.
Is that really such a big deal?
Plus, Mesa Verde,
that's your bread and butter.
You can only push them so far.
There's always another play.
But the rational thing to do here
is close the deal.
Get the guy a few bucks.
Pop the champagne with the other winners
and smile like you mean it.
You want a beer? I'm gonna get one.
Or?
Jimmy?
There's no reason on God's green earth
to take this further.
It's not worth it.
Or?
Or...
we go after Kevin Wachtell.
Gets nasty. Gets personal.
Gets dangerous.
Okay.
- Yeah?
- Hey, it's me.
- Yes, it is.
- Great.
Listen, I got something for you.
Hear me out, because this is a good thing.
I'm sorry, I'm getting
some kind of reverb or something.
Are you in a tunnel, or...?
Yes.
What's that?
Yes. I'm in a tunnel.
Okay.
Anyway,
this is not like that other thing, okay?
It's a straight
piece of oppo research.
This is a lawyer hiring a P.I.
What do you say?
So you're back to being a lawyer?
Yeah. Yeah, totally legit. So...
Did I mention it's a paying gig?
- I'm not available.
- Say again?
No.
Señora.
Good. Good...
Thank you.
Oh, man.
Take it easy.
You don't need to be doing that.
Don't be stubborn.
It's okay. I'm fine. Thank you.
You got this guy where?
Same place as Huell.
So it's like some kind
of underground Craigslist?
It's just a guy who knows people.
People of a certain type.
- He's very discreet.
- Well, he'd have to be.
Here goes.
It'll be fine. Just watch.
I thought I was going to a law office.
Yeah. This is a law office.
Gotcha.
Giselle, this is Mr. X.
It's my work name.
You know,
those things are full of parasites.
Yeah. Duly noted.
The conference room is in back.
Yeah.
- I did the full work-up as tasked.
- And?
Snake eyes. Bupkes. Nada.
Guy is squeaky clean.
That's impossible.
I mean, everybody's got something.
Not this time. You got an Eagle Scout
with a six-figure income.
Arrests?
DUI.
In college, homecoming weekend.
Thirty-four years ago.
Is that what you're looking for?
Girlfriends? Offshore accounts?
No secret bank accounts.
No extra phones, no lunchtime quickies,
no lady friend, no boy toy.
The guy's dull. Like,
Saturday night in Salt Lake City dull.
No offence, but your work
is sounding kind of superficial.
Superficial?
Yeah.
Yeah, not hardly. I went the distance.
I did a self-guided tour of his domicile.
All seven bedrooms, four and a half baths.
Hold on. You're saying
you broke into his house?
Giselle, this is probably one
of those tricks-of-the-trade things.
Probably just focus on the what
and skip over the how.
I'd like to know.
He has a security system
with a touchy upstairs window sensor.
I trip it a couple of times
with an Airsoft...
A BB gun.
The alarm drives the housekeeper crazy.
So I show up in coveralls, toolbox,
alarm company ID,
and she is more than happy
to let me have the run of the place.
Does that meet with your approval?
All right, so you get in,
and you find what?
Like I said. Nothing.
No, there's no such thing as nothing.
Okay? We want specifics.
You want specifics? Okay, well.
I got specifics.
That's the home office.
Now, I spent an extra four minutes
opening the floor safe.
Nothing but life insurance policies,
a couple of rings
and a commemorative half-dollar.
The guy's old school. No computers.
Motel art on the walls,
paperwork on his desk.
What kind of paperwork?
You knock yourself out.
Now, I may not be a nail salon lawyer,
but I know legit when I see it.
So you gonna withdraw
the superficial now?
You think you could get
into his downtown office?
Sure. I could.
But there's a better way.
Yeah?
Yeah. I get two more guys.
Guys who know how to handle themselves.
Now, we roll up to the subject
in an unmarked van.
We grab him, put him in a bag,
and we take him out to the desert.
We're done here.
End of the day, the banker's giving you
everything you're after, all right?
- We're done.
- No, no, no.
Look, you get keys to the kingdom,
guaranteed.
Okay, Sgt. Slaughter,
back to the paintball field.
Okay. The grown-ups
need to talk. Let's go.
That's fine.
I'm just providing options for you.
All right. This is the way out.
Exit through the gift shop.
- All right.
- Don't touch anything, please.
- I will not. Let me say on this...
- I know you're...
I don't know what to say. I'm gonna
complain to management about that clown.
My usual guy is very reliable.
What? What is it?
Got a minute?
Sure.
How's everything?
All good. Kind of crunched, still
dealing with the Tucumcari situation.
And the pro bono work?
It's good.
Is something up?
Listen,
I'm thinking
you could take a break from Mesa Verde.
A break?
A pair of mineral rights beefs
just came in,
they have your name on them.
You can split your time between that
and your pro bono clients.
- Mesa Verde is my client.
- And they still will be.
I'll just step in and take point,
just on a temporary basis.
And, of course, this goes without saying,
this won't affect
any of your compensation,
and that includes your bonus.
You know, Mesa Verde is fully informed
of any potential conflicts.
Kevin signed off himself.
Still, I think you're going to need
to take a break.
I don't understand
where this is coming from.
Don't you?
Kim.
Sometimes the less said, the better.
- And why is that?
- Do we have to?
Yes, we do.
All right.
First, I had to twist your arm to get you
down to Tucumcari for the eviction.
Then you put the full-court press on Kevin
to change sites.
That doesn't work, and abracadabra,
your boyfriend's opposing counsel.
I told you, I explained the situation
to Kevin and Paige.
Yeah. I know you did.
And I'm sorry to say,
I'm just not buying it.
Rich? Rich. Hold on.
What are you saying exactly?
- Let's talk in my office.
- You are accusing me of something.
Go ahead and say it.
Are you talking about malfeasance?
Working against my client's interest?
- Please.
- Rich, tell me.
You know I worked my ass off to get here.
You know that.
- Yes, I do know.
- So tell me.
Please tell me why I would risk everything
for some squatter.
Why? I don't understand. Are you trying
to protect the firm? From what?
Kim, I am not trying to protect the firm,
I am trying to protect you.
I don't need your protection.
I need to represent my client.
If that's how you want it.
So, what do you want from me?
I think it best that Señora Cortazar
doesn't know about our association.
I like to keep my business
as far from here as possible.
You look much better.
I am glad.
So I'm here to see what a big heart
you have, is that the idea?
You throw money at these people,
they bow low.
As far as the people here are concerned,
I am the doctor's friend. Nothing more.
They have no idea you financed
the whole place.
I prefer it that way.
The anonymous benefactor.
Well, that must make you feel pretty good.
And is that supposed
to balance the scales?
Make up for everything else you do?
It makes up for nothing.
I am what I am.
What is this place?
Call it a memorial.
To what?
I already told you
what you can do with your money.
You seem like a guy who can take a hint,
so what are we doing?
It seems to me that
you are at a crossroads.
You can continue as you are.
Drinking.
Estranged from your family.
Brawling with street hoods.
We both know how that ends.
- Yeah?
- You have another choice.
Work for you as a button man.
I'm in a war. I need a soldier.
I'm gonna work for one drug dealer,
killing other drug dealers?
That's your idea of a choice.
You know better. You have met them.
You know what they are.
Meaning the Salamancas.
And you are so very different from them?
Yes.
I am different.
Why me?
Because I believe that you understand.
Understand what?
Revenge.