Jimmy?
Yeah.
It's me.
I'm okay.
You sure?
All right. Stay put,
call me if there's a problem.
Doesn't look like anyone's been down
that road. Definitely no one official.
Bodies, trucks, it's all still there.
A couple of flatbeds headed their way.
They'll clear it all out.
Like it never happened.
And the one who followed you?
We'll be damn lucky
if we ever find that guy.
Well, that'll have to do.
He's in the middle of nowhere.
Don't go to sleep yet.
We gotta work on your story.
All right. Let's do it.
De Guzman. Jorge.
- Seven million dollars?
- Yep.
I'm fine.
Seven million.
Your client has $7 million.
Where'd it come from?
It's not for me to ask
where a client gets his money.
And just who exactly is your client?
Jorge De Guzman.
Yes, hello?
This is extra.
And now, Mr. De Guzman?
Well. You must have a story.
Car trouble. Yeah.
Broke down about six miles
from the pick-up site.
You know there's no cell reception
out there, right?
Car trouble.
Yeah. Just kaput.
So...
Why so long?
It's not that far back to the main road.
You didn't just hitchhike?
I thought of that.
But you know, 7 mil in cash,
I was kind of afraid who might pick me up.
I didn't think it was worth the risk.
I walked north.
Probably not the smartest move,
but after a night
lost in the desert, I made it.
Well, that was the right call.
Hey. Hey. You did good, huh?
Anyway, listen, I wouldn't be too happy.
Seven mil, it really sent up a huge flare.
They're looking into you.
I don't know how long Jorge De Guzman
is gonna hold up.
Hey, listen, by the time
these dipshits figure it out,
I will be long gone, man.
Back home in Mexico, you know?
Yeah.
Hey! Hey, hey. But don't worry.
You and me? We're not done.
We're gonna do things. Big things.
Friend of the cartel, right?
- Right.
So hey, my cousins. They pay you?
Yep.
Perfecto.
So make sure you buy something nice
for the wife. Man, she's a looker, huh?
My... My what?
Yeah! She came by to see me.
Hey, nice job, eh?
I mean, for somebody
who marries that far up...
Bien hecho, man.
Respect, you know?
Let me help.
There.
Oh, my God, Jimmy.
You need to go to an emergency room.
I'm okay. I'm okay. I cleaned it out
real good at the truck stop.
All right. Well, let's at least just go
get you an IV, huh? You're dehydrated.
No. I don't need an IV.
I've been pounding sports drinks nonstop.
- I'm really okay.
- All right.
Come on, you're gonna get in this bath,
though, it'll help your skin.
What is this? Cream of Wheat?
Oatmeal. It's an oatmeal bath.
Anti-inflammatory.
It'll help your sunburn.
- Is the temp okay?
- Yeah. It's good.
You sure?
Yeah.
Okay. You don't want any food
or anything else to drink?
No, I'm good.
I just need to sit. This is good.
I can't believe you walked
through the desert alone for 36 hours.
I... I can't even fathom it.
That's right.
All by myself.
So...
Is there anything you wanna tell me?
- About?
- Lalo.
You saw Lalo?
Yeah.
Jimmy, short of going to the police,
Lalo was the only lead
I had to figure out...
Kim, you have to stay away
from people like Lalo.
- Jimmy...
- You don't see Lalo.
I see Lalo, okay?
- I'm in the game. You're not in the game.
- What?
The game?
Listen, it was perfectly safe.
I was at the MDC, surrounded by guards,
like any lawyer visiting a client, okay?
But he's not your client.
He's my client.
So please, just keep away.
Jimmy, I was worried about you.
And I'm worried about you.
Kim, when I was out there...
I didn't think I was gonna make it.
I thought I was done.
I was that close to giving up.
And the only thing that kept me going...
was knowing that you were here.
So...
Okay.
I won't see Lalo again.
Good.
After all this...
was it worth it?
Go look in the bag.
The bag in the living room.
It's on the chair.
It's a grey bag.
You see it?
Yeah, Jimmy.
I see it.
That's what it's all about.
Six guys, three vehicles, heavily armed.
My guess is they followed
the Salamanca cousins up from Chihuahua,
trailing the money
but not wanting to take these two guys on.
Now, I'm no expert, but they had tattoos.
Same symbol I saw on a job back east.
A Colombian gang.
Draw it for me.
These men were hired.
By who?
I trust you heard the good news.
Gustavo, which good news is that?
Our colleague has been released
by the American authorities.
At a substantial price, but he's free.
And I'm told he will be returning home
to continue operations.
That is good news.
But coming south, you say?
That's correct.
Forfeiting bail is the only way
to assure he remains out of prison.
Well, then.
All will be returning to normal.
And I trust your run of bad luck
will be behind you.
Bad luck?
The DEA. The fire. The arrest.
My hope is that it's over.
Yes. I believe the coming weeks
will be our best yet.
Excellent.
I'll pass on the good news.
Thank you. Enjoy your evening.
I just spoke to the man
responsible for the attack.
Someone we need to worry about?
He was trying to protect his own business
by protecting our business.
If that's him trying to help...
He knows nothing
of what we are trying to accomplish.
Once Salamanca is south of the border,
our actions must be unimpeachable.
Any reflection on me
will not be greeted with kindness.
All right.
Yes?
There's one other thing we should discuss.
Nacho Varga. He wants out.
He's done everything we asked,
he held up his end.
I think it's time we cut him loose.
I see no reason to give up an asset.
Once Salamanca's dealt with,
we have no use for Varga.
He's the only guy they have
running things up here.
He disappears,
Salamanca operation falls apart.
Varga stays.
Better to control the opposition
without their knowledge.
You have a gun to his father's head.
That doesn't sit with me.
You wanna keep Varga for the long run,
I don't think fear is a great motivator.
A dog who bites every owner he's had...
can only be disciplined with a firm hand.
Or put down.
He's taking care of business tonight.
Tomorrow morning,
he's seeing Hector to say goodbye.
After that, I drive him south.
He didn't tell me where.
All I know is I'm dropping him off
and somebody else is taking him
over the border.
Is that it?
Yeah. Hey...
Once he's down, that's it, right?
He's done?
Just do what you're told.
Don't worry about it.
Hey.
Hungry?
You good with cereal?
Or you want me to try an omelette?
Cereal.
Probably the safest thing for my stomach.
- Okay.
- I'll get it.
No, no, no. I got it. Just...
Just relax.
You going in late today?
I just thought I'd stay home today.
Kim, I can take care of myself.
Well, I already called in sick,
so you're stuck with me.
Damn it!
Shit.
- I'm sorry.
- That's okay.
I guess my stomach's
just not ready for this yet.
It's okay.
Not a big deal.
Are you sure you don't have to go in
to work?
Yeah, I'm sure.
We both need to take it easy.
How about a day without drama?
That sounds real good actually.
Oh, hi, Skinny.
- Hello, Ruth.
- Well, Maisie's here.
How are you?
Tell me, is the lord of the universe in?
Yes, he's in, in a bad humour.
Somebody must have stolen the crown jewel.
- Shall we announce you?
- Oh, no, no. I'll blow my own horn.
Bruce, you should better wait here.
I'll be back in 10 minutes.
Even 10 minutes is a long time
to be away from you.
- What did you say?
- What?
- Well...
- Go on.
Well, go ahead.
Well, I just said, even 10 minutes
is a long time to be away from you.
I heard you the first time.
I like it,
that's why I asked you to say it again.
I can stand being spoiled.
The gentleman I'm going in to see
did very little spoiling.
I'd like to spoil him just once.
You sure you don't want me to go with you?
- Oh, no. I can handle it.
- If things get rough, I'm here.
Hi, Hildy. Welcome back.
Saul Goodman. Speedy justice for you.
I'm sorry. No. Today...
It's impossible today. I can't help you.
Yeah, that's right.
Wait, what are they saying?
Are you...?
Just wait 45 minutes. I can be there.
What? Jimmy, no.
Yeah.
You tell them I'm on my way.
Jimmy. Jimmy.
You can barely walk.
What are you doing?
It's my client. He's in big trouble.
They're trying to kill his plea deal
because his buddy was carrying weed.
What? Okay.
So get a continuance.
You don't have to do this today.
No, this guy's scared out of his mind.
I wouldn't feel right leaving him hanging.
Jimmy, look, I know you're lying.
And I know something terrible
happened in the desert.
This isn't about our deal, I'm not
insisting or forcing you to tell me.
I just...
want you to know that I'm here for you.
And you can tell me, okay?
No judgements.
You're right.
Something did happen out there.
When I was in the desert...
I had to drink my own pee.
I was out of water, and in order
to survive, I had to drink pee.
Well... Yeah, that's it, so...
And there you go. Look...
I will recover,
and we never need to mention this again.
I'm gonna go get changed,
and I'm gonna get down there.
Kim. Feeling better?
Oh, yeah. Just a 24-hour thing.
It passed.
I thought I should come in
and prep the Colorado meeting.
They moved that up to this morning.
Stef handled it.
There was no pushback
from Boulder city council?
Stef cleared up the conditional use issue.
Everything's moving forward.
Wow, that's great.
Great.
Well...
Okay.
You wanted to write letters
to the planning board in Broomfield.
Right. Yes, that's right.
I'll get started on that,
if you can just get me those names.
- List is on your desk.
- Of course. Great.
First letter is for Mr. Armand Bakaris,
chairman of
the Planning and Zoning Commission,
and let's just CC the vice chair,
Elaine Perlman, while we're at it.
Dear Mr. Bakaris,
Mesa Verde Bank and Trust
respectfully submit
the following request
for your consideration.
In regards to the resolution number...
PZ 2004-dash-36 variance appeal
to allow for a six-and-one-half foot
encroachment into the...
into the minimum required rear setback...
minimum required rear setback for a...
drive-thru awning to allow...
Strike that. To facilitate...
access to the property at...
841 North.
So can you call his assistant and get
some intel on what he's into right now?
Kim, they told me you were out sick today.
Yeah. No, I...
Rich, you free to talk?
Yeah, is everything okay?
Yeah. I just need a minute.
Okay.
So, what's up?
I...
What?
Marcie, can you do me a favour?
Copy all the pro bono files
and send the originals to my place.
Also, no rush, but
box up my diplomas and photos, please.
Are we moving offices?
I don't want you to worry.
I talked to Rich,
you'll be reassigned to another partner.
Wait, reassigned?
Oh, and they're gonna want these.
I'm parked in my usual spot.
If I left anything else in there,
just put it in the box.
Thank you, Marcie.
- Good luck.
- Kim...
Look...
Cops are gonna go crazy looking for me
for a few months.
Maybe a year.
Then the heat will die down,
like it always does.
Until then,
Ignacio or one of the other guys,
they'll get you anything you need.
Tio, come on. Don't be this way.
There are still lots of moves
to make against Fring.
When I'm home, I'll have Eladio's ear.
I'll make sure
he's sick of the Chicken Man.
Then,
what's Fring's...
will be ours.
Eleven months from now, Tuco gets out
of prison. He'll run things here.
I know, I know. Tuco. He's a hothead.
When he's on the stuff, he's...
We'll make sure someone is on him.
He'll stay clean.
Hi, there.
We're bringing birthday cake out
for Louise, one of our residents.
Everyone's going to sing.
Hector really doesn't like to miss these.
Yeah.
Could you give us a minute, please?
Family is everything.
Okay, guys.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday dear Louise
Where to?
Go. The border.
Hey, that was something.
What happened in there?
Hey, look, don't feel bad.
You can't win them all.
But that one? Sheesh, I thought for sure
I was gonna lose.
There wasn't a chance in hell
I was supposed to win that one.
But there you were.
Snatching defeat
from the jaws of victory.
Ball in your hand, at the goal line,
fumble!
Law students are gonna review the
Goodman Debacle as a teachable moment.
So at least there's that.
And think of all the kids
you'll help learn what not to do
when faced with underwhelming odds.
So embarrassing.
You'll probably have to change your name.
Again.
Hey, just so you know,
I don't think any less of you.
You're still a lawyer.
You can start talking any time.
You said this goes away.
So, what's the time frame on that?
It's different for different people,
I suppose.
For me.
When will this be over for me?
Well, here's what's gonna happen.
One day...
One day, you're gonna wake up,
eat your breakfast, brush your teeth,
go about your business.
And sooner or later,
you're gonna realise
you haven't thought about it.
None of it.
And that's the moment
you realise you can forget.
When you know that's possible,
it all gets easier.
But what about you? Like...
What happened out there
doesn't bother you?
Them wanting to steal the 7 million
didn't work for me.
Not to mention, they wanted to shoot you
in the head.
It was them or it was us.
Cut and dried.
They were in the game.
What about Fred?
From Travel Wire.
Was he in the game?
No.
There was a lot wrong
with what happened there.
Yeah. Lalo.
Lalo killed that guy. And for what?
He killed that guy, and we're helping him.
All this shit, just to...
So he can get out of jail
and just get away?
It's not the end of the story.
Wait a minute.
What does that mean?
Not the end of the story.
What are you saying?
Are you saying what I think you're saying?
Something gonna happen to Lalo?
I didn't say that.
Oh, Jesus. What have I gotten myself
involved with here?
- Look, just tell me, what are you saying...
- Look.
We all make our choices.
Now, those choices, they put us on a road.
Sometimes those choices seem small,
but they put you on the road.
You think about getting off.
But eventually, you're back on it.
And the road we're on led us out
to the desert,
and everything that happened there,
and straight back
to where we are right now.
And nothing...
Nothing can be done about that.
Do you understand that?
I can't believe...
I can't believe there's, like,
over a billion people on this planet,
and the only person
I have to talk about this to is you.
You want me to wait?
Nah.
They'll be here.
Really. Go.
You sure?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Look, I'll be in touch, man.
Hey, that fire you did at Fring's...
That was good work, man.
We're gonna do more.
You'll see.
Sounds good.
Take me back up the road.
Slow.
What for?
Just do it.
Six or seven miles back.
What are we looking for?
The lawyer said his car broke down.
Six miles from the pick-up.
Where is it?
Whoa, let me out here.
Let me out.
Come.
Back to Albuquerque.
What about Marco and Leonel?
What about them? I'll get them a message.
Let's go.
Jimmy?
You okay?
Yeah, what time is it?
It's 6:30.
Oh, sorry.
You wanna go back to sleep?
No. I'm up.
You can still go to a doctor, you know?
No harm in getting checked out.
I'm fine.
I think I just need food.
I haven't eaten since...
well, really, before everything.
Okay.
Maybe go easy.
Just some soup at first.
I'm okay, Kim. Really.
I know.
Good.
What about you? You seem...
worried, maybe?
No. No, no. It's just...
I have news, but it can wait.
- Let's get some food in you first.
- What news?
- What kind of news?
- Nothing bad.
So that means it's good news?
Yeah. I think so.
Great. Let me hear it.
I...
quit Schweikart and Cokely.
And I gave up Mesa Verde.
How about we get some food together?
Wait.
What happened? Did somebody
say something about what we did?
- No.
- What, was it Rich?
Nobody said anything.
It just, it felt right.
It felt right. What? How?
I...
I just... I keep pushing Mesa Verde away
to do my pro bono work, and then...
when you were gone,
I didn't know what happened.
I mean, I...
I thought you were dead. So...
That was... All of it helped me.
To see what's important and what isn't.
So you're just gonna throw it all away?
I mean, you busted your ass for all of it.
I'm not throwing it away. I did S&C.
I did Mesa Verde. I achieved that.
I had that experience,
but it doesn't make me happy.
Look, it's been a rough couple of days.
So why don't you just hold off
on a final decision?
Call Rich,
tell him you're thinking it over.
I already talked to Rich.
And I called Paige.
We had a nice, very long conversation.
It's done.
Then I spent the afternoon
in the courthouse with pro bono clients
without Mesa Verde hanging over my head.
Best afternoon I've had in a long time.
All right, pro bono is wonderful.
It is, but pro bono means no money.
So, what's the plan here?
I don't know. But I'll figure it out.
Okay. Leaving Schweikart, I get that.
It's a bunch of stuffed shirts.
But Mesa Verde?
That's like leaving the Yankees
to play amateur ring toss.
No, it's not. I'm leaving something
that makes zero difference in the world
to help people who are actually in need.
This is a bad idea.
What?
Look. We all make choices, right?
And those choices, they put us on a road.
And the road has good choices,
and it has bad choices.
This is a bad choice road.
- What are you even talking about?
- I'm...
Saying that bad choices lead to bad roads
that lead to bad places.
When you decided to be Saul Goodman,
I didn't get it.
Still don't, really.
But I stood by your decision.
And I'm not changing my identity,
I'm just leaving a job.
What I did was completely different.
- How?
- I was leaving failure for success.
It's not different.
You believed it was right for you.
Give me the courtesy of believing
this is right for me.
And I'm giving you a reality check.
This is too far, too fast.
This is really none of your damn business.
- Yeah?
- Listen to me.
Put your phone down.
Leave it on, so I can hear.
So you can hear... Hear what?
Do what I said right now.
Put it down somewhere it can't be seen.
Jimmy.
Hey, guys.
Can I come in?
Lalo.
Thought you'd be down south.
Enjoying your freedom.
Yeah, well...
Had some business to attend to.
Told you he'd be back.
Nice. I like it.
Hey, look, you want a drink?
We got some beer in the fridge.
Unless you're not staying that...
You shouldn't... I'm sorry.
Sorry, you shouldn't do that.
It upsets the fish.
Look, you wanna talk, we can talk.
But Kim was just stepping out, so...
Nah. She can stay.
I mean, she is part of the legal team,
right?
Hey, relax, sit down.
We're just gonna talk.
Come on. Sit.
Okay.
So...
Tell me what happened.
What happened?
Yeah, when you picked up the money.
Just walk me through it.
What I told you already?
Yes.
Fine. I picked up the money
from your cousins.
It was right where
you told me it would be.
Driving back, my car crapped out.
It was about six or seven miles
from the pick-up site.
There's no phone service.
So I walked north.
Through the desert all night.
Well, I slept a little.
But then in the morning, I walked again,
until I made it to a truck stop.
I went into the bathroom and cleaned up.
I bought some clothes, and I called a cab.
And delivered the money,
took them a couple of hours to count it.
Usual rigmarole, and then I saw you.
Tell me again.
What?
I picked up the money
from those two fine gentlemen.
My car broke down after
about just 10 minutes.
There's no phone service.
And I was afraid to hitchhike
because of how much money was.
And I ran out of water.
So I had to drink my own pee.
A lot of it. So you wanted details,
there you go.
And then I finally
made it to a truck stop.
I called a cab. Then I waited.
And then he took me
directly to the courthouse.
I paid your bail and I got you out.
I'm not sure what you're looking
for here, but...
there you go.
I just wanna hear the story.
Lalo, this is exactly what he told me,
so if you could just...
I just like to hear the story.
I mean...
I paid a lot of money for that story,
so I think I can hear it
as much as I want.
So...
tell me again.
I picked up two big bags of money.
Seven million dollars.
Two heavy, heavy bags
that you paid me to get.
I put them in the trunk of my car.
And about 10 minutes later,
my car's engine went.
I tried to fix it
but it was overheated or something.
So I walked north through the desert.
I walked and I walked and I walked,
with those heavy, heavy bags.
and I finally made it to a truck stop.
And I went right to the bathroom,
and I stuck my head under the faucet,
and I bought
a giant pack of energy drinks,
and I called a taxi, and I waited.
I don't know what the problem is, but...
can she leave here?
She doesn't need to be here.
She had nothing to do with it.
It was me.
It was all me.
- It was all you, huh?
- Yeah.
What'd you do, Saul?
Whatever you think I did.
- I don't really know. I just...
- I saw your car.
- Okay.
- You push it in a ditch?
I what?
Did you push it in a ditch?
- I don't think so.
- You don't think so?
Well, I mean,
you either did or you didn't.
So which one is it?
I don't know what you want.
Do you want the money back?
Because it's in a bag in the other room.
You can take it.
I just want what happened.
- I told you what happened.
- Did you?
Look, okay...
Are you...
Are you kidding me with this?
- Kim...
- Do you know what he did for you?
Seven million dollars of your money.
He hauled it across a goddamn desert
without one penny missing.
And he got you out of jail
for a murder that,
let's face it,
you're definitely guilty of.
He did everything you asked.
And went way beyond what any other lawyer
would ever do.
So, what exactly is it
that you're getting at?
What do you want?
I found his car in a ravine.
Bullet holes on the side.
So I'm just waiting to hear
how that happened.
Bullet holes.
That's it?
Look, I don't know what it's like
where you're from.
But here in New Mexico,
you leave a soda can out,
someone's taking a shot at it.
That... That's what you're on about?
You don't think it's possible
a couple of yahoos with guns
shot up a piece of junk car
and then rolled it down in a ditch?
End of story?
What kind of operation
are you running anyway?
Tell me.
Because I think I know why you sent him
to do this job.
It's obvious.
You have no one else you can trust.
Right?
So you sent some lawyer through the desert
with your 7 million bucks?
That... I... No offence,
but you need to get your house in order.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah. Really.
If you don't trust your men
with your money,
you have bigger problems
than if you trust Saul Goodman.
And for the record, he doesn't lie.
Not to me. Not to his clients.
He's telling you the truth.
But next time you have a bunch of money
and no one you can trust,
leave him out of it. Okay?
Try a wire transfer.
Try a shell company, or...
You've heard of the Cayman Islands, right?
Jesus, get your shit together.
And stop torturing the one man
who went through hell to save your ass.
What now?
Mexico.
Back to the same place?
Nope. Change of plans.
Come on, Ignacio, go.
We got a long way ahead of us.