And anything that already happened,
we're not going back over all that.
Let's just focus on from here on out.
Right. Past is past.
And moving forward...
If I have the urge
to not tell you something,
then I've gotta tell you.
Right. Full disclosure.
And it works both ways.
Works both ways.
And mute.
Okay, what if I have the urge
to not tell you something, but I tell you,
and you don't like what you hear?
I just wanna know what's going on.
- Yeah, but...
- Jimmy.
We'll cross that bridge
when we come to it.
There he is.
So we're really doing this, huh?
Yeah, it looks that way.
- Am I late?
- Nope.
Cool. Good morning.
- Thanks for coming.
- Good to see you.
- Shall we?
- Yeah.
What's up?
Want me to hold the rings for you?
Oh, there's no rings.
Well, I can fix that easy.
I seen a clerk downstairs,
had a nice rock.
Probably about a half a carat.
Huell, no, I...
This is a different kind of thing.
Oh, it's like that.
Then we should do it up right then,
for the rugrat.
No, there's no rugrat.
Well, you at least gonna
take her somewhere after this?
Little honeymoon?
I got a friend who runs a B&B in Roswell,
get you a good deal.
How about we take a raincheck on that?
We just need to get this done. Feel me?
This is a legal arrangement.
This way, if I get into trouble,
they can't make her testify against me.
You getting hitched for that?
Yeah.
Yeah. That's all this is. You got it?
Is she gonna be a McGill or Goodman?
Wexler. I... I gotta go finish this.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Sir, do you have documentation
of your two previous dissolutions?
Yeah.
Great. One sec.
This okay with you?
Of course.
Yeah. I just mean...
this might not be what you dreamed of
when you were 12.
Jimmy, it's not about that.
This is just, you know...
everything we talked about.
Right. Right. I know.
Just making sure.
All set. I just need 25 dollars.
I got it.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Been that kind of day.
So...
Wexler-McGill?
Yes.
- You picked the short vows, that right?
- Yes.
And you have your witnesses.
Okay, then.
Here we go.
Do you, James Morgan McGill,
take Kimberly Wexler...
No middle name.
To be your lawfully wedded wife,
to have and to hold,
from this day forward,
for better, for worse,
for richer, for poorer,
in sickness and in health,
till death do you part?
I do.
And do you, Kimberly Wexler,
take James Morgan McGill
to be your lawfully wedded husband,
to have and to hold,
from this day forward,
for better, for worse,
for richer, for poorer,
in sickness and in health,
till death do you part?
I do.
Do you have the rings?
- We...
- We didn't do that.
No rings.
Okey-dokey.
Then by the power vested in me
by the state of New Mexico,
I now pronounce you husband and wife.
You may kiss.
One more. One more.
So lunch is definitely out?
Sorry, I just can't get away.
But I'll be home early tonight.
Me too.
Saul Goodman, speedy justice for you.
I've been calling you.
Yeah, I had a busy morning.
Go to lockup.
Your client's waiting for you.
My client? What...?
Who got picked up this time?
Jorge De Guzman.
Who the hell is Jorge De Guzman?
Who do you think?
State v. Jorge De Guzman,
case CR2004003022.
Mr. De Guzman.
Murder in the first degree,
robbery while armed with a deadly weapon,
tampering with evidence, arson...
Your Honour, my client waives
the reading of the remaining charges.
How does he plead?
Not guilty. On all charges.
I'd like to schedule a pre-trial hearing
in six weeks.
And I'm going to deny bond.
- Your Honour...
- That's my decision.
Thank you for making time for us
on such short notice.
We wanted to tell you, face-to-face,
how much everyone in the firm regrets
what happened yesterday.
The situation in Tucumcari spiralled
out of control,
and we take full responsibility.
Kevin, you chose me as your attorney,
and that was the best day
of my professional life.
Yesterday was the worst day
I can't tell you how much I regret
that I let you down.
But I want you to know
that if you choose
to move forward with me, and with us...
nothing like that will ever happen again.
No one's denying that things
went off course,
but let's keep in mind
that over the last 18 months,
we've opened 24 new branches.
And until Tucumcari,
the legal work has been...
flawless.
Well...
Kim, you dropped the ball,
that's for sure.
And, heh, with all your smarts,
whole office full of associates
and fancy degrees...
you get rolled over by...
Well, you know what happened.
I expected more.
Thanks for coming in.
Thank you, Kevin.
- Paige.
- Thank you.
Kim, one more thing.
This fellow, McGill,
or Goodman, whatever...
You could do a whole lot better.
I'll say fifty-fifty.
But we gave it a shot.
- Rich, we can't leave it like this.
- Oh, he'll stew for a bit.
- And then we'll see.
- And if he does stick with us?
Then what?
We walk on eggshells forever?
What's our alternative?
- We counted at seven, right?
- Yes, but after the survey...
Sorry to interrupt, but do you mind if
we take just another minute of your time?
I guess.
Kevin, no matter what our relationship
looks like moving forward,
we owe you the truth.
And the truth is,
you ignored our advice.
Oh, so this is my fault?
We said Mesa Verde should reconsider
the site for the call centre.
You declined.
We advised you to keep the purchase lot
as an investment.
You declined.
And we advised you to leave that meeting
when it became apparent
that the other side was negotiating
in bad faith.
You declined.
At every point,
we gave you the best guidance we could,
and at every point,
you chose to go your own way.
We are your attorneys,
and it is our job to advise you.
The decisions will always be yours,
but if you continue to ignore us...
then this is the wrong relationship.
And, Kevin, I have to tell you,
whoever represents you in the future...
I hope you're gonna listen to them
a little bit better.
That it?
All right, then.
See you on Thursday.
Okay.
Well...
I guess we'll get out of your hair.
Thursday.
JMM. What's that?
- Oh, that's my motto.
- Yeah?
Justice Matters Most.
Okay, brass tacks...
How solid is this De Guzman thing?
Because if they find out
you're not who they think you are,
- that could be a little...
- It's not gonna be a problem.
Great.
First up, we gotta get the murder rap
down to manslaughter.
Now I think that the DA's primed
to cut a deal,
so I say, make them come to us,
power move...
- No.
- No?
Nope. No deal.
- Here's the thing about going to trial...
- No, no, no.
No trial. No deal.
Okay, yeah, sure, it's just...
Well, what did you have in mind?
- You're gonna get me out on bail.
- Bail?
That's...
Well, the thing there...
I mean, I don't know how things work
south of the border,
but here, under these circumstances,
well, that's a long shot.
I'm sorry, I don't...
You wanna be a friend of the cartel?
Time to get yourself a new motto.
Just.
Make.
Money.
But what does that mean, ephemeral,
repeated the Little Prince,
who never in his life let go of a question
once he had asked it.
It means,
which is in danger
of speedy disappearance.
Is my flower in danger
of speedy disappearance?
It certainly is.
Okay, kid, we'll finish the rest later.
Now, good night.
Not yet, Pop-Pop.
Just two more pages?
Two more pages, that's it.
All right, now lie down.
My flower is ephemeral,
the Little Prince said to himself,
and she only has four thorns
to defend herself against the world...
She's out.
I think The Little Prince
did the trick.
I think you wore her out
with all that hide-and-seek.
I don't know,
I think maybe she wore me out.
This girl at work,
she can't get her son to sleep.
The kid's 2 years old and he's still
tearing around the house at midnight.
Matty was like that.
Really?
Yeah. Really.
Never wanted to conk out.
Too busy.
He was such a cutie.
I love those pictures of him
sitting on Santa's lap.
Oh, that face.
Cried his eyes out.
Every year.
And every year, he'd wanna try it again.
I'm better now.
What changed?
Decided to play the cards I was dealt.
Just decided he'll see us
at the regular Thursday meeting.
You spoke truth to power.
We'll see if he sticks to it.
How'd your day go?
I got married.
Yeah.
What?
I'm having the urge
not to tell you something.
It's nothing.
I'll... I'll tell you later, okay?
Jimmy, wait, wait. Wait, wait, wait.
What?
I have a new client. He's connected.
I mean, he's a cartel guy. From Mexico.
Pretty high up.
Anyway, he's in for murder,
and he wants bail, which...
That's impossible.
I mean...
no way in hell this dude
is ever seeing sunshine,
but if I could, you know,
somehow find a way...
he said I'd be a friend of the cartel.
Friend of the cartel?
You know what that means?
It means money.
Ranch in Montana kind of money.
Like private jet kind of money.
Press conferences, TV news, the works.
But do you want to be a friend
of the cartel?
No.
Absolutely not, I...
Anyway, it's a moot point.
Because the guy is the definition
of a flight risk.
So, look, I'm gonna put up a fight, right?
Just for show.
There's no judge on earth
who's gonna grant him bail.
I just... I didn't wanna tell you.
So I thought I should tell you.
You know what?
What?
I'm glad you did.
Hey.
No, no, I'm good, I'm good, I'm good.
So, what's happening with 6th Street?
And the take?
Okay.
So, what are you gonna do about it?
Are you gonna send in Ocho Loco?
Even better. Nice.
Listen.
I got something for you to do.
I'm not telling you shit
until we talk about my dad.
What you tell me
and when you say it is not up to you.
Listen, you said,
when Lalo's out of the picture,
we'll talk about my father, right?
Well, he's out of the picture.
- Say your piece.
- I'm done.
I want out.
And you want me to square it with Fring.
Fring's not all of it, it's the cartel.
I disappear,
they're gonna go after my father.
He's gotta come with me.
But no matter what I say,
with him, it's the cops or nothing.
The cops won't solve this.
You got a way?
What are you holding out?
Lalo called me from inside.
He put me back in charge.
And?
And...
he wants me to burn down Pollos Hermanos.
Then he's not out of the picture, is he?
The Avocado Mania promotion,
which we've been testing in select
franchises, has been a smashing success,
contributing to an 18 percent increase
in foot traffic
at participating locations
and a 12 percent bump
in customer satisfaction.
We know a good thing when we see it.
So we are planning
to fully roll out Avocado Mania in Q2.
Additionally, our innovative
family fun remodel
improved the in-store
Whiskerstay's experience,
resulting in increased repeat business
system-wide.
In fact, we are happy to share the news
that the latest ACSI survey
now places Whiskerstay's
in the top 10 percent
of limited-service chains nationwide.
Very nice, Cleo.
Very nice. Thank you.
And now, let's hear from Gustavo Fring
of Los Pollos Hermanos.
- Thank you, Herr Schuler.
- Bitte.
I am delighted to report
that the last quarter,
Los Pollos Hermanos revenues
have increased 8.3 percent.
Comparable restaurant sales
increased by 4.2 percent.
Representing the eighth consecutive
quarter of comparable sales increases.
In addition to our continued focus
on our core menu,
we are very proud to introduce
a new offering
that will extend our product line
while celebrating
our traditional New Mexican culture.
I invite you to taste
our delicious Spice Curls.
The curly fry with the Southwestern kick.
Here we are.
The bathroom has heated floors.
You'll find the dial
just under the light switch.
There's a steam shower.
And bidet.
This controls the drapes.
Many of our guests have enjoyed the rodeo.
It's in town tomorrow, Reliance Stadium.
I highly recommend it.
Oh, thank you.
I'm only staying the night.
Next time then.
Is there anything else, sir?
No. No, no, that will be all.
Thank you very much.
- Thank you, Mr. Fring.
- My pleasure.
Peter. Look who's here.
Hello, my friend.
Gustavo.
Always good to see you, my friend.
Oh, you look well.
Well...
I don't feel well.
Maybe things will improve,
now that you're here.
Lydia tells me Salamanca is in jail.
This means you can continue construction?
Eduardo Salamanca has been arrested
for murder.
However, even from jail, he creates...
issues.
What kind of issues?
He ordered his men
to burn down one of my restaurants.
You're kidding. He's in jail.
He can still do that?
I'm afraid so.
I know it's not exactly
my area of expertise,
but don't people get killed in prison
all the time?
I mean, shanked and shivved, and whatnot.
Anything happens to Salamanca
on this side of the border,
the cartel will assume
that it was my doing.
It would mean war.
War for which we are unprepared.
My God.
- This nightmare never ends.
- He's concerned about the money.
Concerned?
Four million eight hundred thousand euros.
It's a miracle I haven't been caught.
Last year, the auditors came this close.
One of them, a woman, I think she knew.
- Peter...
- At first it was a year.
Then it was two. Then three.
And now you're telling me, how long?
I can't. I can't.
- They will catch me. And then it is over.
- Peter.
- I can't.
Gustavo, please. I can't.
Listen to me.
Do you remember Santiago?
The two of us. Our backs to the wall.
I will never forget what you did.
- Oh, I...
- You are still the same man.
You will do what is necessary.
You stay strong, my friend.
We have come so far.
We are so very close.
Okay.
Good.
Now, you eat.
Tomorrow, you and I are
going to the rodeo.
- The rodeo?
- Yeah.
To see the cowboys.
I've never been to a rodeo.
Well, you're going to love it.
Gustavo?
Prosit.
- Prosit.
- Prost.
Your guest will relax
in the elegant great room,
complete with soaring stone fireplace.
- Soaring stone?
- Yeah, that's the best kind of stone.
How about a lavender farm?
Seriously?
Yeah, well, it's lavender-adjacent.
Tell me more.
Imagine a magical land called home.
Watch the sunset
across your own private meadow
as wildflowers sway in the breeze.
This stunning desert retreat promotes
a casual yet luxurious lifestyle.
I'm casual yet luxurious.
Yeah. Totally.
It's got a five-car garage.
What? How's that gonna work?
- We only get two-and-a-half cars each?
- Yeah. Garbage.
So that was wildflowers
dancing in the sun?
They're swaying in the breeze.
Okay. Well, either way.
They're having a very nice time.
Saul Goodman, speedy justice for you.
I need a word.
A word? Yeah.
Yeah, I have a word for you.
Tunnel.
Which is where I am right now.
Sorry, I can't hear you.
Maybe try again later?
Coming.
Whatever it is, it's not for me.
And it should be for you.
Hey, forget your key...?
Okay, yeah, come right in.
Make yourself at home.
You got me in my underwear,
so enjoy the show.
You're representing Eduardo Salamanca,
aka Jorge De Guzman?
Yeah, he's a client of mine.
Yeah. So?
Well, I need you to get him out on bail.
Wait, what do you have to do
with Lalo Salamanca?
I represent someone who has an interest.
Someone like who?
Someone your client can never know about.
Yeah, look, I don't take marching orders
from the man behind the curtain.
In this case, it's better that you do.
You know what Salamanca did, right?
I am aware.
What's this?
This is everything you need...
to do your job.
Go.
Significant ties to his local community?
What ties?
Did you actually think I wasn't gonna hear
about this private eye of yours?
- Excuse me?
- Dave Clark.
Dave Clark. The mysterious third party
who's coaching your key witness.
All right, good. You know what?
Do the dumb act for Parson. Please.
I can't wait to see him rip you both
a new one.
Any idea what that asshole
is going on about?
I'll call the librarian.
Hey.
Play to the judge, okay?
But don't... Don't play to the judge.
Don't overdo it.
Try not to be too cool.
I mean, look humble.
A little bit scared.
No problem.
- Is that them?
- Yep.
Who's that?
It's gotta be his family.
Fred Whalen.
The guy who died at the Travel Wire.
Mr. Goodman?
Mr. Goodman.
That's right, Your Honour.
Witness tampering.
I have reason to believe
that the prosecution's key witness
was coached
by a private investigator
who was hired to pervert justice.
Does the prosecution have a response?
Unfortunately, Your Honour,
it seems a person unknown to my team
may have interacted with our witness,
causing her to call Detective Roberts
and amend her statement
two months after the initial interview.
This only recently came to our attention,
and we are vigorously investigating.
I would hope so.
Having said that, Your Honour,
this witness is one small element
of the state's case.
In light of the extraordinary violence
of the crime
and the fact that Mr. De Guzman
is a foreign national
with no ties to the community,
we ask that the Court recognise him
as a flight risk
and as a danger to the citizens
of New Mexico.
Mr. Goodman?
All due respect, Your Honour,
but the witness is not just
one small element of the state's case,
she's the only witness tying Mr. De Guzman
to the murder scene.
And she's been manipulated.
Furthermore, the claim that Mr. De Guzman
has no ties to the community,
that's just patently false.
Mr. De Guzman has deep ties
to the city of Albuquerque.
I'd like you to meet his family.
That's his fiancée
and the love of his life, Beth McKinnon.
His stepchildren, Christopher and Ella.
And sitting with them
is Beth's mother, Mary.
Now, Your Honour,
my client is the only father
that these kids have ever known.
They depend on him.
How can you possibly see fit
to separate this beautiful family?
I'm sorry.
The testimony implicating
Mr. De Guzman
in this crime,
it's been fabricated.
You've already held him for three days.
Given the circumstances,
Mr. De Guzman should be granted bond.
Your Honour, a sidebar?
- Your Honour, I really...
- Sit.
I accept the defence's argument
that bond is warranted.
But considering
the severity of the charges,
I will set the amount at 7 million.
- Cash only.
- Oh, Your Honour...
All rise.
Seven million.
Listen, I am so, so sorry.
I can do that.
The thing is...
- I'm gonna need you to pick it up.
- What, me?
I'll call you.
Hey, Jimmy.
Howard.
So, have you thought
any more about the job?
The job. Yeah.
No...
I'm still giving it some thought.
Giving it some thought?
Yeah.
You know what? Don't bother.
It seems I've upset you.
So offer's off the table.
You upset me... How'd you upset me?
You tell me.
This is getting a little weird, Howard.
You wanna know what's weird?
It's weird to offer a job to a man,
and in return,
have bowling balls thrown at your car.
And prostitutes
sent to your business lunch.
That's weird.
Are you listening to yourself?
I don't know what you're into
these days, Howard, but...
prostitutes and bowling balls?
You sound unhinged.
Jimmy, I'm sorry you're in pain.
You're sorry.
You're sorry?
You kill my brother,
and you say you're sorry?
Let me tell you something.
The job offer, it didn't upset me.
It amused me.
Ooh, big job at the illustrious HHM.
A chance to play at the palace.
Little old me?
- I was trying...
- You have no idea what's going on.
You're a teensy, tiny man
in a teensy-weensy, little bubble.
- Oh, Jimmy.
- Oh, don't you fucking oh Jimmy me.
You look down on me? You pity me?
Walk away. That's right, Howard.
You know why I didn't take the job?
Because it's too small!
I don't care about it!
It's nothing to me! It's a bacterium!
I travel in worlds you can't even imagine!
You can't conceive of what I'm capable of!
I'm so far beyond you!
I'm like a god in human clothing!
Lightning bolts shoot from my fingertips!