Hey, did you hear all that?
I heard enough
to know she saved your ass.
So...
So, what happens next?
We'll see.
Who was that?
That was...
That's the guy who saved my life.
Kim, I got the money.
I was on my way back.
I thought I was home free.
And I was...
ambushed by...
a gang.
A cartel gang.
And they took the money,
and one of them...
put a gun to my head.
Then that guy on the phone, he showed up.
He shot them with a sniper rifle.
He killed all of them.
All but one.
One guy got away.
And later,
I helped him to get that one too.
Kim, I...
Jimmy, Jimmy, Jimmy.
Oh, my God.
I think we should get out of here.
Kind of assumed we'd be staying
at a Motel 6 or the nail salon.
It's better to have more people around.
How are your shoulders?
Should I put something on them
or would that just make it worse?
I think...
I'm...
Am I bad for you?
Are you bad for me?
I got you into this.
What happened tonight.
None of this would've happened
if you weren't with me.
You crossed a line.
You're not gonna do it again.
Yeah.
It's been a long day.
Come on, make room.
Good night.
Well?
He went over the border and kept going.
Looks to be headed for his place
in Chihuahua.
He should be there in a few hours.
- Good.
- There's a wrinkle.
He took Varga with him.
Why?
If he thought Varga was working for you,
he would've killed him on the spot.
If I had to guess
I'd say Varga is up for a promotion.
Can you communicate with Varga?
Salamanca's place
is in the middle of nowhere.
Landlines and SAT phones only.
A technical issue.
The way things stand,
he's gonna get caught in the crossfire.
I'm thinking we should find a way
to pull him out of there.
And tip our hand?
He's earned some consideration.
Does Varga know
there's going to be an assassination?
No one's told him,
but he can make a pretty damn good guess.
Perhaps...
there is a way to make use
of this situation.
The men I've chosen for this
are highly skilled.
They're the best in their business.
But the one thing they do not have...
is a man on the inside.
Someone's coming. SUV.
Don't recognise it.
Nachito, come on over, don't be shy.
I'd like to introduce you all to Ignacio.
He's going to be staying with us a while.
He's a friend of mine.
These, these are my people.
Yolanda, she is the best cook
in all of Chihuahua.
You're gonna eat like you have never eaten
before in your life.
Cecilio, he takes care
of all of my gardens.
His tomatoes are the best ever.
Tito, Miguel, Herardo, Raul,
and all the rest of these fools.
They're supposed
to be guarding this place,
but I just keep them around
because they're so pretty, right?
And what about you?
Am I going to have to carry
my own things or what?
Sorry...
Get going, asshole!
Hey, listen. Welcome.
Smile. You're in my house, man.
Come on. Come in.
Hey, did you pack anything
with aloe in it?
Oh, morning.
Morning.
I didn't wake you, did I?
No, you're going to court?
Yeah, I have a hearing at 10:00.
And I wanna see if I can catch Oakley
before I go in.
You seemed like you could use the sleep.
Yeah.
Hey, I think I might have a better idea.
What if we spend the whole day here,
you know?
This place has got everything.
It's got a heated pool,
a swim-up bar, a hot tub.
Well, I didn't pack a swimsuit.
Neither did I, there's a shop downstairs
and we could stop in at the spa.
You know? And get couple's massages.
With your sunburn?
Yeah.
Or a seaweed wrap, you know?
And then we'll just go hang
in the co-ed sauna, you know?
Sweat out some toxins and...
Oh, 24-hour room service.
Hey, what could be more luxurious
than to spend a whole day
being totally pampered
and end it all
with a midnight cheeseburger?
Come on, hey, don't we deserve this?
Jimmy, I have clients.
Yeah.
You just quit Schweikart.
I mean, take one day off.
The clerks love you. They will give you
continuance on anything.
Hey, Kim.
We already sprang for this place.
I'm just saying, let's take advantage.
You know, let's John and Yoko this sucker.
You don't think it's safe.
Probably it is, but...
Here's the thing. Lalo has guys, right?
So it doesn't really matter where he is.
If he finds one loose end,
all it takes is a phone call.
Do you know something
you're not telling me?
No. No, I don't. But what's the harm
in being a little cautious?
What about tomorrow?
Or the next day?
Jimmy, what about next week?
I don't know.
All right.
Then the way I see it,
we just need to keep our eyes open
and get on with our lives.
Kim, listen...
The courthouse...
It's three blocks from here.
It's full of cops,
police headquarters is right next door.
Jimmy...
it's gonna be fine.
I'll see you later.
Hey, it's me. I want an update.
Bullshit.
I wanna know what's going on.
Not good enough. No.
You know what? You...
We are gonna talk about this face to face.
You tell me where you are,
I will come to you...
Hello?
That means we won.
The state dropped the charges.
No, no, no. You don't have
to appear in court again.
Now we both have the morning off.
I'm sorry, Mary, you know what?
I have to go.
But call if you have any questions,
anytime. Okay.
Yes, bye.
Hey, Grant? You got a minute?
How's it going?
Let's see.
I have half an hour to plead out
four taggers and a homeless guy
who tried to stuff
a dozen hard-boiled eggs
down his pants at a Ruby Tuesday's.
Life in the public defender's office.
How's your day so far?
I got some holes in my schedule
I'm looking to fill.
Holes?
You're telling me you're billing,
what, 250 an hour
and you got holes in your schedule?
If I were you, I'd keep things airtight.
I'd like some more PD overflow.
Go talk to the contract liaison,
and Gloria will set you up.
Grant, the thing is, I know I'm not
supposed to choose the cases I get,
but I'm looking for something specific.
Specific? Like what?
I just wanna make sure I'm spending
my time where it'll do the most good.
I gotcha.
So plain old indigents
are not good enough for you.
You want the clients that will get you,
you know, in here.
Grant, just let me have some tricky ones.
Think of all the extra time you'll have
to spend on your egg-stuffers.
If I were going to go along with that,
you'd have to take felonies.
Sure.
We're talking cases
that are headed for trial.
Nothing you can plead out in three
hot minutes with your friendly ADA.
I'll take 20. Today.
Twenty? That's your offer?
Twenty felonies?
Yes.
Hold this.
Come on.
Hey, Dana, any chance you can tell
the judge I'm running 15 minutes late?
Oh, I gotta warn you.
Right now we're backed up
like an outhouse at Woodstock.
So possession raps are here.
Possession with intent.
These are all assault.
Wait.
No. Assault's on the other side
of this shelf.
All of these cases are pending?
Pretty much.
Had more burnouts than usual
this last quarter.
That's what I call
taking that private firm gig.
Getting that sweet company car.
Burning rubber on your way out.
Public intoxication, petty larceny,
destruction of property,
DUI,
trespassing,
involuntary manslaughter,
immigration,
domestic violence.
Or, if you feel like you do want...
Juveniles.
Go ahead, have a look around.
Let me know which ones you want
so we can kick them over.
I'll get you a box.
Flashlight.
When you talk to the boss,
you call him Don.
He asks you a question,
you tell the truth.
Fewest words you can.
If he likes you,
he's gonna give you a bump up.
Hey.
Don't think I don't see you, all right?
I see you. I do.
Right now, steady is what we need,
you know?
And if he doesn't like me?
Ah, you'll be fine.
Give me the socket wrench.
- I gotta hit the head.
- Yeah, yeah.
Straight back to the left.
Hey, don't get any grease on my sink, eh?
Yeah?
There's a gate at the back
of Salamanca's place.
3:00 a.m. tonight.
Unlock it. Open it.
Get the hell away from there.
Who are you?
3:00 a.m. Got it?
You're gonna do this clean, right?
He's got at least seven guys here,
but there's also a couple of old folks,
and they've never done anything
to anybody.
After that, I want you both to be thinking
about how to parse out discovery.
It's gonna be document heavy,
so let's be mindful
of resource management.
Howard.
- Kim.
- Good to see you.
What floor?
Three, please.
Have you met my associates?
Paul Sheppard and Michelle Avila.
I don't think so, hi.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
Guys, this is Kim Wexler.
She's an HHM alum.
And now heads up banking
at Schweikart and Cokely.
Nice to meet you both.
I'm actually not at Schweikart anymore.
Or in banking, for that matter.
Really?
As of yesterday.
Take care, Howard.
Kim! Kim! Hang on a sec.
Out of curiosity, where did you land?
Reeves and Green?
I'm out on my own again.
Rich let you go?
It wasn't up to him. I left.
What about Mesa Verde?
I advised them to stay with Schweikart.
I know it's a personal question, Kim,
but can I ask why?
- That is personal. And I have a...
- Spare me a minute.
Please. It's important.
What's up?
I wasn't gonna say anything.
Last time I tried to get something
off my chest, it didn't go very well.
I just think...
before you make any big changes
in your life...
There's something about Jimmy
you ought to hear.
Okay.
A little while ago,
I offered Jimmy a job at HHM.
I'm guessing he didn't mention it to you.
He said he had to think about it.
But then the very next night,
he threw bowling balls over my front gate.
Bowling balls?
Someone could've been really hurt.
More or less destroyed my car.
Then, a couple of weeks later,
I'm having lunch with Cliff Main.
And I'm accosted by two prostitutes.
Actual prostitutes.
Jimmy had sent them to make a scene.
I confronted Jimmy about it.
And after some hemming and hawing...
he all but confessed.
And that's it?
Sorry...
Howard.
You really had me going there.
Laugh if you want,
but no person in their right mind
would behave the way Jimmy has.
We are talking about someone
who is not in control of himself.
You and I both know it makes no sense
to drop a client like Mesa Verde.
And I gotta think Jimmy had something
to do with that.
Do you have any idea
how insulting that is?
I make my own decisions.
For my own reasons.
You gotta listen to me.
The man needs help.
Howard.
I know Jimmy, and you're wrong.
You know who really knew Jimmy?
Chuck.
Open up. Asshole!
Open this door! I want to talk to you!
What?
You didn't think I'd find
your ultra-secret bat cave?
Well, joke's on you, sucker.
I'm your attorney and you will let me in!
I'm not going anywhere. I mean it.
I got nowhere to be.
Open up now!
Hey!
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Ah, there he is.
Not a fan of the surprise pop-in, huh?
Oh, I can't imagine why.
- Keep it down, I got neighbours.
- I will not keep it down.
I want answers, okay?
The time has come for you
to level with me,
and I'm not going to leave
until you do.
Inside. Now.
Okay, look. Look.
Okay.
You saved my life.
Thank you for that.
But from here on out,
I gotta be kept in the loop, man.
It's not my fault that I got ambushed.
Why did I have to lie to Salamanca
about that?
Who was I lying for?
Now, you gotta tell me
what is happening, now!
That's not your concern.
Oh, come on.
Listen to me.
You are not blowing me off with any
that's not the end of the story crap.
Now, just specifics!
You're asking for information
you can't have.
If anything happens to her...
I can't do this. I can't.
All right.
Now, you listen, and you shut up.
This man has other things on his mind,
he's not thinking about you.
Lalo Salamanca is going to die...
tonight.
Tonight?
This time tomorrow, it'll be done.
Oh, okay.
Now...
I need you to leave.
I have family coming over.
Very nice.
Maybe a little less this time?
We've had some bad luck.
Luck?
Don Eladio,
Gustavo assures me that it's over.
Look who it is!
Don Eladio!
I knew the Americans couldn't hold you!
Bolsa.
I understand it was expensive for you
to get out, was it not?
Hey. You paid the gringos?
I thought you would have...
You know how it goes up there.
But don't worry. I got my pound of flesh.
What's all this?
It's what Bolsa has brought me from Fring.
Excelente.
You think so?
Of course!
Hey, by the way...
I found this key
but I don't know if it's yours.
I don't think so.
That's weird. But...
Let's see what it opens.
Oh, Magnum P.I.!
What a beautiful baby!
She's so smooth.
Eh, Bolsa?
Very smooth.
Perhaps there's...
something in the trunk?
Let's find out.
Don.
On this model the trunk
is in the front.
It's a frunk.
Let's see.
Frunk.
A present!
What is this?
This is the man.
Right, Bolsa?
This is showmanship!
Don Eladio.
I'd like you to meet Ignacio Varga.
He's our new man up north.
Not a Salamanca?
He's been running things
since Hector got sick.
He's a friend of Tuco's.
Tuco. Really?
You okay in there?
I'm joking with you.
Let's talk, you and I.
We'll get to know each other.
So.
How do you think you'll make me money?
I'm going to sell as much stuff
as you can send me.
I'm gonna open up new territory.
Keep the competition out.
New territory?
Who are you taking this territory from?
To start with...
Biker gangs.
Biker gangs?
Bikers?
So you're going to start a war
with a bunch of gringo bikers?
This is your plan.
Don Eladio.
These gangs are divided.
We turn them against each other.
Then we take them out one at a time.
So you are a businessman.
Ignacio Varga.
What do you want?
- What do I want?
- Yes.
Respect.
I want to make my own decisions.
Go my own way.
I don't want anyone
to even think of playing me.
And I don't want to be looking
over my shoulder.
You don't want to be looking
over your shoulder?
You're in the wrong business, my friend.
You're all right.
Salud.
Really?
Really.
How do you know?
I talked to my guy.
- Lalo's in Mexico, and he's staying there.
- But you said he might call someone...
He's not gonna do that.
- Your guy? How does he know for sure?
- He's not gonna tell me, but he knows.
- And you believe him?
- Yeah. I do.
So, we're safe?
Yeah.
My God.
Oh, my God.
Oh, that's great.
It's great, right?
It's... It's...
So, what's wrong? It's over.
This time.
There's not gonna be a next time.
Kim...
it's been a rough ride.
I've been thinking a lot, and...
we should probably just check out
and go home.
I packed my stuff, I think
I got yours too. Just double-check.
We already paid for the night.
What about the spa and all that?
We haven't even tried room service.
Kim, don't you just wanna go home?
A veil of white cheddar draped
over coarse ground Angus beef patty,
locally grown chilli pepper,
house-baked sesame seed buns
served with golden brown shoestring
potatoes seasoned with truffle salt.
Truffle salt.
I'm hungry, Jimmy.
And there is nothing to eat
at home anyway, so...
why not?
So I ran into Howard
at the courthouse today.
Yeah?
Told me something about...
bowling balls destroying his car.
Prostitutes harassing him at lunch.
For what it's worth,
that all happened before we...
Before we got married?
Yeah.
You know why Hamlin told me all that?
It was for my own good.
Like I'm just waiting for him
to ride up on his white horse?
It's...
It's all about him.
It's always all about him.
The guy is in love with himself.
He needed to be taken down a peg.
So...
what's next?
You went after his car.
You went after his reputation, so...
I think maybe the next thing is...
his hair.
Right? Suppose...
I'm just brainstorming here,
but suppose we slip him a mickey.
And then, while he's out,
we get out the old electric clippers.
Shave him bald.
Nair.
What?
It's an old gag,
but sneak into his country club
and put Nair in his shampoo bottle.
And then he takes a shower, and...
- Hair falls out. Nice.
- Yeah.
Or, or, or...
we pour a barrel of chlorine
into his swimming pool.
- So then...
- Bleaches his hair
and eyebrows, everything.
Yes, and the eyebrows.
Or. Or...
Or we break into his house,
replace all the fluffy toilet paper rolls
with single ply.
Ouch. Hit him where he lives.
Or, whatever tanning lotion
he uses, we replace it with sunblock.
He gets in his tanning bed and...
Waste of time.
Or...
Or what?
We'd never do it, but...
Never do what?
What if...
What if Howard does something terrible?
Like he murders a waiter
for putting butter in his cauliflower?
No, I mean really bad.
Like misconduct.
You know, misappropriating funds or...
bribing witnesses, something like that.
You know what that would mean
for the Sandpiper case?
A big class action suit?
It could tank the whole thing.
Cliff Main's hair would be on fire.
He'd get it settled.
Pronto.
He would?
Yeah. Think about how much
they've put into that case.
Almost two years of work?
If it fell apart now, they'd get nothing.
So yeah.
Cliff Main would take whatever
Sandpiper was offering.
I already tried like hell
to get Sandpiper settled.
Yeah, but you went about it wrong.
Sorry, but this is how you do it.
And it's not like
the old folks get stiffed.
If Sandpiper settled now,
they might each get 15, 20 bucks less,
but they get their money now
while they can still use it.
And the lawyers get paid.
How much of the common fund do you get?
We get 20 percent of the common fund.
I'm just... I'm...
- Forget it, okay?
- Okay.
Hey.
Have a seat.
Hey, you did good today, huh?
Tomorrow, I'll show you around.
When you go back up north...
you're gonna be halfway
to being a Salamanca, eh?
Thanks.
Another night owl, huh?
You don't sleep?
No. Not tonight.
Yeah, I never sleep much.
An hour, maybe two.
It's enough.
When it's like this...
that's when I can think.
I get my best ideas
when everybody else is asleep.
Some people, they call it a curse.
I like it.
I don't know.
I'd rather get some shuteye.
And yet here we are.
Got anything stronger?
Now you're talking.
In the bar, bottom shelf, decanter,
that's the good stuff.
Two glasses.
There he is.
I thought you got lost.
You ever had Louis XIII?
I don't think so.
You're in for a treat.
To sleep and those who need it.
To sleep.
What the hell is that?
These morons have no respect!
Ciro!
What the hell is that, asshole?
Inside. In the kitchen.
Ciro!
It's always the same!
Ciro! Get in here!
Ciro.
What's up, boss?
- What did you do? Are you smoking again?
- Boss, I didn't really.
Ciro. Ciro.
Don't lie to me. Don't blame Miguel.
I'm tired of these lies.
Boss, I swear to God, I got myself
a lighter. See? It wasn't me!
Go. Find where it comes out.
What do you see?
It's straight.
At least a hundred metres long.
I can see his blood. He's not far.
What was that?
Was that him?
What do you want?
I'll have a little of everything.
Actually, leave off the mint chip.
I set the alarm for 6:00 since we have
to check out and go home before work.
That's a solid two and a half hours.
Sounds good.
So, what would you do with it?
I don't know. What would you?
I'd hire Stef away from Schweikart.
I'd hire Bruce from HHM.
I'd get Viola.
I'd rent the smallest, shittiest office
I could find at a courthouse
and open a pro bono practice.
Give regular people
the kind of representation
usually only millionaires get.
I was gonna say, we buy a house.
Sorry, yeah. Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We could do both.
Last I heard, Sandpiper was willing
to go to 26 million.
Wow, a third of that is 8.5.
- And 20 percent of that is...
- Around two mil.
But it's not happening.
Come on, Kim.
We're not talking about a bar trick here.
We're talking about scorched earth.
We would have to hurt him.
Hurt him bad.
To get a bunch of lawyers
to run for the exits,
Howard would have
to have done something...
unforgivable.
At the end of it, he might never be able
to practise law again.
He doesn't deserve that.
And who knows if we could pull it off?
Okay, maybe we could pull it off, yeah,
but we won't.
We're talking about a career setback.
A career setback for one lawyer.
Yeah, I know, you could help
a lot of people. I get it, but...
Kim, doing this...
It's not you.
Okay? You would not be okay with it.
Not in the cold light of day.
Wouldn't I?
I'm gonna go take a shower,
so I don't have to in the morning.
Kim, you're shitting me, right?
There's a middle man.
I don't know who hired us.
That's okay.
I do.
You're going to call to them.
And you're going to tell them
it was tough...
but the job's done.
I'll help you.