[theme music playing]
[Billie] For centuries, millennia even,
female sexuality has been seen
as one of the most dangerous forces
in the universe.
Something that needs
to be controlled physically,
legally, psychically.
All the way back to the Garden of Eden
and the very first woman, dear Eve.
Salome, Medusa, Helen of Troy.
We are all sirens...
imbued with great power,
capable of experiencing
and delivering immense pleasure,
but also catastrophic pain.
No matter what,
it's always all on us.
["Until I Fall" playing]
♪ What is more beautiful tonight ♪
♪ And bluer than the sky ♪
♪ I had to climb... ♪
Cooper.
Are you the wife?
Ye... Yes.
Mr. Connelly
has already been read his rights.
He'll be transported to the station
where he'll be booked and kept in lockup
until, and unless bail can be posted.
Any questions?
I'll follow you to the station.
♪ Until I fall, until I fall ♪
♪ Until I fall, until I ♪
[alarm buzzes, then door opens]
Hey, are you okay?
[Billie] Um...
This is Cooper.
This is Majid.
I should go.
- No, no, you don't have to leave.
- I... I think that would be best.
Oh, I'll walk you out.
Ellary woke up.
She was crying.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- I didn't know if she was hungry,
so I gave her the sippy cup thing
that was in the fridge.
- Was that supposed to be heated up?
- No. Thank you.
Yeah.
Um, Hudson's soccer game is tomorrow.
Well, I mean, really, it's today.
Yeah, it's probably
not the best day for that.
Hey, it's all good.
I'll call you later.
Mm.
[door opens, then closes]
You were right.
I couldn't hold them back any longer
and they crashed all over me.
All those beautiful moments.
Oh, Cooper.
I wish I fought harder for you.
I don't know if it would've
made any difference...
but you are the love of my life.
[sobbing] But I'm not yours.
And that hurts so damn much.
Oh, my God.
Come here.
[Hudson] Mommy.
Daddy's here. He's downstairs.
I know, baby.
- Hello.
- Dada.
Yes, Dada. Come here, my girl.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, come here, my loves.
Oh. Come here. Come here, angel.
Come here.
As women, we are taught from childhood
the importance of making others happy.
Be pretty, be quiet, be fun.
Be just the way he wants you to be.
So we learn how to navigate
to present only the parts of ourselves
that are pleasing
to whomever we're trying to please.
But those other parts are still there,
brewing, stewing
in the displeasure of being ignored,
denied, hidden away
and covered with a pretty smile.
A good girl who's really just...
scared.
[cell phone chimes]
[Majid] Hey, khoshgelam.
Good morning.
Why did you let me sleep so late?
Oh, because you were
at the restaurant late.
Besides, I had plenty to keep me busy.
How's the dissertation coming?
It's coming.
It's been a long time coming,
so I've thought a lot
about what I wanna say.
That's great.
It's really spring.
And my buddy, Matteo, called, he wants us
to join him on his boat this weekend.
They're taking it out of dry dock,
sailing to Montauk,
stopping at a bunch of wineries
on the way.
That sounds incredible,
but I have my kids this weekend.
Remember?
Oh, shit.
Is there any way you could switch?
Uh...
I don't know.
I could, but I don't want to. I...
I wanna see my kids.
Of course.
- No, I just...
- Yeah. Look, um...
we should talk about this.
After the accident, um...
I... I kind of just let things
go back to the way they were.
- Billie...
- And I could tell that you were spooked,
and I didn't wanna make things worse,
but we had such a great time that day.
Hudson hasn't stopped
talking about it or you.
But a month...
is a long time for a kid.
So if you're not gonna come around again,
then I should probably let him know.
No.
No, that's not what I want.
Saturday is opening day at Yankee Stadium.
I'll get us tickets.
Are you serious?
That sounds great.
But Sasha's book launch is on Saturday,
and I was hoping
to just slip away for an hour or two.
Maybe we could go to the game on Sunday?
Or maybe Hudson and I
could go to opening day on our own.
Just the two of you?
Like a bro day.
One-on-one, crackerjack,
hot dogs, easy-peasy.
Okay, I mean, only if that's what you want
because I don't wanna force you.
It is what I want.
This is gonna be fun.
Apparently, Singapore is the number one
easiest place to live as an expat.
- Really?
- Mm-hm.
One in every six households
is a millionaire?
- Fancy.
- Ooh.
Which means you can end up
paying 15 bucks for a zucchini.
It's not too late to come with.
Last I checked,
seat 2B was still available.
- Kam.
- Okay, I bought it.
- Just in case.
- Kam.
I'm sorry. I don't understand why
you won't even consider coming with me.
I did consider it.
For one night?
The next morning, it was a hard no.
You're asking me
to give up my entire life,
not to mention my career.
You are a giant success now.
You can write your books
and your tweets from anywhere.
And tell all my fans I moved
to the other side of the world for a man?
For love and adventure.
- See, there's a way to spin it.
- And what about you? Hmm?
Did you consider for longer
than one second not taking this job?
You said it was a done deal,
but you could undo it
if you really wanted to.
Figure out how to run
that organization from New York.
- Sasha, people are counting on me.
- And people aren't counting on me?
I have a foundation, Kam, a business.
I'm up for tenure at Columbia.
You need to check your sexist bullshit.
What does that mean?
Why is it always your assumption that the
woman should be the one to change course?
Give up her plans for the man?
Okay.
Let's say I give up the job,
stayed in New York.
Would you ever stand up to Mick?
[scoffs]
Hmm.
We've been living
in this no man's land for the past month,
flying under the radar.
How do I know
you won't leave me stranded again?
Will the author of Unattached
ever really attach to anyone?
So that's the real problem, hmm.
You don't trust me enough
to take the chance.
You haven't given me a reason to.
Can I at least see you off
at the airport Saturday?
- After my book launch?
- I think that's a no.
Just too hard.
Another airport heartbreak
might turn me off travel forever.
- Can't risk that, not in my line of work.
- So...
this is goodbye?
I guess so.
[Cooper] Hi, I'm Cooper.
I wouldn't exactly say
that I'm an alcoholic.
But I...
I have been 30 days without drinking.
[crowd chuckles]
This last year
has been the hardest year of my life.
I tried a lot of things
to deal with my pain.
Alcohol, drugs...
sex.
But the one thing that I didn't do
was talk about it.
And that's why coming here
and listening to everyone
be so honest, so...
So willing to look at themselves
and what they've done,
I really admire that because I've been
trying to do everything that I can
to avoid taking responsibility for...
For my part in, uh...
Uh...
In my marriage failing.
I used to be such a good guy.
- I haven't been a good guy lately.
- [door opens]
And a lot of people...
have spent a lot of time trying to help me
get back to the person that I was.
I wouldn't let them.
All I can do now is try and make it up.
Try and make amends, right?
Just keep moving forward.
- So...
- [crowd applauding]
Weird, right?
Never thought I'd be the guy giving weepy
confessionals to a room full of strangers.
Don't tell Mom.
- I sent her the video. Was that wrong?
- Bet you did.
Hey, I'm really proud of you.
Thank you.
For everything,
for keeping me out of jail.
- I mean, I probably deserve to go.
- No, you're here.
You paid your fine. You're doing
a boatload of community service.
And bonus, Piper and Bianca,
they agreed to settle the lawsuit.
You're kidding me.
Let's just say
you're not retiring any time soon.
But it's done, and they're okay?
It's enough, right?
It's time to put all this behind you,
focus on the future.
Yeah, because the future
seems so bright, huh?
It's a blank slate.
Well, that's the scary part.
What am I gonna fill it with?
Now that, I can't wait to see.
[announcer]
It's opening day in the Big Apple.
A great day here in the Bronx
and a great day for Major League Baseball.
The Yanks will be squaring off...
- Hi.
- [Hudson] Majid.
Who's more excited about this game?
You or me?
- Me.
- [laughs] Hi.
Oh, he wants a Mickey Mantle bat.
Do not get it for him.
I got something better.
[gasps]
- What do you say?
- Thank you.
Yes. Come on, come here. Oh.
Arms up.
[Majid] Uh... Whoops.
- Sorry.
- It's no big deal.
We'll get a smaller one at the game.
Let's go.
I'll go get the car seat.
- Right.
- [Billie] Yes.
- You can't duct tape him to the back.
- I'm gonna get this. I promise.
- Let's do it. Let's go.
- Come on.
Come on.
[Devon]
Dude, wipe that smile off your face.
- I'm still the reigning pickleball champ.
- Okay, but not today you're not.
You only beat my ass there
'cause I'm a month out of surgery.
Wait till I get my lob back.
I'm glad to know
that's your biggest problem.
Seriously, I had a huge realization
in that crash.
- What have we been doing with our lives?
- Right? I mean, I'm turning it all around.
Like, blank slate.
In fact, I'm thinking about calling Emily.
- Wait, what?
- Mm-hm.
Emily, your ex?
Emily stick-in-the-mud,
sweater set, vanilla latte Emily?
Same Emily you tried to hook me up with.
To make you feel better.
She had puppy dog eyes.
- She thought you could do no wrong.
- Yeah, exactly.
Maybe that's what I need now.
I don't know.
Maybe she was the right woman
for me all along.
You are a fucking snooze-o-rama.
Dude, what I realized is that I've been
wasting my life, at least my sex life.
- I have so many more sexual voyages ahead.
- Okay, Dev. I...
I didn't wanna ask,
but I thought that after the accident
that everything down there, it...
It might have been, uh...
impacted?
Are you kidding? They reconstructed it.
I actually gained an inch.
Really? Okay.
Look, one of the tendons was cut.
But that's a good thing.
- It let some of my inner penis fall out.
- I'm sorry. Inner penis?
We all got one, dude.
You can't tell when it's soft.
- Let me fire it up for you.
- What the hell are you doing?
Doc put a pump in.
I need a little help after the remodel.
- I... I don't wanna see this.
- I wanna see it.
Yeah, everything's fully automated.
I have a stylish new curve, which is cool.
Chicks dig it, right?
Makes it easier to hit the G-spot.
If you actually believe
the G-spot's a thing, am I right?
Who'd have thought
that Piper biting my penis off
would give me a whole new lease on life?
My man, I am just getting started.
- How you doing, champ?
- I'm hungry. Can I have a snack?
Uh...
- I have a mint.
- You don't have any snacks?
- [cell phone ringing]
- One sec. Hey, Alonso. What's up?
- [Alonso] Eva quit.
- What? Shit!
- You owe me a dollar.
- You gotta come in.
Um, Christophe's gotta take over.
- On a Saturday dinner rush?
- It's not a good night.
It's not a good night for any of us.
- Gotta make a quick pit stop, buddy.
- Okay.
How would you like
another Nutella lava melt, huh?
[gasps]
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
That's what I'm talking about.
What's going on?
You can't be nervous.
You're a superstar.
It's not that.
It's this.
His plane leaves
in four hours and 35 minutes.
Not that I set a timer on my phone.
- Oh, honey.
- It's for the best.
He can move on and so will I.
I can focus on my work,
maybe find a new Kam.
- Just like you found Majid.
- Or...
Or what? I'm gonna go live in Singapore?
You could.
Sash, this isn't about
the logistics of work and life.
This is about power.
Who sacrifices for whom,
and someone always has to give first.
You are the one who gave up your power,
sacrificed a huge part of yourself
for a man with disastrous results.
- You're telling me to do the same thing?
- It's not the same.
Cooper and I weren't right for each other,
but I still believe in marriage.
I still believe in that kind
of partnership, and honestly...
if I could go back
and do it all over again...
I might say yes to Brad's proposal
on my driveway.
That kind of love comes...
once in a lifetime.
Now, it's too late for us.
But it's not too late for you and Kam.
Honey, you have a second chance.
Are you sure you don't wanna take it?
Sasha, my star.
Gran.
- Hi, Billie.
- Hi there, Roz.
- I'm so glad you could make it.
- Are you kidding?
This is your manifest destiny.
It is my honor to see you exactly
where you're supposed to be.
I am the master of my fate,
the captain of my soul.
For decades,
those were words reserved for men alone.
Women were expected to support,
to bend, to comply,
to derive their power
from the men to whom they were attached.
But this is a new era for women,
for anyone
who wants to answer only to themselves
and stand unattached
in the glory and power of doing...
what you want...
when you want...
with whomever you want.
Come with me.
Um... [clears throat] Sorry.
When you follow your own path,
find your own way,
you never have to ask yourself
what life could have been...
because you can make it
exactly what you want it to be.
Thank you.
[crowd applauding and cheering]
Great.
Thank you so much for coming.
I'm supposed to get home to Ellary,
but are you okay?
- We did it.
- Roz.
Yes, it is all about me.
Well, call me.
From wherever you end up.
Have a good night.
Oh, it's a shame about Billie.
- Gran.
- She's back at school.
You said. I know.
But she wasted so much time.
You stayed the course.
Didn't let yourself get distracted.
Now you've got everything
you could ever want.
Except I'm alone.
Gran, I will always be grateful to you
for insisting I not throw away my dreams
all those years ago.
I don't think any of this would exist if
I had run off to California when I was 22.
Damn straight.
But I'm not 22 anymore.
And...
I'm not sure this is
how I wanna spend the rest of my life.
Why not?
Kam is back.
Oh, God.
He still loves me.
He wants me to move to Singapore with him.
[laughing]
Of course he does.
So after all this time,
you're just gonna
turn into one of those girls
- who chucks it all to run after some man?
- Not some man.
Kam.
And maybe I am that girl, okay?
Who gets swept away to Rome
and who says yes
to a crazy proposal at the MET and...
And who wants to follow the love
of her life to a tiny island in Asia
where the zucchinis cost
15 fucking dollars.
I've got the success now.
I want the man too.
I wanna at least try to have it all,
so I don't spend the rest of my life
wondering, "What if?"
You just stood on that stage.
Your entire essence is convincing women
to live life on their own terms.
Now, you're gonna go and do the opposite?
Maybe these are my terms.
Hey, buddy.
Only a few more minutes.
I checked the score,
Yanks are up three to nothing.
You need anything? More hot chocolate?
- Okay.
Majid, you gotta take this.
I got a lead on a replacement chef.
Oh.
[dramatic music playing]
[woman] Great.
We got five grilled prawns coming up.
Don't step back. I'm behind.
[woman] We gotta go!
- Flash the tagine for me!
- Excuse me?
What are you doing here?
You gotta go, man.
- Can I have more hot chocolate?
- What?
- Shit, shit!
- I'll get the extinguisher!
It's spreading! Oh, my God!
- Call 911!
- Hudson, why are you in the kitchen?
You're not allowed in here!
What are you doing?
Stay right here! Do not move!
[cell phone ringing]
Hey, how's the game?
Are the Yankees winning?
[Majid] Billie, I'm so sorry.
What happened?
[Cooper] His name's Hudson Connelly.
He's 6 years old.
- He's probably three feet tall.
- [Billie] Cooper.
- Cooper.
- Hey.
[sobbing] Oh, my God. I'm so, so sorry.
- [Cooper] Stop.
- I'm so sorry.
- No, no, stop. It's not your fault.
- It's my fault.
I know, I'm the one who's sorry.
Why did you even bring Hudson here?
- You were supposed to be at the game.
- It was supposed to be a quick stop.
And you didn't think to call
or to even text me to let me know
where you were taking my son?
Billie, it's gonna be okay.
We're gonna find him.
I got my staff out there looking.
Well, I'm not just
gonna sit around here and wait.
Okay, I'll head east. You go west. Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- I'll come with you.
- No. Don't.
Billie.
- What are you doing here?
- Alonso called all the investors.
- How bad is it?
- I don't know, but Hudson was here,
and now he's missing.
- He ran away.
- What?
- I need to go find him.
- I'm coming with you.
I have no idea
where he would even think to go.
- Does he have a favorite spot?
- He doesn't know the city.
He's only been
to Majid's restaurant once before.
Um, the day that
we ran into you in the park.
He loved that bubble guy, remember?
The park's just up here.
- Oh, my God.
- Come on, come on, come on.
Mick is in a very important meeting
right now.
Nice brotox, buddy.
Ow, ow.
What's the matter with you?
My maxillofacials are very sensitive.
- This is who I was, but it's not who I am.
- The fuck is that supposed to mean?
I'm not gonna live a lie anymore
and I'm not gonna hide.
Do I look like I have a vagina?
Save it for The View.
You got a book tour coming up.
I'll do the tour for Unattached,
but only as a promotion
for my next book, Sustained By Love.
So schmaltzy.
Shitstained By Love is more like it.
And last, I checked, your 10%
was paying me to set your brand strategy.
Who are you to start barking orders?
I'm Sasha fucking Snow.
And I've got a plane to catch.
Hey, have you seen a little boy
about this tall, blond?
- No?
I don't see anyone.
Hey. Hey, Billie. Billie, look at me.
We're gonna find him, all right?
Here or somewhere else.
[Billie] Hudson?
Hudson!
- Mommy?
- [Billie] Huds.
Hi, Mama.
I was so worried about you.
There was a fire.
And Majid yelled at me,
and he owes me a dollar.
I came to see bubble man,
but bubble man's not here.
Yes, I know, baby. I know.
That was just a special treat,
not every day.
Those bubbles were great though, eh, mate?
- You're that guy. Mommy's friend.
- [Billie] Yeah.
Mommy's friend.
Hey, you can never run away again.
Okay? Ever.
I'm sorry.
That's okay.
You know, I know what it's like to be
a scared little kid in New York City.
So don't worry. Okay?
[all laughing]
- [Hudson] You said you wanted my sneakers.
- [Brad] Oh, I do.
- You said they were cool kicks.
- Wasn't that funny?
The way you were looking at him,
I was like...
- Oh!
- Daddy.
Oh, buddy, hey.
You had us worried sick.
Thank you for your help.
I didn't do anything.
Oh, yes, you did.
It was Brad's idea where to find Hudson.
He remembered this park
that we'd all been at last month
- where we ran into each other.
- Well, I'm very grateful.
We both are.
Well, I should get inside
and check out the damage.
Check on Majid.
I'll see you around, little man.
Oh, yeah. Nice.
Can you come home with us, Daddy?
- It's fine with me.
- Yeah?
Yeah, we can...
We can set up the guest room again.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. Okay, baby?
- Okay?
- Hey, that would be great.
But, hey, listen to me.
I'm gonna meet you there. Okay?
I just need to do one thing first.
- All right?
- Okay. Yeah.
[dramatic music playing]
Kam, wait.
- Sasha, what are you doing here?
- I'm coming with you.
I don't have anything.
I ran here straight from my book launch.
Well, that and telling Mick
to go fuck himself.
[shouts]
I'm gonna have to buy
a whole new wardrobe in Singapore.
Or, considering the whole
$15 zucchini situation,
may be cheaper
to have Billie send me all my stuff.
Sasha, I'm touched, really,
but you can't come to Singapore.
Yes. I can and I am.
Look, somebody has to give first.
And it's me.
I wanna give for you. For us.
For everything we could be
for the next 17 years of our lives.
It's like you said.
I just don't wanna wake up
one single morning without you in my arms.
I love you, Sasha Snow.
But you cannot come to Singapore.
- Why not?
- [man] Dr. Evans.
We were able to get your luggage
off the plane.
[Kam] Thank you so much.
Because I'm giving first too.
You were right.
It shouldn't always be the woman
who's expected to change course.
I don't wanna be that man
that keeps asking you
to give up your life and follow mine.
The woman I love lives in New York City.
Her life is here,
and I belong wherever she is.
So I'm staying.
Really?
[intercom buzzes]
[woman] Come on up.
[door buzzing]
[woman] And this is why I know
this is gonna be your best year yet.
To the birthday girl.
[all] To Emily.
Cheers. I love you.
Cheers.
Cooper?
What are you doing here?
Wanted to say happy birthday.
Nice to see you, Coop.
Why don't you say a few words?
Oh, no, that's okay.
I don't... [clears throat]
I don't drink anymore.
Um...
I do wanna say something though.
Uh...
Didn't realize I was gonna be saying it
in front of all of you. [chuckles]
But I've realized
that you can lose the people you love
in the blink of an eye.
So...
twelve years ago,
I wasn't the right man for you.
And I couldn't appreciate
all the things that you have to offer,
and that list is long.
You're compassionate, understanding,
you never give up on anyone.
You never gave up on me.
I am not in the same place
that I was the last time you saw me.
I'm doing the work. I'm trying to be
the man that you have always seen in me.
I still don't know
if I'm the man that you deserve, but...
[guests cheering]
So you don't need
to think about it or you...?
My birthday wish came true.
Majid.
Khoshgelam.
Looks like the place is on the mend.
Yeah, we should be
able to reopen next week.
Oh, that's great. I'm glad.
Look, um...
I'm really sorry for what happened.
Me too.
- I've been trying to reach you.
- I know. I...
Just needed a couple of days to cool down.
I didn't wanna make any big decisions
while my emotions were running high.
Billie, I love you so much.
Our time together
has meant everything to me.
But I'm not a dad.
I'm not good at tiny feelings
and car seats and schedules.
The only baby I have is my restaurant.
And honestly,
that's the only baby I've ever wanted.
I know.
But don't break up with me.
There's so much good.
We could go back to the way things were.
Maybe that was the secret sauce.
You have your life in Connecticut
and we have our life together here.
It was working.
Oh, there is so much good.
And there's so much fun to be had, but...
it's not enough.
If there's anything that I've learned...
it's that I don't wanna split my life
into two parts.
And if I can't be in a relationship
that allows me...
to be all of who I am...
then I'd rather be alone.
You're something else.
So I've been told.
["I Am Woman" playing]
[inaudible dialogue]
♪ I am woman, I am fearless
I am sexy, I'm divine ♪
♪ I'm unbeatable, I'm creative
Honey, you can get in line ♪
♪ I am feminine, I am masculine... ♪
[Billie] Surprise. [laughing]
♪ I can teach you, I can love you
If you got it goin' on ♪
♪ If you got it, got it
Got it, got it, got it, got it ♪
♪ If you got it, got it, got it
Got it, got it goin' on ♪
♪ Got it, got it, got it
Got it, got it, got it ♪
♪ If you got it, got it, got it
Got it, got it goin' on ♪
♪ Got it on goin' on, yeah ♪
♪ Got it, got it, got it
Got it, got it goin' on ♪
♪ I am classy, I am modern
I live by my own design ♪
♪ I'm cherry, I'm lemon
I'm the sweetest key lime pie ♪
♪ I'm electric, I'm bass
I'm the beat of my own drum ♪
♪ I could make your goosebumps raise
With the tracing of my thumb ♪
[Trina]
Ladies, are you ready to experience
multiple G-spot and cervical orgasms?
Increased strength
leads to increased sensation.
Now, the G-spot may have been named
after the guy who "discovered" it,
but you certainly don't need a man
to find it for yourself.
- Is she holding that with her...
- Pussy? Sure is.
Okay.
I think I'm gonna need a smaller coconut.
[woman] Wilhelmina Mann.
[audience applauding]
♪ I am woman, I am fearless
I am sexy, I'm divine ♪
♪ I'm unbeatable, I'm creative
Honey, you can get in line ♪
♪ I am feminine, I am masculine
I am anything I want ♪
♪ I can teach you, I can love you
If you got it goin' on... ♪
[all cheering]
♪ If you got it, got it
Got it, got it, got it... ♪
Yes!
♪ Got it, got it, got it goin' on
Got it goin' on ♪
This is the last of it.
There's no more room,
unless you wanna
try and Cooper Connelly it.
What do I always say?
- There's always room.
Oh, Cooper. This was so nice.
- Thank you so much.
- Absolutely.
Hey.
I'm proud of you, Dr. Mann.
Yes.
[both laughing]
Actually, there's something
that I wanted to tell you.
- Yeah?
- Uh...
I'm gonna ask Emily to marry me.
Oh.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
It turns out you can have
more than one love of your life.
It's not just that
she's the right woman for me, um...
It's that I'm the right man for her.
And when I'm with her...
I feel like I'm enough.
That's an amazing feeling.
I know what you're gonna say. You're gonna
say sweater sets and vanilla lattes...
No, no, no, Cooper.
I... I was gonna say...
Um...
Emily's lovely.
That's the kind of girl I thought...
you should have been with all along.
And if I had been more honest
with myself and you...
then maybe you could have been.
I will never regret our time together.
- We made two beautiful children.
- No.
It's not just that.
It's you.
You are...
formidable.
And for whatever time
I was able to call you mine,
I consider myself incredibly lucky.
And deeply...
deeply grateful.
Oh, Cooper.
I'm so happy for you.
And Emily.
Thank you.
[Billie chuckles]
So...
I gotta ask...
Are you happy?
Uh...
I am. Yeah.
I mean, this isn't the fairy tale
I imagined for myself, but you know,
I've got friends, work, kids I adore,
a pretty cute and responsible co-parent.
It's a fairy tale of its own kind.
In the end, all of us will look back
on our lives and say one of two things:
"I wish I had," or "I'm glad I did."
We've had so many amazing
"I'm glad I did" moments...
even in those teary, soul-crushing days.
I'm glad I had those moments too,
because I had them with you.
You're that rare person
who has no "I wish I hads,"
who fearlessly says yes,
even now to a man who is the definition...
of "I'm glad I did."
You are proud,
passionate, open to the world.
And most of all, my best friend.
So, Kam, enjoy her.
[laughter]
But don't forget, it's you and me.
Always.
To Sasha and Kam.
- [all] To Sasha and Kam.
- [man 1] Cheers.
- [man 2] Yeah.
- [man 1] Congratulations, Sasha and Kam.
[Billie] You and me.
Always.
That was beautiful, Billie.
You've always had a way with words.
What are you doing here?
I asked Sasha if I could
come and surprise you,
sweep you off your feet.
She made me promise
to wait until after the cake, but...
[chuckles]
Where's Gigi?
She left.
A while ago, actually.
She's with someone else now,
who didn't just lose his company.
We both knew in our hearts that I could...
I could never be hers completely.
Because I've never stopped being yours.
It's you, B.
It's always been you.
Please tell me this is real.
[chuckles] It's real.
We are real.
We are undeniable.
You know that.
- I think I'm gonna faint. I...
- Here.
["Heavenly Day" playing]
I got you.
And I...
got you.
♪ Oh, heavenly day... ♪
[Billie] As women,
we are imbued with great power.
Most importantly...
the power of choice.
♪ Got no trouble today ♪
♪ The smile on your face ♪
♪ I live only to see ♪
♪ It's enough for me, baby ♪
♪ It's enough for me... ♪
[Billie] When you choose
who to spend your life with,
you're also choosing
who you wanna be in the world.
But you can't make that choice
until you know who you really are.
Once you've discovered and accepted
and delighted
in your true self in all its glory,
then the decision becomes clear.
When you are the you you want to be...
then everything else...
is just gravy.
I'm pregnant.
♪ Heavenly day, heavenly day ♪
♪ Heavenly day ♪
♪ Oh, heavenly ♪
♪ Day ♪
[theme music playing]