[theme music playing]
Now, fuck me.
♪ It's just sex to me ♪
♪ Du-du-dumb, I ain't dumb I can see you ♪
♪ Come, come, come, come
Coming up with ideas ♪
♪ Thought we had a deal ♪
We should run away.
- Are you sure?
- You leave Cooper. I'll leave Gigi.
♪ It's just sex to me ♪
♪ I don't wanna meet your family ♪
♪ Unless your big brother is into me ♪
♪ Sex to me, sex to me
Say, "Hi" for me ♪
♪ You see it's time to leave
Don't cry for me ♪
♪ I thought we had a deal ♪
♪ It's just sex to me ♪
♪ Du-du-dumb, I ain't dumb ♪
♪ I can see you ♪
♪ Come, come, come, come
Coming up with ideas ♪
♪ I thought we had a deal ♪
- I love you so much.
- I love you.
I love you, Brad.
[moaning]
Oh, Brad.
Brad.
It's time, sweetie. Say goodbye.
We talked about this.
You have stunning taste, babe.
Like Architectural Digest
all over the place,
but the black leather
is way too masculine.
Yeah. The couch, right?
Yes, the couch.
Do you hear that? The weeping
of the ghosts of girlfriends past.
Brad.
[chuckles]
God knows what gymnastics
have been performed on that thing.
Hm...
Oh, by the way, the mattress is going too.
♪ No knock on my door ♪
♪ Or footsteps on the floor ♪
♪ Cannot breathe anymore ♪
♪ This grip is pulling me in ♪
♪ Your games and your lies
Are toxic to me ♪
♪ Unlock the chain, let me be free ♪
Honey, what's going on?
Something's not right.
I know you. Is it the couch?
It's blush, not pink.
I know it reads pink,
but it's not like girl pink.
It's very chic.
It was Pantone's color of the year.
It's like a neutral now.
No, it's not the couch.
I know
this has been your place for so long,
but I'm so excited
to make it our place for our family.
Me too.
Oh, yeah? Well, wait until you see
this gorgeous wallpaper I found.
It has hand-painted azaleas.
For...?
The bedroom. Duh. You're gonna love it.
I gotta get out of here.
Oh...
No. I need to go to work.
I'll see you later.
I love you, Brad Simon.
I love you too.
After suffering emotional trauma,
we... crave stability and security.
And so we make choices that...
we believe will keep us safe.
And these choices are solutions
and they do work... for a while.
But, um... sometimes...
our choices can have unexpected...
even disastrous consequences.
[clears throat] So the key
is to address the root of the problem,
the underlying assumptions
and behavior patterns
that led to all that trauma...
in the first place.
Okay. All right, let's...
Let's leave it there for today. Okay?
- [student 1] Hey, I gotta run.
- [student 2] Yeah.
[student 1] I got another class at 10:00.
Yes? Oh, thank you.
Billie.
Brad?
- What are you doing here?
- I had to see you.
You're with Majid now?
How is that possible?
I left Cooper.
- When?
- The night... I came to your place.
You were right. I needed to figure out
what I wanted out of my life,
but also,
Cooper didn't give me much of a choice.
We're separated.
In the middle of a divorce.
It's not pretty.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- Oh, there was no reason to.
You're with... Gigi.
And I'm happy for you, truly.
So, what about Majid?
Are you gonna keep seeing him?
[scoffs]
I...
- I know I have no right to ask. I'm sorry.
- No.
I don't know what I'm gonna do, you know?
This is all just...
a lot.
I should go.
I have to get home to Connecticut.
It's my turn with the kids.
I cannot believe this is where we are.
We are completely screwed.
They told me not to come in till 3:00.
- What time did they tell you?
- 3:30.
Shit. That's not a good sign.
They fire people at the end of the day.
Don't go there.
This is an embarrassing blip that will end
with a slap on the wrist
- if they know what's good for them.
- That's why
they're keeping us out of the office?
Yeah, to make a point. Come on.
I've watched so many overgrown frat boys
at Goldman do way worse.
This will become a war story.
Office legend.
I'm so sorry.
- This is all my fault.
- Hey.
I was there too.
[doorbell rings]
Uh, give me a sec. Olga!
I gotta go. I'll see you later.
[doorbell rings again]
[Paisley] Well, I am a very happy agent.
The Soledad segment
exploded on Twitter and TikTok.
Hashtag "independent woman for life"
was the number one trending topic
all afternoon.
- I'm not even on TikTok.
- Someone clipped it.
- Whoa.
- And Rihanna followed you.
- Badgalriri?
- Mm-hm.
[exhales] My publicist is gonna
cream over this.
I'm creaming right now.
Wait. Paisley, where are we going?
I thought your office was on ten.
But Mick's is on 30.
Mick, this is Sasha Snow.
You'll do great.
[panting]
I've been thinking a lot about Jesus.
Not that I'm a religious man.
Holy fuck shit,
the guy started with 13 followers.
Today, he's got 7 billion.
You know, people talk about Google, Apple,
Amazon, and their amazing campuses.
[blows raspberry]
The Apple campus
is a fucking WeWork donkey stall
compared to Vatican City.
Florence, Rome, that's a campus.
I love Rome.
Jesus was the greatest brand
the world has ever seen.
The popes ruled Europe
even though they didn't have an army.
You know why? 'Cause they didn't need one.
They had words.
They were selling an idea.
Salvation.
Changed the world.
Amen.
- Oh.
- Sasha.
You are a very special writer.
I was reading your book.
Well, actually, the first chapter,
then my bagel was ready.
But my wife, she read the whole thing
and she and her friends
haven't stopped yakking about it.
Then I saw you on TV
and I realize you have a rare voice.
You're a very gifted B-team player.
I'm a New York Times best seller.
What is that, 70,000 books?
Not interested.
Guess what, neither is the world.
Yes, Soledad's got 3 million viewers.
That's still a fucking prayer circle
compared to Gwyneth.
Seven million followers showing up
to buy her vagina-scented candles.
Still a drop in the ocean
compared to Reese.
Twenty-six million.
Oprah?
Forty million.
Michelle Obama?
Seventy million.
But you...
should not worry because you
have something that those women do not.
- A PhD?
- [laughs]
You're so adorable. No, me.
I can get you to the next level,
but you have to want it.
You have to taste it.
And I mean every fucking day.
You have to think big.
I get that.
And I do.
Sasha, I can get you a seat at that table.
But it's not enough to sell your brand.
As Jesus taught us, you have to live it.
You have to... be it.
Then and only then...
the world will listen.
What do you say?
[cell phone chimes]
[front door closes]
Olga, Ellary?
- Where are you, baby?
- [Vivian] We're in here.
[Billie] Holy shit.
Mom.
- Well, that's pleasant.
- What are you doing here?
And why aren't you at work?
Well, I decided to stay
and chat with Vivian,
who flew in for a surprise visit.
And you couldn't have called?
Either of you?
You know, we had a very...
enlightening conversation.
You really think
you should be talking to my mother?
Oh, give Cooper a break.
He's got a lot on his plate.
[Cooper] Thank you.
Where's Ellary?
Olga took her to the park.
I should head in.
- Why don't you come back for dinner later?
- Mom. No.
- Been so long since we all shared a table.
- [Billie] That's not how this works.
This is my time with Hudson and Ellary.
Protected time on which Cooper and I
agreed through very expensive lawyers.
This arrangement is absurd.
Being a part-time parent,
leaving a stranger to fill in the gaps.
Olga's not a stranger
and her living here provides consistency,
which is exactly what the kids need now.
In my day,
Mother provided that consistency.
Hmm. Indeed.
Have a nice visit.
Vivian, such a pleasure.
- I'm glad we got a chance to talk.
- Yes, me too, darling.
- [front door closes]
- [sighs]
You have always been your own worst enemy.
- You sure about that?
- Cooper is a good man and a great father.
And you are not gonna do better.
You need to find a way to get him back.
[cell phone buzzes]
Oh...
Who's Majid? Body not even cold yet.
You're already spreading your legs
for some other man?
Fuck you!
I should go unpack.
I think we both need a minute.
No.
There's been too much unsaid for too long
that's had too much of an effect on me.
What on earth are you talking about?
Whenever something bad happens,
I hear your voice in my head
telling me it's all my fault.
- I've made huge mistakes in my life.
- You have made mistakes.
Your sexual appetite has been a problem
since you were a teenager
and now it's tanked your marriage.
No, no. My desire was never
the problem in my marriage.
My problem was dishonesty, and the source
of that dishonesty was shame.
And it was shame that you taught me.
I have to pick up my son.
Hi. Sasha Snow. I'm here for Doc...
Dr. Evans?
Honey, aren't we all?
Sasha Snow for Dr. Evans.
♪ Do what I say ♪
[moaning]
Hang on. Hang on. Hang on.
Boy, what are you doing?
Mm, mm, mm!
I'm getting ready to make love to my wife.
I'm not your wife yet.
Woman, you were always my wife.
You just didn't know it yet.
♪ You know you like it now ♪
[Kam] Sasha.
You're back.
- Can we talk?
- [door opens]
I need to tell you why I left.
And why I won't be back.
Not exactly the reunion I was expecting.
I've spent the last 17 years
hustling my ass off.
Solo.
And I've loved every second of it,
but this morning, I met an agent
who wants to take me to the next level.
You're already next level.
New York Times bestseller.
No. Women with a voice
are being heard by millions now.
Not thousands.
I need to focus on climbing that mountain.
I can't get... distracted again.
Again?
I distracted you?
When you asked me to move to California,
you were asking me to give up my dreams.
- That is not at all what I was asking.
- Come on, Kam.
It was your grad program,
your career, not mine.
We... We were doing it together.
Not really.
We were doing what worked best for you.
I kept sacrificing my needs,
my future, to fit into yours.
And if I kept doing that, if...
If I went to California with you,
I would never have made it
to where I am now.
I've been to that place.
That place where everything in your career
is going right, after years of struggle,
and you just keep pushing yourself
to see how high you can climb
until one day, you find yourself
literally on top of Kilimanjaro,
looking out across the Eden-like plains
of Africa in all its stunning glory,
and you turn to say,
"Isn't this the most beautiful place
you've ever seen?"
Only there's no one there to hear you,
and you've got to experience
all of that beauty...
alone.
I'm not asking you to sacrifice anything.
What I am saying
is why not try for it all?
Are you free for a drink?
You can run away anytime you want.
- Hey.
This day just keeps getting more insane.
You've got this.
There's no question that what Francesca
and I did represents very poor judgment.
Still, ours is a completely consensual
relationship between two adults...
Let me stop you right there, Cooper.
Mm-hm.
You've been a standout contributor
to this firm
considering how much business,
and frankly, profit you've brought in.
We've decided to let you go...
with a stern warning.
Oh...
Oh, Dave. Thank you.
I deeply appreciate
this vote of confidence.
You will not regret this.
- What happened?
- You were right.
We're golden.
[French hip-hop music playing]
Okay, let's do the lamb shawarma
but, yeah, as a taco.
- Okay.
- Use the fresh mint salsa, but I think...
[Brad] Majid.
Hey, man.
Um, Eva, will you give us a minute?
- Can I get you anything?
- No, I'm good.
Listen.
You got to believe
I had no idea Billie was your ex.
It's crazy what a small town this city is.
Sure.
Still, I understand if you're pissed,
wanna pull your investment.
That's not why I'm here.
Look, I told you I believed in you.
That hasn't changed.
But I do have to ask,
what are your intentions with Billie?
My intentions?
I don't know. I just met her.
My intentions were to see her again,
but I haven't heard from her
since she ran off last night.
So who knows what's gonna happen.
Maybe nothing.
But truth...
I think she's amazing.
So I'm not going down easy.
That gonna be a problem for you?
Just don't fuck with her.
[cell phone buzzing]
Billie. Hey, how are you?
[Majid] Hey, one call, four texts.
I'm still within
totally normal non-stalker range.
- Am I right?
- Yes. Yes.
You're lovely in a very non-stalker way,
and I'm flattered, but...
I can't do this.
You could.
I mean, if you tried really, really hard.
No, look, I'm...
I was honest with you
about what a mess my life is,
and things have...
They've just gotten worse.
- I know it's weird, but Brad and I...
- It's not just that.
My mother's in town.
And having her here
has brought up a lot of stuff,
you know, not just about Brad,
but about me, about the choices I've made.
I get it. I know all about evil moms
who make you question life choices.
Yeah.
Whatever you've done,
whatever your part in it,
that doesn't mean
you don't deserve to eventually move on.
- And at least try to find happiness.
- I don't know.
Maybe I'm not ready.
Maybe I'm just too broken.
Billie.
[school bell rings]
- I'm sorry. I have to go.
- No. Billie, wait...
- Hudson!
- [Hudson] Mommy!
Hi, baby! Oh...
- Oh!
- I missed you so much.
Oh, I missed you too.
What...? Francesca, hey.
What happened? Are you okay?
No, I'm not okay.
I'm fired.
What? That's impossible.
I have to go clear out my office,
they're sending up security
to escort me out.
No, no, no. Okay?
No. This can't happen. I won't let it.
Cooper, please.
I don't want to make this a thing.
It already is.
Hey!
Total bullshit move, Dave.
This is sexism straight up.
Francesca abused her power
as a senior executive.
It was the both of us, not just her.
She was your boss, Cooper.
She knew the rules.
So did I.
We can't have managers
who can't even manage themselves.
- She got a very generous package.
- No. No!
Don't fire her.
Fire me.
Cooper.
And if you won't fire me...
then I quit.
- Cooper, stop it. This is crazy.
- No. They're crazy.
This? This is real.
Do you want a snack?
Are you hungry, baby? No? You ate?
There he is. My big boy.
I have missed you so much!
- Hi, Grandma.
- Oh, honey.
You're still here.
You didn't think I would leave
without saying goodbye, did you?
A girl can dream.
Hi, Olga.
Hello, my sweet girl.
Mommy missed you.
Olga, perhaps you can take the children
upstairs for their bath.
I'd like to speak to my daughter. Alone.
I think we've said enough to each other
for another 25 years or so.
- Don't you think?
- Billie, please, I want to apologize.
I need you to understand...
I'm not the person that you think I am.
At least, I wasn't always.
Mm! Oh, my God.
I can't get over how amazing you were.
So commanding.
So forceful.
So hot.
Fuck those assholes.
Cooper, I don't even know
who you are right now.
Come on.
Oh, believe it or not, growing up...
I was a lot like you.
Interested in boys and sex...
at a time when we were all
supposed to be good girls.
Isn't that all the time? Even now?
You have no idea
what it was like back then.
What is that supposed to mean?
I got caught with one of those boys
that I was so crazy about.
A quarterback.
We snuck off after a game to his car,
thought nobody would see,
and my classmates branded me a slut.
And that never went away.
Not even at home.
My mother made sure of that.
Why didn't you ever tell me this?
Because you're not the only one
who felt shame.
I love you, Billie.
No matter what you think.
All I've ever wanted
was for you to be happy.
Then I need you to understand...
that trying to fix my marriage
with Cooper is not the way.
Right or wrong... Cooper is in my past.
And so is Brad.
And is this Majid your future?
I don't know. I...
I haven't... had the chance to find out.
Things are complicated.
Honestly, I'm scared.
But I wanna be happy. And I want my...
I want my kids to see me happy.
And if I can do that,
then maybe all of this will have been...
worth it.
Then go to him.
What?
You got a nanny
and a grandma in the house.
That's plenty of consistency.
Stop being afraid.
Go find out what your life can be.
When I was at the Cleveland clinic,
I worked on the first face transplant
in the U.S.
- Oh, my God, Kam. That's incredible.
- Yeah.
Finally getting to see her smile.
It was one of
the happiest days of my life.
One of? Come on.
What else could even come close?
My thought exactly,
until a buddy of mine invited me
to Sierra Leone during the Ebola crisis.
I got a taste of what it's like
to help people on a global scale and...
And I never looked back.
I am so proud of you, Kam.
What you've done with your life...
And you're still here.
- Mm-hm.
- Shall we move on to dinner?
That seafood risotto does look slamming.
- Yeah.
- Yeah. Yeah.
[cell phone buzzing]
- Oh, uh... Excuse me. I have to take this.
- Of course. Absolutely.
Mick!
Started your new book?
What new book?
The one I just sold to Random House
for 500 grand.
I soft pitched them a follow-up
to The Third Way.
A follow-up?
I don't even know if there is one.
Oh, there is.
It's called Unattached.
You're pitching it tomorrow at 9 a.m.
That... That's in like 15 hours.
Picasso averaged three paintings a day.
Just saying.
- Everything all right?
- Perfect.
But I have to go.
Apparently, I just sold a new book.
- What? Sash, congrats.
- Thanks!
Now, all I need is an idea,
plus a beginning, middle and end...
all by tomorrow morning.
So...
Now you're gonna run.
I'm sorry.
I'll walk you home.
- [man] Majid.
- Hey, good to see you, man.
Hey, man.
- Next round's on me, okay?
- Thanks.
Need you, boss.
Table 3 is asking for the owner.
- What's the problem?
- Some issue with the hummus.
["Teardrops" by Modis Chrisha playing]
♪ Empty eyes, cold touch ♪
♪ Can you feel it fall apart ♪
♪ Everything we had ♪
We have to stop meeting like this.
Don't worry.
It will not happen again.
I couldn't stop thinking
about that kiss, either.
I ordered the expensive stuff.
Hope there might be
a friends and family discount?
You think this is nice?
The rep from Chateau Musar
is doing a tasting for my sommelier.
You want in?
Absolutely.
♪ Oh, he doesn't know ♪
Sorry, I couldn't wait.
I'm really glad you didn't.
♪ I come home, in the mornin' light ♪
♪ My mother says
"When you gonna live your life right?" ♪
♪ Oh, momma dear
We're not the fortunate ones ♪
♪ And girls, they wanna have fun ♪
♪ Oh, girls just wanna have fun ♪
♪ Girls wanna have their fun ♪
♪ They just wanna, they just wanna ♪
♪ When the workin' day is done ♪
♪ Girls, girls, they wanna have fun ♪
♪ They just wanna, they just wanna ♪
♪ They just wanna
Girls just wanna have fun ♪
Oh, my God. Delicious.
You know the Persians invented winemaking
over 7,000 years ago?
I did not know that.
Legend has it,
there was a beautiful princess
who lost favor with King Jamshid.
Overwhelmed with pain and sorrow,
she tried to poison herself
by drinking from a jar of spoiled grapes.
She got drunk...
- Yeah.
- ...fell asleep,
woke up the next morning
feeling no longer depressed
but rejuvenated.
She took her discovery to the king,
regained his favor...
and the rest is history.
You're adorable.
You are...
fearless.
So at the risk of pushing
my clearly-winning luck,
I gotta ask you something.
There's one more bottle
I want to share with you,
but it's back at my place.
What do you think?
Haven't been here in a minute.
I still remember coming up these stairs
hearing you play your gran's old LPs.
Stevie Wonder.
- Hotter Than July!
We wore that record out.
I remember every scratch and pop.
Listen, I know you gotta work
and I want you to.
And I get it, you're on your road,
and you don't have time
for detours or crazy Waze shortcuts.
But the truth is, you and I
are trying to get to the same place.
We both want to change the world, Sash.
Make our voices heard.
So why not double the horsepower?
We'll get there faster.
Let's take this ride together.
I better go.
Okay.
Good luck with your book.
You know what?
Fuck it. I still got 14 hours.
Wait, no way.
I will not be the reason
you don't finish your pitch.
You need to kill it tomorrow.
And I intend to, but first...
I'm gonna do this.
Are you sure?
What? You gonna take all night?
Maybe.
Wow, look at this place.
It's my first and only apartment
in the city.
- Why would you ever leave?
- Exactly.
- Here.
- Oh, thank you.
When I could finally afford a place
that wasn't on wheels,
I found this day one.
Fixed it up.
New York gods were smiling on me.
[Billie chuckles]
Guess they still are.
[laughs nervously] I'm sorry.
- No, I'm moving too fast, I know.
- No, it's not that. It's just...
I... I haven't been touched
by anyone but my husband...
in nine years.
No one else has even seen me naked
since having kids.
So what we're about to do is thrilling.
Um, it's also scary as hell.
I'm sorry. This is not
what you wanna hear on the second date.
This is exactly what I wanna hear.
Something real.
We don't have to do this.
At least not tonight.
I kind of think we do.
♪ Take it upon yourself ♪
♪ Save yourself... ♪
[breathing heavily]
♪ Bottle it all, oh, oh ♪
♪ And throw it into the sea ♪
♪ The hurt, it won't last too long ♪
♪ Trust me ♪
♪ It never gives in vain ♪
♪ It won't hurt you ♪
♪ It won't break you down, trust me ♪
♪ It never gives in vain ♪
♪ Never gives in vain ♪
♪ Cry yourself to sleep ♪
You are so...
so beautiful.
♪ Pick yourself up ♪
♪ Stand tall, don't look back ♪
♪ The pain you feel will subside ♪
♪ When you decide to smile ♪
♪ Don't give up... ♪
[moans]
♪ It's up to you to want to ♪
♪ Right your way ♪
♪ It's up to you to
Stand up and smile... ♪
[moaning]
I'm... I'm sorry.
It was good.
- It was so good.
- It was?
It feels so good
to be out in the open. Finally.
We can do whatever we want.
Start our own firm,
take our clients with us.
Marry me, Cooper.
- What?
- I love you.
I wanna spend
the rest of my life with you.
Fast track the divorce.
- Give Billie whatever she wants.
- Okay.
- Let's do this.
- Okay. Hold on.
It's what you want too. I know it.
Of course. It's...
That's absolutely what I want.
I just need some time.
Take all the time you need.
We skipped dinner.
I'll grab us some Chinese food.
My hero.
[Francesca] Fast track the divorce.
Marry me, Cooper.
It's what you want too. I know it.
Two orders of kung pao chicken
and I'll get the lo mein on the side.
- [cell phone buzzes]
- Oh...
Okay. I'm also going to add steamed
chicken dumplings and sesame noodles.
Okay. Yup. Yup.
[woman] Someone's very demanding.
You're a good boyfriend.
Not so sure that's true.
- Order 379.
- Yep.
Ah.
Keeping it simple, huh? Good for you.
I did order the chicken double fantasy
just in case.
Never know when you're gonna meet someone
you wanna share your wonton with.
[moaning]
Yeah, yeah.
You got room in there for two?
Always.
[giggling]
Hey, Gigi...
I don't know if I can do this.
Hm?
Did you say something?
Look. Aren't these darling?
Dr. Kim sent them over.
I'm trying to decide
which one to get blown up and framed.
I think they'll look great in the nursery,
or maybe our bedroom.
What?
Did you want to say something?
You're amazing.
Because I have you.
[indie rock playing]
How about we go with this one?
- You read my mind.
- [laughs]
♪ I can't run to you, Father ♪
There he is.
♪ Goddamn it, I cannot bend ♪
It's our son.
♪ I'm all shriveled inside ♪
♪ I'll be tryin' to suck all the liquid
Out the dirt ♪
♪ Tryin' to catch a curve ♪
♪ Diggin' my own grave ♪
Let's do this right.
♪ I'll be tryin' to suck the liquid
Out the dirt ♪
♪ Tryin' to catch a curve ♪
♪ Diggin' my own grave ♪
Marry me, Gigi.
♪ Tell me if I run away ♪
Is that a yes?
♪ How long will I bleed? ♪
[theme music playing]