Previously on Dexter...
My mother was murdered
when I was a boy.
I was there. I saw it.
3 men were arrested
for those murders.
One's deceased,
one's doing life without possibility,
and that's the only one that's still
an open case, Santos Jiminez.
1972 !
Did you have to saw her
into little pieces ?
Did you have to leave two little boys
soaking in a pool
of their mother's blood ?
I don't care what you did.
It's okay.
- Who the fuck are you ?
- Pardon my tits.
How could you do this to Rita,
not to mention her kids ?
Rita broke up with me, okay ?
'cause when you're around, I kind
of feel like I can deal with anything.
Your past is a bigger mystery
than fucking Jimmy Hoffa.
It's time to make Doakes go away.
Sergeant Doakes
is on administrative leave
pending an internal affairs
investigation.
The killer's making us chase our tails.
- You know what that means ?
- That he might be one of us ?
I was working on my piece,
and it just caught fire.
I was so scared.
Promise me that you won't
leave me, that you won't go anywhere.
I'm not going anywhere.
I can't believe he said it.
Even for Masuka, it was too much.
And Batista didn't do anything.
Talk about lame, he fucking sat there.
- You know how much I wanted to...
- Is that the sports section ?
I used to enjoy quiet mornings,
but ever since the fire at Lila's loft,
she's been crashing here
a bit too often.
- Is that my shirt ?
- I thought it was Dex's.
It's not.
It's okay... keep it.
And so now I share the kitchen
with a cobra and a mongoose.
Somebody drank all the coffee again.
Somebody didn't drink all the coffee.
I had a cup, Dexter had a cup,
and it just kind of went like that
until the pot was empty.
- Deb, please.
- What ?
Someone didn't drink all the coffee.
Stupid question.
- Why are you sticking up for her ?
- I'm just trying to keep the peace.
Maybe we should stay
at your place tonight.
Has the fire damage been repaired ?
The insurance company's
dicking me around.
- Won't pay me.
- Don't worry.
- I'll move out soon.
- Stop leeching off your brother ?
- Whatever for ?
- Again, thanks for sticking up for me.
- I am Switzerland.
- Yeah, and I'm out of here.
What's this ?
It's the dragon zombie.
- Cody likes to hide things in my bag.
- He's trying to control you.
By hiding toys in your bag, you have
no choice but to return them to him.
He's 7. He seldom has thoughts more
complicated than the desire for candy.
I'll see you at your loft tonight.
Honey !
Honey, no.
You said we could make breakfast.
- I meant cereal, baby.
- I don't want cereal.
I guess I should give Rita back
her key.
Cody, no.
No, let mommy get the d...
It's Dexter !
- He brought doughnuts !
- I did.
I also brought... A dragon zombie !
I knew you'd find it !
Hope it's okay I'm here.
Could you watch them while I finish
getting ready ? Astor still has homework.
Thank you, Dexter.
Meet me at the car.
Good thing I dropped by.
Don't ever do it again.
- Sorry ?
- It's too hard on the kids
and it's too hard on me.
It's Paul all over again.
Please, Dexter, just stay away.
Notice we have some new faces.
Please make them feel welcome.
Our immediate task
is to re-examine every criminal case
involving our 18 victims.
- Where would you like us to start ?
- By answering every question
as honestly and with as much
detail as you can.
Excuse me, sir.
- Answering questions ?
- That is correct.
I can hardly expect you to investigate
your own cases.
What are you saying ?
Are we under investigation ?
We're now operating assuming
that our killer is somehow connected
to law enforcement.
Whether he be a file clerk,
a dispatch officer,
- park ranger...
- Or a police officer.
Or a police officer.
Is that why you brought in
all these suits ?
Special agents.
Sir, you risk alienating every cop
on the task force if you do this.
We go where the chase leads us...
Even if it gets messy.
It's insulting.
We're as capable as they are
of looking into our own cases.
Who wears a wool suit
in the middle of summer in Miami ?
Nazis. That's who.
It's all about intimidation.
And the idea that one of us could be
the killer is complete bullshit.
What do you mean ? "us" who ?
Lundy has his feds
investigating all of our cases
that are tied to the Bay Harbor victims.
That's good here.
We gotta stand tough here.
We gotta make it clear to them
that we're not gonna be their little
"yes, sir, no, sir" lapdogs.
Gentlemen.
I'd like to go over
some of your cases tomorrow.
Got them listed there.
It would be helpful if you could
gather up any notes you may have taken.
Happy to help.
- Way to stand tough, Dexter.
- Sorry.
That's exactly how Hitler walked.
It seems my manifesto unintentionally
helped Lundy narrow his focus.
That's what I get for trying
to emulate Lila and take the offensive.
I've always worked best in the shadows,
and that's where I have to stay.
Lundy's really pissing people off.
He's got his whole crew
looking through every case
involving any
of the Bay Harbor victims.
- He sounds desperate.
- You know you're gonna be called in.
I'll be curious to see if I show up.
Okay, James,
you need to be a little careful here.
If you wanna keep your job,
you gotta cooperate.
Being on suspension
does not exclude you from this.
And who was it that suspended me again ?
Oh, shit ! That was you.
Please, don't act
like you didn't deserve it.
Your case is coming up for review
in a week.
- If you wanna keep your job...
- You keep saying that.
What makes you think
I wanna keep my job ?
Are you just talking here,
or is this something
that you've seriously considered ?
Well, you and I both know that I've gone
as high as I can over there.
Maybe it's time to move on.
Well, what would you do ?
I don't know.
My father was a butcher.
Maybe I'll open up my own butcher shop.
Yeah, I can just see you
putting on an apron every morning.
Look, I have a friend.
He's the head of personnel
at Stillwater security.
Government contractors.
They're always looking
for people like you.
It's a dangerous world out there.
They pay a lot of money to make it safe.
Yeah, you got that right.
Alright. Set it up.
I'll meet with your guy.
Officer Morgan.
Yes ?
I picked the Rodrigo case for you
to look into.
Small-time dope dealer.
Arrested for murder
ended up walking free, then disappeared
off the face of the earth
until his body was found
in a garbage bag in the ocean.
Not exciting enough for you ?
I'm homicide. I mean,
I thought you didn't want us
checking into our own cases.
You're new to homicide.
At the time of this case, you were
still in vice. No conflict there.
I'm flattered you want me in
on this, but...
Batista and Doakes were lead here.
I feel kind of weird about investigating
my own colleagues.
"Weird". Gosh.
I'd hate for you to feel weird.
You know what I mean.
Would you have dinner with me
tomorrow night ?
Or would that make you feel weird ?
I'd love to have dinner with you.
Good.
I'll take you to the best restaurant
in Miami.
Great.
I like the smell.
Don't you ?
Like something exciting happened here.
It's like when a piece of bread
gets stuck in the toaster.
You like to pretend
there's no poetry in you.
So, what's the problem
with the insurance company ?
It's ridiculous.
They think the fire
is of suspicious origin,
and they need to finish
their investigation.
What do they mean,"suspicious" ?
Are they saying
you started the fire on purpose ?
Who knows what they're saying ?
You know insurance companies.
Anything to keep from paying out.
Especially when a fire
has multiple points of origin.
So, you never told me.
How did it go at Rita's this morning ?
You know, I just returned Cody's toy,
and that was it.
No quickie on the kitchen table ?
Rita doesn't have a kitchen table.
Clever way of not answering
the question.
It was...
Awkward, actually.
Always is.
You can't go back. You know that.
I'm not trying to go anywhere.
The bed's all ready.
- I can't.
- And why would that be ?
I have too much work to do.
I have all these case files
I have to go over for tomorrow.
You didn't bring any work with you ?
At home...
I need... work at home.
Goodbye, then.
So, I'll see you tomorrow ?
Whatever.
Is it possible she started that fire
on purpose ?
I can't imagine why.
What I do know is
that I can't take any risks right now.
- At least, you wanted to...
- Morgan ! Come in.
Can I offer you some tea ?
No, thank you. I'm...
And he pours it anyway.
He's trying to throw me off balance,
show that I don't have the power
to say no to him.
How about some sesame crackers
to go with that ?
So I'll say yes to everything.
I'd love some.
Sorry. Guess I ate them all.
Asshole.
So,
You worked firsthand on, what,
four of the cases related
to the Bay Harbor investigation ?
I believe so.
Your reports
were a real pleasure to read.
Concise, meticulous.
I appreciate that.
- Good. Thank you.
- Does your sister prefer meat or fish ?
You have more than one ?
Sister ?
No. Just Deb.
Or is she more
of a salad kind of person ?
- She's definitely a carnivore.
- Good.
So...
the Rodrigo case.
Let's talk about that one.
Kind of blew it, didn't you ?
- I'm sorry ?
- Anthony Rodrigo.
Crack dealer with an apparent habit
of killing people who got in his way.
I believe this was
yes, Doakes' and Batista's case.
They finally tied Rodrigo
to one of his victims,
built a solid manslaughter case,
would have got him off the street
for a few years.
But the case largely
rested on the bloodwork that you did.
Bloodwork that in the course
of the trial was proven to be, well...
wrong.
So, you...
one of the most cautious and precise
forensic specialists
I've had the pleasure to work with,
you performed bloodwork
that directly led
to Rodrigo walking free.
I asked myself,
"how the hell did that happen ?"
And did you answer:
"Dexter blew the case on purpose
"so that he could get Rodrigo
off the streets for good
"with a cordless reciprocating saw" ?
I'm sorry.
You've caught me off-guard here.
Sloppy bloodwork.
This wasn't my idea.
Could have said no.
Come on, Angel, we have a job to do.
Since when my job is trying to prove
to a fellow police officer
I'm not a killer ?
That's not about that.
- What is this about ?
- It's about finding someone
who had motive and opportunity
to kill all 18 of our victims.
No way it's anybody in our department.
Then help me prove it.
Go through the Rodrigo case with me.
It is not just you.
LaGuerta's cooperating on her old cases.
Even Matthews is coming in.
The Rodrigo file.
You just happen to have it with you.
I'm a reasonable man.
You know how it is.
The defense attorneys bring in
their so-called blood experts
to counter everything I say.
I'm familiar with the process.
I understand how this may look like
sloppy bloodwork to the layman.
That's what Rodrigo's defense
convinced the jury of.
But as you can see,
the low-velocity blood drops
clearly point in the direction
opposite to that in which
we know Rodrigo to have fled,
- which makes it impossible...
- Except those low-velocity drops
were revealed to actually be 90-degree
passive drops that were given tails
due to the angle of the floor.
Perhaps, but if you then examine
- the blood trail...
- Which we know isn't a blood trail,
but projected blood.
You're not winning me over here,
Morgan.
The truth ?
By all means.
I was overworked. I was carrying
half a dozen cases at once.
It was a heat wave...
means a spike in...
homicides.
This one got pushed aside.
I didn't write up my summary
until an hour before the trial.
I obviously overlooked a few things.
A murderer walked free
because you were overworked ?
Yes.
Who's this guy ? Lenny Asher.
Lenny ? He's a nutjob...
But it says he lived next door to
Rodrigo, filed all kinds of complaints.
But he filed complaints
about everybody.
He sat at his window all day
and call us every time
he saw someone move.
He called us once to say
there was something weird
about the clouds.
Still no harm talking to him, right ?
Lenny Asher ?
Who the hell are you ?
Detective Batista.
This is officer Morgan.
We're with the Miami metro homicide.
Can we come in ?
Who's dead ?
- Anthony Rodrigo.
- I know. They found him in the ocean.
I hope a whale ate him
and shat him out,
and then ate him again.
- You weren't too close to him, right ?
- He was scum !
Yeah, you made numerous calls
about him when he used to live here.
He was a drug dealer.
He played loud music,
urinated on my lilies.
You actually saw that ?
They were dead.
That's all I needed to know.
Any thoughts as to
who might have killed him ?
How the hell should I know ?
Look at that joker parked
right in front of the fire hydrant.
I got his license plate, though.
That would be our car.
You take a lot of notes ?
Anything hinky
happens outside this window,
- I note it.
- How long you been doing that ?
Since someone stuck a nail in my tire.
March 1998.
Rodrigo was last seen alive
the day after his trial.
April 16, 2002.
- Think you took any notes that day ?
- If something happened, I did.
You still have those notes ?
Here. 2002.
What kind of order
did you put them in ?
I told you: 2002.
I have no idea if Lundy
bought my excuse.
Either way,
it makes me a little anxious
to see my sister looking through
the Rodrigo files,
Looking for me.
You're never gonna guess
what I found.
What did you find ?
An apartment.
- Great.
- One-bedroom near 78th and Harding.
Big change.
It's time, you know ?
- Good for you. When do you move ?
- As soon as possible,
but not tonight. I have a date.
I thought you broke up with Gabriel.
It's someone new.
Lundy.
Lundy, special agent Lundy ?
He's at least 20 years older than me.
What do you care ?
I don't.
I mean...
I'm sure you wouldn't do
anything like that.
What are you talking about ?
Do what ?
Like try to sleep your way
to the top.
You douche.
That is so not true.
No, of course not. I shouldn't have
even said anything, and I'm sure
that thought would never even occur
Double douche !
You are not allowed
to talk about anyone I date
as long you're seeing
little Miss "pardon my tits".
I am sorry, Dex, but she is gross...
And pale,
and nobody is pale in Miami.
She is obviously a vampire.
A gross english-titty vampire.
You just described the perfect woman.
Truth is I need to avoid Lila
for now.
Harry taught me that the key to survival
was staying one step ahead.
But Lundy almost trapped me today.
I can't be unprepared like that again.
Hey, it's me.
Why aren't you here ? I'm starving.
I thought you knew.
It's my bowling night.
Bowling ? Really ?
What, like Fred Flintstone ?
I'm more in the Barney Rubble category.
How fun.
I'd love to watch you bowl.
It's not really a spectator sport.
Well, I'll close my eyes.
But it's sort of the guys'night out.
Come on, Dex, I want to meet your friends.
Where is it ? What time is it ? Give me the address.
Starlight lanes. 1690 Michigan avenue.
7:00.
I guess I'm going bowling.
Go, Dexter !
He only got three pins down.
I like to celebrate
the little things in life.
If you like little things, I'm your man.
I mean, I'm not little everywhere.
Some places I'm just perfectly average.
You are perfectly adorable.
Why you got a hug
and I got a pat on the nose ?
'cause you're like a retarded puppy.
Your ass does the cutest little thing
when you bowl.
If you guys will excuse me,
i need to use the ladies'room.
She's pretty hot.
Yes. She is.
Nice place.
Very...
Gray.
Yes, the bureau have always been known
for their fashion sense.
Honestly, all I care about is the kitchen.
You cook ?
Like I said, best restaurant in Miami.
Really ?
You're gonna cook for me.
Well, don't ever expect me
to return the favor...
Unless you're a big fan of toast.
I would love to eat your toast.
Gosh, that sounded wrong.
So, what's for dinner ?
Steak florentine
and grilled potatoes italian-style.
Fucking-a.
There's that mouth again.
I'm sorry.
It's just the way I talk.
And if we're gonna be together,
you better get used to it.
Can't change who I am. I'm crass and...
dirty, and...
I have a very filthy mind.
- You're also pretty adorable.
- I know.
Now start peeling potatoes.
I like a man that takes control.
Wash your hands first.
You're so turning me on.
You know, considering our age
difference, you're not too old to spank.
No, stop. Please.
I can't control myself.
My God !
Sure you don't wanna
grab a beer with us ?
Nah, thanks. I'm tired.
I hope you saved enough energy
for me.
That doesn't look like
the look of love.
Sorry. I really am tired.
I think I'm gonna go home.
Help ! Help !
Somebody please come !
God.
You OK ?
- Dexter, you're bleeding.
- It's not deep.
- I mean, what the hell ?
- He tried to grab my watch.
It's stupid.
I should have let him have it.
It was... reflex.
- Sure you're OK ?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Jesus Christ. They sell anyone
a gun in Florida, won't they ?
Yeah, I know. Scary, right ?
- Anyone get a license plate ?
- No, it was all too fast.
- You want us to take you to a doctor ?
- No. Really, I'm fine.
I'll take care of him.
So...
who was it ?
Who ?
That man. He wasn't trying to rob you.
He was trying to kill you.
Santos Jiminez,
the man who murdered my mother.
My God, Dexter.
He must have followed me
to the bowling alley.
- If you hadn't have seen him in time...
- I saw him. That's all that matters.
None of this scares you ?
Nothing you could do, Dexter,
would scare me.
I believe you.
Come here.
Whatever comes,
we'll get through this together.
I'm not leaving your side, Dexter.
I'm not leaving yours.
Really ?
Why would you think that ?
You've just been a bit distant lately.
I get that way when I'm stressed.
What are you stressed about ?
Right now, nothing.
Do you think Dexter will come
for breakfast tomorrow ?
I don't think so, honey.
Well, maybe we should call him.
It's kind of late.
But Dexter stays up late.
She doesn't want to call him.
Why not ?
Dexter and I broke up.
- Why ?
- They don't like each other anymore.
That's not true.
Does that mean
he doesn't like us either ?
No. Of course he likes you.
It's just... That's hard.
when two people break up.
It makes them sad to see each other.
I don't think Dexter's gonna be coming
for breakfast for a while.
Sorry.
Lila may be the right woman for me
but she's wrong about one thing.
Recovery simply isn't an option.
When I let my guard down,
I open myself up for attack...
or capture.
I need to embrace who I am,
who I've always been.
I need to kill the man
who murdered my mother.
I'd almost forgotten this feeling...
Driving toward a kill,
all my senses sharpened.
It's like I've been living
underwater,
holding my breath,
and now I can finally breathe.
So how come
it's so suffocating in here ?
- It's nice to see you.
- Yeah, feels all warm and comfy.
I spoke to Todd about you.
Yeah ?
He's very interested.
He said someone with your special-ops
background
typically starts at about $200,000.
- I could live with that.
- You can meet him tonight.
9:00, bar at the Hilton.
I'll be there.
I appreciate your time.
Can we get this over with, sir ?
It's interesting that of the 18 victims,
9 passed through this very station,
and you worked on cases
involving 4 of them.
And you were unable to obtain
a single conviction.
The Smith case thrown out
because of inadmissible evidence.
Orozco skipped bail,
never to be seen again.
The Rodrigo case lost
due to bad bloodwork.
Excuse me ?
You weren't aware of that ?
The D. A. didn't get a conviction.
That's all I know.
Are we through here, sir ?
- No, actually. We're just...
- We're done.
Look at this.
"June 1st:
Mrs. Holcomb takes out trash,
"drops soda bottle,
doesn't pick it up".
"March 17th:
"airplane flying too low".
I told you, this guy's a fruit bat.
"April".
It's the month we want.
"April 16th"...
Fuck me sideways, listen to this.
"Rodrigo gets into car
parked in wrong space.
"Must be drunk
because someone's carrying him".
The plate's here. This is
from 9:00 the night he disappeared.
Last time he was seen alive.
We gotta run that plate.
Whoever owned this car is our killer.
- I'll get Lundy.
- He's out with his Feds.
I'm calling him in.
Lila almost had me believing
it was possible
to change, to become something else,
as if that ever really happens.
I've always known what I am.
"If the glove fits..."
A secret cabin
in the middle of the Everglades.
what more could
a rededicated serial killer ask for ?
Cocaine.
Apparently Mr. Jiminez
never gave up his old habits.
What a bad, bad man.
What ?
You think it just turned on by itself ?
"There is no such plate".
Is that a 1 or an "i" ? Fuck you, Lenny.
Fuck your handwriting.
Kind of busy here.
Then can you please tell me
where I can find Dexter ?
I brought him some dinner.
- Dexter's not here.
- Where is he ?
How should I know ?
He said he was working late.
Is that what he told you ?
What do you mean ?
He's not working late.
I think he lied to you.
Men are such pigs.
I'm so sorry. I'm sure he'll show up.
He's very excited about this job.
I swear, I've tried every combination.
Nothing is coming up.
I told you Lenny would be
a waste of time.
Maybe it's not a Florida plate.
Try Georgia.
Holy shit, here it is.
The vehicle was registered
to Charlie Lewis.
I know that name.
A drug dealer out of New York.
A tough guy.
Likes to carry a big-ass knife.
That's our guy.
That's the Bay Harbor butcher.
I told you he wasn't a cop.
What ?
Shit.
Where is he ?
According to this,
South Bay correctional facility.
- What ? For how long ?
- Shit.
Charlie Lewis was arrested
April 12, 2002.
That's four days before Rodrigo was seen
being carried into the car.
- Who had his car, one of his gang ?
- This is where it gets really bad.
- The vehicle was seized as evidence.
- By who ?
By our department.
Where was the vehicle held ?
Right here in our evidence lab,
behind a secure gate.
Someone signed the vehicle out,
picked Rodrigo up,
killed him and then
signed the vehicle back in.
- So you have records.
- Why would we keep them ?
The only people allowed access
to those vehicles
are members of the Miami Metro
Police Department.
Holy shit.
Bay Harbor Butcher is one of our own.
We keep this to ourselves for now.
Just the three of us.
I'm gonna go tell it
to a bottle of scotch.
Here we are again.
What... what the fuck ?
I know. I keep asking myself
that same question.
- Let me out of here !
- But...
I'm finding it's best to accept things
you can't change, you know ?
Normally, I'd have a chat
to make sure you understand
why you're here, but...
I think you have a pretty good idea.
Let me go.
I got cocaine.
You can have all of it.
It's funny you should say that.
I am off the wagon.
But that was never my drug.
I'll fucking kill you !
No, Mr. Jiminez.
I'm gonna kill you tonight...
For what you did to my mother...
and because,
well, this is what I do best.
It's kind of fitting, don't you think ?
Astor, Cody, come on, let's eat.
- How'd you get the door unlocked ?
- It was already open.
That's odd.
Dexter, hi.
Look, I'm sorry to bother you,
and I'm sure this is nothing,
but I was just wondering if by chance
you were at my house.
- Well, no.
- It's just that the door was open
and you're the only other one
with a key.
Rita, get out of the house.
Call the police.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
I can't leave you here.
I can't take you with me.
Don't go anywhere !
Hey, I'm sorry to drag you into this.
- No, I'm glad you called. The kids ?
- Next door.
The place is empty.
No sign of forcible entry.
I'm guessing you just forgot
to lock the door.
- If you need anything else...
- No, you're not leaving.
Sir ?
Someone was in this house.
I need you to stay here in the house
until I tell you it's safe.
Really ? I need to do those things ?
I'm with Miami metro homicide.
I know you don't take orders from me,
but if you like, I could get
Lt LaGuerta on the phone.
If you prefer to speak to cpt Matthews,
I can arrange it too.
- Dexter, what's going on ?
- Please, just stay here, okay ?
It's one thing to fuck with me,
another to fuck with...
my ex-girlfriend who hates me.
The Lila experiment is officially over.
Give me Rita's key.
Well, that's your fault,
isn't it, Dexter ?
You lied to me about working late,
and I thought I might find you there.
Do not ever go to Rita's house again.
Do you understand ?
Is this the monster
that you keep telling me about ?
Trust me, when you meet the monster,
you'll know.
You called Jiminez.
Yeah, I suppose I did.
Why ?
Why would you try to have me killed ?
You weren't going to get killed.
That's why I did it at the bowling,
so all your police-officer friends
would be there.
What were you thinking ?
Are you insane ?
I was trying to bring us
back together again !
You were pulling away, and...
Remember at the hotel
after you faced Jiminez ?
That's... That's what I wanted !
To bring you back !
So you called him ?
Well, it worked, didn't it ?
Last night...
You and I...
You fell asleep in my arms.
What ?
You are more dangerous
than my addiction will ever be.
That's saying a lot.
Stay away from Rita.
Stay away from me.
Or what ?
Or you will see the monster.