Previously on Dexter...
Jesus Christ,
you're the Bay Harbor Butcher.
I hate that name.
What's it gonna be, Morgan ?
Kill me now or set me free !
James knows that I believe in him,
so it was worth the risk.
To your job ? To your career ?
When you care about someone,
you do what you have to do.
Your credibility was compromised
when you failed to report a call
from the subject
of a goddamn FBI manhunt.
What really pisses me off
is you might be right.
The kids have been through
so much lately.
I don't want them to feel like they've
been abandoned by everyone they love.
Does this mean we're dating again ?
I track killers. That's what I do.
They tend to move around.
I know that.
Then I'm not sure what you thought
would happen when the case ended.
I like it rough.
Jesus.
I don't need Doakes dead.
I just need his fingerprints
to complete my frame job.
Every saturday,
beginning dive classes
practice underwater skills
beside this dock.
Tomorrow they'll find
a morbid little surprise.
I wanna know if there's anything unusual
about my father's death.
He killed himself.
The idea of a code was one thing,
but the reality of it ?
Harry walked in on what he created...
and he couldn't live with himself.
I always thought hardening arteries
squeezed the life out of my father,
but it was me.
Harry gazed into the eyes
of his creation and saw evil,
pure and simple.
My evil...
It killed him.
That shit about your father...
If you wanna talk about it...
About what ?
That my life is one tragic mistake ?
We've all felt that at one time
or another. I have.
Did you happen to be stuffing a human
leg into a garbage bag at that point ?
If you wanna make a change,
now's the time.
All you got to do
is let me out of here.
It's over, man.
It is over when I say it is !
There's that anger again.
You got to let that out, man.
Careful, sergeant,
you might get your wish.
I'm flying without a code here.
I can unleash the beast anytime.
- You know that's not the answer.
- But it would feel fucking great.
But you would hate yourself
for the rest of your life.
All the things Harry taught me...
everything...
It's bullshit.
It's the only way
I know how to live.
Turn yourself in.
Rule number one...
Don't get caught.
You're spinning. Let me help you.
Sooner or later,
you'll hurt someone else.
I'm talking about your sister
or your girlfriend
or even those kids.
- I would never...
- No, not on purpose,
but you can't control the shit that's
growing inside of you. It's like cancer.
And in case you haven't noticed,
it's spreading.
End it now.
Take responsibility
for who you are, man.
We'll go to the station together.
I'll help you.
Morgan, don't answer that.
Stay with me, man.
Fuck !
Yes, this is Dexter Morgan.
My name is Dr. Hill.
I work at Good Samaritan hospital.
I'm calling on behalf of Lila Tournay.
- How did you get this number ?
- You're on her emergency contact list.
Ms. Tournay was rushed into our E. R.
In respiratory arrest.
Could you come to the hospital ?
I'm two hours away.
Call somebody else.
There's a legal complication.
What kind of complication ?
I can't discuss it over the phone.
You really need to be here.
- Where are you going ?
- Don't worry,
I'll send the FBI your way
soon enough.
- You're still gonna try to frame me ?
- I'm kind of down a path here.
You'll get your chance
to tell them I'm the killer,
and they'll ignore you like before,
and I'll...
- And you'll burn in hell.
- Something like that.
He's gone, Dex.
Dad's heart finally gave out.
Harry's heart gave out
when he saw what's inside me.
He thought he could tame it,
give it a purpose,
help it find a place
in the natural order.
Guess he was wrong.
I need a second alone with him, okay ?
Thanks.
We spoke on the phone
regarding your girlfriend, Ms. Tournay.
She's not my girlfriend.
I thought she said she was.
- She probably did.
- So, you're...
It's complicated.
Look, why is Angel here ?
We found rohypnol,
the date-rape drug,
in Lila's system.
With her bruising,
the wound to the back of her head,
we may be looking at a case
of sexual assault.
No, that didn't happen.
Ms. Tournay has no recollection
of what did happen.
She's requested we perform a rape kit.
I need to talk to her.
You came to see me.
You're so sweet.
The doctors think Angel raped you.
- Did he ? Everything's a bit fuzzy.
- This is desperate.
- It won't work.
- What are you talking about ?
I'm just glad you're here.
I missed you so much.
This is how you win me back ?
Framing a good man
to get what you want ?
Which is precisely
what I'm doing to Doakes.
What's the matter, Dexter ?
You look so sad...
lost.
Don't do this.
I won't press charges against Angel.
I'll do whatever you want.
If you promise to take me back.
Why can't you just let me go ?
Because I'm your real soul mate.
Not Rita.
Me.
I see you.
Inside.
And I'm the only one.
Look where it's gotten you.
You know that I could never do
anything like that, right ?
You don't even have to say anything.
You warned me about her,
but my dick wouldn't listen.
I could lose everything over this.
What would I say to my little girl ?
The doctor said Lila has 72 h
to press charges.
Maybe she'll come to her senses.
I should get home and grab a few hours
of sleep. Let me get this.
No, back off. I got it.
If I got to choose a person...
A real person...
to be like...
Out of anyone, it'd be you.
I'm not really sure what that means,
but, thanks, Dex.
See you in the morning.
I'd appreciate it if you didn't
mention this to anyone at the station.
Of course not.
Thanks.
How did it come to this ?
I've always gone after criminals.
Now I have the fate of two cops
in my hands.
Doakes was right.
The cancer is spreading.
- We're out of yogurt.
- Add it to the list.
- We'll stop by the store tonight.
- The store's on the way to work.
It's also on the way home.
We're gonna be late.
Who joined who
in the shower this morning ?
How about, in the futur,
I set the alarm 10 min earlier ?
Make it 20.
"The future",
I'm liking the sound of that.
We're being ordered to work.
You're the head of the task force,
you do the ordering.
Who's D. D. Adams ?
My boss.
Mission accomplished.
The weapons I tossed into the ocean
were found as planned.
One more nail in Doakes' coffin.
All right, people. Listen up.
This is FBI deputy director Max Adams.
He just got in from Washington.
He's going to be helping us out
for a while.
Once again, I have pledged
our full cooperation and resources,
so let's make him feel at home.
The murder weapons before you
were found yesterday
by a beginning scuba-diving class.
The instructor
contacted the FBI directly
which brought them to my attention.
Fingerprint analysis ties them
to one James Doakes.
- This doesn't prove a damn thing.
- Not now.
- Why wasn't I brought in on this ?
- You just were, Frank.
- Now, we know sergeant Doakes...
- Lundy better watch his back.
He's abandoned the tools of the trade
that means he's probably on the run.
This footage was taken four days ago
at a mobile station
just off highway 41,
southeast of Naples.
Ladies and gentlemen,
sergeant James Doakes.
I can't believe it.
$3.49 for regular ?
So, we...
have let our target get away once.
Let's not drop the ball again.
Asshole.
Highway 41 runs
through the Everglades national park.
It won't be long now.
I can hang this on Doakes and then...
Then what ?
Years of trials and appeals with him
pointing his finger
and calling me killer ?
For such a neat monster,
I'm making an awfully big mess.
Where does this prick Adams get off
taking such cheap shots at Lundy ?
I heard that Doakes walked off
in the middle of Lundy's questioning
and that Lundy didn't stop him.
I might have heard that wrong.
Peters.
Nice hair, Borelli.
I'm sure the johns up in Boystown
are loving that Duran Duran look.
What ?
You meatheads lose your sense of humor ?
Your joke wasn't funny.
We have a warrant
for detective Batista's arrest.
Bullshit. For what ?
A woman named Lila Tournay
has filed sexual-assault charges
against him.
That fucking bitch !
It's okay.
I knew this was coming.
It's not okay. Captain, lieutenant !
Put those away
or I will shove them up your ass !
What's going on here ?
We've been asked to bring
Batista upstairs for processing
I'm sure that detective Batista
will go along with you peacefully.
It's not your fault.
I'll be okay.
It isn't my fault. I warned Angel.
Still, I hate to see him disgraced
in front of everyone.
And LaGuerta about to lose
her former partner, her friend.
Even Lundy is caught in hurricane
Dexter's path of destruction.
Maybe this is how evil works.
Destroying everything it touches...
including my father.
You're not gonna believe
the morning I'm having.
- I know the feeling.
- My car is stalled on harper and 3rd.
Think you can come get me ?
- Hang tight. I'll be right there.
- Thanks, Dex.
I'm the helpful handyman.
How evil can I possibly be ?
I'm sparing Rita and Deb
by framing Doakes.
Right ?
Over here !
Thank God.
I've been held prisoner in a cabin
for 2 fucking days.
Fucking hellhole.
I don't wanna go to the cabin.
I need you to get my ass out of here.
I'm a police sergeant.
Miami metro homicide.
I gotta run upstairs.
There's a whole Batista thing going on.
- Lunch today ?
- Doubtful.
I've got to write up a status report
for deputy director Adams.
Why'd they send that dipshit ?
Washington gets nervous
when there's no movement on a case,
- especially one as big as this.
- No movement ?
You're the reason they found
the blood slides in Doakes' car.
I'm also the one who let him get away.
- We all let him get away.
- I was in charge.
The evidence was there,
but something inside me
wasn't convinced he was our guy so...
I let him walk.
It was a bad call.
- Now we might never...
- Stop it.
- Stop what ?
- Acting like me.
You're a God. Don't you forget it.
So, what do you think it is ?
Carburettor.
Transmission.
That round, black hose thing.
I'm more a boat guy.
The last thing I need right now
is a major repair bill.
Throw in a tow and rental car,
- there goes Astor's piano lessons.
- Take the mini-van.
No, I can't. It's too big
of an inconvenience.
You'll drop me at work.
I'll borrow one from the motor pool.
I'll make it up to you.
Dinner ?
I have a better idea.
Pack a lunch, bring the kids,
I'll take you out on the ocean tomorrow.
- The kids have school tomorrow.
- Think of it as a field trip.
You don't know cody's teacher.
- Just one day... Just one more day.
Is everything okay, Dexter ?
After everything we've been through
lately, I just want...
to be together with you guys.
Is that selfish ?
No, it's lovely.
Sergeant Doakes can rejoice.
I come bearing real food.
Shit.
All right.
Suck my dick, motherfucker.
You understand ?
Friends of yours ?
From what I can tell,
they're friends of that drug dealer.
They would've killed me
once I had all that coke on the boat.
Thanks, Morgan.
Well, this is awkward.
I think we made
some alligators very happy.
So, here we are.
Back to fucking square one.
Not exactly.
I'll tell you what, James.
- Can I call you James ?
- Knock yourself out.
I'm toying with an idea...
I've been under federal investigation
for two months.
My trophies were stolen.
Sorry.
The code I live by has been shattered.
And I have a co-worker in a cage.
Things aren't going so well.
No shit. I can see that.
You told me...
to take responsibility for what I am.
You were right.
Harry killed the wrong person.
- Morgan, you're not thinking about...
- Kill myself ? No, that's pathetic.
But I can't live
in this house of cards anymore,
waiting for it all to fall down.
I need to do something, you know ?
I'm thinking about turning myself in.
That's a good call, Morgan.
That's a tough call,
but that's a good call, man.
I need some fucking relief.
Yeah, you can't keep running, man.
That's for pussies.
You're just gonna end up
in exactly the same situation...
- sooner or later.
- Prison.
I could finally get some sleep.
Yeah.
In the long run
it would be easier on Deb...
Better than watching me
dragged in like an animal...
Which, let's face it, will happen...
someday.
Morgan, we'll do it together.
I'll go with you.
Come on, let's go.
If I do this, I need a day
to get my affairs in order.
Fine. Tie me up,
throw me in the trunk. Let's go.
I brought supplies. Fresh fruit.
Mention that when they interview you
for the story of my life.
Don't leave me in this cage, anything
could happen. What're you doing ?
I think we've seen the worst of that.
I've really enjoyed
our conversations, James.
I lie to everyone I know...
except my victims
right before I kill them.
It's hard to establish
much of a rapport there.
Sorry about the cage.
Fuck.
- What ?
- It's me. What are you doing tonight ?
I'm about to get off of work, why ?
I've got some papers
I need you to sign.
Papers ? What kind of papers ?
I'll explain when I see you.
I'm meeting Masuka
and Batista for drinks.
Why don't you bring the papers
and join us ?
- How's Angel doing ?
- How do you think he's doing ?
It's your fault he's in this mess.
If you hadn't fucked Elvira.
I'm not the best brother, am I ?
Dexter, are you smoking something ?
I've always been curious to try.
Do you have any weed ?
Okay, now I'm really worried.
There's no need to worry.
I'll bring by the papers tomorrow.
It's strange.
This should be difficult,
but a sense of peace
is settling over me.
Calm.
Maybe it's the moonlight.
Tom ?
Can I meet you outside ?
Sure.
I'll check in back home.
I need a personal day.
I hope it's a joke.
Just one day.
I think I can prove James is innocent.
I talked to a couple of FBI agents
- who were in Haiti...
- Jesus, Maria.
We're in the middle of a manhunt.
You're down two detectives
and now you want time off ?
No. We can't spare you right now.
This wasn't a request.
I won't be here tomorrow.
I just wanted you to know that.
- Diablo.
- What is this shit, Masuka ?
- Hey, tequila's all the same.
- Not when it's made from pumpkins.
We're not in the same pay grade.
If I lose my job over this, bro,
- I won't have a pay grade.
- It won't happen.
- We all know you're innocent.
- How am I gonna prove it ?
I can't explain the roofies,
the rough sex.
- Rough sex ?
- It was her idea.
Now it's my word against hers.
I'm screwed.
- You have got to fight back.
- Dude, Morgan's right.
You got to man up, get tough.
Love's a battlefield.
Or in your case, a restraining order.
I appreciate you guys doing this,
but you don't have to stay.
Does it ever floor you guys
that we had a killer
right under our noses this whole time ?
I mean, who doesn't see that shit ?
That didn't come out right.
It's all right.
That stuff doesn't bother me anymore.
Next round's on me.
I was wondering when you'd show up.
We need to talk.
Sounds good to me.
I'm making coffee. Do you want one ?
I'm here to ask you respectfully
to drop the charges against Angel.
If Angel molested me,
as the evidence seems to indicate,
then he should face
the consequences. Don't you think ?
It doesn't matter what I think.
But here's what I know.
After tomorrow,
I won't be around anymore,
so there's no end game in this for you.
You're going somewhere ?
It's looking more and more likely.
Where ?
All that matters is that I'll be
out of reach permanently.
Come on !
Tell me. I have a right to know.
You're the one who taught me
to accept the things I can't change.
This is one of those things.
I don't understand
how men can be so stupid.
Not all men.
Yes, every single one of you.
I mean, how could Dexter and Batista
be so easily duped by Lila ?
I took one look at her,
I knew she was a walking nightmare.
That's not stupidity.
It's simply in our DNA.
When a pretty girl smiles and bats
her eyelashes, we're unable to resist.
I'm worried about Batista.
This is so fucked.
I won't let him take the fall for this.
What can you do ?
I was wondering if you might access
those great, big FBI files of yours
and do a search on Miss Lila Tournay.
You see ? Powerless to resist.
Will Adams be pissed off when he sees
you used FBI files for this ?
I certainly hope so.
She has no warrants.
No criminal record.
Nothing with the DMV.
And no social security number.
What about visas
or green cards or whatever ?
Nothing. No records.
That's impossible.
Everyone has a paper trail.
Everyone real.
That sneaky bitch.
She's using an alias.
That would be my guess.
How do I find out Lila's real name ?
I think you know the answer to that.
Cut off her head, look for a label.
There's probably an easier way.
You got something smaller ?
The last time she was in my apartment,
she microwaved some popcorn.
There's definitely gonna be prints
on this.
All right, got it.
Next time, make her a cup of tea.
This is Marlene from accounting.
Hi, Marlene from accounting.
She's also a notary public.
- Good for you.
- I met with a lawyer yesterday.
He helped me prepare a living trust
that gives you control of all my assets
in the event of my death or...
certain other situations.
God. Go away. This is creepy.
My financial planner said
a guy my age should have a will.
- Just a precaution.
- We're all gonna die eventually.
Is this why you were acting so weird
last night ?
- Probably.
- Sign here
and I'll need to see an ID.
Fine.
Thanks for showing up last night
to support Batista.
I am supporting him.
I stopped by Lila's this morning.
And ?
I talked to her.
I don't think she's gonna be a problem.
Yeah, 'cause she certainly
hasn't been one so far.
I'm free tonight, you wanna stop by ?
We'll have beer,
a couple of steaks ?
I wanna talk to you about something.
Sounds good.
So, what am I getting ?
I could use a new TV.
Okay. But that's the one.
Lundy here.
It's lieutenant LaGuerta.
I'm calling you from Haiti.
Lovely this time of year.
I know I'm not your favorite person
in the station right now,
but I really need your help.
How so ?
I just met with Leones,
the travel agent that Doakes saw.
There's nothing new there.
I had two agents question him for hours.
Yet he never told them
about the blood slides.
What does he know
about the blood slides ?
Doakes was looking for a lab
to have them analyzed.
- Why ?
- I don't know why.
If he's our killer,
he'd keep as trophies.
He wouldn't have them analyzed.
And I also have a list
of special-ops missions
that Leones personally knows
Doakes took part in.
Two of them directly conflict
with murders
we know to have been committed
by the Bay Harbor Butcher.
I'm not sure Leones
is our most reliable witness.
No, but...
it's worth looking into, isn't it ?
Yes. Yes, it is.
For starters, why don't you...
brief me on both those missions ?
Give me all the details.
Come on, Cody. Up and over.
Okay, Astor. Up and over.
There we go.
Watch your step.
- Look, a pelican !
- There's a bunch of them, there.
What's that ?
Welcome to the GPS 3000 teletracker.
Previous destinations.
For so long my boat has been a tool
of my dark trade...
A graveyard transport.
I'd almost forgotten it could double
as a pleasure craft.
The thing is, if you catch a whale,
we're probably gonna have
to put it back.
If it's a baby,
we could put it in the bathtub.
I'm not gonna take a bath
with a whale.
Yes, they always use up
all the soap.
It's peaceful out here.
Rita, I've never been
a very good boyfriend.
I wouldn't say that.
I just need you to know that...
you and the kids
are very important to me.
No matter what happens,
I want you to always know that.
Everything's all right.
I just need to take things slow.
- I have a gift for you.
- You don't need to.
I want you to have this.
It's the pink slip to the mini-van.
- I told you we're okay. You don't...
- Please.
Take it for the kids.
It'll keep them safer
than a broken-down convertible.
Thank you.
Very generous.
You're welcome.
I know I've been
taking things slow with us,
but it's not
because I don't have feelings for you.
It's more like I have
too many feelings, and I just wanna
make sure to get it right.
Me too.
That's not exactly taking it slow.
Sorry. I'll never do that again.
Well, don't say never.
I was looking for you.
The boys looked at Lila's prints.
We hit the jackpot.
Her real name is Lila West.
I ran her prints through the AFIS,
which is tied to ICE.
Get this...
Her visa expired two years ago.
- Bad girl.
- I can have her deported.
Not as easy as it sounds.
Miami's swamped with criminal immigrants
and refugees from 3rd world countries.
They'll take priority
over some British girl.
Then I'll deport her myself.
We got him.
Talked to a park-service manager
in the Everglades
who remembers giving Sergeant Doakes
directions 5 days ago.
So you have a tip... not Doakes.
The park manager said our target
was headed into the Everglades
15 miles north of Sunday Bay.
We will have
the son of a bitch in handcuffs
in 24 hours.
I'd like to urge strong caution
in apprehending the suspect.
I'm looking into new intel
that might come...
I got your e-mail about Leones.
He will say anything for a dollar.
I agree we have to be careful
about this,
which is why I'd like some time.
Show a little guts,
for Christ's sakes.
Why don't you show a little respect ?
You wouldn't be closing in on a suspect
if it wasn't for his work.
You know, as much as I enjoy
hearing from the local talent,
I'm really rather busy right now.
I guess you don't need me
to fight your battles anymore.
Maybe you need me to fight yours.
Aren't you a tough one ?
I'm just warming up.
I thought I lived in a shit can.
Officer Morgan, have you come
to inquire about my welfare ?
I want you to leave Miami tonight.
Don't ever come back.
Don't ever contact Angel
or Dexter again.
And...
why would I listen to you ?
Cause I'm a cop.
And you're here on an expired visa.
I know your real name,
and I've contacted Immigration.
Officers will be here any day now.
They'll arrest you and deport you,
and it won't be pretty.
If this is true,
why are you telling me this ?
Because I want you the fuck
out of here now.
Whether you leave on your own
or Immigration hauls your sorry ass away
I don't give a shit. But I don't want
to give you one more day
to fuck with the people I care about.
I want you gone. Tonight.
You don't want to do this.
It's done.
Tonight.
Welcome. Previous destination.
Starting route guidance.
Left turn ahead.
I keep expecting to come to my senses,
but the pressure is lifting
with each step I take.
I've spent a lifetime keeping up
my guard, watching my back,
wearing my mask.
Relief was never in sight
until now.
If anyone deserves to take me
into custody, it's Deb.
But how do I tell her what I am ?
I'm the Bay Harbor Butcher.
Deb, I'm the Bay Harbor Butcher.
Down on the ground, motherfucker.
It's me.
I'm the Bay Harbor Butcher.
I'm him...
the Butcher.
This isn't going to be easy.
I brought extra beer.
We're getting drunk.
Fine with me.
What's the occasion ?
I ran Lila out of town today.
Really ?
Turns out she's here illegally.
You should have seen me, Dex.
I was like an Old-West sheriff.
You're really feeling good.
Fuck, yeah.
I got to say, great timing, Dex,
getting together tonight.
Lately, I was starting to feel like
I had my head pretty far up my ass.
No one blames you.
Your world was turned upside down.
Like mine is now.
For the 1st time
since that Ice-Truck Killer shit,
I feel like I'm back.
New and improved, even.
When all that...
stuff was happening...
With Rudy, I mean...
did you ever consider
doing something drastic ?
Are you kidding ?
All kinds of fucked-up shit
ran through my head.
Thank God I had you.
Really ?
Every time I started to spin
out of control, I had you to grab onto.
Hell, you let me live here
practically forever.
It was tough, though.
I'd have done almost anything to get
out from under the weight of it all.
How'd you finally do it ?
I just...
saw through it.
You know ?
You decide who you are,
who you want to be...
and you hold onto that
and ride it out.
Like an Old-West sheriff.
Brother,
this is worth living for.
Right ?
You are absolutely right.
What did you want
to talk to me about ?
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
So this is me, riding it out.
Harry may have rejected me,
but Deb clearly believes in me,
so why shouldn't I ?
I'm not turning myself in.
This isn't Harry's life.
It's mine.
I made a plan to frame Doakes,
and I'm going to stick with it.
No shit ?
I'm on the way.
They found Doakes'
fucking rental car.
They found...
Really ? His car ?
Did they find Doakes ?
Not yet.
But the search grid's closing in.
We got to get to the station.
Actually I got to make sure
they don't find Doakes in a cage.
Hallelujah.
Hey, I'm in here !
Who's out there ?
Anybody out there ?
Ending route guidance.
Somebody in there ?
You have arrived
at your destination.