Previously on Dexter...
Two treasure hunters made a ghastly
discovery today,
when they found what appears
to be an underwater graveyard
in a crevice off the coast of Miami.
It means there might be
a new mass murderer
way worse than the Ice Truck Killer.
The "Bay Harbor Butcher" ?
That's what the press
is calling him.
Last thing Miami needs
is another serial killer.
13 and counting.
They're so swamped up there
they had to bring an outside talent.
Frank Lundy's a rock star.
The green river killer, the D.C. sniper ?
Tough case, but he broke it.
This is the man who stands
between me and death row.
With your help,
we'll find whoever did this awful thing.
So let's get a jump start
on the Bay Harbor Butcher.
With Doakes tailing me,
my life's been all Jekyll and no Hyde.
Paul kept insisting to me
that you knocked him over the head,
dragged him to his motel
and shut him up with drugs.
I hit Paul to protect you
and the kids.
If there's anything left between us,
you'll answer me this one question
and you will tell me the truth.
Are you an addict ?
Yes, I have an addiction.
My name is Caroline.
- I'm an addict.
- Hi, Caroline.
I started taking pain pills
after my back surgery.
I don't need them for the pain
any more.
Now...
Now, I just need them.
And I need duct tape, 3 or 4 rolls,
running low on
heavy duty trash bags...
Until last time,
I sharpened my knives...
And then, I lost my license,
Tears, now ?
It's very hard to concentrate in here.
How am I supposed
to get any work done ?
My husband says
he's gonna leave me
if I don't stay sober.
But I have to do this for myself.
"No self control, lost everything,"
"trying to stop".
Same whiney story over and over for...
ten minutes...
It feels like 10 hours.
Lortabs, Darvocet...
Percocet,
and anything I could get
my hands on.
Even now...
I'd kill for a Vicodin.
- Lightweight ?
- First hit at narcotics anonymous.
But I don't belong here.
You guys are real addicts.
So, how was the meeting ?
Tell me everything.
It was... interesting, hearing
the same story over and over again.
- Knowing you're not alone.
- Exactly.
- Did you get fortune cookies ?
- Only the ones with the good fortunes.
So did you share or just listen ?
I just wanted to take it all
in my 1st time out.
Think they forgot...
Here they are ! Spring rolls.
What about a sponsor ?
Did you find one ?
I didn't want to rush into anything.
It's an important relationship.
Absolutely.
OK, so, let's see
your newcomer's chip.
My newcomer's chip ? Yeah...
- You did stay until the end, right ?
- Of course I did, right...
till the end.
You're a terrible liar.
I know too much
about 12 steps programs
to be easily conned, Dexter.
I didn't stay till the end-end,
if that's what you mean.
I had some important errands to run.
Important ? But... am I important ?
Are the kids ?
Yes, of course.
You just gonna have to figure out
how important,
'cause if you don't work the program,
and I mean really work it,
I just...
I can't go through this again.
All right, kids. Dinner.
How important are they ?
I'm sure someone with a heart
could answer that question.
Tomorrow. I'll go tomorrow.
I'll stay.
Hold the elevator !
Thanks.
Nice dodge last night,
flooring it through that yellow light.
Were you behind me ?
See you tonight.
... detective will be with you.
How long will we have to...
We will get to all of you.
Take their names, and keep them out
of the bullpen, till we figure this out.
Sue McMillan !
She disappeared 4 years ago.
Who are they ?
Family members of every missing person
for the last decade.
Including some sad, lonely
and presumably single woman
courtesy of Lieutenant Pascal.
It's not her fault.
That reporter's an asshole.
Sergeant ? Hold the rest of them
downstairs. We're out of room, here.
Have you seen Pascal ?
Pascal is just caught
in a cycle of reaction.
She's not co-creating
her own reality.
You know those words
don't mean anything, right ?
Look around you.
She's manifesting negativity.
It's on again.
- Lieutenant ?
- No comment.
Dozens of bodies found
- in that underwater grave site.
- Not dozens.
The boss' sweater melons
look bigger on TV.
The operative word is boss.
Show some respect.
I thought I was.
- One dozen, two dozens ?
- 18 or so.
- Excuse me.
- Have the families been notified ?
We're still trying to identify them.
Our viewers with information
can contact you ?
Yes. Fine.
So police are seeking
any leads that can help them identify
the 18 faceless victims
of the Bay Harbor Butcher.
If you have any information...
Pascal is definitely off her game.
Word is, her fiancé is catching
some strange in the sly.
That'd do it.
The shit stops here.
Give it to me.
Most of these people
won't find answers here.
Chances are good their loved ones
weren't among my chosen few.
May I have your attention, please ?
First of all, I wanna tell you
what a great job
you've all been doing
on this horrific case.
And with the help of the best man hunter
in the FBI, we should have answers soon.
In the meantime,
the daily work of this precinct
must continue to serve the public.
So, we'll be dividing up our resources.
Agent Lundy has requested the following
officers for his joint task force.
Officer Cook !
Landy made me L.F.I.
- L.F.I ?
- Lead Forensics Investigator.
Sorry you got boned but, hey,
no blood spatter.
It sucks to be me.
Actually, it keeps me off
Lundy's radar.
Sergeant Lee.
Detective Ramos...
Officer Panko.
- Detective Batista.
- Yes !
I saw this happening.
And officer Debra Morgan.
Those called'll report directly
to Special Agent Lundy.
But let's not forget
this is on all of us, folks.
Let's keep our eyes
and ears open.
The Ice Truck Killer was an amateur
compared to this guy.
I'd also appreciate it
if your lieutenant would consult with me
before speaking to the press.
I'll rip her a new one,
if I can find her.
Prints, fibers, trace evidence.
No, they won't find anything.
I followed all of Harry's
painstaking preventative measures.
He knew that nothing stays
buried forever.
His code will protect me.
Still, I wish my own sister
weren't hunting me,
makes for an awkward
family dynamic.
So... I'm a fed. My suit proves it.
The other suits here are feds.
But, suit or...
ugly Hawaiian shirt,
no offense,
we're a team.
And our first play is
IDing those bodies.
Once we know who they are, we'll fill in
every detail of their lives.
From their huevos rancheros
to their crème brûlée.
And... get used to food references
because...
I like food.
Mr. Masuka and his team're gathering
DNA, prints and dental records.
The rest of us are going call through
cold cases and missing persons’ files.
Also, I want that crowd out there
interviewed.
Though most of them'll be
a waste of time.
He has negative thinking.
You four, move them out
as quickly as you can.
But be thorough. If we get
even one hit, it'll be worth it.
Everyone else work the files.
Remember,
IDs will lead to a pattern,
which will lead to our man.
When the manhunt is on,
the hunted go shopping.
Not for a new car.
For my next project.
I won't act on it... yet.
I'm still laying low,
Harry would insist on that.
Just getting the research
out of the way.
Someone talked his way
into the homes of two women
and didn't leave
till they were dead.
Ann Cohen, and a month before her,
Lynn Hall.
A certain car dealership
ran credit checks on both women.
Both bought cars elsewhere,
so nobody thought about it twice.
But who requested
those credit checks ?
Roger Hicks.
All I need is some DNA proof.
A cup of coffee should do the trick.
How many kids you got ?
Enough...
I hear you.
When my two came along,
it was bye bye convertible.
Of course,
they're worth it.
Must have taken after their mom.
That they do. Thank God !
Yeah, I tell you
I miss my convertible but...
the truth,
my minivan's got a much nicer ride.
- So, you own one ?
- The same one you're looking at.
I know, whipped, right ?
But my kids love
the twin DVDs. They're crazy
about Sponge Bob. You see ?
- Actually, I do.
- My wife loves the NAV system and all
the safety features,
and when they're happy...
- You're happy.
- That's right.
Except the kids
and the wife don't exist.
And he owns a Beemer,
not to minivan.
Still, he's seemless.
- Impressive.
- It's not flashy, but...
What did flash ever get me ?
Get me pulled over, that's what.
I'm definitely not in the flash.
You gotta sit in the captain chair,
though.
It's like a 747, man.
Manuel, hold up !
Thank you, sir.
So... We should take it out.
- Check out the ride.
- No, I'm just doing research.
OK, you don't want
a big sales pitch, I get that.
Let me at least pull the specs
for you.
Because, truthfully, we have
a hard time keeping these on the lot,
you might wanna grab the test drive
while it's still here.
I think I have all the information
I need to make a decision.
Then, you've seen the Stow&Go
seating system, right ?
I have had everything in here
from a soccer team,
to a freaking deer carcass.
It was an accident, of course.
But I sure was glad
for the ample cargo space.
Not to mention the tainted windows.
I can see
how that might come in handy.
I'll just grab the keys.
I go to stalk a killer
and I end up with a new car...
- How did that happen ?
- New car ?
You're getting married ?
Not that I know of.
So what's with the mommy-mobile ?
I'm...
not sure.
Synthetic...
Even Roger's hair is a lie.
I could learn a thing or two
from this guy.
Who's your daddy ?
Harry Morgan.
Dude, the lead forensics investigator
of the joint task force.
That's who.
- So, you want in on this bitch or not ?
- What bitch ?
The only bitch in town, baby.
The Bay Harbor Butcher.
I got you temporarily assigned.
- You didn't have to.
- Nothing sexy, of course,
just some bone marrow collection
for DNA IDs.
But it'll get you in the tent.
And you gotta see the tent. Amazing !
Say it.
- You're my daddy.
- It sounds weird when you say it.
I haven't been much use,
since he disappeared.
I know I'm supposed to move on...
But...
Here's a picture of him.
He looks...
nice.
Not according to my mother.
Or the police.
He was in and out of jail.
But...
my heart raced whenever I saw him.
I brought his toothbrush.
They say you can get DNA off it.
You can find him with this, right ?
Look, thanks for choosing me
for the task force and all, but...
I'd appreciate
you finding someone else.
- You want off ?
- Just as soon as you can replace me, sir.
This is a chance to solve
a pretty important case.
Most people get into
this line of work to do just that.
I've got cases of my own backing up,
and the precinct's shorthanded with all
this shit, so, if you don't mind...
I'll see what I can do.
In the meantime,
if you could continue the interviews...
Yeah, of course.
Thank you.
Most of them have been underwater
for years, but some...
It's awesome, you can't even tell.
The temperature in the ocean floor
and the airtight bags kept them intact.
I mean a little gelatinous residue
sure, but...
I'd rather remember my old playmates as
they were. Neat, clean little packages.
- I appreciate the favor, Vince, but...
- Actually, you're doing me the favor.
I need your help, buddy.
The pressure's fucking ridonkulous.
Glad to be of service.
Field morgue, for the overflow,
but it's state of the art.
Fucking FBI, hey ?
A good percentage is just bones,
Must have fed the fish
when the bags tore.
Humpty fucking Dumpty, right ?
Exactly.
They weren't meant
to be put together again.
They were meant to remain
in the silent shadows,
keeping their secrets.
Now, they're exposed to the glare,
reflecting my darkness
like some grotesque carnival mirror.
Harry was right.
Nothing stays buried.
Perhaps, not even me.
Looking for my Taurus, Sergeant ?
Keep looking.
You don't need to know
where I'm going tonight.
... and, genius me,
not only do I leave my works
in my girlfriend's car,
but also all the dead fish
from the fishing trip, right ?
Then I collapse
in her parents' house,
scare her kids, and get myself
fired, 'cause guess what...
We work together.
So now,
I'm 20 day sober,
again,
hoping to make it to 21.
Thanks, Gordon.
This meeting recognizes
lengths of sobriety
with chips.
So...
If there's anyone who'd like
a newcomer's chip...
You've got 3 minutes to share
if you want it.
Really ?
Go ahead.
You among friends.
Well, I...
What's your name ?
Hi, Bob.
And I'm a...
an addict.
I use...
heroine.
Shoot it.
It's affecting my job.
My boss found my works. He fired my ass.
But I showed him. I spent every penny
on my final paycheck on junk.
And doctor said I...
I almost died.
Coffee sucks.
As bad as the doughnuts.
It's better next door. Come on.
It is good coffee. Thank you.
So tell me...
exactly...
how full of shit are you ?
I'm not full of anything.
It was a nice performance in there.
Where did you download it ?
From Addict.com ?
Look, I have no reason to lie.
Sure you do.
We all do.
- You thought I was lying ?
- I don't know...
Well, it is anonymous.
Everyone in that room,
has heard or lived
far worse
than anything you've ever done.
I doubt it.
So, you're super-junky.
I don't mean to imply that what you've
been through hasn't been difficult.
But there is no way that I could know
what you've experienced, right ?
I couldn't possibly
feel that need.
Like a thousand hiding voices
whispering...
"This is who you are..."
And you fight the pressure.
The growing need rising like a wave.
Prickling and teasing
and prodding...
to be fed.
But the whispering gets louder,
until it's screaming "Now !".
And it's the only voice
you hear.
The only voice you want to hear.
And you belong to her.
To this...
shadow self.
Dark passenger.
The dark passenger.
I'm sorry, but...
I need to go.
Thanks for the coffee.
She knows.
She recognizes demons,
dark passengers...
Maybe the others can too.
This program is too risky.
Especially now.
Rita will have to understand.
You just missed story time.
I was at a meeting.
Thank you.
It made me realize
something important.
Really ? What's that ?
Those meetings
are not a good place for me.
I know how this sounds,
but I can do this on my own.
- You need a program.
- I've read studies,
people are ten times as likely
to change on their own as they are
- with the help of doctors or programs.
- So, you're quoting studies ?
I lived this.
I watched Paul try and fail
with white-knuckle sobriety.
I'm not Paul.
I'm not any of those people.
Going to those meetings, will do
more arm than good. I swear to you.
I'm better off, alone.
I pray you change your mind.
What just happened ?
I though you were staying at Rita's.
I'm taking the night off.
I though you'd be on the treadmill.
Taking the night off.
With no money down, guaranteed,
or we'll make your first two payments...
A night off is good
to remember what's important.
Two women are dead.
The killer is selling minivans
and I have an opportunity to prove it.
Even if I am laying low.
Having a victim prepped and ready
will take the edge off the wait...
I hope.
Hang on a second, OK ?
What's going on, Dex ?
Any problems, the service center
can take care of you,
- but they're around the corner.
- Actually, the minivan's fine.
Yes, I'd never sell a lemon.
- I'm rethinking the extended warranty.
- I'll ask the warranty writer.
I'm thinking roof rack
and premium sound system.
Going all out.
That's great.
But I'm with a customer and so...
One of my associates
will take care of you.
I'll just wait for you
in your office.
DNA, DNA, come out and play.
Roger's got you in a box. Once you're in
a box you don't leave without a deal.
Don't worry, you're safe with Roger,
he's the best.
I'm just dropping off
this thank you note.
I was just leaving.
He sent you across the street,
didn't he ?
- Across the street ?
- he told me not to tell anyone too.
I don't know how he makes a living
sending all of his commissions
to other dealers.
Maybe he has ulterior motives.
Or maybe he knows
I can't afford this price.
After he ran a credit check ?
TRW doesn't lie.
So, you're single ?
Makes it tougher to afford
those big ticket items like cars...
houses. You rent an apartment ?
A house. I hate sharing walls,
you hear everything.
Tell me about it.
No pets though, right ?
Is this a come-on ?
'Cause it's a little weird.
Must be why I'm still single.
Another brunette.
Single, neighbors out of distance.
No guard dog.
The credit check gives Roger
all the details he needs.
She's next.
And I can't do anything about it.
Not until this manhunt ends.
Harry would insist on it.
What ?
I'll take care of it.
I know the card is in his name.
I just wanna check the charges.
Well this supervisor I spoke with
this morning allowed it.
Yeah, I'll hold. Yes ?
Just to remind you that the Biscayne
drive-by warrant needs your approval.
I'll look at it.
And the homicide
that came in last night
still need to be assigned.
Right. Thanks.
I know things are awful with your fiancé
right know, and I'm sorry.
But we need to keep
clearing that board out there.
You're right, I'm sorry.
I seem to have had
my head up my ass, lately.
It's called being human.
OK, who's up ?
- Samuels and Kent are up.
- Put them on the liquor store shooting.
And where is the Biscayne warrant ?
Right here.
Simps and Hoagy
want SWAT for entry ?
I think it's a good cautionary
measure given the weapon charge.
Excuse me, I'm gonna need a minute.
Just gonna need a minute.
I'll handle it.
You're not taking my calls
and now you're checking
my credit card charges ?
Roger's DNA matches
the semen found at both crime scenes.
Irrefutable.
If I do nothing,
another woman dies.
Is that my long-dormant
conscience talking ?
Or the dark passenger whispering ?
Hi, it's me.
Hi, Dexter.
Kids home from school yet ?
Colleen's bringing them home now.
I'm a...
little confused.
I'm sorry you're confused.
It is pizza night,
shall I pick up the usual ?
Did you go back ?
To a meeting ? Thinking about it.
The kids and I will order in, then.
So...
This is it ?
It's up to you, Dexter.
I want to know where is she.
Mí Teresita, she's so young.
Seven-year old.
You heard me.
- I know you find her.
- We'll do what we can.
Don't cry.
Only English. Angel !
Just tell her we'll call her.
She thinks you can find
her daughter.
But there are no kids down there.
Tell her I can't help her.
I can't help you.
It's been 24 hours
since I asked to be replaced.
Has it ?
What's taking so long ?
Every cop on the damn force wants in
on this case, just take your pick.
I've been wondering about that,
actually.
Everyone wants on but
you want off.
I told you I've cases.
I don't think so.
Jesus, I just don't wanna be
on your task force, alright ?
Why ?
Because I'm the last person
in the world that should be on it.
You want me to find a serial killer ?
I was engaged to one, for Christ's sake !
What kind of cop...
- What kind...
- That's why I chose you, you know.
Because of what you went through.
You survived.
I don't know how.
I can't begin to imagine
the strength it took,
continues to take.
More than that,
you got a first-hand look
into the mind and heart of a killer.
And you're still here.
If you can accept that,
really accept it,
you could use it.
Mix that
with some of your strength and...
you could catch someone
even worse than the Ice-Truck Killer.
But you have to stop running.
Finish today's interviews.
Then if you still want out,
you got it.
Lead fucking investigator.
Translation: everyone's bitch.
I do have a life, you know.
You do ?
Just give me a bone marrow
DNA results.
No matches.
Big surprise.
Do me a favor
on your way out, OK ?
Drop these dental X-rays at the morgue
for me. Tech should still be there.
Fucking Bay Harbor butcher's
butchering my online social life.
Sorry.
I figured you'd still be here.
You were a pain in the ass,
but always a damn hard worker.
And of course,
you knew how to handle the press.
Come here a minute.
The public needs to believe that we can
protect them when all hell breaks loose,
so I need all my people
operating at their highest levels.
I agree.
Should I be worried about Pascal ?
Why ?
You can cut the crap, Maria.
I know she's been AWOL
on personal matters.
The press fuck up is huge.
And I'm beginning to hear rumors
about erratic behavior.
- You're asking me because ?
- Because you've done the job.
So she is out,
that means you're back in.
That makes you her harshest critic
and I want it straight.
Take your shot.
You know what "erratic" means ?
It's code, for non male.
This is the same bullshit sexism
I put up with when I was in charge.
I won't dignify rumors, captain.
Pascal's fine.
Minivan's that way.
Field morgue's this way.
I'll wait.
You should take the night off,
sergeant.
On pizza night ? No way.
What's that girlfriend of yours
seeing in a freakshow like you anyway ?
- You have to ask her.
- Maybe I will.
What exactly is it
you think I've done ?
I know you're connected
to the Ice-Truck Killer.
- Could you be more vague ?
- I know you're too careful.
Your assets are all in cash,
you don't belong to any organizations
or alumni groups.
You were top of your class in med school
but you changed for blood spatter.
I know you studied martial arts
in college.
But I don't know what a lab geek needs
with advanced Jiu-Jitsu.
Do you know what an easy credit is ?
I know you're a good liar too.
Not good enough.
Sergeant Doakes
thinks he knows my secrets.
But he only needs to look at this,
my body of work,
- to know the real me.
- Suit up if you gonna touch them.
I'm just dropping off some X-rays.
- I'm Dexter Morgan.
- I know who you are.
Right.
Looks like the lab tech's gone home
for the night, so I'll just...
You hoping they'll talk to you ?
The ones with heads, anyway.
They always speak, eventually.
Just gotta ask the right question.
Which is ?
Why were they chosen ?
Looking for a pattern ?
One doesn't kill
this many people in this...
careful, methodical way
without a reason.
Some... twisted set of principles.
They would have to be twisted,
wouldn't they ?
The worst killers
are usually the ones
who think their murders
were somehow... just.
Even deserved.
Leaders have slaughtered whole
populations for the same wacky reason.
But there's never any justification
for killing.
Well, one, of course.
To save an innocent life.
How many more bodies would there be,
had I not stopped those killers ?
I didn't do it to save lives.
But save lives, I did.
Motivation aside,
I think Harry and Lundy
would agree on this one.
Roger the artful dodger.
You scared me, bro.
We have some unfinished business.
Right, the warranty and stuff.
Listen, I can't write you up now,
the wife's waiting for me.
Not married.
- Ex, I gotta take the kids.
- You don't have any.
- They're hers.
- Nope.
OK, what about this one ?
I don't give a shit !
Neither do I.
You were right
about the ample cargo space.
Where am I ?
Looks different under plastic
but you've spent an evening here.
With Ann Cohen.
You took her last breath from her right
over there, you remember ?
You're wrong, I wouldn't !
No, you would, and you did
and you're about to do it again,
that's why we're here.
No, this is crazy.
You've got the wrong guy, I...
I sell cars, for God's sake.
I've never hurt anyone in my life,
definitely not a woman.
- Why can't I do that ?
- Do what ?
Lie like that.
When I thought I was good,
but you, it's...
I don't lie !
OK, that one was weak.
Hey, look.
Any car in the lot, it's yours.
T- bird, town car, you name it.
Yours. Free. I'll call it in right now.
- Lot's closed.
- I'll have it opened. I'm the manager.
- The manager is Rick Boxton.
- But I've been there longer than him.
- You've been there 3 months.
- At the other lot.
It's like watching
someone ski moguls.
You just hop from one lie to the next,
no shame, no embarrassment, you just
don't give a shit.
That's the key, right ?
Not to care about anyone
- or anything.
- I care.
- I care a lot.
- It was a compliment.
- I don't care either.
- Yes, you do.
- Like about your wife.
- Not married.
Girlfriend, then.
I saw it the minute
you walked on the lot.
What did you see ? Tell me.
Most guys of your age,
they beeline...
Right through the horse power.
You know, something flashy, sexy.
But you, you there all alone,
no one there to nag you,
and you don't even glance
at the coupes.
The only thing you look at
is the minivan.
Like you can see her
in the passenger seat,
- and the kids in the back.
- Leave the kids out.
You're lying to yourself
if you think you don't care.
She's just a companion really.
It started that way, anyway.
Someone who...
looked good, normal.
- They worm their way in.
- Yeah, they do.
And they shut you out.
That's what this is about ?
That she shut you out ?
OK, I get it.
I've been there.
But you can't let her
get to you like this.
'cause they're all the same.
Fucking bitches.
You do everything for them, and then
they fuck you. She's not worth it !
You're better off
without that cunt !
Don't talk that way
about my girlfriend.
I'm Dexter.
and...
- I'm not sure of what I am.
- Hi, Dexter.
I just know there is something dark
in me.
And I hide it.
I certainly don't talk about it.
It's there,
always.
This dark passenger.
And when he's driving, I feel...
Alive.
Half sick with the thrill,
the complete wrongness...
I don't fight him. I don't want to.
He's all I've got.
Nothing else could love me.
Not even...
especially not me.
Or is that just a lie
the dark passenger tells me ?
Because lately, there are
these moments when I feel
connected,
to something else.
Someone.
It's like
the mask is slipping.
Things,
people,
who never mattered before
are suddenly starting to matter.
It scares the hell out of me.
Hello.
That's all the time we have
for sharing.
Would someone lead us
in the serenity prayer ?
I knew there was
something wrong with you.
The secrets, the sneaking around...
Now it all makes sense.
A lot of cops been where you are.
The booze, the drugs.
It makes the job go down easier.
Stay clean and stay out of my way.
And we won't have a problem.
And you owe me a new Michelin,
you motherfucker.
I have all your forms so we'll do
what we can to bring your dad home.
I'm sorry, you don't understand.
I don't want him home.
Just tell me he's dead.
We need to know he's gone.
Alright. You want closure.
I want peace.
He made our lives a living hell.
When he'd go to prison,
it was a blessing, but...
you kept letting him out.
I need to tell my mother,
my sister that they're safe.
That he's rotting in hell.
Call me when you can tell me that.
Lundy, wait !
I think...
it could be a coincidence but,
there are 2 of them.
Two ?
Missing people with records,
prison records.
Interesting.
And who typically
has a prison record ?
I don't know.
Bad guys ?
Bad guys.
- Do you think it could be...
- A pattern ? Maybe.
We'll run all the victims' DNA
against the criminal database.
DC lab is still open.
Come on. Let's get to work.
Dexter, what ?
You were right. I'm sorry...
to wake you up, but I had
to let you know that you were right.
- About what ?
- The program...
It's...
It's good, it's really good.
I...
am always so in my head.
But this, it was...
good.
In fact it's already helped me
a lot.
Thank you.
I do love this car.
I thought you might.
So, I will pick you up in an hour.
We'll go some place nice for lunch.
- Here's my sponsor.
- Really ? Where ?
The guy in the blue shirt ?
No, next to him. Laila.
I'm back.