[Karadec] Four-King-82
in pursuit of a white sedan.
License 6, Frank,
Charlie, Indigo, 9-4-0.
Heading south on Vine.
Requesting air support
and backup.
Suspect's name is Derek Price.
He is armed and dangerous.
[♪ "Los Angeles" playing]
♪ How can anybody have you?
How can anybody have you
And lose you? ♪
♪ How can anybody have you
And lose you
And not lose their minds too? ♪
♪ How can anybody have you?
How can anybody have you
And lose you? ♪
♪ How can anybody have you
And lose you
And not lose their minds too? ♪
♪ How can anybody have you?
How can anybody have you
And lose you? ♪
♪ How can anybody have you
And lose you
And not lose their minds? ♪
[Morgan] Please have good news.
I lost Derek. [sighs]
What about the weapon?
-He took it with him.
-[Selena] Damn it.
We need you back here
right now.
Why? What's going on?
You got a lead
on the Game Maker?
Uh, yeah, we sure do.
He just walked in.
[Karadec] He did what?
♪ How can anybody have you? ♪
♪ How can anybody have you
And lose you? ♪
And lose you
And not lose their minds ♪
[Karadec]
He really just walked in here?
[Selena] He says he heard his
face was on the news last week,
wants to know why.
[Karadec] Who is he?
"Matthew Clark."
-He got a record?
-Squeaky-clean.
Lives downtown, has for a year,
works cash jobs.
[Karadec] Cash jobs.
Makes it hard to track
his money or his movements.
What about family?
His mom did time
for grand theft, but she died
when he was a kid.
So basically, you're saying
there's not much to tie him
either to Maya Price
or the others he abducted.
No, he wouldn't have
walked in here
unless he knew he was gonna be
able to walk out.
-Let me talk to him.
-No, Adam will talk to him.
We all know he came here
to talk to me.
And we can't give him
what he wants, Morgan.
-I can handle it.
-No coloring outside the lines.
We need more on this guy
other than the fact
that he is an organ donor.
Still nothing from Daphne
or Oz?
No, not yet.
-[sighs]
-Anything?
Front desk says
a Roman Sinquerra checked in
last week,
just like our friends here
in Henderson told us.
Okay,
so we're in the right place.
Roman is here.
Or was.
Maybe he forgot to check out
before he left.
I usually do.
Hey.
[sighs] Thanks
for coming in today, Matthew.
-You understand your rights.
-I do.
And I've got nothing to hide,
so why was my face on the news?
[Karadec] Spencer Wallace.
Sierra Shuman.
And Lev Ozdil.
All three were abducted
last week...
Yeah. That's...
That's terrible.
...by a man
matching your description.
Really? Mmm.
Uh, they all look so sad.
-He's toying with us.
-Let him try.
Well, they're all members
of the same grief group,
meets once a month out
in Echo Park.
You know the one.
The one you attended.
Sounds like you think
I did this, Detective.
I think when we bring
these people in here,
they'll identify you.
From a grief group.
I'm sorry, Detective,
I think you lost me.
Come on. What is Karadec doing?
-Is this an interrogation
or a first date?
-Give him time.
Matthew Clark came in freely
of his own free will.
We push too hard and he leaves,
we could lose the only chance
we have to find out
what really happened to...
[Karadec] Maya Price.
Is this woman saying
I abducted her too?
Mm-mmm. We're still trying
to locate her.
Maya disappeared
two nights ago.
So it sounds like she's not
saying much of anything.
-Hmm.
-He's taunting us.
-[typing on phone]
-Morgan,
let Karadec do his job.
[phone buzzes]
Where were you last night
around 9:00 p.m?
I was at home reading a book.
Why?
Because my colleague saw you
at a party in the Bird Streets.
Did she?
"She." Did you hear that?
He said, "she." Karadec didn't
specify a gender.
We're gonna need more than
a pronoun to press charges.
[Matthew] Detective,
I do have one of those faces.
[sighs]
Tell me,
how do you know David Roy Peck?
I wish I could be more helpful,
Detective, but I don't know
anyone by that name.
-Morgan, that's enough.
-He's lying.
Is that your wife?
[gasps]
A little something on the side.
Is this fun for you?
Playing games
with people's lives?
Whoever's texting,
it must be very urgent.
Are you in a love triangle,
Detective?
I understand that badge
can be very persuasive.
[Karadec sighs]
-Wait here.
-I'd love a snack.
Uh, cookie. Anything Pillsbury.
-Really, Morgan?
-Yeah, Adam.
Knock it off.
This guy has you both
exactly where he wants you.
I'm sorry, uh,
there's a mother missing,
and this bozo's in here
asking for cookies.
He can ask
for whatever he wants.
It doesn't mean
we're gonna give it to him.
Hold on a second.
He didn't ask for just cookies.
He asked specifically
for Pillsbury.
What is that,
some kind of clue?
The Pillsbury variation.
In chess, it's a variation
of the Queen's Gambit Declined.
A move in which Black
declines White's temporary
pawn sacrifice
to establish a solid position.
It's basically
an elaborate chess move
to secure your defense.
What the hell does that mean?
It means we have to decline
the temporary sacrifice.
We've got to release
Jason Howard.
Whoa, whoa, Morgan,
you do realize Derek is
still out there.
I know,
and Maya's still out there too,
and the only way
to get her back
is to play this game.
We don't have enough evidence
to hold Jason Howard
much longer anyway.
Adam and I will go talk
to Jason while we keep Matthew
on ice.
-Okay, I'll keep an eye on him.
-From which side of the glass?
Oh, so you do know
how to interrogate people.
[scoffs]
[door closes]
So you no longer believe that
my client killed Maya Price?
Not anymore, no.
But now you're saying that
someone else wants to kill me
because they think
that I killed Maya.
Yes, that's right.
Her ex, Derek Price.
Right. Uh, so why?
Jason,
do you recognize this man?
Matthew Clark.
-Nope.
-[Selena]
We're questioning him now.
We suspect he fed Derek
some false information
so that he'd believe you killed
Maya and try to get revenge.
Revenge. Wow, this is insane.
Okay, well, where's this Derek
who wants to kill me?
We don't know.
We're searching for him now.
-Nice.
-[Selena] And Maya.
Until we find both, we need
to offer you police protection.
-What are you proposing?
-Three officers
outside the home.
They can secure the perimeter
and make sure that Derek
never comes near you,
or you're welcome to stay here.
No, no, no. I'll go home.
[stammers] What about Maya?
You think she's alive?
We hope so. [sighs] We think
she might just be a pawn.
A pawn. In what?
A game that ends in a murder
he could never be charged for.
Oh, my murder.
My murder. Right.
[phone buzzes]
-Is everything okay?
-Everyone here is doing great.
Hey, Mom.
And Elliot wants to say
something to you, so I'm gonna
hand him the phone now.
Hi, okay, so the school
talent show is tomorrow,
and I wasn't going to do it,
but a kid got pink eye,
so a spot opened up,
and I really want it,
but I know we're not really
supposed to leave the house
just because that man Dad said
is stalking us.
Buddy, you want to do
a talent show, you're gonna do
that talent show.
Why don't we just invite
Officer Chester?
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
So what are you gonna do?
Uh, that's a surprise.
But it's super cool. And I know
you're gonna love it.
- Can you put your dad on?
-Yeah.
I can't tell you what Elliot's
doing for the talent show.
I'm sorry.
What do you mean
you can't tell me?
Elliot swore me to secrecy.
Ludo, the kid
gets bullied enough at school.
Now he wants to go up on stage
in front of everyone
and do something
that he considers cool?
"Beowulf" by Anonymous.
-[student] Dork!
-"Lo! the Spear-Danes"--
-[student 2] You suck!
-Mom!
He's gonna get eaten alive.
He's going to be fine.
I'm going to help him.
You? No.
Why would you help him?
You're not...
You're not the one.
-Hey, are you doing okay?
-[Matthew] Hello?
I'll call you back
as soon as I can.
[Matthew] Hello?
Is anyone there?
I've never been
in one of these rooms before.
I remember hearing about people
who would confess
to things they didn't do.
I never understood why.
But now that I'm here,
I get it.
These concrete walls.
The glass.
I only got in trouble once
when I was a kid.
Some friends and I
were playing chicken.
We were biking
right toward each other.
Don't blink.
You swerve, you lose.
Hmm.
-[door opens]
-[Selena] Morgan, you gotta go.
We heard about a bomb threat
on a Metro bus.
-What about this guy?
-We believe the threat was him.
Someone on the bus heard it
ticking and called 9-1-1.
-Anyone see who left the bag?
-No.
-And the cameras
on the bus were broken.
-Where's the bomb?
There wasn't one. [sighs]
It's just a timer
with a thumb drive
taped to the back.
I recognized your woman.
♪ I feel fine and I feel good ♪
♪ I feel like
I never should... ♪
She's singing
"Bizarre Love Triangle"
by New Order.
That's why Matthew Clark
mentioned a love triangle
in his interrogation.
-When was this video recorded?
-Wish I could tell you.
Whoever made the video wiped
all the metadata.
Okay. That means
even after we find Derek,
we can't use this video
to prove to him
that Maya's still alive.
It gets weirder.
The bag tested positive
for ammonium nitrate,
a chemical used in bomb making.
Okay, so he wants us to know
there is a bomb.
It's just not here.
And we have less than
two hours to stop it.
[Morgan] "Helen of Monaco."
I don't recognize that brand.
It's a brand-new bag.
What's with this loose thread?
You think
that means something?
Everything means something
with him.
[Morgan] Oh, my God.
We need to know when
this bus started its route,
because if it was after Matthew
walked into our precinct,
he just gave himself
the best alibi ever.
Yeah, the entire Los Angeles
Police Department.
Roman Sinquerra.
We're Detectives Ozdil
and Forrester with the LAPD.
-What, you guys lost?
-No.
No, we just want to talk to you
for a minute.
I gotta be somewhere.
[Morgan] What am I missing?
There's got to be
something here.
Yeah, well, I hope
you're right, 'cause we're
running out of time.
I had the techs put a rush
on that bag.
The only DNA they're gonna find
on that bag is
from whoever Matthew paid
to drop it on the bus,
and I doubt he showed them
his face.
Lieutenant must still be in
with him.
Here.
-[phone buzzing]
-It's Oz.
[sighs]
Hey, any news?
We found Roman.
He wouldn't talk with us,
so we're tailing him now.
There he goes.
[Oz]
I'm sending you a photo now.
[phone buzzes]
That's not Roman.
[Daphne] Are you sure?
Got a fairly decent look
at the guy
when we had a child together.
So, yeah, pretty sure.
I've never seen that man before
in my life.
Okay, then we need to find out
who he is
and why he's using Roman's name
out here in Nevada.
Thank you.
-[Daphne] Yeah, we got you.
-[Oz] How's that other thing?
Oh, you mean catching the guy
who tried to drown
my favorite coworker?
You heard me, Daphne.
-I get it.
-Just be careful.
You too.
Gotta go. [grunts]
-[exhales sharply]
-Hey, you good?
[sighs] Good enough.
What more do you want me
to say?
You could start
with a solid alibi.
I can't be the only person
in this city who stays
at home to read.
Only one suspected
of abducting four people,
including one of my own.
Go ahead,
check my bank accounts, my car.
Hell, you can search
my apartment.
You consent to a warrantless
search of your place?
Knock yourselves out.
I've got nothing to hide.
He wouldn't let us
in that apartment if there
wasn't something to find.
We checked the units above,
below and on either side.
No trace of any explosives.
You're good to go.
[Morgan] Come on.
What's this man trying
to tell me?
[Karadec]
That he likes monkeys.
Morgan, we gotta hustle.
Less than an hour
before a bomb might go off,
and we still have no idea
where Maya is.
So far all we've learned
about Matthew Clark
is he volunteers
at the local hospital.
-He said he was reading
last night, right?
-Yeah, not the best alibi.
So maybe it wasn't an alibi.
Maybe it's a clue.
This one's upside down.
It's about the man
who saved the world,
Stanislav Petrov.
Please give me
the shortest possible version.
Petrov was a Soviet colonel
during the Cold War.
-[siren wailing]
-Was in charge
of a nuclear warning system
that falsely recorded a missile
launched by the United States.
[Petrov breathing heavily]
[panting]
If Petrov had reported
the alert, it would have
started that nuclear war.
Okay, I get it.
He's sending us a message,
but I mean, it's not exactly
a crime to improperly
shelve your books.
What does that mean?
I'm saying we have to let
Matthew go and keep searching
for Maya and Derek.
-What? Are you insane?
-Morgan,
we don't have any evidence.
No, it's not a game anymore.
This is about escalation.
He's telling us this is war.
-[sighs]
-[camera shutter clicks]
Until one of us blinks.
Let me see that video
of Maya again.
-What, you think
we missed something?
-Yeah, pull up Maya's video.
-Okay.
-[Maya singing
"Bizarre Love Triangle"]
Yes, look at her eyes.
They're blinking like crazy.
In the Vietnam War,
a US naval officer
was captured,
and they made him send home
a video message
saying that he
and his fellow prisoners
were doing just fine.
They were being treated fairly,
right?
I have adequate food.
Only the whole time,
his eyeballs were going nuts.
And I receive medical care
when I require it.
♪ Why can't we be ourselves
Like we were yesterday? ♪
-It's Morse code.
Yeah, not letters.
These are numbers.
See, 2492.
-She's repeating 2492.
-2492 Blue Jay Way.
That's Jason's address
in the Bird Streets.
So Maya's telling us
to go there,
but we already conducted
a sweep of Jason's house.
Even if she was there
when they recorded this video,
she's certainly not there now.
So maybe the message isn't
from Maya.
♪ I feel fine and I feel... ♪
[Morgan]
I think he's sending us this.
♪ I feel like I never should ♪
But that just feels
really sloppy, right? Like,
why-why have us double back?
[sighs] Well,
he was there at Jason's party,
maybe he left something there
for us to find.
If so, we got to find it fast.
Come on. Clock's ticking.
[Morgan]
I'm not cleaning that up.
I hope you found
what you were looking for.
[siren blares]
According to
the stopwatch he left,
we have less than a minute.
I'm telling you this doesn't
feel right. Why would he
send us back here?
What?
Do I need my lawyer for this?
No, we just need
to look around.
-For what?
-We don't know.
You need to search my place,
but you don't know
what you need to look for?
Listen, we might find
something here that can help us
find Maya, okay?
Look, I'm not trying
to be difficult, but in terms
of my own comfort--
Hey, bud, we're in a bit
of a time crunch here,
so help us help you.
-Time's up.
-What?
[timer ticking]
[Morgan screams]
[Jason]
You've got to be kidding me.
That bomb was in one
of your cars, Lieutenant.
And until we know more,
you're still safer with us.
Believe me.
How are you going
to protect me? You can't even
protect yourselves.
[scoffs] Let's go.
Where the hell's he going?
Jason Howard just hired
his own private security.
Look, I don't blame him.
We're lucky no one was
inside that car.
Yeah, we're lucky.
I'm feeling super lucky.
Morgan, do you need more time?
I don't need time.
I need us to get this guy.
[grunts]
How the hell did this happen?
Well, apparently,
he put a bomb on Karadec's car
the day of the party.
But why come after us?
He's never targeted
the police before.
The message wasn't for us.
The message was for Jason.
Matthew Clark needed my car to
blow up outside Jason's house
so he'd stop letting us
protect him.
And we still have no idea
where Derek is.
[sighs]
Yeah, or how to find Maya.
Adam, contact Jason's lawyer,
see if she'll listen to reason,
even if he won't.
I'll get an update on Derek.
And, Morgan,
I want you to go home.
-Check on your family now
while you can.
-Lieutenant--
We have no witnesses,
no evidence, no leads.
The minute we do,
you'll hear from me.
Go home, get some rest.
Looks like it's gonna
be a long night anyway.
Go, go, go.
Hey, sorry about before.
Why don't you let us give you
a ride back to LA, huh?
I never told you
where I was going.
-Your jacket did.
-Yeah, I like blue.
Look, we know you're not
Roman Sinquerra,
so why don't you tell us
why you're using his name?
Well, that depends.
Did they start letting LAPD
make arrests out of state?
-We just want to talk.
That's it.
-Right.
Have a nice drive home,
Detectives.
Morgan Gillory sent us.
Sorry. Never heard of him.
What happened to the chips?
Oh. What a beautiful greeting.
-Where's Ludo?
-Elliot's room. [sighs]
They still practicing
for the talent show?
Mm-hmm.
I tried to talk some sense
into both of them, but...
-Do you know what he's doing?
-No, uh-uh.
Did you try listening
at the door?
Yeah, but all I heard
was Elliot pushing back
on creative differences.
Okay. All right, well,
I guess we'll see tomorrow.
-Mm-mmm. No, I'm not going.
-Yeah, you're going.
-No, no, no. Not going.
-Uh-huh. Mm-hmm.
You're gonna be there, you're
gonna support your brother,
and you're gonna support
your mom.
This is gonna be
quite a challenge for me.
Yeah, no kidding.
Might be the greatest
social train wreck
in school history.
Oh, boy.
[knocks on door]
[laptop beeping, chiming]
-Hey, Mom.
-Perfect timing.
El and I were
just about to take five.
-Mind if I jump in?
-He's all yours.
Wow.
You guys rehearsing some sort
of a Tasmanian Devil routine?
Tasmanian devils are often
depicted as hyperactive
and aggressive,
but they're actually pretty shy
and solitary animals,
except when feeding or mating.
Yeah, I know.
I was just doing
a little Looney Tunes thing.
-So, you all ready
for tomorrow?
-I will be. [sighs]
Okay.
Well, I can't wait to see it,
whatever it is.
You're worried I'm gonna do
something super nerdy
and get my butt kicked.
Me? No. No, I don't... I don't.
It's okay. I'm worried too.
Are you? Oh, buddy.
I was maybe feeling
a little bit nervous.
You and I are not like
other people, and honestly,
I think that's cool,
but sometimes it can make us
a little bit of a target,
right?
You know what? I'm actually
dealing with a bully
at my work right now.
I think that might be
why I'm feeling
a little overprotective,
but I don't want you
to be scared.
I want you to work really hard
on whatever this is
and go out there tomorrow,
and have fun
and be proud of yourself,
no matter what the reaction is.
I will.
And they might make fun of me,
but sometimes you have to lose
the battle to win the war.
Right. Right.
Maybe I'm not supposed to win.
What do you mean?
The guy at work, he was reading
a book about Stanislav Petrov.
The man who saved the world.
I think he's telling me
to be more like Petrov.
I think the only way
I can beat this guy...
is if I'm willing to lose.
Dad, break's over,
it's getting weird in here!
I think screaming
should be your talent.
-What happened?
-[Morgan] I gotta go.
-Where?
-Play a game of chicken.
What did you say to her?
[knocks on door]
We need to talk.
Come on in.
-This is quite a surprise.
-I doubt that.
Did you find
your missing woman?
No, not yet.
Your friends at the LAPD,
do they know you're here,
Morgan Gillory?
No.
Pool closes at 10:00,
restaurants at 11:00.
Thank you.
[Matthew]
If you really think...
I did...
all of those horrible things,
why would you come here alone?
Because if you wanted me dead,
I already would be.
I think you like this game
as much as I do.
-I think that's why
you're here.
-You're wrong.
[chuckles]
I don't like it.
I'm here to quit.
It's a game of chicken, right?
You knew I was standing
on the other side
of that glass.
You wanted me to know
that you loved
playing this game
when you were a little kid.
Two sides racing
toward each other, if no one
swerves, total annihilation.
I swerve.
I don't believe you.
You don't have to believe me.
I'm just done.
You know where I live.
You know where I buy groceries.
You've proven that you can
get to me and my children.
And I will protect them.
So I have to protect myself
for their sake.
Can you imagine being a little
kid and losing your mom?
I'm not gonna do that to them.
This is my fault.
I put us in danger.
I was trying to prove
that I could do this,
but I can't because you are
smarter than me, so you win.
That's it, it's done.
Just tell me where Maya is.
[phone buzzes]
Your partner's probably
worried about you.
Adam, we just got a hit
on Derek's credit card,
a location on the east side.
-Morgan's not answering.
-We'll keep trying her.
Right now, I need you
to make sure we get to Jason
before Derek does.
Send me the address.
I wish I could help you,
Morgan, but like I said,
I don't know anything
about this missing woman.
What?
That's it? Nothing?
No, no, come on, no, I...
I gave you what you wanted.
I quit, you won.
The game is over.
I really do hope you find her.
[gasps]
Hey, Morgan.
It's an old building.
The elevator's been acting up.
You should probably
play it safe.
Take the stairs.
[Jason] I don't belong
in this situation.
You guys are gonna eat
with me, right?
I feel like I'm in a cage.
-[security]
Stay in the room, sir.
-I need some air.
[Jason] I'll be right there.
Morgan, where are you?
Just checking something out.
You?
Derek just checked into a hotel
on the east side.
We think Jason did too,
but he's not picking up,
so I'm headed over there to try
to find him before Derek does.
-Do you hear that?
-[song playing in distance]
-"Bizarre Love Triangle."
-Where are you?
I'm at Matthew's
apartment building,
third floor.
-Maya. [panting]
-What the hell are you doing
over there?
-Maya!
- Morgan, I'm sending backup.
No, I'm fine.
Go get Jason. Maya!
- Morgan. Morgan, hello?
-Maya!
LAPD.
Hey, Jason and Derek both
checked in a half hour ago.
Morgan? Morgan, talk to me.
Oh, God. That sucks.
[grunting]
[panting]
Hi, yeah, you want...
you wanna help out?
Go get the super or something.
Come on. Maya! [panting]
I know this looks weird, okay?
Don't you call the cops.
I'm on the phone with one.
Maya!
Another?
Oh.
No, another's not gonna help.
I'm on the roof.
[Morgan] Karadec, we're calling
for the super. He has a key.
I've got eyes on Jason.
Don't do it!
Derek! Derek! No! No! No!
LAPD! Guns down!
[Morgan]
Oh, my God. What's going on?
Now.
Derek, I need you
to listen to me, man.
-Okay?
-He killed her.
-[Jason]
I've never killed anybody.
-You sick bastard.
[Jason whimpers]
Maya. [stutters]
I got her right here.
Derek, Maya is alive.
Okay, Maya,
I work with the police,
and Derek
is about to kill someone
who he thinks killed you,
and I need you to tell him
that you're alive. Okay?
-Why do you lie to me?
-[Maya] Derek!
-He killed her.
-[Maya] Derek, Derek, I'm okay.
I'll never see her again
and I'll never be able
to make it up to her. [cries]
Morgan, I need you to keep her
talking, personal details,
whatever it takes.
Make him believe it.
[stammering] Derek, we were...
We were married
in Santa Barbara and...
and we always... We never took
a honeymoon, but we always said
we were going to.
And-And Max when he was born,
-we barely made it
to the hospital...
-Maya?
...and he was eight pounds
and seven ounces.
And I want you to see him
again, Derek. [sobbing]
It's her.
Sorry.
I'm sorry. Okay.
I'm sor-sorry. It was...
[pants] You did it.
You did it. It's okay.
-Is Max okay?
-Yes, he's fine.
-He's okay. It's okay.
-[cries]
It's okay.
It's okay. [panting]
-Someone's here to see you.
-[Max] Mom!
-I missed you so much, baby.
-I missed you too.
[mouthing words] Thank you.
DA still doesn't think
there's enough evidence
to arrest Matthew
for Maya's abduction.
What are you talking about?
We found her
in his apartment building.
Yeah, well, the landlord says
the apartment's been vacant
for weeks
and CSU still hasn't found
anything yet.
And since Maya didn't see
the man who abducted her...
Then we are right back
where we started.
Hey, don't worry,
he'll see the inside
of a prison cell soon.
I don't think so.
[sighs]
Do you remember the photograph
of the monkey we found
in his apartment?
It's a tarsier monkey.
I think he hung it up
on the wall as a reminder.
A reminder of what?
Tarsier monkeys refuse
to be taken into captivity.
The second they get inside
of a cage,
they get so stressed out that
they start to self-mutilate
and try and kill themselves.
You're saying
he won't be taken alive.
Hey, look who's back.
Sorry, we didn't bring you
a souvenir from Vegas.
I'm sorry
we didn't catch the guy.
It's all right.
[sighs] Secretly hoping to put
the cuffs on him myself.
Hey, guys, take a look at this.
Maya's medical records
just came in.
No broken bones, no bruises,
no drugs in her system.
How do you abduct someone
without leaving a scratch?
The blood in the trunk
matched Maya's,
and she didn't have any cuts.
How's it possible?
Because the blood
didn't leave Maya's body
within the last 48 hours.
What are you thinking?
[knocks on door]
You're back. Please.
To what do I owe this pleasure?
Oh, you know, I just...
I was reading about your mom.
Oh.
Yeah, she worked at a hotel
in Bel Air, is that right?
Up until the point
where she was accused
of stealing by a guest.
-My mom never stole anything.
-Oh.
But in her file,
it's pretty clear
she confessed.
It was a forced confession.
But she still died in jail,
right?
Left you bouncing around from
family member to family member,
just being a lonely kid
with nobody to play with.
[chuckles]
See, I don't think you ever
meant to hurt Maya at all.
I think you were just trying
to get my attention,
but you did need for Derek
to think that Maya was dead.
[Matthew, distorted]
This is the LAPD.
It's about Maya.
'Cause he needed to be
mad enough to go kill Jason.
Thus the blood.
[chuckles]
-I don't understand.
-Yeah, that happens a lot.
Let me help you.
Maya's blood was
on the dagger in her trunk,
but Maya didn't have any cuts
on her,
so that leads me to ask myself,
where the heck did that blood
come from, right?
And then I remembered, uh,
this guy is such a good guy
he volunteers
at his local hospital,
the very same hospital
where Maya donated blood.
Maybe your mom wasn't a thief,
but her son sure is.
I was just texting
with my partner.
Yeah, they checked the footage
at the hospital.
Sure enough, there you are,
stealing Maya's blood.
So officers will be here
any minute to arrest you now,
but I just wanted to make sure
that I got here first
'cause I really wanted
to see your face
when you realized...
you will end up in a cage.
Well played.
She was a good mom.
She worked so hard.
She always made time for me.
Gosh,
I bet she would be so proud
that you honored her memory
by harming another mom.
I never hurt anyone.
Oh, it didn't hurt Maya
to be kidnapped and taken away
from her child?
What about Jason?
You set him up to be killed.
He didn't have anything
to do with any of this.
The rich are all the same.
They rig the game so that
they always win, and we...
always lose.
We're just pawns to them,
Morgan.
Disposable.
Like my mom,
just a convenient scapegoat for
a fraudulent insurance claim?
Some rich jackass
destroyed my life,
turned her into a criminal,
and the police,
they helped him do it.
I believe you.
I just don't care.
[♪ "How It Ends" playing]
My mom died in prison.
♪ Hold your grandmother's Bible
To your breast ♪
♪ Gonna put it to the test ♪
♪ You want it to be blessed ♪
♪ And in your heart ♪
♪ You know it to be true ♪
♪ You know what you gotta do ♪
[Matthew, distorted]
My mom died in prison.
♪ They all depend on you ♪
But I won't.
♪ And you already know ♪
♪ Yeah, you already know ♪
♪ How this will end ♪
[police radio chatter]
♪ There is no escape ♪
[Karadec] He's all yours.
Matthew Clark,
you're under arrest
for the kidnapping
of Maya Price, Spencer Wallace,
Sierra Shuman.
And me.
[Ludo] You're just as limber
as she is.
Whoa. Hey.
-[whispering] Sorry, sorry.
-[whispering] No, it's okay.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Okay.
Oh, she's still spinning.
[Ludo] Yeah, I'm getting dizzy.
[groans] Someone's gotta
teach her about leaving them
wanting more.
Okay.
Elliot's up next.
Sit up. Sit up, and then smile.
Uh, next up, we have Elliot,
who will be doing...
Well, I'll let you see
for yourselves.
Here we go.
[mic feedback]
-Good evening.
-[mic feedback]
-[snickering]
-Dork!
Most of you only know me
as Elliot,
but tonight,
you get to meet MC Squared.
-I came up with the name.
-Okay.
-Here we go.
-[through laptop] Here we go.
-[beatboxes]
-[through laptop]
♪ La, la, la, la ♪
[through laptop] Here we go.
-[beatboxes]
-[through laptop]
♪ La, la, la, la ♪
Dork.
-♪ Give me a chance ♪
-♪ La, la, la, la ♪
♪ And then you'll see ♪
[through laptop] Here we go.
♪ I'm like you,
And you are just like me ♪
-[electronic voice]
♪ Give me a chance ♪
-♪ La, la, la, la ♪
♪ And then you'll see ♪
[through laptop] Here we go.
♪ I'm like you
And you are just like me ♪
-[siren blares]
-Here we go, here we go.
[rapping]
♪ You let me drop a truth bomb
Mic check one, two ♪
♪ See the label's coming
At me ♪
♪ Yeah, I seem too weird,
Know-it-all ♪
♪ All the gossip in the hall ♪
♪ Like I'm some kind of puzzle
That you can't solve ♪
♪ Or you can stop
And ask my name ♪
♪ It's a triple dog
Dare I'll say ♪
[electronic voice]
♪ E equals me
Equals MC Squared ♪
[Elliot] ♪ I'm just a kid
with an active mind ♪
♪ But I'm really just
Like you ♪
♪ We should kick it sometime
We don't need all the labels ♪
♪ Just meet me at the table ♪
♪ My brain's wired different
But I bet that we're able ♪
♪ To overcome
This lame divide ♪
♪ And find some common ground
Where we can reside ♪
[song ends]
[mic feedback]
Whoo!
-[cheering]
-Oh, yeah!
Whoo-hoo!
[Ludo] MC Squared!
-[cheering]
-Whoo!
[Morgan] All right!
-[baby crying]
-[Morgan] Ooh!
So you guys were surprised?
About the part
where you broke the microphone.
I wonder where he gets
his lyrical genius from.
Oh, boy.
Can I go say something
to those idiots?
Say something, do something.
I'm not watching.
Hey.
You did it.
Hey, guys,
why don't I meet you outside?
-Okay?
-Sure.
Come on.
Lead the way, superstar.
Who are you?
I'm Arthur.
Okay, Arthur, you wanna tell me
why the hell you're
at my kid's school
-and why you were using
Roman's name?
-Take it easy.
I'm here because he told me
that you were the one person
he could trust,
but he also told me
that he can't trust
law enforcement.
-When did he tell you
all of this?
-Last week.
So, if you wanna tell me
why the one person he's
looking out for is
actually hanging out
with the people
he's running from,
then please,
don't hesitate to call.
What was in the backpack?
What backpack?
The backpack you had in Nevada.
I saw a picture,
and you had it,
and I know it wasn't yours.
And what makes you think that?
Well, no Dodgers fan
is gonna wear an Angels pin
on the strap of their backpack.
That was Roman's team.
Plus,
he never threw anything away.
He wanted to fix it himself,
which explains the stitching
on the seams.
So you think I stole his bag?
Or he gave it to you.
Either way, I wanna know
what was in the backpack.
I-I assume that was
why you were in Henderson,
right?
Look, Roman asked me
to put eyes on you and Ava
just to make sure
you two were okay.
[mumbles]
You have a good night, Morgan.
[Ludo] The audience could have
answered the call-and-response
a little bit more,
you know what I mean?
So why did that girl
get first place? She was just
doing stupid ballet.
A motion has been put forward
to get ice cream
in order to celebrate
MC Squared here.
-How do you vote?
-Aye.
It's unanimous. Motion passed.
Last one to the car has to pay.
Mom?
Who is he?
I don't know yet.