[♪ "Red Right Hand" playing]
♪ Take a little walk To the edge
of town And go across the tracks ♪
[teenager 1] Where do I
have to put it?
♪ Where the viaduct looms like A
bird of doom As it shifts and cracks ♪
♪ Where secrets lie ♪
♪ In the border fires
In the humming wires ♪
Anywhere you want as long as
the pumpkin touches the porch.
[stammers] Maybe
we should just go to the party.
Come on, show some backbone.
We've both done it.
[sighs]
♪ His catastrophic plan ♪
♪ Designed and directed
By his red right hand ♪
Yes!
Yes.
[screaming]
Come on.
[screaming continues]
[grunts]
[gasps]
What's she doing to him?
[teenagers scream]
-[Elliot] Mom.
-[gasps] What? Are you okay?
-Guess who I am?
-Uh...
A sassy friar?
Hang on.
Dad ordered this for me on Prime to
be sure it got here before Halloween.
-How about now?
-Okay, uh... a science friar.
I'm Copernicus.
He was the first one to realize the
sun is at the center of the solar system.
Oh, yeah. Okay.
Yeah, I see it. I love it.
What time is it?
Jeez, I fell asleep, huh?
What's that?
Well, this is...
Let's just say it's the reason
your sister and I aren't
exactly talking right now.
What's she doing?
Is she still up too?
She's barely come out of her
room since you grounded her.
-I think you should talk to her.
-Oh, you do?
Okay, well,
thank you for your advice,
but I think I'm going to
Aristotle this one.
Aristotle. He thought silence
was louder than yelling.
Close enough.
Yes, but Aristotle also believed anger
must always be within the golden mean,
not excessive, at the right
time for the right purpose.
Dead on, kid.
All right, fine. I'm gonna
talk to her at some point.
-[phone buzzes]
-Don't worry about it.
Oh, I got a work thing
I gotta go to.
-You go to bed. Why are you still even up?
-Yeah. Okay.
Go. I love the costume.
[police radio chatter]
[creaking]
[wind whistling]
[clock clicking, gongs]
[clock ticking]
[gongs]
[camera shutter clicks]
This is perfect. It's our
first Halloween together.
-Is it?
-Yeah.
Hop on in here, buddy.
I'm not eating candy
at a crime scene.
Right, right. Why have fun?
I would've thought Halloween
was your favorite holiday.
-Why would you think that?
-It's like the one day of the year
you can let your hair down,
throw a costume on,
be somebody other than you
for one night.
[doorbell rings]
Trick or treat!
Okay, I was wrong.
-Can we focus on our dead man?
-Yeah, let's do that.
This is Danny Sternblatt.
Divorce lawyer
to the 1%, including the mayor
when he split
from his wife last year.
What happened to the walls?
Who killed the lights? The
electricity is on in the block.
Says the motion-sensor werewolf
across the street.
[screams] Down! No!
He knows.
The power's cut at
the main panel, as in severed.
I'm not sure yet by whom
or who went at the walls.
Also, the, uh, 911 call
was unusual.
A group of teens said that they
heard a scream through the window
and claimed to see something
white and flowy attack him.
White and flowy? Come on.
As far as I'm concerned,
it could've been the curtains.
Yeah, or their imaginations.
Could be Sternblatt just
died of natural causes,
-which is part of what we're here to find out.
-He's got marks on his arm.
Looks like somebody
grabbed him real hard.
Or Danny grabbed his own arm,
maybe during a medical event?
Perhaps a heart attack, shooting
pain down the arm, certainly a symptom.
Uh-huh. His hair is either
falling out or he is pulling it out.
That with the dark bags
under his eyes,
I don't think
Danny was sleeping very well.
[Karadec] Mmm.
Well, we know
who murdered the woodwork.
These blisters on Danny's hands
say he was the vandal.
Benzo's for sleep, which
clearly weren't working very well.
And heart meds, nitroglycerin.
It's another point for natural causes.
We're thinking he was
sitting over here working
when his heart gave out, knocked
over his plate on his way down
and ended up there.
At least he won't have to read
his own handwriting anymore.
Something doesn't
make sense here though.
Imagine you're Danny.
He's having a heart attack.
You know you have a bad heart. You
have lifesaving medication over there.
Why would you
run away from the bathroom?
He must've been going
towards something this way.
That?
Either obsidian
or black tourmaline.
-Why this?
-Maybe an ugly gift from a wife?
Yeah, could be. Danny's
going through his own divorce.
We contacted the wife, Lorraine.
She's on business in London,
catching the first flight back.
-So the white flowy thing, not a wife.
-Mmm.
Depends which wife. Lorraine Sternblatt
or the ghost of Maddie St. Croix?
Sorry, did you just say ghost?
Mm-hmm.
[Daphne] Oh, wait,
just to be clear,
I am not suggesting a ghost
killed Danny Sternblatt.
You're not not suggesting it.
I like true crime podcasts, sometimes
ghosts stories. No shame there.
And the Spencer house,
where we are now, checks both.
Have you heard of Dash Spencer
and Maddie St. Croix?
1940s movie stars, screwball
comedies. Uh, mostly involved a monkey.
Well, they were married
in real life too.
The it couple of their day,
and this was their house.
Got that from Spencer house.
They died young, right?
A little after they married, Maddie found out
Dash had been cheating on her from day one,
and in a fit of heartbreak, she took her
own life with an overdose of secobarbital.
Then, a few months later,
on Halloween,
Dash fell from that balcony
and broke his neck.
Which is called a coincidence.
Police ruled the death accidental.
Yes, but the ghost story crowd
always said Maddie's ghost
pushed Dash over the rail,
-and she still haunts the house today.
-Ooh.
Look, I am not saying
I believe that, but...
Good. Because a ghost definitely
did not kill Danny Sternblatt.
We have two options. It's
either murder or natural causes.
[phone buzzes]
-Lieutenant.
-[Selena] I'm sending you a text.
The kids who called 911
sat with our sketch artist.
Curious to hear your take.
-What? What is it?
-[Karadec sighs]
Sorry, you were just saying...
[Daphne] Oh, wow.
They even nailed the scalloped
lace on Maddie's veil.
[Oz laughs]
Fine, then you explain it.
What did they see?
That photo, Daph.
You found it online.
They could've too.
It's a Halloween prank.
They did say they came to the
house because of its history.
Verbena, it's calming.
[phone buzzing]
ME's prelim is in. Danny
Sternblatt died of a heart attack.
It wasn't his first.
He had one a few years ago.
So unless we have something
that proves otherwise,
they're gonna rule
natural causes.
Anyone else feel that?
No? Weird.
[inhales sharply, sighs]
[crunching]
Is this salt?
Oh, oh. We might wanna pump
the brakes on the natural causes.
-[Karadec] Because...
-Because Oz is right.
At first, I thought it was just
plaster dust, but it's not. It's salt.
Yeah, look, the salt leads to
fluorite, carnelian, labradorite,
obsidian, and
I'm thinking... smoky quartz.
Five stones connected by salt.
Danny made a pentacle.
It's a symbol of protection in some
cultures, and so is that bracelet.
Detective Karadec might not
believe in ghosts, but our victim did.
Danny thought
his house was haunted.
[Danny screaming]
[Morgan] He was
hearing and seeing crazy things
he couldn't pinpoint,
so he trashed this entire place
trying to figure out
where it was coming from.
Guy had electricians, pest control,
plumbers, everyone checked this place out.
Okay, Danny was hearing things
that go bump in the night,
but we know it wasn't a ghost.
I think somebody
who knew Danny had a bad heart,
staged a haunting
to scare him to death.
That would be murder.
All this witchy stuff
is not Danny's style.
Somebody had to help him
set it up.
And someone who could stop a
haunt might be able to fake one.
Danny's phone
is password-protected.
It's gonna take TID
some time to crack it.
Oz, any of those invoices over there have
something to do with ghost remediation?
-[Oz] Um...
-[papers rustle]
No. But there is this.
[Karadec] And just for my file,
the full name is Calliope...
[Calliope] Just Calliope.
I knew something felt off today.
What was the nature of your
relationship with Mr. Sternblatt?
Verbena? It's good for stress.
Oh, thank you. We got our fill
at the crime scene.
I was Danny's spiritual advisor.
He was raised in a traditional faith
and never really connected with it.
So when he reached a crossroads in
life, he preferred to ask the universe.
Spiritual, not religious.
Would you mind?
We did a very difficult reading
for a client this morning.
We need time to ground.
What sort of crossroads
did you talk about with Danny?
Business, mostly. Managing his
law firm, sometimes investments.
Investments like buying
the Spencer house?
[Calliope] Especially
the Spencer house.
He wouldn't sleep there until
I performed a clearing ritual,
but it was his wife's dream
of dream houses.
Sadly, the work I performed
there didn't last.
After Lorraine left,
something dark welled up.
So you're the one who helped him set
up all those protective elements, right?
-Have you been in the house?
-Mm-hmm.
So you felt the cold spot in the
basement? Heard the crying woman?
-Mmm.
-Can't say that we have. Where was this?
In the butler's pantry.
Well, that's where I heard her.
Danny heard her at the same time
in the sitting room across the house.
The energy
in that place is very off.
Yeah. Hey, how much do each
of these clearing rituals cost?
Around 5,000.
-Dollars?
-Yes. Why?
Uh... I need a minute to ground.
What my partner's saying is it
seems you caught yourself a whale.
Danny was terrified and
more than willing to shell out.
[chuckles] -Yeah, and
these rituals didn't work,
but you knew that, didn't you?
This green candle over here, you got
it just drenched in bergamot and myrtle.
That's an abundance spell, right?
Only typically those are done
during a waxing moon,
and right now the moon's waning.
You know your stuff.
Ah. My cleaning lady
must have flipped that.
Oh. Yeah. Yeah,
I think I do know my stuff.
I also know that a woman who refers
to herself and her tarot deck as "we,"
doesn't need to consult a calendar
to find out the moon phases.
-You calling me a fraud?
-I am.
[Karadec] So, Calliope,
what happened?
Did Danny catch on to your scam?
Cut off the funds,
so you scared him to death?
[chuckles]
No, why would I do that?
My entire business would collapse if
people found out my clients were dying.
Now, unless I am under arrest,
please leave and take your
closed hearts with you.
This is a sacred space.
This is a bungalow
in El Segundo.
Morgan, let's go.
If you don't believe the
Spencer house is haunted, fine.
But the things
I told you did happen,
so perhaps focus less on me
and look into what caused them.
What? She put me in a bad mood.
-When were you in a good mood?
-I'm a delight.
Well, fraud or no fraud,
Calliope made a good point.
It wasn't in her best interest
to kill her golden goose.
And she gave us
specifics we can use.
A cold spot in the basement,
a woman crying.
Someone planted those scares
to freak Sternblatt out.
And maybe they left
some evidence behind.
[crow caws]
[clock ticks]
[clattering]
[loud thud]
[rattling in distance]
[rustling]
[clattering]
[squeaking]
-[phone buzzing]
-[sighs]
-Yeah?
-Hey, how's it going down there?
Uh, great. If you like spiders.
Otherwise, not much to report.
You?
Just a rat,
cute little guy or gal.
Not a lot of differentiating
characteristics.
Morgan?
Calliope said
that they heard a woman crying
in two different parts
of the house, right?
Well, my kids used to talk to each
other through the vents in their bedrooms.
Oh, hello.
-Morgan?
-Mm-hmm.
I think you're gonna
want to see this.
Morgan, where are you?
What's going on? Just tell me.
Someone...
or something.
LAPD, put your hands
where I can see 'em.
We got another runner.
[♪ "Go Dumb" playing]
♪ I go forty down to fifty ♪
♪ I can rise With the
tide... ♪ -[Morgan shrieks]
-Get-Get off!
-[grunting]
-Not what I was expecting.
-Yeah, me neither. Get off me.
-[grunts]
-[Karadec] Get up.
[intruder grunting] - On your
feet. On your feet. On your feet.
-Let me go. I didn't do anything.
-All right.
Found this in a vent. Let's see.
Okay, a couple of iPads,
some computer stuff,
just standard things
that somebody hiding in a basement
wearing a wedding dress would have.
-I'm guessing these are yours.
-Come on. Let's go to the station.
You can tell me more about
how you weren't doing anything.
Easy. Easy.
[sighing] Oh, thank goodness. I'd hate
to think anybody was getting any sunlight.
I've been outside.
Wasn't impressed.
-How was work?
-Pretty good.
I helped stop a fleeing suspect
today, mostly by just standing there,
but still, the job got done.
She's being questioned
right now, so I had a little time.
I thought I'd come home and get
dinner started before Ludo gets here,
then I gotta head back.
How were your days?
Chloe go down for her nap okay?
Uh, yeah, Ava got Chloe down,
no problem. School was the usual.
I'm pretty sure Mr. Cabral doesn't know
the difference between mass and weight,
but don't worry,
I pulled him aside after class.
Mmm. I bet he loved that.
So what do you think?
Burritos okay for dinner?
We're still doing this, huh?
Ava was invited to a Halloween party
this weekend, and she really wants to go,
but I think she's still upset
that she's grounded.
Really?
You think it might be
a smart idea to apologize
for blatantly disobeying me first,
and then we could go from there?
[huffs] -Ava thinks she
didn't do anything wrong.
Babe, it's not your job
to fix this, okay?
We're all right. Why don't you go do
something that doesn't involve a screen?
Okay.
Ava, how long do you
want to play this game?
Mom, it's been a week.
This is so unfair.
[door slams]
Children are such a blessing.
Captain Wagner, a word.
Anytime.
This case is a weird one, huh?
It is.
It's not every day a captain insists
on questioning a suspect himself.
Oh, come on. Woman
in an antique wedding dress
pretending to be a ghost
to scare a man to death.
How often do one of those
come along?
The mayor's a family friend.
Wants updates.
Pretty sure he and half his golf
buddies want this case closed
before Sternblatt's law practice
and all their divorce details
get dragged through the mud.
-I see.
-Shouldn't affect you, though.
I provide cover. You work
the case, long as it takes.
That's a nice sentiment,
only I just got off the phone
with the Department of Media.
They were fact-checking a
press release about the arrest,
the one I assume
you're holding right now.
Rushing this out when
we don't have the facts yet
doesn't seem to me like
letting the wheels of justice turn.
This arrest, sloppy police work?
No, she's our haunter.
Then you have
nothing to worry about.
-[sighs]
-[door closes]
[Nick] Shawna Khurmi.
That's K-H-U...
Is the furniture small?
No, you're big.
Guess the world wasn't built
for people my size, huh?
Anyway, it's Khurmi.
K-H-U-R-M-I. Twenty-seven.
Special effects wiz.
Electrical engineering. Oh.
Cal Arts grad. Wow.
-I've asked for a lawyer.
-Yes, I heard, as is your right.
It's just that this release is
gonna go out before they get here,
so I thought I'd give you
a chance to correct the error.
So it is true.
New cap's doing the interview.
Mm-hmm.
Mind if I watch?
Knock yourself out.
You know, I won't lie. Lawyers hate
these releases. Court of public opinion.
Once we tell the world you're a killer,
good luck convincing a jury otherwise.
But we're just gonna go
with what we know.
You applied your skills
to stage a high-tech haunt
spanning a matter of months.
You used your fancy toys
and an inspired cameo as
the ghost of Maddie St. Croix
that led to the death of Danny.
You killed him. And then you
saw those kids at the window.
You knew the cops
were coming then, right?
At least that's the story now.
But you know, I know you have
a lot of student debt,
and I also can't tie you to Sternblatt,
which means someone paid you.
Shawna, give me their name,
and this press release
disappears.
You don't get labeled a killer
and this whole thing
comes grinding to a halt.
[Oz chuckles]
Help me help you.
I tried to save him,
but I don't know CPR,
and she never told me
about his heart condition.
She who?
Danny's wife, Lorraine.
Wow, that's, uh...
[clears throat] ...that's good.
It's good work.
Sure, but he still
could've told us.
-Lorraine back in town yet?
-She should've just landed.
She did say something about
having to stop by her office first
before coming to see us.
Then have Karadec and Morgan
meet her there.
I think she'll squeeze us in.
[person] I'm just trying to
make sure you're taken care of.
No, you're not. You're trying to
You always loved that house
more than you loved my dad.
Excuse me. LAPD.
Did you just say
Danny Sternblatt was your dad?
Yeah, I'm Paloma Nichols.
I'm really sorry for your loss.
It doesn't sound like Lorraine
in there is your mom?
[scoffs] Dad's second wife.
He and my mom split ages ago.
Wait, do you think Lorraine had
something to do with his death?
It's too soon to comment.
[sighs] I wouldn't
put it past her.
She invited me here
to supposedly make peace.
Really, she wanted
to feel out my intentions.
My dad's body
isn't even cold yet.
Uh, sorry, Ms. Nichols, we may
have some questions for you too.
-Is there any way we can reach you?
-Yeah.
It's Dr. Nichols.
Here's all my info.
When you are ready to comment,
I'd love to hear it.
[Lorraine] Jody, I'm wiped.
I'm gonna head home.
Hey, if the, uh,
police call again,
let them know
I'll go there in the morning.
Saved you the trip.
Ms. Khurmi
identified you by name.
Says you met when you spoke
at a class she took,
and a few months later, you
approached her for help with a haunting
and offered her a job
at your firm in exchange.
Shawna says she had no idea about
Danny's heart, and we believe her.
The problem is you did know,
because he'd had a previous heart
attack when you guys were married.
I knew.
His recovery was the last time
I can remember us being good
to each other.
So it sounds like you did
love each other at one point.
Yeah, I mean, I...
He used to write me
these letters all the time.
We were one of history's great
couples, like Dash and Maddie.
Until Danny started acting a little too
much like Dash and cheated on you.
I was devastated.
And then when I decided that I had
enough, he used every trick against me.
He changed locks while I was
traveling, swore I'd never get the house.
It was all about winning.
So you decided to play dirty too and used
his superstitions to get what you wanted.
[sighs] Listen,
I know that it went too far,
but I never wanted to kill him.
I just wanted the house.
I mean, I figured if I spooked him
enough, he would just sign it over.
Wait, you met his daughter
on her way out.
The house was in Danny's name.
He... He left it to her.
She would inherit the house.
You needed him to give it over
to you while he was alive.
Yeah, well...
Doesn't change the fact that he's
dead and I have to live with that.
Wait,
is this Danny's handwriting?
Oh, this doesn't look anything
like the letters at the house.
That writing was really messy,
shaky, like his hands were weak.
Also, I think
he was off-balance.
Poor guy was stumbling all
over the place like the undead.
Karadec, I think we've gotta
check those sleeping pills.
I'll have the ME
fast-track his tox report.
[stutters]
Wait, what's going on?
You could have scared Danny
to death, but I don't think you did.
I think he was poisoned.
Lab reports are back.
Those weren't sleeping pills.
Danny Sternblatt died from
a potassium chloride overdose
which induced
a fatal heart attack.
ME said it was a smart way
to kill someone.
Potassium chloride spikes
naturally in the blood after death.
Autopsy never would've
caught it.
Which means if we
hadn't tested those pills,
Lorraine Sternblatt would've gone
down for a murder she didn't commit.
Solid catch by Morgan.
So, someone knew the wife was
gaslighting Danny and piggybacked on that,
making it look
like she haunted him to death.
-Who?
-Had to be someone close to him,
someone with access
to the pills.
You take a closer
look at the daughter?
Paloma will get the house, but
the money motive feels weak.
I mean, she's an orthopedic surgeon
married to another orthopedic surgeon.
She's fine.
What about Sternblatt's practice?
Didn't the wife say he was tough as nails?
Yeah, said he used
every nasty trick in the book.
Even came up with some new ones.
Maybe a divorcé he did
a number on wanted revenge?
Or maybe a rival lawyer.
We'll head over to his firm.
If the guy had enemies
over there, we'll find out.
-He was murdered?
-Mmm.
Oh, my God. I figured
his heart just gave out.
Were you aware Mr. Sternblatt
thought that his house was, um, haunted?
He made it impossible
not to know.
Danny was freaking everyone out, that
woo-woo bracelet, jumping at shadows.
We're wondering if anyone he
went up against with in court
might've known that too and
used that knowledge against him.
[scoffs] I wish.
Well, I'm sorry.
[stammers] That came out wrong.
I just meant that Danny wasn't
in court anytime recently.
He was too wrapped up in his own
divorce and winning that damn house.
He handed off all his other
cases months ago,
stopped coming in at all
the last few weeks.
Look, I was worried
about my friend.
Wouldn't you be?
Have at it.
I have to call my wife.
Huh. Well, sounds like Sternblatt
wasn't making any enemies here.
-Took himself completely off the board.
-Mm-hmm.
Feels like all roads keep leading
back to the Spencer house.
What do you say we give
Daphne's ghost theory another run?
I just do not get this guy.
I mean, digging in
out of spite, that's one thing,
but Sternblatt hated the house.
He wasn't sleeping.
He knew he had a bad heart.
At a certain point, you would think,
that the fear of having a heart attack
would override the desire
to win a divorce.
[phone buzzing]
You're missing out, Gillory.
It looks like one of your crime boards
exploded all over our victim's office.
Only in every direction it's
nothing but house, house, house.
-Maybe it is something.
-[Oz] What's that?
Well, I was doing a little digging around
in the Sternblatt divorce documents
trying to find something that would
pop out as a motive to kill Danny.
-And?
-Nothing popped.
But then I noticed something
weird about the house.
The appraisal when they bought it
showed it as 300 square feet smaller
than it was when it was
appraised in the 1940s.
I mean,
maybe that's a mistake, but...
No. No, it's here
on the blueprints too.
300-square-foot difference
between the old and the new.
How could they lose 300 square feet,
but the footprints look exactly the same?
-It's like there's a...
-Disappearing room?
I don't think
we're done there yet, boys.
I think the Spencer house has
more secrets to tell.
And I'm sensing you have
a way of figuring that out?
He didn't need
to straighten that.
Mind if I ask why you pulled
half my bullpen down here?
Do you mind if I answer
in the form of a story?
Don't answer that. It's
happening. It's starting right now.
Deep in the gloomy glens of ancient
Scotland stands Castle Glamis.
Legend has it that the heir
of the 11th Earl of Strathmore
was hidden away in a secret room that
was walled up, never to be seen again.
But then, a few hundred years later,
there was a new lady of the castle,
and she set out to find
the infamous hidden chamber.
This Lady Glamis knew that if a
room had actually been walled up
that it would
still have a window.
So she asked
her ladies-in-waiting
to tie a handkerchief to
every window they could find.
And lo and behold,
only one window remained that
was hanky-free from the outside.
And that was
how she found the secret room.
And there it is.
I'm guessing
this was Lorraine's craft room
before Danny booted her out.
Okay, that secret room's gotta
be behind these bookshelves.
Oh!
-You see it?
-Why don't you help us see it?
This panel, it's plain sawn.
It has to do with
how they cut the lumber.
These shelves are all quarter
sawn, so is the rest of the house,
but this panel is plain sawn.
Maybe Danny broke that panel
when he was tearing this place up
and then repaired it,
but why only make the one fix?
[screaming]
Mmm. Maybe to hide this?
This is Maddie's old boudoir.
Oh, and that hat, that's the
hat that she wore to the premiere
of the last film
she made with Dash.
Can I try a couple of these things on
before they get shipped off to some museum?
-They're evidence.
-I'll be careful.
So we think this room's been
tucked away for 70-plus years?
Well, Maddie took her own life.
Dash must have walled it up.
Probably because his conscience
couldn't handle any reminders
of the woman
he'd driven to suicide.
[Daphne] Check out this gem.
This room might've never been found if
Lorraine hadn't started haunting Danny.
This room is part of history. Why would
Danny want to hide that from the world?
Well, the same reason he didn't
leave when he started being haunted.
Gotta be something in here
worth sticking around for.
Like this?
-Oh, yeah, that would do it.
-Speaking of gems.
It's the only thing
not covered in dust.
There is a rumor that when Maddie
caught Dash with his mistress,
he tried to make it up to her
with a diamond necklace.
-If those diamonds are real...
-They're real.
They'd be worth enough
to kill for.
Hey, want some of this?
I figure we deserve
a little unwind
while we wait to see if that
necklace you found is real.
Root beer on an unprotected
lip? You're a madman.
-I'll take it slow.
-Did I shame you into that?
No, no, it was time.
All winning streaks
have to come to an end.
Is that what we're calling it?
It's okay. I'll take the can.
Hey, you a Dash and Maddie fan?
-Mmm.
-Yeah, I was.
Little disappointed
in all the gory details.
Yeah, this case isn't a ringing
endorsement for marriage.
Ever been?
Married? No.
No. No, I mean, weddings are
great. There's... It's very sweet.
I get it. [stammers] I just...
It's good for people. I just... The whole
courthouse and the paperwork and the...
the permanence of it, you know,
kind of kills the romance.
-Yeah?
-Oh, just seeing some things.
I don't think you are.
-If this was an interrogation...
-It's not though.
It's not an interrogation,
so knock it off.
-Well, now I know I'm right.
-[laughs]
Okay. Fine,
what things are you seeing?
Well, first of all, you're
gripping that can so tight,
I'm worried you're going
to be wearing the soda.
The neck massage, a little self
soothing, fiddling with the candy.
Those eyes of yours are jumping
around to everywhere but mine.
I think the talk of marriage is
making you a little anxious.
-Okay.
-[chuckles]
[titters] Yeah, yeah,
I don't like it, you know.
My brain has a way of making
sure relationships don't last very long,
so let's just leave it at that.
-Okay.
-What about you?
Me? Oh.
I'm into a four-year deal
that's working out pretty well.
-Really?
-Yeah.
She understands me, and, for
the most part, I understand her.
[Morgan chuckles]
-She's gorgeous.
-Thanks.
-She have a name?
-Ingrid.
Well, congratulations.
Ingrid seems like a real catch.
Thank you.
What about an actual human woman?
Have you ever married one of those?
[chuckles]
Got real close.
She passed away a few years ago.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, me too.
[phone buzzes]
Hmm. Looks like they need us.
[Karadec] 18-karat white gold waterfall,
102 cushion antique cut diamonds,
85 French cut for
a grand total of 317 carats.
Designed in Paris by celebrated sisters
Ophelia and Josephine Beaumont in 1946.
-It's a strong accent.
-Hmm.
So it's authentic.
According to our contact,
based on the piece itself,
-she said it was worth around ten million.
-[scoffs]
That and a sexy providence
with a tragic Hollywood ending
-and you, what, double the price?
-[gasps]
Sounds about right.
[Nick] So why was it
still there?
Sternblatt must've
ball parked its worth.
Why didn't he put it in Fort Knox
or try to find a tycoon to buy it?
The guy was a divorce attorney.
Nobody knew better than him that if
Lorraine found out, she could claim half.
[Selena] So we're thinking he
opted to leave it behind the wall
until the divorce was final.
Anything else
would've been too risky.
Then he could sell it and make
up a story about where he found it.
But somebody else
knew it was there,
and their plan was to kill
Danny, steal the necklace.
Until the kids saw Shawna
being Maddie's ghost
and got us down there so fast, the killer
missed the window to complete the theft.
The good news is this person
doesn't know we have the necklace,
so that could be a good...
[Morgan] I don't think Danny
was sleeping very well.
I just wanted the house.
-No!
-The energy in that place is very off.
You're trying to make sure
you're taken care of.
You know who did it, don't you?
-Yeah.
-So?
So let's give 'em their window.
Based on evidence uncovered by
detectives in LAPD's Major Crime Squad,
we have arrested
Lorraine Sternblatt
on suspicion of poisoning
her estranged husband,
noted attorney
Daniel Sternblatt.
You must be devastated.
If it helps to ease your mind,
those who cross over
no longer feel the pain we do.
That's what I'm not so sure of.
The crossing over.
I went there this morning. The
police released the house to me.
Maybe it's all the stress
talking, but I felt him there.
Well, energy can linger.
But then he could be in pain, trapped.
Wait. Could you help him?
Of course. I would recommend
a clearing ritual.
[♪ "Don't Fear the Reaper"
playing]
[Calliope] All I would need is a
few hours to myself in the house.
And then I think
we can put him to rest.
♪ Seasons don't
Fear the Reaper ♪
♪ Nor do the wind,
The sun or the rain ♪
♪ We can be like they are ♪
♪ Come on, baby ♪
♪ Baby, take my hand ♪
-[gasps]
-Boo.
[screams]
[Morgan] Oh, I know that look.
That's the "who are you and how
did you guys figure me out" look.
-Partner, you wanna start this one off?
-Sure.
Did you know to
get rid of decades of tarnish
from a priceless diamond necklace,
all you need is a dab of essential oil?
Now, I would recommend verbena.
Supposedly, it's good for stress.
Yeah, she's-she's crazy
about that verbena.
You see, when I saw a bunch of
tarnish-free fingerprints on those links.
That very calming smell
led me to believe
that you knew
about the necklace all along.
I think Danny told you
that he was being haunted,
and you jumped
right on that opportunity.
You knew somebody else was already
gaslighting this very gullible man.
How they were doing it didn't
really matter. You didn't care.
All you needed to do was
draft off of their haunting
and collect your paychecks.
Poor Danny trusted you so much
that when he found Maddie's necklace,
he told you about it, right?
I mean, after all, he never made a
move in this house without consulting you,
-and you came up with a plan to kill him.
-[Morgan] That's right.
You switched out his sleeping
pills for potassium chloride,
and you convinced him to
check in with you every morning
to discuss all of the creepy things
that happened the evening before.
You see, we have a tech team.
They cracked Danny's phone,
and we saw the texts.
So the day
you didn't receive one,
you knew that Danny had
had his coronary event.
Your plan had worked, you could've just
came back here and swiped the necklace.
But the police got here too fast,
didn't they? Blew your window.
So we tried to help you out.
We staged an arrest for Lorraine.
That way Paloma could lure you
back into the house.
Guess it worked. Happy
Halloween. You're under arrest.
-Karadec.
-Mm-hmm.
-Where's the bird?
-Bird?
Yeah, that giant awesome black
raven that was perched on the clock,
casting a super creepy shadow
when we first got here.
Do you remember?
I guess I was just focused on the
body. Don't know what to tell you.
[caws]
[sighs]
-Hey.
-I heard you out here.
-You did?
-It was a very loud sigh.
-Was it?
[sighs]
Can I go first?
-Depends.
-It's all your fault.
-No, you can't.
-No, no, no, I mean,
you're mad at a younger you.
I'm not like you in a lot of ways, but
I'm way too much like you in others.
Did you always
listen to your mom?
-I-I mean...
-Of course not.
Makes me think that the 15-year-old
you would've done exactly what I did,
-because me and you...
-You and I.
[sighs]
You and I aren't wired to just
sit by if we want something.
I mean, there's this guy that might
be able to tell us about my dad,
and I was supposed to
do nothing?
I know it wasn't
the safest thing to do,
but you guys are going to
our favorite diner.
I couldn't help myself.
So I'm sorry I scared you.
But I'm not sorry that I went.
Okay, I'm done. Your turn.
Okay. I accept your non-apology.
And I'm not sorry
that I put my foot down.
I can't keep looking for your dad if
it means you're not gonna be safe.
I-I need you
to keep looking for him.
So if that means I have to
start listening, then I guess I will.
-[both chuckling]
-There she is.
I love you so much.
I love you too, Mom.
[sighs] So am I still grounded?
Why don't you ask me the
question you really wanna ask me?
Can I go to Emma's
Halloween party?
Depends. How
inappropriate is your costume?
Zombie cheerleader, and
my skirt's longer than yours.
-That's fair. [chuckles]
-Can I show you?
Yes, but I wanna show you
something first. Come here.
-Is that...
-That's it.
Have you opened it?
Yeah. It took me a minute,
but I got there.
-And?
-I don't know yet.
I don't know if any of it means anything
or if it's gonna help us find him.
-Can we?
-Yeah.
[♪ "Nirvana" playing]
♪ These are the times
That I think about ♪
♪ Red lights and the feeling
That I needed you ♪
I'm gonna give all this stuff
to Lieutenant Soto tomorrow,
but I just I wanted to
make sure that you saw this.
♪ And now I'm out there running
Like a lonely soul on fire ♪
This was from my recital.
Mm-hmm.
First grade. You guys were all
sunflowers, do you remember?
How did he know about that?
Well, I think
he must've been there.
♪ And I've been running
In circles again ♪
♪ But I swear that I can feel
The end if I'm not in Nirvana ♪
♪ You're not out of my head ♪