♪ Ooh ooh ♪
♪ Once I had a love
and it was a gas ♪
♪ Soon turned out had
a heart of glass ♪
♪ Seemed like the real
thing Only to find… ♪
-How many?
-Table for two, please.
-Meeting someone special?
-Very special.
That's so sweet. Well, come
on. Let's get you seated.
Oh. Wow. Some people
can be so rude.
No worries. Best
seat in the house.
I'll let you look that over
while I get all that cleaned up.
Uh, excuse me.
Do I look okay?
-I think you look dashing.
-Thank you.
♪ Ooh ooh ♪
Guys, come on, let's go.
Ludo's gonna be here any
second. Breakfast is ready.
I see you've inherited
my judgmental stare.
I thought only Ava got that, who
happens to love toaster waffles,
I'll have you know.
Ooh, toaster waffles.
One of 'em does. I
can't keep track.
-Hot, hot, hot.
-Here.
What are these?
Just a little project
I'm working on
now that we have some
walking-around money.
I thought I'd hire a
little part-time help.
-I recommend this one.
-Oh, yeah?
She plays laser tag. Heightened
peripheral vision, fast reflexes.
Important traits as
Chloe starts walking.
I feel like you picked
her 'cause she's pretty,
but you're doing a
good job of hiding it.
Oh, I know her. She was a
senior when I was a freshman.
-Yeah? What do you know about her?
-I don't know.
Seniors don't talk to freshmen.
Well, maybe dig around in her
social media or something.
I'm thinking about hiring
somebody part-time.
Oh, right. Back to
work full-time today.
That's right. And while I'm
at work, I wanna make sure
that you guys are getting
the support you need at home.
Ludo needed some backup, I got him
that. So, tell me what you guys need.
-I'd still love to visit the morgue.
-I love that idea, you know.
Why don't you show me you
can change Chloe's diaper
without passing out from the smell,
and we'll graduate to formaldehyde?
What about you, Ava?
I'd love to hear some
news about my dad.
I mean, it's okay.
I know you haven't really had the
chance to talk to Lieutenant Soto,
but now that you're back,
maybe she has some news.
I'm definitely
gonna look into it.
But right now I'm needed at a
crime scene. You take over, okay?
See if you can keep these guys
alive till Ludo gets here?
-I love you. Goodbye.
-Love you.
-Pay me what you're gonna pay her.
-Oh, absolutely.
You send that invoice to
accounts payable, okay?
-Bye.
I think what she means
by accounts payable is...
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I got it.
Victim's name is
Nathan Gould, 46.
Address on his license puts
him right in the neighborhood.
Café hostess found him behind these
dumpsters with a bag taped over his head.
Money and credit
cards are still here.
Yeah. Phone too. Doesn't
seem like a robbery.
Maybe something more personal?
Is he gonna make it?
He was in cardiac arrest when we
got here. No pulse, no respiration.
Got a heartbeat back, but he
hasn't regained consciousness.
Ventilator's doing
the breathing for him.
So he could be brain dead.
They'll be able to tell
more at the hospital.
We just don't know how long he was
without oxygen before we landed.
Poor guy's luck might
have finally run out.
Finally? You know this guy?
Nathan was a frequent flyer.
Rode with us more than once.
History of suspicious injuries.
-Suspicious how?
-He told us he fell and broke his leg.
Before that it was burned
his hand on the stove.
Always just said he was clumsy.
But you think
someone else helped?
Nathan was a good guy.
I hope you find who did this.
You said a hostess found him?
Yeah, she's a little shaken, but I
think she can answer some questions.
He was so nervous.
Said he was meeting
someone special.
That poor man.
This where he sat?
I went inside to get
some cleaning supplies,
and when I came out,
I thought he'd left.
I found that pin, and I ran
up the street to look for him.
Then things got busy, and I
just forgot about cleaning up.
I'm glad you did.
Karadec, check this out.
You ever spill a drink on
yourself at one of these tables?
Uh, can't say I
recall doing that, no.
Of course you haven't. You
like to put on a Hazmat suit
when you eat something crumbly.
But just pretend for one second
that you're a normal guy
having a normal meal, okay?
There you are, sipping on a
refreshing drink on a hot summer day
when, uh-oh, you spill
it all over the table.
It drips through the cracks and lands
all over your unprotected pants.
No!
Mm-hmm. I know.
But look at these spills.
They all landed evenly.
All over the ground, the chairs.
There weren't even
butts in the seats.
The spills were staged.
Someone knew Nathan
was going to be here
and wanted to make sure
he'd sit by the alley.
What time would you say you seated him?
And when did you find him in the alley?
I guess he got here
around a quarter to eight.
Okay, so how'd
you find the body?
-I heard ducks.
-Ducks?
Ducks quacking
somewhere in the alley.
I went to look, and…
And I found him.
I think that's all
we have for now.
If there's any other questions,
we'll be sure to let you know.
Okay.
What?
I thought you were gonna launch
into a comprehensive breakdown
of the migratory patterns of
ducks in the Los Angeles area.
-Is that what you thought? Hmm.
-Yeah.
Well, I could, but that would be pointless
'cause there were no ducks in that alley.
Did you see signs of
ducks? There was no poop.
That's all ducks do. They poop.
I don't know what she heard,
but I don't think it was ducks.
All right, we put
a pin in the ducks.
Vic's apartment's just
a few blocks from here.
If the paramedics were convinced
someone was repeatedly hurting him,
let's go find out who.
Well, books on player stats,
half a dozen team schedules.
Nathan Gould really
loved his sports.
-Oh, yeah? Who's his team?
-Enlighten me.
Me? I can't even figure out
what his favorite sport is.
I've been all over this place.
There's not a baseball cap or a
jersey, not a banner on the wall.
This place is wild though.
If anybody this obsessed with
stats was actually into sports,
do you know what it
would look like in here?
It'd look like the inside
of a stadium gift shop.
But I did also notice
this very impressive stack
of overdue bills, a sport
I'm very familiar with.
Looks like Nathan was
a couple of weeks away
from having
everything turned off.
So you don't think Nathan loved
sports, you think he loved gambling.
And I don't think gambling loved
him back, which could explain
all those mysterious injuries that
the paramedics were talking about.
Nathan had fallen behind on his debts,
and to the kind of people who do worse
than turn off the water
when the payment's late.
Hmm.
What do you think it is?
Don't know. It could be a bank account,
or passcode, international phone number.
Hmm.
Okay, those scary guys you
were just talking about,
the debt collectors,
they know home addresses?
Shh.
We're nice people. You
could have just knocked.
Ah!
Call the Lieutenant.
Have her send backup.
♪ Man, I love it when
they try to run ♪
Move.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
-You okay? Good?
-Yeah.
♪ Hold up, hold up
There's no time to wait ♪
♪ Best good guy to have on your
side No replace, y'all know ♪
♪ Nobody gotta get hurt ♪
♪ Sit back y'all
better watch me work ♪
♪ Nobody gotta get hurt ♪
♪ Sit back y'all
better watch me work ♪
♪ Nobody gotta get hurt ♪
♪ Sit back y'all
better watch me work ♪
You've reached
Lieutenant Soto.
Please leave a message, and I'll
return your call as soon as I can.
♪ Oh, oh, ey ♪
Hey! Cops.
♪ Nobody gotta get hurt ♪
♪ Sit back y'all
better watch me work ♪
Oh.
On your stomach.
Hands behind your back.
Uh-huh.
"Marco Deleon."
Buddy ditched you pretty quick there,
Marco. That hurt your feelings?
-He's not my buddy.
-Well, no, not after a stunt like that.
I think what Marco means is
they're just business associates,
isn't that right, Marco? Oh.
Lookee here. I found something.
So this is what we're
thinking, Marco.
You and your business associate work
for whoever Nathan Gould owed money to.
And you or someone else
who works for your boss
slipped a plastic bag over
Nathan's head this morning.
He's still alive, by the way.
Probably not gonna make it though.
Anyway, knowing that Nathan's never
going to make good on his debts,
your boss sent you over here to recoup
what you could in stolen valuables.
Sound about right?
Does he have anything else in his pocket,
a weapon, a vial of something to inject?
No. Why? What are you thinking?
Thinking we may have misjudged
our friend Marco here.
And if I'm right about that,
you are really gonna wanna
introduce us to your boss.
Hey. We got a…
Hey, Ray, we're here to ask some
questions about Nathan Gould.
I don't talk to cops.
Works for me. I'm not a cop.
And I wouldn't hate it if
this one didn't talk at all.
Oh, my goodness. Is that
the WhisperShoe Ultra?
Ugh. Electric card
shuffler. Those are so cool.
Does every table in
here have one of those?
Sure does. Oh, man, I
wish my kid was here.
He's going through a real
card phase right now.
Just the other day, he made me sit
through an entire YouTube video
on the ins and outs of
how this machine works.
Ain't that so random?
Everybody out.
Now!
Um…
What just happened?
It turns out these card shuffling machines
aren't as random as people think they are.
Right, Ray?
And that one in particular, the
WhisperShoe Ultra, is really not random.
In ways a disreputable house
could use to stack the odds.
Definitely not something
Ray wants getting out there.
You got stones.
I'll give you that.
Coming in here,
lobbing accusations.
Actually, Ray, I
think you heard wrong.
Thanks to my colleague here,
we're pretty certain that
you weren't involved in
the attack on Mr. Gould.
At least not the
one this morning.
Yes, see, when we found
that empty syringe on Marco,
we realized he was going to inject an
air bubble into Nathan's bloodstream.
So if Marco went there
to kill Nathan then,
that means you and your guys
didn't attack Nathan earlier.
Ain't that ironic? Hmm?
Sending a guy to commit a murder proves
that you didn't commit that murder.
Send that one to Alanis, right?
But that makes me wonder.
Why did you send Marco
with just an empty syringe?
I mean, injecting an air bubble
into someone's bloodstream,
that would make their death
look like natural causes, right?
But someone like you, in
the reputation business,
would want Nathan's
death to send a message.
Unless you had a way to
profit off of Nathan's death,
but only if it looked
like you didn't kill him.
185004606. Does that
number sound familiar?
It does. It did sound
familiar. Do you see that?
That number we saw at Nathan's, that
was Ray's Social Security number.
You see, before the
current randomized system,
Social Security numbers were
issued based on the state
where the applicant lived, and
when the application came in.
Now, I can roughly guess
your age, you know,
even with the ten or so years
that hard living put on you.
And thanks to that photo over there
of you marching in the Mummers parade,
which is an annual Philly thing, I'm
guessing you're from Pennsylvania.
Both of those make sense with
the number that we found.
But that begs the question.
Why would Nathan Gould have his
loan shark's Social Security number?
But you hate talking to cops,
so I'll answer this one for you.
You need someone's Social Security
number, and in many cases a notary,
which would explain
the ink smudge,
to make them the beneficiary
of your life insurance.
So, in other words, Ray, you forced
Nathan Gould to make you the beneficiary
on his insurance policy as
a way to pay off his loans.
And then because you
love to stack the deck,
you sent Marco to
make sure you collect.
I didn't force Nathan to do
anything. It was his idea.
Really? Care to elaborate?
I'm not getting the
sense that he does.
Mmm. Well, we wanna know who else
is mad enough to kill Nathan,
we need to find out whose name
he took off the life insurance.
See you, Ray.
Jessica, this is the old beneficiary form
from your father's life insurance policy.
We had the insurance
company pull it for us.
Until a few weeks ago, you were in line
to collect $100,000 when your dad died.
It made us wonder how you felt
about it when he changed the form.
This is the first I'm hearing my dad
even had a life insurance policy,
much less that my
name was on it.
Honestly, I'm surprised.
He wasn't exactly
good with money.
Sounds like you
two weren't close.
He and my mom split
when I was eight…
…over his gambling
habits, mostly. I think.
-Where's your mom now?
-Denver with my stepdad.
I came back out here…
…after school for work.
I tried to keep in touch
with my dad over the years,
but he never followed through.
Till a couple of months ago he
reached out, out of the blue.
He said he was going away soon, and he
wanted to make things right before he did.
We've seen each other more in the last
couple of months than we have in decades.
Jessica, when your dad was attacked, he
was carrying a pin on him in a gift box.
It was a ladybug. Does
that mean anything to you?
Oh. Um…
Ladybug was his nickname
for me as a kid.
Because he said I was
cute and good luck.
Here you go.
Well, then, if the
gift was for you,
you're the person your dad was
expecting to meet this morning.
Can I ask why you didn't show?
I did show, he didn't.
So you were at Dudley Market in
Venice around 7:45 this morning?
No, I was waiting for him at
Ground Wire in Toluca Lake.
That's where we were
supposed to meet.
Thanks, Jessica.
We'll reach out
when we know more.
-Nathan Gould's daughter?
-Yep, Jessica.
We're checking her alibi,
but we don't like her for it.
What you got there?
I just noticed the hotel across the
street from the café had security cameras.
So Lieutenant wanted me to check and
see if it caught the attack, but…
…nothing.
Anything interesting?
Well, Nathan and his daughter were
estranged for most of her life.
He'd reached out recently and reconciled.
They were supposed to meet this morning,
but for some reason they ended
up at two different cafés.
We're still figuring that out.
One thing she mentioned, he told her
he was planning to go away for a while.
So did he book any airline
tickets or hotel rooms
that would let us know
where he was going?
I've been going through his
credit card and bank statements.
I haven't seen anything
about travel plans.
Well, this is weird.
He had a subscription for a specialty dog
food that he canceled a few weeks ago.
We were just at his place. Did
you see any signs of a dog?
I did not.
I mean, I guess it's possible
the dog could have died,
but what if he gave it away?
That would make a lot more sense.
Go on.
Well, Nathan recently
reconciled with his daughter,
who he hasn't had any
contact with for years.
He settles his debts with a loan shark by
signing over his life insurance, right?
And then he tells his
daughter he's going away,
despite there being
no evidence of travel.
Put that together with
giving your dog away,
and I think this man was
planning on taking his own life.
That's what he meant by
going away for a while.
So somebody decides to kill the guy
right when he's about to kill himself.
But why?
-They didn't have any stevia.
-That's fine.
-Or oat milk.
-Less fine.
And I didn't think you'd
want their decaf. So…
So you went with hot water.
What a treat.
This is the hospital's
transplant coordinator.
They're discussing
organ donations.
-So he's officially brain dead?
-Yeah.
Some timing, huh?
This poor woman finally
reconciles with her father.
You okay?
You just, I don't know,
seem a little quiet for you.
Ava asked if there was
any news about her dad.
You haven't told her
about Arthur yet, huh?
-No.
-Hmm.
Well, even I've heard her say she
wants you to treat her like a grown-up.
Maybe take her at her word.
You think he was going
to take his own life?
You didn't know?
Oh.
Emmett. His dog.
Dad asked me to take care
of him while he traveled.
But why did he wanna die?
It's just a theory right now, but we think
he actually may have been protecting you.
Your dad owed money to some loan sharks.
They would have kept hurting him.
Eventually, probably
a lot worse.
Knowing how these people
operate, we think that
maybe they threatened
to come after you next.
So by changing his life insurance
policy, and offering to end his own life,
we think he was making sure you
didn't end up paying for his sins.
Yeah. Was your dad close with anyone
he would have talked to about this?
I… We had barely gotten
to know each other again.
I just… I don't know enough
about his life to say.
Did your dad know
you were pregnant?
How did you know?
Well, the smells in here
are driving you nuts.
I see that saltine peeking out of
your purse, and you've got ginger tea.
Been there a few times.
Congratulations.
Uh…
I told him the last
time we saw each other.
And… …he was so excited.
We joked about how much fun it is
to have a ton of doctor visits.
It was the one thing
we bonded over.
He told you about his injuries?
Um, his injuries? No, no.
Uh, the visits that he talked
about were to a cardiologist.
He said he recently had a whole
series of scans and tests.
Did he mention any
specific symptoms?
No. If anything, it
was the opposite.
He went out of his way to make sure
I knew that everything was fine.
Why would someone who's fine put
themselves through a series of tests?
Oh, we're like 20 minutes
early. I didn't even realize.
I know. I'm so impressed. I'm
not sure how we pulled that off.
I like this look on us.
I can get some alone time in the
hydroponics lab before homeroom.
-Bye, love you.
-Bye, have a good day.
The joys of being a dweeb.
I'm not sure what I'm supposed
to do, but I'll manage.
Ava.
Why don't you hang
back for a second?
I need to talk to
you about something.
So, at least as of a few weeks
ago, my dad was living in Nevada?
According to this Arthur guy.
Did he say how long he
was living there for?
No.
And all we know about Arthur
is that he's a landscaper?
I guess so.
I know it's not a lot of information
and we're gonna keep digging around.
I didn't want to
fill you in too early
'cause I didn't want you to get
your hopes up or be let down.
No, I-I want you to
tell me everything.
I know you do. I heard you, so that's
why I was filling you in on this.
Ooh. I gotta go to work.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah, I'm fine.
Are you sure? 'Cause if not, I'll
just tell him I'm not coming in today.
-No, no, no. Mom, it's okay.
-You're gonna play hooky...
I'm fine.
-Okay. I love you.
-I love you.
Can you find your way
to school from here?
Yeah, Mom, I'll
plug it into Waze.
Hey. Daphne, you got
Nathan Gould's phone?
Yeah, TID unlocked it.
Nathan got an email the
night before the attack,
claiming to be from
his daughter Jessica,
changing their meeting to
7:45 at the café in Venice.
Let me guess, this is not
Jessica's email address.
I checked, it's a fake.
Yeah, that would explain
why Nathan and Jessica
ended up sitting
at different cafés.
Whoever did this wanted Nathan
at that café, and alone.
Since Nathan and Jessica
had just reconciled,
he might not have even noticed the
email came from an unknown address.
Uh, Morgan, what are you doing?
There's an alarm set on
Nathan's phone for 8:01 a.m.
and the ringtone is
set to the duck sound.
That's what the café hostess
heard in the alleyway.
The killer wanted somebody to find his
body around 8 o'clock in the morning.
Long enough after the attack
to make sure he was brain-dead,
but soon enough to make sure
his organs were still viable.
I think Nathan Gould was
killed for his heart.
Robbed again, call the cops.
Good timing. Cops are here.
Sorry, I-I didn't see you.
You were saying something
about being robbed?
He's kidding about
calling the cops.
People steal things off the
bus when we're on calls,
even more so lately with all
the drug supply shortages.
We just write it up, but it's
not the controlled stuff.
That's locked up.
-It's not the controlled stuff, right?
-Albuterol. An asthma med.
We got more back at the house.
Is there something
we can help you with?
We had some questions about
the Nathan Gould call.
We're hoping you can walk
us through the timeline.
Sure, shoot.
Well, the 911 call came in around
8:01, 8:02. Is that about right?
Yeah, sounds right. Just after our
shift started, which was at 8:00.
And how long after that
for you to arrive on scene?
About five minutes.
Café's close.
And maybe another three minutes
after that to get a heartbeat back.
One last question. It's a doozy.
How long would a
victim have to be down
in order to guarantee
they'd be brain dead?
Eleven minutes, give or take.
Appreciate it.
You were right.
Course I was right.
Also, you should think about stocking
up on Albuterol if you need it.
They're having a theft
problem apparently.
Think I'm all good
there, but thank you.
Where's Soto?
She stayed back at the hospital
to ask a few more questions.
This attack was timed to turn Nathan
Gould into the perfect organ donor.
He was down for at least 11
minutes before help arrived.
I've been thinking about
it. I think there's more.
Nathan was in on it.
The cardiac work-up. He was making
sure his heart was in good shape.
Right. We already knew that he
was planning on killing himself.
Nathan had arranged with
someone to give them his heart.
But then he found out he was
gonna become a grandfather,
and he changed his mind, so
the killer had to kill him.
Unbelievable.
Everything okay?
Yeah.
You're not gonna blast the
old-timey car horn, are you?
More than one novelty
ringtone per case?
I don't think so. That
would be overkill.
Fair enough, because it seems
to be, our next question is,
"Who is Nathan Gould's heart going to?"
We find them, I think we find our killer.
'Scuse me. Hi, I
work with the police.
I saw you talking to
Jessica Gould yesterday
about her father's
organ donations.
-Yes, I remember you.
-Yeah.
Has it been decided where
Nathan's heart's going yet?
I'm, uh, sorry, I wouldn't know.
Aren't you the hospital's
transplant coordinator?
And you're on the
committee, right?
Yeah, they call you guys
"The God Committee."
You literally get to decide
who lives and who dies.
If you can't answer our
questions, then who can?
I…
I meant I don't know
off the top of my head.
Make an appointment with my office,
and I'll look it up for you.
Okay?
Any luck?
I didn't realize the question about
where a donor heart was going was scary,
but that woman seemed
afraid to answer.
Same deal with the
transplant surgeon.
I get the feeling these guys
are circling the wagons.
As if someone with a lot of
pull is keeping them quiet.
Mmm.
Because maybe they want
the heart for themselves.
One thing I did find out, Jessica
Gould has given her consent,
so Nathan's set to be taken
off life support tomorrow.
-Organs will be harvested then.
-Meaning if we're right,
and someone is forcing the
hospital to give them the heart...
It'd be good to
find out who first.
Hello.
W-What? Where is she?
I'll be right there.
Ava just got arrested.
U-Uh…
What the hell happened?
Are you okay?
You can uncuff her now, please.
Can't do that. Building owner
caught her vandalizing his property.
-Ava, it's one of your dad's murals.
-Yeah, I'm aware.
-Oh, honey, I am so sorry.
-Just leave me alone, okay?
Okay. So what happens now?
We take her in.
No, listen, that's not
necessary, all right?
Her dad painted that.
This is a family matter.
I will take care of it.
Tell that to the owner.
Guy wants to press charges.
That's the owner? How about this?
I go smooth it over with him,
we assure him the young
lady's gonna come back,
clean this mess up later,
and forget it ever happened.
-No paperwork for you.
-Sorry, Detective.
If the girl really
wanted to clean this up,
she had her chance
before you got here.
Come on, on your feet.
-No, don't touch my daughter, okay?
-Morgan, it's all right.
I know it's all
right! I'm all right!
-Ma'am!
-And don't call me ma'am. Okay, sir?
Don't call me ma'am right now.
I don't need that from you.
What I need from
you is to understand
that giving a 15-year-old
girl a criminal record
over some paint is
completely insane.
Can we all agree on
that? I mean, it's paint!
-Ava...
-Can we not here?
'Cause of her?
Ava, that woman has her
own problems to deal with.
No offense.
Yeah.
-Thanks, Gina.
-You got it.
"Treat her like a
grown-up," he said.
You're welcome?
Hi.
I'm sorry.
Oh, buddy, come here.
I messed up.
Sometimes I forget that there's a right
time to drop huge information on someone
and a wrong time, which would be right
before you send her off to school.
It wasn't that.
I know I said I wanted to know
everything, but I was wrong.
This is way worse
than not knowing.
What do you mean?
My dad's been alive this whole time
living his life one state over.
And with everything
you've been finding out,
I actually let myself believe he
cared, that he didn't abandon us.
I still believe that.
-How?
-Because I know who your dad was,
and we haven't heard his side
of the story yet, you know?
Maybe there's a reason
that he's had to stay away.
My whole life?
I can't for the life of me wrap my
mind around what that reason would be,
but the one thing I do know,
is that he loved you more than
anything in the whole world.
Okay.
You know, I'm actually
working on a case right now
where this father is
estranged from his daughter,
and once he came back
into the picture,
the only thing he cared
about was making it right.
And that's what
all this is about?
It's part of it.
I'm looking for somebody who
needs a heart transplant.
Somebody powerful enough to intimidate
an entire hospital to get it.
So, I figured I'd start
with their biggest donors.
-These guys.
-Mm-hmm.
You are looking at a who's
who of LA philanthropy.
What about him?
Carson Wood. Looks like
he's a big producer.
This photo wasn't from that premiere.
Do you see who's behind him?
Uh-huh.
Oh, my God. Mom, seriously,
do you live under a rock?
She's an actress. She's
in, like, everything.
-Right.
-Okay.
Anyway, this whole thing
went down about this dress.
She dissed the designer, and
they were going back and forth
for, like, weeks, but that
happened, like, over a year ago.
-Really?
-Mm-hmm.
Well, look at you.
And you didn't think you
were anything like me.
-I mean, first we get arrested together…
-Okay, okay.
-Can we look this guy up?
-Yeah.
Let's see.
Here he is.
Mmm, old.
Old.
-All these are old.
-Yeah. That one's definitely old.
Okay, so if you're right, this guy
hasn't been seen in public for months,
but he's posting old pictures
as if they're recent.
-Shady.
-Might be more than shady.
Maybe he's been hiding
the fact that he's sick.
-Everything good with Morgan?
-Yeah.
She had to visit Ava's school, clear
up a little truancy thing yesterday.
What's going on here?
Showed up just as Carson
Wood was about to head out.
I suggested he wait, his
people didn't like that.
So you decided to
block the driveway.
-Things are getting a little tense.
-Copy that.
Carson Wood.
Detectives Karadec and Forrester, LAPD.
Mind if we ask you a few questions?
If it gets you the hell out
of my driveway, ask away.
Make it quick.
Does the name Nathan Gould
mean anything to you?
Should it?
He's a murder victim whose
death we're investigating.
Never heard of him.
PS, I don't know if
you looked at me,
but I'm literally on my way
to get a heart transplant.
I'm not running
around killing people.
Well, uh, now that you mention
it, one of the reasons we're here
is to see if you're in the
market for a new heart, sir.
We believe Mr. Gould was killed so that
his would be available for transplant.
As for killing him yourself, I think
you could hire some people to do it.
I can't argue with that.
Hey, Karadec.
The GPS is set for the
airport, not St. Clair's.
Mr. Wood, would we be right that
you pressured St. Clair's Hospital
to bump you to the top
of their transplant list?
Maybe I did. Maybe I
didn't. Doesn't matter.
Got a better heart
waiting for me in Utah.
Wait, so you're saying you
don't want Nathan Gould's heart?
Is that the one at St. Clair's?
Doc said it wasn't a great match,
technical stuff, not my department.
And if that concludes our business, I'd
appreciate you getting out of the way.
Time's the one
thing I don't have.
Hey, how'd it go at the school?
I convinced him that 30
minutes in a holding cell
can serve as detention, but
whatever. That's not why I called.
I got a message from Soto.
St. Clair's Hospital called.
Oh, yeah, yeah, we know.
Carson Wood didn't even
need Nathan's heart.
Guessing it got put
back into the system?
Well, it would've,
but it's been stolen.
-How does someone steal a heart?
-That's what we're trying to figure out.
Hospital said everything went
normally with the organ removal.
They took the heart out of Nathan,
they packed up the transport.
That's when it was supposed to
be driven to another hospital.
But that's when everyone
lost track of it.
Someone with knowledge of the
process intercepted the heart
on its way out of the building.
So far, we haven't spotted anything
on the hospital surveillance,
but we're still looking.
How much time can pass between taking out
a heart and putting it into someone else?
Hospital says six hours tops,
two of which have already passed.
Then that's how
much time we have.
Someone this killer cares about is
about to get a heart transplant,
which means our best
chance to find the killer
is while that person is
still in a hospital bed.
After the patient's safe and sound,
our guy could be in the wind.
Now, it felt like the transplant
coordinator was hiding things yesterday.
Let's have her back
in for a conversation.
Now that the pressure's off from Wood,
maybe she'll be more forthcoming.
Yeah.
I'm starting to feel like
I should have a lawyer.
Oh, that's definitely
a way you could go,
given that we could charge you
with obstructing an investigation.
You might lose your job, so
lawyering up might be the smart move.
But, the truth is, we're not
looking to come after you.
We need to find Nathan Gould's
killer, and we need to find him now.
If you help us, we'd be inclined
to forget your role in all of this.
My role in this?
I didn't have a choice.
If we didn't find Mr. Wood a heart, he
would have cut off millions in funding.
That's money we use to
save countless lives.
We're not here to judge.
Okay.
We have reason to
believe that at one point
Nathan Gould and his
killer were cooperating.
Let's say Carson Wood never interfered.
Who would have gotten the heart then?
Nathan Gould left behind
a directed donation.
He named the person he
wanted his heart to go to.
And when Mr. Wood pressured
us to find him a heart,
the committee and I, we
invalidated Mr. Gould's directive.
-Whose name was on the directed donation?
-I don't know.
I deleted any record
on the hospital system.
You deleted the intended recipient's name,
and you don't even remember who it was?
It's not that I don't remember.
I didn't even look.
That person is something
I don't wanna think about.
So, their name should still be
on the transplant list, right?
Yeah.
Is this the information we got
from the transplant coordinator?
-The UNOS database?
-Yes.
You're looking at everyone waiting on a
heart in the southwestern United States.
Good, because that heart only has
about two hours of viability left.
How we gonna narrow this down?
Mm-mmm. No. Okay.
This one, this one, this one all live
too far away to get the heart in time.
These are the wrong blood type.
And since a key factor in
a heart match is body size.
You're out. You're out.
You're definitely out.
-There we go.
-Hey, good work, Morgan.
We can just reach out to
each of these hospitals...
No, we won't have to.
I gotta check something real
quick, but if I'm right,
I know where to find the killer.
Rosemary Caferri, 70 years old at Eaton
General, in end-stage heart failure.
-She's the one getting the heart.
-How did you know?
Because she was the only one left whose
profile said she was on Albuterol.
Yeah, paramedics said people were stealing
Albuterol because of a drug shortage.
I don't doubt that there
was a drug shortage,
but people were not stealing Albuterol,
one of the paramedics was, for his mother.
-That's what you had to check.
-That's right.
Caferri was Rosemary's
second husband's last name.
Her first husband was a Bishop, just like
one of our paramedics, Christopher Bishop.
He's Rosemary's son.
Christopher and Nathan knew each
other because of Nathan's injuries.
They must have shared their
struggles with each other.
So when Nathan decided
to end his life,
he offered to direct his
heart to Christopher's mother.
But then Nathan
changed his mind.
Which meant Christopher had to
take matters into his own hands.
He staged the messy
tables to make sure that
Nathan sat exactly
where he wanted him to…
…and then he dragged
his body into the alley.
And he set an alarm to make sure
that someone would find Nathan
at exactly the right time.
This even explains
the where and when.
Close enough to Christopher's firehouse
so he could show up to his shift
before the call came in
and give himself an alibi.
And he could make sure that he was
the paramedic who was taking the call.
He did all this to
save his dying mother.
Well, I'll have unis
posted to stop Christopher
and give Eaton
General a heads-up.
We're gonna stop her from
getting the heart, aren't we?
I had no idea. I swear.
I was only told that
a heart was available.
Does he know that you know?
He dropped off the heart
along with the paperwork
saying it was for
you, and he left.
Mr. Gould's directed donation
was still on file here too.
We had the hospital text
Christopher as your next of kin
and say they needed him to
come back, which he did.
We have him in custody now.
He's gonna go to
prison, isn't he?
Um…
You gonna let me see him?
Please.
I'll have my officers
bring him in.
Thank you.
Of course, you will go back on the
waiting list for another heart.
I really…
I don't really care
about the heart now.
Oh, my.
My sweet boy.
Hey, Mom.
Hi, sweetheart. Hey. Come here.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
-I love you so much.
-I love you too.
I tried. I tried.
♪ Hold on, I thought that
I could take it from here ♪
♪ Oh, I thought that I
was calm In the clear ♪
♪ Now it's getting harder… ♪
Police techs are all done with this. I
think your dad meant to give it to you.
♪ I fought the current… ♪
♪ …Running just
the way you would ♪
Actually, he already
gave me one just like it.
I think he meant to
give this one to her.
♪ And it's getting harder ♪
Can I ask you a question?
Your dad was absent your whole
life, and you let him back in.
How did you do that?
Guess that's how
my mom raised me.
You take care.
Angela Lee, 17,
congenital defect.
Got progressively worse. Eventually,
the docs couldn't repair it.
♪ Like falling water
coming down on me ♪
She got the heart.
♪ I never loved you fully…
Just the way you would ♪
Thank you.
See you tomorrow, Gillory.
-♪ You were like falling water… ♪
-♪ In the creek ♪
♪ …Coming down on me ♪
♪ I never gave you… Coming
from where you stood ♪
♪ But now I'm in the creek ♪
♪ Falling water in the creek ♪
♪ I was like falling
water in the creek ♪