[♪ "Give It Up For
The Machines" playing]
[whirring]
♪ I'm one hundred percent ♪
♪ I want you dead or alive ♪
-Come on, let me do it.
-Dude, hey, stop.
Come on. Let go.
[person 1] You're gonna
make me crash. No!
No.
Look, it's still filming.
[person 2] Is that a car?
[electronic screeching]
[both] Oh!
[♪ Theme music plays]
[♪ "One More Time" playing]
♪ She's drinking holy water ♪
♪ When she's thirsty for a gin ♪
How did you find me?
Well, when you wouldn't take my
calls, I had to stalk your reviews.
Turns out Steve from Pen Tech, very
satisfied with his Thursday lawn care.
Five stars.
What can I help you
with, Morgan? [sighs]
I was just wondering why you'd give me
your business card and then ghost me.
Roman asked me to check
on you and his kid.
I told him you were good.
The job is done.
So you and Roman
are what? Pen pals?
[grunts] Before I got the call, I
hadn't spoken to the man in 15 years.
So, someone you haven't spoken
with in over a decade calls,
and you drop everything to go
pick up a backpack in Nevada,
and then spy on my
daughter and me?
Yeah, well, it sure
seems that way.
Do you know where Roman is?
Roman called me from
a burner, all right?
I didn't even see him
when I got out there, so.
I want that backpack.
[chuckles] Then, why don't you ask
some of your cop friends about that?
-They can help you with it.
-Yeah, you're right.
I am friends with some
people in the LAPD…
[Arthur] Mm-hmm.
…Including the Financial
Crimes division.
I wonder if they would peek
into your business for me.
You know what? You probably
have nothing to worry about.
I'm sure you've reported
every single dollar
of your cash-only business
to the IRS, right?
[scoffs]
Good. I'll be in touch
with a time and a place.
Keep up the five-star
work, Arthur.
One of the things I'm most
proud of as your lieutenant
is this team's
commitment to its duty.
Every day, you tackle the toughest
crimes this city throws at you
with honor and tenacity.
And tenacious is also how I
would describe Captain Wagner.
His track record
speaks for itself.
Welcome, Captain Nick Wagner.
Thank you, Lieutenant Soto.
I know what it's like to
have a change in command
and all the uncertainties
that come with it,
which is why I want
to be clear up front.
I'm not here to step on toes.
My job is to support
you, so you can do yours.
I'm looking forward to
getting to know you better.
And to start that process, I'm gonna
be meeting with you individually.
It's nothing formal.
Just some talk.
And since my office is on three,
I was hoping Lieutenant Soto
wouldn't mind if I used hers
as home base for a few days.
-Whatever you need, Captain.
-Great.
-Thank you, everyone.
-[indistinct chatter]
Detective Ozdil,
free for a chat?
Sure.
Hey, you okay with all this?
Are you referring to getting
kicked out of my own office
or Captain Wagner in general?
Yes.
[laughs] I'm fine, really.
First few days of new command
is always a little bumpy.
Daphne. What do we
know about Wagner?
Well… [exhales] …I know
he's one of the Wagners.
-[Morgan] What does that mean?
-The Wagners are an LAPD dynasty.
Grandfather, father,
uncle. All made captain.
His dad retired a decade
ago and went into politics.
I heard his dad pulled some strings
to get his son into command.
Must be nice to have
that kind of in.
Hey, guys. I just got a call.
Dead body found at
Shay Ranch Pond.
Go check it out.
-[Karadec] What are we looking at?
-Victim was shot in the chest. No ID.
Car is registered to a
Tori Nolan. Thirty-one.
We pulled a pic from the DMV.
We think the car might have
been stolen by the vic.
No, she didn't steal Tori
Nolan's car. She is Tori Nolan.
Looks like Tori had
some work done recently.
Botox, microplaning, threads,
cheek fillers, eyelash extensions.
She chopped her hair
off and dyed it brown.
Sounds like she went through a lot
of trouble to change her appearance.
Yeah, either she succumbed to the
pressures of being a woman in LA,
-or she was hiding from someone.
-Mmm.
Hey, these bullet wounds definitely
came from a small caliber, maybe a .380.
[Morgan] Those are steam burns,
but look, these seem chemical.
[Karadec] There's red staining
on her clothes and skin too.
None of it looks like blood.
[exhales] Some kind of dye?
All the windows are missing.
Might have been shot out.
Looks like Tori
had a storage unit.
Hold on. Why is this still dripping?
The rest of the dash is dry.
Okay.
So Tori Nolan changed
her face, carried a gun,
only to get shot, burned,
and dumped into a pond.
Well, whoever she was hiding from,
it looks like they found her.
Hula Hound. And you know
about this place because…
I know all the bars in
LA with trivia nights.
Don't judge me. Knowing random facts
is the whole point of a pub quiz.
-They love it.
-Mmm.
Maybe they don't love
it because, you know,
I'm banned from most of them,
but that's not why we're here.
We're here because you said
Tori had a storage unit, right?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
Ta-da.
Nobody's popping into the
Hula Hound for no reason,
and I'm thinking Tori's
reason was proximity.
Yeah, it's as good a
place to start as any.
Tori's last known
address was in Koreatown,
but landlord said she hasn't
lived there for years.
-Let's go see what she was storing.
-Let's.
[♪ Suspenseful music playing]
[♪ Music ends]
-What do these mean?
-I don't know yet.
There was no laptop
in Tori's car.
Maybe the killer took it.
Whoa. Look at these.
[Morgan] Ha.
All these match up with the
places on the filing cabinets.
Tori was traveling the world
under assumed identities.
Who was this girl?
Carmen Sandiego?
[exhales] It's gonna take days
to piece all that back together.
We might not have to.
Okay, so everywhere Tori traveled,
there was some sort of big scandal.
Crystal Lake had this
massive E. coli outbreak
from faulty water
pipes in July of 2018.
Late 2023, an American
au pair agency
was running a human trafficking
ring out of Cambodia.
And do you see these
red symbols right here?
Those are editing marks.
And these numbers, they're dates
and issue numbers from a magazine.
Tori wasn't an international
woman of mystery.
She was an
investigative reporter.
Well, whatever story she was covering
now might have gotten her killed.
Find anything in Tori
Nolan's financials?
Oz.
-Oz.
-[clears throat] Uh. Sorry.
Okay, you've been acting weird ever
since your meeting with the captain.
-I thought you said it went well.
-Yeah, it did.
I think. I don't know.
-You'll see when you meet with him.
-[phone rings]
[Karadec] Daphne,
what'd you find out?
Okay, I cross-referenced
the location,
dates, and issue
numbers you sent.
Morgan was right. Tori was a
journalist for Takedown Magazine,
an online publication
known for its exposés.
[Oz] According to her editor, Tori
always wrote under a pseudonym.
Apparently she got doxed after an article
she published in her college newspaper.
Having her private information
blasted all over the Internet
was so traumatic she
dropped out of school.
Did the editor know what Tori
was currently investigating?
No, but that wasn't unusual.
She said Tori would drop off
the grid when following a story.
Good news is they insisted on
getting proof of life from her
whenever she was undercover,
so I'm sending that to you now.
[phone buzzes]
[Morgan] This is recent. She had
the same nails on when she died.
There's no grow-out
around the cuticles.
But this picture could have
been taken anywhere, Morgan.
There's no landmarks or anything
else in the background we can use.
Not true.
You got a poodle dog.
There's literally no poodle.
Okay, I get it.
We're looking for poodle dog plants, but
how do you know this is the right area?
Because there was a fire in these
hills just a few months ago.
Poodle dog bushes are
pyrophytes. Fire followers.
Their seeds lay dormant until the
intense heat of a fire wakes them up.
Based on the size of the plant
in this picture she took.
This location fits the timeline.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, look. Look,
we're getting close. See?
Okay, stop. Check it out.
-She took the picture right here.
-[Karadec] Hmm.
Okay, if I am Tori, I am not taking
no trespassing for an answer.
If you're Tori?
Well, why would I? Any bozo can
buy a sign, tack it to a fence.
Morgan, whoever put up that
sign, they might mean it.
Tori's embedded herself in some dangerous
situations with some dangerous people,
so we don't know what we
might be walking into here.
[♪ "Wanna Go Wild" playing]
What is this place?
Oh, you don't have a teenager.
This is a content house.
[chuckles]
[screams, laughs]
These guys all live here and shoot
videos for their streaming platforms.
Could explain
Tori's enhancements.
She'd have to be camera ready 24-7 if she
was going undercover as an influencer.
[Karadec] Mmm. Well, this isn't really on
par with the other stories she went after.
What was she investigating here?
Can I help you?
I'm Detective Karadec. This
is Morgan Gillory, LAPD.
You recognize this woman?
That's Darla.
She lives here.
Is she okay?
No, unfortunately
she's not. She's dead.
Hey. Anyone else want to
take a dip in the gel-cuzzi?
Uh, that's a no?
[creator 1] Darla…
Well, Tori, I guess,
she'd only been in the house a
few weeks, but everyone liked her.
-What kind of content did she make?
-ASMR videos.
Her channel wasn't doing
great, but it was growing.
[Karadec] When's the
last time you saw Tori?
[creator 3] A day
ago, maybe two.
When everyone's filming, we
tend to lose track of time.
[Karadec] Do you know anyone
who would want to hurt her?
[creator 2] No, we've all
had creeps in our comments,
but Tori never mentioned
anyone she was concerned about.
Do you think one of her
followers killed her?
Well, we're not
ruling anything out.
Thanks. We'll be in touch.
[sighs] No one claims
to know what happened.
You got anything?
Just that these kids are under
a crazy amount of pressure.
You know, that bit
that Prénkz was doing?
A six-ounce box of
gelatin makes two cups.
A standard kiddie pool
is about 400 gallons.
That's 3,360 boxes
just to fill it up.
I'm guessing from set-up
to clean-up, that's what?
Thirty hours of work
for a 30-second video.
That's barely gonna move the
needle on his goal chart.
This guy Phineas is running
this place like a sweatshop.
-Okay. Looks like we found Prénkz's lair.
-[toy squeaks]
Red dye?
Like the red dye that
was all over Tori's body?
[creator 3] What are you gonna
say? You don't know what happened.
-Just let me talk!
-Play it cool. Okay, we're going in.
Something you guys
wanna tell us?
-We did it. We did it. We killed her.
-Uh. It was an accident.
One of you shot Tori?
She was shot?
How do you think you killed her?
Like that.
Oh, no, no, no, no,
no, no. No. Karadec!
-You might wanna turn back.
-What…
-[Morgan screams] Oh!
-[Prénkz] Oh, geez.
Darla, um, Tori leaves the house every
Wednesday afternoon to do errands.
Since we knew she'd be in her car, Prénkz
and I set up a situation in her back seat.
What kind of a situation?
The devil's toothpaste.
Exactly what happened to
Detective Karadec, except bigger.
Show me.
[Raquel chuckling on laptop]
[Prénkz chuckles] Get ready.
[chuckles] This is
gonna get so many hits.
[creator 3] Sorry, Darla,
but you asked for this.
-[explosion]
-[creator 3] Oh, my God.
-[Prénkz] What do we do?
-I don't know.
[Prénkz] Hurry, the car's still
rolling. We need to get outta here.
[creator 3] Just
stop filming, Prénkz!
Did you check on her?
Well, we freaked out, so we
called Phineas. [exhales]
He runs Cloud House.
Phineas said Darla was
fine but really mad.
She was just gonna go
for a drive and cool off.
No, with a force like that,
Tori was definitely concussed.
She wasn't driving anywhere.
You guys, that was a
really dangerous prank.
I know. I didn't think it'd
be that big of an explosion.
All right, what was in it?
Just dye, soap,
yeast, and peroxide.
-How much peroxide?
-A lot.
A lot. Okay, well, that
explains the steam burns.
When hydrogen
peroxide meets yeast,
it produces a lot of
oxygen and a lot of heat.
The oxygen forms
a fabulous foam,
and the higher the peroxide
percentage, the bigger the boom.
[explosion]
It also explains the lack
of blood in Tori's car.
The peroxide would
have cleaned it up.
Mmm.
In the video, you said
Tori asked for it. Why?
She stole my L3 protein powder.
Live Laugh Lift.
I was supposed to do an
exclusive promo for them.
I'm the only content creator in the
country to get L3 before the launch.
It was gonna bring a ton
of traffic to my channel,
but Tori stole the powder
before I could film it.
Why would she do that?
Probably because her own
channel wasn't doing so well,
so she wanted to sabotage mine.
Those morons could've killed
Tori with that dumb prank,
but I don't think they shot
her. I think someone else did.
Look, red dye and tire tracks
extend down into those weeds.
I think this is
where Tori was shot.
[car approaches]
Wonder who would've
wanted to do that.
[tires squeal]
Let's get back to the
car. I'll put out a BOLO.
Hold on… [chuckles] …one second.
Did you just try and
chase after a sports car?
It was an instinct.
Your instinct was that you could
catch up to a twin-turbo V-8?
-Morgan.
-This might be the best day of my life.
[Karadec] Uh-huh.
I just wanna thank you
for that beautiful gift.
[Karadec] Okay.
[door opens]
[door closes]
We didn't know
you'd be home early.
Clearly. What is this?
Oh, a PB and J.
Cookies are not bread.
Argh. Air patrol's out looking
for a guy, so I got a little time.
That's so cool. You should
have asked for a fly along.
Mmm. I prefer to do
my barfing on land.
[Chloe cries]
Hey, uh, Elliot, can
you go grab your sister?
I thought you were
hiring a babysitter.
Can you just go get her?
Please? You're her favorite
person in the whole wide world.
I know you're just saying
that to manipulate me.
Is it working?
Yes, but only because it's
true. She's a big Elliot fan.
-Aren't we all?
-Mmm. He's all right.
Argh. Gross.
The other reason I wanted
to swing by home was
to let you know that I tracked
down Arthur this morning.
-The guy who knows my dad?
-Mm-hmm.
Does he know where he is?
No, but he did agree to
give me his backpack.
-Okay, let's go get it.
-Hey… [chuckles] …hold on a second.
We haven't figured out
a time or a place yet,
but when we do, I
will get the backpack.
-I can't go with you?
-No.
-Why not?
-We don't even know who this guy is.
I'm not letting him
anywhere near you. No.
-But, Mom, what if he has information or…
-Ava.
It's not a negotiation.
[softly] Okay.
I'll keep you posted.
[Daphne] Phineas's orange
Lamborghini wasn't hard to find.
Highway patrol picked him
up in Ventura an hour ago.
So far he's had nothing to say.
Keeping his mouth shut is probably the
smartest thing he's done in a while.
[Daphne] Mm-hmm.
I'm not interrupting, am I?
No, Detectives Oz and Karadec
are letting Phineas sweat a bit
before starting
their interrogation.
Good. So Detective
Forrester has a minute.
I hope you don't mind, but I stopped
at your desk and I couldn't resist.
No, that's what
they're there for.
I never had a sweet tooth…
[exhales] …until I joined the force.
Now I can't go a day
without having sugar.
Oh, well, there is worse habits.
True, and there's some habits
that serve you well on your job.
I saw your file, Detective.
Have you ever considered
sitting for the sergeant's exam?
[stutters] Y-Yeah, I thought
about it, but nothing serious.
You should. I have a friend
that used to be a test assessor.
He can give you tips, get you
the right study materials.
That's great, but you know,
I'm really happy here and...
No, of course you are,
but it never hurts to
be curious about
broadening your horizons.
I'm sure Lieutenant
Soto would agree.
-I do.
-I love to hear it.
-I'll set it up.
-Thank you.
What did I miss?
Nothing. They haven't started
the interrogation yet,
but I'm glad you
popped in, Morgan.
I was hoping we could sit down
and have that talk and see...
Ye… Oh. You know
what, I-I… Great.
I can't though 'cause I gotta
give this my attention, so later.
[Phineas] Maybe someone can
tell me what this is about.
Maybe.
Of course.
-Let's talk about Tori Nolan.
-Who?
The reporter you shot and
then dumped in a pond.
We're thinking you found out
she was embedded at your house.
You were worried about the story
she'd run, and so you got rid of her.
You mean Darla?
So the details are
familiar but not the name.
I d-didn't know that was Darla.
I-I definitely didn't know
that she was a reporter.
Why was she at Cloud House?
We were wondering the same
thing, but then we had a look
at your financials.
-$200,000 sports car.
-Mmm.
Several stays at the
Ibiza Four Seasons.
You work the kids hard, pay them
way less than they're earning,
then skim all the
profits for yourself.
That sounds like a story to me.
Any money that I take from the
creators is for their room and board.
Right. 50K a month each.
Seems a bit steep,
doesn't it, Phineas?
Even by Los Angeles standards.
-I gotta do a quick mic pop.
-A what?
[Morgan] I need
to see his watch.
[Karadec] Watch, please.
Thank you.
Check out the joints. There's
corrosion in there, you see that?
That's what happens when titanium comes
in contact with concentrated peroxide.
Ooh. You see, after the explosion,
Tori was covered in that, Phineas,
and you must have gotten a
good bit of it on yourself too
when you moved her body
from the driver's seat.
You were in Tori's car after
Raquel and Prénkz foamed it.
You're the one who shot
her and then moved the car.
[inhales] I moved the body,
but I swear I did not kill her.
Uh. There was so
much foam everywhere.
I had no idea that she was
shot until I got to the pond.
If you didn't kill her,
why'd you move the body?
Because I'd lose the
lease on the house.
Landlord's been trying to
evict Cloud House for months.
The neighbors hate us,
and if they kick us out,
I'd have to shut the
entire thing down.
-Can you prove that you didn't kill her?
-I can.
[stutters] Do you guys
know what bots are?
Fake account holders
on social networks.
People use them to pad
their followers. Yeah.
Exactly. Darla's number...
Tori's numbers were terrible,
and right before Prénkz
and Raquel came running up,
I was in my office buying bots
to pump up Tori's channel.
Which you never would have done
if you were planning on getting
rid of her a minute later.
Exactly.
Damn it.
We booked Phineas for evidence
tampering and illegal transport.
He offered up Tori's bag as a
bargaining chip for leniency.
Said he took it to keep
anyone from ID'ing her.
Somebody who loves cars didn't think we
could find her through her VIN number?
[Oz] Come on.
Great. Tori has state-of-the-art
encryption on here.
Not surprising for
someone with her job.
[Morgan] Raquel was right. Tori
did steal the protein powder.
But why? I checked Tori's
Cloud House channel.
-She never advertised it.
-Yeah, well, why would she?
She didn't actually
care about her numbers,
which means she wouldn't
sabotage somebody else's.
Morgan, how about this?
You recognize anything
in these lab results?
Yeah, nothing super
interesting, except castoreum.
-What's that?
-Beaver butt secretion.
It's a flavoring agent.
So is ethyl
methylphenylglycidate.
Artificial strawberry.
I know that from my weekly fight
with my kids in the cereal aisle.
Yep.
Strawberry.
Okay, so Tori wasn't
investigating the content house,
she was investigating
the protein powder. Why?
Yeah, the woman made a career
out of exposing major scandals.
She covered corruption.
-She saved animals from abuse.
-[horse whinnies]
[Morgan] She took on big
oil. And then protein powder?
Going after a small-time
product doesn't make any sense.
We said she was doxed, right?
Yeah, she wrote an
article about a classmate
who was running a
test-taker-for-hire business.
He cyberbullied her for revenge.
His name was, um, Robert Romano.
Well, I think he
goes by Bobby now.
-Thank you.
-Robert Romano?
Whoa, my full name.
That's what my mom calls me
when I'm in trouble. [chuckles]
-Wait, am I in trouble?
-No, we just wanna talk.
It's an impressive
operation you got here.
Thanks, man. Yeah, it's
exciting times at L3.
Yeah, our pre-orders are flying.
I'm trying to stay humble,
but I got a feeling
Live Laugh Lift is gonna
revolutionize the fitness industry.
Really?
Oh. 'Cause it kind of looks
like you're just repackaging
a bunch of bulk protein powder from
China and slapping your label on it.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no. [chuckles]
It's way more than that.
-Is it?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
L3 is a movement, okay? This
guy gets it. I can tell.
Bobby, San Dimas delivery
is gonna be late.
The truck got a flat.
If you two are from the health department,
our certifications are in compliance.
Don't worry, they're not health
inspectors. They're just cops.
Guys, this is Lamar Vulpis.
He's my operations manager.
Can we help you with something?
Yeah, we were hoping to
take a look around, Lamar.
Sure, you got a warrant?
I don't know. Is there something
here that warrants a warrant?
Whoa, no, no. We don't… They don't
need a warrant, dude. [chuckles]
-We're just talking, right?
-That's right.
Yeah. Look, Lamar,
I'll call San Dimas.
-You got it, Boss.
-[Bobby] Okay, thank you.
I know, he seems pretty tough,
right? That's just his job.
I couldn't run the
place without him.
Hmm -Yeah, I don't doubt it.
I mean, your other businesses
were all scams, right?
Designer shoe company that turned
out to be low-end knockoffs.
The concert app that was
kicking out fraudulent tickets.
Oh, yeah. That one got you
pinched for wire fraud.
You did two years
in prison, right?
Mm-hmm. Yeah, the feds got interested
in you because of an anonymous tip,
but she wasn't so
anonymous for you, was she?
-Yeah, you're talking about Tori Nolan?
-Hmm.
-She just has it out for me.
-Oh, yeah?
You think it had anything to do
with the time you doxed her so bad
she had to drop out of school?
I really regret that.
I was a stupid kid, and
I did stupid things.
[Bobby sighs]
Please.
So, why are you
asking about Tori?
Well, Bobby, um, she's dead.
[huffs] That's heavy.
[Karadec] Mm-hmm.
Wait, you don't think I had
something to do with it?
Strong and smart.
-He's the whole package.
-Thanks.
When's the last time you
had contact with Tori?
Well, she called me a week ago.
She told me she was
this big reporter now,
and she was gonna take me
down for good this time.
-Well, how was she gonna do that?
-I have no idea.
I hung up on her.
That kind of negative energy is not
what Live Laugh Lift is all about.
It's nonsense anyway,
because L3 is legit. [scoffs]
Okay, so that must have really pissed you
off, that she was trying to take it down.
I wouldn't hurt anyone.
You can look around all
you want. I'm an open book.
-Morgan…
-Karadec, he's an open book.
-Yeah, I'm cool with it.
-He's cool with it.
He was at a gym across
town when Tori was shot.
Because I never skip leg day.
-Can you verify that?
-Yes.
Oh, you meant, like, an alibi.
Yeah, my pump partner
can vouch for me.
Oh, God, this keeps
getting better.
I'll check out Bobby's alibi,
see if the gym had cameras.
You're saying you don't trust
the word of his pump partner?
Well, even if his story is true,
it doesn't mean he had nothing
to do with Tori's death.
-He could've hired someone to kill her.
-Yeah, maybe.
His nav app doesn't have
him going to Cloud House,
however it does say
that he stops by a place
called Serenity Arms
at least once a week.
-[Karadec] Mmm.
-It sounds like a cult.
No, actually, it's a
halfway house for ex-cons.
Maybe Bobby stayed there
after he got out of prison.
Might be a good place
to get some confirmation
as to how reformed
he actually is.
[phone buzzes]
Great, I'm being summoned for
my meeting with the captain.
No, thank you. It's
good timing though.
I gotta grab my car from the station
and deal with a family thing.
Everything okay?
Oh, yeah. Never any drama
in the Gillory household.
Oh, never.
[knocks on door]
Detective Karadec, come in.
Don't worry, it's not yours.
I wasn't worried.
Nor should you be. I
didn't even read your file.
Your reputation
precedes you. Please.
Morgan Gillory,
tell me about her.
I thought this
meeting was about me.
It is, but she's your partner,
and I think we can both admit
that it's unconventional
and really not your
style, Detective.
So, you have read my file.
I don't need to read anything to know
that you're a badge-and-oath kind of guy.
But Morgan, she doesn't strike me
as somebody who stays in her lane.
[scoffs]
Well, we work well together
-if that's what you're getting at.
-You certainly do.
Your case rate has increased
ever since you two teamed up.
You were smart to claim
her as your partner.
You don't know Morgan if you
think anyone can claim her.
Mmm.
[Karadec sighs]
Was there something else
you needed, Detective?
No.
Hey, heard back from the guy that
runs Serenity Arms, Gavin Tillman.
-He's available to meet.
-Hmm. Let's go.
[♪ "Sad Sandra" playing]
[Arthur grunts]
I think you forgot something.
-I wanna talk first.
-About what?
This is very simple.
You've got the backpack.
You give me the backpack.
End of transaction.
[scoffs]
So, you really think that,
uh, whatever's in that bag
will give you answers and
not just more questions?
You didn't look in it, did you?
Why?
I don't know, I thought
about it, you know?
But I know Roman, okay?
The dude is solid,
and he wouldn't just
up and disappear from
his people for no reason.
So, I keep asking myself, what
the hell happened 15 years ago
that was bad enough to
make a good man run?
And to be quite honest, I'm not sure
if I wanna know the answer to that.
Do you?
Yes, so give us the bag.
[stutters] What are you… How
did you know where I was?
The family tracker app. You can
see my location, I can see yours.
-No, we're not doing this, okay?
-No, Mom, stop.
We didn't get the bag yet.
You can go, but I'm not
leaving here without it.
[chuckles]
No, it's…
You look just like your dad when he's
about to start digging into something.
-You really knew my dad?
-Oh, yeah.
You know, him and me, we went way
back. I mean, we came up together.
We were practically inseparable.
And he spent so much
time at my house,
ate so many meals, that my mom
started calling him Plates.
[chuckles]
We need your help.
I don't understand why my
dad left me, but I need to.
[inhales] All right,
look, I get it, okay?
When I heard his voice, it was like
time hadn't passed, but it had.
I mean 15 years is a
long time to disappear.
And I miss him.
My mom's like ridiculously smart,
so if there's a clue in that bag,
she'll find it and then
maybe we'll find him.
Please?
All right. Okay.
I'll get it to you.
Wonderful. Ready?
-I know you didn't want me here...
-Not another word.
-No. Do you see? I helped.
-Ava, stop it.
-He wouldn't have given it to us if I...
-We will talk about this later.
Right now, I am so angry I don't trust
anything that would come out of my mouth.
[Oz] What can you tell
us about Bobby Romano?
I've run this place 22 years,
and I can honestly say I've
never met anyone like Bobby.
-Is that a good thing?
-[Gavin] Oh, yeah.
See, a lot of people land here,
they're fresh out of prison.
They're mad at the world.
They want to burn it all down.
But not Bobby.
He dusted himself off and
decided to make the world better.
With protein powder?
[chuckles] Okay, yeah, I know it
sounds silly, but Bobby believes in it.
What's the harm?
Well, if Bobby felt so
strongly about his business,
how far do you think
he'd go to protect it?
What are you asking?
A woman's been murdered.
Um, Tori Nolan.
She and Bobby had a bit of a
past. Do you know that name?
Bobby mentioned Tori a few
times when he first got here,
said that she actually
helped put him in prison,
but he wasn't angry about it.
Like I said, Bobby left all
that behind when he got out.
But then… she threatened him.
-He told us she called him.
-[Gavin] Oh, she did more than that.
She showed up at his warehouse.
She said not only would
she ruin his launch,
but she'd see to it that he
went back to prison for life.
What did Tori find out?
Bobby wouldn't say.
But when he missed his last group
session that morning, I called him.
He was frantic.
He said… [huffs] …"I should have
taken care of this ten years ago."
Look, I thought he meant get a
restraining order or something.
I didn't think he'd hurt her.
-LAPD.
-Bobby, open the door.
How long has Bobby been dead?
ME says a few hours.
An employee told us that Bobby was
very upset after we spoke with him,
sent everyone home early and
locked himself in his office.
And we're guessing that's where he
swallowed enough pills to overdose?
-[Oz] Mm-hmm.
-What'd he take?
It's a new party drug
called Dazzle Kitty.
It's a euphoria inducing stimulant like
ecstasy, but five times more potent.
In large quantities, it
can cause cardiac arrest,
which we believe is
what happened to Bobby.
The L3 was a cover for
shipping the drugs.
We found bags of it hidden
in the powder canisters.
Now, most of these are real companies
just purchasing protein powder,
but this code, 44889,
corresponds to the orders that
had bags of drugs in the powder.
We assume they're being trafficked
to distributors around the country.
We also found a .380 pistol in his desk
that matches the gunshot wounds on Tori.
-We're sending to ballistics for testing.
-[Morgan] Beef and barley soup!
Beef and barley soup.
Saying it again doesn't
make it any clearer, Morgan.
Somebody wants us to think that
Bobby killed Tori and then OD'd.
-But you don't buy it.
-No, when we were here earlier,
Bobby couldn't wait
to show us around.
Now he's not the brightest
bulb, but even he's smart enough
to not want cops digging around
in a place where there's drugs.
-Plus, the soup.
-Soup?
I opened his mouth and
I smelled inside of it,
and it definitely smells
like beef and barley soup.
And he dribbled a little
bit on his T-shirt.
You can see it there.
That wasn't there before.
This guy ate the soup and died
right around the same time.
-Okay?
-There's no soup container.
We checked all the
trash cans, nothing.
We also checked the sink drain.
-Is that…
-A carrot?
Mm-hmm. And a half-melted
capsule of Dazzle Kitty.
So, either Bobby drugged
his own soup, ate it,
and then high as a kite,
dumped the rest down the drain,
magicked the container
away before passing out…
-Or…
-Or someone else put the drug in the soup.
And that someone
wants us to think
that the drug operation and Tori's
murder were all Bobby's doing.
And now that he's dead,
it's a closed case.
Yes. I think whoever killed
Bobby also killed Tori
and masterminded
the whole thing.
Then who's the brains?
[siren wailing]
-[officer 1] Freeze!
-[officer 2] Hands up!
Gavin Tillman, get out of the
vehicle with your hands up.
[indistinct chatter
on walkie-talkie]
I hope you're curious how
we found out about this,
'cause I've been pretty
excited to tell you.
At first, we thought, "Oh,
for sure, it's Lamar."
Yeah, we brought him in for questioning,
but he wouldn't give anything up.
He's loyal, isn't he?
I'll give him that.
But Bobby didn't get
the same courtesy.
Lamar was very quick to tell
us that he met Bobby in prison,
and Bobby brought him into
his L3 drug operation.
See, the problem there is that
neither of those things are true.
A, Bobby had no idea there
was a drug operation,
and B, they weren't in
prison at the same time.
They sure weren't.
After they got out, they spent time
at your halfway house, Serenity Arms.
Once we made that connection,
Lamar was much more cooperative.
[Morgan] Oh, yeah,
he gave you right up.
Yeah, but Lamar insisted he had nothing
to do with Tori and Bobby's deaths,
and he had the
alibis to prove it.
He sure did. No, that was all you. But
you were honest with Karadec and Oz.
Bobby did tell you about
Tori in his sessions,
and Bobby did talk to
you about Tori's threats.
[Karadec] Bobby had no idea what
Tori was talking about, but you did.
Tori reaching out to
Bobby blew her cover.
You knew exactly
where to find her.
[Morgan] So, you
waited at Cloud House,
and when Tori's car came
into view, you shot her.
[screams]
You couldn't have predicted
the state she'd be in,
but you just used it
to your advantage.
At that point, Bobby
was a liability.
Lamar said he called you right
after we showed up to the warehouse.
You needed to tie up loose ends.
When we talked to you at the halfway
house, Bobby was already dead.
-I want a lawyer.
-Oh, I bet you do.
Maybe more than one.
Go deep on that bench.
[Karadec] Spoke to the
editor of Takedown Magazine.
They're gonna finish Tori's last
article and put out a tribute issue.
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
Aw, I like that. The world
needs more Toris in it.
Yeah.
I'm gonna get out of here
before the captain ambushes me.
You know, you can't
avoid him forever.
Um. I have owed
the Culver City Public
Library $3.50 since the '90s,
so, I'm gonna beg to differ.
Mmm. You know there's always some growing
pains when a new person joins a team.
There is?
I remember nothing but absolute
delight when I came on board.
Oh.
See ya.
-[car door slams]
-Hey, you need some help?
No, I'm good.
She just needs some
coolant or she gets cranky.
-Not cranky, assertive.
-[chuckles]
I thought you were gonna
come by for a chat today.
Nah, I made that up to buy some
time so I could get out of it.
Plus, I was busy, you
know, doing my job.
Yeah, you like working here.
-Is that a question?
-No, that's a surprised observation.
-Why surprised?
-I just heard some rumors
you don't respond
positively to authority.
I don't respond positively to
authority that abuses their power.
Is that how you see me?
I don't know.
I haven't decided on that yet.
Well, what have you decided on?
[inhales] Um…
I've decided I'd like you to
get your car out of my way
so I can go home to my kids.
All right, Gillory.
Let me have it.
All right… [clears
throat] …Let's see.
You're from a legacy
family, right?
So, that tells me you
could take the easy road,
but you choose not to because you want
to prove to everybody that you can.
And that's admirable, but
it also makes you smug.
You like being captain. You like
the respect, like the authority.
Love the boots.
But you also miss
being in the field
a little bit more than
you thought you would.
You like to be in the action, right?
'Cause that makes you feel important.
Anything else?
Mm-hmm.
You like to keep people guessing
if your interest in them is real
or just a way to get
something you want.
Pretty good.
You got two out of the three.
Oh, yeah? Which one
did I get wrong?
I'm not as good at
this game as you are.
But I've learned
one thing for sure.
You give Morgan
Gillory a puzzle,
she won't stop thinking
about it until it's solved.
Good night, Morgan.
[car door slams]
Hey.
You're still mad.
[sighs] Yeah, I am.
I love you more than
anything in this world,
so I'm gonna do whatever I
need to do to keep you safe.
If I say no to you, I
expect you to listen.
-But nothing bad happened.
-That's not the point.
I told you no, and you went off and
did whatever you wanted to do anyway.
-Sounds familiar.
-Excuse me?
If you don't agree with someone,
you never listen to them.
-What would you have done if you were me?
-[grunts]
-Yeah, exactly.
-Ava.
You're not wrong, okay? The
difference is I am an adult.
-I get to make those choices. You don't.
-You're such a hypocrite.
Okay, I'm glad the SAT prep is paying
off, but let's watch the tone, please.
I'm serious. You're
being unfair.
I'm being your mom. Ava, I
make mistakes all the time.
This isn't one of them, okay?
-And actions have consequences.
-What does that mean?
It means I need to think about
how much I want to involve you
in the stuff with your dad
until I can trust you again.
You're never gonna trust me
enough because you don't want to.
I'm sorry, trust is something
that you earn from a p...
No, stop. You think you're
some cool mom or something,
but you're really
just embarrassing.
[door slams]
[sighs]
[♪ "Pieces" playing]
♪ Hey there, child ♪
♪ Pick up the pieces,
pick up the pieces ♪
[knocks on door]
♪ …'cause I've seen everything ♪
♪ Oh, I know 'cause
I've seen everything ♪