You guys made mistakes,
I've fixed 'em. Let's not
make a big deal out of this.
What mistakes did you see?
I have a compulsion
to put things right.
If I see a mistake,
I need to correct it.
Ta-da.
I have an IQ of 160.
The technical term
is high potential intellectual.
Means you have
advanced cognitive abilities.
Come do this full-time.
We need you.
-You know this woman?
-I'm his partner.
We're not partners.
She's actually
just a consultant.
When you and I split up,
we agreed
we're gonna remain a family
no matter what.
Ludo thinks of you
as his daughter.
-It's not the same.
-Your father loved you.
That's why he left.
I need you to find someone.
Roman Sinquerra.
-He vanished 15 years ago.
-You got a deal.
- You made this for your dad?
-If you find him.
It turns out Roman was working
as an FBI informant.
"Two hours
to make your move."
Sounds like
some kind of game.
The kidnapper
wants us to play
by their rules.
They're watching us.
Oz isn't
answering his phone.
I got him.
This kidnapper is
really toying with me.
He's making a run for it.
-I'll take this for you.
-Thank you.
Ava and I are too old
for this game.
And Chloe's gonna need
a couple more years.
Morgan, I know where he is.
Roman. He's alive.
Hey, how's it going over there?
Pretty good.
Just read him his third bedtime story.
What? Only three
bedtime stories?
You got off easy.
Thank you so much
for babysitting.
I really needed tonight.
- Of course. Are you
on your way home?
-Yeah. Yeah, I'm on my way.
-Okay. Be careful.
Will do.
-Love you guys. Bye.
-Love you.
"Let's play.
" We have 34 minutes to make our move.
"The fun has just begun."
They made me play games.
They were wearing
a white anime mask.
And they're watching us.
Whoever is playing games
with us,
it isn't David Roy Peck.
Well, then
who the hell is this guy?
Mom, help! Help me!
What? What is it?
No one can help you.
What are you doing?
Are you serious?
He's... He's cheating.
My pillows, my rules.
Stop, okay?
First of all,
it's a pillow fight.
There's no way to cheat.
Second of all,
they are not your pillows.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
-She lulled me
into a sense of security.
-You have two, that's not fair!
Hello! I am trying to read
my baby sister to sleep.
- Oh, okay, we'll do it
quietly. Shh.
- Ow!
You know, maybe if we
weren't stuck in this
house for like a week,
- we wouldn't be acting
like animals.
- Wild animals. I can't.
- Snake attack!
Your boss is here.
Oh!
Perfect timing.
You're sleepy now, right?
Go to bed.
Okay.
Do you mind?
I got him.
Thank you.
I got him, I got him.
So... how we holding up?
Not great.
Pretty terrible, actually.
I don't know what's worse,
being stalked
by a deranged psychopath
or having to lie
to my kids about it.
There's no need to scare them.
We're gonna catch
this guy soon.
-Everything will be back
to normal.
-I hope so.
It's only a matter of time
before they realize
Ludo's not crashing
on the couch because
of a palm weevil infestation.
They're native to
his neighborhood. I figured
Elliot would check. He did.
Do you have anything else
for me besides this homework?
I wish I had more
of an update on Roman.
We're pretty confident
Gio's contact had good intel.
He's staying somewhere
in Henderson, Nevada.
We got the force out there
helping us get closer.
Do you have an address?
Not yet, but we'll get one.
We'll figure it out.
How's he doing?
Karadec?
He's ready to have you back.
We all are.
-Whoa, whoa! Daph,
where you going?
-I got plans.
Really? At this hour?
Settle yourselves.
It's just a friend.
And you guys need to get
out of here too.
We can't be pulling
back-to-back all-nighters.
Yeah, you know what, Oz?
She's right. Go home.
Why? It's not like
I'm gonna sleep anyway.
Not until we catch the bastard.
Well, I appreciate
the sentiment,
but burning yourself out is
not gonna help the cause.
Yeah, what about you?
I'll be right behind you.
- You're a terrible liar.
-Yeah, that wasn't great.
-Later, guys.
-See you.
Okay.
Hey, why you calling me
so late?
There's my grumpy guy.
Nice to hear your voice too.
Why you working so late?
How do you know I'm working?
Well, you answered
your phone at 2:00 a.m. and
you don't have a social life.
Yeah, you know, this guy
went after one of our own.
He got close to you.
He got close to your kids.
So it's been impossible
for any of us to slow down.
I really thought
we would've found him by now,
especially with his sketch
all over the news.
Yeah. So did I.
You know, it's very detailed.
Yes, it's very detailed.
I worked hard on that
with two different artists.
No, the nose is too aquiline.
The zygomatics
are just bananas.
What are you doing? Oh,
I thought I said a slight
cleft and just a little dimple,
but apparently,
I said John Travolta,
and I don't remember it.
Clear the whole thing.
God, I just
gotta learn how to draw.
I don't like
this feeling, Karadec.
It sucks. I hate it.
Yeah. I do too.
Yeah.
Get yourself some sleep.
You too.
-Morning, Chester.
-Hey. What you got there?
Well, nothing says, "Thanks
for looking after my family,"
- like an open box
of shortbread cookies.
I would've brought you what
I made Chloe for breakfast,
but it was disgusting.
Yeah, Lieutenant Soto
didn't mention this
assignment would have perks,
so thank you.
It's a quiet night?
Yeah, yeah, all good.
Hey, you all dressed up,
where you going?
Just gotta go run some errands.
-I'll see you later.
-All right.
Nobody came by?
No, just the usual.
Babies, dogs, you know.
Why?
Wrong address.
Everything all right, Morgan?
Yeah, I'm just gonna
go around the corner for a sec.
You want me to call
for a police escort?
That's okay.
No, I'll be quick.
Keep an eye on the house.
Why is no one picking up
their phones? I've been
texting like a maniac.
You guys, it's the Game Maker.
He sent me this piece
of mail so that I would
walk by a very specific house.
I know it was him.
Do you have any idea
how rare it is
for the US Postal Service
to deliver mail
to the wrong address?
Between optical
character recognition,
barcode scans
and the ZIP+4 code system.
It's super rare.
And he knows that I know that.
And he also knows that
the street
next to mine is a cul-de-sac.
So he knew I would have
to walk past, that house
to get to this address.
I know it was him.
Good morning, Morgan.
Welcome back.
-I blasted in?
-Little bit.
It's too much.
Sorry.
Good morning, Daphne.
Oz, it's really nice
to see you back at work.
You too.
-You doing okay?
-Yeah.
Me neither.
And yes, Morgan,
we did get all of your texts.
And two voice notes.
Which were kinda hard to
hear 'cause it sounded
like you were running?
Yeah, what?
Am I gonna tiptoe or mosey?
Of course I'm running.
It's important. Have that
dusted for prints, please.
What else is in this bag?
Probably teething crackers
or something.
I-I don't know. Don't make
a big deal out of it.
Also, that bag looks like
it can be used many more times.
Give it back to me
when they're done.
Okay, so do we really think
that this could be
the Game Maker?
- Yes.
- Not sure.
- I am sure.
- Are you?
Because last week,
there were other cases where
you were pretty confident--
I understand, okay?
I jumped the gun a couple
of times, but, you guys,
think about it.
The song "The Lion Sleeps
Tonight," paired with
the Jungle Animal Match game
that he slipped into
my grocery bag
next to my children. It is him.
-What do we have so far?
-We're still gathering
information,
starting with the person
who lives at that address.
Just one name on the lease.
Maya Price. We left word
for her this morning.
Hopefully, we'll hear
back soon and she's okay.
Maya Price is my sister.
We can't find her.
1522 Wells Avenue?
Where's Mommy?
I was babysitting Max
last night.
And I went to Maya's place
this morning when she
didn't show to pick him up.
Her front door was open.
I just knew something
was wrong.
But how did you guys find out
that she was missing?
Our consultant, Morgan,
happened to be walking by.
I live one street over.
-Really?
-Yeah.
It's a weird coincidence.
Sarah, take us through
everything from last night.
Okay,
Maya got some free tickets
to see a show
at Sound Night Club.
Any idea who she was with?
A friend from work, I...
I think.
You know, she sent me a...
a photo.
-Where do they work?
-AGM, Artful Gal Music.
She also works part time
at Costco to make ends meet.
Sarah, any chance
that Maya
may have had too much to drink,
ended up crashing
at someone else's place
last night?
No, she's... Doesn't drink.
She's the most responsible
person I know.
Sorry, I'm so scared that
something happened to her
and I'm...
- Play Flappy Bird, but...
- Let's see.
Yeah, I'm trying to hold it
together for Max.
What's the situation
with Max's father?
Derek, he's-he's...
He's a good guy.
He just has bad habits.
He struggled to hold down
a job. It got kind of messy.
Messy? How?
Custody issues.
Yeah, they have
a court date set next week.
Sarah,
do you recognize this man?
He's connected to another case
that we're working,
and we think--
And, um, that's all
we have right now.
No.
I-I'd remember
if I'd seen him before.
I don't forget faces.
Sarah, as soon as we have
some answers,
we'll be in touch.
That's it.
Reminds me of my club days.
Add that to the list of things
Maya and I have in common.
Now, if the doorman
at the club said
he saw Maya leave alone
around 9:30 p.m. last night,
then the question becomes
where did she go?
This parking lot.
She hadn't been out in forever.
She's not gonna drive around
looking for a meter.
Plus proximity, you know.
Believe it or not, we don't
love using a pepper spray.
Fair enough. Well, Maya
drove a silver Honda Accord.
If it's not here,
I'll have Daphne
put out a BOLO on the car.
I don't know, Morgan,
this is just way too exposed.
It's unlikely
she was abducted here.
-There had to be
a second location.
-Nope.
This is the spot.
Those busted street lights
provided the perfect
darkness for him to hide in.
And you see this?
This is a little heel
cap from her shoe.
A shoe, not necessarily Maya's.
I'm just gonna keep going.
This is where he attacked her.
She fought back.
She got away by using
her purse as a weapon.
That lip balm, candy...
and these little
glass fragments...
...that smell
like orange blossom
must have been from
a perfume sample
from a department store.
I'm familiar.
Then she ran.
It was a Friday night.
There had to be a guard
in that booth over there.
She needed help.
But she didn't get it.
So then her heels
must've left these marks,
presumably as he was
dragging her to his vehicle.
Yeah, or hers.
Which means she would've
been parked
in the spot right here.
Karadec, look.
There's two lines
of heel marks, and then
it just turns into one.
So at a certain point,
only one heel
was dragging leaving a mark.
That means she lost her shoe
during the struggle.
Found it.
He crammed her unconscious body
into the trunk of her own car.
He was in control
the whole time.
And she knew it.
I put the BOLO out
on Maya's car.
Good. Now alert the press.
Let them know we'll have
a briefing later today
and get a photo
of Maya ready to go.
Done and done.
And maybe show 'em a picture
of this guy again.
Not until we know we can tie
the Game Maker
to her abduction.
Right now,
we focus on finding Maya.
I'm very focused
on finding Maya,
which is why I want
to focus on the man
who abducted her.
I think she's right. There
are too many coincidences.
-Prints are in
on Morgan's mail.
-And?
Yours and the postman's.
Looks like Maya pulled a permit
for a weapon a few months back.
- Protection from her husband?
-Let's find out.
I want Derek in here for
questioning stat, and we're
cleared to search Maya's place.
Let's get over there.
Clock is tickin'.
Hmm. You know, this record
doesn't fit the rest
of her collection.
We'll take it with us,
check it for prints.
Locks are new,
probably installed
in the last month or so.
Okay, so it certainly appears
like Maya purchased a gun.
There was a record of sale
from two weeks ago,
but I can't find
a weapon anywhere.
All right, Daph.
We'll keep looking, all right?
Okay.
-Karadec?
-Yeah?
Look at this. Prada,
Gucci, Versace.
That's thousands of dollars
of stuff Maya can't afford.
Gifts from someone.
-Yeah, but they're all missing.
-Well, maybe they were stolen.
Karadec. Karadec!
Yes, Morgan?
I'm pretty sure those
expensive items weren't stolen.
They were sold. Let's go.
-Go where?
-The Boneyard.
The Boneyard? Yes, of course.
Why wouldn't we be going
to the Boneyard?
You guys check out Maya's work,
Artful Gal Music.
Call me with anything.
Fritzy.
Good to see you.
Hey, it is too late to buy back
your mixer, Morgan.
It's long gone.
No, I don't want the mixer.
I also have a job now
that allows me
to keep my appliances.
We're here on official
police business, Fritzy.
-You're a cop?
-No, but they do sign
my paychecks.
This woman is missing.
And I know she recently got rid
of some pretty pricey
designer stuff.
So...
So I'd like them, please.
She could've sold
that stuff anywhere.
Yeah, but she also picked up
an electronic piano
for her kid.
What? I have a monopoly
on electronic kiddy pianos?
Fritzy.
There was a sticky spot
on the side of it
in the shape of a dog bone.
You sell people's stuff
and then you take off
the price tag,
but you never remove the goo.
-Pain in the ass to get off.
-I know.
Okay, fine. All right.
I did a good deal by that lady.
But I can't be handing over
thousands of dollars
of goods to you.
It's hard enough to keep
the lights on
as it is these days.
-Uh, the LAPD will put it
on their tab.
-There is no tab, Morgan.
The LAPD will reimburse you
from the city slush fund.
Not a thing.
Fritzy, why don't you
just turn over the items?
Otherwise, I'm gonna have
to fast track a warrant
for a more invasive search,
and who knows what kind
of illicit goods
we'll find in here.
What are you doing?
It's too much.
You trying to feel big?
He's trying to feel big.
This guy's trying to keep
his lights on.
Fritzy, I am so sorry.
I'll tell you what,
you let me borrow the stuff
and I promise to give it
back to you
as soon as we're done with it.
-Fine.
-Yeah?
All right. Well,
thank you, sir.
And if what you're saying
about that lady is true,
you might want to talk
to the fella
she was arguing with
out in my parking lot.
Did you get a look at him?
No, but my cameras did.
Derek, the reason
why we brought you
in here today is
because Maya's been missing
since last night.
She was abducted
from a car lot in Hollywood.
Oh, my God!
I had no idea.
-I... What about Max?
Is Max okay? Is he--
-Max is fine. He's with Sarah,
and you would have known
sooner,
but we couldn't find you.
Well, I was having
a few drinks
at a bar in NoHo.
Okay, I had more than
a few drinks. I was upset.
I haven't seen my kid
much lately.
Looks like things g
ot pretty heated between you
two outside the Boneyard.
Look, she...
She'd been dodging my calls.
I-I admit it was a mistake
to follow her, yeah.
She'd been getting
expensive gifts from someone.
And I-I got jealous.
I admit that. Okay?
Look, I would never...
I would never hurt her.
Did you know that Maya
recently purchased
a firearm, Derek?
I mean, why...
might she do that?
What? No, no.
Maya hates guns.
He didn't do it.
We're wasting time.
Maybe he did. Maybe he didn't.
Maybe he knows something
we don't.
Derek, what happened
to your hand?
Honestly, I don't know.
I can't remember.
I made it back
to my buddy's place,
and then I passed out.
Maya is my whole world.
Love of my life.
And I miss my son.
I-I-I've made mistakes,
yes, but I...
I would never.
You have to find her.
Uh, we're digging
into Derek's alibi.
-Okay.
-Oz and Daphne came back
with someone
-I think you're gonna
wanna talk to.
-Barry Gibb?
The woman that Maya
was with at the club.
We had a blast.
It was obvious she needed
a night to herself.
The custody battle was
stressing her out,
and she was freaking out
over how expensive lawyers
can be.
Your boss, uh,
Jason Howard, correct?
We'd like to talk to him,
but he's been hard to locate.
That doesn't surprise me.
He nepo'd his way
into the CEO position
years ago,
and he has the work ethic
to prove it.
He's more likely to be
on a scouting trip to Italy
or at one of his vacation homes
than to be at the office.
Hmm, gross.
Uh, was Maya seeing anyone?
Maybe somebody who could
afford designer stuff?
She told me about the gifts.
I have my suspicions
on who sent them,
but she wouldn't confirm it.
You think Jason was
sending her those gifts?
I'm pretty sure the only reason
he comes to AGM at all
is to see her.
He gave us those tickets
to the club.
Told Maya she deserved
to let go for a night.
I mean, do you think maybe...
No. Hell no. Maya would never.
She felt weird about
taking the tickets
in the first place,
but it was Gaga night
and peer pressure...
Am I a bad friend?
You're here, aren't you?
You know, you kind of
look like her.
Hey, Daphne.
What else we got on Jason?
Half a dozen
sexual harassment complaints
over the last five years.
Looks like they all
settled out of court.
Sounds like he's paying people
to be quiet.
No, not people. Women.
-Morgan, where are you going?
-To get some air.
Oz, call your favorite judge.
We need a search warrant
for any and all residences
linked to Jason Howard.
I know you guys aren't
a 100% sold
on my Game Maker theory yet,
but hopefully,
this should clear things up.
I'm guessing this is
what the inside
of your mind looks like.
Oh, buddy. Not even close.
Okay, you ready?
Jason Howard is a diabetic,
just like Spencer.
As a matter of fact,
he is on the board
of a research initiative
at County General,
meaning he would know exactly
how long a person could be
without insulin.
He's also a painter.
These are his original works.
Kind of reminds you of the ones
that we found hanging
in the gallery.
Guys, turns out a trust fund
and a work aversion gives you
a lot of free time for hobbies
because he's also
a certified scuba instructor.
I mean, half the guy's
Instagram pictures
are of him in exotic locations,
you know,
teaching impressionable
young women in wet suits
all about the secrets
of the abyss.
You ready for the big finish?
I have to admit
this is pretty fun.
Mm-hmm.
Mm-hmm!
So?
Jason and the Game Maker
are one and the same.
No! No, it's a trap.
Guys, I just went
into the war room.
It took me like five minutes
to get all this stuff
off the Internet.
He's trying to get us
to focus over here
so we can keep slithering
around over there.
It's just too easy.
This is what I think.
The Game Maker is
trying to frame Jason
to be a part of
whatever game this is
he's currently playing.
Or, it's Jason.
It's always been Jason.
And your guy is just
a Good Samaritan who helped
save the frozen turkey.
Okay, then how did
that card game
get into my groceries?
Whoever's doing this
has pulled off more
complicated tricks than that.
Look, we're just saying,
isn't it possible?
Sometimes, the easiest
answer is the right one.
I don't care if it's possible.
This is what's happening.
We still have
to follow protocol.
I want to be
on your side here, Morgan.
But why would he go
to so much trouble
to frame this particular guy?
Gosh, Oz, I'm not sure.
Let's find him and ask him.
All right, enough.
For now, we keep all
investigative paths wide open
until the facts
tell us otherwise.
Go be with your kids.
Keep your phone close.
The stress is getting to her.
She's not a cop.
-She certainly didn't
sign up for this.
-Selena, stop.
Adam, she said no.
Said no to what?
The job. When I offered it
to her,
I pushed her into it.
I promised to help her
with the Roman case
if she came on as a consultant.
Why are you telling me
this now?
Because I put her
in this position!
No, you gave her
an opportunity.
You did the right thing
by bringing her on.
We need her.
If she goes rogue
and something happens,
maybe I just take her
off the case.
You trust me?
-You know I do.
-Okay. Well, I trust her.
Would you like me
to take over?
Now that all the work is done,
that's when I really shine.
It's okay. I'm good.
Are you?
It's Roman.
I think they're getting
pretty close to finding him.
What happens if they find him?
What happens
if they don't find him?
I just really want
this for Ava.
I'll eat later if that's cool.
Wait, where are you going?
-Keisha's having
a few people over.
-Oh.
It's dinner time.
You know,
I'm still a growing boy.
Okay, it'll be ready soon.
It's not
a really great day for that
'cause we're having
family night tonight.
Again? We've been doing
this for like a week now.
Mom, I'm not stupid.
I know something's going on.
I'll set the table.
Where are the cookies?
Uh, the cookies?
It doesn't matter because
we eat our growing food before
we even think about cookies.
The Ayurvedic system believes
that a small portion of dessert
sets up
the digestive system for...
-I'll wait.
-Yeah, you'll wait.
Hey.
Of course you're not stupid.
And yes, we need to talk,
but can we do it when we have
a little bit more privacy,
please?
-Yeah.
-Thank you.
Hi, Morgan.
Hey.
Did you get my text?
No?
We're going to a party?
You've got to be kidding me!
Eh...
The hell kind
of party is this?
Jason's hosting
an album release
for one of his artists.
He said he couldn't get
out of it, but he's happy
to talk to us here.
Let's just take the weird win.
Weird like these masks look
kind of like the Game Maker's?
-Duly noted.
-Is there a mask
that speaks to you
or would you like me
to match one to your aura?
I tell you what, this one
right here is yapping at me,
but I think you should
match his aura.
No, that would not be
necessary.
If I'm being honest,
yeah. Go nuts.
Uh-huh.
Really get in there, yep.
Yeah, bingo.
Nailed it.
-Thank you.
-Bye.
Morgan, I need you to focus.
We still have to find Jason.
I am focused,
and I already found him.
He's right over there
in front of that wall
of 19-year-olds.
Detectives,
thanks for showing up.
Uh, can I get you anything?
Yeah, a quieter place to talk.
Maya's worked
for me almost a year.
She schedules all my stuff,
my social and philanthropic...
stuff!
Is that why you bought her
so many gifts, Jason?
Gifts?
-Tickets to Sound nightclub.
-Oh, those are comps.
I'm just generous.
Yeah, a lot of stores
on Rodeo Drive
that would agree,
not to mention
your platinum card.
I-I was worried you'd
find out about that.
Now why would you say that?
Because I didn't buy
those things.
Maya did.
She has access
to my credit card
for work stuff,
and my people noticed
a transaction
on my statement last week,
and I confronted her.
So you didn't fire her
even though
she stole thousands
of dollars from you?
Well, she denied it, and
I... have a soft spot
for single moms.
Besides, it's just money.
Yeah. Totally. Just money.
Ooh, those are beautiful.
What are those, Tantõ daggers?
Yeah.
Yeah, I bought those
in Sakai City.
They belonged to a samurai.
Are you a collector?
Me? No. No.
Those are a teeny bit
outside my price range,
but, uh, I love how
you've displayed them.
Yeah, they're arranged
by shogunate periods.
They sure are. Let's see.
Minamoto, Taira, Tõdõ,
Ashikaga, Oda, Tokugawa.
Except one's missing.
The Takeda. It's not there.
You don't strike me as a guy
who would display
an incomplete set.
Jason, I'm gonna need you
to think real hard on this one.
Where were you
last night around 9:30?
I was here.
I had my chef make me a meal.
I caught up on paperwork,
and then I went to bed early.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I have to get back to my party.
Taffy Boi needs me.
I hope you find Maya.
I really do.
You guys can see
yourselves out, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, he's lying. That man
doesn't work during the day,
let alone at night.
You're waiting on me
to leave so you can poke around
Jason's den without a warrant?
Yeah.
Morgan. Morgan!
Karadec!
Karadec! He's here!
Hey, hey, hey, don't move.
Mask off now.
Jason Howard,
you're under arrest
for the kidnapping
of Maya Price.
I want all my lawyers.
At least two.
They're on retainer.
You have the right
to remain silent. Anything
you say can and will be used...
Excuse me. Hey.
I saw him. I know it.
Who?
Him, not Jason. I know
I saw him. He was just here.
-Well, where did he go?
-I don't know.
-Well, Morgan, we still
have to find Maya.
-Yeah.
Morgan.
I want
your badge number
and your phone number.
- Hey.
- Karadec.
Come here. Where is she?
Where's Maya?
Did you kill her?
Now, where is she?
Hey, I got your messages.
The doors and windows
are locked,
and Chester's on alert.
How are you holding up?
Uh, I think it's gonna be
a long night.
He was smiling at me.
He's enjoying this.
You guys are good?
Uh, yeah.
We're doing okay.
I think it was the right
thing to do, telling
the kids what's happening.
-Are they scared?
-Yes, but mostly for you.
I told them their mom's
got the entire police
department looking out for her.
You're a good dad. Thank you.
-I'll be home
as soon as I can.
-Be safe.
Jason is not saying
another word.
Which means we're no closer
to finding Maya.
Maybe Jason isn't telling us
where Maya is 'cause Jason
doesn't know where Maya is.
Well, he knew where she was
the night she was taken.
The gifts were bought
on his card.
Her bracelet's in his pool.
The missing dagger
from his wall.
Yeah, I'm not saying
the evidence
doesn't point to Jason.
I'm the one who said
it would. Remember?
We just gotta figure out why.
How dark was it at the party?
One face,
all those people.
What are you implying?
Are you implying
I didn't see him?
No, we know you saw him.
It would really help
if one of us could see
him too at some point.
Yeah, it sure would help.
I would love that,
but only I saw him
at the party.
Just me.
That's how he wanted it.
It was clearly by design.
So,
what is the game, Morgan?
I don't know what the game is.
Maybe the game is figuring out
what the game is.
And, yes, I hear
how crazy that sounds, but
- what else can we expect
from this guy?
Are you...
Are you really suggesting
that I don't remember his face?
That man is a danger
to my children.
Okay?
I'm never gonna be able
to forget his face.
Long after we're done
with this,
long after we get him,
and we put him away,
and you guys move on
to another case,
he's gonna live up here,
cemented inside of my brain,
along with all
of the other things
I gotta look out for
to make sure my kids are okay.
So if we could just, you know,
close the book
on this whole Morgan-made-up-
an-imaginary-man thing,
that would be great.
Okay, I've got something.
A salvage yard in Sun Valley
just reported Maya's car.
Go check it out.
And you call me as soon
as you land on the scene.
Lieutenant Soto.
Officer Sigman,
how are things in Nevada?
That's right. That's right.
Roman Sinquerra.
What do you got?
The car showed up last night.
I saw your BOLO
when I ran the VIN.
Did you see who brought it in?
No, sorry.
This is it.
It's all yours.
-Hey. Are you okay?
-I-I don't know.
What do you think?
If we pull Jason's prints
off the dagger
and get him to talk,
maybe we can get to Maya.
Just because she's wounded
doesn't mean
she isn't still alive.
Morgan.
You heard?
I did.
I also heard from our friends
in Nevada. They called
with an address.
-Roman?
-I think so.
I came after they called.
I figured you'd wanna
hop in a car.
I can drive.
It's just a few hours away.
No.
No, I'm not. I can't
leave my kids here
with that guy still out there.
Daph and I can go,
if you want.
Yeah.
-Whatever you need, Morgan.
-What... What is... going on?
After everything we went
through last week,
I filled them in too.
Okay. Yeah, thank you.
I'll call you as soon
as we have eyes on him.
Who called him?
Roman?
No, Derek, Maya's ex, the dad.
He was at the police station
when we got there with Jason.
Did somebody call him
and give him a heads-up
that we had made an arrest?
No, Major Crimes
doesn't notify
victims' families
about active investigations.
But he knew
we were gonna be there.
He was waiting for us
when we came in
with Jason. Do you remember?
If we didn't tell Derek
that Jason might've killed
Maya, who did?
Hello.
Derek, this is the LAPD.
It's about Maya.
I wish we had better news.
- It was him.
-You think the Game Maker called Derek.
He must've wanted Derek
to see Jason getting arrested.
-Why?
-That's what we gotta find out.
First, I thought he sent
this to me to get my attention,
to lead me to Maya's house,
but what if I'm not
the only person
who got this flyer in the mail?
It'd be pretty
easy to steal Jason's
credit card if he had a key.
He's the one who sent Maya
all those gifts and made it
look like Jason did it.
He stole her bracelet
when he abducted her,
dropped it in the pool.
And then he grabbed
the weapon on the way out.
Okay, but why do all this?
Just to frame Jason?
No, I think leading us
in the wrong direction was
only part of the game.
So what's the rest?
What's his next move?
Well, look at all these gifts.
All the red ones are
either Versace or Gucci.
What do those two men
have in common?
They were murdered.
They were both shot
and killed.
Where's Derek?
-You think Derek
is his next victim?
-Not exactly.
Keep going. I'm listening.
The weapon that Maya
supposedly registered for.
-We never found it.
-I don't think
she bought a gun at all.
I think he wanted Derek
to think that she did.
Did you know that Maya
recently purchased a firearm?
What?
The Game Maker knew
Derek would want revenge,
and so he placed a gun
in Maya's house
after we searched it.
It's possible Maya was just
bait, and she could
still be alive.
Yeah, it's possible.
We're still waiting on DNA
and a blood type
from Maya's trunk.
Yeah, I hope so.
But if she's not part
of the game anymore,
he doesn't need her.
Look, if we did everything
we were supposed to do.
We played the game.
We played the game his way.
None of the other victims
have died.
Maybe he's not a murderer.
Not if he got someone else
to do it for him.
So it's Jason
he wants dead.
We gotta find Derek.
The Game Maker
created a murderer.
And we put the weapon
right in his hand.
Derek! Stop!
This is it.
Roman Sinquerra?
The lab should have
the blood test results
in 24 hours.
Excuse me.
Apparently,
you're looking for me.