He shot her. I don't know
what to do. He just shot her.
Oh!
He's here.
I know, I get it. I'm late.
Honestly, I didn't notice.
I got a ticket,
and I did stop this time.
Was it a complete stop?
Not necessarily.
That's poor time management.
By the sound of your voice,
this is somehow my fault?
This
get-out-of-jail-free card--
Not
a get-out-of-jail-free card.
That is
a police consultant ID badge.
It's useless. I should just
go back to flirting
to get out of tickets.
It doesn't work,
but at least it's fun.
Or quit rolling
through stop signs.
I don't need you to tell me
what I should and shouldn't do
-with stop signs--
-Morgan. Read the room.
You guys are so bad
at pretending to work.
I should put on a clinic.
What's going on?
Soto's up for captain.
Slot's been open for a while.
Word is
she's got the inside track.
Okay, that's exciting.
-Is that a good or a bad call?
-I was just about to ask you.
That's not
what you all thought.
When I have news,
I will tell you.
You two, come.
911 had a call
a few minutes ago.
You two should have the file.
Here's audio of the call.
He shot her.
I don't know what to do.
He just shot her.
Oh!
He's here.
Dispatch traced the call
to the address of Raina Viera.
Okay, we could have two victims
and a shooter on the loose. Go.
Raina Viera,
you made a call to 911
about a shooting
and an intruder in your home.
No. I've already
told the other officers,
I made no such call!
Okay, well,
we listened to the call,
and it was traced
to this address.
-Anyone else live here?
-I live alone.
No one else was here. I don't
know what else to tell you.
It wasn't me,
and that's the end!
Oh, except that it was.
Are you calling me a liar?
No, she's just
calling you Gullah Geechee
from the coastal community
in the southeast.
Yeah, beautiful accent,
but it's also very rare.
In my life, I've only known
one other person who had it.
My old boss at the DMV.
Her name was Pearl.
Lord, Morgan.
I got to fire you, girl.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Oh, well,
the picture over there of you
under the loblolly pines that
are native to South Carolina,
plus your accent,
which I've caught twice now...
- Oh!
- And that's it.
...kinda prove that you did
make that 911 phone call.
Well, unless having an accent
is a crime, you can go.
We will be happy to go, ma'am,
as soon as we clear this up.
Would you mind
if we just take a quick look
at your cell phone?
Why would I lie
about calling you?
We just want to make sure
you're safe. That's it.
Well, if it'll make you leave,
go ahead.
No 911 call.
-Weird.
-Yeah.
Well, just real quick, for me,
otherwise it's gonna drive me
nuts the whole way home.
You have
such a beautiful kitchen,
so what's up
with these cheap pans
on your stove?
You know,
I have pans like that.
That makes sense for me,
but it doesn't really fit
into this kitchen.
Is she for real?
We're good here.
We appreciate your cooperation.
Oh...
She makes a call to 911
and then she denies it?
What does that tell you?
That maybe she saw something,
but now she's afraid to talk.
Exactly. So if someone's
pressuring her to stay quiet,
how do we leave now?
Because she told us
to get out of her house
and she hasn't
committed a crime.
Patrol canvassed the area.
No one saw or heard anything,
and my guy swept the place.
There's no sign of foul play
and no intruder hiding inside.
-Right now she's safe.
-Oh, what a relief!
I'll put in a request
for unmarked surveillance
outside the house.
Roman asked me
to put eyes on you and Ava.
I sincerely wish
you'd stop using my computer.
Maybe you should get
a less guessable password.
I take it you're still worried
about Raina Viera.
Of course I am.
Soto getting surveillance
approved helps.
She fast-tracked it,
which actually took some juice.
Maybe it's a sign that
Soto got the captain's gig
-Really?
-Yeah.
Okay, so if she moves up
to captain, where do you go?
Probably in there
as acting lieutenant.
Then who am I with?
Someone else.
I don't want to be
with someone else.
Unless it's Oz or Daphne.
-They're already partners.
-I can just work with them.
There's no throuples
in law enforcement.
That's just a failure
of imagination.
Yeah. Look, I get it.
A mind like yours,
everything is organized chaos.
So when things outside
your control change,
it's disruptive.
I don't like it.
If there is a transition,
it will be smooth.
We'll make it work.
'Kay.
Karadec.
We did everything we could,
Morgan.
Did we? It wasn't enough.
Daphne's finishing up
with the neighbors.
So far, no one saw or heard
anything suspicious.
No signs of gunshot wounds
or other damage.
Looks like
she just fell and hit her head.
Well, Raina had
three missed calls
from somebody named Lucy.
-Let's find out who that is.
-Yeah, will do.
-Huh.
-I got my own "huh" down here.
Oh, yeah? You first.
Raina's got a stain
on the back of her shirt.
Doesn't look like dried blood.
Dirt maybe, right in the middle
of her back.
I doubt she put it there.
I zip myself
into enough dresses.
That's a tough spot to reach.
Yeah, my thinking exactly.
Your turn.
Well, when you're about to eat
it at the top of the stairs,
you grab the banister, right?
Look at all the rings
on her hands.
There'd be scratches,
but there's not.
So either she jumped
or somebody pushed her.
Raina witnessed a murder
and somebody killed her
before she could
finish reporting it.
So where's that crime scene?
According to the neighbors,
there was a wild party
across the street.
Let's start there.
This place
doesn't look so good.
So, rough night?
Just a few people over
for a hang.
You mean a couple
of dozen people.
Throw in some alcohol,
things get out of hand.
Maybe someone left worse
than they came.
Or maybe they didn't leave
at all.
Whoa, I don't know
what you think
happened here, man, but--
Any guns
in the house, Logan?
Because we received
a 911 call
from your neighbor
about a shooting.
And we're
starting to wonder
if maybe they got shot here.
Maybe a drug deal gone bad?
Drug deal? Based on what?
How about not
judging the cover of a person
without reading the book?
Oh, boy. It was close.
No, not judging, just noticing
the unicorn sticker
on your mailbox
signaling to your customers
that you're open for business.
Customers like that
jittery guy out there just
circling around on his bike,
waiting for us to leave
so he can come in
and you can sell him drugs.
Drugs that I'm guessing are in
that drawer that you looked at
when I mentioned your drugs.
Oh, yeah, there they are.
Logan! Hey!
Right behind ya.
Yo, yo, yo. Give me the bike.
Sorry, man.
Logan!
So, Logan,
here's what we're thinking.
Someone died at your party.
Raina had a front-row seat,
and you killed her.
I didn't kill anybody.
And Raina, bro,
I was helping her.
Mmm, helping her how?
You were her dealer.
I don't identify
by that characterization.
I'm a legit unlicensed
neighborhood pharmacist.
Hmm. Okay, so, uh, drug dealer.
No. I rob Peter to treat Paul
when the system denies
the meds people need.
Hmm.
-And, uh, what did Raina need?
-Migraine meds.
She fell on hard times,
lost her insurance,
couldn't afford the meds.
So I hooked her up.
I really liked that lady.
I would never hurt her.
Logan, around 9:30
this morning, Raina made
a 911 call reporting a murder.
-Where were you?
-With Raina.
She was showing me some
stuff in her basement, things
she could sell for bills.
Then I get a call from Bones,
so I popped upstairs.
I hang up with him and
then Raina comes back upstairs.
And she made no mention
of a 911 call
or witnessing a murder?
No, I swear.
She was completely calm.
What time
did you talk to Bones?
Probably around the same time
y'all got that 911 call,
9:30 or so.
Okay, so Raina calls 911
while witnessing a murder
from her basement?
That seems weird.
Yeah, assuming Logan's
telling us the truth.
But I think I have a way
to check his timeline.
Black light, huh?
What are you looking for?
Is this like a fluid situation?
No, it's not.
There's no way Raina
witnessed a murder in here
-unless it happened in here.
-Okay, so Logan might be lying.
If we can find his fingerprints
down here,
it means
he could be telling the truth.
Instead of waiting a day or two
for Forensics to dust
and process prints...
- You are bending the rules.
Look at you.
Logan's behavior tells me
he's got a ton of drugs
in his system.
That changes
the way fingerprints look
under a black light.
They shine
brighter than normal.
You see the difference?
Yeah.
Yeah, I can almost guarantee
the glowing print is Logan's,
which puts him here
in the basement, but in order
to clear him as a suspect,
we have to place him upstairs
at 9:30.
My turn.
Do you remember the four beeps
in the 911 call?
Yeah, it was faint,
but I heard it.
I don't know what to do.
He shot her.
Okay, I think that was
Raina's bougie coffee maker.
Yeah, she was
drinking a cup
when we walked in.
I think it was set to turn on
at 9:30 in the morning,
but the thing is,
coffee makers like these
beep eight times
when the pot is ready.
I've had some really bad bosses
with great taste in coffee.
-But we only heard four beeps.
-That's right.
Somebody turned the alarm off,
and I think that someone
was Logan.
This proves Logan was here
at 9:30,
so she definitely
made that 911 call
from down here.
But why? What could
she have seen
from the basement?
Let's see.
Who are you? Oh, look.
-2007's calling.
-Raina had a second phone.
Yeah, but without cell service.
That doesn't matter. Since '96,
the FCC requires
that all cell phones,
active or not, have
the capability to call 911.
Hmm!
-You knew that already,
didn't you?
-Yeah, I did.
I was hoping you did too,
'cause I thought
it'd be nice
to let you have this one.
Appreciate it.
Okay,
she turned it on from here,
made the call from here,
but why? What did she see?
Three boxes of brand-new
cheap pots and pans?
Buy one, get two free?
No, she needed them as backups
'cause she kept burning hers.
She was leaving the stove on,
and she was also putting items
from her kitchen
in the wrong spots.
The pills she was taking
weren't for migraines.
Those pills also treat
early onset dementia.
So Raina wasn't lying
when she said
she didn't make the 911 call.
-She just didn't remember.
-Dementia can rob you
of your memories
but can also jumble them all up
so new memories can get lost
and old ones can resurface.
But something
would've had to trigger it.
You think while she was looking
for stuff to sell,
maybe something set her off?
Yeah, I think so.
And, honestly,
it really could be anything.
It could be a smell or a sound.
Morgan.
Oh!
Or a bloodstained dress.
-That looks
like a trigger to me.
-Yeah, that would do it.
So Raina did witness a murder.
The question is:
when did she see it?
So Raina witnessed a murder.
We just don't know
when it happened.
If we can date the dress,
we can date the cold case.
The earliest age
most people start
to form memories
is around three or four.
Given Raina's age,
we can rule out
any cases prior to 1975.
That's 50 years of cold cases.
15,320 cases, give or take.
Someone needs
to whittle that down.
Didn't you tell me
one time that vintage
is your love language, Morgan?
I've never once said
"love language" to you,
but I can take a crack at it.
Lot of staring. Everybody just
staring right at me.
Yeah, a little space.
Thank you.
I need a lighter.
You just asked for space.
Now you need a lighter?
Yeah, I'm a complex woman.
Can I have a lighter, please?
This fabric
has a slight shine to it.
It's not as glossy as satin,
but it's more polished
than cotton.
I think it might be Tencel.
-Anything else?
-Yeah, some scissors.
You do know this is evidence,
right, Morgan?
Yeah. Yeah. You should
probably turn around.
Yep, burns quick and clean.
This is Tencel, which
was not available until 1985.
Now the fabric
is just the first clue.
Is the US registered
identification number
the second?
It most certainly is, Daphne.
Okay, 178549.
This dress was manufactured
by Cibrian Creations,
but they went out of business
in 2015.
Okay, you guys know
when they started putting tags
in clothes?
In 1971, manufacturers had
to provide clear instructions
so that people
wouldn't screw up their clothes
when they were doing laundry.
In 1998, the FTC approved
the use of symbols.
The care tag in this dress,
it's all symbols.
Now the final piece
of the puzzle
is the one that's missing.
There's no barcode.
There's no inventory number.
This dress was made
before the year 2000.
See, I like this staring.
That time frame leaves us
with 200 cases.
Yeah, but Raina's 911 call,
she said the person was shot.
And then there were nine.
No, that's not it.
Okay, only one case
had a victim wearing a dress
that looks a lot like Raina's.
Greta St. John,
25-year-old black woman,
up-and-coming singer,
last seen
New Year's Eve 2000 at a club
called the Black Jewel.
She was found across town
in an alley.
Died of a gunshot wound
to the chest,
but no weapon found
at the scene,
no witnesses,
not many suspect interviews.
The ME didn't even list
a clear time of death.
The ME noted powder burns
and shrapnel on her right side
but did very little about it.
This case
didn't get any attention.
Young Black woman found
on the wrong side of town.
Let me guess,
it wasn't a top story
on the evening news.
Okay, so 25 years ago,
Raina witnessed
the murder of Greta St. John.
And then was killed
before she could tell us
what she knew.
It stands to reason
that Raina and Greta
were killed by the same person,
likely someone
who knew them both.
According to the file,
there was a guy
named Eddie Friedman
who managed the Black Jewel
at the time of the murder.
-Go look, see what he knows.
-Lucy,
the woman that called Raina
three times,
just got back to me.
-She's willing to talk to us.
-Divide and conquer.
You guys track down Eddie.
We'll talk to Lucy.
Copy that.
What can you tell us
about Greta St. John?
Oh, she had a voice
like no other.
The New Year's Eve show
was her moment.
She was about to go big.
And did that rub anyone
the wrong way?
Oh, yeah. Raina Viera.
So, Lucy,
how did Raina
and Greta know each other?
They were rivals
at the Black Jewel.
Raina was a singer too,
but she didn't like talking
about Greta all too much.
Any specific reason why?
I met Raina
when I photographed her
for a piece I did
in Static Vinyl magazine.
It was about lost voices
of the '90s,
talented women who just
never really broke into
the cutthroat LA music scene.
I think it was hard for Raina
to talk about Greta.
She defied the odds
when Raina hadn't.
Greta's evolution as an artist
was...
...something else.
It made sense to all of us
why her star was rising.
During that
New Year's Eve show, everyone
knew who the star was.
This doesn't really sound
like an artist on her way up.
You're right.
See, that was Greta before.
And this... is Greta after.
Oh, wow. That hardly sounds
like the same woman.
So this song was recorded
after something happened.
What was it?
Mac Epps.
His name came up
in my research.
He was Greta's manager
at first,
but then he started working
with Raina,
and now
he owns the Black Jewel.
So two rivals
and the same manager?
Sounds like a bad idea.
Did Raina ever talk about Epps?
Not really,
but I did get the sense
that she blamed him
for her career
never taking off.
He was shady. After Epps
got arrested on a drug charge,
Greta found her voice, I mean,
literally and figuratively.
But after Epps got out,
he wanted to be a part of it.
Did Greta give in
to his demands?
No, and he didn't take it well.
He started harassing her.
The rumor was the only reason
he started managing Raina
was to get close to Greta.
He was using Raina as a pawn.
I think Raina realized
he wasn't really interested
in her career.
Then why didn't she leave?
He was a dangerous man
with powerful friends,
even then.
And that's why Greta
wanted nothing to do with him.
He turned her family's life
upside down for decades.
It explains why everyone
was radio silent
during
the original investigation
into Greta's murder.
I should have told the cops
what I knew back then,
but I was scared.
We all were.
If you have any photos
or videos
from the Black Jewel
that we could borrow,
that'd be helpful.
You bet. I have
more than you could ever
want or need.
We think Raina may have been
keeping a secret
that got her killed.
Do you have any idea
what that could be?
No, I have no idea
who would want to hurt her.
I can't believe she's gone.
She and I got really... close.
She was
like a second mother to me.
We're gonna find who did this.
The mailbox is full and cannot
accept any messages
at this time.
How long
till the lab gets back to us
with the results on that stain?
Oh, a lot longer
than we'd like. But you know
what's faster than the lab?
-Me?
-Hmm.
Can I have
everyone's attention, please?
You may have heard that I was
up for the captain's chair.
Turns out you're stuck with me.
Don't be so disappointed.
Right now, all I know
is they're bringing someone in
from another squad,
but no matter
who the captain is,
I expect you to treat him
with the same respect
you treat me.
You're still my squad.
Continue to do me proud
just like you always do.
Let's get back to work.
-It's not fair.
-Should have been you.
Clearly they don't know who
keeps things on the rails
around here.
I appreciate all that.
Why are you being
so cool right now? I hate this.
What are
this new guy's qualifications?
I'm assuming it's a guy.
Statistically, yes.
But you know what I hate?
Unsolved cases.
We have two right now.
So how about we focus
on who killed Greta and Raina.
So, suspects?
Well, Eddie Friedman
alibied out.
He was at Corbyn Lanes
with his bowling league.
Lucy Hastings was at
a photo shoot at Griffith Park.
She was alone, but her pictures
were time-stamped.
That leaves Mac Epps
as our prime suspect.
He's built an empire,
a mix of illicit
and legitimate businesses,
including the Black Jewel.
Yeah, and he had a motive
to kill Greta
because she was
about to blow up
and wasn't taking him with her.
What about Raina? Does he look
good for her murder too?
Well, Raina moved
into her current home
shortly after Greta's death.
No way she bought that house
in her 20s
unless she won the lottery.
Which is why we looked
at the deed.
The first few years,
Mac Epps's name was on it.
It was either a gift
or more likely
a payment for her silence.
A silence she maintained until
a dementia-induced episode
led her to reveal the truth.
Any indication Epps knew
that could be a possibility?
Well, we dug up CCTV footage
from outside of the Black Jewel
a few days ago
-and we found this.
-That is Mac Epps.
Yeah, doesn't look like
a friendly reunion.
No, it looks
like a motive for murder.
I think it's time
to visit the Black Jewel.
I know your silences, Morgan.
-My silences? It's not a thing.
-Mm-hmm.
Oh, it's a thing.
You get quiet a lot.
You got family-drama quiet,
a little furrow of the brow
and you start messing
with your cuticles like you're
trying to dig up a secret.
There's case-frustration quiet,
clenching of the jaw
and your eyes start scanning
like you're mentally breaking
apart the crime scene.
There's the pissed-at-me quiet.
That's a classic.
It's a stone-cold stare and
a little flare of the nostrils.
And then we've got this one
right here,
which is
the something-you-want-to-say
quiet.
Pursing of the lips,
distant look.
Whatever. I'm just worried
about Soto, aren't you?
-Have you talked to her?
-No. I don't plan to.
-That's it?
-Every cop's wired differently.
If she wanted
to open up to me, she would.
Okay, so your silence is just
"do nothing, say nothing."
Yeah.
Well, it's dumb,
and I don't care for it.
-Right back
to the pissed-at-me quiet.
-All right!
Mr. Epps isn't expecting you,
so I have to ask him
if it's okay.
It's okay
because I said it's okay. Okay?
You know what?
Just let him do his thing.
Otherwise he's gonna pull
his badge out, get all showy.
It's pretty annoying.
-Hey, boss. We got--
-Mac Epps.
- Detective Karadec, LAPD.
-  This is my-- -Yo, my man.
I don't really care who you are
or whatever she is.
Let me tell you how we do it
in the Black Jewel.
Make an appointment, come back
during office hours. Cool?
-Yeah, I don't think so.
-Oh, you can't.
Assaulting an officer
is a serious charge, son.
I tried to warn you, didn't I?
I just... I just warned him.
Thank you. Hi. Hi, I'm Morgan.
- Can I scooch?
- Hi. Yeah.
I'm Julie. I love this jacket.
Girl, I see you,
your style is everything.
-Thank you.
-Yeah.
-Is this for everyone?
-You know what?
I asked the same thing
when I got here
and I didn't get an answer,
-so I've just been going in.
-You just jumped
right in anyway?
-You got to. Mm-hmm.
-I like your style too.
Do me a favor.
Ask your questions and go.
Two names. Greta St. John,
Raina Viera.
-What about 'em?
-They're both dead, Mac.
Greta for 25 years,
case still cold.
Raina, about 36 hours or so.
I mean, you got anything
to say about that, Mac?
Nah, nothing.
Huh. That's interesting because
you managed both of them.
Matter of fact, you... you
bought Raina a house shortly
after Greta was murdered.
Suspicious timing, you know?
One thing has nothing to do
with the other.
I made a deal with Raina.
A big one.
I got the rights to her music
in exchange for the house.
But you know what?
I lost my ass on that deal.
Her career never took off,
but I let her have the place
out of the goodness
of my heart.
Aw. That's nice.
Um, speaking of your heart,
you were more
than Greta's manager.
She had a compass tattoo
on her wrist,
and I see that North Star.
Perfect match.
Two tools of navigation.
The compass leads the way.
The North Star holds steady.
That's so romantic.
So maybe Greta
wasn't just walking away
from your business.
Maybe she was walking away
from you.
Something personal
went down after that
New Year's Eve celebration.
Ball drops, confetti flies,
and then maybe a few
hours later, the next day--
You know what?
I've heard enough.
Now, either y'all leave now,
or I'ma tag my lawyer in
on this.
JJ Pierce. They call him
"The Badge Collector."
Heard of him?
I haven't heard of JJ.
-Have you heard
of nickel dermatitis?
-No.
It's a reaction to cheap metals
like the ones
that are in foil confetti.
When I saw pictures of Greta
before midnight,
her skin was so smooth
and clear, beautiful.
But at midnight,
the ball dropped
and so did the confetti.
And wherever the confetti
landed on her skin,
there were hives.
Nickel can trigger hives
very quickly,
in under a minute.
They were still there
in the autopsy photos.
You put all that together,
and what I'm saying is,
Greta was murdered in this club
just a few hours
after midnight.
-I'm done talking.
-Well,
we're not done digging.
I have a feeling
we'll see you again real soon.
And next time, put out
some little share plates.
-It's less confusing
and more sanitary.
-Morgan.
Oh. See how many times
- I put my fingernails in there?
- Mm-hmm.
I just got a call
from Epps's lawyer, JJ Pierce.
What does The Badge Collector
have to say?
That if we ever go back
to the Black Jewel
without a warrant,
he will add to his collection.
Well,
this is interesting.
Soto, look at this picture.
And this one a week later.
And then this one
a month after that.
Do you see what I see?
-She had a baby.
Um, I don't get it.
Yeah, well,
that doesn't surprise me.
Love you, LA.
Nobody really
teaches you
about women's bodies.
People think the party returns
when the pregnancy ends,
but being postpartum sucks.
Look, she's got a splint on
'cause she had mommy wrist.
Repetitive hand
and wrist movements while
holding a baby can do that.
She ditched the heels 'cause
you're not hauling around a kid
and a diaper bag in high heels.
That's just dumb.
And then she started
styling her hair differently
because it was falling out.
All of these are symptoms
of that three-month period
after a baby's born.
It's called
the fourth trimester.
And then when Epps
was behind bars,
Greta really found herself.
I think
it's because she became a mom,
and to protect her child,
she had to hide that baby
from a dangerous father.
She had Epps's baby,
and when he eventually
found out about the child,
there was a confrontation
and he killed her.
How do we prove
he pulled the trigger?
That gun is long gone.
But maybe
it left something behind.
Here's what I'm thinking.
Look at all these pictures
of Epps. Do you see
his right hand?
-Do you notice anything?
-Yeah, New Year's Eve, no scar.
New Year's Day,
a bandaged hand.
He hurt himself that night.
That's right.
And Greta's autopsy photos,
the right side of her face.
-Powder burns on her jaw.
-Yeah, given to her
from Epps's gun.
He shot her in the chest,
but that wouldn't have
caused the powder burn
on her face,
so he fired again.
But that wouldn't have caused
the scar on his hand.
An explosion would.
The only way a gun explodes
is by firing it
after it was jammed.
So the first shot
was to her chest,
the second shot was a jam,
and the third shot exploded,
ripping through his hand,
and burning her face.
And Raina witnessed
the entire thing.
What did you do?
Which explains
the blood on Raina's dress.
Greta!
That scar
puts the murder weapon
in Epps's hand.
Looks like
The Badge Collector's
about to get his warrant.
I'll get it within the hour.
You go back to the club,
I'll get Daphne and Oz
to go to his home.
- You stay here.
- What? No, I'm coming with you.
-Morgan, it's not safe.
-I will be fine.
Karadec, I need to see
the look on his smug face
when he finds out
we got him for murder.
I cannot risk you getting hurt
in a raid.
I'll bring in Greta's killer.
You find her child.
Fine,
but when you get him--
You'll see his smug face when
I put him in the box. Promise.
Excuse me. Move, move, move.
Excuse me.
Epps!
Outta the way. Move, move.
Excuse me. Outta the way.
Let me go!
-Put the gun down, Epps!
-Nah, I like where it is.
The place is surrounded.
The only way out for you
is in cuffs.
You must be crazy if you think
I'm going back inside.
You should have thought
about that before you killed
Greta St. John.
Greta got exactly
what she deserved.
You tell me what kind of woman
keeps a man
from his child, huh?
For years,
I searched everywhere.
You stand down right now
and I promise you
I will do everything I can
to help you find your child.
It's too late! You stand down,
or she's gonna end up
just like Greta.
If you do that, Mac,
you leave me no choice
but to respond.
I'd rather be carried by six
than tried by 12.
Let's see who blinks first.
Who's that guy?
I don't like him from out here.
-Internal Affairs.
-What?
You discharge your weapon,
it's a big deal.
He saved Julie's life,
and it's not like
he killed the guy.
Doesn't matter.
This is the process.
Well, should I be worried?
Epps killed Greta. I think
he killed Raina.
You can't expect me
-to just sit at home.
-It's policy.
You have to be cleared
by behavior science section
before you can return to work.
Come on, Solomon.
You know how long
it takes to get an appointment.
It's my job to make
sure you follow the rules,
not help you break them.
Okay, fine. So call and get me
on the books first thing.
-That is not
breaking the rules.
-No, but it's bending them.
And that is not my style.
It used to not be yours.
I wouldn't ask
if it wasn't important.
Every case is important, Adam.
I'm sorry. Policy is policy.
Doesn't policy say
that we withhold judgments
and investigate every case
to the fullest extent
of the law, hmm?
That didn't happen
for Greta St. John.
If the job had been done right,
I wouldn't have had to pull
that trigger, and Raina Viera
would still be alive
because Mac Epps would
have been in prison and
not out running the streets.
What does policy say
about that?
Just this
once I will make the call.
Thank you. Whatever time
they have, I'll be there.
Then go with Morgan
to the impound.
Check Epps's car for anything
tying him to Raina's murder.
Yeah.
I've heard some things
about this consultant.
Then you know
how invaluable she is.
Her value comes
with a lot of things
that make me nervous.
Kind of nervous that has me
looking at your reports
a bit more often.
What happens with my squad
is none of your business.
Till it is.
Good night, Selena.
Pretty clean car
for such a giant dirtbag.
Let's just hope
we find something in here that
helps us prove he killed Raina.
Hey, you okay?
I'm fine. Why?
Because you just shot
somebody yesterday.
You don't go from that to fine
in 24 hours.
I told you it was a clean shot.
IA will clear me.
I'm not worried
about your badge.
I'm worried about you.
Typically when someone pretends
that something big
doesn't matter,
it means that it really does.
You and Soto are doing a lot
of pretending that you're fine.
A cop's worst nightmare
is having
to discharge their weapon.
Yeah, I bet. How many times
have you done that?
Three. But I never hit anyone
till now.
Epps had a gun pressed
to a young woman's temple.
He'd killed before, would have
had no problem doing it again,
so I had exactly two options.
Let him go or shoot him.
Knowing that if I missed--
You might kill the person
you're trying to protect.
How'd you do that?
Weren't you worried
you might accidentally hit her?
Every morning
I start my day
at the gun range.
Discipline. Repetition.
Endless hours
focused on one thought.
What would I do if a day
like yesterday ever came?
I'd seen that shot in my mind
every day for the last
20 years, and I took it.
I knew I wouldn't miss.
Check this out.
Some kind of pass.
Monday is
when Raina was killed.
It's a visitor's pass
to a federal prison.
So Epps was visiting a prison
on Monday.
California's got
13 federal prisons.
I'll have Daphne and Oz
start calling each one.
Are there any near
the Mojave Desert? 'Cause
that's where this car was.
Yucca moth. They're dependent
on Joshua trees for survival,
so if one
hit Epps's windshield,
this car was in the Mojave.
Well, the only one
out that way is Victorville,
but it's a two-hour drive.
Epps confessed to killing Greta
25 years ago.
But if he was two hours away
in the desert
when Raina was killed...
Then he's not our guy.
All right, so...
...Raina helped Epps
cover up Greta's murder.
Which is
why we've been thinking
Epps pushed Raina
down the stairs to keep
Greta's murder a secret.
But the prison
in Victorville confirmed
he was there
at the time of Raina's murder.
Mm-hmm. That means
Raina and Greta were killed
by two different people
25 years apart.
Okay, so if Raina's murder
wasn't about keeping secrets,
maybe it was about revenge.
You're thinking
someone found out Raina's role
in Greta's murder
and then killed her.
Yep, so now we need to be
thinking about family members.
Maybe even Greta's child.
We still have no idea
what happened to the baby.
Well, there was no record
of Greta giving birth in LA.
She could've
used an alias.
Or given birth
somewhere else entirely,
making it nearly impossible
to find her child.
Well, hang on,
I think I know exactly
what happened to Greta's kid.
And to Raina.
Detective, Ms. Gillory, uh,
is there news
about Raina's case?
-Yes, we've had
a big break actually.
-Thought you'd like to know.
We finally know who killed her.
That's great.
It's you.
What? I loved Raina.
That might be true,
but you also killed her.
I couldn't have killed her.
I told you I was at work.
Right. You said that,
at the time of the murder,
you were taking pictures
at Griffith Observatory.
With one
of your cameras that has
the built-in time stamp.
You know what's more reliable
than a time stamp? The sun.
A couple cool things about
the Griffith Observatory:
The observation deck has these
bronze lines built into it,
and it shows you the position
of the sun in the sky
throughout the year.
And that weird ring sculpture
with the wire through it,
that's actually a sundial.
So your time stamp said you
took those pictures at noon
on a Monday,
but the sun tells me
they were taken around
3 p.m.-ish last December.
This is crazy.
-No, it's not crazy.
-It's science.
And we can prove
you're the one
that pushed Raina.
Raina had a smudge
on the back of her shirt,
drove my partner here crazy.
Yeah, I couldn't figure out
what that stain was.
So once again, your profession
was your undoing.
Turns out
it was silver nitrate,
something photographers
like yourself use when
you're developing pictures.
You must have had
a small amount of it on your
hands when you pushed her.
The only question was
why would she do that?
Why would you kill Raina?
You said she was
like a second mother to you.
We're guessing that all
went out the window as soon
as you realized
she was lying to you
about your actual mother,
Greta St. John.
The last time
we were here,
you said that Epps terrorized
Greta's family for decades.
It's not something
you would know, Lucy,
not unless you were family.
Unless you were the reason
that Greta made
all those sacrifices.
I just came here searching
for answers
about what happened to my mom.
Yes, I found Raina, and
I kept my identity a secret.
But then she...
...started having
all these episodes,
because of her dementia.
That's when she confessed to me
that she was a part
of covering up my mom's death.
But she wouldn't give you
the whole story.
No, and...
...I find out that
Mac Epps is my dad,
and that
he probably killed her.
So I just wanted Raina
to tell me the truth
about what happened.
So I did. I confronted her,
but then she just...
she flipped out on me,
threatened to never speak
to me again.
I snapped.
Look, I swear...
...I swear I did not mean
to kill her.
Lucy, we got justice
for your mom, and now we have
to do the same thing for Raina.
Oh, my God.
You're under arrest
for the murder
of Raina Viera.
Come on. This way.
Seriously, Gillory?
We can get you a computer.
I'll go get it myself.
How am I gonna make you nervous
about your search history
if I'm on my own computer?
Mmm.
Y-You were right.
I'm sorry. Could you say
that again? I didn't hear you.
What was I right about?
I've been taking care
of myself for a long time.
So long that sometimes I forget
what it's like to have
somebody looking out for me.
You were right about me
not going to the Black Jewel.
Certain things
a police consultant
does not need to be around.
-You were right too.
-Oh, yeah?
Mm-hmm. My "do nothing,
say nothing" silence,
it's not optimal.
You have no plans
to change that, do you?
Well, I don't need to.
I've got you.
Something else?
Yeah, one last thing.
You're allowed
to be pissed with me.
-Morgan, what did you do?
-Nothing.
No, I didn't mean you're
allowed to be pissed at me.
You can. You're my boss.
You can do whatever you want,
but that's not
what I'm talking about.
I feel like I lost track of
this conversation
before it started.
Despite your
overwhelming qualifications,
you were passed over
for captain.
And I have to assume
that part of you wonders
if that has anything to do
with you being a woman.
-Because if it were me--
-You would have gone
scorched earth.
Oh, absolutely,
and I would have loved
every single second of it,
so they're lucky
that you're not me.
You're you.
You gotta be strong
for everybody out there.
I understand that.
One of the beautiful things
about me not being a cop is--
Is that
I can be pissed with you.
Anything you need.
Anytime you need it.
I could just be your friend.
I'm pissed.
It should have been me.
Yeah.
This never happened.
I never even cared in
the first place. I don't know
what you're talking about.
-Hi.
All I want is
to enter my house justified.
Okay.
It's just a line from
an old western I love.
Mmm.
It's a line from the Bible.
That's right, it is.
Peckinpah stole it.
Anyway,
it's my clumsy way of saying
you look like somebody
who's proud
of a good day's work.
Thank you. I am.
I'm also so tired
I might fall asleep in my car.
All I want is to fall asleep
in my car justified.
So what's someone like you
doing in a police station?
Trying to get that mustache
to make sense?
That's good.
I've heard about you.
-Excuse me?
-Morgan Gillory, right?
Major Crime's secret weapon.
I didn't mean to freak you out.
I've just been
looking forward to meeting you.
Okay.
-Are you not getting off?
-Nah, I was supposed
to get off at three.
I just wanted
to finish our conversation.
Third floor. That's Command.
So it is. Nick Wagner.
Your new captain.