1
00:00:02,109 --> 00:00:04,880
I called earlier about a missing
U.S. citizen in the Middle East.

2
00:00:04,883 --> 00:00:06,049
How are you, Sara?

3
00:00:06,052 --> 00:00:08,318
I wanted the State Department, not you.

4
00:00:08,353 --> 00:00:10,918
Any chance Poseidon will
just let us kill her?

5
00:00:10,921 --> 00:00:12,522
I've learned some things

6
00:00:12,558 --> 00:00:14,624
about who it is we're
apparently both looking for.

7
00:00:14,660 --> 00:00:16,693
You think Michael's in Yemen?

8
00:00:16,728 --> 00:00:19,796
- We're gonna get you out of here.
- I don't know who you are.

9
00:00:19,832 --> 00:00:23,133
Your brother was using
this shop for his escape.

10
00:00:23,168 --> 00:00:24,434
We're here for passports.

11
00:00:27,639 --> 00:00:30,240
Figure we got a day to
get out of this hole.

12
00:00:30,275 --> 00:00:32,961
We're still getting out. All of us.

13
00:00:33,828 --> 00:00:36,550
_

14
00:00:36,586 --> 00:00:38,328
_

15
00:00:38,357 --> 00:00:40,619
Poseidon put us in
here to get Ramal out,

16
00:00:40,622 --> 00:00:42,065
but then he abandoned us.

17
00:00:42,068 --> 00:00:44,036
Ramal's Poseidon's guy, not ours.

18
00:00:44,039 --> 00:00:46,882
Our friend told me about the escape.

19
00:00:46,885 --> 00:00:48,385
He will betray you.

20
00:00:48,388 --> 00:00:49,960
When those lights go black,

21
00:00:49,995 --> 00:00:52,229
we're gonna disappear from
this place like ghosts.

22
00:00:52,264 --> 00:00:53,530
I can't get it open.

23
00:00:53,565 --> 00:00:55,332
Help me out.

24
00:00:55,367 --> 00:00:57,968
You pull my brother up first.

25
00:01:03,208 --> 00:01:04,708
Don't shoot.

26
00:01:07,012 --> 00:01:10,480
_

27
00:01:14,887 --> 00:01:16,887
- Hey.
- Hey.

28
00:01:16,922 --> 00:01:18,722
How are you feeling?

29
00:01:18,757 --> 00:01:20,624
Body is fine.

30
00:01:20,659 --> 00:01:22,058
My head is

31
00:01:22,094 --> 00:01:24,427
trying to figure out how
to get those passports

32
00:01:24,463 --> 00:01:26,029
we couldn't get last night.

33
00:01:26,064 --> 00:01:28,765
For you, those kids.

34
00:01:28,800 --> 00:01:30,400
Well, that's something you shouldn't

35
00:01:30,435 --> 00:01:31,835
be worrying about right now.

36
00:01:31,870 --> 00:01:33,570
You should rest up.
We're gonna need you.

37
00:01:33,605 --> 00:01:35,138
I can rest when I'm dead.

38
00:01:35,173 --> 00:01:39,009
Well, that's what I'm worried about.

39
00:01:39,912 --> 00:01:41,878
Didn't know you worried.

40
00:01:41,914 --> 00:01:44,014
About the right things.

41
00:01:46,902 --> 00:01:48,368
Your brother.

42
00:01:49,655 --> 00:01:51,988
He make it out?

43
00:01:52,024 --> 00:01:54,558
- I'm sorry.
- Yeah.

44
00:01:57,272 --> 00:01:59,338
Sheba, do you mind if I
borrow Linc for a second?

45
00:01:59,341 --> 00:02:01,264
- Yeah.
- Okay.

46
00:02:01,300 --> 00:02:03,633
Please get some rest.

47
00:02:14,366 --> 00:02:16,066
Listen. We got to start talking

48
00:02:16,102 --> 00:02:17,568
about leaving the country.

49
00:02:17,603 --> 00:02:18,802
What are you talking about?

50
00:02:18,838 --> 00:02:21,238
I spoke to my friends at the mosque.

51
00:02:21,273 --> 00:02:23,607
ISIL is taking
neighborhoods by the hour.

52
00:02:23,642 --> 00:02:25,509
If they cut off the
route to the airport...

53
00:02:25,544 --> 00:02:28,479
I'm not leaving Michael.

54
00:02:28,514 --> 00:02:31,448
If they cut off the airport,
no one is getting out.

55
00:02:31,484 --> 00:02:33,417
Not you, me, Sheba.

56
00:02:34,453 --> 00:02:38,188
As much as it kills me to say...

57
00:02:38,224 --> 00:02:41,859
we can't risk all of it for...

58
00:02:41,894 --> 00:02:43,127
just one man.

59
00:02:44,390 --> 00:02:46,424
You're right.

60
00:02:46,427 --> 00:02:47,664
You can leave.

61
00:02:47,700 --> 00:02:49,299
But I can't.

62
00:02:49,335 --> 00:02:52,469
Get that family to the
airport as fast as you can.

63
00:02:52,505 --> 00:02:53,804
I'll work something out.

64
00:02:53,839 --> 00:02:56,607
Mr. Burrows?

65
00:02:56,641 --> 00:02:59,409
I wanted to thank you
for saving my daughter.

66
00:02:59,445 --> 00:03:02,505
And offer you something in appreciation.

67
00:03:02,508 --> 00:03:04,648
I might have a solution
for how to get your brother

68
00:03:04,650 --> 00:03:06,183
out of that prison.

69
00:03:07,987 --> 00:03:11,088
Before the city goes to hell.

70
00:03:12,275 --> 00:03:16,159
_

71
00:03:18,732 --> 00:03:19,658
You hear that?

72
00:03:19,661 --> 00:03:21,364
That was the closest one yet!

73
00:03:21,400 --> 00:03:22,499
100 yards!

74
00:03:22,535 --> 00:03:23,967
Just when you think
it couldn't get worse

75
00:03:23,969 --> 00:03:25,602
locked up in a Porta Potti,

76
00:03:25,638 --> 00:03:29,273
they start dropping 2,000-pound
bombs on the Porta Potti.

77
00:03:29,308 --> 00:03:31,975
Whip. Keep it together, please.

78
00:03:37,587 --> 00:03:39,120
The escape artist is nervous.

79
00:03:39,123 --> 00:03:40,284
You should be, too.

80
00:03:40,319 --> 00:03:43,320
Those artillery strikes,
they don't discriminate.

81
00:03:43,355 --> 00:03:45,489
The difference is I have faith.

82
00:03:45,524 --> 00:03:47,157
Allah will deliver me.

83
00:03:47,193 --> 00:03:48,892
What do you have?

84
00:03:48,928 --> 00:03:51,195
Ja!

85
00:03:51,230 --> 00:03:52,347
Ja, are you there?

86
00:03:52,371 --> 00:03:53,197
I'm here.

87
00:03:55,434 --> 00:03:56,333
Whip's right.

88
00:03:56,368 --> 00:03:58,468
The strikes are getting closer.

89
00:03:58,504 --> 00:03:59,803
I pity you.

90
00:03:59,839 --> 00:04:01,438
I triumph either way.

91
00:04:01,473 --> 00:04:04,877
Either I will be in paradise
or Allah will save me.

92
00:04:04,913 --> 00:04:06,279
You,

93
00:04:06,282 --> 00:04:08,312
you're just going to die.

94
00:04:12,546 --> 00:04:15,179
ISIL has broken through the checkpoints.

95
00:04:15,182 --> 00:04:16,553
They're coming into the city.

96
00:04:16,555 --> 00:04:17,855
These uniforms are like targets

97
00:04:17,890 --> 00:04:20,324
- on our backs.
- ISIL isn't here yet.

98
00:04:20,359 --> 00:04:22,159
The government says
it will push them back.

99
00:04:22,194 --> 00:04:23,894
You out of your head? This is happening.

100
00:04:23,929 --> 00:04:25,662
Sana'a is falling.

101
00:04:30,342 --> 00:04:31,675
They're going to retreat.

102
00:04:31,707 --> 00:04:33,971
I've seen that look before in the army.

103
00:04:34,006 --> 00:04:36,373
Men who will do anything
to save themselves.

104
00:04:36,408 --> 00:04:38,609
And how do we save ourselves?

105
00:04:38,644 --> 00:04:41,044
ISIL takes this prison, we'll
be the first they slaughter.

106
00:04:41,080 --> 00:04:42,813
When they take this prison, it will be

107
00:04:42,848 --> 00:04:45,249
to liberate their leader, Ramal,

108
00:04:45,284 --> 00:04:46,950
but if when they get here,

109
00:04:46,986 --> 00:04:48,919
we have him with a knife

110
00:04:48,954 --> 00:04:50,454
to his throat,

111
00:04:50,489 --> 00:04:52,122
then we call the shots.

112
00:04:52,157 --> 00:04:53,824
And we might just live.

113
00:04:53,859 --> 00:04:56,124
Whip, I got a Hail Mary.

114
00:04:56,156 --> 00:04:58,343
- That a prayer or a plan?
- Plan.

115
00:04:58,346 --> 00:05:00,197
I left something the
last time I was in here.

116
00:05:00,199 --> 00:05:01,865
Let me guess, you got a contingency.

117
00:05:01,901 --> 00:05:04,101
They lock me away in
a box for four years.

118
00:05:04,136 --> 00:05:05,402
I'm not just gonna sit there.

119
00:05:05,437 --> 00:05:07,478
It's a long shot, but
it might get us out.

120
00:05:07,481 --> 00:05:09,408
The infidel still tries to escape.

121
00:05:09,411 --> 00:05:10,874
The desperate rat.

122
00:05:10,910 --> 00:05:12,542
The desperate rat's gonna light you up

123
00:05:12,578 --> 00:05:13,810
once we get out of here,

124
00:05:13,846 --> 00:05:15,712
- you bugged-eyed freak.
- Whip.

125
00:05:15,748 --> 00:05:18,148
Whip! An "S." Is there an "S"

126
00:05:18,183 --> 00:05:19,449
carved in your wall chest high

127
00:05:19,485 --> 00:05:21,084
in the corner?

128
00:05:22,029 --> 00:05:23,796
Come on, come on.

129
00:05:23,824 --> 00:05:25,155
That's not it.

130
00:05:25,190 --> 00:05:27,257
I'm not seeing anything.

131
00:05:27,293 --> 00:05:28,605
I'm not seeing it.

132
00:05:28,608 --> 00:05:30,136
Ja, it's got to be you.

133
00:05:30,139 --> 00:05:32,329
Come on. Tell me you got
an "S" carved in your wall.

134
00:05:32,331 --> 00:05:33,463
It's our last chance.

135
00:05:33,499 --> 00:05:34,517
No.

136
00:05:34,520 --> 00:05:35,900
It's not here, no.

137
00:05:51,383 --> 00:05:54,151
That's because I have it in my cell.

138
00:05:56,889 --> 00:05:59,489
My armies of the caliphate

139
00:05:59,525 --> 00:06:01,558
are coming closer.

140
00:06:01,593 --> 00:06:03,794
The moment they reach this place,

141
00:06:03,829 --> 00:06:07,931
all of you will be put down
like the dogs that you are.

142
00:06:41,858 --> 00:06:43,899
_

143
00:06:52,327 --> 00:06:54,093
All right, Sara.

144
00:06:54,129 --> 00:06:57,230
Our friend, Poseidon, has surfaced.

145
00:07:09,577 --> 00:07:11,143
Good God.

146
00:07:11,179 --> 00:07:13,179
Another ISIL attack.

147
00:07:14,066 --> 00:07:16,800
They're ripping the city apart.

148
00:07:16,831 --> 00:07:19,064
They're animals.

149
00:07:19,097 --> 00:07:20,953
I've been a bureaucrat my whole life.

150
00:07:20,955 --> 00:07:22,504
Hated it.

151
00:07:22,540 --> 00:07:24,290
Corruption, backslapping.

152
00:07:24,326 --> 00:07:26,732
But today, maybe some
good will come of it.

153
00:07:26,735 --> 00:07:28,727
I went to grammar school with this boy

154
00:07:28,763 --> 00:07:30,396
named Ibrahim.

155
00:07:30,399 --> 00:07:33,074
All the years later,
he's a federal judge.

156
00:07:33,077 --> 00:07:35,810
You, uh, saying this judge can help us?

157
00:07:35,813 --> 00:07:37,579
I called him a few
hours ago and told him

158
00:07:37,615 --> 00:07:38,981
about your brother's case.

159
00:07:40,367 --> 00:07:41,881
_

160
00:07:41,884 --> 00:07:44,453
Redecorating, I see.

161
00:07:44,489 --> 00:07:47,789
Just readying for the
coming change of seasons.

162
00:07:47,825 --> 00:07:51,560
Luxury is something the
Wahabbists frown upon,

163
00:07:51,596 --> 00:07:53,795
so luxury will stay behind closed doors.

164
00:07:53,831 --> 00:07:55,579
You should flee the country.

165
00:07:55,603 --> 00:07:56,998
I'm a survivor, you know that.

166
00:07:57,034 --> 00:07:58,934
I thought Mr. Burrows could perhaps

167
00:07:58,970 --> 00:08:00,469
help with his brother's cause.

168
00:08:00,505 --> 00:08:03,138
Ah, yes.

169
00:08:03,174 --> 00:08:07,876
A full pardon from the
Supreme Judicial Council.

170
00:08:07,912 --> 00:08:10,445
But you will have to uphold
your end of the bargain,

171
00:08:10,481 --> 00:08:12,615
Jamil.

172
00:08:14,496 --> 00:08:17,986
German engineering. 77,000 miles.

173
00:08:18,022 --> 00:08:19,938
Five liter, seven speed, V10.

174
00:08:19,941 --> 00:08:22,624
It will be a welcome bit of luxury.

175
00:08:22,660 --> 00:08:25,294
Behind closed doors, of course.

176
00:08:25,297 --> 00:08:28,230
Best of luck to both of you.

177
00:08:28,266 --> 00:08:29,498
I really appreciate this.

178
00:08:29,534 --> 00:08:30,866
Thank you.

179
00:08:30,902 --> 00:08:32,968
It's already done.

180
00:08:33,004 --> 00:08:37,706
It would've been left behind anyhow.

181
00:08:39,553 --> 00:08:40,888
May both of our families

182
00:08:40,891 --> 00:08:43,311
get safely out of Sana'a tonight.

183
00:08:45,341 --> 00:08:47,245
We can't just sit here and die.

184
00:08:47,256 --> 00:08:49,651
You-you got a window
like this one, right?

185
00:08:49,687 --> 00:08:51,044
Maybe we can pry it.

186
00:08:51,047 --> 00:08:52,854
It's too small, reinforced.

187
00:08:52,890 --> 00:08:54,614
Built into the rebar infrastructure.

188
00:08:54,617 --> 00:08:56,169
You got people on the outside, right?

189
00:08:56,172 --> 00:08:57,660
And they're gonna try and get us out.

190
00:08:57,662 --> 00:08:58,994
They were supposed
to meet us at the shop

191
00:08:58,996 --> 00:09:00,328
last night and we didn't show.

192
00:09:00,364 --> 00:09:01,496
We can't just quit

193
00:09:01,532 --> 00:09:03,798
- and let Poseidon beat us.
- Ramal?

194
00:09:03,834 --> 00:09:06,101
There's a way out if we work together,

195
00:09:06,137 --> 00:09:08,203
but escape has to start from your cell.

196
00:09:08,239 --> 00:09:10,239
I'm no longer interested.

197
00:09:10,741 --> 00:09:13,904
The only thing left
for you to do is to beg.

198
00:09:13,907 --> 00:09:16,845
Beg that I might let you
live once my armies came,

199
00:09:16,881 --> 00:09:18,346
if only as a slave.

200
00:09:18,382 --> 00:09:20,482
I've been a slave for
the last seven years.

201
00:09:20,518 --> 00:09:22,051
I won't do it anymore!

202
00:09:26,047 --> 00:09:28,447
I will miss you when you're dead,

203
00:09:28,483 --> 00:09:30,416
but only for a minute.

204
00:09:30,452 --> 00:09:31,617
Then you will be forgotten

205
00:09:31,653 --> 00:09:35,888
by both time and the world.

206
00:09:35,924 --> 00:09:38,424
Well, she's my kid, too, Cindy.

207
00:09:38,427 --> 00:09:40,058
I have the weekends and...

208
00:09:40,094 --> 00:09:41,393
Well, no, I have the weekends

209
00:09:41,429 --> 00:09:43,149
and I don't want a Wednesday afternoon.

210
00:09:43,152 --> 00:09:44,351
Why would I want that?

211
00:09:44,354 --> 00:09:47,332
Yeah, nobody does.

212
00:09:50,305 --> 00:09:53,672
Uh-huh.

213
00:09:53,708 --> 00:09:55,808
No, that's okay, Cindy.

214
00:10:02,305 --> 00:10:04,817
Mm-hmm.

215
00:10:04,853 --> 00:10:06,084
Yeah, that's fine.

216
00:10:06,120 --> 00:10:07,319
What other days?

217
00:10:07,355 --> 00:10:08,842
What other days do you want?

218
00:10:13,736 --> 00:10:15,810
Actually, you know what?

219
00:10:15,858 --> 00:10:18,158
I don't want to discuss this now.

220
00:10:18,217 --> 00:10:19,998
No, we'll talk about it later.

221
00:10:20,034 --> 00:10:21,834
Bye.

222
00:10:24,672 --> 00:10:26,638
Of all the things

223
00:10:26,674 --> 00:10:28,474
that mystify me in this world

224
00:10:28,510 --> 00:10:30,209
since I've been released,

225
00:10:30,245 --> 00:10:33,812
is that kale is the rage.

226
00:10:33,848 --> 00:10:35,013
Kale.

227
00:10:35,049 --> 00:10:37,382
Theodore Bagwell.

228
00:10:37,418 --> 00:10:39,518
Thing that mystifies me equally

229
00:10:39,554 --> 00:10:41,053
is seven years ago,

230
00:10:41,089 --> 00:10:42,941
you exonerated Michael,

231
00:10:42,944 --> 00:10:44,189
Lincoln, all of them,

232
00:10:44,225 --> 00:10:46,216
except me.

233
00:10:48,496 --> 00:10:50,095
- Really?
- Yes!

234
00:10:50,131 --> 00:10:51,230
That's why you're here?

235
00:10:51,266 --> 00:10:53,177
Because I didn't exonerate you?

236
00:10:53,180 --> 00:10:54,333
A murderer,

237
00:10:54,369 --> 00:10:56,768
a sexual predator a dozen times over.

238
00:10:56,804 --> 00:10:58,170
"Was" is the key word.

239
00:10:58,206 --> 00:11:00,780
I'm a man moving toward the light now,

240
00:11:00,783 --> 00:11:02,249
and the light's beckoning me.

241
00:11:02,252 --> 00:11:04,911
I just don't know who's
pulling the strings.

242
00:11:05,880 --> 00:11:07,246
But Sara says it's you.

243
00:11:07,282 --> 00:11:09,715
Oh, Sara put you onto me?

244
00:11:09,751 --> 00:11:11,149
Okay.

245
00:11:11,185 --> 00:11:12,985
I don't know who the bigger idiot is,

246
00:11:13,021 --> 00:11:14,253
you or her.

247
00:11:14,289 --> 00:11:15,730
I was helping her.

248
00:11:15,733 --> 00:11:19,992
You were hacking her phone
and sending those people

249
00:11:20,028 --> 00:11:21,527
after her... Don't...

250
00:11:21,563 --> 00:11:22,929
lie.

251
00:11:25,466 --> 00:11:27,132
Now...

252
00:11:27,168 --> 00:11:30,068
how about you pour me one of
them nasty little kale jobbies,

253
00:11:30,104 --> 00:11:33,205
and tell me what's all this got
to do with Scofield and myself,

254
00:11:33,241 --> 00:11:34,506
who your friends are,

255
00:11:34,542 --> 00:11:36,041
who you are... I want to see

256
00:11:36,077 --> 00:11:38,210
the true face of who's
pulling my strings

257
00:11:38,246 --> 00:11:39,879
once and for all.

258
00:11:44,379 --> 00:11:46,018
You have two visitors in the lobby.

259
00:11:46,020 --> 00:11:47,253
Tell them I'll be right down.

260
00:11:57,301 --> 00:11:59,368
Hey.

261
00:11:59,841 --> 00:12:01,541
I got this, Grace.

262
00:12:14,045 --> 00:12:15,648
They're in the city.

263
00:12:21,617 --> 00:12:22,616
What are you doing?

264
00:12:22,619 --> 00:12:24,855
What do you think I'm doing?

265
00:12:24,858 --> 00:12:25,924
Don't run, you dog!

266
00:12:25,927 --> 00:12:27,593
Don't run!

267
00:12:27,629 --> 00:12:29,895
It is happening. Be ready.

268
00:12:36,230 --> 00:12:37,714
This pardon better get him out of here.

269
00:12:37,716 --> 00:12:40,064
We don't have much time...
we have to get to the warden.

270
00:12:40,942 --> 00:12:42,007
What's going on?

271
00:12:47,081 --> 00:12:49,481
They're abandoning the
prison. That's why Ibrahim

272
00:12:49,517 --> 00:12:50,816
gave us that pardon.

273
00:12:50,852 --> 00:12:52,136
He knew it was worthless.

274
00:12:52,139 --> 00:12:54,453
You and C-Note get the
others to the airport

275
00:12:54,489 --> 00:12:56,555
as fast as you can...
There's maybe one flight out.

276
00:12:56,591 --> 00:12:57,847
Save two seats.

277
00:12:57,879 --> 00:12:59,291
All right?

278
00:12:59,327 --> 00:13:00,659
What are you going to do?

279
00:13:00,695 --> 00:13:03,261
I'm gonna get my brother.

280
00:13:12,698 --> 00:13:14,898
Mustapha!

281
00:13:23,852 --> 00:13:25,919
Back up!

282
00:13:25,957 --> 00:13:28,073
Back up. Anyone comes at me, dies.

283
00:13:28,108 --> 00:13:30,699
- Understand?
- You think you can shoot all of us?

284
00:13:31,812 --> 00:13:34,279
Anyone else want to play the lottery?

285
00:13:34,314 --> 00:13:36,281
Huh? You're filth.

286
00:13:36,316 --> 00:13:38,483
I'll let ISIL sort you out.

287
00:13:40,420 --> 00:13:43,235
Mustapha!

288
00:13:43,238 --> 00:13:45,457
Mustapha! Mustapha, wait!

289
00:13:45,492 --> 00:13:47,025
Don't lock me in here!

290
00:13:47,060 --> 00:13:48,460
You coward.

291
00:13:48,495 --> 00:13:49,527
Mustapha, please.

292
00:13:50,462 --> 00:13:52,229
Coward!

293
00:13:58,888 --> 00:14:01,677
- I need to get in!
- I need to get out!

294
00:14:01,680 --> 00:14:03,575
- Well, give me the key.
- I don't have the key.

295
00:14:03,610 --> 00:14:05,844
You passed the guy who does.

296
00:14:39,846 --> 00:14:41,746
Stay back! I don't want to shoot you!

297
00:14:49,547 --> 00:14:50,591
The guards are gone!

298
00:14:50,594 --> 00:14:52,390
They're abandoning their posts!

299
00:14:53,694 --> 00:14:55,393
We're gonna be free!

300
00:14:55,429 --> 00:14:58,096
No. We're not free.

301
00:14:58,131 --> 00:15:00,532
Things just got a lot worse.

302
00:15:00,567 --> 00:15:01,933
Push the gate open!

303
00:15:01,969 --> 00:15:03,401
Stop! Stop!

304
00:15:03,437 --> 00:15:04,643
What are you doing?

305
00:15:04,646 --> 00:15:06,938
- We have to get through the gate!
- If ISIL controls the city,

306
00:15:06,940 --> 00:15:09,474
like they say, it will be
a prison out there as well.

307
00:15:09,509 --> 00:15:10,937
We will be persecuted,

308
00:15:10,940 --> 00:15:13,181
as we have been in here, only worse!

309
00:15:13,184 --> 00:15:14,383
At least there's a chance!

310
00:15:14,386 --> 00:15:15,447
You want a chance?

311
00:15:15,481 --> 00:15:17,245
Our chance lies in there,

312
00:15:17,276 --> 00:15:18,675
in solitary.

313
00:15:18,706 --> 00:15:20,233
Our bargaining chip.

314
00:15:20,253 --> 00:15:21,686
We get Abu Ramal!

315
00:15:21,722 --> 00:15:23,222
We negotiate passage

316
00:15:23,253 --> 00:15:24,889
out of the country.

317
00:15:24,925 --> 00:15:26,458
No, it's madness.

318
00:15:26,493 --> 00:15:29,027
Come on. If we work together,
we can push open the gate.

319
00:15:29,062 --> 00:15:30,729
Is that you, Princess?

320
00:15:30,764 --> 00:15:32,998
It is you. We remember this one!

321
00:15:33,033 --> 00:15:35,500
- Right? We remember him!
- Please...

322
00:15:35,503 --> 00:15:37,535
Friend to Kaniel Outis,

323
00:15:37,571 --> 00:15:39,838
the man who would not
lend my brother a hand!

324
00:15:39,873 --> 00:15:41,706
The man who killed my brother,

325
00:15:41,742 --> 00:15:44,045
as far as I'm concerned, right?

326
00:15:44,048 --> 00:15:46,344
- We are going to go in there and get Abu Ramal!
- No! Please!

327
00:15:46,346 --> 00:15:47,979
- No! Please!
- And when we are there,

328
00:15:48,015 --> 00:15:52,317
I am personally going to
slice Kaniel Outis' throat.

329
00:15:52,352 --> 00:15:55,353
And you are going to be the one
who's going to help me do it.

330
00:15:55,389 --> 00:15:56,888
- No!
- You sent him!

331
00:15:56,923 --> 00:15:58,156
Take him!

332
00:15:58,191 --> 00:15:59,691
All of you!

333
00:15:59,726 --> 00:16:01,139
Will you stay here?

334
00:16:01,170 --> 00:16:03,495
And let ISIL slaughter you?

335
00:16:03,530 --> 00:16:05,663
Or will you stand with me?

336
00:16:05,699 --> 00:16:06,931
And fight!

337
00:16:11,505 --> 00:16:13,304
Doesn't sound very promising!

338
00:16:13,340 --> 00:16:14,506
Ramal,

339
00:16:14,541 --> 00:16:16,071
you want to rethink helping us?

340
00:16:16,074 --> 00:16:17,475
Escape has to start

341
00:16:17,511 --> 00:16:18,308
from your cell!

342
00:16:18,339 --> 00:16:20,178
All you infidels can go to Hell!

343
00:16:20,213 --> 00:16:22,280
We are in Hell, Ramal.

344
00:16:22,315 --> 00:16:24,115
Question is do you want out?

345
00:16:26,086 --> 00:16:28,438
Smash through the door!

346
00:16:32,959 --> 00:16:35,126
Tell me what to do.

347
00:16:47,574 --> 00:16:49,307
Come on, come on...

348
00:17:02,555 --> 00:17:04,269
_

349
00:17:04,939 --> 00:17:06,148
_

350
00:17:06,500 --> 00:17:08,648
_

351
00:17:08,726 --> 00:17:10,110
_

352
00:17:10,328 --> 00:17:11,670
_

353
00:17:11,724 --> 00:17:14,632
_

354
00:17:14,669 --> 00:17:16,200
_

355
00:17:25,279 --> 00:17:27,046
I'm not hacking anybody's phones.

356
00:17:27,049 --> 00:17:28,572
You're so off base on this,

357
00:17:28,575 --> 00:17:29,588
you have no idea.

358
00:17:29,591 --> 00:17:30,915
Am I?

359
00:17:30,951 --> 00:17:32,350
Y-Yes.

360
00:17:34,354 --> 00:17:36,321
That is terrible,

361
00:17:36,348 --> 00:17:37,960
by the way. What is that,

362
00:17:38,007 --> 00:17:39,958
an act of contrition?

363
00:17:39,993 --> 00:17:42,227
Like a hair shirt?

364
00:17:42,262 --> 00:17:44,796
Torture yourself with kale
to make up for your sins?

365
00:17:44,831 --> 00:17:46,764
I don't have any sins anymore, man.

366
00:17:46,800 --> 00:17:49,000
- That's you.
- How about the sin of deceit?

367
00:17:49,035 --> 00:17:50,568
Hmm?

368
00:17:50,604 --> 00:17:53,838
A kale-drinking man named
Kellerman by the light of day,

369
00:17:53,874 --> 00:17:56,689
a murderous CIA rogue
named Poseidon at night.

370
00:17:56,692 --> 00:17:57,775
Poseidon?

371
00:17:57,811 --> 00:17:59,818
His eyes light up.

372
00:17:59,821 --> 00:18:00,853
She was right.

373
00:18:00,856 --> 00:18:03,615
Oh, you think I'm Poseidon?

374
00:18:03,650 --> 00:18:06,384
Okay.

375
00:18:06,419 --> 00:18:08,116
Are you mixed up with Poseidon?

376
00:18:08,119 --> 00:18:08,920
Oh, hell,

377
00:18:08,955 --> 00:18:10,155
we got to go old school with this?

378
00:18:10,157 --> 00:18:11,189
Is that what you want?

379
00:18:11,224 --> 00:18:13,057
- T-Bag snapping fingers.
- Ow!

380
00:18:13,093 --> 00:18:15,426
That's very... you just gave
me something to work with.

381
00:18:15,462 --> 00:18:16,794
Poseidon? Poseidon.

382
00:18:20,600 --> 00:18:22,331
I'll tell you about Poseidon.

383
00:18:22,334 --> 00:18:24,769
I mean, he's one of those myths
you hear about in the system.

384
00:18:24,771 --> 00:18:27,238
He's an operative so untouchable,

385
00:18:27,274 --> 00:18:29,741
so deep, you couldn't find
him with a nuclear sub.

386
00:18:29,776 --> 00:18:31,305
Hence the nickname.

387
00:18:31,336 --> 00:18:33,645
And how does this involve me?

388
00:18:33,680 --> 00:18:35,947
What's he want with Michael?

389
00:18:38,156 --> 00:18:39,984
Ramal, listen closely.

390
00:18:40,020 --> 00:18:41,486
The brick with the "S," it's loose.

391
00:18:41,521 --> 00:18:42,954
You got to remove it.

392
00:18:53,133 --> 00:18:55,200
It's a spoon, string.

393
00:18:55,235 --> 00:18:56,564
- How?
- A string a day from

394
00:18:56,567 --> 00:18:58,171
my uniforms for four years.

395
00:18:58,989 --> 00:19:01,680
A spoon a guard overlooked
one time in a thousand.

396
00:19:02,876 --> 00:19:04,317
There's a water pipe above you.

397
00:19:04,320 --> 00:19:06,311
Hook it, pull it down.

398
00:19:06,346 --> 00:19:08,079
Do it!

399
00:19:17,134 --> 00:19:19,424
Hey. Let me get this straight.
This is getting him out?

400
00:19:19,426 --> 00:19:20,992
It's getting us all out.

401
00:19:21,027 --> 00:19:22,962
This is a two-cell job, mine and his.

402
00:19:22,965 --> 00:19:25,129
That's why I couldn't pull it
off when I was in that cell,

403
00:19:25,131 --> 00:19:26,598
because the guy across from me,

404
00:19:26,633 --> 00:19:28,715
the guy in this cell,
wouldn't cooperate.

405
00:19:28,718 --> 00:19:30,368
We have to work together.

406
00:19:30,370 --> 00:19:31,603
Come on!

407
00:19:31,638 --> 00:19:33,304
- No.
- Cross!

408
00:19:33,340 --> 00:19:35,039
I'm not working with you.

409
00:19:35,075 --> 00:19:37,809
No. No.

410
00:19:37,844 --> 00:19:40,411
Come here! Come on, sweetheart.

411
00:19:40,447 --> 00:19:43,381
Show them your pretty
face! Come on, get up here!

412
00:19:43,416 --> 00:19:44,916
Look! Stop what you're doing

413
00:19:44,951 --> 00:19:47,279
and tell Kaniel Outis
I will kill the girl!

414
00:19:48,989 --> 00:19:50,655
Take him!

415
00:19:50,690 --> 00:19:53,124
Come on! I'm not through with you yet!

416
00:19:53,159 --> 00:19:54,941
They're beating the crap
out of Sid. They'll kill him

417
00:19:54,943 --> 00:19:56,628
- unless we surrender.
- If we surrender,

418
00:19:56,663 --> 00:19:58,468
they'll kill us. They only want Ramal.

419
00:19:58,471 --> 00:20:01,767
Our best chance of saving
Sid is getting out of here.

420
00:20:01,801 --> 00:20:04,135
Make them forget about
him, start chasing us.

421
00:20:06,439 --> 00:20:07,572
Okay, good.

422
00:20:07,607 --> 00:20:09,741
Now pick it up. String the cord

423
00:20:09,776 --> 00:20:10,808
and pull it through.

424
00:20:11,845 --> 00:20:13,311
Come on, come on!

425
00:20:13,346 --> 00:20:14,312
Yeah!

426
00:20:15,107 --> 00:20:17,315
I will kill the girl, I swear it!

427
00:20:17,350 --> 00:20:18,483
No!

428
00:20:24,257 --> 00:20:25,857
I will say it again,

429
00:20:25,892 --> 00:20:28,910
there will not be any
killing in this prison!

430
00:20:28,933 --> 00:20:30,461
Not on my watch!

431
00:20:30,497 --> 00:20:32,449
This is completely insane.

432
00:20:32,452 --> 00:20:34,402
It's a freakin' Mexican
soap opera out here!

433
00:20:36,784 --> 00:20:38,621
Ramal, don't stop. Don't start thinking.

434
00:20:38,624 --> 00:20:41,406
Don't pin your hopes on one guard.

435
00:20:41,441 --> 00:20:42,607
Walk away!

436
00:20:42,642 --> 00:20:44,909
Hide in the cell block!

437
00:20:47,650 --> 00:20:49,283
What are you doing?

438
00:20:49,295 --> 00:20:51,180
The prison is done, brother.

439
00:20:51,183 --> 00:20:52,482
For the love of God!

440
00:20:52,485 --> 00:20:54,986
For the love of God,
a man seeks justice.

441
00:20:55,021 --> 00:20:57,389
In everything he does, at all times!

442
00:20:57,392 --> 00:20:59,428
Now, everybody, back in the block!

443
00:20:59,431 --> 00:21:01,777
There are no prisoners
and guards anymore!

444
00:21:01,780 --> 00:21:03,428
You realize that, right?

445
00:21:03,463 --> 00:21:05,563
If ISIL gets in here,

446
00:21:05,598 --> 00:21:08,266
we are all the enemy.

447
00:21:08,301 --> 00:21:09,767
Sinners,

448
00:21:09,803 --> 00:21:11,836
deviants...

449
00:21:11,871 --> 00:21:14,405
and those that locked up their leader.

450
00:21:15,449 --> 00:21:18,242
You will be the only
guard that they catch.

451
00:21:18,278 --> 00:21:20,011
The noble one.

452
00:21:20,046 --> 00:21:23,614
They will behead you for it. But...

453
00:21:23,650 --> 00:21:25,650
if we work together,

454
00:21:25,685 --> 00:21:27,251
we get Ramal,

455
00:21:27,287 --> 00:21:28,920
we have a bargaining chip.

456
00:21:28,955 --> 00:21:30,355
I will see to it

457
00:21:30,390 --> 00:21:34,192
that you will get out
with the rest of us.

458
00:21:34,227 --> 00:21:36,678
Just give me the keys to solitary.

459
00:21:36,681 --> 00:21:38,581
I don't have the keys.

460
00:21:38,584 --> 00:21:40,298
I know you do.

461
00:21:40,333 --> 00:21:42,767
Join us

462
00:21:42,802 --> 00:21:44,702
and you will live.

463
00:21:44,738 --> 00:21:46,771
I give you my word.

464
00:21:46,806 --> 00:21:48,439
I don't have them.

465
00:21:52,879 --> 00:21:54,412
Kill him!

466
00:21:56,349 --> 00:21:59,784
But you have something much better, huh?

467
00:22:03,890 --> 00:22:05,189
Move. Move!

468
00:22:05,225 --> 00:22:06,858
Oh, my God.

469
00:22:06,893 --> 00:22:09,694
Oh, my God. They killed the guard!

470
00:22:09,795 --> 00:22:12,095
They got his gun. They're coming for us!

471
00:22:18,927 --> 00:22:20,961
Got to make this count, Ramal.

472
00:22:20,996 --> 00:22:23,797
String that fishing
pole through that slot.

473
00:22:23,832 --> 00:22:25,432
That's right.

474
00:22:25,467 --> 00:22:26,800
Now, you can remove the pinions

475
00:22:26,835 --> 00:22:28,325
on my door... the hinges.

476
00:22:28,357 --> 00:22:29,890
There are two of them.

477
00:22:31,607 --> 00:22:33,106
No way.

478
00:22:35,692 --> 00:22:37,143
What are you doing?

479
00:22:39,239 --> 00:22:40,238
What are you doing?

480
00:22:40,273 --> 00:22:41,472
I'm doing mine.

481
00:22:41,507 --> 00:22:43,441
We don't have time for this, Ramal!

482
00:22:52,352 --> 00:22:53,832
I'm telling you, it's a two-cell job,

483
00:22:53,853 --> 00:22:55,486
that's the point. That side of the wing

484
00:22:55,521 --> 00:22:57,255
is new construction. The pinions

485
00:22:57,290 --> 00:22:59,123
are covered in the hinges...
You can't pull them.

486
00:22:59,125 --> 00:23:01,525
This side is original.
They're open, loose.

487
00:23:01,561 --> 00:23:03,427
You want me to free you?

488
00:23:03,463 --> 00:23:06,286
Yes, and I, in turn, free you
with those keys, down there.

489
00:23:06,289 --> 00:23:08,466
Why would I trust you more
than the madman out there?

490
00:23:08,468 --> 00:23:10,868
'Cause you just heard
what his word is worth.

491
00:23:16,376 --> 00:23:17,675
Kick it.

492
00:23:20,480 --> 00:23:22,513
This is it. It's all
about whose word you trust.

493
00:23:22,548 --> 00:23:24,916
I promise you... you release me,

494
00:23:24,951 --> 00:23:27,051
I release you.

495
00:23:39,799 --> 00:23:42,400
Little more, little more.

496
00:23:51,377 --> 00:23:52,343
Thank God. Come on.

497
00:23:52,378 --> 00:23:54,845
Okay, the bottom.

498
00:23:54,881 --> 00:23:56,669
Yes!

499
00:23:57,841 --> 00:23:59,408
Come on,

500
00:23:59,419 --> 00:24:01,285
- come on. Come on.
- Come on.

501
00:24:01,321 --> 00:24:03,521
Yes!

502
00:24:03,556 --> 00:24:04,622
Almost there!

503
00:24:13,933 --> 00:24:15,700
Yes.

504
00:24:15,735 --> 00:24:17,201
Come on.

505
00:24:18,237 --> 00:24:20,037
Got to hurry up, come on.

506
00:24:22,491 --> 00:24:24,875
Yes. Yes, come on!

507
00:24:34,587 --> 00:24:36,654
Where are you going?

508
00:24:36,689 --> 00:24:37,922
Open my door.

509
00:24:40,934 --> 00:24:42,426
I'm getting the hell out of here.

510
00:24:42,428 --> 00:24:44,829
Open my door.

511
00:24:44,864 --> 00:24:48,065
- Leave him, man, you crazy?
- Open my door.

512
00:24:48,101 --> 00:24:50,468
Once we're outside these walls, we need

513
00:24:50,503 --> 00:24:51,936
safe passage out of the country.

514
00:24:51,971 --> 00:24:53,437
Even now, you negotiate.

515
00:24:54,807 --> 00:24:58,109
We work together or we both die.

516
00:25:00,279 --> 00:25:01,746
You have my word.

517
00:25:01,781 --> 00:25:03,347
Open the door.

518
00:25:11,557 --> 00:25:13,124
We got to go now.

519
00:25:22,192 --> 00:25:23,868
No, no!

520
00:25:29,642 --> 00:25:30,975
Mr. Tic Tac.

521
00:25:32,078 --> 00:25:33,044
What are you doing here?

522
00:25:33,079 --> 00:25:34,245
You gonna fight ISIL men?

523
00:25:34,280 --> 00:25:35,946
Get out of here, kid, hide!

524
00:25:35,982 --> 00:25:38,149
- This is no place for you.
- You gonna fight ISIL men?

525
00:25:38,184 --> 00:25:40,051
Yes.

526
00:25:41,354 --> 00:25:43,921
Listen very closely, all right?

527
00:25:43,956 --> 00:25:46,624
American! American!

528
00:25:46,659 --> 00:25:47,958
American!

529
00:25:47,994 --> 00:25:49,461
_

530
00:25:49,516 --> 00:25:50,141
_

531
00:25:50,180 --> 00:25:52,382
_

532
00:25:53,675 --> 00:25:54,724
_

533
00:26:04,388 --> 00:26:06,514
_

534
00:26:14,353 --> 00:26:16,420
- You go to Bubble Gum Man now?
- Yeah.

535
00:26:19,292 --> 00:26:21,892
Thanks for your help. Here, take that.

536
00:26:21,928 --> 00:26:24,328
Get somewhere safe, okay?

537
00:26:27,600 --> 00:26:30,401
Mr. Tic Tac goes to Bubble Gum Man!

538
00:26:33,809 --> 00:26:37,541
Ramal... don't want to kill you.

539
00:26:37,577 --> 00:26:39,844
Just your friends. You understand?

540
00:26:39,879 --> 00:26:42,405
What are we doing in here?
This is not helping us.

541
00:26:42,408 --> 00:26:43,608
You're gonna make a phone call

542
00:26:43,611 --> 00:26:45,470
so you can hold up your end of the deal.

543
00:26:45,473 --> 00:26:47,384
There's an auto body
shop off Nashwan plaza.

544
00:26:47,420 --> 00:26:48,886
I want vehicles there, full tanks of gas

545
00:26:48,888 --> 00:26:50,721
so we can get to the border, all of us.

546
00:26:50,756 --> 00:26:51,822
I'm not going with you to the border.

547
00:26:51,824 --> 00:26:53,181
You don't have a choice.

548
00:26:53,184 --> 00:26:55,191
We're gonna ride to the
border, then say sayonara.

549
00:26:55,194 --> 00:26:56,392
You're our insurance.

550
00:26:56,395 --> 00:26:57,809
Ramal, I don't want to kill you.

551
00:26:57,811 --> 00:26:58,996
You understand?

552
00:26:59,031 --> 00:27:01,765
Or would you rather be
their insurance? Take it.

553
00:27:13,146 --> 00:27:15,946
I want to know what he's
saying. He could be screwing us.

554
00:27:15,982 --> 00:27:17,574
He's screwing with us, all right.

555
00:27:17,577 --> 00:27:19,196
We just need to screw with him first.

556
00:27:19,199 --> 00:27:20,317
Where's Ja?

557
00:27:20,353 --> 00:27:22,086
I don't know.

558
00:27:25,858 --> 00:27:27,717
- Oxycodone...
- Hey, we got to peel.

559
00:27:27,720 --> 00:27:28,692
Percocet...

560
00:27:28,728 --> 00:27:30,661
Come on, you Japanese
junkie son of a bitch.

561
00:27:30,696 --> 00:27:32,496
I'm Korean, you Canadian monkey.

562
00:27:32,532 --> 00:27:35,299
Canadian? Oh, that's really funny, Ja.

563
00:27:35,334 --> 00:27:37,808
You'd split my sides if we
weren't about to be slaughtered.

564
00:27:37,811 --> 00:27:40,104
Hey, remember what Woody Allen said.

565
00:27:40,139 --> 00:27:42,106
What did he say?

566
00:27:42,141 --> 00:27:43,741
"I don't mind dying.

567
00:27:43,776 --> 00:27:47,077
I just don't want to be
around when it happens."

568
00:27:47,113 --> 00:27:48,345
Hey, come on.

569
00:27:48,381 --> 00:27:50,447
We need you, okay?

570
00:27:50,483 --> 00:27:51,749
What's the holdup?

571
00:28:05,265 --> 00:28:06,516
_

572
00:28:15,975 --> 00:28:18,042
Scofield's a dead man.

573
00:28:18,083 --> 00:28:19,431
He's tangling with Poseidon.

574
00:28:19,434 --> 00:28:20,650
I see what you're doing here.

575
00:28:20,653 --> 00:28:23,347
Talking Poseidon in third person,

576
00:28:23,382 --> 00:28:24,682
like you're not him.

577
00:28:24,717 --> 00:28:26,050
State Department has been

578
00:28:26,085 --> 00:28:27,718
looking for Poseidon for years,

579
00:28:27,753 --> 00:28:30,248
you idiot. He's a rogue CIA operative.

580
00:28:30,251 --> 00:28:31,250
Nobody knows who he is.

581
00:28:31,293 --> 00:28:33,092
- Here we go.
- I know it's a little

582
00:28:33,095 --> 00:28:35,186
above your pay grade
being a common criminal.

583
00:28:35,194 --> 00:28:36,890
I mean, we're talking
about a single man.

584
00:28:36,893 --> 00:28:38,162
Right? A hawk

585
00:28:38,197 --> 00:28:40,564
who apparently doesn't
like how the White House

586
00:28:40,600 --> 00:28:42,199
goes about foreign policy,

587
00:28:42,235 --> 00:28:44,268
and decided to take
matters into his own hands.

588
00:28:44,303 --> 00:28:46,073
Not with armies, not with invasions,

589
00:28:46,076 --> 00:28:47,791
but by getting a single person killed,

590
00:28:47,794 --> 00:28:50,074
by getting a single
person elected to office,

591
00:28:50,109 --> 00:28:53,677
by getting a single person
released from prison.

592
00:28:53,713 --> 00:28:56,213
Prison, like the one in
Yemen, where Michael's at.

593
00:28:56,249 --> 00:28:57,648
You want my guess?

594
00:28:57,683 --> 00:29:01,452
It's Abu Ramal that Poseidon wants free.

595
00:29:01,487 --> 00:29:03,254
Guy I seen on the prison telly.

596
00:29:03,289 --> 00:29:06,490
Wait, I thought the CIA was
supposed to kill terrorists,

597
00:29:06,516 --> 00:29:08,670
- not release them.
- Poseidon is no longer CIA.

598
00:29:08,682 --> 00:29:10,182
He doesn't report to anybody.

599
00:29:10,185 --> 00:29:12,296
He just pursues his own ideology.

600
00:29:12,331 --> 00:29:14,565
Okay, for instance, listen.

601
00:29:14,600 --> 00:29:16,834
Let's say you think Russia and Iran

602
00:29:16,869 --> 00:29:19,370
are having too much
influence in the Middle East,

603
00:29:19,405 --> 00:29:20,671
and you don't think Washington

604
00:29:20,706 --> 00:29:22,473
is getting the job done.

605
00:29:22,508 --> 00:29:23,774
You free Ramal.

606
00:29:23,809 --> 00:29:26,343
Sure, he's an Islamic radical nut job,

607
00:29:26,379 --> 00:29:28,479
but he will fight Iran
and Russia for you.

608
00:29:28,514 --> 00:29:31,135
The enemy of my enemy is my friend.

609
00:29:31,138 --> 00:29:33,317
And what's so shrewd about Poseidon

610
00:29:33,352 --> 00:29:34,985
is he does it all without a network,

611
00:29:35,021 --> 00:29:37,621
which is why he's so hard to find.

612
00:29:37,657 --> 00:29:39,290
One man can pull strings like that?

613
00:29:39,325 --> 00:29:41,725
One man manipulating
a handful of others.

614
00:29:41,761 --> 00:29:44,461
Abu Ramal is a monster.

615
00:29:44,497 --> 00:29:47,464
And there's a spot in
Hell reserved for him,

616
00:29:47,500 --> 00:29:50,968
but the hottest spot is
reserved for Poseidon,

617
00:29:51,003 --> 00:29:53,729
because he is letting Ramal
loose on the world again.

618
00:29:53,732 --> 00:29:56,440
Those men, they have
the blood of thousands,

619
00:29:56,475 --> 00:29:59,043
thousands on their hands.

620
00:29:59,078 --> 00:30:01,845
Compared to them, you and
me are a couple of angels.

621
00:30:04,283 --> 00:30:06,483
- "Angels"?
- Mm-hmm.

622
00:30:06,519 --> 00:30:07,985
You find out who Poseidon is,

623
00:30:08,020 --> 00:30:09,987
and how Scofield is wrapped up in it,

624
00:30:10,022 --> 00:30:12,456
maybe your fate...

625
00:30:12,491 --> 00:30:14,391
is to be a patriot.

626
00:30:16,629 --> 00:30:18,529
What...?

627
00:30:25,338 --> 00:30:27,638
Go. Go!

628
00:30:51,931 --> 00:30:53,464
There's a time for everything.

629
00:30:55,735 --> 00:31:00,149
911? I need help... now.

630
00:31:06,052 --> 00:31:07,612
They're going over the top.

631
00:31:07,615 --> 00:31:09,353
Let's go.

632
00:31:24,075 --> 00:31:26,337
Go, go, go, go, go!

633
00:31:26,372 --> 00:31:28,272
This way!

634
00:31:35,161 --> 00:31:36,736
It's locked!

635
00:31:36,739 --> 00:31:37,648
It's a dead end.

636
00:31:37,683 --> 00:31:39,817
No, no, no, no. No. No, no, no, no.

637
00:31:39,852 --> 00:31:41,118
Ramal?

638
00:31:43,823 --> 00:31:46,624
Hide! Hide!

639
00:31:46,659 --> 00:31:49,922
I don't want to kill
you! Just your friends.

640
00:31:49,925 --> 00:31:52,954
- You understand?
- Sid, you're alive?

641
00:31:52,999 --> 00:31:55,666
- We'll see about that.
- Ramal?!

642
00:31:55,701 --> 00:31:57,542
Let's hand the son of a bitch over.

643
00:31:57,545 --> 00:31:59,111
Won't work.

644
00:31:59,114 --> 00:32:00,547
They'll gun us down anyway.

645
00:32:00,582 --> 00:32:02,916
Can't just wait here and die.

646
00:32:04,766 --> 00:32:06,386
Your game is up.

647
00:32:06,421 --> 00:32:07,988
Come out!

648
00:32:20,002 --> 00:32:22,736
Anyone

649
00:32:22,771 --> 00:32:26,673
who gets between me and Abu Ramal dies.

650
00:32:26,708 --> 00:32:29,476
You understand?!

651
00:32:32,550 --> 00:32:34,149
Where is Ramal?

652
00:32:34,204 --> 00:32:36,149
Tell me now!

653
00:32:40,656 --> 00:32:42,622
There's a boy.

654
00:32:42,658 --> 00:32:45,759
Ithaca, New York. Mike Scofield.

655
00:32:45,794 --> 00:32:48,695
If I don't make it out of here alive,

656
00:32:48,730 --> 00:32:50,797
tell him his father loves him very much.

657
00:32:50,832 --> 00:32:52,799
"His father"?

658
00:32:59,241 --> 00:33:00,640
If I don't smother that gun,

659
00:33:00,676 --> 00:33:02,175
they'll kill us all.

660
00:33:46,555 --> 00:33:49,122
Move back!

661
00:33:52,861 --> 00:33:55,629
Move back! Go!

662
00:33:55,664 --> 00:33:57,864
Let me through!

663
00:34:07,129 --> 00:34:10,666
Michael! Michael!

664
00:34:17,419 --> 00:34:19,853
Michael? Michael!

665
00:34:37,873 --> 00:34:39,272
Poseidon sent you?

666
00:34:39,308 --> 00:34:40,807
Where's your friend?

667
00:34:40,842 --> 00:34:41,975
He's long gone.

668
00:34:42,010 --> 00:34:43,777
Back door.

669
00:34:45,006 --> 00:34:46,539
Locked from the inside.

670
00:34:46,542 --> 00:34:47,480
He's in here.

671
00:34:47,483 --> 00:34:48,615
Find him.

672
00:34:50,862 --> 00:34:52,886
I was you once, killing for a lie.

673
00:34:52,905 --> 00:34:55,297
Now you're what?

674
00:34:55,316 --> 00:34:56,789
Dying for the truth?

675
00:34:56,792 --> 00:34:59,793
It's human nature to find stuff out,

676
00:34:59,828 --> 00:35:02,562
so you will.

677
00:35:02,597 --> 00:35:05,165
Or she will.

678
00:35:05,192 --> 00:35:08,493
And then the lie has to kill the truth.

679
00:35:09,771 --> 00:35:12,005
Which one of you is gonna die ne...?

680
00:35:34,634 --> 00:35:36,534
Time to get scarce.

681
00:35:36,537 --> 00:35:38,605
Hey!

682
00:35:43,105 --> 00:35:45,872
What did he say to you?

683
00:35:47,008 --> 00:35:48,816
Nothing.

684
00:36:18,967 --> 00:36:20,633
Auto shop's a few blocks up.

685
00:36:20,668 --> 00:36:22,902
And your men better be coming.

686
00:36:22,937 --> 00:36:24,070
They will be there.

687
00:36:24,105 --> 00:36:25,471
Where is Ja?

688
00:36:28,874 --> 00:36:31,441
Ja,

689
00:36:31,476 --> 00:36:33,679
- what are you doing?
- I'm starving, man.

690
00:36:33,682 --> 00:36:35,714
You know how long it's
been since I seen fruit?

691
00:36:35,717 --> 00:36:37,580
You're stopping to eat?

692
00:36:37,616 --> 00:36:38,982
Are you high?!

693
00:36:39,017 --> 00:36:40,884
Don't come at me, man.
You're not my mama.

694
00:36:40,919 --> 00:36:43,915
You know what? You're done.

695
00:36:43,918 --> 00:36:45,088
- You're gone.
- What?

696
00:36:45,123 --> 00:36:47,857
- Wait.
- I said, walk! You're a liability!

697
00:36:47,893 --> 00:36:51,286
Wait. Wait. You said you'd get me out,

698
00:36:51,289 --> 00:36:53,489
all the way home. That was the deal.

699
00:36:56,028 --> 00:36:58,028
Ramal, this man follows us,

700
00:36:58,031 --> 00:36:59,397
tell your men to shoot him.

701
00:36:59,400 --> 00:37:01,438
Gladly.

702
00:37:10,903 --> 00:37:14,939
_

703
00:37:31,369 --> 00:37:33,269
Where'd you go, Michael?

704
00:37:34,506 --> 00:37:36,940
Where'd you go?

705
00:37:49,769 --> 00:37:51,086
_

706
00:38:02,857 --> 00:38:04,602
_

707
00:38:08,206 --> 00:38:09,935
There you are, my men.

708
00:38:09,938 --> 00:38:12,662
Seize these dogs so that
we can put them down.

709
00:38:12,663 --> 00:38:15,082
_

710
00:38:17,716 --> 00:38:19,516
Ramal.

711
00:38:19,519 --> 00:38:23,554
Ramal, what are you doing?

712
00:38:23,588 --> 00:38:25,481
You thought you tricked me?

713
00:38:25,484 --> 00:38:31,155
Take the long way around
while your friend...

714
00:38:32,491 --> 00:38:35,826
gets here first to get weapons.

715
00:38:35,829 --> 00:38:38,885
You were going to screw me.
That's the American slang.

716
00:38:38,920 --> 00:38:41,332
- Isn't it?
- You were gonna screw me.

717
00:38:41,367 --> 00:38:43,534
So much for our word.

718
00:38:43,569 --> 00:38:46,270
Lying to enemies.

719
00:38:46,305 --> 00:38:48,405
It's called Taqiyya.

720
00:38:49,742 --> 00:38:51,475
Take off the camera.

721
00:38:52,807 --> 00:38:54,316
I will show the world

722
00:38:54,351 --> 00:38:56,551
what happens

723
00:38:56,586 --> 00:38:59,487
when you screw Abu Ramal.

724
00:38:59,523 --> 00:39:01,356
On your knees!

725
00:39:01,391 --> 00:39:03,825
- It's not gonna happen.
- Make them on their knees!

726
00:39:23,347 --> 00:39:24,679
Enough!

727
00:39:26,516 --> 00:39:28,155
Drop your weapons.

728
00:39:36,393 --> 00:39:38,793
Step away from my brother.

729
00:39:39,896 --> 00:39:41,363
Linc.

730
00:39:41,398 --> 00:39:43,216
How much do you love
this brother of yours?

731
00:39:50,287 --> 00:39:54,043
Why don't you step down from that truck?

732
00:39:54,046 --> 00:39:56,691
Stop. Stop, stop, stop.
No, it's not going down

733
00:39:56,694 --> 00:39:58,513
like this, okay? Just...

734
00:39:58,548 --> 00:40:01,160
stop. I got way too many
questions for my friend here.

735
00:40:01,163 --> 00:40:04,252
- Step back!
- I went to prison for killing

736
00:40:04,287 --> 00:40:05,954
a guy in a bar fight. I didn't even want

737
00:40:05,957 --> 00:40:08,491
to get into it, okay? He
starts talking yang to my girl.

738
00:40:08,526 --> 00:40:09,858
I tell him to beat it.

739
00:40:09,861 --> 00:40:12,360
He pulls a knife, and I see red.

740
00:40:12,396 --> 00:40:14,510
One second later,

741
00:40:14,513 --> 00:40:17,899
I'm holding his bloody knife,
and it's his body on the ground.

742
00:40:17,934 --> 00:40:20,535
- You're not that fast.
- One second.

743
00:40:20,570 --> 00:40:22,037
Please don't do this.

744
00:40:22,072 --> 00:40:24,005
You will lose.

745
00:40:24,041 --> 00:40:26,539
Listen to your friend.

746
00:40:26,542 --> 00:40:28,909
I'm talking to you, Ramal.

747
00:40:28,944 --> 00:40:32,245
I told you! Step down from that truck.

748
00:40:32,281 --> 00:40:33,853
Pick up your weapons!

749
00:40:33,856 --> 00:40:36,016
You've got one second till
that one second happens.

750
00:40:36,051 --> 00:40:37,651
Go to hell.

751
00:40:51,808 --> 00:40:53,708
We got more coming!

752
00:40:53,735 --> 00:40:56,002
- And more over here!
- This is a big problem.

753
00:40:56,038 --> 00:40:58,271
Let's get the hell out of here.

754
00:41:05,955 --> 00:41:08,018
_

755
00:41:24,533 --> 00:41:26,566
- You wanted to see us?
- Ouch.

756
00:41:31,858 --> 00:41:33,380
Come on. Come on.

757
00:41:58,993 --> 00:42:01,468
Behold the villain.

758
00:42:13,802 --> 00:42:16,650
Who the hell is this guy?

759
00:42:16,685 --> 00:42:19,175
He's my brother.

760
00:42:21,823 --> 00:42:24,858
He's my brother.

761
00:42:24,893 --> 00:42:26,593
I can't believe this.

762
00:42:26,628 --> 00:42:30,107
I just can't believe
this. I can't believe this.

763
00:42:30,110 --> 00:42:33,333
Back at the prison. Why?

764
00:42:33,368 --> 00:42:35,235
- Why did you say?
- I had to deny you.

765
00:42:35,270 --> 00:42:37,304
You were... you were filming me.

766
00:42:37,339 --> 00:42:40,430
- They can't know.
- Who can't know?

767
00:42:40,433 --> 00:42:42,042
- They can't know I'm getting out.
- Who?

768
00:42:42,044 --> 00:42:44,978
I'll explain everything later, just...

769
00:42:45,013 --> 00:42:47,380
Sara and-and Mike?

770
00:42:47,416 --> 00:42:49,082
They're good.

771
00:42:49,117 --> 00:42:50,917
- They're fine.
- Oh, thank God.

772
00:42:50,952 --> 00:42:52,469
Thank God.

773
00:42:52,472 --> 00:42:54,192
Questions just keep piling up, huh?

774
00:42:54,195 --> 00:42:56,423
That's you.

775
00:42:56,458 --> 00:42:58,182
It's all of us.

776
00:42:58,185 --> 00:42:59,559
What are they saying?

777
00:42:59,594 --> 00:43:03,396
That ISIL has taken over
the government station.

778
00:43:03,432 --> 00:43:05,865
That their beloved leader, Abu Ramal,

779
00:43:05,868 --> 00:43:09,011
has been martyred.

780
00:43:09,014 --> 00:43:12,006
That we're the ones that did it.

781
00:43:12,009 --> 00:43:16,034
The entire army of ISIL
just declared war on us.

