1
00:00:02,203 --> 00:00:04,627
Kaniel Outis. He's
been working with ISIL.

2
00:00:04,629 --> 00:00:05,828
You know that's not Michael.

3
00:00:05,864 --> 00:00:07,029
We're gonna need you.

4
00:00:07,065 --> 00:00:08,864
I can rest when I'm dead.

5
00:00:08,900 --> 00:00:10,366
That's what I'm worried about.

6
00:00:11,436 --> 00:00:12,968
I'm not leaving Michael.

7
00:00:13,004 --> 00:00:15,471
We can't risk all of
it for just one man.

8
00:00:15,507 --> 00:00:17,306
ISIL has broken through the checkpoint.

9
00:00:17,342 --> 00:00:18,774
Sana'a is falling.

10
00:00:18,810 --> 00:00:21,477
We work together or we both die.

11
00:00:21,513 --> 00:00:23,440
You have my word.

12
00:00:23,479 --> 00:00:26,783
It's Abu Ramal that Poseidon wants free.

13
00:00:29,854 --> 00:00:31,487
Poseidon sent you?

14
00:00:35,894 --> 00:00:37,226
Enough!

15
00:00:39,931 --> 00:00:41,664
Who the hell is this guy?

16
00:00:41,699 --> 00:00:44,366
- He's my brother.
- Back at the prison...

17
00:00:44,402 --> 00:00:48,404
I had to deny who you
were. They were filming me,

18
00:00:48,440 --> 00:00:49,772
and they can't know.

19
00:00:49,808 --> 00:00:51,371
Abu Ramal has been martyred.

20
00:00:51,374 --> 00:00:52,606
The entire army of ISIL

21
00:00:52,672 --> 00:00:55,144
just declared war on us.

22
00:01:02,053 --> 00:01:03,886
Behold the villain.

23
00:01:17,335 --> 00:01:18,901
Hi.

24
00:01:18,937 --> 00:01:22,304
Hey. I, uh, I ran into
town to get some coffee.

25
00:01:22,340 --> 00:01:24,373
- Do you want anything?
- No. I'm good.

26
00:01:24,409 --> 00:01:25,849
Thanks, honey. I'm almost done here.

27
00:01:25,877 --> 00:01:28,043
I will see you at the lake
in a little while, okay?

28
00:01:28,079 --> 00:01:30,479
Okay. I'll see you back at the house.

29
00:01:30,515 --> 00:01:32,081
The hubby?

30
00:01:32,117 --> 00:01:34,374
Uh, what did you learn from Kellerman?

31
00:01:34,428 --> 00:01:37,486
There's no easy way to
deliver this news, darling.

32
00:01:37,522 --> 00:01:39,589
It's a heartbreaker.

33
00:01:45,629 --> 00:01:47,494
Doesn't get any better.

34
00:01:47,497 --> 00:01:48,965
He's rotten all the way to the core.

35
00:01:48,967 --> 00:01:50,526
You've been sleeping
with the enemy, baby.

36
00:01:50,528 --> 00:01:51,700
I don't understand.

37
00:01:51,736 --> 00:01:54,103
I followed them two monkeys
from Kellerman's house

38
00:01:54,139 --> 00:01:55,637
right after they put a bullet in him.

39
00:01:55,673 --> 00:01:57,807
Needless to say he wasn't our guy.

40
00:01:58,982 --> 00:02:00,510
He did say some pretty alarming things

41
00:02:00,512 --> 00:02:02,911
about your boy, Poseidon,
the world shaker.

42
00:02:02,947 --> 00:02:05,081
Didn't give me enough
to put all the pieces together.

43
00:02:05,083 --> 00:02:07,282
Back up, back up, back
up. What did they say?

44
00:02:07,318 --> 00:02:08,628
Jacob? His words?

45
00:02:08,631 --> 00:02:11,087
I couldn't get close enough
to hear much, but what I did...

46
00:02:11,105 --> 00:02:13,444
what I did hear was
your name and Michael's.

47
00:02:13,447 --> 00:02:14,693
Yes, they seemed pretty cozy,

48
00:02:14,696 --> 00:02:16,068
- the three of them.
- Oh, my God.

49
00:02:16,071 --> 00:02:17,805
It's a nasty bag of conspir...
Where are you going?!

50
00:02:17,807 --> 00:02:19,206
To my son!

51
00:02:21,666 --> 00:02:25,134
Stay down. Stay down.

52
00:02:25,170 --> 00:02:27,470
It's another artillery strike.

53
00:02:31,109 --> 00:02:34,043
But they sure as hell are used to it.

54
00:02:42,987 --> 00:02:45,121
Go, go!

55
00:03:06,584 --> 00:03:13,837
_

56
00:03:20,064 --> 00:03:24,893
_

57
00:03:24,896 --> 00:03:28,897
Allahu Akbar. Allahu Akbar.

58
00:03:28,933 --> 00:03:30,032
Allahu Akbar.

59
00:03:30,667 --> 00:03:35,156
_

60
00:03:35,210 --> 00:03:40,442
_

61
00:03:43,649 --> 00:03:45,640
_

62
00:03:54,792 --> 00:04:00,166
_

63
00:04:00,760 --> 00:04:02,865
ISIL just offered
ten million for our heads!

64
00:04:02,867 --> 00:04:05,534
Wait. Wait. Stay here.

65
00:04:05,570 --> 00:04:07,837
We got to get off these
streets or we're dead.

66
00:04:08,843 --> 00:04:10,472
Ten million rial?

67
00:04:10,508 --> 00:04:11,807
You give up your mother

68
00:04:11,843 --> 00:04:12,942
for cash like that.

69
00:04:12,977 --> 00:04:14,629
It's about what I paid

70
00:04:14,632 --> 00:04:16,278
for Freddie Mercury's ashes.

71
00:04:16,314 --> 00:04:18,480
Freddie Mercury now, really?

72
00:04:18,516 --> 00:04:20,616
It's better than talking
about 500,000 people

73
00:04:20,652 --> 00:04:22,284
looking to kill us.

74
00:04:22,320 --> 00:04:23,552
Come on.

75
00:04:23,588 --> 00:04:25,588
Found a place to figure out next steps.

76
00:04:25,623 --> 00:04:27,030
Let's go.

77
00:04:39,370 --> 00:04:41,303
This is the part you
tell me what's going on,

78
00:04:41,339 --> 00:04:42,671
the whole thing.

79
00:04:42,707 --> 00:04:44,239
No. Th-There's no time.

80
00:04:44,275 --> 00:04:45,283
Country's about to fall.

81
00:04:45,286 --> 00:04:46,642
You'll get your answers, I promise.

82
00:04:46,644 --> 00:04:48,277
Right now our window is closing.

83
00:04:48,280 --> 00:04:49,077
We need to...

84
00:04:49,113 --> 00:04:51,213
We need to pivot to
the next contingency.

85
00:04:51,249 --> 00:04:53,049
- Train station.
- Get up to the north.

86
00:04:53,084 --> 00:04:54,116
Exit the country that way.

87
00:04:54,118 --> 00:04:55,598
Things have changed in the four years

88
00:04:55,620 --> 00:04:57,519
you've been locked
up in Ogygia, Michael.

89
00:04:57,555 --> 00:04:58,796
Your plan's redundant.

90
00:04:58,799 --> 00:05:01,510
ISIL control the north, roads,
checkpoints, train stations.

91
00:05:01,526 --> 00:05:04,626
Even if we make it across
the city, it's suicide.

92
00:05:04,662 --> 00:05:06,495
No. You're wrong. It's a shell game.

93
00:05:06,531 --> 00:05:08,297
You go where they never expect you.

94
00:05:08,333 --> 00:05:09,732
Wait. You came all the way
to Yemen looking for him.

95
00:05:09,734 --> 00:05:11,034
You think he was lost or something?

96
00:05:11,036 --> 00:05:12,301
Come on.

97
00:05:12,337 --> 00:05:14,503
You want to live?

98
00:05:14,539 --> 00:05:16,033
The airport's the only option.

99
00:05:16,036 --> 00:05:18,908
The airport's known as the main
artery to the outside world.

100
00:05:18,910 --> 00:05:20,609
It's the first thing
ISIL will shut down.

101
00:05:20,645 --> 00:05:23,952
Planes were flying an
hour ago. You got a phone?

102
00:05:23,955 --> 00:05:26,548
No, but he does.

103
00:05:26,584 --> 00:05:28,480
Burned it up jacking
off to Queen, though.

104
00:05:28,483 --> 00:05:30,419
Guilty as charged.

105
00:05:30,455 --> 00:05:33,121
C-Note's organizing a passage
on the flight as we speak.

106
00:05:33,157 --> 00:05:34,608
No, I'm telling you,

107
00:05:34,611 --> 00:05:36,044
my plan will work.

108
00:05:36,047 --> 00:05:37,392
Once... once you leave

109
00:05:37,428 --> 00:05:38,960
the northern part of Sana'a...

110
00:05:38,996 --> 00:05:41,596
Enough. We shouldn't even
be talking about this.

111
00:05:41,632 --> 00:05:42,965
Get off me!

112
00:05:43,768 --> 00:05:44,834
How are you alive?!

113
00:05:44,869 --> 00:05:46,702
In Yemen?!

114
00:05:46,738 --> 00:05:49,038
What happened to you, Michael?!

115
00:05:51,776 --> 00:05:55,210
Now, I'm not moving another
inch until you tell me

116
00:05:55,246 --> 00:05:57,680
what the hell is really going on here.

117
00:06:34,568 --> 00:06:37,401
Michael Scofield had to die.

118
00:06:37,437 --> 00:06:40,972
I had to fake my death.

119
00:06:41,007 --> 00:06:43,407
Go away.

120
00:06:43,443 --> 00:06:45,743
It was part of the deal I made.

121
00:06:47,914 --> 00:06:50,347
If I went to work for
a deep-cover operative

122
00:06:50,383 --> 00:06:51,549
named Poseidon...

123
00:06:54,588 --> 00:06:56,688
we would all go free.

124
00:07:03,663 --> 00:07:05,697
We were free.

125
00:07:08,168 --> 00:07:09,433
We were exonerated.

126
00:07:09,469 --> 00:07:14,705
No. That's what we thought...

127
00:07:14,741 --> 00:07:17,642
but we were wrong.

128
00:07:17,677 --> 00:07:20,978
A few weeks before I married Sara...

129
00:07:21,014 --> 00:07:22,651
I was approached by Poseidon.

130
00:07:22,654 --> 00:07:25,416
You think I'm showing?

131
00:07:25,467 --> 00:07:27,366
I'm not used to that yet.

132
00:07:27,387 --> 00:07:29,713
I got to... I got to tell Michael.

133
00:07:29,716 --> 00:07:31,099
Here you go. Burgers will

134
00:07:31,102 --> 00:07:32,546
- be just a second.
- Hello?

135
00:07:35,061 --> 00:07:37,128
Yes, this is Michael.

136
00:07:44,618 --> 00:07:47,007
Poseidon told me Kellerman didn't have

137
00:07:47,010 --> 00:07:50,487
the authority or jurisdiction
to exonerate our crimes.

138
00:07:51,542 --> 00:07:53,408
He used that as a legal fulcrum.

139
00:07:53,437 --> 00:07:56,246
Told me he could put
us all away for life

140
00:07:56,282 --> 00:07:59,217
within the mandate of the law unless...

141
00:08:01,988 --> 00:08:03,655
unless I went to work for him.

142
00:08:04,924 --> 00:08:06,924
What the hell can they be talking about

143
00:08:06,960 --> 00:08:08,292
at a time like this?

144
00:08:09,229 --> 00:08:12,262
I don't know...

145
00:08:12,298 --> 00:08:15,833
but big brother's hearing
things I want to hear.

146
00:08:15,869 --> 00:08:17,034
We cannot stay.

147
00:08:17,070 --> 00:08:19,036
We must go now.

148
00:08:19,072 --> 00:08:21,439
Maybe we don't.

149
00:08:22,533 --> 00:08:24,342
What the hell are you talking about?

150
00:08:25,345 --> 00:08:26,410
Maybe all this running

151
00:08:26,446 --> 00:08:28,780
is just delaying the inevitable.

152
00:08:30,283 --> 00:08:34,852
Die alone here. Die alone at home.

153
00:08:36,489 --> 00:08:39,991
God, you need a girlfriend, man.

154
00:08:42,862 --> 00:08:46,762
Those voices are heading our
way. They're almost on us.

155
00:08:46,809 --> 00:08:48,999
Who the hell is this Poseidon guy?

156
00:08:49,035 --> 00:08:51,069
A psychopath.

157
00:08:51,104 --> 00:08:55,039
A frustrated policy wonk in the CIA

158
00:08:55,075 --> 00:08:57,955
who felt he could do
better than his superiors.

159
00:08:58,002 --> 00:09:02,613
So, he created a cell within
the CIA called 21-Void,

160
00:09:02,649 --> 00:09:05,216
implementing his own
intelligence operations.

161
00:09:06,571 --> 00:09:08,260
And he needed my help

162
00:09:08,322 --> 00:09:12,023
breaking out people
imprisoned all over the world.

163
00:09:12,058 --> 00:09:13,724
Terrorists,

164
00:09:13,760 --> 00:09:15,570
political dissidents...

165
00:09:16,696 --> 00:09:18,830
rogue agents...

166
00:09:20,934 --> 00:09:24,402
and if I did it, you
and Sara, you'd go free.

167
00:09:24,437 --> 00:09:26,136
Your record's expunged,

168
00:09:26,172 --> 00:09:30,875
but... there was a rub.

169
00:09:32,178 --> 00:09:35,713
I wasn't allowed to have
contact with any of you,

170
00:09:35,749 --> 00:09:38,182
including my son.

171
00:09:38,218 --> 00:09:40,050
Michael.

172
00:09:40,086 --> 00:09:44,856
So, Michael Scofield was dead and...

173
00:09:46,189 --> 00:09:49,159
over the years I assumed many names.

174
00:09:49,195 --> 00:09:53,282
Kaniel Outis... the most recent.

175
00:09:53,328 --> 00:09:55,767
Why didn't you tell me?

176
00:09:55,802 --> 00:09:57,401
Why didn't you reach out to me?

177
00:09:57,437 --> 00:09:59,303
I didn't have a choice.

178
00:09:59,339 --> 00:10:03,107
Poseidon made that... very clear.

179
00:10:03,143 --> 00:10:05,877
How?

180
00:10:05,912 --> 00:10:09,279
At first, I said no.

181
00:10:09,315 --> 00:10:11,181
I wouldn't do it.

182
00:10:11,217 --> 00:10:16,120
Then within weeks, Sara
was incarcerated, beaten.

183
00:10:17,824 --> 00:10:19,090
And so I gave in.

184
00:10:20,386 --> 00:10:22,659
Everything I did, I did for family,

185
00:10:22,695 --> 00:10:24,661
for you, for Sara,

186
00:10:24,697 --> 00:10:28,900
for Mike... so none of you would
ever have to spend another day

187
00:10:28,935 --> 00:10:33,871
inside a prison cell or...
or live a life on the run.

188
00:10:34,874 --> 00:10:37,074
Look at us now.

189
00:10:39,133 --> 00:10:41,145
They're starting to
search the buildings.

190
00:10:41,147 --> 00:10:43,280
- Train station.
- Airport.

191
00:10:43,316 --> 00:10:45,383
Train station.

192
00:10:53,960 --> 00:10:57,628
All passengers must present a ticket.

193
00:10:57,664 --> 00:11:01,965
All passengers must present a ticket.

194
00:11:02,001 --> 00:11:04,468
Never gonna get to our seats.
We need to go through there.

195
00:11:04,504 --> 00:11:06,303
Even the pilot can't get on the plane.

196
00:11:06,339 --> 00:11:07,853
This is an airport full of planes.

197
00:11:07,855 --> 00:11:09,584
- There's got to be others.
- It's no good.

198
00:11:09,587 --> 00:11:11,608
People will die here today.

199
00:11:11,644 --> 00:11:12,776
We need another option.

200
00:11:12,812 --> 00:11:14,344
- My man, Omar.
- Omar?

201
00:11:14,380 --> 00:11:15,712
That slippery brother?

202
00:11:15,748 --> 00:11:17,548
Trust is a luxury right now.

203
00:11:17,584 --> 00:11:20,284
He can be trusted. To a
point. He has connections on

204
00:11:20,320 --> 00:11:22,152
- the western coast, across the desert.
- No.

205
00:11:22,188 --> 00:11:24,655
Lincoln and Michael are
coming here. That's the plan.

206
00:11:24,658 --> 00:11:26,690
They don't have a next move if we leave.

207
00:11:26,693 --> 00:11:28,593
Now they're out there
somewhere, God knows where.

208
00:11:28,595 --> 00:11:30,661
Your friends are too
late. Look around you.

209
00:11:30,697 --> 00:11:32,434
This airport is no good to them.

210
00:11:32,437 --> 00:11:34,098
We're not leaving.

211
00:11:40,306 --> 00:11:41,772
What is that place?

212
00:11:43,309 --> 00:11:44,975
Where the westerners went

213
00:11:45,011 --> 00:11:46,310
when they made their escape.

214
00:11:46,346 --> 00:11:48,312
I ran into one at the Forger's Den.

215
00:11:48,348 --> 00:11:49,680
I can help.

216
00:11:49,716 --> 00:11:52,182
And how do you expect
to find the foreigners

217
00:11:52,218 --> 00:11:53,551
with only one eye?

218
00:12:05,198 --> 00:12:06,430
They're here. ISIL are here!

219
00:12:12,438 --> 00:12:14,771
Come on, come on. I have an idea.

220
00:12:14,807 --> 00:12:17,808
The pilot.

221
00:12:17,844 --> 00:12:19,877
Okay, follow me. Follow me!

222
00:12:19,913 --> 00:12:21,984
Don't lose him. Don't lose the pilot.

223
00:12:29,188 --> 00:12:32,490
Come on. Come on, come on.

224
00:12:33,826 --> 00:12:35,660
Come on, come on, come on, come on.

225
00:12:35,695 --> 00:12:37,828
No, just stay down.

226
00:12:45,638 --> 00:12:48,039
Okay. Wait here.

227
00:12:48,074 --> 00:12:48,985
- What?
- I'll be back.

228
00:12:48,988 --> 00:12:50,674
- Benjamin...
- I'm going alone.

229
00:12:50,710 --> 00:12:51,909
Don't do it.

230
00:13:00,129 --> 00:13:01,801
Halt!

231
00:13:11,129 --> 00:13:12,395
What are you doing here?

232
00:13:12,431 --> 00:13:14,330
- On your knees!
- Halt!

233
00:13:14,734 --> 00:13:16,600
Come out. Come out.

234
00:13:16,636 --> 00:13:18,068
Who are you? Papers.

235
00:13:18,104 --> 00:13:20,103
- Don't shoot. Don't shoot.
- Papers.

236
00:13:20,139 --> 00:13:21,271
Infidels!

237
00:13:21,307 --> 00:13:23,907
The infidels are in the airport.

238
00:13:23,943 --> 00:13:26,176
The killers of Ramal! I've
seen them with my own eyes.

239
00:13:26,212 --> 00:13:28,679
- What?
- I want my reward.

240
00:13:28,715 --> 00:13:31,081
The ten million rial. I will be rich.

241
00:13:31,117 --> 00:13:33,413
- Take us to them.
- Not until you promise

242
00:13:33,416 --> 00:13:37,187
I will get my ten million rial.

243
00:13:37,223 --> 00:13:39,623
If you speak the truth,
you'll have the money.

244
00:14:00,076 --> 00:14:02,646
You kick a lot of ass for a good Muslim.

245
00:14:04,674 --> 00:14:06,474
You can take the man out of the streets,

246
00:14:06,485 --> 00:14:08,252
but you can't take
the streets of the man.

247
00:14:08,254 --> 00:14:10,354
Why do you help me? Who are you?

248
00:14:10,390 --> 00:14:12,356
I'm a man, just like you,

249
00:14:12,392 --> 00:14:14,324
trying to get out of this madness,

250
00:14:14,360 --> 00:14:17,728
but we're not gonna get
out through those gates.

251
00:14:17,764 --> 00:14:19,224
The only way out now

252
00:14:19,227 --> 00:14:20,998
is up, brother.

253
00:14:21,034 --> 00:14:22,632
The 747 is done.

254
00:14:22,668 --> 00:14:23,934
It's been secured by the rebels.

255
00:14:23,936 --> 00:14:26,236
I'm not talking about Yemenia Air.

256
00:14:26,272 --> 00:14:27,471
I have my eyes

257
00:14:27,507 --> 00:14:29,040
on a different set of wings.

258
00:14:43,356 --> 00:14:44,588
- Mom?
- Hey.

259
00:14:44,591 --> 00:14:45,457
Sara!

260
00:14:45,491 --> 00:14:46,690
You scared us.

261
00:14:46,726 --> 00:14:47,944
- Sorry.
- Is everything all right?

262
00:14:47,946 --> 00:14:50,313
Yeah, no, It's fine. I
just... it's been a crazy day,

263
00:14:50,316 --> 00:14:52,296
made more so by the fact that
I forgot Mike's Spanish lesson.

264
00:14:52,298 --> 00:14:53,964
- Spanish?
- Yeah.

265
00:14:54,000 --> 00:14:55,900
- That's not today.
- We're gonna talk about it in the car, okay?

266
00:14:55,902 --> 00:14:57,715
Are you sure? Is everything okay?

267
00:14:57,718 --> 00:14:59,369
Really. Yes. We're fine. Thank you.

268
00:14:59,405 --> 00:15:01,086
Well, let me get Mike's bag.

269
00:15:01,089 --> 00:15:03,980
No, no, don't worry about it.
I'll get it tomorrow.

270
00:15:09,173 --> 00:15:10,909
I want you to get in the car
and no matter what...

271
00:15:10,911 --> 00:15:14,757
- You don't get out, okay?
- Hey, hey, hey! Where you going so fast?

272
00:15:14,760 --> 00:15:16,812
Get in.

273
00:15:16,815 --> 00:15:18,749
Thank you.

274
00:15:20,786 --> 00:15:22,519
How was that department
meeting yesterday?

275
00:15:24,623 --> 00:15:26,456
You usually meet with killers?

276
00:15:28,827 --> 00:15:30,861
Sara. Sara. Please, please, please.

277
00:15:30,896 --> 00:15:32,855
I can explain, okay? Just listen to me.

278
00:15:34,633 --> 00:15:37,066
I was sick with worry.

279
00:15:37,102 --> 00:15:39,802
I needed to protect you,
to-to protect our family,

280
00:15:39,838 --> 00:15:41,671
so I picked up your phone from the shop

281
00:15:41,707 --> 00:15:43,139
and I took it to Andrew Nelson,

282
00:15:43,175 --> 00:15:45,174
my buddy in the computer
sciences department.

283
00:15:45,210 --> 00:15:46,643
He did a deep dive,

284
00:15:46,679 --> 00:15:49,279
some kind of data
archaeology, and he did it.

285
00:15:49,315 --> 00:15:51,151
He tracked those bastards down.

286
00:15:51,154 --> 00:15:52,802
Got their cell information.

287
00:15:52,805 --> 00:15:54,704
So... so I called them,

288
00:15:54,740 --> 00:15:56,533
thinking I could-I could maybe

289
00:15:56,536 --> 00:15:58,589
- make a-make a deal with them.
- You called them.

290
00:15:58,592 --> 00:16:00,566
Sara?

291
00:16:00,569 --> 00:16:02,145
Sara, please, listen to me.

292
00:16:02,148 --> 00:16:04,147
Sara, this was for you.

293
00:16:04,183 --> 00:16:06,550
You're gonna want to get
out of the way right now.

294
00:16:06,586 --> 00:16:08,552
Sara. Sara!

295
00:16:16,896 --> 00:16:18,728
This is it.

296
00:16:18,731 --> 00:16:21,698
Our ticket out of the country.

297
00:16:21,734 --> 00:16:24,634
I'm telling you, Michael,
this is a bad idea.

298
00:16:24,670 --> 00:16:27,237
ISIL are everywhere.

299
00:16:28,374 --> 00:16:30,320
No, I can do this.

300
00:16:30,323 --> 00:16:32,476
You really paid the
equivalent of ten million rial

301
00:16:32,478 --> 00:16:33,944
for some dude's ashes?

302
00:16:33,980 --> 00:16:35,912
Not just any ashes, man.

303
00:16:35,948 --> 00:16:39,617
Freddie Mercury's ashes.

304
00:16:39,652 --> 00:16:43,186
I would've paid twice that.

305
00:16:43,222 --> 00:16:44,621
Come on.

306
00:16:44,657 --> 00:16:47,458
Keep your head down.

307
00:16:54,300 --> 00:16:56,499
I think it's time we get
sane and head to the airport.

308
00:16:56,535 --> 00:16:57,801
No, no, no.

309
00:16:57,837 --> 00:17:00,403
This is better. They
control the station.

310
00:17:00,439 --> 00:17:04,474
They'll never think to
look for us here now.

311
00:17:04,510 --> 00:17:06,443
They're repurposing
those trains for cargo,

312
00:17:06,479 --> 00:17:07,677
not passengers.

313
00:17:07,713 --> 00:17:09,079
Once we're on, it's...

314
00:17:09,115 --> 00:17:10,914
it's a straight shot to the north.

315
00:17:10,950 --> 00:17:13,650
They won't check the cars again.

316
00:17:13,686 --> 00:17:15,625
That's what you see
when you see the train?

317
00:17:15,628 --> 00:17:17,754
I see a bunch of dudes with AK-47s

318
00:17:17,790 --> 00:17:19,889
who don't look a thing
like us. You really believe

319
00:17:19,925 --> 00:17:22,392
we can survive 300 miles on a train

320
00:17:22,428 --> 00:17:23,860
through ISIL territory?

321
00:17:23,896 --> 00:17:25,395
Now that's suicide.

322
00:17:25,431 --> 00:17:27,998
It does seem risky. No kidding.

323
00:17:32,077 --> 00:17:33,777
No, no.

324
00:17:33,780 --> 00:17:36,306
We get in that line of cargo
carriers. Keep our heads down.

325
00:17:36,308 --> 00:17:39,456
Once we're on the train,
lay low the rest of the trip.

326
00:17:39,459 --> 00:17:43,113
Besides, we don't
need to look like them.

327
00:17:43,149 --> 00:17:46,082
Tell the believing
men to lower their gaze

328
00:17:46,118 --> 00:17:47,651
and be modest.

329
00:17:47,687 --> 00:17:49,520
Come on.

330
00:17:49,555 --> 00:17:50,754
From the Koran.

331
00:17:56,829 --> 00:18:01,532
All the roads are blocked.

332
00:18:04,737 --> 00:18:09,206
So you'll have to find a
different way to the border.

333
00:18:15,014 --> 00:18:16,280
By train!

334
00:18:18,384 --> 00:18:21,185
Heather, what now?

335
00:18:21,220 --> 00:18:22,719
What now?

336
00:18:22,755 --> 00:18:24,287
I mean, it was all a lie.

337
00:18:24,323 --> 00:18:25,555
Wasn't it? Everything.

338
00:18:25,591 --> 00:18:27,123
Our whole life, our whole marriage.

339
00:18:27,159 --> 00:18:29,826
He was standing as close
as you were to me right now,

340
00:18:29,862 --> 00:18:32,295
and he was chatting with
the woman who shot him.

341
00:18:32,331 --> 00:18:34,864
You're saying he planned
to get himself shot

342
00:18:34,900 --> 00:18:37,367
like it was some sort
of, uh, sick performance?

343
00:18:37,403 --> 00:18:39,402
I don't know. I don't know.

344
00:18:39,438 --> 00:18:41,004
I mean, I...

345
00:18:41,040 --> 00:18:44,074
- Yes. Yes, it was.
- But he almost died.

346
00:18:44,110 --> 00:18:46,176
So, the plan was to wing him, right?

347
00:18:46,212 --> 00:18:49,030
To just put him above suspicion,
but the shot went wide.

348
00:18:49,033 --> 00:18:50,480
He gets hit.

349
00:18:50,516 --> 00:18:54,304
- He knows that he's married to a doctor.
- Sara, Sara, stop. Stop.

350
00:18:54,307 --> 00:18:56,152
You haven't slept in three days, right?

351
00:18:56,188 --> 00:18:59,189
You're upset about the home invasion

352
00:18:59,225 --> 00:19:01,591
and you're tying yourself up in knots

353
00:19:01,627 --> 00:19:04,427
because the love of your life,

354
00:19:04,463 --> 00:19:08,132
the father of your baby, might be alive.

355
00:19:10,369 --> 00:19:14,037
And I can't get through to Lincoln.

356
00:19:14,073 --> 00:19:16,106
But I saw that video.

357
00:19:16,142 --> 00:19:17,373
It's him.

358
00:19:17,409 --> 00:19:20,081
- Okay, and I...
- That's Michael.

359
00:19:20,084 --> 00:19:22,312
And I believe you. I do.

360
00:19:22,348 --> 00:19:23,646
And that matters.

361
00:19:23,682 --> 00:19:25,248
That's all that matters.

362
00:19:25,284 --> 00:19:26,616
No, I know.

363
00:19:26,652 --> 00:19:28,318
But Jacob is a good man.

364
00:19:28,354 --> 00:19:30,253
He's your husband.

365
00:19:30,289 --> 00:19:33,156
- Yeah.
- And he helped you start a new life.

366
00:19:33,192 --> 00:19:34,691
Together.

367
00:19:35,932 --> 00:19:37,966
And that's him.

368
00:19:39,999 --> 00:19:42,332
- I have to answer it.
- No. No.

369
00:19:42,368 --> 00:19:45,568
- No, you don't.
- Leave a message and we'll get back.

370
00:19:47,139 --> 00:19:49,037
Heather, Heather? Is Sara there?

371
00:19:49,040 --> 00:19:50,707
Please, I-I need to speak with her.

372
00:19:50,743 --> 00:19:52,376
Look, there's been a
huge misunderstanding

373
00:19:52,378 --> 00:19:53,610
and I can explain everything.

374
00:19:53,646 --> 00:19:55,128
Will you just... Will you tell her that?

375
00:19:55,130 --> 00:19:56,079
And to call me?

376
00:19:56,115 --> 00:19:57,347
He's tracking me.

377
00:19:57,383 --> 00:19:59,449
Oh, Sara, honey. I'm your best friend.

378
00:19:59,485 --> 00:20:01,699
Of-of course he's
gonna call here first.

379
00:20:01,702 --> 00:20:03,169
It doesn't make him Deep Throat.

380
00:20:04,356 --> 00:20:05,401
Listen,

381
00:20:05,404 --> 00:20:07,658
let's just see if there's
a simpler explanation.

382
00:20:07,660 --> 00:20:09,159
Hmm?

383
00:20:09,195 --> 00:20:11,294
Okay.

384
00:20:11,330 --> 00:20:14,466
What was the name of that
computer tech that he mentioned?

385
00:20:14,469 --> 00:20:16,599
Uh... Andrew.

386
00:20:16,635 --> 00:20:18,301
Nelson. Andrew Nelson.

387
00:20:18,337 --> 00:20:20,670
Okay, well, I have an old
friend in that department.

388
00:20:20,706 --> 00:20:22,205
We can find out

389
00:20:22,241 --> 00:20:23,706
if Jacob's full of it in one call.

390
00:20:23,742 --> 00:20:25,442
Okay.

391
00:20:35,688 --> 00:20:41,321
_

392
00:20:42,198 --> 00:20:44,227
_

393
00:20:44,230 --> 00:20:46,873
_

394
00:20:46,876 --> 00:20:48,829
_

395
00:20:48,829 --> 00:20:50,748
_

396
00:21:20,366 --> 00:21:22,733
Get on the other side of that train!

397
00:21:33,879 --> 00:21:35,279
Come on, come on, come on,

398
00:21:35,281 --> 00:21:37,080
come on, come on!

399
00:21:42,655 --> 00:21:44,388
Come on, let's go.

400
00:21:58,437 --> 00:21:59,569
What do you want?

401
00:21:59,605 --> 00:22:01,571
Look at the picture I just sent you.

402
00:22:01,607 --> 00:22:03,879
I can see the murderers now.

403
00:22:06,445 --> 00:22:07,610
Where?

404
00:22:07,646 --> 00:22:09,345
Not so fast.

405
00:22:09,381 --> 00:22:11,902
Bring your weapons, I will stay on them.

406
00:22:13,280 --> 00:22:15,147
And I call the shots now.

407
00:22:18,967 --> 00:22:22,169
We checked. There's enough
fuel to get us out of Yemen.

408
00:22:28,623 --> 00:22:31,176
Question is, can you
fly an old bird like this?

409
00:22:31,220 --> 00:22:32,619
We'll find out.

410
00:22:40,674 --> 00:22:42,221
There's another station,

411
00:22:42,223 --> 00:22:44,197
30 miles outside Sana'a.

412
00:22:44,228 --> 00:22:45,891
We can find a way there, hop a train.

413
00:22:45,893 --> 00:22:48,927
They won't anticipate
us coming that way.

414
00:22:48,963 --> 00:22:51,199
Doubling down on a bad bet.

415
00:22:51,202 --> 00:22:52,430
Just like you did

416
00:22:52,466 --> 00:22:54,466
seven years back with the CIA.

417
00:22:54,502 --> 00:22:56,030
Look around you.

418
00:22:56,033 --> 00:22:58,370
Your plans affect people,
you don't even see it.

419
00:22:58,406 --> 00:23:01,306
I don't blame you for resenting me.

420
00:23:01,342 --> 00:23:02,785
You're damn right I resent you.

421
00:23:02,788 --> 00:23:05,877
I see it, Linc. I see it.

422
00:23:05,913 --> 00:23:07,712
Every second of every day,

423
00:23:07,748 --> 00:23:09,514
the people, the collateral damage,

424
00:23:09,550 --> 00:23:11,917
the lives I've... affected.

425
00:23:13,454 --> 00:23:15,159
But I can't start thinking about that.

426
00:23:15,162 --> 00:23:16,354
Because if I do,

427
00:23:16,390 --> 00:23:17,556
then it all falls apart

428
00:23:17,592 --> 00:23:19,214
and none of us get to go home.

429
00:23:19,217 --> 00:23:20,849
I have to stay focused,

430
00:23:20,852 --> 00:23:23,095
be the man with the plan.

431
00:23:23,130 --> 00:23:24,529
Just like Fox River.

432
00:23:24,565 --> 00:23:27,199
Remember?

433
00:23:29,578 --> 00:23:30,844
We got wheels.

434
00:23:30,847 --> 00:23:31,912
Good work.

435
00:23:31,915 --> 00:23:33,882
The airport's the only play.

436
00:23:35,243 --> 00:23:37,642
The airport is five miles away.

437
00:23:37,678 --> 00:23:39,178
The border is hundreds.

438
00:23:40,648 --> 00:23:42,013
Look,

439
00:23:42,049 --> 00:23:44,405
the airport might be the right choice,

440
00:23:44,408 --> 00:23:46,685
but I trust my instincts.

441
00:23:46,721 --> 00:23:48,320
They've gotten us this far.

442
00:23:48,356 --> 00:23:49,501
And my gut says

443
00:23:49,504 --> 00:23:52,184
we can still make it out through
the north. Choice is yours.

444
00:23:54,264 --> 00:23:55,796
Look, man,

445
00:23:55,799 --> 00:23:58,027
I agree with you, even if
I don't know you from Adam.

446
00:23:58,030 --> 00:23:59,030
But...

447
00:23:59,033 --> 00:24:01,303
got to go with the horse

448
00:24:01,306 --> 00:24:03,553
that got you here, you know? So...

449
00:24:03,556 --> 00:24:05,056
he's my horse.

450
00:24:10,286 --> 00:24:12,485
Craziest horse I've ever met.

451
00:24:12,513 --> 00:24:14,446
But got us this far.

452
00:24:14,482 --> 00:24:15,580
Crazy only works

453
00:24:15,616 --> 00:24:16,949
if it doesn't get you killed.

454
00:24:31,051 --> 00:24:33,679
_

455
00:24:33,968 --> 00:24:35,533
Andrew?

456
00:24:35,569 --> 00:24:37,936
Uh, Professor Hayden
told us to speak with you?

457
00:24:37,972 --> 00:24:39,738
Oh, yeah. Uh, yeah, right.

458
00:24:39,774 --> 00:24:40,672
Sorry.

459
00:24:40,675 --> 00:24:42,507
Uh, hi, Andrew.

460
00:24:42,510 --> 00:24:44,376
I'm Sara Scofield.

461
00:24:44,412 --> 00:24:45,744
Thanks for taking the time.

462
00:24:45,780 --> 00:24:47,479
By any chance,

463
00:24:47,515 --> 00:24:50,448
did my husband Jacob Ness ask
you to work on my cell phone?

464
00:24:50,484 --> 00:24:53,585
Yeah, he did, uh, yesterday.

465
00:24:53,621 --> 00:24:55,020
What did he, uh...

466
00:24:55,056 --> 00:24:56,584
What did he ask you to do?

467
00:24:56,587 --> 00:24:59,167
Uh, he said he was looking to
find the contact information

468
00:24:59,170 --> 00:25:01,727
for the people who
were stalking his wife.

469
00:25:01,762 --> 00:25:04,696
So I did a data dive and
gave him what I could find.

470
00:25:04,732 --> 00:25:06,665
How?

471
00:25:06,709 --> 00:25:10,143
They hacked your phone
and lifted the data,

472
00:25:10,171 --> 00:25:13,338
but in the process, left a
very slight electronic signature

473
00:25:13,374 --> 00:25:15,473
that I was able to track back to them.

474
00:25:15,509 --> 00:25:16,775
Wait, who are "they"?

475
00:25:16,811 --> 00:25:19,445
Don't know. It was a dummy IP address,

476
00:25:19,480 --> 00:25:21,747
but the cell and location were correct.

477
00:25:21,782 --> 00:25:23,182
They couldn't hide that from me.

478
00:25:29,590 --> 00:25:32,758
The man himself.

479
00:25:37,231 --> 00:25:38,596
Hello.

480
00:25:38,632 --> 00:25:40,832
Sara, listen, I know you're upset,

481
00:25:40,868 --> 00:25:43,501
but I need you to come to the
Whitney Heights police station,

482
00:25:43,537 --> 00:25:44,769
right now.

483
00:25:44,805 --> 00:25:46,372
Please.

484
00:25:55,549 --> 00:25:57,449
So, now we got some time to talk.

485
00:25:57,485 --> 00:25:59,385
Um...

486
00:26:00,354 --> 00:26:02,354
Well, your name's Michael.

487
00:26:02,390 --> 00:26:04,089
Cool.

488
00:26:04,125 --> 00:26:05,757
You have a brother.

489
00:26:05,793 --> 00:26:08,327
What else don't I know?

490
00:26:11,255 --> 00:26:13,855
Serious, I need to know.
I've been traveling so fast,

491
00:26:13,858 --> 00:26:16,068
for so long, I didn't even
stop to think who you really are

492
00:26:16,070 --> 00:26:17,569
or what we're real doing here.

493
00:26:17,605 --> 00:26:18,737
I don't even know why

494
00:26:18,773 --> 00:26:20,372
you dragged me into all this, you know?

495
00:26:20,408 --> 00:26:23,675
You got to forget the
past, Whip, the details.

496
00:26:23,711 --> 00:26:24,976
None of that matters now.

497
00:26:25,012 --> 00:26:27,245
What have my actions
been all these years?

498
00:26:27,281 --> 00:26:28,780
Who's been taking care of you

499
00:26:28,816 --> 00:26:30,849
through everything, huh?

500
00:26:30,885 --> 00:26:32,250
Me. Right?

501
00:26:32,286 --> 00:26:34,753
Right?

502
00:26:34,789 --> 00:26:36,088
Yeah.

503
00:26:37,258 --> 00:26:38,390
Nothing changes.

504
00:26:38,426 --> 00:26:39,791
You're still my whip hand...

505
00:26:39,827 --> 00:26:41,547
Whip hand, yeah, I
know, I'm your whip hand.

506
00:26:41,562 --> 00:26:44,696
It's... it's not good
enough this time, man.

507
00:26:46,100 --> 00:26:47,566
Can you just give it to me straight?

508
00:26:47,601 --> 00:26:48,967
You know, I'm a big
boy, I can handle it.

509
00:26:48,969 --> 00:26:50,869
There's a reason you're my whip hand.

510
00:26:50,905 --> 00:26:53,809
A reason that's gonna change your life.

511
00:26:53,812 --> 00:26:55,894
There's a light at the
end of the tunnel for you.

512
00:27:01,715 --> 00:27:03,282
What the hell was that?

513
00:27:07,856 --> 00:27:09,354
Oh, son of a bitch.

514
00:27:09,390 --> 00:27:10,622
We got to go.

515
00:27:10,658 --> 00:27:11,890
Let's go!

516
00:27:36,292 --> 00:27:38,487
- There's no way out.
- Back of the hospital's

517
00:27:38,490 --> 00:27:40,189
been shelled to rubble. It's blocked.

518
00:27:40,192 --> 00:27:42,058
Upstairs is blocked, too.

519
00:27:42,061 --> 00:27:43,579
We're gonna go downstairs.

520
00:27:43,622 --> 00:27:45,322
Look for a way out.

521
00:27:45,350 --> 00:27:46,850
You do the same.

522
00:27:52,881 --> 00:27:54,380
Thanks.

523
00:27:57,796 --> 00:27:59,830
What's going on?

524
00:28:01,351 --> 00:28:03,184
Sara, just...

525
00:28:04,227 --> 00:28:05,626
just come with us.

526
00:28:05,662 --> 00:28:07,495
You'll see. Please.

527
00:28:13,378 --> 00:28:15,870
Hello, ma'am. Um, Sara Scofield?

528
00:28:15,905 --> 00:28:17,304
Yes, sir.

529
00:28:17,340 --> 00:28:20,541
Thanks for coming in,
I'm Detective Kennan.

530
00:28:20,577 --> 00:28:23,378
We'd like you to point out
who broke into your home.

531
00:28:23,413 --> 00:28:24,445
And...

532
00:28:24,481 --> 00:28:27,014
the one who shot your husband.

533
00:28:30,060 --> 00:28:31,260
It's three and four.

534
00:28:31,287 --> 00:28:33,221
The man and the woman was the shooter.

535
00:28:33,223 --> 00:28:35,089
Are you sure?

536
00:28:43,299 --> 00:28:45,332
Yes, sir.

537
00:28:45,368 --> 00:28:47,001
Yes, I'm absolutely sure.

538
00:28:50,540 --> 00:28:52,005
There's got to be a way out.

539
00:28:52,041 --> 00:28:54,076
Something... something that
connects to the surface.

540
00:28:54,078 --> 00:28:56,540
Going down's not gonna work, Michael.

541
00:28:56,543 --> 00:28:58,293
We need to set up an ambush and fight.

542
00:28:58,314 --> 00:29:00,614
Yeah, well, fighting is
your default setting.

543
00:29:00,650 --> 00:29:03,050
It's not always about fists.

544
00:29:03,086 --> 00:29:05,319
I'm telling you, there's no way out.

545
00:29:05,355 --> 00:29:07,889
Then find something
to fight with, you idiot.

546
00:29:20,398 --> 00:29:22,302
I don't think it's that kind of a party,

547
00:29:22,338 --> 00:29:23,771
but I like your style.

548
00:29:23,807 --> 00:29:25,806
What are you going to do with that?

549
00:29:25,842 --> 00:29:28,308
I don't know.

550
00:29:28,344 --> 00:29:29,877
Beats a fist.

551
00:29:41,583 --> 00:29:43,015
Rubbing alcohol?

552
00:29:43,018 --> 00:29:44,218
What the hell are you doing?

553
00:29:45,792 --> 00:29:48,796
You'll go blind, you idiot.

554
00:29:48,832 --> 00:29:51,031
It's only 95% alcohol.

555
00:29:51,067 --> 00:29:53,834
I'll only go 95% blind.

556
00:30:02,145 --> 00:30:04,979
There. There's an air shaft.

557
00:30:23,166 --> 00:30:26,901
Well, it's about fists now.

558
00:30:45,054 --> 00:30:46,420
Michael?

559
00:30:49,592 --> 00:30:53,127
No. It's them.

560
00:31:17,620 --> 00:31:20,487
My first lover was much older than me.

561
00:31:20,523 --> 00:31:22,865
He was my friend's father.

562
00:31:22,868 --> 00:31:25,984
Massi was his name.

563
00:31:28,798 --> 00:31:31,999
It was the greatest of scandals

564
00:31:32,035 --> 00:31:33,600
that we kept to ourselves.

565
00:31:33,636 --> 00:31:37,204
But his wife discovered us

566
00:31:37,240 --> 00:31:39,340
and told her brothers.

567
00:31:43,012 --> 00:31:47,447
Massi was taken into the desert...

568
00:31:47,483 --> 00:31:51,051
and buried.

569
00:31:51,087 --> 00:31:53,220
Alive.

570
00:31:54,591 --> 00:31:57,892
They brought his eyes to me in a rag.

571
00:32:03,099 --> 00:32:06,434
I need you to use that on me.

572
00:32:07,236 --> 00:32:09,303
End my suffering.

573
00:32:10,273 --> 00:32:11,846
What, this?

574
00:32:11,849 --> 00:32:15,309
Ja's right. All this running is pointless.

575
00:32:15,345 --> 00:32:18,712
Do you know what they
will do to me here,

576
00:32:18,748 --> 00:32:21,215
away from seeing eyes?

577
00:32:23,186 --> 00:32:24,452
I can't.

578
00:32:26,322 --> 00:32:28,022
I won't let that happen.

579
00:32:28,057 --> 00:32:29,756
Do you understand?

580
00:32:29,792 --> 00:32:31,787
I won't let that happen.

581
00:32:31,790 --> 00:32:35,062
Listen. Sid.

582
00:32:35,098 --> 00:32:37,030
I'm not giving up.

583
00:32:37,066 --> 00:32:40,519
And queer or no, you're not, either.

584
00:32:42,472 --> 00:32:44,238
They're in the wrong.

585
00:32:44,273 --> 00:32:45,906
Not you.

586
00:32:52,348 --> 00:32:55,849
What are you gonna do with that?

587
00:33:16,606 --> 00:33:19,106
Michael, come on.

588
00:33:21,044 --> 00:33:24,444
I'm sorry, Linc.

589
00:33:25,915 --> 00:33:29,049
I should have come to you.

590
00:33:29,085 --> 00:33:31,451
I should've asked for your help

591
00:33:31,487 --> 00:33:36,057
when Poseidon offered
me the deal. I blew it.

592
00:33:36,092 --> 00:33:38,092
At the time, I thought,

593
00:33:38,127 --> 00:33:42,096
if I dealt with it myself,
the pain would only be mine.

594
00:33:42,131 --> 00:33:46,266
But instead I opened this Pandora's Box.

595
00:33:46,302 --> 00:33:49,637
I wanted to make it better,
but I only made it worse

596
00:33:49,672 --> 00:33:52,473
for everyone.

597
00:33:52,508 --> 00:33:55,376
And somewhere in there...

598
00:33:57,647 --> 00:33:59,947
I became a ghost.

599
00:34:22,438 --> 00:34:24,204
I made a lot of mistakes.

600
00:34:24,240 --> 00:34:28,175
A lot of foolish, imperfect choices,

601
00:34:28,211 --> 00:34:30,911
but every one of them...

602
00:34:33,516 --> 00:34:36,784
every one of them I made for love.

603
00:34:36,819 --> 00:34:39,487
I know. I know.

604
00:34:42,058 --> 00:34:43,623
Michael,

605
00:34:43,659 --> 00:34:47,294
you're the smartest
person I've ever known,

606
00:34:47,330 --> 00:34:49,897
but you can't carry the
load on your shoulders alone.

607
00:34:51,801 --> 00:34:54,034
You need to share the burden.

608
00:34:54,070 --> 00:34:55,268
Yes.

609
00:34:55,304 --> 00:34:56,703
That's family.

610
00:34:56,739 --> 00:34:59,926
That's what family's for.

611
00:34:59,929 --> 00:35:02,576
Sara, I don't know
what you thought, but...

612
00:35:02,612 --> 00:35:04,845
I'm just a husband who
was worried about his wife.

613
00:35:04,881 --> 00:35:08,081
And yeah, I-I should have told
you what I was doing, but...

614
00:35:08,117 --> 00:35:10,317
Look, I felt like... like
everything was spiraling

615
00:35:10,353 --> 00:35:12,833
out of control and I had to do
whatever I could to protect you.

616
00:35:12,855 --> 00:35:16,157
So you thought you'd
contact two hired killers?

617
00:35:16,192 --> 00:35:18,658
I was trying to play the white knight.

618
00:35:18,694 --> 00:35:21,907
Not very well.

619
00:35:21,910 --> 00:35:23,797
And it was insanity.

620
00:35:23,833 --> 00:35:25,398
I was scared to death.

621
00:35:25,434 --> 00:35:27,267
A-A blubbering idiot,

622
00:35:27,303 --> 00:35:30,738
but I thought they would
respond to money, you know?

623
00:35:30,773 --> 00:35:33,473
Pay them whatever it
took to make them go away.

624
00:35:33,509 --> 00:35:36,576
More than they were already making:

625
00:35:36,592 --> 00:35:38,779
$50,000.

626
00:35:38,815 --> 00:35:41,281
Look, I, uh...

627
00:35:41,317 --> 00:35:44,818
I had a tracker in it, Sara.

628
00:35:44,845 --> 00:35:48,980
This little thing, but
they didn't touch it.

629
00:35:50,259 --> 00:35:54,294
I contacted the police before the meet,

630
00:35:54,330 --> 00:35:56,997
but we nailed them anyhow.

631
00:35:57,033 --> 00:35:58,933
We nailed them.

632
00:35:58,968 --> 00:36:00,259
Jacob.

633
00:36:00,262 --> 00:36:02,583
I am so sorry I put you through this.

634
00:36:17,753 --> 00:36:20,354
Let's do this.

635
00:36:24,727 --> 00:36:27,699
A wrench and a pipe against AKs.

636
00:36:28,397 --> 00:36:29,896
It'll be fun.

637
00:36:29,932 --> 00:36:33,367
I've always wanted a
crack at these bastards.

638
00:36:53,422 --> 00:36:58,058
♪ I paid my dues ♪

639
00:37:00,162 --> 00:37:02,196
♪ Time after time ♪

640
00:37:03,599 --> 00:37:05,966
♪ I've served my sentence ♪

641
00:37:06,002 --> 00:37:06,967
Come back.

642
00:37:07,003 --> 00:37:09,870
♪ But committed no crime ♪

643
00:37:09,906 --> 00:37:12,372
♪ And bad mistakes ♪

644
00:37:12,408 --> 00:37:13,473
Get over here...

645
00:37:13,509 --> 00:37:15,876
♪ I've made a few ♪

646
00:37:15,912 --> 00:37:17,521
You're gonna get yourself killed!

647
00:37:17,524 --> 00:37:20,013
♪ I've had my share ♪

648
00:37:20,049 --> 00:37:22,415
♪ Of sand kicked in my face ♪

649
00:37:22,451 --> 00:37:24,251
♪ But I've come through ♪

650
00:37:24,287 --> 00:37:28,455
♪ And I go on and on and on ♪

651
00:37:29,825 --> 00:37:32,525
♪ We are the champions ♪

652
00:37:32,561 --> 00:37:35,062
♪ My friends ♪

653
00:37:44,707 --> 00:37:47,641
♪ We are the champions ♪

654
00:37:47,677 --> 00:37:52,046
♪ We are the champions... ♪

655
00:38:02,338 --> 00:38:05,826
I love you, you crazy
Japanese son of a bitch!

656
00:38:05,829 --> 00:38:07,106
It's Korean, champ.

657
00:38:07,142 --> 00:38:08,175
Whatever. I still love you.

658
00:38:08,177 --> 00:38:09,375
ISIL are like roaches.

659
00:38:09,411 --> 00:38:10,510
More will be here soon.

660
00:38:10,546 --> 00:38:12,612
What do we do now?

661
00:38:12,648 --> 00:38:14,547
I need to take a break
from making decisions.

662
00:38:14,583 --> 00:38:16,511
Linc, airport?

663
00:38:16,514 --> 00:38:17,550
Airport.

664
00:38:22,091 --> 00:38:23,589
Hey.

665
00:38:23,625 --> 00:38:25,826
I got someone I want you to talk to.

666
00:38:28,831 --> 00:38:29,862
Hey.

667
00:38:29,898 --> 00:38:31,931
Oh, man!

668
00:38:31,967 --> 00:38:34,334
Now that's a voice I never
thought I'd hear again.

669
00:38:34,370 --> 00:38:36,688
Man, you got some
explaining to do, brother,

670
00:38:36,691 --> 00:38:38,371
- risen from the dead and all.
- Soon.

671
00:38:38,407 --> 00:38:39,672
Where can we meet you?

672
00:38:39,708 --> 00:38:41,674
Uh, hangar two. Right
off the main runway.

673
00:38:43,379 --> 00:38:44,787
But you better hurry your ass up.

674
00:38:44,790 --> 00:38:45,545
Hangar two?

675
00:38:45,581 --> 00:38:47,014
We could be there in 20 minutes.

676
00:38:47,049 --> 00:38:48,281
We can be there in 20 minutes.

677
00:38:48,317 --> 00:38:50,984
I don't know if we have that long.

678
00:38:51,020 --> 00:38:52,919
Wait for us. We'll be there.

679
00:38:52,955 --> 00:38:54,187
We got to move.

680
00:39:05,234 --> 00:39:06,599
Sid...

681
00:39:06,635 --> 00:39:08,234
Sid!

682
00:39:08,270 --> 00:39:10,670
I heard your call, infidel.

683
00:39:10,706 --> 00:39:14,408
Wings will not carry you to safety.

684
00:39:14,443 --> 00:39:17,559
One call, and my brothers

685
00:39:17,562 --> 00:39:19,715
will find your friends at the airport.

686
00:39:22,585 --> 00:39:26,404
_

687
00:39:34,730 --> 00:39:36,563
- Sid!
- Sid!

688
00:39:38,667 --> 00:39:40,634
Son of a bitch.

689
00:39:45,607 --> 00:39:47,107
No, no, no, no, no.

690
00:39:51,580 --> 00:39:54,047
Talk to me, Sid. Stay with us.

691
00:39:54,083 --> 00:39:55,515
Stay with us.

692
00:39:56,752 --> 00:39:58,985
Sid...

693
00:39:59,021 --> 00:40:01,555
Sid.

694
00:40:04,259 --> 00:40:06,326
He's gone.

695
00:40:21,276 --> 00:40:22,709
Don't waste yourself on him.

696
00:40:24,714 --> 00:40:26,274
You'll beat him by surviving.

697
00:40:33,355 --> 00:40:36,556
You will die, you hear me?

698
00:40:38,694 --> 00:40:40,594
You will all die!

699
00:40:41,864 --> 00:40:43,141
Oh, my...

700
00:40:43,144 --> 00:40:45,060
They're moving
more trucks into position.

701
00:40:45,063 --> 00:40:46,219
- Yeah.
- We can't wait.

702
00:40:46,222 --> 00:40:48,912
There won't be enough runway
to take off. We must go now.

703
00:40:48,915 --> 00:40:51,404
I owe Lincoln my
life. He deserves better.

704
00:40:51,440 --> 00:40:54,053
But with so many souls in our hands,

705
00:40:54,056 --> 00:40:55,723
do we really have a choice?

706
00:41:00,296 --> 00:41:02,729
Listen, we wait five more minutes.

707
00:41:02,732 --> 00:41:03,950
Okay?

708
00:41:03,986 --> 00:41:06,552
And then we take care
of the souls that we can.

709
00:41:06,588 --> 00:41:08,288
Understand?

710
00:41:14,548 --> 00:41:16,096
What the hell are you doing?

711
00:41:17,837 --> 00:41:20,066
The hell are you doing?

712
00:41:22,638 --> 00:41:25,638
Listen, we are not leaving my friends!

713
00:41:25,674 --> 00:41:26,773
Shut it down. Shut it down!

714
00:41:26,808 --> 00:41:28,341
You would condemn us all to death.

715
00:41:28,377 --> 00:41:30,491
If you stop me, no one gets out.

716
00:41:30,494 --> 00:41:32,946
Your friends can still make
it to safety. We will not.

717
00:41:59,374 --> 00:42:00,874
Yeah?

718
00:42:02,077 --> 00:42:04,677
C-Note? You got to
get out of here, man.

719
00:42:04,713 --> 00:42:07,881
Hey, no, no, no, no. W-We can
do this thing, man. We can do it.

720
00:42:07,916 --> 00:42:11,021
No! Go now! Otherwise,
you and the kids are dead!

721
00:42:11,024 --> 00:42:13,193
We'll work something out.

722
00:42:13,196 --> 00:42:15,355
We've been through worse.

723
00:42:18,694 --> 00:42:22,195
Linc, I'm so sorry.

724
00:42:22,231 --> 00:42:24,698
I'm so sorry, brother.

725
00:42:31,183 --> 00:42:33,149
Lincoln? Find Omar. He...

726
00:42:33,152 --> 00:42:34,394
What?

727
00:42:34,397 --> 00:42:35,841
I can't hear you. What?

