1
00:00:04,332 --> 00:00:06,177
We're gonna get you out of here.

2
00:00:06,180 --> 00:00:08,960
_

3
00:00:08,963 --> 00:00:10,497
_

4
00:00:10,500 --> 00:00:12,504
Poseidon put us in
here to get Ramal out,

5
00:00:12,507 --> 00:00:13,832
but then he abandoned us.

6
00:00:13,835 --> 00:00:15,837
Ramal is Poseidon's guy, not ours.

7
00:00:15,873 --> 00:00:18,173
The escape is on.

8
00:00:18,208 --> 00:00:19,875
He's my brother!

9
00:00:20,385 --> 00:00:21,977
Who the hell is this Poseidon guy?

10
00:00:21,979 --> 00:00:23,690
A frustrated policy wonk

11
00:00:23,693 --> 00:00:25,847
in the CIA, who created a cell

12
00:00:25,883 --> 00:00:28,983
within the CIA called 21-Void.

13
00:00:29,019 --> 00:00:30,385
And he needed my help

14
00:00:30,421 --> 00:00:33,455
breaking out people
imprisoned all over the world.

15
00:00:35,793 --> 00:00:38,060
We've awoken something.

16
00:00:38,095 --> 00:00:40,462
Any chance Poseidon will
just let us kill her?

17
00:00:40,497 --> 00:00:42,064
- Point.
- It's three and four.

18
00:00:42,099 --> 00:00:44,081
The man, and the woman was the shooter.

19
00:00:44,084 --> 00:00:45,650
Step back! That's not gonna happen.

20
00:00:45,653 --> 00:00:47,869
Go to hell!

21
00:01:24,678 --> 00:01:27,542
Even on the outside, I
feel the world crushing in.

22
00:01:27,578 --> 00:01:29,444
That's what being locked up does.

23
00:01:29,480 --> 00:01:32,147
You carry the prison
with you on the outside.

24
00:01:33,050 --> 00:01:35,150
I can't live that way.

25
00:01:36,253 --> 00:01:38,353
I've got to know the walls disappear.

26
00:01:38,388 --> 00:01:41,857
It's called being scared.
Happens when you're sober.

27
00:01:41,892 --> 00:01:43,992
Don't give me the pill talk.

28
00:01:44,027 --> 00:01:46,755
I won't give you the
poor little orphan talk.

29
00:01:46,758 --> 00:01:47,728
How your friend here

30
00:01:47,731 --> 00:01:49,531
isn't the father figure
you thought he was gonna be.

31
00:01:49,533 --> 00:01:50,833
This isn't helping.

32
00:01:50,869 --> 00:01:53,268
The walls are going away, brother.

33
00:01:53,303 --> 00:01:55,504
We're gonna make 'em go away.

34
00:01:55,539 --> 00:01:57,186
We're getting out of this country.

35
00:01:57,189 --> 00:01:58,273
All of us.

36
00:01:58,308 --> 00:02:00,242
Oh, really? Which
contingency's that gonna be?

37
00:02:00,244 --> 00:02:01,443
You burned through them all.

38
00:02:01,478 --> 00:02:03,745
Truck to border, train, airport.

39
00:02:03,780 --> 00:02:04,913
None of those.

40
00:02:04,948 --> 00:02:06,214
We're exactly where

41
00:02:06,250 --> 00:02:08,817
I don't want to be: improvising.

42
00:02:08,852 --> 00:02:11,319
Well, we need to improvise
something real fast

43
00:02:11,355 --> 00:02:12,754
or it's gonna be us down there,

44
00:02:12,789 --> 00:02:14,055
strung up like that.

45
00:02:14,091 --> 00:02:16,024
Omar. Sheba's guy.

46
00:02:16,059 --> 00:02:17,825
She said he had a way out.

47
00:02:17,861 --> 00:02:19,060
We can trust him?

48
00:02:19,096 --> 00:02:22,797
No. But he's our last option.

49
00:02:37,881 --> 00:02:41,483
You made bail. You're being released.

50
00:02:44,010 --> 00:02:46,377
Don't be a stranger, sugar.

51
00:02:52,389 --> 00:02:54,322
Poseidon got you out first.

52
00:02:55,332 --> 00:02:57,232
I thought I was his favorite.

53
00:03:02,052 --> 00:03:04,286
Son of a bitch really escaped.

54
00:03:04,289 --> 00:03:05,655
Yep.

55
00:03:05,658 --> 00:03:09,454
But why kill Ramal? I
thought they were allies.

56
00:03:09,489 --> 00:03:12,857
It's not our job to ask questions.

57
00:03:12,892 --> 00:03:14,192
Maybe we should.

58
00:03:14,227 --> 00:03:19,197
Poseidon says we find
Kaniel Outis and kill him.

59
00:03:19,232 --> 00:03:22,066
That's what we're gonna do.

60
00:03:23,970 --> 00:03:26,370
And I think I know how to do it.

61
00:03:32,912 --> 00:03:35,813
Omar.

62
00:03:39,486 --> 00:03:41,519
What are you doing here?

63
00:03:41,554 --> 00:03:43,621
You're radioactive, my friend.

64
00:03:45,191 --> 00:03:47,258
You killed Abu Ramal. Really?

65
00:03:47,293 --> 00:03:50,261
That was a very stupid move, man.

66
00:03:50,296 --> 00:03:51,896
Just tell us where you're headed.

67
00:03:54,801 --> 00:03:57,635
300 miles across the desert. Phaeacia.

68
00:03:57,670 --> 00:03:59,403
Old smuggling friends.

69
00:03:59,439 --> 00:04:01,772
Uh, autonomous zone. No ISIL.

70
00:04:01,808 --> 00:04:02,940
Perfect.

71
00:04:02,976 --> 00:04:04,709
Not perfect.

72
00:04:04,744 --> 00:04:07,580
Four of you, one of
me. Not enough seats.

73
00:04:07,583 --> 00:04:09,747
Okay, okay, all right. What
about getting another vehicle?

74
00:04:09,749 --> 00:04:11,215
Tell you what.

75
00:04:11,251 --> 00:04:13,869
Because it's Sheba and I owe her,

76
00:04:13,872 --> 00:04:16,612
maybe we can help each other.

77
00:04:16,615 --> 00:04:18,288
I have another vehicle.

78
00:04:18,324 --> 00:04:19,257
A Land Cruiser.

79
00:04:19,292 --> 00:04:21,058
I was going to leave it behind,

80
00:04:21,094 --> 00:04:22,527
but if you can get it,

81
00:04:22,562 --> 00:04:25,096
it's in a parking garage
two blocks from here.

82
00:04:25,131 --> 00:04:27,431
I'll let you follow.

83
00:04:27,467 --> 00:04:29,336
Deliver my second vehicle,

84
00:04:29,339 --> 00:04:32,007
and maybe I get the Phaeacians
to get you a boat somewhere,

85
00:04:32,010 --> 00:04:34,639
to Europe, France, Italy,
Spain, wherever you want to go.

86
00:04:34,674 --> 00:04:36,607
How's that sound?

87
00:04:38,149 --> 00:04:40,049
Keys are here.

88
00:04:41,938 --> 00:04:45,806
Uh, left side, the
red brick. First floor.

89
00:04:45,856 --> 00:04:48,591
Battery might be dead, so you might need

90
00:04:48,647 --> 00:04:50,480
- all of you to push.
- We got it.

91
00:04:51,169 --> 00:04:54,258
Whip, you stay with him. Let's move.

92
00:04:59,999 --> 00:05:02,300
He always give you orders like that?

93
00:05:06,039 --> 00:05:07,905
It's complicated.

94
00:05:08,808 --> 00:05:10,308
I got an order for you.

95
00:05:11,411 --> 00:05:12,843
Load up.

96
00:05:12,879 --> 00:05:14,612
One more bag inside.

97
00:05:20,067 --> 00:05:21,366
There!

98
00:05:22,768 --> 00:05:24,601
Give it a push on my say.

99
00:05:30,129 --> 00:05:32,697
Battery's working perfectly.

100
00:05:34,434 --> 00:05:35,833
How far away is this garage?

101
00:05:35,868 --> 00:05:39,003
Only two blocks. No problem.

102
00:05:39,038 --> 00:05:41,319
Someone says there's no problem,
there's always a problem.

103
00:05:45,168 --> 00:05:47,011
He set us up. Get in!

104
00:05:52,051 --> 00:05:52,984
Hold on.

105
00:06:58,002 --> 00:07:00,336
Nothing personal, my friend.

106
00:07:00,371 --> 00:07:03,839
In another life, no doubt
we smoke the hookah together.

107
00:07:19,290 --> 00:07:21,657
No! No, you don't!

108
00:07:27,431 --> 00:07:28,530
Whip, you okay?

109
00:07:28,566 --> 00:07:30,326
Thought you were gonna
be a millionaire, huh?

110
00:07:30,334 --> 00:07:31,571
I didn't have a choice.

111
00:07:33,671 --> 00:07:36,572
Come on! Coldcocking son of a bitch!

112
00:07:36,607 --> 00:07:39,475
Hold on, hold on. Easy
now, we may need him.

113
00:07:39,510 --> 00:07:41,443
Yes. You need me.

114
00:07:42,847 --> 00:07:45,281
I want a map to this Phaeacia place.

115
00:07:45,316 --> 00:07:47,383
You do realize this is Yemen, don't you?

116
00:07:47,418 --> 00:07:50,084
Phaeacia is a hundred people.

117
00:07:50,087 --> 00:07:52,855
Mud huts. There is no map.

118
00:07:55,217 --> 00:07:57,017
But I can lead you there.

119
00:07:58,389 --> 00:07:59,956
You want to trust this guy?

120
00:07:59,959 --> 00:08:01,794
Well, if he screws with us,

121
00:08:01,797 --> 00:08:04,198
we'll just let Whip
finish what he started.

122
00:08:04,233 --> 00:08:05,966
And I will kill you.

123
00:08:06,001 --> 00:08:08,135
I can't wait to kill him.

124
00:08:08,170 --> 00:08:11,538
You coldcock me, I end you.

125
00:08:11,574 --> 00:08:13,941
Rule number one in my country. Okay?

126
00:08:13,976 --> 00:08:16,510
And rule number one in my country is

127
00:08:16,545 --> 00:08:18,946
when things get bad, go to the desert.

128
00:08:37,366 --> 00:08:39,233
We are desperate, desperate men.

129
00:08:39,268 --> 00:08:40,968
Not as desperate as Omar right now.

130
00:08:41,003 --> 00:08:42,436
If there's one man you don't want

131
00:08:42,471 --> 00:08:44,304
to get on the wrong side of, it's Whip.

132
00:08:45,507 --> 00:08:48,408
That might apply to you, too, Michael.

133
00:08:48,444 --> 00:08:50,944
I get the sense the kid thinks
you betrayed him somehow.

134
00:08:51,858 --> 00:08:54,659
I could understand why he thinks that.

135
00:09:05,894 --> 00:09:08,762
I really am sorry, my friend.

136
00:09:08,797 --> 00:09:10,897
When I'm scared, I make poor choices.

137
00:09:10,933 --> 00:09:12,866
Zero comes out of your mouth. Okay?

138
00:09:15,004 --> 00:09:18,639
I'm having a really bad
couple days. Just the worst.

139
00:09:29,051 --> 00:09:31,118
Agent Kishida.

140
00:09:33,496 --> 00:09:35,330
Settling into your new office, I see.

141
00:09:35,357 --> 00:09:38,225
I still see this as
Kellerman's office, ma'am.

142
00:09:41,363 --> 00:09:43,430
As you probably know,

143
00:09:43,465 --> 00:09:45,465
before he was killed,

144
00:09:45,501 --> 00:09:48,068
Kellerman had been looking into 21-Void.

145
00:09:48,103 --> 00:09:49,939
I knew that. Yes.

146
00:09:49,970 --> 00:09:52,172
I need Paul's files.

147
00:09:52,207 --> 00:09:54,341
Obviously, he was
getting close to something

148
00:09:54,376 --> 00:09:56,843
and they killed him for it.

149
00:09:56,879 --> 00:09:58,845
Actually, I've been
looking into his leads,

150
00:09:58,881 --> 00:10:00,547
and there's nothing there.

151
00:10:00,582 --> 00:10:04,250
I hate to say it, but this
file is full of dead ends.

152
00:10:04,286 --> 00:10:06,086
There's nothing here.

153
00:10:06,121 --> 00:10:08,322
There must be something.

154
00:10:08,357 --> 00:10:11,058
Look, I don't want Paul
to have died in vain,

155
00:10:11,093 --> 00:10:13,393
but we need to look at this
whole thing with new eyes.

156
00:10:13,429 --> 00:10:14,895
Read it for yourself.

157
00:10:17,800 --> 00:10:20,933
Okay, you want to put
new eyes on this? Fine.

158
00:10:20,936 --> 00:10:22,433
Now that you report to me,

159
00:10:22,436 --> 00:10:24,338
I need you to look into the possibility

160
00:10:24,373 --> 00:10:26,073
that there was an insider involved.

161
00:10:26,108 --> 00:10:28,675
Here? At the State Department?

162
00:10:28,711 --> 00:10:31,578
Anywhere along the evidence chain.

163
00:10:31,613 --> 00:10:33,347
Will do, ma'am.

164
00:10:49,455 --> 00:10:50,621
Agent Kishida.

165
00:10:50,624 --> 00:10:52,324
I wasn't expecting a call at this hour.

166
00:10:52,327 --> 00:10:55,235
I just wanted to follow up
on our earlier conversation.

167
00:10:55,270 --> 00:10:56,770
The situation in the Middle East?

168
00:10:56,805 --> 00:10:59,439
Situation's developing.

169
00:11:00,709 --> 00:11:01,975
We need to meet soon.

170
00:11:02,010 --> 00:11:03,977
Fair enough.

171
00:11:04,012 --> 00:11:06,146
The moment we're back, we'll call you.

172
00:11:10,590 --> 00:11:12,056
You worked at NSA?

173
00:11:13,387 --> 00:11:17,055
Team Eye in the Sky for ten years.

174
00:11:17,072 --> 00:11:19,236
Watched the most heinous
crap you can imagine

175
00:11:19,239 --> 00:11:21,239
by satellite.

176
00:11:21,242 --> 00:11:22,896
Stonings, rapes.

177
00:11:24,236 --> 00:11:26,900
Just had to sit back and watch
it like a horror film, helpless,

178
00:11:26,902 --> 00:11:29,069
until Poseidon tapped my shoulder,

179
00:11:29,104 --> 00:11:31,738
gave me a chance to
do something about it.

180
00:11:33,575 --> 00:11:35,976
Emily, good to see you again.

181
00:11:36,011 --> 00:11:37,210
Likewise.

182
00:11:37,246 --> 00:11:39,546
You got my message? Kaniel Outis?

183
00:11:39,581 --> 00:11:41,879
You gonna help us locate him?

184
00:11:41,902 --> 00:11:44,384
Look, protocol says no.

185
00:11:44,420 --> 00:11:47,387
We stay clear of CIA,
any offensive action.

186
00:11:47,423 --> 00:11:49,055
We're surveillance only.

187
00:11:49,091 --> 00:11:50,524
We just want to put eyes on him.

188
00:11:53,470 --> 00:11:55,688
I think I can get you in as observers

189
00:11:55,691 --> 00:11:57,595
under interagency auspices.

190
00:11:58,834 --> 00:12:00,600
I knew I could count on you.

191
00:12:00,636 --> 00:12:02,068
But you owe me.

192
00:12:02,104 --> 00:12:04,905
That B&B we went up to in Connecticut,

193
00:12:04,940 --> 00:12:06,573
I want that weekend again.

194
00:12:09,378 --> 00:12:11,611
That exact weekend.

195
00:12:22,124 --> 00:12:23,557
What you got back here, anyway?

196
00:12:23,592 --> 00:12:25,392
What is this, guns, drugs?

197
00:12:26,829 --> 00:12:28,195
Fireworks?

198
00:12:28,230 --> 00:12:30,330
You don't understand the Phaeacians.

199
00:12:30,365 --> 00:12:32,766
They are beautiful. Generous.

200
00:12:32,801 --> 00:12:35,502
They just want to smile.

201
00:12:35,537 --> 00:12:36,770
Unlike you.

202
00:12:36,805 --> 00:12:38,505
Oh, is that right?

203
00:12:38,540 --> 00:12:40,774
Ah, holding grudges.

204
00:12:40,809 --> 00:12:42,018
It's very bad for the heart...

205
00:12:42,021 --> 00:12:43,937
You know what else
is bad for your heart?

206
00:12:43,979 --> 00:12:46,847
If I shove a Roman candle
through the middle of it.

207
00:12:56,663 --> 00:12:58,559
Ja, please.

208
00:12:58,595 --> 00:12:59,927
Don't check out on us.

209
00:13:02,231 --> 00:13:04,231
Still trying to figure
out why you got me out.

210
00:13:04,266 --> 00:13:08,201
I need that great big mind
of yours clean and clear.

211
00:13:11,343 --> 00:13:13,310
It's the number from
the airport last night.

212
00:13:15,810 --> 00:13:17,543
C-Note, what's up?

213
00:13:17,571 --> 00:13:18,970
Lincoln, it's Sheba.

214
00:13:19,006 --> 00:13:20,305
I got Benjamin's phone.

215
00:13:20,308 --> 00:13:22,048
Oh, hi.

216
00:13:22,084 --> 00:13:24,050
Did you find Omar?

217
00:13:24,086 --> 00:13:25,819
Yeah, we found him.

218
00:13:25,854 --> 00:13:27,120
We're traveling.

219
00:13:27,155 --> 00:13:28,855
You okay?

220
00:13:28,891 --> 00:13:31,090
Yes. We're in Jordan.

221
00:13:31,126 --> 00:13:34,761
Leaving for the U.S. tonight.

222
00:13:34,796 --> 00:13:36,329
How's C-Note?

223
00:13:36,365 --> 00:13:38,431
He's fine.

224
00:13:38,467 --> 00:13:41,134
We all are.

225
00:13:41,169 --> 00:13:43,803
Everyone.

226
00:13:43,839 --> 00:13:45,405
We're going to make it.

227
00:13:45,440 --> 00:13:47,741
It's because of you.

228
00:13:47,776 --> 00:13:49,642
Because of my money.

229
00:13:49,678 --> 00:13:52,011
It's because of you.

230
00:13:52,047 --> 00:13:53,413
Come on.

231
00:13:53,448 --> 00:13:55,849
There is nobility in you, Lincoln.

232
00:13:55,884 --> 00:13:57,450
Hey, uh...

233
00:13:58,752 --> 00:14:01,321
when I get back, I'll,
I'll buy you a drink.

234
00:14:01,356 --> 00:14:03,723
I don't drink.

235
00:14:05,394 --> 00:14:06,626
But I'll buy you a drink.

236
00:14:06,662 --> 00:14:08,028
How about that?

237
00:14:09,164 --> 00:14:10,897
Sounds good.

238
00:14:14,603 --> 00:14:16,102
We got a hit,

239
00:14:16,138 --> 00:14:17,737
Franklin's cell phone lit up in Jordan.

240
00:14:17,773 --> 00:14:20,182
The one he bought with a credit
card in Yemen a few days ago.

241
00:14:20,184 --> 00:14:22,354
Making an outbound call
to an unknown number.

242
00:14:22,357 --> 00:14:24,731
Currently right outside Sana'a, Yemen.

243
00:14:24,734 --> 00:14:26,701
Rerouting a drone to that target now.

244
00:14:26,747 --> 00:14:29,115
We just found our man, didn't we?

245
00:14:36,608 --> 00:14:38,710
There. Two vehicles heading west.

246
00:14:38,713 --> 00:14:39,690
Drones in position.

247
00:14:39,693 --> 00:14:41,093
Let's take a peek.

248
00:14:45,927 --> 00:14:47,793
They're stopping.

249
00:14:47,829 --> 00:14:50,229
Pull up all known data on that location.

250
00:14:54,093 --> 00:14:55,291
Why did we stop?

251
00:14:55,331 --> 00:14:57,937
Phaeacia is 300 miles that way.

252
00:14:59,474 --> 00:15:01,974
We need to fill our
gas tanks up to the top.

253
00:15:02,879 --> 00:15:06,016
- As-salamu.'alaykum.
- Alaykumu s-salaam.

254
00:15:06,048 --> 00:15:07,446
Michael, where you going?

255
00:15:07,448 --> 00:15:08,580
Been under Poseidon's thumb

256
00:15:08,616 --> 00:15:10,115
for the last seven years.

257
00:15:10,151 --> 00:15:14,019
It's about time I got out from under it.

258
00:15:14,055 --> 00:15:15,287
Internet?

259
00:15:15,290 --> 00:15:16,788
_

260
00:15:16,791 --> 00:15:18,190
Shukraan.

261
00:15:24,880 --> 00:15:27,346
They have no clue
we're watching, do they?

262
00:15:27,349 --> 00:15:28,801
Not at this height.

263
00:15:40,493 --> 00:15:41,772
_

264
00:15:45,887 --> 00:15:47,552
Who is this?

265
00:15:47,588 --> 00:15:49,764
A friend from far away.

266
00:15:49,767 --> 00:15:52,991
Your government has always
considered us an enemy.

267
00:15:53,027 --> 00:15:54,292
Officially.

268
00:15:54,328 --> 00:15:59,398
But some of us have a
more enlightened view.

269
00:15:59,434 --> 00:16:02,134
Abu Ramal was a great visionary.

270
00:16:02,170 --> 00:16:04,836
You have our sincerest condolences.

271
00:16:04,872 --> 00:16:06,071
What do you want?

272
00:16:06,107 --> 00:16:07,272
The same thing you do,

273
00:16:07,308 --> 00:16:09,378
to eliminate the men who killed him.

274
00:16:09,381 --> 00:16:11,848
And as a sign of good faith...

275
00:16:14,782 --> 00:16:17,249
we'll tell you exactly where they are.

276
00:16:27,270 --> 00:16:28,769
Hey, can you see me?

277
00:16:28,772 --> 00:16:30,138
Not yet.

278
00:16:30,141 --> 00:16:31,701
Blasted computer camera thing.

279
00:16:31,702 --> 00:16:33,067
Who makes these things?

280
00:16:33,103 --> 00:16:34,869
All right, I see you.

281
00:16:34,905 --> 00:16:37,432
Come on, hurry. Get this off of me.

282
00:16:37,435 --> 00:16:39,256
Hold your hand still.

283
00:16:39,310 --> 00:16:40,642
Just do it already.

284
00:16:41,812 --> 00:16:43,278
Do you want to stay like this?

285
00:16:43,314 --> 00:16:45,948
You're lucky we cut you loose.

286
00:16:51,965 --> 00:16:54,447
The men who killed Abu Ramal,

287
00:16:54,450 --> 00:16:56,624
Leaving Sana'a, heading
west on Highway 80.

288
00:16:56,660 --> 00:16:58,240
- Okay.
- Highway 80.

289
00:16:58,243 --> 00:16:59,642
We're leaving now.

290
00:17:04,168 --> 00:17:05,801
- I'm coming, too.
- No.

291
00:17:07,738 --> 00:17:10,205
This is not your fight anymore.

292
00:17:10,841 --> 00:17:12,207
Understand?

293
00:17:28,504 --> 00:17:30,227
_

294
00:17:31,532 --> 00:17:32,800
_

295
00:17:47,044 --> 00:17:49,611
You know it's been four years
since I've had air conditioning?

296
00:17:49,647 --> 00:17:51,303
I'm done with the heat.

297
00:17:51,335 --> 00:17:53,772
Kind of like it out here.

298
00:17:56,787 --> 00:17:58,019
No walls.

299
00:17:58,055 --> 00:18:00,319
No walls, okay? Ain't about walls.

300
00:18:01,859 --> 00:18:03,291
My opinion, you know what you need

301
00:18:03,327 --> 00:18:04,859
more than anything else in the world?

302
00:18:04,895 --> 00:18:06,494
Got to laugh more.

303
00:18:06,530 --> 00:18:08,329
If he wants to laugh,

304
00:18:08,365 --> 00:18:09,897
Phaeacia 's the place.

305
00:18:09,933 --> 00:18:11,833
I always wanted to bring Sheba;

306
00:18:11,869 --> 00:18:13,367
for her to see the people.

307
00:18:13,390 --> 00:18:15,403
No technology, no politics,

308
00:18:15,439 --> 00:18:16,671
no modern nonsense.

309
00:18:16,707 --> 00:18:18,439
They know how to enjoy life.

310
00:18:18,475 --> 00:18:19,941
No technology?

311
00:18:19,977 --> 00:18:21,606
Freddie Mercury here couldn't hack it.

312
00:18:21,609 --> 00:18:22,510
Freddie Mercury?

313
00:18:22,546 --> 00:18:24,045
I could hack it.

314
00:18:24,081 --> 00:18:26,114
I was alive before cell phones.

315
00:18:26,150 --> 00:18:27,716
You're more addicted to
that screen than you are

316
00:18:27,718 --> 00:18:29,551
to them pills, and that
is saying something.

317
00:18:36,126 --> 00:18:37,258
Be ready.

318
00:18:37,294 --> 00:18:40,261
Ah, my friends. We got problems!

319
00:18:40,297 --> 00:18:42,230
Michael, we got to go!

320
00:18:42,266 --> 00:18:43,965
Michael? Let's go!

321
00:18:44,001 --> 00:18:45,233
I got to go.

322
00:18:45,269 --> 00:18:46,734
Hold on, let me try something else.

323
00:18:46,770 --> 00:18:47,969
Can you see me now?

324
00:18:48,005 --> 00:18:49,837
No. Take a screen capture.

325
00:18:49,873 --> 00:18:51,072
What of?

326
00:18:51,108 --> 00:18:53,608
A screen capture. Take it.

327
00:18:55,012 --> 00:18:57,111
ISIL militants coming from the east.

328
00:18:57,147 --> 00:18:59,047
This should get interesting.

329
00:19:04,021 --> 00:19:06,212
Don't think one bullet is
going to get us out of this.

330
00:19:06,215 --> 00:19:08,823
One bullet? Who the hell
carries a gun with one bullet?

331
00:19:08,859 --> 00:19:11,259
The man who would kill himself
before being captured by ISIL.

332
00:19:25,676 --> 00:19:27,342
Get closer. Zoom in.

333
00:19:27,378 --> 00:19:29,071
Hold on.

334
00:19:29,074 --> 00:19:31,913
These militants, how'd they find them?

335
00:19:31,949 --> 00:19:33,882
Damnit, what are you
waiting for? Shoot back!

336
00:19:33,884 --> 00:19:35,216
We only got one bullet.

337
00:19:35,252 --> 00:19:36,852
- One bullet?
- Exactly.

338
00:19:42,283 --> 00:19:44,049
We're seriously screwed here.

339
00:19:44,052 --> 00:19:46,661
Unless I can make this one bullet count.

340
00:19:46,697 --> 00:19:48,029
What?

341
00:20:04,815 --> 00:20:07,215
You sure as hell made it count, kid.

342
00:20:07,251 --> 00:20:09,350
Hell yeah, you did.

343
00:20:12,489 --> 00:20:14,389
Oh, my God.

344
00:20:15,692 --> 00:20:17,658
Michael.

345
00:20:17,694 --> 00:20:19,227
He's in a bad way, Linc.

346
00:20:26,234 --> 00:20:28,784
More coming, we got to
get the hell out of here!

347
00:21:37,881 --> 00:21:39,321
What are they stopping for?

348
00:21:39,324 --> 00:21:40,523
Don't know.

349
00:21:48,585 --> 00:21:49,984
We can't go any further.

350
00:21:50,020 --> 00:21:51,085
We can go a lot further.

351
00:21:51,121 --> 00:21:52,386
We've got to get to Phaeacia.

352
00:21:52,422 --> 00:21:53,928
There's no roads, Whip.

353
00:21:53,931 --> 00:21:55,923
The roads are in Omar's
head along with the map.

354
00:21:55,959 --> 00:21:58,226
That's what I'm trying to tell you.

355
00:21:58,262 --> 00:22:00,428
Our map is dead.

356
00:22:13,200 --> 00:22:14,666
We got to head back.

357
00:22:14,701 --> 00:22:16,902
To what?

358
00:22:16,937 --> 00:22:18,837
He's right.

359
00:22:18,872 --> 00:22:20,338
We'll die out there without a map.

360
00:22:20,374 --> 00:22:22,073
We don't know that.

361
00:22:22,109 --> 00:22:24,042
We 99% know that.

362
00:22:28,382 --> 00:22:29,881
Guess we're not out of the woods yet!

363
00:22:29,917 --> 00:22:31,623
We got to lose this guy, whoever he is!

364
00:22:31,626 --> 00:22:33,385
- Let's go!
- Then move it, damn it.

365
00:22:51,738 --> 00:22:54,172
All targets now bearing 2:15.

366
00:22:54,208 --> 00:22:55,607
Stay with them.

367
00:22:55,642 --> 00:22:57,809
No. Pull the drone.

368
00:22:57,844 --> 00:22:59,650
Time for our visitors to leave.

369
00:22:59,653 --> 00:23:01,279
What are you talking about?

370
00:23:01,315 --> 00:23:02,547
We find Kaniel Outis in Yemen,

371
00:23:02,583 --> 00:23:04,416
and then rebels show up to take him out?

372
00:23:04,451 --> 00:23:06,291
Was I supposed to think
that was a coincidence?

373
00:23:06,320 --> 00:23:08,253
This isn't surveillance, is it?

374
00:23:08,288 --> 00:23:09,955
This is assassination.

375
00:23:09,990 --> 00:23:12,346
You're using me for some sort
of black work, aren't you?

376
00:23:12,349 --> 00:23:15,360
This is way over your head, Tricia.

377
00:23:15,395 --> 00:23:17,262
Stop asking questions.

378
00:23:17,297 --> 00:23:21,284
If you don't get out of my
sight, I will blow the whistle.

379
00:23:21,323 --> 00:23:23,112
Right now.

380
00:23:27,774 --> 00:23:30,867
Would've been a hell of
a weekend in Connecticut.

381
00:23:38,452 --> 00:23:40,151
It's playing with fire,

382
00:23:40,187 --> 00:23:42,120
co-opting other agencies like that.

383
00:23:42,155 --> 00:23:43,755
You think she'll talk?

384
00:23:43,790 --> 00:23:47,058
Run it up the flag pole?

385
00:23:47,094 --> 00:23:49,227
You got designs on killing her?

386
00:23:49,263 --> 00:23:50,802
I'll kill you.

387
00:23:53,359 --> 00:23:55,025
Relax, will you?

388
00:23:57,638 --> 00:24:00,672
I'm getting pretty
tired of chasing Outis.

389
00:24:00,707 --> 00:24:03,109
- Always being behind him.
- Me, too.

390
00:24:03,112 --> 00:24:05,543
That's why I keep thinking
about all that time that he spent

391
00:24:05,545 --> 00:24:08,446
in that gas station in Yemen.

392
00:24:08,482 --> 00:24:10,282
ISIL on his tail,

393
00:24:10,317 --> 00:24:12,596
and he just hangs in there?

394
00:24:12,627 --> 00:24:14,736
What was he doing in there?

395
00:24:28,702 --> 00:24:31,503
The sun is directly overhead.

396
00:24:31,538 --> 00:24:33,968
I can't tell which way is east, west...

397
00:24:33,971 --> 00:24:36,205
We got to stop.

398
00:24:42,101 --> 00:24:43,767
Hey, Ja.

399
00:24:43,770 --> 00:24:45,257
You got a compass on that phone?

400
00:24:45,260 --> 00:24:46,885
No signal.

401
00:24:46,920 --> 00:24:48,987
We're flying blind.

402
00:24:49,022 --> 00:24:51,289
Completely blind.

403
00:24:55,529 --> 00:24:57,362
But he's not.

404
00:24:57,397 --> 00:25:00,865
We're leaving him a beautiful
set of tire tracks to follow.

405
00:25:00,901 --> 00:25:02,600
Who the hell is this guy?

406
00:25:06,306 --> 00:25:08,373
It's the guy who killed Sid.

407
00:25:08,408 --> 00:25:11,176
Son of a bitch is like
a dog with a bone, huh?

408
00:25:11,211 --> 00:25:13,378
You kill someone's spiritual leader,

409
00:25:13,413 --> 00:25:16,047
they'll follow you to the
ends of the Earth, apparently.

410
00:25:16,083 --> 00:25:18,216
Why is he stopping?

411
00:25:19,553 --> 00:25:20,852
He's refueling.

412
00:25:20,887 --> 00:25:22,287
Now?

413
00:25:22,322 --> 00:25:24,956
He knows he's got more gas than we do.

414
00:25:24,991 --> 00:25:27,592
All he has to do is follow our tracks.

415
00:25:27,627 --> 00:25:29,761
Then wait until we run out.

416
00:25:29,787 --> 00:25:31,583
There are four of us.

417
00:25:31,595 --> 00:25:33,104
Let's just swarm him, take him out.

418
00:25:33,107 --> 00:25:34,272
Not out here.

419
00:25:34,275 --> 00:25:36,096
Not with an AK-47.

420
00:25:36,099 --> 00:25:37,435
We wouldn't get within
a hundred feet of him

421
00:25:37,437 --> 00:25:38,803
without taking a bullet.

422
00:25:38,839 --> 00:25:40,849
Then we got to outthink him.

423
00:25:43,810 --> 00:25:46,144
What you gonna do with that, flog him?

424
00:25:46,179 --> 00:25:48,437
Gonna transfer gas from
that tank to this one.

425
00:25:48,440 --> 00:25:50,240
Almost all of it.

426
00:25:50,243 --> 00:25:51,710
It's not gonna help.

427
00:25:51,713 --> 00:25:55,182
It's gonna help this
one get to Phaeacia.

428
00:25:55,185 --> 00:25:56,921
We pile into one vehicle?

429
00:25:56,957 --> 00:25:58,356
He still has more gas than us.

430
00:25:58,392 --> 00:26:00,125
He can still follow our tire tracks.

431
00:26:00,160 --> 00:26:03,094
That's why we leave a little
bit of gas in that one.

432
00:26:03,130 --> 00:26:04,996
And make two sets of tracks.

433
00:26:05,031 --> 00:26:07,984
He's gonna have to choose.

434
00:26:15,041 --> 00:26:17,776
I got four rocks in my hand.

435
00:26:17,811 --> 00:26:19,344
Three red, one white.

436
00:26:19,379 --> 00:26:22,747
Get the red rock, get in
the Jeep, go to Phaeacia.

437
00:26:22,783 --> 00:26:24,916
Get the white rock,

438
00:26:24,951 --> 00:26:27,552
deal with our friend.

439
00:26:35,223 --> 00:26:36,689
Stick out your hand.

440
00:26:39,900 --> 00:26:41,900
Red.

441
00:26:45,065 --> 00:26:46,698
Whip.

442
00:26:46,729 --> 00:26:48,006
Come on.

443
00:26:50,844 --> 00:26:52,677
Red.

444
00:26:57,350 --> 00:26:58,450
Linc.

445
00:27:01,755 --> 00:27:03,822
No.

446
00:27:03,857 --> 00:27:06,124
You knew the rules, Linc.

447
00:27:07,696 --> 00:27:10,096
He's picking up again.

448
00:27:10,099 --> 00:27:12,297
I'm not leaving you out here to die.

449
00:27:12,332 --> 00:27:13,998
I have no intention of dying.

450
00:27:14,034 --> 00:27:15,864
Anyway, you've got the harder job.

451
00:27:15,867 --> 00:27:18,503
You've got to find Phaeacia
out there somewhere.

452
00:27:18,538 --> 00:27:22,707
Leave tracks so I know how to find you.

453
00:27:43,864 --> 00:27:46,498
Just one.

454
00:27:49,503 --> 00:27:52,971
You want to play, you son of a bitch?

455
00:28:08,488 --> 00:28:11,356
Now how the hell am I
gonna get out of this?

456
00:28:33,818 --> 00:28:36,122
We're driving blind.

457
00:28:36,161 --> 00:28:38,988
It's the same damn
thing everywhere we look.

458
00:28:39,023 --> 00:28:41,257
There's something to be said for that.

459
00:28:41,292 --> 00:28:42,891
Makes you use your senses.

460
00:28:42,894 --> 00:28:44,126
Will you stop talking crap

461
00:28:44,129 --> 00:28:45,610
and talk elephant in the room, please?

462
00:28:45,612 --> 00:28:47,029
We just left Michael back there.

463
00:28:47,064 --> 00:28:48,264
It's completely wrong.

464
00:28:48,299 --> 00:28:51,367
I'm the last guy you
want to say that to.

465
00:28:51,402 --> 00:28:52,701
Well, why are we doing it, then?

466
00:28:52,737 --> 00:28:53,857
Because he said, that's why.

467
00:28:55,039 --> 00:28:57,139
One thing you don't understand.

468
00:28:57,174 --> 00:28:58,641
When Michael takes on the world,

469
00:28:58,676 --> 00:29:01,210
the world always loses.

470
00:29:42,653 --> 00:29:44,653
We've been looking the whole time.

471
00:29:44,689 --> 00:29:45,888
That's the problem.

472
00:29:45,923 --> 00:29:46,989
What?

473
00:29:47,024 --> 00:29:49,091
Stop the engine.

474
00:30:00,338 --> 00:30:01,971
You hear that?

475
00:30:02,873 --> 00:30:04,139
Birds?

476
00:30:04,175 --> 00:30:06,508
Not just birds. Gulls.

477
00:30:06,544 --> 00:30:10,312
As far as I know, gulls got
no interest in the desert.

478
00:30:10,348 --> 00:30:12,039
They only got interest in the sea.

479
00:30:12,042 --> 00:30:13,475
It means we're close.

480
00:30:13,478 --> 00:30:15,044
All you got to do is follow them.

481
00:30:16,249 --> 00:30:18,749
Maybe we got GPS after all.

482
00:31:53,317 --> 00:31:54,616
Is this Phaeacia?

483
00:31:54,652 --> 00:31:57,186
Phaeacia! Phaeacia!

484
00:32:00,153 --> 00:32:04,126
Omar! Omar!

485
00:32:04,161 --> 00:32:07,362
Omar, Omar.

486
00:32:10,601 --> 00:32:12,734
Hello.

487
00:32:19,376 --> 00:32:22,411
You bring Omar car, but not Omar?

488
00:32:22,446 --> 00:32:25,781
Omar had to go somewhere safe.

489
00:32:25,816 --> 00:32:28,117
Because of the war?

490
00:32:28,152 --> 00:32:31,553
Yeah, the war. That's right.

491
00:32:32,957 --> 00:32:35,891
He told us to bring this stuff for you.

492
00:32:37,507 --> 00:32:40,763
Also said you could
arrange a boat for us.

493
00:34:52,263 --> 00:34:56,231
Back in the city...

494
00:34:56,267 --> 00:34:58,734
I told you you would die.

495
00:35:01,859 --> 00:35:05,627
We will both die out here, American!

496
00:35:35,278 --> 00:35:37,973
Turns out that gas
station outside Sana'a

497
00:35:38,020 --> 00:35:40,592
had a computer with Internet access.

498
00:35:40,628 --> 00:35:43,228
He sent this image from Yemen. Why?

499
00:35:43,264 --> 00:35:45,464
We're gonna find out as soon as we talk

500
00:35:45,499 --> 00:35:46,832
to the guy he sent it to.

501
00:35:48,569 --> 00:35:52,371
Blue Hawaii in Portland, Maine.

502
00:35:52,406 --> 00:35:53,672
Think we got a snowbird?

503
00:35:53,707 --> 00:35:56,675
I don't think that's quite it.

504
00:36:17,398 --> 00:36:19,711
Welcome to Graceland.

505
00:36:19,766 --> 00:36:22,367
Don't just stand there
and let the AC out.

506
00:36:25,283 --> 00:36:27,183
Come on in.

507
00:36:30,944 --> 00:36:34,212
What can I do for you fine folks?

508
00:36:45,287 --> 00:36:47,620
Linc, where are your tracks?

509
00:37:06,708 --> 00:37:08,708
Tracks, tracks.

510
00:37:14,165 --> 00:37:16,265
No, no, no, no!

511
00:37:24,270 --> 00:37:27,805
No, no. No.

512
00:37:27,841 --> 00:37:30,994
Come on. Come on!

513
00:37:59,372 --> 00:38:01,973
Come on, Mike, come on.

514
00:38:02,008 --> 00:38:04,442
Where are the tracks?

515
00:38:04,477 --> 00:38:07,445
Where are the tracks?

516
00:38:10,416 --> 00:38:12,183
This is for you. Look.

517
00:38:15,121 --> 00:38:17,855
W-Wait, go easy, go easy.
Start with the small stuff.

518
00:38:17,891 --> 00:38:21,058
Flowers, snakes, we'll move
onto the artillery later.

519
00:38:26,399 --> 00:38:27,498
Fireworks okay?

520
00:38:27,534 --> 00:38:28,633
Yes, yes, of course.

521
00:38:28,668 --> 00:38:30,735
- It's okay to use?
- Thank you.

522
00:38:32,238 --> 00:38:34,305
Omar was right.

523
00:38:34,340 --> 00:38:37,108
This place.

524
00:38:37,143 --> 00:38:40,945
It's like the rest of
the world doesn't exist.

525
00:38:40,980 --> 00:38:43,763
I'll go check on Linc.

526
00:38:46,252 --> 00:38:49,320
Hanging in there?

527
00:38:49,355 --> 00:38:53,624
You're right. I shouldn't
have abandoned him.

528
00:38:53,660 --> 00:38:55,824
If he doesn't find those
tire tracks by nightfall,

529
00:38:55,827 --> 00:38:57,426
he never will.

530
00:38:59,673 --> 00:39:01,299
Where are you going?

531
00:39:01,334 --> 00:39:02,600
Going out to find him.

532
00:39:02,603 --> 00:39:04,267
You can't go out there at night.

533
00:39:04,270 --> 00:39:06,036
You'll never find him.

534
00:39:06,039 --> 00:39:08,873
Doing nothing's not an option.

535
00:39:08,908 --> 00:39:12,209
I didn't say do nothing.

536
00:39:51,084 --> 00:39:52,550
You got to have faith.

537
00:39:57,724 --> 00:39:58,789
Sarah.

538
00:40:03,363 --> 00:40:04,929
Sarah.

539
00:40:50,510 --> 00:40:51,909
Michael!

540
00:40:53,212 --> 00:40:55,713
Michael!

541
00:40:59,136 --> 00:41:02,453
Michael!

542
00:41:25,645 --> 00:41:28,713
That's it.

543
00:41:44,630 --> 00:41:45,730
Michael.

544
00:41:45,765 --> 00:41:47,298
Thank God, you made it.

545
00:41:47,333 --> 00:41:48,948
He poisoned me.

546
00:41:48,951 --> 00:41:50,519
- What?!
- Antifreeze.

547
00:41:53,639 --> 00:41:55,272
Need a doctor.

548
00:41:55,308 --> 00:41:56,708
Get the doctor now.

549
00:41:56,711 --> 00:41:58,642
The doctor, the only
doctor is in Sana'a.

550
00:41:58,678 --> 00:42:00,211
We can't go back to Sana'a.

551
00:42:00,246 --> 00:42:01,508
We just came from there.

552
00:42:01,511 --> 00:42:03,814
It's 300 miles across
the friggin' desert.

553
00:42:03,850 --> 00:42:06,450
We got to do something. He's dying.

554
00:42:06,486 --> 00:42:08,816
Michael, Michael.

