1
00:00:02,236 --> 00:00:04,070
Previously on Prison Break...

2
00:00:04,073 --> 00:00:05,573
The strikes are getting closer.

3
00:00:05,575 --> 00:00:07,617
We got a day, maybe two, tops,

4
00:00:07,620 --> 00:00:10,359
- to get out of this hole.
- Desperate times, desperate measures.

5
00:00:10,362 --> 00:00:13,531
- Michael's reaching out to us.
- We got to get help. A woman named Sheba.

6
00:00:13,534 --> 00:00:15,768
Your brother speaks in riddles, does he?

7
00:00:15,771 --> 00:00:17,323
ISIL. We're gonna get stopped.

8
00:00:17,326 --> 00:00:19,581
Why don't we forget
each other ever existed.

9
00:00:19,584 --> 00:00:22,385
Beauty's not so easily forgotten.

10
00:00:22,388 --> 00:00:24,010
Friends in high places, Bagwell.

11
00:00:24,013 --> 00:00:27,284
I can equip you with a
fully articulate prosthetic.

12
00:00:27,287 --> 00:00:28,867
- Who's behind this?
- Nobody.

13
00:00:28,870 --> 00:00:31,547
- This is Kaniel Outis.
- Okay, but you and I both know

14
00:00:31,550 --> 00:00:33,934
- who Michael Scofield was.
- We've awoken something,

15
00:00:33,936 --> 00:00:36,095
something people are trying
to hide about Michael.

16
00:00:36,098 --> 00:00:37,664
Jacob?

17
00:00:37,667 --> 00:00:39,348
That's game theory. You meet people.

18
00:00:39,351 --> 00:00:40,742
You bring them into your life

19
00:00:40,745 --> 00:00:41,989
until the moment

20
00:00:42,000 --> 00:00:43,577
you need to manipulate the relationship

21
00:00:43,579 --> 00:00:44,630
to your advantage.

22
00:00:44,633 --> 00:00:46,128
You agreed to help him... how?

23
00:00:46,131 --> 00:00:47,630
If I could arrange a blackout.

24
00:00:47,633 --> 00:00:49,432
He knew someone who could get him out.

25
00:00:49,435 --> 00:00:51,285
Someone found my father.

26
00:00:51,288 --> 00:00:52,607
It means the escape is on.

27
00:00:52,610 --> 00:00:54,202
ISIL forces are also bent

28
00:00:54,205 --> 00:00:56,189
on freeing their leader Abu Ramal,

29
00:00:56,192 --> 00:00:58,726
known for his extreme
views and practices.

30
00:01:00,459 --> 00:01:02,101
_

31
00:01:02,102 --> 00:01:03,975
_

32
00:01:10,902 --> 00:01:14,281
_

33
00:01:52,387 --> 00:01:55,888
_

34
00:02:48,665 --> 00:02:50,961
He says Bubble Gum Man sent him.

35
00:02:52,138 --> 00:02:53,888
Someone in the prison he hasn't met,

36
00:02:53,891 --> 00:02:57,478
but gives him gum in
exchange for errands.

37
00:02:57,513 --> 00:03:00,014
He says he's frightened.

38
00:03:00,049 --> 00:03:01,816
Tell him it's all right.

39
00:03:01,851 --> 00:03:04,718
Ask him if he does Tic Tacs.

40
00:03:04,752 --> 00:03:06,185
He can have the whole lot

41
00:03:06,222 --> 00:03:08,823
if he keeps the messages coming.

42
00:03:08,858 --> 00:03:11,392
Thank you, Tic Tac Man.

43
00:03:14,764 --> 00:03:18,365
Tic Tac, Tic Tac, Tic Tacs.

44
00:03:18,401 --> 00:03:20,034
It's a passage from the Suras.

45
00:03:20,069 --> 00:03:21,467
"And Yusef said to the prisoner:

46
00:03:21,470 --> 00:03:24,004
'Remember me in the
presence of your lord.'

47
00:03:24,040 --> 00:03:25,673
"But Satan made him forget,

48
00:03:25,708 --> 00:03:26,975
and Yusef stayed in prison

49
00:03:26,978 --> 00:03:29,410
for several years."

50
00:03:29,445 --> 00:03:31,078
The calligraphy is unusual,

51
00:03:31,113 --> 00:03:34,058
the spacing, the way it's shaped,

52
00:03:34,061 --> 00:03:36,995
like, like spokes on a wheel.

53
00:03:37,994 --> 00:03:39,360
Like the center of Sana'a.

54
00:03:43,516 --> 00:03:45,349
You think his brother sent us a map?

55
00:03:45,352 --> 00:03:46,760
There's a red dot

56
00:03:46,796 --> 00:03:49,141
dotting the "I",

57
00:03:49,164 --> 00:03:51,091
and whatever this is here.

58
00:03:51,779 --> 00:03:53,824
He's trying to give us a location.

59
00:03:53,827 --> 00:03:55,026
A location for what?

60
00:03:55,029 --> 00:03:56,189
The only thing I can think of

61
00:03:56,205 --> 00:03:57,605
is where we're supposed to meet him

62
00:03:57,607 --> 00:03:59,634
when the escape goes down tonight.

63
00:04:03,041 --> 00:04:04,882
Your brother is your business now.

64
00:04:04,885 --> 00:04:07,043
I have to get my family
on a flight tonight

65
00:04:07,078 --> 00:04:08,519
- before the airport shuts down.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.

66
00:04:08,521 --> 00:04:09,908
Hold up.

67
00:04:09,911 --> 00:04:11,541
We need tickets, too, three of them.

68
00:04:11,544 --> 00:04:13,344
One for me, one for Michael, one for C.

69
00:04:13,347 --> 00:04:15,850
If I'm getting anybody any
tickets it's these kids,

70
00:04:15,853 --> 00:04:17,286
not your mercenary brother.

71
00:04:17,322 --> 00:04:19,488
And how are you going to
do that without any money?

72
00:04:22,513 --> 00:04:24,107
You're holding these kids' freedom

73
00:04:24,109 --> 00:04:25,509
over my head, is that it?

74
00:04:25,544 --> 00:04:28,845
Sheba, you get me those plane tickets,

75
00:04:28,881 --> 00:04:30,459
and I'll pay for every
single one of these kids

76
00:04:30,461 --> 00:04:32,845
to get out of this country.

77
00:04:32,886 --> 00:04:36,086
Something tells me that's
what you want to do anyhow.

78
00:04:36,121 --> 00:04:37,287
Careful.

79
00:04:37,322 --> 00:04:39,964
You're accusing me of having a heart.

80
00:04:55,841 --> 00:04:57,407
Out of my way. Get out of my way.

81
00:04:57,443 --> 00:04:59,376
Hmm? Huh? What, you want to go?

82
00:04:59,411 --> 00:05:01,578
Hey.

83
00:05:01,613 --> 00:05:03,116
Keep it together.

84
00:05:03,119 --> 00:05:05,395
You got to have it together
to keep it together.

85
00:05:08,821 --> 00:05:11,488
One of those hits us now,

86
00:05:11,523 --> 00:05:13,690
- after all this time, I swear to God...
- Nine hours.

87
00:05:13,725 --> 00:05:16,226
Nine hours till we get
out, you understand?

88
00:05:16,261 --> 00:05:17,465
It's 1:00 a.m.

89
00:05:17,468 --> 00:05:19,496
We get through today
and we're on the bricks.

90
00:05:19,498 --> 00:05:20,931
And then what?

91
00:05:20,934 --> 00:05:22,621
It was four years ago.

92
00:05:22,624 --> 00:05:24,790
All of our plans, the
passports, the shop,

93
00:05:24,793 --> 00:05:27,894
everything is probably
under rubble by now.

94
00:05:28,788 --> 00:05:30,622
I got someone on it.

95
00:05:31,834 --> 00:05:33,510
What, the kid you throw planes to?

96
00:05:36,215 --> 00:05:37,378
No.

97
00:05:37,381 --> 00:05:39,583
I'm talking about the only
person I trust in the world

98
00:05:39,585 --> 00:05:42,586
as much as I trust you.

99
00:05:43,724 --> 00:05:46,591
So, this is it, the spot on the map.

100
00:05:46,594 --> 00:05:48,391
The owner says he sold the auto shop

101
00:05:48,393 --> 00:05:49,860
to an American four years ago

102
00:05:49,895 --> 00:05:52,462
and hasn't seen him since.

103
00:06:06,059 --> 00:06:09,894
You know that American
was Michael, right?

104
00:06:09,929 --> 00:06:12,897
Question is what was
he using this place for.

105
00:06:14,567 --> 00:06:16,167
Planning his escape.

106
00:06:20,621 --> 00:06:22,624
It looks like his original exfil point

107
00:06:22,627 --> 00:06:24,226
was at the northern border.

108
00:06:24,934 --> 00:06:26,368
Won't be doing that now.

109
00:06:26,371 --> 00:06:28,779
It's ISIL territory.

110
00:06:31,718 --> 00:06:34,252
Mock-ups, passport photos,

111
00:06:34,287 --> 00:06:36,587
disguises.

112
00:06:36,623 --> 00:06:40,258
But it looks like he just wasn't
planning on getting himself out.

113
00:06:40,293 --> 00:06:42,460
He was getting Abu Ramal out.

114
00:06:44,964 --> 00:06:46,397
This guy's the enemy

115
00:06:46,432 --> 00:06:49,033
of everything that's civilized, Linc.

116
00:06:50,203 --> 00:06:52,403
That brings me to my real question.

117
00:06:52,438 --> 00:06:54,277
Who in the hell are we breaking out?

118
00:06:54,280 --> 00:06:55,940
Is it Michael Scofield

119
00:06:55,975 --> 00:06:58,476
or Kaniel Outis?

120
00:07:41,030 --> 00:07:42,421
_

121
00:07:42,543 --> 00:07:44,253
_

122
00:07:44,547 --> 00:07:46,213
What the hell's going on?

123
00:07:46,216 --> 00:07:48,813
Ramal's men are gonna
institute Sharia law.

124
00:07:48,849 --> 00:07:51,349
And that son of a bitch
himself is gonna enjoy the show.

125
00:07:51,384 --> 00:07:53,552
We just have to keep our
heads down and get through this

126
00:07:53,554 --> 00:07:55,476
- so we can get out tonight.
- _

127
00:07:55,546 --> 00:07:59,227
_

128
00:08:04,700 --> 00:08:05,963
_

129
00:08:05,966 --> 00:08:07,665
No. No, don't let them take me!

130
00:08:07,701 --> 00:08:09,534
No!

131
00:08:22,375 --> 00:08:24,544
_

132
00:08:26,713 --> 00:08:28,589
_

133
00:08:32,292 --> 00:08:34,626
- Sorry.
- No!

134
00:08:35,289 --> 00:08:37,181
_

135
00:08:37,265 --> 00:08:39,585
_

136
00:08:39,671 --> 00:08:41,732
_

137
00:08:41,735 --> 00:08:43,301
Ramal!

138
00:08:47,274 --> 00:08:50,508
Get back. Just let him go.

139
00:08:50,544 --> 00:08:52,310
Ramal!

140
00:08:53,847 --> 00:08:54,913
What are you doing?

141
00:08:54,915 --> 00:08:56,080
- Stay out of this.
- No.

142
00:08:56,116 --> 00:08:57,549
The escape is tonight.

143
00:08:57,584 --> 00:09:00,084
If you want to get out, you
need me and you need him.

144
00:09:00,120 --> 00:09:01,719
Get to the point.

145
00:09:02,856 --> 00:09:04,756
Let him go, Ramal.

146
00:09:11,231 --> 00:09:12,230
Then I'll do it.

147
00:09:12,265 --> 00:09:14,098
Do not touch him.

148
00:09:14,134 --> 00:09:15,400
Get back, dog!

149
00:09:19,523 --> 00:09:23,441
There will be no killing in
this prison... Understand?

150
00:09:33,486 --> 00:09:35,320
He's tried to contact her before.

151
00:09:35,355 --> 00:09:38,323
Only difference is he
succeeded this time.

152
00:09:38,358 --> 00:09:41,292
It's smart... going through the boy.

153
00:09:43,019 --> 00:09:44,534
Ask a question?

154
00:09:47,567 --> 00:09:49,407
Why are we pulling our
punches with this woman?

155
00:09:51,271 --> 00:09:53,638
I got sent to her house
a couple of days ago,

156
00:09:53,673 --> 00:09:55,640
started spilling blood, but
I'm just supposed to stop

157
00:09:55,642 --> 00:09:58,910
before I start spilling hers.

158
00:09:58,945 --> 00:10:00,345
How's that work?

159
00:10:00,380 --> 00:10:04,182
You'll get used to Poseidon's game.

160
00:10:04,217 --> 00:10:05,817
It's all chess.

161
00:10:05,852 --> 00:10:08,353
It's a performance.

162
00:10:12,068 --> 00:10:15,660
A performance designed to
make Outis reach out to her.

163
00:10:15,695 --> 00:10:17,762
Now all we got to do is listen in,

164
00:10:17,797 --> 00:10:20,265
find out what his plans are.

165
00:10:20,300 --> 00:10:22,333
And she doesn't know it.

166
00:10:22,369 --> 00:10:26,371
She's the one that's
going to lead us to him.

167
00:10:26,406 --> 00:10:27,777
They said I can go in the morning.

168
00:10:27,780 --> 00:10:30,172
Your femoral artery was severed.

169
00:10:30,175 --> 00:10:33,243
That's not something you usually
just get up and walk away from.

170
00:10:33,246 --> 00:10:35,480
Hey, they gave me the okay.

171
00:10:35,515 --> 00:10:37,282
They're the doctors
on this one, not you.

172
00:10:37,317 --> 00:10:40,297
And I'm going full mental
in here, so I'm gonna go.

173
00:10:40,300 --> 00:10:42,319
Okay. How about this?

174
00:10:42,322 --> 00:10:44,622
When you are discharged,

175
00:10:44,658 --> 00:10:47,158
why don't we go up to
your parents' lake house?

176
00:10:47,193 --> 00:10:49,927
I'll just pick you up
with Mike and we'll go.

177
00:10:49,963 --> 00:10:51,256
Mmm.

178
00:10:51,356 --> 00:10:54,223
You don't want to be
in the house, do you?

179
00:10:54,259 --> 00:10:56,221
Somebody comes into your house

180
00:10:56,224 --> 00:10:58,518
and shoots up your husband
and they're still out there.

181
00:10:58,521 --> 00:11:01,030
No.

182
00:11:01,065 --> 00:11:02,698
What?

183
00:11:02,734 --> 00:11:04,767
No, it's just something
you do with your nose

184
00:11:04,802 --> 00:11:05,968
when you're determined.

185
00:11:06,004 --> 00:11:07,470
- With my nose?
- It's subtle.

186
00:11:07,505 --> 00:11:09,505
- I mean, it's really subtle.
- Better be.

187
00:11:09,541 --> 00:11:12,575
The face is amazing.

188
00:11:12,610 --> 00:11:14,377
I mean,

189
00:11:14,412 --> 00:11:18,548
the tiniest detail,
less than a millimeter,

190
00:11:18,583 --> 00:11:20,416
differentiates everything.

191
00:11:20,451 --> 00:11:23,519
An emotion on one person can be...

192
00:11:23,555 --> 00:11:26,222
so troubled

193
00:11:26,233 --> 00:11:28,218
and on another...

194
00:11:30,258 --> 00:11:32,191
so beautiful.

195
00:11:32,194 --> 00:11:35,695
You're not trying to get
somewhere, are you, Mr. Ness?

196
00:11:35,698 --> 00:11:37,531
Yes, actually,

197
00:11:37,534 --> 00:11:38,767
I am.

198
00:11:54,519 --> 00:11:57,520
Hello there.

199
00:11:57,555 --> 00:12:00,210
I come as a compatriot, Sara.

200
00:12:00,213 --> 00:12:02,327
Get out of my way or I'll scream.

201
00:12:02,330 --> 00:12:04,245
Last thing I want.

202
00:12:11,426 --> 00:12:12,993
For your information,

203
00:12:12,996 --> 00:12:15,263
I know about Kaniel Outis.

204
00:12:19,265 --> 00:12:21,277
Tell me what you know.

205
00:12:21,312 --> 00:12:23,929
The day I hit the bricks from Fox River,

206
00:12:23,932 --> 00:12:25,531
someone named Outis,

207
00:12:25,534 --> 00:12:27,300
out of the goodness of their soul,

208
00:12:27,335 --> 00:12:30,783
unsolicited, pays for
this modern prosthesis.

209
00:12:32,073 --> 00:12:33,439
What's that?

210
00:12:33,475 --> 00:12:36,042
A million bucks? Why would anyone

211
00:12:36,077 --> 00:12:37,717
come out of a pocket
for a wretch like me,

212
00:12:37,746 --> 00:12:39,946
a penny, much less a million bucks?

213
00:12:39,981 --> 00:12:43,604
Yeah, if you're coming to me
for answers, I don't have any.

214
00:12:43,607 --> 00:12:46,386
Oh, I went looking
for answers, Doc Sara.

215
00:12:46,421 --> 00:12:48,721
I looked up Outis on the Interwebs.

216
00:12:48,757 --> 00:12:51,291
Whose face comes up but
your dead ex-husband's,

217
00:12:51,326 --> 00:12:52,525
looking very much alive.

218
00:12:52,561 --> 00:12:54,527
Lazarus arisen from the dead.

219
00:12:54,563 --> 00:12:57,363
He's drawing us into
something, isn't he?

220
00:12:58,679 --> 00:13:00,733
He wants something, doesn't he?

221
00:13:00,769 --> 00:13:04,237
Come near me or my family
again, I will kill you.

222
00:13:04,272 --> 00:13:06,372
Better to have me on your side, Sara.

223
00:13:06,408 --> 00:13:08,608
We can figure this out together.

224
00:13:17,521 --> 00:13:19,088
We have all heard the war

225
00:13:19,091 --> 00:13:20,853
outside.

226
00:13:20,856 --> 00:13:24,289
But even if it is just
within these walls,

227
00:13:24,292 --> 00:13:27,903
the law of the land is still in place.

228
00:13:27,906 --> 00:13:32,298
The law of God supersedes
the law of this corrupt land.

229
00:13:32,334 --> 00:13:35,969
We will not be reduced to animals.

230
00:13:38,473 --> 00:13:40,940
Amazing you still trust him.

231
00:13:40,976 --> 00:13:43,443
He will use you for the
escape and he will leave you.

232
00:13:43,478 --> 00:13:46,245
No one's escaping.

233
00:13:46,281 --> 00:13:47,947
Who are you?

234
00:13:47,983 --> 00:13:49,549
A man who knows your friend there

235
00:13:49,584 --> 00:13:51,017
more than anyone in this prison.

236
00:13:51,052 --> 00:13:53,052
I was in solitary with him

237
00:13:53,088 --> 00:13:54,253
- for years.
- Yeah, so was I.

238
00:13:54,289 --> 00:13:56,053
But not in the cell across from him.

239
00:13:56,056 --> 00:13:59,125
He told me about the escape.

240
00:13:59,889 --> 00:14:01,519
- We have to work together.
- No.

241
00:14:01,522 --> 00:14:03,936
Tried to convince me to go with him,

242
00:14:03,939 --> 00:14:05,999
just the two of us.

243
00:14:06,034 --> 00:14:07,834
But I told him no.

244
00:14:07,869 --> 00:14:10,003
I would not leave my brother.

245
00:14:10,038 --> 00:14:11,838
That is the Army in me,

246
00:14:11,873 --> 00:14:14,043
the Christian in me.

247
00:14:14,046 --> 00:14:15,642
He is an opportunist.

248
00:14:15,677 --> 00:14:18,111
He will use whoever he needs.

249
00:14:18,146 --> 00:14:20,780
He has told you something
about the escape. I know he has.

250
00:14:20,815 --> 00:14:22,582
You were in the cell with him. You.

251
00:14:22,617 --> 00:14:25,551
You tell me, so I can help you,

252
00:14:25,587 --> 00:14:29,288
before he uses you to get that devil out

253
00:14:29,324 --> 00:14:32,080
and we are all left here to die.

254
00:14:46,908 --> 00:14:49,208
We need passports, Omar.
You think you can help us?

255
00:14:49,243 --> 00:14:51,638
Hold on. We're gonna trust this guy?

256
00:14:51,641 --> 00:14:54,002
He's the one who stole my
passport in the first place.

257
00:14:54,005 --> 00:14:55,967
It was honest bargaining, friend.

258
00:14:56,002 --> 00:14:57,836
I took nothing. Besides,

259
00:14:57,871 --> 00:15:00,271
your passport is long gone,

260
00:15:00,307 --> 00:15:02,874
somewhere far overseas by now, I bet.

261
00:15:02,909 --> 00:15:06,478
If you want, um, I can have
the forgers make you another.

262
00:15:06,513 --> 00:15:09,047
My own fake passport coming from you?

263
00:15:09,082 --> 00:15:10,580
You have another option?

264
00:15:12,352 --> 00:15:14,586
Quick. I'm leaving the city.

265
00:15:14,621 --> 00:15:17,455
Nowhere is safe anymore.

266
00:15:17,491 --> 00:15:19,524
I need two passports. One for me,

267
00:15:19,559 --> 00:15:22,527
one for my brother, Michael Scofield.

268
00:15:25,360 --> 00:15:27,665
$1,000 U.S. each, deposit.

269
00:15:27,701 --> 00:15:30,034
$1,000 U.S. when you pick them up.

270
00:15:30,070 --> 00:15:32,771
C?

271
00:15:35,490 --> 00:15:37,308
You screw with me and I'll kill you.

272
00:15:37,344 --> 00:15:38,810
I screw you,

273
00:15:38,845 --> 00:15:41,346
I won't be around for you to kill me.

274
00:15:41,381 --> 00:15:43,381
11:00 tonight, Sheba.

275
00:15:43,417 --> 00:15:45,383
Passports will be ready.

276
00:15:46,586 --> 00:15:48,386
That means we're gonna have to split up.

277
00:15:48,422 --> 00:15:50,112
You two get the passports,

278
00:15:50,115 --> 00:15:52,290
and I'll go with our friend
here to the power plant

279
00:15:52,292 --> 00:15:54,759
and kill the lights.

280
00:15:54,795 --> 00:15:58,296
And we get Michael out.

281
00:15:58,331 --> 00:16:00,532
A U.S. State Department
spokesperson said

282
00:16:00,567 --> 00:16:01,539
the capital of Yemen

283
00:16:01,542 --> 00:16:03,134
grows ever closer to collapse

284
00:16:03,170 --> 00:16:04,869
and it's only a matter of time

285
00:16:04,905 --> 00:16:07,972
until Sana'a's fallen to
the hands of ISIL radicals,

286
00:16:08,008 --> 00:16:11,276
with the total collapse
coming as soon as tomorrow.

287
00:16:13,982 --> 00:16:15,847
Hey.

288
00:16:17,150 --> 00:16:18,950
Looking for a smartphone?

289
00:16:18,985 --> 00:16:20,718
Yeah. You, um...

290
00:16:20,754 --> 00:16:22,954
you fix phones, too, right?

291
00:16:22,989 --> 00:16:24,289
Yeah.

292
00:16:24,324 --> 00:16:27,525
I think somebody hacked my cell.

293
00:16:32,232 --> 00:16:34,065
Whoa.

294
00:16:34,100 --> 00:16:38,136
Is there any chance you
can help me figure out who?

295
00:16:44,627 --> 00:16:46,391
_

296
00:16:46,680 --> 00:16:48,860
_

297
00:16:48,954 --> 00:16:52,051
_

298
00:16:52,426 --> 00:16:54,641
_

299
00:16:54,654 --> 00:16:56,120
That Christian guy said

300
00:16:56,156 --> 00:16:58,690
you told him you'd just
take him. No one else.

301
00:16:58,725 --> 00:17:00,458
He's a liar. You don't want anything

302
00:17:00,494 --> 00:17:03,394
- to do with him.
- I don't know. Christian, Army.

303
00:17:03,430 --> 00:17:05,363
- Seems pretty up front to me.
- Did he happen to tell you

304
00:17:05,365 --> 00:17:06,965
about some of the arrests
he and his brother made

305
00:17:06,967 --> 00:17:09,601
- at their security checkpoint?
- No, focused on you.

306
00:17:09,636 --> 00:17:11,402
They had a specialty: women.

307
00:17:11,438 --> 00:17:13,505
Body parts strewn around Yemen.

308
00:17:13,540 --> 00:17:14,906
That's why they're here.

309
00:17:14,941 --> 00:17:16,808
Wearing a cross is one thing.

310
00:17:16,843 --> 00:17:19,444
- Living by it is another.
- All right, okay, sure.

311
00:17:19,479 --> 00:17:20,778
Just promise me I can trust you,

312
00:17:20,814 --> 00:17:22,914
that we're still doing this tonight.

313
00:17:22,949 --> 00:17:25,517
All these years

314
00:17:25,552 --> 00:17:27,105
we've been working together,

315
00:17:27,108 --> 00:17:28,847
you've been able to
trust me the whole time.

316
00:17:28,850 --> 00:17:30,854
Last four years in the
hole, sitting in the dark,

317
00:17:30,857 --> 00:17:32,524
I couldn't even hear
a voice. I don't know.

318
00:17:32,526 --> 00:17:34,092
Maybe something's changed or...

319
00:17:34,127 --> 00:17:36,694
Nothing's changed.

320
00:17:36,730 --> 00:17:39,430
Poseidon put us in
here to get Ramal out,

321
00:17:39,466 --> 00:17:42,171
but then he abandoned us.
Ramal is Poseidon's guy,

322
00:17:42,174 --> 00:17:45,336
- not ours. He's an animal.
- I suggest

323
00:17:45,372 --> 00:17:48,706
you watch your mouth. Some
of these guys speak English.

324
00:17:48,742 --> 00:17:51,142
Why are we still getting him out?

325
00:17:51,177 --> 00:17:53,912
We're telling him we're getting
him out. There's a difference.

326
00:17:53,947 --> 00:17:55,513
We got to act like we're

327
00:17:55,549 --> 00:17:57,002
on his side until the moment we're not.

328
00:17:57,004 --> 00:17:58,583
But what if you're acting
like you're on my side

329
00:17:58,585 --> 00:17:59,651
till the moment you're not?

330
00:17:59,653 --> 00:18:00,829
You are getting paranoid.

331
00:18:00,832 --> 00:18:03,178
Yeah, well, four years in the
box is gonna do that to you.

332
00:18:03,181 --> 00:18:04,689
I'm not leaving you behind.

333
00:18:04,724 --> 00:18:06,858
- You're my whip hand.
- I don't know that.

334
00:18:06,893 --> 00:18:09,627
How do I know I'm your whip hand?

335
00:18:09,663 --> 00:18:11,930
- You'll understand later.
- I want to understand now.

336
00:18:11,965 --> 00:18:14,198
Okay?

337
00:18:15,764 --> 00:18:17,702
Get your hands off me.

338
00:18:17,737 --> 00:18:20,104
Answers, now. I'm serious.

339
00:18:20,140 --> 00:18:21,706
Okay.

340
00:18:22,809 --> 00:18:24,108
I said don't touch me!

341
00:18:25,245 --> 00:18:26,644
Okay. Mm.

342
00:18:26,680 --> 00:18:29,047
Mm. Okay, that's fair.

343
00:18:29,082 --> 00:18:32,106
Hey! Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!

344
00:18:32,109 --> 00:18:34,286
You want the hole again, huh?

345
00:18:34,289 --> 00:18:36,422
No, we're good.

346
00:18:37,557 --> 00:18:38,623
No.

347
00:18:38,658 --> 00:18:39,557
We're good.

348
00:18:39,593 --> 00:18:42,093
We're far from good.

349
00:18:54,929 --> 00:18:58,276
By tomorrow, we won't
have to worry about him.

350
00:19:08,822 --> 00:19:10,575
Keep your head down.

351
00:19:10,578 --> 00:19:12,657
Don't make eye contact with anybody.

352
00:19:12,659 --> 00:19:15,193
A lot of ISIL sympathizers everywhere.

353
00:19:15,228 --> 00:19:17,462
We get our passports, we're out of here.

354
00:19:17,497 --> 00:19:19,130
Understand?

355
00:19:36,125 --> 00:19:38,215
Planning on leaving?

356
00:19:38,218 --> 00:19:40,797
Right when the glorious
revolution is beginning.

357
00:19:40,800 --> 00:19:44,689
I'm not here for political
discussion, just passports.

358
00:19:47,727 --> 00:19:48,893
Money first.

359
00:19:48,928 --> 00:19:51,496
Passports first.

360
00:20:02,208 --> 00:20:04,342
They're empty.

361
00:20:06,946 --> 00:20:09,747
Sheba!

362
00:20:28,710 --> 00:20:30,510
I'm sorry I hit you.

363
00:20:30,545 --> 00:20:32,678
- I can explain.
- Can you explain why

364
00:20:32,714 --> 00:20:34,447
you were going to let that man kill me?

365
00:20:34,482 --> 00:20:36,449
I wouldn't have let him kill you.

366
00:20:36,484 --> 00:20:38,718
You sure seem to be chums
with the head of ISIL, friend.

367
00:20:38,753 --> 00:20:41,988
Didn't know you participated
in these conversations, Ja.

368
00:20:42,023 --> 00:20:43,689
Only when they're interesting.

369
00:20:43,725 --> 00:20:45,758
And they're usually not.

370
00:20:45,793 --> 00:20:48,547
There are people in my government,

371
00:20:48,550 --> 00:20:50,283
believe it or not, who want that man out

372
00:20:50,286 --> 00:20:53,099
for their own convoluted
foreign policy over here.

373
00:20:53,134 --> 00:20:55,701
That's the job Whip and
I were sent here to do.

374
00:20:55,737 --> 00:20:56,903
But for some reason,

375
00:20:56,938 --> 00:20:58,704
we were betrayed.

376
00:20:58,740 --> 00:21:01,507
Which means we're
getting out without Ramal.

377
00:21:01,543 --> 00:21:03,843
And every one of you
is crucial to that plan.

378
00:21:03,878 --> 00:21:05,311
How?

379
00:21:05,346 --> 00:21:07,013
Your whole escape's already wired.

380
00:21:07,048 --> 00:21:09,382
Lights out, you're over the wall.

381
00:21:09,417 --> 00:21:11,684
What do you need a Korean junkie

382
00:21:11,719 --> 00:21:14,320
- like me for?
- Korean genius, you mean.

383
00:21:14,841 --> 00:21:17,575
Getting over that
wall is just the start.

384
00:21:17,611 --> 00:21:19,411
Once that happens,

385
00:21:19,446 --> 00:21:21,413
there are things only you can do.

386
00:21:21,448 --> 00:21:24,318
Back on point: you hit me.

387
00:21:24,321 --> 00:21:27,518
You wanted proof that I
sided with you and not Ramal.

388
00:21:27,521 --> 00:21:29,689
- And splitting my lip does that how?
- Son of a bitch

389
00:21:29,691 --> 00:21:32,420
Kaniel Outis keeps playing, doesn't he?

390
00:21:41,635 --> 00:21:43,168
Where is my watch?

391
00:21:43,203 --> 00:21:44,936
I don't know what you're talking about.

392
00:21:44,971 --> 00:21:47,372
Hmm. You don't?

393
00:21:47,407 --> 00:21:52,043
I'm going to break you in half
when I find that watch, you know?

394
00:21:55,882 --> 00:21:57,716
Toss the cell.

395
00:22:24,911 --> 00:22:27,045
It's not here.

396
00:22:30,917 --> 00:22:32,784
Order a lockdown of the whole prison.

397
00:22:32,819 --> 00:22:34,930
No one gets out of their cells

398
00:22:34,933 --> 00:22:36,787
until that watch is found!

399
00:22:37,954 --> 00:22:40,023
_

400
00:22:41,857 --> 00:22:42,943
_

401
00:22:43,151 --> 00:22:44,403
_

402
00:22:47,803 --> 00:22:48,782
_

403
00:22:49,536 --> 00:22:52,003
I told you, Ramal's not
going anywhere. Only we are.

404
00:22:52,038 --> 00:22:55,129
We're gonna be locked in our
box just like the rest of them,

405
00:22:55,132 --> 00:22:56,865
only our box has a way out.

406
00:22:56,868 --> 00:22:59,344
And in two hours when
those lights go black,

407
00:22:59,379 --> 00:23:01,713
we're gonna disappear from
this place like ghosts.

408
00:23:01,755 --> 00:23:04,956
Yeah, all right.

409
00:23:28,909 --> 00:23:30,375
Sheba!

410
00:23:31,478 --> 00:23:34,245
Who are these men you work with?

411
00:23:37,417 --> 00:23:39,818
They're beneath you.

412
00:23:39,853 --> 00:23:41,820
You're beneath me.

413
00:23:46,593 --> 00:23:49,227
It pains me to hurt you,

414
00:23:49,262 --> 00:23:53,898
but a good woman is a humble woman.

415
00:23:53,934 --> 00:23:58,069
Remember that.

416
00:23:58,104 --> 00:24:00,705
Who are these men?

417
00:24:00,740 --> 00:24:02,540
Doesn't matter.

418
00:24:02,576 --> 00:24:04,209
They're leaving.

419
00:24:04,244 --> 00:24:07,045
I am not the bad guy here.

420
00:24:07,088 --> 00:24:09,555
You and I have a history.

421
00:24:09,583 --> 00:24:10,596
How I doted

422
00:24:10,599 --> 00:24:15,186
on you in grade school,
how I waited and I waited.

423
00:24:15,222 --> 00:24:17,180
You did not wait.

424
00:24:17,183 --> 00:24:18,844
You tried to rape me!

425
00:24:23,839 --> 00:24:25,964
Please.

426
00:24:27,634 --> 00:24:30,368
Please. Please untie me...

427
00:24:31,922 --> 00:24:33,922
so I can take your other eye.

428
00:24:46,519 --> 00:24:49,254
Afternoon.

429
00:24:49,296 --> 00:24:53,832
I'm looking for a cell phone
that a woman stole from me.

430
00:24:53,860 --> 00:24:56,427
She looks like this?

431
00:24:59,642 --> 00:25:01,673
No, can't help you.

432
00:25:01,676 --> 00:25:04,777
Can't... or won't?

433
00:25:04,780 --> 00:25:08,273
Sorry. Store policy, that's all.

434
00:25:15,561 --> 00:25:18,216
Hey, what are you doing?

435
00:25:18,251 --> 00:25:20,084
- Just...
- Ow!

436
00:25:20,120 --> 00:25:21,920
- Oh!
- Let's go again.

437
00:25:23,423 --> 00:25:25,857
Have you seen her?

438
00:25:25,892 --> 00:25:27,792
Yes. Yes!

439
00:25:27,827 --> 00:25:30,495
She was here, like, ten minutes ago.

440
00:25:30,530 --> 00:25:32,645
Said her phone was hacked
and wanted to know who did it.

441
00:25:32,647 --> 00:25:34,814
And now she knows, doesn't she?

442
00:25:38,538 --> 00:25:40,872
She baited us.

443
00:25:58,858 --> 00:26:00,509
Dead end.

444
00:26:43,603 --> 00:26:45,003
Any chance Poseidon'll just

445
00:26:45,038 --> 00:26:47,271
- let us kill her?
- It might come to that.

446
00:27:13,024 --> 00:27:15,992
We get out, where are you going?

447
00:27:16,027 --> 00:27:17,994
Back to my couch.

448
00:27:18,029 --> 00:27:20,129
My couch in Seoul.

449
00:27:20,164 --> 00:27:22,498
Where the walls are mine,

450
00:27:22,522 --> 00:27:25,801
the floors are mine,

451
00:27:25,837 --> 00:27:27,949
no one can get to me.

452
00:27:28,002 --> 00:27:31,003
The world stays outside
like it's supposed to.

453
00:27:32,410 --> 00:27:33,976
Calgary.

454
00:27:34,012 --> 00:27:35,511
Canada?

455
00:27:35,546 --> 00:27:39,148
I'm going to be a ski jumper.

456
00:27:39,183 --> 00:27:42,518
You've never seen snow, have you?

457
00:27:42,553 --> 00:27:44,387
That's the point.

458
00:27:44,422 --> 00:27:46,989
Everything in my life
till now in this country...

459
00:27:47,025 --> 00:27:51,627
The heat, the hate, the
skies that never snow.

460
00:27:51,686 --> 00:27:53,985
You talk about the world.

461
00:27:54,015 --> 00:27:56,282
I want to be on the other side of it.

462
00:28:02,470 --> 00:28:07,142
_

463
00:28:07,512 --> 00:28:09,812
Hey, Dad. Hey, Mom.

464
00:28:09,847 --> 00:28:11,347
Hi, son. Yeah, Sara,

465
00:28:11,382 --> 00:28:13,459
- let me, uh...
- Thanks, sir.

466
00:28:14,053 --> 00:28:16,818
Oh, give me one sec. Sorry.

467
00:28:16,821 --> 00:28:19,488
Hello?

468
00:28:19,524 --> 00:28:22,889
Hi. This is Brian at
Jep's. I got this number

469
00:28:22,892 --> 00:28:24,593
when I activated your new phone.

470
00:28:24,629 --> 00:28:26,077
You never came back.

471
00:28:26,080 --> 00:28:27,914
I'm sorry. I don't think I'm going to.

472
00:28:27,917 --> 00:28:30,468
Well, okay, I just want
to let you know that

473
00:28:30,501 --> 00:28:32,868
I figured out who was
hacking your phone.

474
00:28:32,904 --> 00:28:34,437
Who?

475
00:28:34,440 --> 00:28:36,301
You... hacked your own phone.

476
00:28:36,304 --> 00:28:37,403
What are you talking about?

477
00:28:37,406 --> 00:28:40,598
Your thumbprint is your
password, right? Well,

478
00:28:40,601 --> 00:28:43,231
whoever hacked your phone
used your thumbprint, so,

479
00:28:43,234 --> 00:28:46,983
unless you're missing
a thumb, that's you.

480
00:28:46,986 --> 00:28:48,884
I don't know what you're messed up in,

481
00:28:48,920 --> 00:28:51,311
but I'd watch your back...

482
00:28:51,356 --> 00:28:53,956
When you were in the hospital,

483
00:28:53,991 --> 00:28:56,741
the woman who attacked us
came back with her partner.

484
00:28:56,744 --> 00:28:57,559
What?

485
00:28:57,562 --> 00:28:59,250
They tracked me down
using my cell phone,

486
00:28:59,253 --> 00:29:01,563
so I brought it to Jep's
to try and figure out

487
00:29:01,566 --> 00:29:03,720
- who they were working for.
- Whoa, wait. Sara, this has police

488
00:29:03,722 --> 00:29:05,891
- written all over it.
- Police haven't been able to do a thing.

489
00:29:05,893 --> 00:29:07,670
So, what? You went to Jep's Electronics

490
00:29:07,705 --> 00:29:09,981
in some hackneyed attempt
at counter-espionage?

491
00:29:09,984 --> 00:29:13,275
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. It's just...

492
00:29:13,311 --> 00:29:15,211
I get you don't know where to turn,

493
00:29:15,246 --> 00:29:16,879
but I got a stake in this, too.

494
00:29:16,914 --> 00:29:19,749
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay? This is my wife, my son.

495
00:29:20,304 --> 00:29:22,494
You want to get back at these guys?

496
00:29:22,497 --> 00:29:24,722
The university. I mean,
it has real resources,

497
00:29:24,725 --> 00:29:26,089
their computer sciences department.

498
00:29:26,091 --> 00:29:28,356
The phone's done. It's
gonna stay at Jep's.

499
00:29:28,359 --> 00:29:32,049
So that's your plan... just
bury your head in the sand?

500
00:29:34,464 --> 00:29:36,731
No.

501
00:29:36,734 --> 00:29:38,200
No, I've learned over the years

502
00:29:38,203 --> 00:29:40,770
that's exactly what
you don't do. Thank you.

503
00:29:52,641 --> 00:29:54,207
Which one's this?

504
00:29:54,242 --> 00:29:56,676
The one you accosted in a bathroom.

505
00:29:56,712 --> 00:29:59,612
Oh, that wasn't accostment, honey.

506
00:29:59,648 --> 00:30:01,648
I've learned some things

507
00:30:01,683 --> 00:30:05,385
about who it is we're
apparently both looking for?

508
00:30:05,420 --> 00:30:08,021
But I need to know that you're
willing to go the distance.

509
00:30:08,056 --> 00:30:10,457
I'm made of the distance, honeysuckle.

510
00:30:10,492 --> 00:30:12,607
I am the distance.

511
00:30:12,610 --> 00:30:15,061
Good. Because you're
gonna have a conversation

512
00:30:15,097 --> 00:30:16,629
with Paul Kellerman for me.

513
00:30:16,665 --> 00:30:19,132
Bull. Kellerman's behind this?

514
00:30:19,167 --> 00:30:21,167
And you are gonna get
every shred of information

515
00:30:21,203 --> 00:30:23,770
you can about what's really going on.

516
00:30:25,707 --> 00:30:29,142
15 minutes.

517
00:30:29,177 --> 00:30:33,012
I'm soiling myself
here, just so you know.

518
00:30:38,855 --> 00:30:43,224
Look, I'm just gonna
say one thing, okay?

519
00:30:43,291 --> 00:30:45,625
You're like a brother to me,

520
00:30:45,660 --> 00:30:47,360
like an older brother.

521
00:30:47,396 --> 00:30:49,872
- I'm not much of a brother.
- Sure.

522
00:30:49,875 --> 00:30:53,333
Point is that I had zero,
nobody, till you recruited me.

523
00:30:53,368 --> 00:30:56,896
When you pulled me out of that prison
in the Ozarks, you had integrity.

524
00:31:00,642 --> 00:31:03,209
I know we were doing CIA work, sure,

525
00:31:03,245 --> 00:31:04,944
you know, pulling their people out, but

526
00:31:04,980 --> 00:31:09,282
it was about you and me,
and having each other's back.

527
00:31:09,317 --> 00:31:11,678
And it didn't matter if you
were Ramon Cadena when we did

528
00:31:11,681 --> 00:31:14,753
the Colombian break,
or, you know Asaf...

529
00:31:14,756 --> 00:31:17,190
What was his name?

530
00:31:17,225 --> 00:31:19,526
Whatever. The one in Egypt.

531
00:31:19,561 --> 00:31:21,428
You were still you.

532
00:31:21,471 --> 00:31:25,973
And it's the same with this one.

533
00:31:26,001 --> 00:31:28,435
You know, we trump
you up as Kaniel Outis,

534
00:31:28,470 --> 00:31:30,136
big international terrorist.

535
00:31:30,172 --> 00:31:33,696
It's just a name,

536
00:31:33,699 --> 00:31:37,500
it's just a rap sheet, it's
a way to get you locked up.

537
00:31:37,503 --> 00:31:38,869
Right?

538
00:31:41,290 --> 00:31:44,050
I guess what I'm asking you is did...

539
00:31:44,100 --> 00:31:47,836
did something happen to you
while you were in solitary?

540
00:31:49,691 --> 00:31:51,537
Did you become Kaniel Outis

541
00:31:51,540 --> 00:31:54,828
in there in your head?

542
00:31:54,863 --> 00:31:58,331
Do you now want Ramal out after all?

543
00:31:58,366 --> 00:32:01,676
I already told you Ramal
is out of the picture.

544
00:32:01,679 --> 00:32:04,146
Yeah, you said that,
but one small thing...

545
00:32:04,149 --> 00:32:06,989
We go up through that hole,

546
00:32:06,992 --> 00:32:08,926
and then we skirt above the block.

547
00:32:08,929 --> 00:32:12,879
Goes right above
Ramal's cell, doesn't it?

548
00:32:12,914 --> 00:32:15,081
Knock out a couple tiles,

549
00:32:15,116 --> 00:32:18,485
he joins the escape, doesn't he?

550
00:32:21,857 --> 00:32:23,456
What did you whisper to him

551
00:32:23,492 --> 00:32:26,059
in that moment after the fight?

552
00:32:26,830 --> 00:32:29,331
You whispered something, what was it?

553
00:32:31,972 --> 00:32:34,907
Nine minutes.

554
00:32:34,942 --> 00:32:36,508
How do you know?

555
00:32:36,569 --> 00:32:38,838
He told me at dinner.

556
00:32:38,874 --> 00:32:41,107
He said he would come for us.

557
00:32:41,142 --> 00:32:44,611
It's supposed to be only me,

558
00:32:44,646 --> 00:32:47,614
but you will all be coming.

559
00:32:49,098 --> 00:32:51,155
Open block five.

560
00:32:53,593 --> 00:32:55,159
Everyone out.

561
00:32:55,194 --> 00:32:56,660
Shakedown.

562
00:33:09,442 --> 00:33:11,142
Got it.

563
00:33:11,772 --> 00:33:14,706
Found it, Mustapha. It was
in the emir's coat here.

564
00:33:16,912 --> 00:33:18,906
You trusted the liar, didn't you?

565
00:33:24,115 --> 00:33:27,684
Now, we just pray they
get the lights out.

566
00:33:27,719 --> 00:33:29,820
We got to hurry, man.

567
00:33:29,855 --> 00:33:31,054
We got less than ten minutes

568
00:33:31,089 --> 00:33:32,889
to kill the power.

569
00:33:32,925 --> 00:33:34,428
Don't worry.

570
00:33:34,431 --> 00:33:36,972
With luck, both your friend and my son

571
00:33:36,975 --> 00:33:38,641
will be free within the hour.

572
00:33:41,166 --> 00:33:43,308
Okay, breakers are down.

573
00:33:43,311 --> 00:33:45,418
Now, we just need to
pull the redundancies.

574
00:33:45,421 --> 00:33:46,887
They're down the hall.

575
00:33:46,918 --> 00:33:49,005
I'll stay here and
deal with security. Go.

576
00:33:51,543 --> 00:33:53,243
Okay.

577
00:33:53,278 --> 00:33:55,345
Come on, where are you?

578
00:33:55,380 --> 00:33:56,680
Ah.

579
00:33:58,951 --> 00:34:00,684
Oh, come on.

580
00:34:02,018 --> 00:34:04,018
Oh, when in doubt, go old school.

581
00:34:18,971 --> 00:34:20,390
Let's go.

582
00:34:24,105 --> 00:34:25,277
Get the generators up.

583
00:34:25,280 --> 00:34:26,668
Get these inmates back inside!

584
00:34:26,706 --> 00:34:28,278
Now!

585
00:34:35,993 --> 00:34:37,954
Let's go, let's go!

586
00:34:39,157 --> 00:34:40,957
The weapons, get their weapons.

587
00:34:49,990 --> 00:34:51,810
They are trying to escape without us.

588
00:34:51,835 --> 00:34:53,368
Get to their cell.

589
00:34:53,371 --> 00:34:56,273
Block six. Come on!

590
00:35:03,015 --> 00:35:04,725
You heard them, brother.

591
00:35:04,728 --> 00:35:05,994
- Block six.
- Yes.

592
00:35:06,232 --> 00:35:07,999
Ja, give me your phone.

593
00:35:08,002 --> 00:35:09,802
Come on.

594
00:35:15,099 --> 00:35:16,799
Mount flashlights.

595
00:35:16,834 --> 00:35:18,100
Secure every room.

596
00:35:18,136 --> 00:35:19,769
Shoot only if you have to.

597
00:35:19,804 --> 00:35:21,804
And if you do, shoot to kill.

598
00:35:43,528 --> 00:35:45,317
This way.

599
00:35:45,320 --> 00:35:47,897
A shortcut to block
six, brother, come on!

600
00:35:47,932 --> 00:35:50,299
Get off me, you sick bastard!

601
00:35:50,334 --> 00:35:52,234
It's easier if you don't struggle.

602
00:36:19,730 --> 00:36:22,398
This is how you treat me?

603
00:36:22,433 --> 00:36:24,976
You're going to die now, dog.

604
00:36:41,719 --> 00:36:45,321
Sheba, Sheba, it's me, it's me.

605
00:36:45,356 --> 00:36:47,523
Are you okay?

606
00:36:58,604 --> 00:36:59,803
Linc, talk to me.

607
00:36:59,831 --> 00:37:02,064
Get to the rendezvous, the auto shop.

608
00:37:02,108 --> 00:37:04,182
We ain't gonna make it.
Sheba's busted up real bad.

609
00:37:04,185 --> 00:37:06,209
- What happened?
- Just get to the rendezvous.

610
00:37:06,212 --> 00:37:09,079
We got to be there for Michael, damn it!

611
00:37:11,050 --> 00:37:13,984
Damn. Lockdown.

612
00:37:14,020 --> 00:37:15,953
Extra guards on the roof.

613
00:37:15,988 --> 00:37:18,956
Question is whether they move on.

614
00:37:18,991 --> 00:37:22,092
Quickly! Hurry, hurry!

615
00:37:22,128 --> 00:37:23,727
It's here, this one!

616
00:37:23,763 --> 00:37:26,852
We got problems.

617
00:37:26,855 --> 00:37:29,600
- Guys are trying to get into the cell.
- Problem.

618
00:37:29,635 --> 00:37:31,168
- What's wrong?
- People coming.

619
00:37:31,204 --> 00:37:32,403
Damn it, we got guards up here.

620
00:37:32,405 --> 00:37:33,637
Try and buy us some time.

621
00:37:33,673 --> 00:37:35,839
I'm taking care of it.

622
00:37:38,135 --> 00:37:39,777
No, they're escaping, hurry!

623
00:37:42,848 --> 00:37:44,365
Ah!

624
00:37:44,380 --> 00:37:47,284
No, please! Don't leave us.

625
00:37:47,320 --> 00:37:48,819
Please, we are Christians,

626
00:37:48,854 --> 00:37:50,454
they will kill us! Please!

627
00:37:50,489 --> 00:37:52,022
No, we're still not clear up top.

628
00:37:52,058 --> 00:37:53,257
Make sure they don't get up.

629
00:37:53,292 --> 00:37:54,858
Go!

630
00:37:54,894 --> 00:37:56,227
They're coming, Ja.

631
00:37:56,262 --> 00:37:58,295
- How we doing?
- Not good.

632
00:37:58,331 --> 00:38:00,331
Guards are even closer.

633
00:38:00,366 --> 00:38:03,000
Pull yourself up!

634
00:38:07,773 --> 00:38:09,473
Help, help!

635
00:38:10,376 --> 00:38:11,942
Sid!

636
00:38:15,982 --> 00:38:17,982
Sid!

637
00:38:19,552 --> 00:38:21,385
Help me out!

638
00:38:21,420 --> 00:38:22,653
Get him up here first.

639
00:38:22,688 --> 00:38:23,921
That's not how this works.

640
00:38:23,923 --> 00:38:25,756
You pull my brother up first.

641
00:38:25,791 --> 00:38:27,725
Hurry, Ramal is coming.

642
00:38:27,760 --> 00:38:30,060
Lend me your hand. I swear I'm gonna...

643
00:38:30,096 --> 00:38:32,162
The kid comes up first!

644
00:38:34,600 --> 00:38:36,333
Step away, step away.

645
00:38:36,369 --> 00:38:38,602
- No!
- Muza, Muza, look at me!

646
00:38:38,638 --> 00:38:40,504
Muza! Muza!

647
00:38:40,539 --> 00:38:42,473
No! No, look at me, brother.

648
00:38:42,508 --> 00:38:46,010
Go, go, go! It's Ramal.

649
00:38:46,045 --> 00:38:47,645
Look at me! Muza!

650
00:38:54,420 --> 00:38:56,687
Hurry. We've got a minute
tops to get out of here.

651
00:38:56,689 --> 00:38:57,788
Get up there, after him.

652
00:38:57,823 --> 00:38:59,590
Drop them!

653
00:38:59,592 --> 00:39:01,992
Drop them!

654
00:39:02,028 --> 00:39:03,661
Put it down!

655
00:39:09,468 --> 00:39:10,977
Do it!

656
00:39:13,313 --> 00:39:16,273
- No!
- Down, now!

657
00:39:17,498 --> 00:39:19,943
- Board spans the gap.
- Blanket covers the wire.

658
00:39:19,979 --> 00:39:21,912
Get out!

659
00:39:27,353 --> 00:39:29,119
What are you doing in this cell?

660
00:39:32,425 --> 00:39:34,191
They're on the roof!

661
00:39:45,004 --> 00:39:46,603
Don't shoot!

662
00:40:44,303 --> 00:40:46,539
I trusted you, Kaniel Outis.

663
00:40:46,542 --> 00:40:48,131
And you lied to me.

664
00:40:48,134 --> 00:40:51,835
By God and my armies of the caliphate,

665
00:40:51,871 --> 00:40:53,404
you will die for it.

666
00:40:53,439 --> 00:40:55,639
Maybe even tomorrow.

667
00:41:40,753 --> 00:41:42,820
Sara...

668
00:41:44,690 --> 00:41:47,591
I'm putting you in
danger by saying this,

669
00:41:47,626 --> 00:41:51,161
but maybe it doesn't
matter because I'll be dead,

670
00:41:51,165 --> 00:41:53,298
and they'll leave you alone.

671
00:41:55,887 --> 00:41:59,722
But I love you.

672
00:41:59,773 --> 00:42:03,041
You see, I loved you.

673
00:42:03,091 --> 00:42:07,644
I never stopped loving you.

674
00:42:07,680 --> 00:42:11,582
This whole lie, it was for you.

675
00:42:12,651 --> 00:42:17,521
Sara, if I... if I do die,

676
00:42:17,556 --> 00:42:20,624
don't let them put Kaniel
Outis on the headstone

677
00:42:20,659 --> 00:42:24,428
because that's never what it was.

678
00:42:25,914 --> 00:42:29,299
Make them put my real name,

679
00:42:29,335 --> 00:42:31,702
the man I have always been.

680
00:42:35,875 --> 00:42:38,275
Michael Scofield.

