Hold it right there!
What do you think you're doing?
The charges stand as follows.
"A man identified as John Wilkinson Thackery
"was apprehended inside a pharmacy
"at number 745 Hudson Street
at 3:00 this morning.
"At that time, he was observed
to have in his possession
"an assorted half dozen stolen bottles
of cocaine and paregoric."
Paregoric?
The man doesn't have enough problems.
He suffers from diarrhea, too.
Ever since this country's cargo ships
became bottled up in the Far East,
not a night goes by we don't arrest
a couple desperate hopheads
or them that would sell it to them.
Surely you don't mean to include
Dr. Thackery among those miscreants?
He is a white man,
those are immigrant crimes.
He was holding a hypodermic needle.
He is also a practicing doctor.
And he had removed his shoes.
Captain,
if I can convince the owner of the pharmacy
to drop his complaints against Dr. Thackery,
will this sufficiently
satisfy your understanding
of the letter and the spirit of the law?
Breaking and entering carries with it
a minimum sentence of five years
at Sing Sing.
And something for the roundsman
who apprehended him.
So I think this makes us even,
don't you think?
- You need a lift?
- No, thank you.
I need to stretch my legs.
Where do you live?
Park Avenue, just below the train station.
Climb aboard.
To your health, sir.
What are you even about?
What?
I always assumed the reason
Dr. Thackery never decamped
to a more prestigious hospital
is because he was in some way
indebted to you.
Let me ask you a question, Mr. Barrow.
I'm not going to find out to my displeasure
that you've known about
Dr. Thackery's condition all along, am I?
I can say that I never wanted to
believe this about Dr. Thackery.
I bought myself a hospital full of doctors.
You ought to be able to find one
who can treat him.
Here's something that'll interest you.
"Narcotic shortages caused by the war
wreak havoc here.
"A case in point, last night, a man identified
as a prominent New York doctor
"was arrested after breaking into
a Greenwich Village pharmacy
"in order to meet the increasingly
desperate needs of his patients.
"Informed of the doctor's motives,
"the proprietor of the pharmacy,
Mr. W.A. Cleveland,
"hailed his selflessness
and subsequently withdrew the complaint."
John?
John, let me in!
You alone?
Of course I am.
Who would I be with?
"When sorrows come,
"they come not single spies,
but in battalions."
-I beg your pardon?
-Who sent you?
-Nobody sent me.
-Was it Robertson?
-Miss Robertson?
-Her father.
Did that son of a bitch
send you to spy on me?
John, did something
happen to you last night?
You look terrible.
-When did you last eat?
-I'm not hungry.
Have you slept?
That is the question.
I've never been more tired in my life.
Why don't you let me give you a bath
and put you to bed?
I can't go to bed. I have bedbugs.
You don't have bedbugs.
I can feel them under my skin.
I've treated people with bedbugs
and that's not what they do.
Wait a minute. How did you know
something happened to me last night?
Barrow sent you, didn't he?
It was in the morning newspaper.
-I don't believe you.
-It didn't name you.
But the way you've been acting,
I just assumed...
I don't believe you. It was Barrow
who sent you to spy on me, wasn't it?
Wasn't it?
Oh, God.
What can I do to help?
Nothing.
Just tell me what I can do.
You can find me
an ocean of cocaine.
Look here.
What’s your game?
Well, I assure you
there is no game, Mr. Collier.
You don't think I know why you're here?
You think I don't know how to read
between the lines?
That was your man Thackery, wasn't it?
Your top doctor's turned out
to be a fucking cocaine fiend.
You see what dire straits we're in
when a man of Dr. Thackery's reputation
must resort to burglary
for the sake of his patients.
Oh, for Christ's sake.
I'm in the hooker trade.
You don't think I recognize
a burny blower when I see one?
Then you also know
that it is in your best interest
to get Dr. Thackery back on his feet.
Because I can never repay you without him.
Well, I ain't gonna loan you any more money,
I'll tell you that right now.
But I may find it in my heart
to advance your man
some few bindles of the drug.
You can do that?
Ain't you been listening?
I'm in the hooker line.
How do you think these dumb young clucks
are able to face each day
of their miserable fucking lives?
Cocaine, morphine, ether.
I can get my hands on practically anything.
Consider it part of your loan.
Mr. Collier,
I don't know how to thank you.
Oh, oh.
Aw...
You can thank me
by never again fucking telling me
what's in my fucking best interest,
you fucking mutt!
That's no problem at all. And thank you.
Dr. Johnston from Metropolitan
did black out at the last surgical conference.
It was a bit of a scandal, really.
I'd wager anything
it was Thackery.
Don't let me interrupt.
I believe you were
all talking about Dr. Thackery.
It would account for
the superhuman energy he has.
Perhaps it's what distinguishes
a great man from an ordinary one.
I'd say it's more likely
some sort of drug addiction.
What's the man accused of stealing?
Cocaine and paregoric.
Why paregoric?
They drink it for
the camphorated opium it contains
so they're able to sleep on those
rare occasions when they actually do.
Thackery shows all the signs.
Boundless energy,
euphoria alternating with exhaustion.
Insomnia, paranoia,
a compulsion to itch, hallucinations.
In nursing school,
I treated some soldiers who were addicted.
Nurse Elkins,
do you have a moment
to discuss next week's rotation?
I don't know.
Johnston has this very weird laugh.
I mean, we shouldn't rule him out.
Tell me what you know about
Thackery's condition.
I don't know anything.
Your loyalty is commendable,
but I need to know everything right now.
I don't know a thing.
Let's both of us be frank here, shall we?
You're betraying no confidences here.
I was the one who fetched him
from the police station this morning.
-Is there really no cocaine to be found?
-No, there is not.
And I ought to know.
Since this war began,
I've been horse-trading
every manner of drugs
from every reputable hospital
and pharmaceutical company
on the East Coast.
What about the disreputable ones?
Is there anything I can do?
Pray for peace in the Philippines.
Not now.
Well, I suppose you get
what you pay for.
HOW did this happen?
He stubbed his toe
against a table leg.
Looks like
he gave it a good swift kick.
It wasn't nothing
but a little out at first.
But it won't close
and that was two weeks ago.
Was he always like this?
A couple of times a day whenever
he's not eating, and he's always eating.
I never knew a boy who ate...
Dr. Edwards, when you're finished,
I need to talk to you in your office.
Wait for me there.
You're late?
Three weeks late.
-Could it be Phillip's?
-No.
That's impossible.
Algie, do you want to keep the child?
Yes.
Stop and think about it a little.
I don't need to think about it.
It's our child, Cornelia.
Keep your voice down.
Don't you?
I do.
And I wouldn't even hesitate to lie about
who the father is if only...
If only it wasn't a colored man.
Everyone will know when they see the child.
Does it...
Does it have to be a procedure?
Is there a medicine?
No.
A girl I knew at school said she heard
there was an old Indian remedy.
There's no proven method except surgery.
Edwards, stop right there.
I really haven't the time, Doctor.
If you'll kindly excuse me.
Edwards.
You cannot change treatment
on one of my patients
without my prior approval.
To do so is nothing less
than a breach of medical ethics.
-Which patient are you...
-Miss Gibson.
Which is she?
She's the woman who ingested
the so-called sanitized tapeworm
in order to slim her figure.
You cannot be serious.
-Do you remember her or not?
-Yes.
Yes, I remember her.
Miss Gibson, the rich, fat white lady.
-Edwards.
-I remember thinking,
"No one will ever make the mistake of
confusing her with the real Gibson Girl."
Don't walk away from me!
You prescribed castor oil as a purgative.
And what is wrong with that?
They have been prescribing castor oil
as an anthelmintic
since the time of the Egyptian pharaohs.
Eleanor?
Darling, what are you doing here?
Are you feeling all right?
I fear it's another brain fever.
Are you feeling ill?
No, it's the baby, Everett.
But never you mind.
I think you'll be proud of me.
I took a page from your book
and put its little head in an ice bath.
I don’t want to play in your yard
I don’t like you anymore
You’ll be sorry when you see me
Sliding down our cellar door
Don't stop.
You can’t holler down our rain barrel
You can’t climb our apple tree
I don’t want to play in your yard
If you won’t be good to me
Where'd you get this?
Barrow got it for you.
Salt water.
Now,
what can I do for you this afternoon?
I'm a friend of Dr. Thackery's.
I thought you might know
how to get the cocaine he needs.
It is difficult enough to acquire opium
for my customers here.
Please tell Dr. Thackery
sorry.
You have quite a dainty foot.
In Chinese, we say it is jin ping mei.
A golden lotus.
Here, I'll write it down for you.
During the act of passion,
a man's pleasure may
be enhanced immeasurably
by having his concubine
place her foot in his mouth.
Do this for me,
and I shall trade you
ten grains of opium
and
one hundred Yankee dollars.
You heard the news?
The whole hospital's in tears.
Two little girls in as many months.
If I was Everett, I don't know what I would do.
I suppose you'd find comfort in your faith.
Faith isn't always a comfort.
I've lost so many over the years.
God blesses every child, born and unborn,
with an immortal soul.
All I can do is pray for them,
especially the unbaptized ones,
wherever they may go.
Aren't they all allowed into heaven?
I just assumed.
But we can hope
that God, in His infinite mercy,
will one day still welcome them
into His eternal communion.
And may He do the same for me.
What have you got for me?
Lamb chops.
I thought you might be hungry.
Oh, Lucy, please
don't tell me you've come empty-handed.
What is it?
A few grains of opium.
How did you know where to get this?
Don't be angry,
but I followed you one night.
You got it from Ping Wu?
I'm sure he took quite a liking to you.
As long as you didn't have
to put your golden lotus
in his mouth to pay for it.
Could you grab that lamp and matches?
And light the lamp for me.
Just hold that over the flame.
Am I doing it right?
Just, uh, just hold it over here.
How did you pay for this?
My bicycle.
-Good morning, Dr. Edwards.
-Good morning.
Nurse.
I'm afraid it's just
the two of us on the ward today.
Oh. Well, doesn't appear to be anything
the pair of us can't handle.
Shall we?
Mr. Oates.
I want you to open your eyes for me.
And, please, don't be alarmed.
I'm a colored man.
Don't make any difference to me.
Doctor?
Patient presents
capsulocretaceous cataracts in both eyes.
I advise surgery.
Anesthetic?
In the absence of cocaine,
I'd recommend Holocaine.
Looks like we are meeting halfway.
It would seem so.
My father says
that's a sure sign of any good relationship.
I was just headed to see if
Dr. Thackery needed anything.
Hmm.
You've been awfully solicitous
of Dr. Thackery lately.
Should I be jealous?
What do you mean?
-No, I just...
-What did you think?
Nothing. Um...
Mr. Barrow is looking for you.
No, Sir, I did not say that.
And I do sympathize with your situation.
I just wish you'd show
a bit of sympathy for mine.
No, sir, I have not had that privilege.
Good bye.
Horse-trading?
The army's requisitioned the lot
from the German Hospital.
Waiting to arrange shipment
to the US military post at Havana Harbor.
They can't be persuaded to part
with a lousy hundred bindles or so?
- The army would never miss 'em.
- Not for love or money.
Well, that's the Germans for you.
Never been a race better
at squeezing the life out of a dime.
I thought that was the Jews.
Nice of you to grace us
with your presence this morning.
How's Dr. Thackery? Better?
No better.
The drugs you gave me were salt water.
-Can you get your money back?
-I don't think so.
Do you happen to speak any German?
-What?
-Nothing.
Go to work, Lucy.
It's going to be a very long day.
Dr. Thackery.
Always a pleasure.
What can I do for you today?
It's more a question of what
I can do for you.
I have agreed to accept your offer
to endorse Thackery's Rejuvenating Liniment.
Uh-huh.
I think you mean
Peter's Rejuvenating Liniment.
He's a fine doctor.
Natural-born salesman, too.
Can't you peddle two of them?
That ship has sailed, Doc.
In fact, it might be
the only ship that's sailed around here lately.
That damn war in the Philippines
has interrupted my supply of narcotics.
They're prohibitively expensive
if they can be found at all.
I venture to guess that's the reason
for your coming here today?
What's in this stuff anyway?
Oh, blackstrap and
whatever else I can find for an added kick.
-Cocaine?
-Would if I could find any.
Mr. Luff,
would you consider
giving me a small advance
in earnest of the day
when the war is over
and you can sell one of these
with my name on it?
I'm afraid I can't help you.
Well, then I'm afraid
I will be forced to go to your competition.
I'm afraid they won't help you either.
You see, in our line of work,
a man has to present to the customer
a convincing air of healthful vitality.
Not to mention trustworthiness
and incorruptibility.
Please, please, please, please.
I'll do anything.
Yes, that is exactly my point.
Now, if you'll unhand me, sir,
this moldy rogue
has some business to attend to.
Nurse. Nurse. Nurse!
I don't think I know you.
No, ma'am.
They sent me over
from the hospital's nursing school.
Surgical specialty.
Well, you should have come
to see me straightaway.
I'm Nurse Braun,
Superintendent of Nurses.
Nurse...
Thackery.
Welcome, Nurse Thackery.
Scrub in and report to Herr Dr. Schmidt
in the main surgery.
Where is that, ma'am?
The other end of this corridor on the left.
And where is the drug dispensary, ma'am,
in the event I'm asked to fetch something?
Across the hall from it.
Thank you, ma'am.
What do you think you are doing?
Dr. Schmidt asked me
to fetch him some supplies, ma'am.
-Excuse me, ma'am.
-What's under your cape? Show me.
I said remove your cape. Stop her!
Stop that woman!
Get undressed in there.
Do you want me to get completely undressed?
Yes, it's advisable.
Because I'll be bleeding?
The procedure is called
dilation and curettage.
The cervix is dilated
and an instrument called a curette
is inserted to remove the...
Tissue.
Will it hurt?
No, you'll be etherized.
Cover yourself with this.
Algie.
Algie, why won't you look at me?
I can perform the procedure,
but I cannot perform it on you.
You have to.
Please.
I can't kill my own child.
What are the alternatives?
We could sail to Europe.
Liberia.
They're more tolerant there.
Europe? Liberia?
There's no place on earth
we can raise it, Algie.
-Shh.
-Are you insane?
We have no choice.
I'm sorry.
-I can't.
-Algie.
-Please.
-I can't.
Well done, Nurse Elkins.
Here, let me do it.
You're a resourceful girl.
You're the most
resourceful,
most wonderful,
beautiful girl
I have ever known.
Oh, you.
Wait, let's douse your sex with it.
No.
Let's douse yours.