The Chickering residence.
He's asleep.
Do you realize the hour, sir?
Hold the wire.
Bertram.
Bertram?
Yes, What is it?
- Telephone.
- What?
This is Bertie. Um, Bertram.
Yes.
Yes, Dr. Thackery.
I'll be right there.
And what did your esteemed chief
want so urgently?
- He needs me at the hospital.
- Now?
It had best be an emergency.
It's just some experiments.
What kind of experiment
can't wait until the sun comes up?
- Dr. Thackery.
- Ah, Bertie. Good.
You're finally here. Scrub in.
We got a lot of work to do.
Introductions. This is Lin-Lin
and this wonderful creature is Delores.
There's no chance in hell that's her real name,
but it seems to suit her.
Now, I once met a Thai girl in the profession,
swore her name was Colette Bonaparte.
I suppose it's all
part of the transaction, you know?
She pretends, we pretend.
A good time is had by all.
How long have you been working in here?
What day is it?
Strictly speaking, it's Monday morning.
Two days.
All weekend without a break?
We took a few small breaks.
Doctor, I think you need some sleep.
Nonsense. If you please.
These ladies work by the hour
and their rate is on the high side
due to their cleanliness and good humor.
So scrub in, Bertie the Wise,
for I have many new secrets to reveal to you.
Believe then, if you please,
that I can do strange things.
So what did Christiansen do wrong?
Besides blow his brains out.
I'm not sure what you mean.
All of those placenta previa cases
and the babies that he endeavored to save.
I pored over those papers
and there was nothing
that he did wrong surgically.
His problem was conceptual.
You know, he believed that
the one variable he needed to change
was him getting faster,
but there was a second variable
he never even considered.
Come on, Bertie, you've got to think bigger.
You know, widen your mental scope.
Are you tired?
'Cause I can give you something for it.
What else could have changed
about the surgery?
The patient dying slower.
Precisely!
Bertie the Wise indeed.
You know, it is such a shame that
your father doesn't share
your sort of curiosity.
That man seems to practice medicine in 1885.
But how could that be accomplished,
the patient dying more slowly?
Pressure on the tear in the womb.
To slow the bleeding. We tried that.
A wrap around the woman's abdomen.
Pressing down on specific sites.
We even tried tight bandages
around the womb.
All attempted from outside of the organ.
I intend to put pressure
directly on the bleed in the womb
from the inside.
Right, but, okay,
short of crawling up in there,
I'm not sure that could be done.
The Lord knows we've all wanted to try that
at one time or another.
But in this case, we're just gonna have to
rely on pneumatics to do the job for us.
-You know what this is?
-A Champetier de Ribes balloon.
Correct. Used in the vaginal canal
to speed dilation.
-But I don't like it.
-Why not?
Because it's French and I didn't invent it.
And it's also the wrong shape
for our purposes.
Good old American basketball.
Much more preferable.
What is that?
This is something that I invented yesterday.
Or the day before.
It's a sheath that allows the bladder
to keep its correct shape for insertion.
You know, if a penis
can make the trip one way
and a baby the other...
Look, this is what we do.
We insert the basketball bladder bullet,
the BBB,
up into the vagina, up into the uterus,
and then we leave the air tube trailing
and remaining outside.
We then remove the sheath
so that the bladder can open.
We then attach a pump to the air tube
and we pump up the bladder
inside the woman
so that it expands
and hardens against the bleed.
We then add a weight to the tube
so that it puts pressure on the wound,
slowing the bleeding,
giving ourselves more time.
Brilliant. Does it work?
Well, I've been trying it on the girls
and we need more study.
That's why we're gonna spend
the rest of the night in here,
um, inserting these into our lady friends
and testing all variables.
Um, right. Well, they're not pregnant.
So there's gonna be a problem
with the difference of the size of the uterus
-as well as the lack of dilation of the cervix.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah. That's all true.
But, you know, our budget
won't allow for pregnant prostitutes.
So we're just gonna have to make do
with what we see here.
Okay.
She looks better
this morning, more robust.
Look at her cheeks. They're pink.
That's a healthy pink.
Mrs. Gallinger,
I feel it's important to be candid with you.
Lillian's fever has gone up.
That's the pink you see.
She's not responding to light or sound.
Her fontanel's protruding further,
telling us she's got enormous brain swelling,
and it's increasing.
She's going to get better.
We've all been praying for that
and you can't give up hope
your little girl will recover,
but you also need to know there's a chance
that the Lord will be calling Lillian home.
No. No.
Everett will think of something.
There's really almost nothing...
You brought this
into our house.
You admitted so yourself.
You have to fix this.
Do something for her, Everett.
Our daughter is dying.
Eleanor, please.
You said there was almost nothing.
That must mean there's something.
What is it, Everett?
Venesection.
What is that?
- Bleeding.
- It has very little chance.
I'll take any chance.
Chinatown. Mott Street.
So long.
Thank you, ladies.
You've been such a great help.
See you tonight, Johnny?
Possibly.
Could you tell Wu that
I'll settle my tab for your services then?
Mmm-hmm.
Bertie!
You know, I think I need to make
a few small modifications to the sheath.
It might be a tad snug. Did you sense that?
I had to use a little more force than I expected.
And those ladies aren't drums.
But the pressure on those
last few attempts felt correct.
I agree, but it's all just conjecture
until we get an actual previa patient.
I'm gonna have Sister Harriet
put out requests at the other hospitals.
Any chance we can give them
is better than what they're facing now.
You know, you might consider using water
instead of air for the bladders.
It'll add more weight and might
conform better to the patient's anatomy.
Brilliant.
Bertie, fine work today.
You're making great progress.
Near as we can tell,
the typhoid started at Elihu Brown’s house
eight months ago and moved to
the Cooke house on 5th a month later.
Next came the nine guests
at the Bedford Hotel.
Uh, then it started taking it
back to your circle again
at the home of Roger Conaughton's widow.
Two of her grandchildren went down with it
as well as a garden man and scullery maid,
who may or may not have been cavorting.
You saw the look on her face, Jacob.
Cavorting was the least those two were doing.
From the Conaughtons'
to the Abbott country home in Oyster Bay,
getting the young one and the father.
Next came Cora and Daniel Hemming.
How's the young girl doing?
There have been complications
and another surgery,
-but the disease seems to have run its course.
-Hmm.
After the Hemmings?
The VandenNerfs up in Riverdale got it.
And now the Selwyn Arms Restaurant.
That's at least 11 more right there.
So what's the link?
They got only one thing in common.
Something they all
seem to be enjoying these warm days.
-The ice cream?
-More like what's in the ice cream.
A peach. Or, specifically, peach melba.
And the woman who prepared it
for every one of those people who got sick...
- Mary Mallon.
- Mmm.
A lot of places to work in such a short time.
Well, families often hire
part-time cooks for a week here or there
and then on to the employ
of some other home or restaurant.
In this case, to infect more people.
She must be a filthy thing
and sick as a cod in a cesspool.
Believe me, no mistress would hire her
if she looked the least bit ill.
Well, that's a conundrum we can solve
when we get our hands on the cow.
We got to find her first.
Families like these
use only two agencies to find their help.
Mrs. Grover's for the new money
and Bigsby's for the old.
If she's working
for the wealthy in New York City,
she's been through
at least one of those doors.
Then we're gonna have
to go through them, too.
Where are you, Typhoid Mary?
Where did you say
this machine was originally?
The fellas at Johns Hopkins had it.
They've since found a better model,
so I took it off their hands,
which is fortunate for you.
-And it works fine?
-Like it was new.
My children were taking dozens of X-rays
of themselves on it the other day.
Had the thing running for hours.
No trouble at all.
Seem to be some nicks and dents.
Well, that's to be expected
from a secondhand piece.
If you don't take my word for it,
try it out for yourself.
Never had an X-ray made.
Well, what would you like to see?
Your hand? Rib cage perhaps?
My head.
Why not?
Step right over here.
There you go. Just right there.
Now, if you would, put that plate
up to your face.
Good.
Now, the trick is
to stay as still
as possible for the best results.
There.
This should take about an hour.
Very well done.
Now you'll always have a photo
to remember her by.
My condolences, ma'am, sir.
This looks like a very solitary way
to spend your lunch.
Are you coming or going?
Going. I'm meeting Inspector Speight
for some more interviews
about the typhoid cases.
Oh.
How's that going?
We think we may have found the source.
We?
Sounds intimate.
Algie.
I don't blame you.
He's ill-mannered, his clothes are stained,
and he always seems to have
some food hanging out of his mouth.
Every woman's dream.
You think Phillip will understand?
A gentleman knows when he's been bested
and must step aside.
How's my mother feeling?
You wouldn't have to ask
if you came to the house more often.
I know. I know. I've just been so busy here.
Well, she's fine.
In fact, she looks better than you.
Are you sleeping at all?
Not enough.
Working at The Knick all day
and researching at night.
I don't know how Thackery does it.
Where does his endless energy come from?
You know all about stamina.
All those contests you,
Henry and I used to have.
That time we tried to stand on the roof
on one foot the longest, see who would win.
Ah.
I was out there for only a minute
before I felt the slightest breeze and ran in.
Henry quit right after me,
but you, you stayed out there for hours.
-Mostly in the rain.
-Hmm.
The contest was over,
but you wouldn't budge.
I think you're tougher than you think you are.
Dedicating yourself
to The Knick is no ladies' tea party.
Perhaps.
I should be going.
It was good talking with you, Algie.
Anytime.
And say hello to your secret love.
I feel like I'm looking into my soul.
Let's talk about your price.
Well, new, a machine
like this could cost as much as...
3,000. I am aware.
But it is not new,
which is precisely why I called on you.
The hospital has limited funds.
Well, I could give it to you for 2,500.
I was thinking more in the range of 1,500.
It's not just the machine.
it's ordering the photographic plates.
And who knows how long
the uranium inside will last.
I'll meet you halfway.
2,000.
Well...
It is still more than I had hoped.
But we've gone long enough
without one.
So...
2,000 it is, Mr. Luff.
Wonderful.
-Is this the new machine?
-It is indeed.
Can we have a turn on it?
Be my guests, ladies.
- How does it work?
- Allow me.
All right, closer.
Closer. Closer.
Not that close!
All right, here we go.
So it's rest and healing for several weeks
until the flap fully attaches.
And no vigorous movement.
Sadly, I haven't had occasion
for vigorous movement in quite some time.
Oh, come now, John.
I won't pretend that this
isn't absolutely ridiculous.
So, uh, I'll see you back here soon
and we'll finish the job.
Let's get you a cab.
I prefer to walk.
-Really?
-Of course.
It's a lovely day.
Well, it was looking like rain.
Yeah.
It always looks like rain
if you only look at the clouds.
Don't look at the clouds so much, John.
So you will let me
know if you receive a previa case?
Thank you, Dr. Rasmussen.
That is appreciated.
Good day.
-Dr. Thackery.
-Mr. Luff.
So what will you be attempting
to sell me today?
I have all the surgical supplies I need.
I was actually hoping to interest you
in doing a little selling of your own.
Who are the new heroes in America?
Sousa and Joplin?
President McKinley? Cap Anson?
No longer.
People now believe passionately in the
men who will bring them miracles.
Doctors, inventors, architects.
These are the new American gods.
Edison, Halsted, and Roebling.
Technology and innovation
will be the world's salvation
and the people know it.
They crave what's coming next.
And their faith... Ah, their faith is bottomless.
And you mean to exploit that faith.
No, I mean to give them the solutions
that they're looking for.
We are the supplier
of the finest medical products in the world.
We want to be the maker
of the best medicines and elixirs as well.
And with your help, we think we can be.
You want me to invent medicines for you?
That's not my field of expertise.
No need. The medicine's already been crafted.
Dr. Thackery's Rejuvenation Liniment.
Rub it on your trouble spots thrice daily,
your malady will disappear.
Look, that's your picture right there.
We're gonna run articles and advertising
in newspapers around the country.
Even send you to the Paris Exposition
this summer.
"Dr. Thackery's Rejuvenation Liniment
"treats rheumatism, neuralgia,
"sciatica, crippled back, lumbago,
"contracted muscles, toothaches, sprains,
"kidney pain, liver troubles,
"heart lameness, leg swellings,
and cataracts."
Is that all?
Those are very real claims.
Well, then perhaps you won't mind telling me
the ingredients that make up
this miracle potion.
Let's not be coy with each other, Doctor.
This is a booming market.
We want our share of it.
Last year Dr. Ayers' Pectoral Plaster,
Brown's Bronchial Troches,
Dr. Corbett's Brain Food,
and Dr. Wordsley's Female Pills
accounted for $5 million in sales.
Dr. Pepper's brain tonic is doing so well,
they're serving it at fountains
all around the city.
As much a beverage as it is a remedy.
You are one of the most
respected physicians in the nation.
And with our help, we think we can
make you one of the richest as well.
And all I have to do is loan you my name?
Precisely.
The money will roll in by the shovelful.
You'll be one of the most
famous men in America.
Nothing, nothing will be beyond your reach.
Can you give me some time to think about it?
Absolutely. How much time do you need?
Until hell freezes over.
In the meantime, would you be so kind
as to stick your head firmly up your ass?
Away, you moldy rogue.
Away.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
If you'd like five or six more,
we can just keep making circles of the park.
Making believe we've never met the vendor
every time we come 'round.
How much are your pretzels, sir?
Really? Well, then I'll try one.
So, how are you enjoying the hospital so far?
It's been seven weeks.
You've been counting?
Well, the place did get a bit rosier
when you arrived.
Do you say that to all the new nurses?
No, of course not.
I was only teasing.
I know you wouldn't do that.
Because I wouldn't.
My mother says
the first time you meet someone,
in that moment, you can know their soul.
I wish I knew that when we first met.
You were helping an edema patient into bed.
Oh.
So you remember the first time you saw me?
Don't go getting full of yourself.
I also remember
the first time I saw Mr. Pouncey
and he was picking at his ear with a twig.
I'm not sure it's true you can know someone
from the first moment,
but maybe you can get to know them
from some other moment.
Even the hardest people can surprise you.
That's where Dr. Thackery lives.
I know.
It's nicer inside than you might think.
Have you been inside?
When you had me fetch him
for the bowel repair.
Right. Right.
The evening of Mr. Gentile's
miraculous nerve block.
He had me inside while he readied himself.
That was quite a day.
It certainly was.
There's no one like Thackery.
No, there isn't.
I tried to explain it to my father
and he just scoffs.
He wants me to join his practice at Columbia.
But why would I do that
when I could be watching the man
invent the future right in front of me?
To work so closely
with a surgeon of his genius,
-it's...
-Intoxicating?
Yeah.
It means a lot to me that you understand.
I do.
I just realized I don't even like pretzels.
I, uh...
I don't know why I bought that.
Best not fix on going toe-to-toe
with the Big Nig.
He ain't no free swinger.
A fella your size can get inside and surprise.
The man's trained. Professional-like.
Knocked out Jake Kilrain in five.
Floored "Mexican" Pete Everett seven times
before they stopped it.
And took Tom Sharkey all the way
to the bloodiest draw I ever saw.
The Big Nig will kill a man like you
in that alley
and never break a sweat.
...Thursday, then I might be too late.
You know?
Hey!
What?
My deepest sympathies to you both.
Thank you, Sister.
I can only imagine
the tremendous pain in your hearts right now.
God knows your suffering.
I hope you know He's here with you.
She's going to get better.
Who, dear?
Lillian.
God will bring her back to us.
Eleanor.
You'll say a prayer, Sister?
A prayer for Lillian's return to health?
Of course.
Dr. Gallinger,
may I have a word with you for a moment?
Of course.
She won't accept it.
She even prepared breakfast
for Lillian this morning.
It's not uncommon.
Once you place Lillian in the ground,
I don't envy the powerful wave of melancholia
that will engulf this house.
Perhaps there might be a solution
to help ease your loss.
What is it?
Recently a very young baby, a girl,
was found on the doorstep of the orphanage.
I understand my impertinence,
but I've seen many a grieving mother.
Death takes not only the soul of the child,
but can destroy the souls
of those left behind.
If Eleanor can hold a baby, nurture it,
you can begin to find your way again to heal.
All I ask is that you consider it.
What are you doing here?
We have business to tend to.
-May I help you?
-Inspector Speight, Department of Health.
We were told by Grover's
Domestic Placement Agency
that a cook named Mary Mallon
is currently in your employ.
-That true?
-Oh, I don't know any of the help by name.
Of course not, but we'd like to
come in ourselves and meet your staff.
Of course. The cook is right inside.
We're just sitting down for lunch.
You're more than welcome to join us.
I'd feel safer biting into a bag of horse shit
than eating anything that twat made.
Looks like we found her. Mary Mallon?
Who's asking?
Inspector Speight
of the Health Department.
This is Miss Robertson of the Knickerbocker.
-Officer Phineas Sears.
-Well, this ain't me kitchen.
I was just hired on in the last days.
You need to speak with Miss Nisbet.
Actually, we need to speak with you,
Miss Mallon.
What's your business?
Are you the Mary Mallon who
was employed at the Hemming residence?
-Yeah.
-And prior to that,
did you work at
the Abbott's country home in Oyster Bay,
Elihu Brown's, the Haldemans',
the Bedford Hotel, and the Selwyn Arms?
What of it?
We believe, Miss Mallon,
that you may have infected
those families and others with typhoid fever.
Typhoid?
Well, you're loony. Do I look sick to you?
- No, however...
- However we've got at least a dozen infected,
many of them have already
gone to Abraham's bosom.
The one thing they got in common,
your filthy mitts.
Now, we need you to come
with us to The Knick
and give us your urine,
saliva and feces for testing.
I ain't going anywhere with you people.
I'm working and these boys need to eat.
Not what you're cooking.
This ain't an invitation.
You don't want to come,
Officer Sears and me can force you to comply.
Come now, lady.
Let's make this easy for all of us.
You want me saliva?
There!
Now the other two ain't gonna come so easy.
Grab the bitch!
- Get off of me! Get off of me!
- Stop her!
Can't you see I'm not sick,
you stupid woman?
Shut up!
Get the fuck off of me for fuck's sake!
-Shut your filthy mouth.
-Get off of me!
Jesus Christ!
I never seen a society girl
join the fracas that quick.
Definitely a new century.
Huh.
This is quinine. A teaspoon every four hours.
If she develops any pain in her lower region,
have her douche with creolin solution.
I'll make sure and check on her
in the next few days.
Bless you.
I don't know what we would do.
That'll be $8 for today, ma'am.
I can look toward
to a poor night of rest again.
Well, perhaps you need a fella by your side.
Stay out of that habit
for an hour or two longer,
you shall have no delay in finding him.
All right, Harry,
what's behind the sleeping trouble?
Half of the time I lay in bed
convincing myself
that what I'm doing is right by everyone.
Like that girl up there just now,
her floor boss forcing himself on her.
I'm guessing it's the other half
of the time that's the trouble.
That's when I lay there wondering
if I'm already dead.
Fate sealed.
And whatever good
I think I might do won't save me.
See? That.
That's the part that helps me sleep the best.
If I'm going to the furnace, I'm going.
Besides, can't be worse
than the place I come from.
Where was that?
St. Joseph's Orphan Home
in Enniskean.
The nuns were wicked cuntiballs.
Nothing like the house you run at The Knick.
These sisters, they were happy
to whale on you all the day long.
Hmm.
What's that say?
It's chicken scratch. Hmm?
Compliments of Sister Clarice.
She'd whale on my left hand with
a 3-foot dowel every time I tried to use it.
Forced me to use my right.
Taught me left-handed were wicked,
sinister-like.
She'd whack me,
giving it out till I puked myself.
A couple of years of that will turn you against
them evil goats, God, the whole thing.
You can't paint us all with that brush, Cleary.
I serve God my way.
I do His work and remain true to His cause.
Except for the abortions and all.
-I meant...
-I know what you meant.
And I know you ain't them.
I don't know much,
but I would wager that God
will put you far ahead of Sister Clarice
when it comes to passing
through the pearly gates.
She'll have one.
How long have you been bleeding?
On and off for the last few months.
And this didn't occur
with your previous pregnancies?
Not with any of the other five.
Is there a problem?
Your lower uterine wall has thickened.
And that, I'm afraid,
is your placenta out of place.
-Should I call for the surgeons?
-Yes.
Someone else.
Dr. Thackery. Bellevue just called.
We got one. It's coming in right now.
Ready?
Equipment is aseptic and ready for use.
Are you sure we're ready?
Having doubts?
It's to be expected.
Not from me.
How can you be so certain?
Perhaps a few more trials with
the female subjects.
I could help pay for their time.
I miss them, too.
They are more proof of God than
anything else I've ever seen on this Earth,
but their usefulness to us, at least medically,
has passed.
What you choose to do with them
on your own time is entirely up to you.
Dr. Chickering is now inserting
the deflated bladder,
which is sheathed to keep the shape small
while entering the vaginal canal.
We are now entering the uterus.
With this new procedure,
there is no danger of exsanguination,
as our bladder has slowed
the bleeding to a trickle.
Retractors.
The baby is alive.
The patient will live to mother it.
Gentlemen,
I give you the Christiansen-
Thackery-Chickering
Placental Repair.
Bertie.
To Dr. Jules Christiansen,
who deserves to be here with us.
-Is the paper finished?
-Almost.
I left some of my notes in the lab.
-Should I fetch them?
-No,no,no,ngo.
You should go home, get some rest.
Have breakfast with your father
and tell him all about
how you'll soon be a published surgeon.
-Good night, Doctor.
-Night, Bertie.
What the hell is this?
...how long the wax has
been impacted in there.
But that sodium bicarbonate solution
should help loosen...
-What are you doing here?
-What am I doing here?
I sincerely hope I'm in a state of delirium,
because this cannot be what it appears.
-Get them out of here.
-Just let me...
Out, Edwards, now!
This way.
The unbelievable brass on you
to think you can run a clinic
for Negroes in my hospital
like some goddamn underground railroad.
Full disclosure?
It is much, much more than just a clinic.
What do you mean?
Have you lost your fucking mind?
These people needed help
and I needed to do it.
This goes beyond disobedience
into outright negligence.
I was never anything of the sort.
Stolen equipment, unregistered patients,
procedures performed in unsterile conditions
with unqualified people.
I hope you don't believe that your association
with the Robertsons will
save you from termination.
What was I supposed to do?
Huh?
Wait around for you
to allow me into your lily-white theater?
You are a man of science.
Show me, show me any proof
that says that I should not be allowed
to work alongside you as an equal.
This is not about a disparity
between the ability of blacks and whites.
This is about lies. It's about duplicity.
This is about your lack of morality.
Morality?
Morality from a man whose own morality
allows sick and desperate people
to be turned away,
because he believes them
to be less human than he.
Edwards, you are finished.
These people cannot stay here.
You find them another place to go.
Yes, sir.
What is this?
It's for suctioning.
No cranking?
No. Frees up a hand.
Did you invent this?
Modified it from an existing product.
That's not the only thing
I've come up with down here.
My solution for the inguinal hernia.
I then separate the cord from the sac
and continue for one-half inch
around the inside of the interior ring.
And what happens if you find
that the hernia is congenital?
I separate a strip from the back,
the bottom of the sac from the rest,
and catch the cord and the testicle
using a continuous silver suture.
-Silver?
-It has incredible holding power.
Where'd you find silver suture?
Another item I had modified.
How many hernia patients have you seen?
They're not hard to find,
considering most of the jobs
colored folks can get involve heavy lifting.
How many have you lost?
-One.
-One?
Mmm-hmm.
And solely because
he disregarded my instructions
to refrain from strenuous activity.
Did you come up
with the idea for this booklet as well?
I did. It was easier than relying
on my staff down here to take all my notes.
-Where'd you get the camera?
-I bought it,
like most of what you see down here.
One of the reasons
I'm still living at that hotel.
My salary got diverted.
You endangered
your entire career with this stunt.
What if it wasn't me
that stumbled across you?
What if it was Barrow or Gallinger?
Right, because you were so charitable
when you discovered me.
I never planned on this going as far as it has.
It started with me wanting
to help one or two people.
And once the discoveries began, it...
You had to see it all the way through.
I understand.
You know, this is good.
This is better than good.
So where do we go from here?
Well, all of this ends.
But not until these people are fully recovered.
And until then, I should be able to
treat my other patients as well.
You just make sure you keep that door locked
so that no one else stumbles in here.
What about my findings?
Well, I think we'll be making that
the new standard hernia procedure.
Well, if it's the standard here,
shouldn't it be the standard everywhere?
Meaning you want this to be published?
I could never get published in this country
on my own.
But if I had a co-author...
Oh! You want me to co-author
with you on this?
As lead or as equals?
As long as it gets my name out there,
I don't care what my accreditation is.
And one more thing.
I think it's time I be allowed
to work with you officially in the theater
as your deputy chief of surgery.
I don't want you just to get me
when you can't find someone else.
And if I don't allow you?
Then I'll take my future discoveries elsewhere.
And you will miss out on all the fun.
Dr. Edwards.
Hmm.
May I officially welcome you to The Knick?
Cards.
That's a nice one. And that is a nice one.
Good evening, gentlemen.
Neely.
Come to bring your dad some good luck?
Hobart's taken all your inheritance.
Is that true, Mr. Showalter?
Perhaps just dented it a bit.
You'll get it all back
when you and Phillip are married.
Is that an incentive
for me to keep losing to you?
Just look at me as a conveyer of your wealth
to my future daughter-in-law.
If you don't mind,
I'd prefer to cut out the middleman
for the next few hands.
And how are you doing?
Will we begin our marriage penniless?
No, only down a bit,
but to my father and yours,
so we'll likely see it again.
Mmm. How's The Knick?
You still on the hunt?
Oh, Cornelia's been playing a bit of detective
alongside a health inspector.
We got our girl today.
Inspector Speight and I apprehended
the suspect this afternoon.
Apprehended? Listen to my girl.
She sounds like Big Bill Devery
down at police headquarters.
You think she can be bought as easily?
It was exciting, Phillip,
to get out into the street and do some good.
I don't know.
It was wonderful to feel so useful.
What's wonderful is to see
such a flush in your cheeks.
Congratulations, Neely.
An epidemic has been
averted because of you.
-Yes.
-A toast to my little girl.
I agree. To you, my love.
Perfect way to wind down
your tenure at The Knick.
My wife will always have the best stories
to tell her lady friends at lunch.
Well, thank you all.
It's been a long day.
-Good evening.
-Sweet dreams, dear.
Phillip, it's to you.
- 100.
- Oh!
Come in, Gertrude.
My dress is ready to be hung.
Mr. Showalter?
Dear, I've known you since you were born.
You're going to be my daughter.
Why don't you start calling me Dad?
I don't think your own father
would mind too terribly much,
do you?
Very well.
I always wanted a daughter.
We lost two in childbirth.
I'm sorry.
But now I have one of my very own.
I suppose that's true.
Phillip has given us a beautiful,
beautiful daughter in you.
I've invested a tremendous
amount of money with your father.
I believe in the union of our two families.
I know he's grateful...
I don't want his gratitude.
I did it because I believe our coming together
is a wonderful thing that will provide
rewards and pleasures for all of us.
Do you think it's a wonderful thing, Neely?
Of course, Mr. Showalter.
Dad.
Open or closed?
What?
The door. Open or closed?
Closed.
Sleep tight.