[somber suspenseful music building]
[Gilbert] I used to think of truth
as a single shining light,
an answer.
But my time in Bodkin taught me
the truth is really like light
through a prism.
Different colors,
different points of view,
a tangled mystery.
It's not Fiona.
Wh...
What does that mean?
It means it's not fuckin' Fiona.
[exhales shakily]
[rain pattering]
- [Gilbert, hushed] Seamus! Seamus!
- [engine starts]
Where are you going?
[engine idling]
I've spent 20 years in purgatory.
Finally, tonight,
I'm gonna get some answers.
[music fades out]
["Peacach" by IMLÉ playing]
[rain pelting]
So where are we going?
[music fades out]
We're off to see the King.
♪ Well, it's one for the money ♪
♪ Two for the show ♪
♪ Three to get ready, now go, cat, go ♪
♪ But don't you step
On my blue suede shoes ♪
[music continues over speakers]
♪ Well, you can do anything
But lay off of my blue suede shoes ♪
♪ Well, you can knock me down ♪
- Excuse me.
- ♪ Step in my face ♪
- ♪ Slander my name all over the place ♪
- Miss? Hello?
- ♪ Do anything that you wanna do... ♪
- Huh.
Service here is terrible.
Believe me,
no one comes here for the service.
♪...step on my blue suede... ♪
[music ends abruptly]
I'm not a superstitious man.
But fuck me if I'm not staring
at the ghost of a dead fucking badger.
[thunder rumbles]
The last time I saw you,
I promised I'd skin ya alive.
Just...
Come on. Let's keep it calm, Ed. Huh?
[breath quivers]
[sobbing]
[whimpers] Oh.
[crying] I thought you were fuckin' dead.
- [sobs]
- [pats back]
- [sobbing]
- [Seamus chuckles softly]
[sobs] Oh.
- [snivels]
- Okay.
Jackie fucking McFadden. [sobs]
It... it's "Seamus" these days.
"Seamus Gallagher."
"Seamus," eh? Hmm.
Well, that'll take a minute
to get used to.
Who's your man?
Oh, no. He's just a friend.
Gilbert.
Hi.
Eh.
I need something from you, Ed.
But you can't ask why.
No surprise there, huh?
I have to talk to the McArdles.
[hushed] Why the fuck
would you want to speak with them?
I just told you, Ed.
You can... You can't ask why.
They have not mellowed with age, Jackie.
Ed, I'm desperate.
No.
That life's behind me.
I've got a legitimate business now.
And, uh... how's your business doing?
[rain pelting]
[thunder rumbles]
I mean, it can't be easy...
running this place.
You know,
Elvis isn't the draw he once was.
Everyone loves Elvis.
[hesitantly] Yeah, sure.
But here's the thing.
Look, I... I am a podcaster, Ed. Right?
A famous podcaster.
I have a big reach.
I mean, hundreds of thousands of people.
Millions.
It's free advertising.
I mean, this could be a destination spot.
Yeah, American tourists
would love this place,
if they knew it existed.
Fine.
I can't force you to live
if you don't want to.
[engine revving]
So, the McArdles,
they sound, uh,
not nice.
I was raised on a farm up north.
Bandit country.
[mutters]
It was a different time back then.
Lot of risk, but a fuckload of reward.
Meself and Malachy dug tunnels
under the cow shed, to cross the border.
We'd move anything we could sell.
Diesel, drugs, guns.
Toilet roll.
The McArdle brothers were the same.
You know, they had their patch.
We had ours.
[inhales deeply]
But then, one day, I caught word
they'd got their hands on a big shipment.
Semtex.
Worth a fortune.
What is Semtex?
Oh. Plastic explosives.
So I had a word with a fella,
who had a word with the...
Well, Jon-Joe, Desy,
and Oisín McArdle all got nabbed,
sent down to Long Kesh,
leaving meself and Malachy
to rob them blind.
What, you... you stole their explosives?
Well, with the McArdles gone, we expanded.
Malachy set up shop in Bodkin.
You know, he'd get shipments in by boat.
I'd smuggle them up into the north. Pssh.
We had a great thing going.
Till Good Friday.
- The Good Friday Agreement?
- Mm.
"Peace in our time."
A lot of lads got released from prison.
And I'm just at home, frying an egg.
Next thing I know... boom!
Oisín McArdle kicks me door in,
waving a gun in me face,
screaming about all the things
he's gonna do to me.
[scoffs, inhales shakily]
I snapped his neck with a cast iron pan.
[sighs softly]
Yeah.
Semtex is one thing, but the McArdles
were never going to forgive me now.
I phoned Malachy, warned him
to grab Fiona, run.
I burned the farm down,
drove as fast as I could to Bodkin.
But... [inhales shakily]
...I was too late.
They were gone.
[engine revving slowly]
So if anybody knows
what's happened to Fiona,
it's the fucking McArdles.
[foreboding music playing]
[Gilbert] The McArdles. The Badger.
A decades-old rivalry
between criminal gangs.
Two bodies, lost for over 20 years,
found in the trunk of a local Garda's car.
A long night's journey
into the darkness of Seamus's past.
Fuck. This is awesome.
[sighs] Okay, I just gotta figure out
how it all fits together.
[inhales deeply] Okay, okay.
Uh... Okay. [hesitates]
Note to self... imagery?
Uh, uh, Rubik's Cube? Or a prism?
- You know, something that helps resolve...
- [door opens]
There she is.
Brónagh McArdle,
the nasty cunt.
But, wait, that's one
of the terrifying McArdles?
[chuckles] She's a little old lady.
Brónagh was married to Jon-Joe McArdle,
an absolute and total fucking psychopath.
- And even he was scared of her.
- [Gilbert] Hmm.
Oh, oh, okay. Wait.
[hesitates] Are you sure that charging
in there with a gun is a good idea?
[breathes deeply]
Yeah. You're right.
You're right. You should go.
Wh... Uh...
- O... okay. Now, that's an...
- You go in. Go in. Keep her distracted.
I'll go round the back,
and I'll get the jump on her.
Seamus, come on. Do you hear yourself?
- I'm just not...
- It's only frightening...
if you think about it.
[birds chirping]
[sighs softly]
[door chime jingling]
[wind chimes tinkling]
[inhales softly]
Oh, hello, love.
You're up bright and early.
Well, it's never too early for a souvenir.
[Brónagh chuckles]
Wow. Lovely place you got here.
Every piece handcrafted by local artisans.
Are you enjoying your holiday here?
Well, actually, I'm...
I'm here for business.
I'm a... a podcaster.
Are you, now?
I love a good podcast,
especially the true crime.
- Really?
- [Brónagh] Oh yes.
I'm listening to the one
about your man who set up a cult
and forced everyone to get married
and then kill themselves.
- [chuckles]
- [Brónagh] Do you know it?
No, I can't say I do, Brónagh, but...
[wind chimes tinkling]
[inhales softly] Maybe it's my age,
but I don't remember
telling you my name.
- [ominous music playing]
- [shotgun cocks]
[Brónagh] It wouldn't be the first time
I've cleaned blood up off this floor.
So get talkin'.
[door chime jingles]
[chuckles softly]
What the fuck am I looking at?
- [Gilbert] Seamus.
- The back door was locked.
"Seamus" now, is it?
Put the gun away, Brónagh.
You know, I didn't realize it was possible
for ghosts to put on weight.
But here I am,
looking at a fat fuckin' ghost.
Get the gun, Gilbert.
But she might shoot me.
She won't shoot ya.
I might shoot ya.
[shards shattering, clatter]
You break it, you buy it.
[tense music playing]
[exhales anxiously]
[gasps, sighs]
I'm in a bad mood now, Brónagh, so...
Don't point it at me. Point it at her!
[breathes nervously]
What happened to Fiona?
Who the fuck is Fiona?
[exhales frustrated]
Where did you bury her?
In Bodkin?
And who... whose body is that in the car?
Are you not listening to me, Jackie?
I don't know a cunt called Fiona.
And where the fuck is Bodkin?
[exhales agitatedly]
[voice breaking] Don...
Don't lie to me now.
[breath quivers]
[clock ticking]
Doesn... Doesn't make sense.
- [mysterious music playing]
- [sighs softly]
It's nice seeing you again, Jackie.
We missed you.
[Seamus] Fuck. [mutters]
[door chime jingles]
[tense music drones]
Again,
lovely place you got here.
[mysterious music continues]
- [door opens]
- [door chime jingles]
[speed dial beeping]
[ringing tone]
[line clicks]
I've just had a visit from an old friend.
["Suspicious Minds"
by Fine Young Cannibals playing]
♪ We're caught in a trap ♪
[music continues on car stereo]
♪ I can't walk ou... ♪
- [button clacks]
- [music stops]
- Be back in Bodkin soon.
- [Seamus inhales]
Doesn't matter now.
I have to leave Bodkin.
Leave? Why?
They know where I am.
But you can't just...
I mean, it's your home.
Power saw the McArdles that night,
said they killed them.
Look, Seamus...
And if they... didn't kill Malachy,
then who did?
And, like, where's Fiona?
[grunts frustrated]
What if she's alive?
[ominous music playing]
[Gilbert] You see something in that tree?
- [Dove screams]
- [tires screech]
Gonna be right back.
[engine idling]
[muffled indistinct chatter]
[indistinct chatter continues]
[Dove chattering indistinctly]
...about Power, about the car,
about the bodies.
- That's not what happened.
- What did you say about Power?
I told you not to tell him
the bodies were in Power's car.
Jesus, Gilbert!
Malachy's body... in Power's car?
[sighs] Ah, shit.
Y... You knew that?
- That bastard.
- Seamus.
- [Seamus] I'll kill him.
- Seamus!
[Seamus] I'll kill him!
[tires screech]
- [Gilbert] Shit. He's going after Power.
- [Dove] He'll have to find him first.
He was taken to Killamore General.
Had a heart attack.
He had a heart attack?
- I may have gone overboard.
- Jesus, Dove. What'd you do?
[monitor beeping regularly]
[exhales softly]
[menacing music playing]
[Seamus] You're a hard man to find, Power.
[door creaking]
I caught up with my old friends,
the McArdles,
who say they had nothing to do
with Fiona and Malachy,
which... makes sense.
Now I hear it was your car
pulled out the bog.
Which means you... have been lying to me...
[beeping quickens]
...for 20 fuckin' years.
- Seamus...
- Shut up!
[beeping continues]
Have you anything to say?
[Ruairi breathing heavily]
Malachy came to me that night.
Said the McArdles
were after him and Fiona.
I was going to get them away,
but Fiona never showed.
I went to look for her,
but couldn't find her.
When I got home,
my car was gone, and Malachy with it.
I just thought
the McArdles had got them both.
[voice whines] That's all I know, I swear.
- [splutters] That makes sense. Right?
- Why didn't you tell me about the car?
I didn't tell anybody!
I had to protect myself and my family.
I'm all Teddy has!
Something happens to me
and that boy is all on his own.
[rapid beeping continues]
[gun de-cocks]
[Seamus breathing heavily]
I find out you're lying to me...
[breath quivers]
...I'll truss Teddy up
and bleed him out like a fuckin' pig.
Bury him where you'll never find him.
Yeah?
And you can spend 20 years
wondering what happened to him.
I didn't kill Malachy.
[whining] I didn't.
I really hope not.
Hey, Seamus. Come on, calm down.
He lied to me!
And he's not the only one
who's lied to me!
Okay, ju... I didn't lie, exactly.
I was just waiting the...
the right time to tell you.
Oh, jeez! [grunts]
What else have you been waiting
the right time for, hmm?
- [breathes anxiously]
- [tense music playing]
The... the tourists... who want a boat ride?
- Mm-hmm?
- You shouldn't make that deal.
Why is that now?
There's a chance
they might actually work for Interpol.
Is that the truth, now?
[softly] Yeah.
- [cell phone ringing]
- [Gilbert huffs]
- [ringing continues]
- You should answer that.
- [Gilbert breathes heavily]
- [ringing]
- [Seamus sniffs]
- [grunts, exhales]
- [Gilbert sighs]
[ringing continues, stops]
Hey, Amber.
Um. Hi. How are you?
[mouthing inaudibly]
Oh. Oh, wow. That's...
that's amazing. You're coming here?
[softly] Crap. Wow.
[Seamus grumbles softly]
No, no, no. I'm just a little...
a little short of breath.
Yeah. [chuckles nervously]
But I can't wait to see you.
Yeah.
[spluttering] But, look,
I'm kinda in the middle
of an interview right now, so if, uh...
Yeah, okay. Okay, hon. [mumbles]
See you... See you soon.
[chuckles] Yeah.
Comin' to Bodkin, is she?
[softly] Yeah.
That's nice, Gilbert.
Happy families.
[Gilbert sighs]
[sighs]
- [somber music playing]
- [text alert chimes]
[breathes heavily]
Fuck me.
A prism breaks light
into its component colors.
- Each color is true...
- [gun de-cocks]
- [distorted scream]
- [Gilbert] ...but not the whole story.
- [soundscape distorting]
- [knife thrums]
[knocking echoes]
[Damien] Dove?
Dove, do you understand what I'm saying
about the extradition order?
[soft ambient music fades in]
[Damien] Hello?
[Dove chuckling]
There's no way they're sending anyone
to this shithole to take me home.
Fuck that.
- [Damien] Dove...
- [keypad clacks]
- [sighs softly]
- [footsteps approach]
All going well in work, then?
[scoffs shakily] If by "well,"
you mean "fucking apocalyptic."
Anything to do
with the poor man who hung himself?
[hesitates]
How do you know about that?
It's the 21st century, Dove.
I'm not gonna go gallivanting with you
without doing a little online stalking.
Yeah.
Is there anything I can do?
There's absolutely something you can do.
[instrumentals play over speakers]
[Frank] ♪ I wanna know what love is ♪
- [man 1] All right, yeah?
- [Frank] ♪ Oh, baby, yeah, now ♪
[off-key] ♪ I want you to show me ♪
- That was delicious. Let's go again.
- [Mary chuckles]
Okay, hold on. I do not want
to spend my night puking my ring up.
Shots are lonely animals.
It's cruel to just do one.
- [music fading out]
- It's not gonna end well.
[sighs deeply] Exactly.
[man 2, over microphone] And next up,
Dubheasa Maloney
with "Zombie" by the Cranberries.
- [cheers]
- That's me!
Ha! I thought you were having a laugh
when you put your name.
Oh, I never joke about karaoke.
[Mary] Oh.
[indistinct chatter]
[chuckles]
[crowd chattering indistinctly]
[Dove clears throat]
["You Were Always on My Mind"
instrumentals playing]
That's not my fuckin' song.
[piano prelude playing]
[man 3 chuckling]
- [hesitantly] ♪ Maybe I didn't... ♪
- [shrill microphone feedback]
[crowd continues chattering]
[Dove] ♪ Quite as good as I should have ♪
♪ Maybe I didn't hold you ♪
[indistinct chatter]
♪ Quite as often as I could have ♪
[sweetly] ♪ Little things
I should have said and done ♪
♪ I just never took the time ♪
♪ You were always on my mind ♪
[chattering continues]
- ♪ Tell me ♪
- [music swells, drowns out background]
[confidently] ♪ Tell me
That your sweet love hasn't died ♪
♪ Give me ♪
♪ Give me one more chance
To keep you satisfied ♪
♪ Satisfied ♪
[soundscape fades in]
- [women giggling]
- [crowd chattering]
[man 4] Come back over here!
[music fades out]
[man 2] Okay. And on that note,
we'll be taking a 15-minute break.
[up-tempo pop music playing]
[chuckles]
Who knew you had that
in your dark little soul?
I'm filled with magic and wonder.
[Mary] Hmm.
[gulps, sighs]
I just don't boast about it.
- [Dove exhales]
- [Mary sighs]
[Dove] I'll be right back.
Okay.
- [muffled music continues]
- [glass bottles clatter]
[bottles clattering]
[huffs]
[gags]
Christ. Your mother would be proud of ya.
[foreboding music playing]
[door closes]
[man 5] Watch where
you're fuckin' going, right?
[man 6] Watch yourself. God's sake.
You know who's proud?
You're the one
who's fuckin' proud, you f... you f...
you fuckin' pig.
Go away home with yourself.
You can barely stand.
You're in the shit with those bodies.
You don't think I know you're connected?
I know everything.
- [clattering]
- [glass shatters]
Who do you think you're talking to?
This is my town, ya fuckin' cunt.
You'd do well to remember that.
I know it's your car.
In the bog.
Your car with two bodies inside.
What's your town gonna say about that?
You're full of shite.
[gritted teeth] I found Teddy's knife
in the car. I know it's yours.
- Which makes you a suspect in two murders.
- [breath trembles]
What d'you think about that...
[breathes anxiously]
...Sergeant fuckin' Power?
[Emmy] Dove, stop!
D'you know what they do to pigs in prison?
- They make them fuckin' squeal! Piggy!
- [Ruairi whimpers, gasps]
- [Emmy] Dove! Dove, stop! Get off of him!
- [Ruairi gasping]
[Emmy] Stop! He's having a heart attack!
[Fagan] Call an ambulance!
- [indistinct chatter]
- [Ruairi grunting]
[mutters] What did you do?
[Fagan] Get back. Give him some space.
- [foreboding music continues]
- [Ruairi grunting]
[breathes heavily]
- [music swells]
- [Ruairi gasping]
[music fading out]
[birds chirping]
[snorts]
[groans, sniffs]
- [loudly] Mam, she's awake!
- [Dove groans]
[Dove] "Mam"?
[Mary laughing]
That's too much butter.
- Butter is life.
- [scoffs]
Oil. Oil is the answer.
It, erm, helps the pancakes
lift off the pan.
[girl] Butter, Mam. Only butter.
- [chuckles] Delicious butter.
- [Mary laughs]
Do you, eh, want some tea?
[oil sizzling]
[Dove exhales softly]
Yeah. Eh, please, yeah.
[Mary] Do you, eh...
d'you wanna flip some pancakes?
No.
So what kind of trouble
did you two get into last night?
Ah, just the, eh, normal kind.
Eh, nothing much.
Just a quick pint at Fagan's.
Your mam was drunk as a skunk.
Mam! [chuckles]
It's just a drink, Dove.
It's the truth.
[Mary] Yeah, well, not everything
needs to be spoken out loud.
No harm in it.
[chuckles softly]
What would you know about
what you should say to children?
I know lying to children
is a special kind of cruelty.
- You don't...
- Maybe if you lied less to your daughter,
she wouldn't be running around town
shooting seagulls out of the sky.
It's none of your business
what my daughter does.
[chuckles] Well, it doesn't seem like
it's your fucking business either.
You should leave.
[sighs] Bye, then.
[door opens]
- [inhales deeply, sighs]
- [door closes]
[smacks lips] So what's this
about seagulls?
[whimsical music playing]
[sheep bleating]
[Dove] What the fuck?
[intriguing music playing]
- [wind gusting]
- [leaves rustling]
- [branch snaps]
- [Dove screams]
- [brakes squeal]
- [tires screech]
[Dove] Ow.
[Dove groaning]
Dove!
Dove, are you okay?
Fuck off, Gilbert.
[Gilbert sighs] Oh.
You wouldn't believe
what happened to me today.
I'm hungover.
I fell out of a tree.
I'm getting extradited.
Honestly, I don't give a shit
about your day.
You're getting extradited?
Okay, what the hell is going on?
- Just don't worry about it.
- [Gilbert] No, I have to worry about it.
The ethical implications for the podcast
are pretty profound.
Oh, you wanna talk about ethics?
What about the ethics of you paying off
your gambling debts with Seamus's money?
Now you're pallin' around with him?
I suppose you told him everything.
About Power,
about the car, about the bodies.
- That's not what happened. I...
- What did you say about Power?
I told you not to tell him
the bodies were in Power's car.
Jesus, Gilbert!
Malachy's body... in Power's car?
[sighs] Ah, shit.
Y... You knew that?
- That bastard.
- Seamus.
- [Seamus] I'll kill him.
- Seamus!
[Seamus] I'll kill him!
- [tires screech]
- [engine revs]
- [intriguing music continues]
- [Gilbert] Nice one, Dove.
[knocking on door]
Teddy?
[bird cawing]
Teddy, I promise I'll go away
if you just open the door.
[Teddy] Leave me alone.
I, uh... I just want to...
wanted to explain
about last night with your dad.
It's...
I... You know, it's... [exhales softly]
[inhales deeply, sighs]
Look, there's no easy way to spin this.
It was his car in the bog, with the
bodies inside.
So...
you might need to prepare yourself,
because things are...
they... they're probably gonna get rough.
- [inhales deeply, sighs]
- [Teddy breathes nervously]
I... I get it, Teddy.
My mother was a spineless piece of shit.
You can't trust anyone in this life.
You only have yourself,
and you're better off alone.
But I'm... I mean, I'm... [exhales]
I'm really sorry
you had to find out like this.
[Teddy inhales deeply]
Like, it's... [breath trembles]
[breathes heavily]
It's all mixed up
in my head.
I...
I... I forget things.
I forget things, but...
but I... I remember the blood.
[breathing heavily]
Blood.
Blood and the brick. [exhales sharply]
I had a brick in my hand.
[breathes deeply]
I... I think I killed them.
[distressed breathing]
Malachy and Fiona. I...
Teddy...
[hesitating]...that... that can't be true.
But the blood!
[breathes heavily] Then they were gone.
No, the body in the mortuary,
it isn't Fiona.
[breathing heavily]
Who is it?
I don't know.
But your father does. It...
It was his car
dumped in the bog.
[Teddy sighs]
[somber music playing]
He's let you believe this all these years.
He put the blame on your shoulders
for something he did. He...
he lied to you.
You're innocent, Teddy.
But what your father did,
it's not right. It's not.
I need to go speak to him,
but I'll be back. Okay?
Just... just...
just promise me you'll stay here,
and I'll get this sorted.
It'll be fine, Teddy.
It will.
Why did you lie?
[monitor beeping regularly]
- Why?
- Look, the car was...
No, not the car.
Teddy.
You let Teddy believe
he murdered Malachy and Fiona.
[exhales sharply]
I'll tell you what happened,
but you've got to promise
to protect Teddy.
Protect him from who?
From Seamus. He was just here.
I was trying to get Fiona
and Malachy out of town that night,
but Fiona never showed.
So I went to find her. No joy there.
When I got back to the house,
the whole room was covered in blood.
Teddy is standing there
with a brick in his hand,
Malachy's body dead on the floor.
They had a fight over Fiona.
The poor boy didn't know his own strength.
[sighs] Oh God. Teddy.
[Ruairi] What was I supposed to do?
So who's the other body?
[breathes nervously] I went out
to hide Malachy's body,
and I hit
some fucking New Age Traveler girl.
That was two bodies I had to take care of.
Fuckin' Samhain! [breathes heavily]
So you sank the car in the bog
to protect you both from jail?
No! I was never protecting us from jail!
I was protecting us from Seamus!
I'd put my life
in front of my son's any day.
But if Seamus finds out the truth,
Teddy is a dead man.
- [Ruairi breathing heavily]
- [text alert pings]
[somber music playing]
[Gilbert] Once the light of truth
has been shattered,
can it ever be remade?
- [Teddy] Go away.
- [Dove] I found Teddy's knife in the car.
I know it's yours.
[Gilbert] Can you put
all the stories back together
to find that singular shining truth...
[soundscape distorting]
- [grunting, gasping]
- [Emmy] He's having a heart attack!
[Fagan] Call an ambulance!
- [Emmy] What did you do?
- [Gilbert] ...or is it broken forever?
[rock music playing over speakers]
What's up with her?
- [heavy breathing]
- [Frank] ♪ In my life ♪
- ♪ There's been heartache and pain ♪
- [Fintan grunting]
[both panting]
- ♪ I don't know ♪
- Oh my God. What's going on out there?
- ♪ If I can face it again ♪
- [pants] Karaoke night.
- Whole town's out.
- [Frank] ♪ Can't stop now... ♪
Frank always misses the fucking high note.
[both chuckle]
- Wait for it.
- [Frank] ♪ To change this... ♪
- [screeching] ♪...lonely life ♪
- [both laugh]
Wait, come on now. Concentrate.
[both panting]
[Frank] ♪ I wanna know what love is ♪
[patrons cheering, laughing]
[Dove] ♪ You were always on my mind ♪
[indistinct chattering]
- [Dove] ♪ You were always on my mind ♪
- I love this song.
♪ Maybe I didn't hold you ♪
[Emmy] She's a bully,
a hypocrite,
a fucking narcissistic black hole.
So you're the victim here?
Bullshit.
You choose to be a victim.
You manipulated me for Dove.
You're obsessed with her.
[Emmy scoffs]
No.
It's obvious. She's the power,
and you want that power.
So you're willing to do whatever she asks.
You're the beta to her alpha.
I'm not a beta.
Look at the data.
You tricked me, manipulated me,
all because she asked you to.
So either you're desperate
for her approval
or you're a sociopath.
I mean, I'm not
against sociopaths, per se.
They tend to have an excellent work ethic.
Yeah, but she's such a bitch.
[sighs] Be logical, Emmy.
The world is a series
of inputs and outputs.
All problems have solutions.
You've tried being a doormat
and letting her have her way.
But you're so much more.
So it's obviously time
to try something different.
[Dove, faintly] I know it's your car.
What's your town gonna say?
- [glass clatters, smashes]
- [woman] Oh my God!
- [Emmy sighs] God. What is she doing now?
- [indistinct arguing]
[Dove] Know what they do
to pigs in prison?
They make them fucking squeal!
- [Emmy] Dove!
- Piggy!
Dove, get off of him!
- Stop! [breathes heavily]
- [Ruairi gasping]
[Fagan] Somebody call an ambulance!
[softly] He's having a heart att...
He's having a heart attack!
[Ruairi gasping]
What did you do?
[Fagan] Get back. Give him some space.
[gasping]
[Emmy breathes anxiously]
Just get me out of here.
Get me the fuck out of here.
[soft jazz music playing on car stereo]
Stop the car.
What?
Stop the car!
- [car slows]
- [seatbelt clacks]
[jazz music continues]
- [grunts]
- [leaves rustle]
[ear-piercing scream]
[shouting loudly] I fucking hate you,
you fucking cunt!
You piece of shit! "Oh, look at me!"
"I'm so fucking mysterious!
I'm so fucking mysterious!"
"And my fucking sunglasses on
at fucking night!"
You look like fucking Bono!
I fucking hate you!
- [jazz music continues]
- [sighs]
Feeling better?
[Emmy] Mm-hmm.
[inhales deeply]
[sighs]
[gull calling]
[breathing softly]
Hi. I'm Claire.
Fintan wanted to know
if you'd like anything. Coffee? Breakfast?
[hesitates, softly] No.
No, I... I'm good, thanks.
[Claire] Okay.
[gulls calling]
[Emmy sighs]
[email notification whooshes]
[indistinct chatter]
[sniffs]
[keyboard clacking]
[email notification whooshes]
[indistinct chatter]
[gulls calling]
[chuckles softly]
Did, uh, Claire offer you
some coffee, breakfast?
Uh, yeah. Yeah. Thanks.
[inhales] I think I should head back
to Mrs. O'Shea's.
Maybe check on Dove.
That was intense last night.
I'm kinda worried about her.
- But I guess she's just driven or...
- [Fintan sighs]
...something.
You have to stop chasing after Dove.
You're not just a dogsbody.
You're more than that.
And I should know.
I hire a lot of dogsbodies.
No offense, Claire.
What do you want?
[inhales hesitantly]
Well, um,
- I... I guess... [hesitates]
- [Fintan] Listen to me, Emmy.
Once upon a time,
I was just "Shitpants" McGurk.
Now look at all these people
working for me,
on my vision for this town, on Bodkin 2.0.
You can let this world happen to you
or you can happen to it.
There's nothing wrong
with demanding what you want.
It's the only way you'll get anywhere, Em.
Demand it.
[chuckles softly]
Thank you.
- [Emmy] He's having a heart...
- [Dove] Fuckin' Power.
- Know what they do to pigs in prison?
- Sounds like a mad night last night, Edna.
- Poor Ruairi.
- [chatter continues over phone]
- [Dove] Piggy!
- Can't imagine winding up like that.
- [Ruairi gasping]
- And on camera, no less.
- [tutting]
- [Fagan] Call an ambulance!
Oh. Look what the cat dragged in.
Mr. Millionaire kick you to the curb?
Sean,
what I do with my time
is none of your fucking business.
- [Emmy clears throat]
- Just starting conversation, you know.
Have Dove or Gilbert
come down for breakfast?
Well, it seems
they didn't come home last night either.
I don't know what the hell
I'm supposed to do with all this.
I'll take care of that. I'm a growing lad.
[Emmy sighs]
Oh my God.
[Sean] What?
The body in the car, it's not Fiona's.
[metal clattering abruptly in kitchen]
If it isn't Fiona, then who is it?
[Emmy scoffs softly]
That, Sean,
is an interesting question.
How is it possible to just disappear
for 20 years without anyone noticing?
Where's my tenner?
[inhales deeply]
- [sighs]
- [banknote rustles]
[clears throat]
Gotta move quick
before ol' Mary comes back.
[girl] Uh!
Another tenner to touch it.
[inhales deeply, sighs]
[exhales softly]
[pen rustling]
[intriguing music playing]
[exhales softly]
"Greta."
Greta.
[woman, over recording] I spent months
trying to shift Darragh, but...
[audio scrambling]
[priest] You know, yourself.
A nod is as good as a wink to a blind man.
[audio scrambling]
[Maeve] Nah, not really.
We had a few business dealings
over the years.
[audio scrambling]
[Maeve] I wouldn't know.
I missed the entire thing.
I gave my pal Greta
a lift to Dublin that night.
But by the time I got back,
it was all over.
[audio scrambling]
I gave my pal Greta
a lift to Dublin that night.
[intriguing music fading out]
Got ya.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Gilbert] Stories and truths, of course,
are never as simple
as the clear light of a prism...
[horse whinnies]
[Gilbert] ...because each story creates
a new truth, a new version of events.
And light, like time,
moves only in one direction.
How can we ever hope
to look into the past?
How can we ever truly know what happened?
- [dog barking]
- [horse whinnies]
[Emmy] The other body, her name is Greta.
Maeve used her as an alibi
for the night of Samhain.
Which means Maeve
might actually be guilty...
[Dove] No.
[Emmy] Sorry. "No"?
Power killed Greta,
while he was trying to bury
Malachy's body.
Wait. Power killed Malachy?
No.
Teddy did.
Whoa.
Th... that's crazy.
Yep.
Then why would Maeve lie about Samhain?
[Dove] Is this her caravan?
There's a little window on top.
If you give me a lift up, I can probably
wriggle in and just, you know, um, go...
[inhales]
[Emmy clears throat, sighs]
- [suspenseful music continues]
- [door creaking]
[latch clacks]
Anything?
Just some old magazines
and a stash of nicotine gum.
Hello.
[Gilbert] Wait. Is that Maeve?
She said she wasn't at Samhain.
[suspenseful music building]
Wait. Look at this.
Maeve was pregnant?
No, she wasn't.
[Dove] Fiona was.
[Gilbert] Answers are funny things.
Like light, they illuminate.
But light can blind us as well...
- [Seamus] Sean.
- [Gilbert] ...hide everything from our view.
[Seamus] Shut up. Call off the deal.
The deal with those Japanese wankers,
it's off.
Just call and let them know.
Just fuckin' do it!
- [muffled creaking]
- [whoosh]
[whooshing]
[crackling]
[fire crackling]
What the fuck?
[clattering]
- [pounding]
- [flames whoosh]
[Gilbert] And then what?
- [Seamus straining]
- [Gilbert] When we're blinded...
- Fuck!
- [Gilbert] ...how can we ever see the truth?
[Seamus groans, screams]
[Gilbert] A broken light
is still better than nothing.
'Cause otherwise,
it's just darkness.
[music swells, fades out]
["Burning Love" by The Computers playing]
♪ Well, Lord Almighty
I feel my temperature rising ♪
♪ Oh, higher and higher
It's burning through to my soul ♪
♪ Girl, girl, girl
You're gonna set me on fire ♪
♪ My brain is flaming
And I don't know which way to go ♪
♪ 'Cause your kisses lift me higher ♪
♪ Like the sweet song of a choir ♪
♪ And they light my morning sky ♪
♪ With burning love ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh
I feel my temperature rising ♪
♪ Oh, help me, I'm flaming ♪
♪ I must be 109 ♪
♪ Burn, burn, burn
And there's nothing can cool me ♪
♪ Oh, I just might turn into smoke
But I feel fine ♪
♪ Because your kisses lift me higher ♪
♪ Like the sweet song of a choir ♪
♪ Oh, and they light my morning sky ♪
♪ With burning love ♪
[instrumentals continue]
♪ Because your kisses lift me higher ♪
♪ Like a sweet song of a choir ♪
♪ Oh, and they light my morning sky
With burning love ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, burning love ♪
[music fades out]