[pulsating somber music playing]
[Gilbert] Folktales are more
than just stories.
They're a warning.
In Ireland, they tell the story
of the fetch.
The fetch is
your supernatural doppelgänger,
your twin.
And if you happen to see yourself,
to see your fetch...
[music fades out]
...means you're going to die.
- [folk music playing]
- [lyrics in Irish]
[music fades out]
[in English] Guys, everyone back, please.
Move back.
- Back, back, back, back.
- [indistinct chattering]
- [man 1] Isn't that Seamus's boat?
- [man 2] I think so, yeah.
Everyone, please. Will you get back?
You can't record that either.
- [man 1] Easy.
- Sergeant?
You have to move it along now, please.
Oh... what?
I thought ye were all "#vanlife."
Jesus, lads, you're good.
Oh yeah. Come on.
[Charles] Any bodies?
Seamus?
We're sending divers in.
Well, no, but I...
I paid my pal Billy 20 euro
to go in and... and take a gander.
[chuckles] Yeah, 'tis not exactly
CSI: Skibbereen around here.
We've been tasked to work
with the local Gardaí for an extradition.
Since your superior's in the hospital,
we'll need your help in apprehending one
"Dubheasa Maloney."
[squeals]
Uh... [chuckles]
- Will I need a gun?
- No.
- Well... maybe.
We just need you to arrest her.
This is your jurisdiction.
I'll be accompanying you.
I've got you now.
[intriguing music playing]
[gulls calling]
[laptop clacks shut]
[softly] Two fuckin' years.
[Emmy] Do you think Seamus knows?
No. No way.
I mean, if he knew, he would...
- Yo, Emmy, do you have an iron?
- No.
Well, it seems like
the sort of boring thing you'd have.
[exhales] I don't have an iron, Dove.
Huh.
[sighs]
[grunts]
I've got sausages from Clon,
so thick they look like crubeens.
I've got cherry tomatoes from Ballydehob,
and I've got eggs
from my man at the English market.
Eggs. Eggs would be great.
Um. What I'd really like is some yogurt.
Yogurt?
Yeah. Or some fruit, maybe.
A banana, or...
[Edna sighs]
Hmm.
You could've at least had a sausage.
You know, they're thick as crubeens.
You don't know what a crubeen is.
No, but, you know, that they're thick.
Psst.
[whispers] Wanna see something weird?
Some papers tied with a curtain tie?
No.
It's a fucking cincture.
A belt from a nun's habit.
It's just a bunch of old utility bills,
her nursing certificate.
I... I don't really understand.
What's the significance of the cincture?
Cinctures are unique to each order.
This one's from the Sisters of Mercy.
The same order as the nuns
on Inish Mac Tire.
Meaning?
Sisters of Mercy are a nursing order.
Mrs. O'Shea has already told us that...
What the hell are you doing?
- Why do you have a nun's cincture?
- None of your business.
[papers rustle]
My past is my own.
[Gilbert] Wait. You were a nun?
I told you that.
You sure didn't.
- You said you were a nurse.
- Yeah.
I was a nurse. I am a nurse.
- And a fuckin' nun.
- I've got a headache. Please.
Please, just... Oh.
- Very fucking convenient.
- Maybe reel it in a bit, Dove.
- Are you all right?
- She's fuckin' grand.
Aren't ya, Sister?
[foreboding music playing]
It's not a doll's house, Dubheasa.
This is my home.
You come here, tearing through our lives,
and for what?
Some pale, limp retelling of a story
that you will never understand.
Now... why don't the three of you fuck off
back to where you came from?
Okay, uh, maybe we all take a breath
and just sit down
around a nice plate of thick sausages...
[Edna] Breakfast is canceled!
[music fades out]
We know Fiona was pregnant.
Teddy, the boy she had a strong bond with,
killed Malachy, only to go missing,
and appeared three days later
with a head injury.
Found by a nun.
Yeah, Sister McDonagh,
who was babbling about boats, remember?
- Sister McDonagh, the nun.
- And Mrs. O'Shea.
Was a nun.
If the Sisters of Mercy
are a nursing order,
then O'Shea could've been a nurse
and a nun at the same time.
- She seems connected.
- There's literally an island of nuns.
Yeah, everything does seem like
it's pointing back to Inish Mac Tire.
Lads, In this country,
when a pregnant woman goes missing,
the nuns are the equivalent
of "the butler did it."
They're definitely hiding something.
- [Emmy] Hmm.
- And O'Shea's in on it.
I'll book three tickets
for the first ferry.
- Today?
- Oh, what? That doesn't work for you?
I'm meeting my wife.
She flew in.
I... I kind of have to see her today.
Are you joking?
We have a sonogram. We have a lead.
This is your podcast, Gilbert.
This is what's important.
You have all night to shag your wife.
I need to see her. All right? Talk to her.
And then I'll just follow you out.
- Maybe we should wait for you.
- Absolutely not. We leave immediately.
If you're worried about the timing issue,
with the... extradition...
What extradition?
You know what you are, Gilbert?
- You're a fucking buffoon.
- [chair scrapes]
A serious man would put his work first.
Be quick, Gilbert.
I can't take her on my own for long.
- [whimsical music playing]
- [Emmy sighs]
[sheep bleating]
[bird cawing]
[Seamus huffs]
[suspenseful music playing]
[breathing heavily]
What the fuck happened to you?
Some cunt set fire to my boat,
with me in it.
Jesus Christ.
Here, have you seen
any strange fellas around town?
Huh? Northern accents?
- [Sean] No.
- [Seamus] Fuck.
Anyone comes asking for me,
you don't know me.
- Well, what's going on?
- Some old friends have found me.
[breathing heavily]
I have to leave town.
Leave? What, like leave leave?
Who's after you?
The fuckin' McArdles.
I've got some grab bags
hidden about the place.
I'll talk to Pablo and Hector.
Think I can get the deal back on track.
You, get them the eels tonight.
And then,
I'm gone.
What, so...
so, all this, I can just...
I can just have it?
Hey, did you cancel them Yakuza?
I was thinking about that, yeah.
Their offer's way better
than the Spanish lads.
- Why don't we ju...
- I don't need your fuckin' cost analysis.
Did you tell them to fuck off or not?
Yeah, yeah. I did, yeah.
Good.
[sighs, grunts]
[grunts] Fuck.
[grunting]
[water babbling]
We just need to slow them down.
Give us time to think.
I'll call you back.
I have orders here
to detain Dubheasa Maloney.
Top-secret orders, like,
if you catch my drift.
Do you, now?
[Emmy] I should have been told
about the extradi...
- It's none of your business.
- Of course it's my business.
There might be ethical concerns
if you get arrested...
If I get carted off to jail,
you'll just move on
to whatever new gig needs a dogsbody.
Never have to think of me again.
You'll be grand.
Ladies.
- How lovely to see you.
- We're here to see Sister McDonagh.
Oh. I'm afraid Sister McDonagh
has taken a turn for the worse.
Don't start, Bernadette.
We're seeing her. If you stop us...
Why don't I have Sister Clodagh see
if she's up and about?
Thank you. [chuckles]
Of course.
Why don't we wait in my office?
It's more comfortable.
[whimsical music continues]
[music fades out]
Sister Clodagh is rousing her.
Wonderful nurse,
if a tad rough.
[chuckles]
McDonagh will be glad
of our Lord's more gentle embrace.
Bit of cáca milis?
- Oh. Cake. That means cake. [chuckles]
- [Bernadette] Ah.
[in Irish] You speak some Irish?
[in English] Sorry.
I ran out of lives on Duolingo.
You have to wait for them to recharge. Uh...
[in Irish] The girls read.
[in English] One should hope so.
Oh. None for me. Thanks. [chuckles]
[in Irish] The cake is a bit...
[in English]...fuckin'...
[in Irish] ...uh, dry.
Hmm.
I've never had any complaints.
It's as dry as...
a... a...
a nun's pussy.
A country without a language
is a country without a soul.
[birds chirping]
[gulls calling]
[in English] Gilbert?
Oh, hey, Amber.
Oh my God. You look great.
- Hey. Thanks.
- [Gilbert sighs]
Yeah, I took a walk around the bay,
had something called a "breakfast bap."
It's crazy seeing you right now.
In Bodkin, Ireland, the Emerald Isle.
- [chuckles]
- Is everything okay? You seem a bit manic.
Honestly... everything's
grand.
Here.
[Dove] Did you know Fiona?
The girl who went missing? No.
I'd say you've seen the inside
of many a Mother Superior's office?
Hmm?
You're the first to offer tea.
Ah.
[inhales] I'm sure she's fed you
a tragic origin story.
[gasps] "The nuns. The nuns."
"God help us and save us,
the things they did to me."
[chuckles]
I think growing up in a boarding school
would be tough for anyone.
It wasn't a boarding school.
It was a convent.
And they didn't have to take her in,
but they did.
- That's not what happened.
- And do you know how she repaid them?
She set fire to their chapel.
That's not what happened.
After they housed her,
fed her, and cleaned her.
That's not... what happened.
Difficult thing to tag onto
the end of a sob story.
I want to see Sister McDonagh now.
She's getting ready. I told you.
[knocking on door]
Come in.
Sorry, Mother. You're needed downstairs.
[Bernadette] Ah. Thank you.
Excuse me, ladies.
[Dove sighs]
[sighs deeply]
[door clacks, rattles]
[Dove] Of course.
[sighs]
[inhales] Never trust a fuckin' nun.
[rock music playing]
♪ Well, it's been a while ♪
♪ Since I've seen... ♪
- Half.
- [Seamus scoffs]
Half?
What the fuck? Are you joking?
- Half.
- But it needs to be done tonight.
Are you good with that?
Yeah.
Then it's a deal.
Meet you at the warehouse.
We'll be ready.
[scoffs] Fuckin' grabbin' his ankles.
Listen, Sean here will be
your point of contact in the future.
Until he inevitably fucks it up,
of course.
[all chuckling]
[Emmy] Dove.
- [intriguing music playing]
- [sighs]
Dove, relax, okay? I don't think
anything insidious is going on.
- She locked us in.
- Yeah, I'd lock you in too.
She's stalling.
Probably destroying evidence as we speak.
[clacking]
Let's go find McDonagh.
[music continues]
Ireland, oh, you're gonna love it.
It's just... It's so energizing.
I mean, everyone is so lovely...
Gilbert, this isn't how
I wanted to do this.
[jaunty Irish music playing]
[sighs] But enough is enough.
[inhales deeply]
I need you to sign the divorce papers.
You can't keep avoiding this. It's time.
[music ends]
[intriguing music continues]
No.
Keep watch.
- [door closes]
- [huffs]
[ragged breathing]
[respirator whirring]
[ragged breathing continues]
That's a lovely memory, Sister.
Thank you for sharing that.
Sorry.
I must have nodded off there.
You were just telling me
a wonderful story about
Fiona.
- Sister Fiona?
- [Dove] No.
She came here about 20 years ago.
A pregnant woman.
I was telling you about her?
[Dove] Yeah, you were.
You were just about to tell me
what happened to her. Eh...
Where did she go?
She's still here, pet.
Sorry. What do you mean,
"She's still here"?
She'd watch over me as I worked.
[mysterious music playing]
She was Sister...
Dominica.
A good name, don't you think?
We'd work the hives together,
just the two of us.
Sister Dominica is Fiona?
Has she been hiding here all this time?
Bees will work
to protect the queen, you know?
Sacrifice themselves.
Anything to protect her.
It's all about the queen.
[music continues]
[buzzing]
[eerie music droning]
[buzzing continues]
[rustling]
[in Irish] You live in shadows.
[in English] Fiona's alive.
She's on the island.
- What?
- Looking for a "Sister Dominica."
- A beekeeper.
- Dominica?
Uh. Nun name. They all take a nun name.
Oh, technical term, is it?
By the way,
Bernadette's definitely lying to us.
There's no way McDonagh's
on her last legs. She's grand.
- [ragged breathing continues]
- [respirator whirring]
[exhales wheezily]
- [Gilbert] I'll do anything.
- Jesus, Gil.
No, what? Seriously.
Whatever you need
to save our marriage. Please.
Whatever you want, I'll do it. Anything.
Can you change the past?
- All I did was tell a story.
- It wasn't your story.
[sighs]
There are Reddit pages about me,
fucking fan theories...
Yeah, yeah.
Because our story touched the world.
I mean, our story, it helped people.
It didn't help me.
It exposed me.
I hired a forensic accountant. I know
that you're hemorrhaging money and...
But this podcast is gonna
put us back in the black.
For a man who spends his life listening,
there is a lot you just don't hear.
If I had to pinpoint exactly what it is
you like about podcasting,
I'd say it's recording
those fluffy intro ramblings
before every fucking episode,
where everything is still hypothetical,
still abstract, still The Gilbert Show.
Okay, well now you're making me
sound like a... buffoon.
- [jaunty music continues]
- [sighs] Things have changed, Gilbert.
We've changed.
You can't fix everything in the edit.
Please sign.
Please.
For me.
[pages rustle]
[Gilbert breathes deeply]
[music fades out]
I'll ask if anyone's seen Fiona,
slash Dominica.
[indistinct chattering]
[woman 1] Oh, great. Thank you, Sister.
That's perfect.
- [unsettling music playing]
- [soundscape muffles]
[voices whispering]
- [bell tolls eerily]
- [women chuckling]
[Dove] Mam?
Hey.
Mam? Wait!
[unsettling music continues]
Hey, stop!
Mam?
Hey, wait!
[breathing heavily]
[door creaking slowly]
[voices whispering]
[men chattering indistinctly]
- [woman 2] Breathe!
- [man] One, two, three.
[woman 3] Get her out of here!
- [door slams]
- [Dove gasps]
[women chattering]
Apparently, Sister Dominica's
down at the convent's day spa,
which is a sentence
I never thought I'd say.
- Dove?
- Uh...
Yeah, um... Yeah, fine.
Okay.
[intriguing music playing]
[nun] That's for you.
- [birds chirping]
- [music continues]
- [music fades out]
- [women chattering indistinctly]
[Emmy] You've got to be
fucking kidding me.
[inhales deeply, exhales shakily]
They're just bodies, Emmy.
Lots and lots of human bodies.
[intriguing music continues]
[indistinct chatter]
[men grunting]
Fuck you.
- [music fades out]
- Sister Dominica? You just missed her.
- She went back to the apiary.
- Oh my God. Thank you.
Dove?
[unsettling music playing]
[thrum echoes]
[voices whispering]
[girl, echoing] Mam!
[young Dove] Get off!
No!
No! Get... Stop!
Let go! Get off!
No!
Help!
- [echoes] Mam!
- [Dove breathing anxiously]
- [crying echoes]
- [disembodied voices chattering]
[voices whispering]
[young Dove] No!
- [muffled soundscape]
- [women chuckling]
[unsettling music continues]
[young Dove] Let go!
- No!
- [Dove gasps]
- [nuns grunting]
- [young Dove] Let go! Help!
- [garbled voices]
- [nun] Bitch!
- [music swells]
- [Dove gasps]
Dove?
- What is wrong with you?
- Fuck. Oh fuck, Emmy.
[breathing heavily]
It's the tea.
Sister Bernadette, she...
she put something in the tea.
- What?
- She fucking dosed me.
[softly] Emmy... I'm tripping.
Oh, come on, Dove. They're nuns.
They didn't dose you with psychedelics.
- Come on.
- [Dove mutters, breathes shakily]
My work is all about truth,
peeling away layers of opinion
and story to...
Fuck.
"Gilbert Show"? Fuck that.
[Dove breathes heavily]
- Oh, no, no, no, no. Wait up.
- Breathe.
- No, I ju... I... I... I need to rest.
- Okay.
Okay.
[voices whispering]
[unsettling music continues]
[disembodied voice, in Irish]
You live in shadows.
[voices whispering]
[Dove breathing heavily]
[Dove, in English] Mam! Hey!
Mam!
- [door slams]
- [breathes shakily]
Where's my mam? I just saw her.
Uh, yes. She was just here.
She wanted to check in on you,
make sure you're okay.
She's better?
Oh, yes. [chuckles softly]
- But...
- [voices whispering]
...didn't she wanna see me?
I think, um...
[sobs softly] When's she taking me home?
[voices whispering]
I'm sure she'll come for you soon.
[whispering voices echoing]
[crying]
[echoing whispers continue]
[crying, breathing heavily]
- [whispering ends]
- [Emmy breathes heavily]
[Dove crying]
[Emmy] Oh, um...
[Dove sobbing]
Okay, how about you wait here,
and I'll find Dominica?
No. [sniffles]
No, please. [sobs]
Please, Emmy, don't.
[sobbing]
Just, please...
just don't leave me.
- [sobs]
- Um...
[door opens]
[intriguing music playing]
[Dove sobbing]
Emmy.
[whimpers, sobs]
- [music continues]
- [door creaks]
[lights zapping]
[softly] Holy shit.
You know your nun-dosing theory?
- [indistinct chatter]
- [cell phone vibrating]
Hey. I just got here.
[Emmy] Gilbert, bad nuns.
I repeat, bad nuns.
They've dosed Dove with mushrooms.
I think they're dosing everyone.
Don't drink the tea, Gilbert.
Slow down.
What are you talking about? Where are you?
We're on our way to the apiary.
Meet us there. We need you.
But don't drink the tea.
[line beeping]
What the hell is an apiary?
[indistinct chattering in distance]
- [Teddy] Just tell me what happened.
- Teddy, there's nothing to say.
[Teddy] Come on.
[intriguing music continues]
[bees buzzing]
[Dove breathes shakily]
- Please, Emmy. I can't go in there.
- Come on.
- Come on. [grunts]
- No.
- No, Emmy. You can't make me go in.
- I'm sorry, Dove. We have to.
- Jesus, Dove.
- No, Emmy, you...
- You don't understand. I...
- It'll be grand.
- [Dove gasps]
- [door slams]
- [breathing heavily]
- [bees buzzing]
[exhales]
- [soundscape distorting]
- [breathing heavily]
- [bell tolls]
- Mam?
- [intriguing music continues]
- [breathing softens]
[lighter clinks, zips]
[bees buzzing]
[unsettling music playing]
[voices whispering faintly]
What is wrong with you?
You selfish, stupid bitch.
[flames whoosh ferociously]
[music intensifies]
[softly] What?
[breathes heavily]
[in Irish] We all live
in each other's shadows.
[whispering voices echoing]
- [music ends abruptly]
- [bees buzzing]
[in English] Are you Sister Dominica?
Mm-hmm.
You're not Fiona?
Who's Fiona?
[softly] Great.
[sighs]
[birds chirping]
[water babbling]
[Teddy] Tell me what happened.
I know something happened.
[Maeve] Teddy, you need to calm down.
- [Teddy] I know you know something.
- [mysterious music playing]
- [Maeve] I can't help you, Teddy.
- [Teddy] I remember your boat.
[Gilbert breathes heavily]
[Teddy] Why won't you just
tell me the truth, Maeve?
[button clacks]
I know something happened on this island.
I... I know you know something.
[breathes agitatedly] I don't.
[Gilbert] Liar.
I know you lied about being in Dublin
the night of Samhain.
And I know Fiona was pregnant.
I, um...
I... I ran out of Dad's house
to find Fiona.
I... I saw you down on the pier.
Fiona asked me to sail her to Wales.
But you didn't get there, did you?
[birds chirping]
[Gilbert] How'd Teddy get hurt?
Maeve, how did Teddy get hurt?
We were loading up,
and he just came outta nowhere.
I thought you were Seamus
coming after Fiona. [inhales sharply]
I lamped you with an oar.
[Teddy breathes deeply]
So you brought him here,
because you knew there was a nurse.
Mrs. O'Shea.
- It was quicker than going to a hospital.
- And Fiona?
[Maeve sighs softly]
You were here when Teddy was young.
He was a golden boy.
Smart, outgoing,
could've done anything.
You destroyed that.
[breathes shakily]
It was an accident.
[Gilbert sighs]
What happened to Fiona?
[Gilbert] Tell us, Maeve.
Tell us what happened to Fiona.
[coughs]
[Emmy exhales] You okay?
Thanks.
[retches, vomits]
[Emmy scoffs]
- Sorry.
- [sighs]
[softly] God.
Well, that was a waste of time.
Were you high when you were talking
to Sister McDonagh?
[sniffs]
Yeah, I think so.
[breathes heavily]
She was an angel for a bit, and
there was a bee in her bed.
Eh, what exactly did she say?
Why did you think
Fiona lived on the island?
She said Fiona used to
watch over her... [retches]
[gulps]...while she tended the bees.
[vomits, coughing]
[sniffs]
[Emmy] Dove.
There's no name, no date. Just...
What's that word?
Máthair.
It means "mother."
[Teddy] I...
I don't understand.
We sent you home.
But Fiona was worried
she'd missed her opportunity.
Seamus was in town and on the warpath,
looking everywhere for her and Malachy.
She stayed here.
She was safe.
And with Edna taking care of her
and me running supplies,
she had everything she needed
to deliver the baby.
[Bernadette] What is going on here?
What are you doing?
This is a most egregious transgression.
You have no right to come in here...
Maeve.
What happened to her?
Not a word
to anyone about this.
You must promise.
- [button clacks]
- [mysterious music playing]
[Bernadette] She was early.
We were prepared, but
she died.
She and the baby both.
31st of May, the Feast of the Visitation.
The day Our Lady went
to visit her cousin, Elizabeth,
who was also pregnant.
You don't get too many stories
in the gospels about just women.
It is one of the most joyous feast days
in our calendar.
- [Dove grunts]
- [Bernadette gasps]
Oh. Dove! Dove!
Shit. Dove!
[Seamus] Sean's a fuckwit,
I know, but you know,
he's harmless.
I'm sure he'll be here any minute now.
[tense music playing]
[Hector grumbling]
What the fuck is that?
- [hollow metal clangs]
- [Hector] Where's my eels?
[hollow metal clanging]
[tense music intensifies]
Fuckin' Sean.
[breathes irately]
I'll fuckin' kill him.
He's a dead man!
Fucking dead man!
- [kettle whistling]
- [music fading out]
I was just smoking in the chapel.
I didn't mean to burn the fucker down.
- [whistling subsiding]
- [water bubbling]
But I also wasn't sorry about it.
I can't absolve you, you know.
- My mother was an addict.
- [water pouring]
[Bernadette] She was ill.
She left me at a convent.
[Bernadette] There are worse places.
And then she got clean.
Such a stupid expression.
[Dove] I saw her once... after.
She came back to the convent. She...
She didn't even wanna see me.
[inhales shakily]
I thought she hated me.
Maybe she hated herself.
Maybe she was a woman of limited choices.
Or maybe she was...
Kind of an arsehole.
You can only ask forgiveness
for yourself, Dove.
Maybe she loved you, maybe she didn't.
Which story do you want to tell?
[voice breaks] The one
where I was good enough.
[footsteps approaching]
Personally, I've always preferred
confessing face-to-face.
And what would a Mother Superior
have to confess?
[chuckling] Oh.
Oh, Dove, the way it all played out,
it lies heavy on my immortal soul.
I buried a woman here on my island
and demanded silence from my flock.
Hardly the actions
of the pure and the chaste.
But I, too, had responsibilities
to a story.
[clicks tongue] I'll be honest,
I thought you were gonna
ask forgiveness for fucking dosing me.
[Bernadette] Ha!
- And your poor penitents.
- [chuckles]
They come here searching for revelation.
And we deliver.
I have to believe
that the ends justify the means,
and I'd assume
that you're of like mind in that regard.
[knocking on door]
Ah. I'll leave you to catch up.
- [door closes]
- Something's up.
Bernadette just said she buried Fiona.
Only Fiona.
And the grave just says "mother."
The Catholics have pretty famous ideas
on babies in wombs.
I googled the Feast of Visitation,
and it said...
The dates don't match up
with the sonogram.
- Bernadette's lying.
- [Dove sighs]
[door opens]
Dubheasa Maloney,
I'm placing you under arrest.
I'll ask you now to come with me.
Fuckin' nuns.
- [footsteps approaching]
- [handcuffs clatter]
- [dramatic music plays]
- Go, Dove! Run!
Run!
Ow! God!
Ah! Oh!
- [screams] Ah!
- What the...
- [music fades out]
- Ah!
Oh!
Fuck!
- Ends justify means?
- [Gilbert screams] Ah!
- Something like that.
- [Gilbert whimpering] Oh God! Oh fuck!
[handcuffs clacking]
Oh my God!
- [Gilbert cries out]
- [Eoin] Told you I needed a gun.
- [Gilbert cries out, groans]
- [Charles] We'll be back for him.
[coughs, whimpering]
Fuck.
Ah. Come on, loveen.
They're waiting to take you
back to the mainland.
And you don't want
to keep the Gardaí idling.
[smacks lips] 1997.
1998.
1999.
Huh. [chuckles]
Mrs. O'Shea isn't in this one.
The year she left.
That was a traumatic year.
A mother and her unborn child dying.
Only the child didn't die, did he?
Do you think I'm an idiot?
Mrs. O'Shea didn't leave the order
and adopt a Romanian child.
- [intriguing music plays]
- She left with Fiona's healthy baby.
Sean.
Sean is Fiona and Seamus's child.
[exhales shakily]
Jesus. [breath trembles]
Would you people ever just fuck off?
[inhales deeply, huffs irately]
[breathing shakily]
[intriguing music continues]
It's grand, okay?
Everything's grand, I promise.
Do the hand-over tomorrow.
Shouldn't be a problem.
But just to clarify... Seamus will be there?
Things have changed.
[exhales] I'm the man now.
[crowd cheering in distance]
[Gilbert] To see yourself,
to know yourself,
to speak your truth,
isn't that the prime currency
of our modern world?
- [cheering continues]
- [drums pounding]
Dove,
do you think that looks like me?
The Irish know better than that.
To see who you really are
means something has to die.
'Cause who can really live
with themselves?
[music fading out]
["Don't Cling To Life"
by The Murder Capital playing]
♪ Don't cling to life, don't cling to life
There's nothing on the other side ♪
♪ There's nothing on the other side ♪
♪ Don't cling to life
Don't cling to life ♪
♪ There's nothing on the other side ♪
♪ With all your chances gone awry ♪
♪ To be collected by your palms ♪
♪ If I had only stood aside ♪
♪ With dour sediment in hand ♪
♪ Forego delusion to disarm ♪
♪ Then dance around your lonely cave ♪
♪ In my relentless state of charm ♪
♪ Let's stay enclosed for all our days ♪
♪ It feigns a deadly grip ♪
♪ The world collapses 'round my room ♪
♪ The water floats, the floor's adrift ♪
♪ Your eyes demand the darkest blue ♪
♪ With hands held tight
It goes and goes ♪
♪ The light that once shone on the pale ♪
♪ Our steady hands return to stone ♪
♪ Let's stay enclosed for all our days ♪
♪ Failing this, let's dance and cry ♪
♪ So we remember why we die ♪
♪ We remember why we die ♪
♪ Yeah, failing this
Let's dance and cry ♪
♪ Failing this, let's dance and cry ♪
♪ So we remember why we die ♪
♪ We remember why we die ♪
♪ Don't cling to life
Don't cling to life ♪
♪ There's nothing on the other side ♪
[music ends]