I don't see why things have
to change.
Because you keep putting it off.
You said that you were ready!
Do you even want to move in
together? Stop asking me, OK?
I just... I just need some space.
If you don't want me here,
I can go. No!
I didn't mean that!
You're not listening to me!
Do you know what? I am listening.
I loved you.
And I wanted to know you. And
you don't even like that about me.
Firing order received
on the broadcast.
Repeat. Firing order received
Weapons Engineering Officers to
the control room.
Repeat. Weapons Engineering Officers
to the control room.
Weapons Engineering Officer's
here, sir.
Firing orders received.
In the clear.
Stand by. Stand by.
Firing orders received.
Firing order received 0100.
Ship Control, bring the submarine to
Action Stations Missile
for a missile launch.
Adams! Sorry, we're getting the boat
to launch depth.
Adams! Ah!
Action stations. Action
stations. All compartments close up.
Submarine is going to ordered
launch depth.
The firing unit keys have been
issued to the SMO.
WEO command, set condition 1SQ.
You all right there? Yeah.
Yeah. You're hurt, we should get you
to the medic.
No, I'm... Repeat, launch procedures
have been authorised.
Set condition 1SQ.
Take the submarine to
ordered launch depth.
Is released for launch.
Commander, at launch depth.
What? What's happening?
Better get her out.
What? No!
Out of the control room. Now.
Amy, you've had your instructions.
You need to leave the control room.
Instructions?
What's wrong with your head?
Nothing, I just banged it.
Weapon System in 1SQ. Weapon System
in 1SQ. WEO, Command, roger.
What did he mean, weapons?
Out you go, Amy.
WEO, Command, you have my
permission to fire.
What? STOP!
Amy!
It's just a drill. It's just
a drill. It's just a drill.
It's just a drill.
Launch drill
completed.
Repeat. Launch drill completed.
Get her to the sickbay.
Amy.
Carry on, everyone.
Um...
Amy.
Amy, are you OK?
Are you all right?
# Do you want me on your mind?
# Or do you want me to go on?
# I might be yours as sure as
I can say
# Be gone, be far away... #
You made a statement to the Navy
regarding an incident
in Port Havers.
That's part of an ongoing inquiry.
You'll need to speak
to my superiors. We have.
What happened in Port Havers is
highly classified so whoever
leaked it to you is breaking the law
and compromising national security.
Now, you know that you are obliged
to co-operate with us today.
And failure to do so will see you
facing charges.
In the best-case scenario,
that's your career gone.
I haven't shared my information
with anyone.
You met with Patrick Cruden
this afternoon.
What was the nature of that
conversation?
How long have you been following me?
Did you discuss
Port Havers with him?
He was trying to help me
find Jade Antoniak's killer.
You haven't answered my question.
He suspects the Navy covered up
an incident in Florida,
but he doesn't know what happened.
Well, obviously, you're concerned
about the information Cruden is
leaking to the press.
I assume you were aware of his
relationship with Jade.
We're familiar with her. Yes.
Was MI5 running surveillance on
Dunloch peace camp?
We monitor them.
Their activities, who they talk to.
But it's a light touch.
Why do you monitor them?
All the reasons that you'd expect.
Most of them are harmless,
but not all of them,
especially when they link up
with other activist groups.
In August there was a demo which
involved three groups
and it got violent.
Jade told me you had operatives
in the camp.
What were they doing there?
DOOR OPENS
You've had plenty of time to
ask your questions.
Anything else you can
submit in writing.
Let's go.
Whilst we respect your
independence...
That's very gracious of you.
..there are issues of
national security here.
We need you to keep a dialogue
open with us.
Yes.
We'll be sure to go through all
the proper channels.
I had no choice in the matter.
By the time they told me, you were
already in with them.
They've been following me
since I met with Cruden.
Maybe earlier.
So, what did you get out of them?
I asked about operatives
in the camp.
They didn't give me a straight
answer.
I've got a few ideas, though. OK.
Let's get you home.
We can pick this up in the morning.
Fall out from Action
Stations.
Second watch. Watch dived.
Second watch.
Are you all right?
Could you tell the Cox'n I'd like
to see him?
I'll meet him in his office.
Yes, ma'am.
Your team come up
from there. Yeah.
And then we come down from
there. Yes.
Actually, can I leave that with you
for a second? I'll type it up.
Tea or coffee? Hm?
Or, I mean, you could try the soup
if you're feeling masochistic.
Kirsten Longacre. DS. I just
transferred from CID.
Amy Silva. DCI. I know.
When did they put this machine in?
When the clamour for bad soup got
too loud to ignore.
I wanted to ask you something,
if you don't mind.
I've got my Inspector
interview coming up
and Robertson said that you would be
the best person to help me prep.
Now's not a good time. Sorry.
OK. No worries.
Can I buy you a hot chocolate?
No. I'm good.
No, I'd like to.
Erm...
So, what would you say is the
biggest mistake people
make in their interviews?
Mm.
Yes? Yeah, five minutes.
Thank you. OK.
Thank you, that is all I need.
They said you were waiting for me.
Why didn't you tell me
it was a drill?
It's our job to complete the test as
quickly as possible.
Not to calm you down.
How are you feeling, anyway? Are you
OK? I think you should sit down.
Are you having an affair with
Tiffany Docherty?
What? I think you're the man in
those pictures.
And Craig Burke was using them
to blackmail you.
He needed information on Port
Havers. On the two contractors.
The accident. You knew about that,
didn't you?
I can't... I can't discuss that.
He was going to leak it to
the press, exposing the Navy's
cover-up. I think he needed your
help to do that.
No, it wasn't like... OK, if you're
not going to be honest with me,
we can go to the Captain. We can
have this conversation
in front of him.
So now you're blackmailing me, too?
So you did help him?
So, when did he approach you?
Just a couple of weeks
before the patrol.
Did you give him any evidence?
Any proof it happened?
There wasn't any. Not that I would
have given it to him
even if there was. He must have
needed something to go to the press.
Otherwise the Navy would just deny
the whole story.
And he had that photo of you,
so he could have just kept pushing
you, asking you for more.
He had the power to ruin your
career, your marriage, your family.
The only way that's going to go
away is if Craig Burke did.
So...
Are you implying that I had
something to do with his death?
You were with him the day of
the trawler.
You've lied to me throughout this
whole fucking investigation!
What! This is... This is ridiculous.
I didn't kill Craig Burke!
How would I have even done
that anyway?
Do you know what? It doesn't even
matter what you think any more.
Not after that stunt you pulled
today in the control room.
Excuse me? Everyone on this boat
thinks that you are deranged!
It was only me that didn't.
Now you're on your own.
Rough night?
I've not slept much.
I've gone through all this footage
from the loch-side the night Jade
was killed. So far, not much.
Leave that for a sec, there's
something else I want to look at.
Jade told me that she was in a train
station on her way
back from a protest
and she recognised someone.
Now, she thought he was MI5.
And I'm thinking... Well, no,
I'm hoping
that maybe a camera picked it up.
Do you know when? And which station?
MI5 mentioned a protest that got
violent in August.
You could start there.
Yeah. That was here in Glasgow.
OK, well, let's look at both ends of
the line, Kirkmouth
and Glasgow Central.
See if we can spot Jade.
No-one gets it first time.
No-one.
Well, that's good to know.
Any tips, though?
Even just to fill the silence.
Yeah, don't be too nice.
Don't be an arse, but just don't be
too nice either, you know?
You don't have to please everybody.
Not everyone deserves it.
Spoken like a true misanthrope.
You've sort of got to be,
haven't you?
It's part of the job description.
Trust no-one, don't get
emotionally involved.
Have you ever thought about
motivational speaking?
A great detective shuts herself off.
She focuses on the work at the cost
of everything else.
So, what you're saying, then, is...
..accept total loneliness.
OK.
Do you really believe that?
Yeah, wholeheartedly. Oh.
So you do have a heart, then?
Despite what you're claiming?
No. Not when I'm at work I don't.
Aye. But you're not always
at work, though, are you?
Breakfast, ma'am.
Erm, thanks.
I just heard about your son.
Found out this morning.
He's getting out. That's amazing!
They're just letting him go?
I think there was new evidence
or something.
Anyway, he'll be back home
waiting for me.
I can't believe it! I know!
I need to get back to this, hen. OK.
DCI Silva, I need you in sickbay.
What for?
I need to run a check-up on you.
Captain's orders.
OK.
Mm, you haven't taken your
pain meds.
I told you, I feel fine.
OK, what's going on?
KNOCKING
Surgeon Lieutenant Docherty,
can I have your report?
DCI Silva's injury is superficial.
No evidence of concussion.
It's harder to say about
the medication.
Sorry, what? It's been brought to my
attention that you have
a serious medical condition, for
which you brought
unauthorised medication on board.
Yeah, OK, I don't know
what's been said... What are
the effects exactly of withdrawal
from that medication?
Trouble sleeping.
Poor balance.
Anxiety.
Psychosis is rare, but it
can happen.
Do you think that might account for
your outburst this morning?
I never told you about
my medication.
You did mention it. No.
Look. We're just trying to help
you, Amy.
We're worried about you. That's all.
Oh, that's... That's kind.
Look, Captain, this is some kind of
an attempt to undermine me.
I witnessed your behaviour.
I'd just woke up and no-one told
me it was...
You know I didn't tell you about my
medication.
I'm certain of that.
So, Lieutenant Docherty must
have told you.
You know these two are having an
affair, so this isn't about me.
This is about them trying to make me
look... Cox'n assures me that there
has been no inappropriate contact.
OK, I need to interview the Cox'n
under caution.
Craig Burke was gathering
information on Port Havers.
He was going to take down the whole
boat, and the Cox'n knew that.
He's already admitted to me
that Burke was blackmailing him.
Do you have any evidence? That is
what I'm trying to do.
I'm trying to gather evidence but
you're not giving me the appropriate
assistance. How so?
You failed to mention the sinking of
the trawler.
You failed to mention Port Havers.
That is classified information which
has no bearing on this case.
That isn't for you to judge.
DCI Silva, I can't have you in
questionable health,
disrupting drills, and making wild
accusations.
I think you're unfit.
You're relieved of your duties.
You don't have the authority to
do that. I do.
And you'll stay in my cabin
for the rest of the day.
You'll rest and you'll follow
Lieutenant Docherty's advice
regarding your health. There is
someone on board Vigil who
is dangerous.
I am trying to help you find out
who that is.
I need your full support right
now. Why don't you...?
Convince the medic that you are fit
for duty, and we'll revisit this.
If you can't do that, I will confine
you to quarters
for the duration of this patrol.
Yes?
Lieutenant Docherty will escort you
to my cabin now. Sir.
Ah, cheers. There you go.
Here's Jade.
This is just outside Central Station
on the day of the protest.
I've gone through all the cameras in
the area and picked up this guy.
That's an ice hockey jacket.
Can we get any closer?
She just took their photo.
Did they see her take that?
Do we have footage inside
the station?
Hasn't come through yet. Not sure
what we'd get on
that other guy, though.
Can't make out much with the cap.
So, we know her phone is missing.
Maybe someone took it. What else
have we got?
We've pulled the local shops,
the car park, street cameras...
Try the car park.
There! That's him there.
Let's get an address for that car.
Car's registered to a Peter
Ingles, 44.
Not much on him. No arrests.
He's home.
INTERCOM BUZZER
He's on the move!
There's got to be another way out.
Bring the cars round the other side!
SIRENS
THEY GRUNT
HE GRUNTS
Peter Ingles, you are under arrest
on suspicion
of the murder of Jade Antoniak.
Do you recognise this woman?
No.
Are you sure? Look again.
Her name's Jade Antoniak.
She would have recognised you.
What do you mean?
If she recognises me, why don't you
bring her in here?
Maybe she can tell me
what this is all about.
What happened to your shoulder?
It started bleeding when I tackled
you to the ground.
Custody sergeant said you refused
medical attention.
I'm fine.
No. I don't know about that.
See, I think if we had that
examined, we would find a wound
there.
Made by a pair of scissors
about three days ago.
This is all clearly
a misunderstanding.
You left blood all over my carpet,
Mr Ingles.
You're not getting out of this one.
I'd like to contact my lawyer now.
They're only antihistamines.
I can't force you to take them,
but I hope you will.
Coming off antidepressants can be
really nasty,
so these will help.
Look. I know you want to protect
him, but...
Covering up for him, that's not
going to help you.
I'm not. He's a liar.
He's certainly lied to his wife,
but you knew that.
Doesn't it matter to you that you
can't trust him?
Get some sleep, OK?
How is she? Not good.
You could've told me you were going
to the Captain.
I was just trying to protect you.
Oh, were you?
Yeah, of course. I need to go.
If you didn't know Jade Antoniak,
how do you explain us
finding this outside your flat?
A digital forensics examination
has managed to
recover 17 of the 20 integrated
circuit card numbers.
They're a match with her SIM.
Was it you she was meeting the night
she died?
Or did you go after her because you
realised that she was onto you?
Did you know that she'd taken photos
of you and your colleague?
Why were you targeting her?
You should co-operate.
This, the bloodstains.
See the big picture here.
Mr Ingles, are you an MI5
intelligence officer?
KNOCKING
Well...
This has been fun.
What the hell's going on?
The man you interviewed
isn't Peter Ingles.
It's Piter Vasiliev.
He works for the Russian embassy
and he has full diplomatic immunity.
He's a GRU intelligence officer.
Are you saying he's a Russian spy?
Yes. And I'm afraid we have to
let him go.
He murdered Jade.
You don't know that.
And he's the man who attacked me.
Him and another. Kirsten,
there's nothing we can do.
We can't let him go!
The only thing we could do is
talk to the Russian embassy
and ask them to waive his immunity.
And we've done that and it's a no.
He'll leave the country today.
And after that the Foreign Office
will take it up as an issue.
It's not an issue!
He killed a girl who was barely in
her twenties!
I'm afraid we have no choice in
the matter.
If you'd kept us updated on your
investigation, like we asked,
we wouldn't even be in this
situation. No.
I don't accept that.
We could have watched him.
And maybe even figured out who
he works with by now.
Isn't it your job to know
that in the first place?
Do you have any idea how many
Russian intelligence officers
there are currently operating in
the UK?
Our sources gave no indication
of him being active in that way.
Intelligence officers with
diplomatic cover usually just
run agents. They keep their
hands clean.
So, this level of interference is
practically unheard of.
Jade Antoniak managed to figure out
that something was going on.
I think I have something.
Thank Christ!
I found this.
It's an online thread
about fishing
that Peter Ingles has been posting
on from this laptop.
Someone's responded with more.
But these aren't Ingles'
personal images.
They're from all over the world.
I think it could be some
sort of code
hidden in the pixels of the photos.
It's possible...
We can decode these
and look for encryptions
in the pixels.
Who were they being sent to?
We'll look at the responses
but it's likely they were sent
on a public network.
How often are the exchanges?
A few times a week.
Mostly concentrated over
a fortnight, before they stop.
When was the last one?
It says here, the 30th of August.
That's the day before Vigil
went out on patrol.
Navigation, alter course to the
south, head for the shipping lane.
Aye, sir.
We're changing course?
New orders.
We need to take additional measures
to avoid detection.
Keep the team alert, Cox'n.
No more close-quarters situations.
Yes, sir.
Maintain depth
between 50 and 60 metres. Yes, sir.
Oh, God, I don't...
I really don't do this.
Oh! Not on a school night.
Well, I mean, that's good to know.
Cos nobody should be drinking
this much whisky. No. Mm-mm.
But it's a special occasion, so...
Mm-hm. Very true.
Actually, on that,
here's to fucking up my interview.
Again. Again. Oh, God, again.
You look different
when you're having a good time.
What? What do you mean?
I dunno, it's like your whole face,
like it opens up. My what?
It does. It's lovely. It's love...
Oh. Um... I'm sorry.
I'm sorry,
I shouldn't have done that.
I'm not.
I did know that.
Erm...I did know that.
Oh, God, I'm going to go.
Just cos we've got an early start.
Based on the evidence
that we found at Ingles' flat,
we're convinced that he was
responsible for Jade's death.
And given the pattern
of messages that he sent,
we think it's possible that he was
in contact with someone on the boat.
So, you're saying there could be
a Russian asset onboard Vigil?
No, this is...
I—I don't believe that that's...
They're all vetted. Yes,
but you have hundreds of sailors.
People can slip through. We don't
have solid evidence of it yet.
We're just trying to establish
any possible connection to Burke.
As in...Burke was a Russian asset
or...Burke was killed
by a Russian asset?
These are the questions.
We think Burke was a whistle-blower.
I can't see the Russians
targeting him over that.
If anything, they would
encourage a whistle-blower.
Embarrassing us is a win for them.
Unless he was going to be talking
about Russian spies in the Navy.
Oh, come on.
This is...fanciful stuff.
We have presented an area
of concern. What about you?
Is there anything we should know?
Look, none of us are used to
opening our books to each other
but we cannot afford to hold back.
Not now.
Right. Nothing about Russians.
However...
..there are concerns about
the trawler that went down
off Barra Head.
At the peace camp they're saying
it was dragged down by a submarine.
It was. An American submarine.
We identified it
from the tiles that came off
when it hit the trawler net.
We have confronted the Americans
and they have admitted it.
They'd been shadowing Vigil
since she left port.
Why would they do that?
They won't disclose that.
And why wouldn't they tell you more?
Well, I think in the light
of Mr Peter Ingles,
they're going to have to
give us something.
I'll have the conversation.
..it wasn't until after
that I realised what happened
in the first place and then...
Sir? Come and have a look at this.
Two seconds, Jack.
Walsh, what are you doing here?
You're supposed to be stood down.
Yeah, I know, sir. I've been coming
down to check these padlocks...
You see, it looks fine.
Then you turn it over.
We used to jimmy locks all the time
when I was a kid. That's been
tampered wae.
The RCMS panel is in here.
You could use that
to force a reactor shutdown.
Keep this to yourself until
I've spoken to the Captain. OK? Sir.
SHE GASPS
Oh, God.
Oh, I didn't mean to wake you.
I just brought you some scran.
That's OK.
Thanks, Jackie. That's good news
earlier. About your son.
Must be a relief. Yeah, it is.
What happened to him?
He just...
He made some bad choices.
Teenage stuff.
Got in some bother.
He was in prison?
I'm not judging, I... I see kids
all the time make mistakes.
Sorry, love, I shouldnae be
talking to you.
I've left some extra pudding
to cheer you up.
Your report said you followed
Vigil for "operational reasons".
Were you concerned that Russia might
be planning something with Vigil?
I have told you what I can.
Well, with respect, you'll have to
do better than that.
The Americans
were concerned about the patrol
but rather than share their concerns
with us, they chose to shadow Vigil.
They didn't want to risk
their source.
Do they have any idea
what the Russians are planning?
No.
We'll need to brief Downing Street.
Right, Branning,
would you set that up, please?
Yes, sir. Thank you.
Can you call Vigil back
without a replacement ready?
They won't want to do that.
They need proof of an active threat.
Will you at least inform the
Captain? Yes. But the question is,
what can Newsome do about it?
If he puts guards on key systems,
they'll realise something's up.
That in itself
could provoke an action.
If there's a traitor onboard,
we need a name.
That's how we protect Vigil.
Are you absolutely sure?
Yes, sir.
Walsh found that there was clear
signs of tampering.
It's the only explanation
for the reactor scramming like that.
Sabotage?
I've spoken to everyone
who was on watch during the scram.
None of the back'afties saw any...
Say no more for now.
We'll have to investigate
without drawing attention. Yes, sir.
What are you doing here? I was going
to ask you the same question.
I came to see the Captain,
instead I find a rating outside,
guarding the door.
I've been confined to quarters.
Again.
Unlike you. Right.
Hm.
Look...the Captain
definitely has his faults,
but he also has to make
some very difficult choices
and this is a...demanding job.
I'm not sure I trust him.
Oh, I think you can.
I appreciate that's a little bit
rich coming from me but... No.
Cos I know which lies you told
and why you told them, so...
As it stands, you're the only person
on this boat that I do trust.
Hm.
Right.
Do you know anything about
what happened to Jackie's son?
Oh. Yeah,
that's a horrific situation. Um...
He's in Indonesia,
he's locked up on drugs charges.
Indonesia?
Yeah, and they're very strict.
Long prison sentences,
not a lot anyone can do about it.
They execute drug smugglers.
I think he's got
a ten-year sentence.
He's getting out.
She found out this morning.
I just...
I thought she seemed a bit odd.
Well, I'm sure it's not something
she's massively proud of. Mm.
How long's he been in?
Not sure. Maybe a year?
So he was in the process
of an appeal?
Yeah. Yeah, I believe so.
I think he appealed last year
and he got turned down.
So he's one year
into a ten-year sentence
and he's just getting out,
just like that?
That doesn't make sense.
DOOR OPENS
Secretary of State for Defence,
Detective Chief Superintendent
Robertson,
Detective Sergeant Longacre,
who are going to update you
on their investigation.
Good afternoon.
We've been uncovering a series
of coded messages sent between
Piter Vasiliev, also known as Peter
Ingles, and an unknown associate,
whom we have reason to believe
might be a crewman on board Vigil.
All right.
What evidence do you have?
Their communications stopped the day
before Vigil went out on patrol.
And we've deciphered some encrypted
data that Ingles had hidden
in a series of images.
This is from ERV Services,
the company you use to supply
the ventilation systems
on Trident submarines.
Now, according to them,
a code that we found in one of the
messages refers to the operation
of this bit of kit,
the atmosphere management plant.
I should point out that if anyone
were able to tamper with this,
it would be extremely dangerous
for anyone on board.
So you believe this crewman
is actively engaged
in sabotaging Vigil?
Do the messages give any clue
as to his or her identity?
We're still trying to decode them.
But it could take weeks.
Well, we clearly don't have
that long.
How can we be certain
this is their plan?
There are also two murder victims
who we know are connected.
We don't have the full picture,
but you can see the implication.
They were killed because they
uncovered what the Russians were
planning.
Will you call Vigil back?
I should say that that is not
our official recommendation yet.
The Rear Admiral tells me
we don't have a boat ready
to replace Vigil for another week.
You are asking me to break
the continuous at-sea deterrent.
But given everything
that we've discovered,
it is something
to be considered, no?
This might be exactly
what they want us to do.
Parliament is taking a vote
next week
on whether or not to replace
Britain's nuclear warheads.
What message would it send out if
we were to be without the deterrent
while that vote is happening?
Minister, if something were to
happen to the crew of Vigil,
could you live with knowing
that you knew there was a problem,
and you didn't bring them home?
Well...
..there's a lot to consider.
Thank you. I'll talk to the PM.
First thing? Aye, first thing.
OK, first thing tomorrow.
Shouldn't you be calling it a day?
Three new cases this week.
When was the last time you were home
by nine? There's a lot to do so...
OK.
And I don't like going home.
So at least I feel useful here.
But, look, I could, um...
I could finish up if you wanted
to go for a drink or something.
Come on, then.
INDISTINCT CHATTER
ALARM BEEPS
Watch, stand to, close quarters.
Something must have snagged
the wire.
All communications are down, we need
you on one-deck now. Yes, sir.
Loss of all broadcast.
You see the discolouration?
Burke ingested some kind of toxin.
Thank you, Minister, I will.
Sir?
Urgent message for Vigil.
She's to return to port immediately.
Get a response on receipt
of this order. Yes, sir.
The comms wire is going to take
two to three hours to repair.
Till then we won't receive
any messages. Just get it fixed.
Until then, we're on our own.
Aye, sir.
Carry on.
Why are you out of the cabin?
I think I know who poisoned
Craig Burke.
I just found this
in Jackie Hamilton's bunk.
I think it's connected to her son.
He's just been released from drugs
charges in Indonesia. Believe me,
they don't go away overnight.
I need to get this backed up.
We need to speak to her
straight away.
You're just going to have to
trust me on this.
Ship control, full main broadcast.
Petty Officer Jackie Hamilton
to the control room. Immediately.
Petty Officer Hamilton,
please report to the control room.
Repeat. Petty Officer Hamilton,
Hello.
CAT PURRS
# Took the breath from my open mouth
# Never known how it broke me down
# I went in circles somewhere... #
Don't let anybody tell you that
you don't know how to throw a party.
This is all your fault.
Mine?! No.
# Storing up on your summer glow
# You went in search of someone else
# And I hear your ship is comin' in
# Your tears a sea for me to swim
# And I hear a storm is comin' in
# My dear, is it all
we've ever been? #
What are you doing?
You said you weren't into women.
I like you.
Oh, you like me?
Tell me that when you're sober.
OK.
I will.
I mean, I'll have a headache
but I'll...still feel the same.
# They taught the hand
that taut the bride
# Both our eyes locked to the tide
# We went in circles somewhere else
# And I hear your ship
is comin' in... #
PHONE RINGS
Boss.
They've sent a message
to Vigil to come back.
That's great.
That was an hour ago.
Boss?
They haven't had a response.
They should've by now.
What does that mean?
Boss? What does that mean?
We are in the shipping lanes.
We keep a wide berth of anything
that might snag the comms wire,
you know that. Yes, sir.
Sir, it was their bearing
and the sea surface.
We didn't hear... You sharpen up.
I'm sorry, sir.
Look, it's been five minutes,
I should go and look for her.
Bring her to the wardroom when you
find her. For the last time...
..focus.
Have you seen Jackie?
Eh, no, but I think the Cox'n
went to look for her.
Oh, God.