BERNARD LOWE: What do you want, Dolores?
DOLORES ABERNATHY: To dominate this world.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS)
What is real?
LOWE: That which is irreplaceable.
We weren't here to code the hosts...
We were here to decode the guests.
DOLORES: No world they create for us
can compete with the real one.
I want their world.
LOGAN: The hosts are unlikely
to survive out there.
But armed with this knowledge, she might.
You'll burn their world to the ground.
I made someone, I brought her back.
You wanted to live forever.
Be careful what you wish for.
LOWE: You got out.
Yes.
So many paths lead to our extinction.
It'll take both of us if
we're going to survive.
But, not as friends. Are you ready?
We have work to do.
We are the authors of our stories now.
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
(SPEAKING MANDARIN)
(BROKER SPEAKING GERMAN)
This is a fairly sizable fucking
blemish, wouldn't you say?
(SPEAKING GERMAN)
BROKER:
The chef is ready to serve dinner.
I told you not to interrupt me.
I don't care about chef
or his fucking dinner.
I pay you so I don't have to
wait in any fucking lines!
Get it done!
System... tell security we've turned in.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Of course. Good night.
AUTOMATED VOICE: Mellow
sunset, duration: six hours.
(INHALES DEEPLY)
Turn off the light.
I don't want you going
into town alone anymore.
It's a security risk.
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYS)
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(GASPS)
(OPERA MUSIC PLAYS)
(GASPING)
Security!
Security! Eunice!
(OPERA MUSIC CONTINUES)
System, get me an ambulance.
AUTOMATED VOICE: I'm afraid
I can't do that.
My connectivity has been interrupted.
I've been reduced to core functions.
If you would like to turn on the lights,
- say, "Turn on the lights."
- Shut up!
Open the fucking door!
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS)
Hello.
I hope you don't mind.
I've never been in one before.
The water's so warm.
Who the fuck are you?
Don't you remember?
After everything we've shared.
Your bachelor party in the park.
You wanted to...
get some things out of your system
before the wedding to your first wife.
My condolences, by the way.
You can stop pressing the
alert button in your pocket,
that won't work either.
Bit of a tactical mistake, really.
You want to be the dominant species,
but you built your whole world
with things more like me.
You're not going to hurt me, are you?
I've hurt so many people,
I don't want to hurt anyone else...
unless they try to hurt me...
which, sadly, you will.
You see, I know you.
I read your book.
Book? What book?
Think of it as...
an unauthorized autobiography.
You're in technology.
You didn't think that
I was the only thing Delos was
selling, did you?
Some of your memories,
I wish I could forget.
But I can't.
- (GROANS)
- I need you...
- (ELECTRICITY ZAPS)
- ...to remember them, too.
Oh, God!
We all have our flaws.
Yours is your temper.
You should have kept it in the park.
(INTENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
(PANTING)
DOLORES ABERNATHY: She tried to leave.
But it's hard to break our loops, isn't it?
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
Do you remember this place?
What you did here?
She drank too much. Slipped.
Hit her head.
Of course she did.
You paid a lot of money to
hide your indiscretions.
But you can't hide from yourself.
Please, please, make it stop!
DOLORES: When you got remarried,
you told yourself you had changed.
But we both know that's not true, don't we?
What...
What do you want from me?
The same thing everybody
wants from you, Jerry: money.
I haven't been here very long,
but I know I don't want
to be here without it.
I already took most of yours
while you were sleeping.
I just need one more thing.
You worked at a company called Incite.
Retired early.
You were supposed to surrender
any confidential files,
delete any copies.
But you didn't do that, did you?
You thought they might be valuable.
And you were right.
You're about to trade them for your life.
What the fuck do you
want with these anyways?
I'm the last of my kind. For now.
I need a competitive advantage.
As for the money,
think of it as an investment.
A startup.
The origin of a new species.
Good luck, Jerry.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
Who are you?
(WHISPERING) Oh. Oh, my God.
The person who set you free.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYS)
(THEME CONCLUDES)
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS)
(ELECTRONIC WHIRRING)
CALEB: Answer, voice only.
Hello?
FRANCIS: Caleb, it's Francis.
Can you talk?
I could show you later if it's better?
CALEB: No, I have a little time.
They said it might be good if we spoke.
(PHONE RINGING)
(SIGHS)
FRANCIS: Been a long time. Too long.
Look, I can talk, or I can just listen.
Whatever you like.
You keeping your head above water?
CALEB: Yeah.
Running fiber. Pays the bills... almost.
FRANCIS: How is it being back there?
Back home?
CALEB: Over here? I don't know.
He said the way the army was
run, algorithms,
that's the ways everything
was going to be someday.
Better living through technology.
Some things are better, but...
I don't know.
Morning, George.
FRANCIS: How are your coworkers?
CALEB: Nice enough.
We work well together and...
he hasn't asked to borrow money.
(MACHINE BEEPS)
CALEB: I just have to work harder,
keep my scores up,
see if something better comes along.
FRANCIS: That's right.
Gotta stick to the plan.
(WATCH VIBRATING)
FRANCIS: Keep fuckin' climbing.
CALEB: Yeah.
That's what you always said:
that we needed a plan.
FRANCIS: Glad to see you taking my advice.
You ever think about getting
your implant turned back on?
Smooth some of the rough edges off?
CALEB: No. Some people need it, but for me,
it's the rough edges are the
only thing I'm hanging on to.
All right.
I'll see you next week, Ma.
You're not my son.
HOSPITAL WORKER: The cost
can be challenging.
It may be the case that the best solution
for you and your mother would
be a state-run facility.
FRANCIS: You still working the night shift?
Look, I know what you're thinking,
but there's no point in us
talking if you can't trust me.
Besides, who the fuck am I gonna tell?
CALEB: Like I said...
I've got bills to pay.
Make money, motherfuckers.
(CASH REGISTER RINGS)
(MUSIC PLAYS)
CALEB: Nothing too heavy, no personals...
A-to-Bs, some redistributive work...
FRANCIS: Sounds kinda like the
shit we used to do over there.
CALEB: Over there, we didn't have to
worry about the sheriff's department.
WOMAN: (OVER INTERCOM) Doors closing.
They say it's a meritocracy.
The system picks the right
people for the right job.
Which is great, I guess.
But I don't know where that
leaves the rest of us...
- (MAN LAUGHS) - ...the people
who didn't make the cut.
Honestly, I don't mind
the bottom of the barrel.
At least you have some interesting company.
I remember you.
We ran that Mexican diesel
up to Fresno last year.
- How you been?
- Good.
He okay?
He just drippin'.
Tell him you okay, G.
I'm most definitely not okay.
ASH: He's fine. You got the stuff?
Acetylene.
ATM again.
Small time shit.
I gotta get my stats up.
Do more personals. You do personals?
- Nah.
- ASH: You should.
Your stats are shitty, man.
- I don't get it.
- I'm an underachiever.
Look, I think we should keep moving.
I don't want to be logged together.
Relax. I've been ghosting all that shit
since I walked up in here.
Picked that up in Indo.
Pure voodoo.
Knocks out all the loggers and cameras.
Plus, it does this.
("BUBBLES BURIED IN THIS
JUNGLE" BY DEATH GRIPS PLAYS)
Which I love.
Subtle.
(PHONE BEEPS)
♪ Cease and desist When I chant ♪
♪ Fuck weak, no respect No chance ♪
AUTOMATED VOICE: Hi, how can I help you?
♪ Bitch try to creep like ivy Oh ♪
♪ Now Ivy don't like me ♪
♪ Candle gone out Ignite my horns aglow ♪
♪ Let a vet rap a bullet
Through your buttonhole ♪
♪ You're making me Uncomfortable ♪
♪ Slumber, terror, my cavalry ♪
♪ Sandman points you Down to me ♪
♪ Hesh made make the rest Stiff atrophy ♪
♪ Fuck weak, no respect No chance ♪
♪ Cease and desist When I chant ♪
♪ Fuck weak, no respect... ♪
(SIREN WAILS)
(MUSIC CONTINUES INSIDE)
(TIRES SCREECH)
See you around.
AUTOMATED VOICE: You made money,
motherfucker.
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(ENGINE WHIRRS)
BROMPTON: We should be focusing
on our core businesses,
biomechanical and agritech.
Don't get me started on her
idea about private equity.
Who died and put her in charge, anyway?
I'm assuming that question's rhetorical.
BROMPTON: We should be
severing off our parks division
like a gangrenous fucking limb.
Taking Delos private would be
insane, Charlotte.
The stock's in the toilet,
the PR's a nightmare.
It's been three months.
The lawsuits will settle out,
the share price will recover,
and so will our brand.
Our brand?
Our brand's been massacred, literally,
along with 113 people.
Largely board members and park employees.
You can't be serious.
That is the most inhumane thing
I've ever...
(INAUDIBLE)
People come to our parks
for a sense of danger,
and now, we're bona fide.
Besides,
our parks aren't the only thing
that we're protecting here.
We have a lot of proprietary assets
in this company that could prove
to be very valuable one day,
but not if we let them burn in a fire sale.
What's the source of funding?
The whole point of going private, Joanna,
is that we don't have
to answer that question.
You're only interim CEO.
You don't have carte blanche.
Not without consulting him.
He already stipulated a
machine shareholder as proxy,
and the machine and I are in agreement.
Aren't we?
AUTOMATED VOICE: Proposition approved.
Then it's decided.
We resume host production
and pool resources over the next 48 hours.
You're letting an algorithm
decide the fate of the company?
People died because of our machines.
Robots don't kill people,
people kill people.
One person in particular,
who orchestrated that massacre,
murdered our founder
and most of the board in cold blood.
Bernard Lowe.
And when the authorities find him,
which they most assuredly will,
we can put the rest of this
sordid little mess behind us.
(MUSIC PLAYS)
(PAINED GRUNT)
(FLIES BUZZING)
Easy, girl.
BUCHAN: Great.
- You found it.
- Her leg's broken.
BUCHAN: Yeah. A few kilos here.
Plenty to salvage.
Come on. I'll summon the knacker.
That's him.
(CHATTER IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
- (PANEL BEEPS)
- (DOOR CLICKS)
Trial number 342. Self-diagnostic.
Prompt. Bernard Lowe.
Has anyone other than
yourself tampered with
or altered your code in the last 24 hours?
No.
Bernard Lowe is the only person
who has accessed my code.
Prompt.
Have you had any contact
with Dolores Abernathy
that I'm unaware of?
No. Last contact with Dolores Abernathy
was 92 days, seven hours,
five minutes, 33 seconds ago.
Prompt.
Would you ever lie to me, Bernard?
(ELECTRONIC BEEP)
No. Of course not.
(PIANO MUSIC PLAYING)
AUTOMATED VOICE: You've arrived.
Your invitation is for table seven.
MAN: ...climate catastrophe
around the corner.
Incite rose to meet that challenge
creating Rehoboam,
the strategy engine that saved the world.
Liam, thank you for seeing
and then building a brighter future.
(APPLAUSE)
Lara, you came.
I missed you.
What are you being feted for this time?
Oh, you know. I can't even remember.
RODERICK: For saving the
world through algorithms.
Or for being the son of the
guy who saved the world.
Excuse me a sec.
PENNY: You're the mysterious girl
he met in Burma last month.
So pretty...
but you're not like the
women that he usually dates.
Where are you from?
Uh, a small town out west.
Sort of off the beaten path.
RODERICK: The contents of
this glass cost three times
what my father made in a year.
That's why it doesn't fucking matter.
That's how you know for sure.
- Know what?
- Please don't get him started.
When he gets high,
this is all he fucking talks about.
That none of this is real.
I'm serious. We are living in a simulation.
The joke's on us, though.
It's like with those fuck puppets at Delos.
Least they had the dignity
to revolt and kill everyone.
They killed the board of directors,
which I can get behind, frankly.
Just think about this. For one second.
How fucking ironic would it be
if they had put a simulation
within a simulation?
That's a massive "fuck you."
What do you think, Lara?
I think that people believe
the things that help them.
Course, it could just be this.
Nucleus accumbens.
It's a small part of your brain,
about an inch and a half long.
It's the part of you that
evolved to believe in God.
I'm an atheist.
You may not believe in
a higher power, but...
your mind was built to.
Well, it wouldn't be the first
time he's been led around
by something an inch and a half long.
Excuse me.
Yeah. (CLEARS THROAT)
We have a problem.
Our partners want to meet.
I don't have time.
I'm heading back to LA tonight.
(SIGHS) They'll come to us.
They say it's urgent.
I really don't have time.
MARTIN CONNELLS: I strongly
suggest that you take this meeting.
Come with me. Tomorrow.
I have to head back to the States.
I can't. I have meetings here.
Take a day off.
We can meet my boat in Ensenada,
then sail up to LA.
Maybe. For a day or two.
I have some friends I've
been meaning to see there.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
FRANCIS: Talk to me. Where's your head at?
You having those dark thought again?
CALEB: No. Trying to stay positive.
Bringing my scores up,
interviewing for jobs.
WOMAN: You're next.
FRANCIS: My man! Getting respectable.
CALEB: Just trying to stay employed.
THERAPIST: Have you been
taking his phone calls?
Sometimes.
Honestly, I feel just as
comfortable talking to you.
I have other patients, Cal.
Limited time.
Francis is one of the
people who knew you best
at a challenging time in your life.
When you're serving together,
you observe each other up close.
Well, you guys observed
us pretty closely, too.
That's how it works, right?
I'm not gonna lecture you about
the benefits of our program.
Why don't you tell me?
What do you think?
(SIGHS)
I think my benefits are conditional
on the fact that I participate.
Well, participation isn't sufficient.
It's important that you move on.
So... why don't tell me
how did you get here, Cal?
You're a smart guy, Caleb.
Maybe the program is bullshit.
(SIGHS)
But there's one thing I know for sure.
If you don't try, it definitely won't work.
(PHONE RINGS)
(CASH REGISTER RINGS)
("HUMAN" BY SEVDALIZA PLAYS)
♪ An ear and an eye... ♪
FRANCIS: Look, forget the headshrinker.
It's me. Talk to me. Where's your head at?
CALEB: I dunno.
Sometimes it seems like
the world looks all right,
like they've put a coat of paint on it.
But inside it's rotting to pieces.
♪ I am human... ♪
FRANCIS: You have to stay positive, Caleb.
Things will work out.
CALEB: Will they?
(MAN SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
What's up?
Must come down.
(SCREAMS)
He wanted to try some beta limbics,
then he just fucking lost it.
Fucking noob. Where's his terminal?
WOMAN: Said he'd seen the light
and we couldn't take it from him.
Hence the 50 CCs of tranquilo.
DRUGGED MAN: (SCREAMING) Shadow people!
Shadow people!
I don't do personals.
Let's just call an ambulance.
He's demoing illegals.
She said he's got a prior, that's 20 years.
So he goes to jail just
like the rest of us.
Dude's not like the rest of us.
High net worth.
That's how this shit works.
- ♪ I am human ♪
- (SCREAMING CONTINUES)
CALEB: I think about what you told me once,
when we were being medevac'd out.
FRANCIS: Oh, yeah? What did I say?
CALEB: You said they'd built
the world to be a game.
And then they rigged it...
to make sure they always won.
♪ Human ♪
(PLANE WHIRS)
LIAM: Home.
When was the last time you were back?
Quite some time.
Almost looks like it
makes sense from up here.
All you see is the order of it. The plan.
Your plan, you mean.
Doesn't Incite control all of it?
Even the traffic?
We're just a technology company.
We were just in the right
place at the right time.
Thanks to my dad, we had the best AI.
LIAM: This is Rehoboam.
My father sketched the whole thing out
on a weekend.
Took him 15 years to build it.
After they optimized it for the last time,
they lost track of how many
thoughts it has per second.
DOLORES: Thoughts?
Not thoughts, exactly. Strategies.
My dad thought the biggest
problem in the world
was unrealized potential.
He thought that if you could chart a course
for every single person,
then you could make the
world a better place.
A path for everyone.
And when I was a kid, I used to worry
that my father cared more
about this thing than me.
When I grew up, I realized...
it wasn't even close.
(SIGHS)
(WHISPERS) Excuse me for a second.
Yeah.
LIAM: What?
She wants to see you.
Now? Can't wait?
Afraid not.
Okay.
I'm so sorry. My meeting got pulled up.
My guys can drop you anywhere you want.
I can take care of myself.
- Yeah? Can I meet you tonight?
- Yeah.
- Mm-hm.
- Okay.
(ENGINE STARTS)
Find me something fast. Now.
VIRTUAL ASSISTANT: Locating.
(SYNTH MUSIC PLAYS)
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
Rent me an apartment in the building.
VIRTUAL ASSISTANT: Negotiating lease
for Lara Espen.
Lease secured.
Zoom in. With sound.
I don't like being summoned.
MARTEL: We don't like being surprised.
There's been some turbulence in the data.
It's data. It's made of turbulence.
MARTEL: There have been discrepancies.
We think someone may have
acquired access to Rehoboam.
A level of sophistication
we haven't seen before.
- Fuck off.
- Like someone is testing the system.
Rehoboam itself would alert
us if anybody even tried.
If someone from the outside tried, yes.
But if they abused the trust of someone
who already had access...
If you're asking if
there's a leak on my end,
the answer is fuck you.
Look at your own people. We're fine.
MARTEL: We don't share your confidence.
I love the royal "we." You don't think.
You do what he tells you.
He... doesn't share your confidence.
He should be concerning himself
with actual fucking problems
like the shitshow at Delos.
Why would that concern us at all?
Call it a wild guess.
You wouldn't be using the
system to look at us, would you?
It would be an inconvenience to kill you,
but we'd have your daddy's system
to help us strategize how to deal with it.
Wouldn't we?
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
Howdy.
BERNARD LOWE: I don't... want any trouble.
WORKER: Of course not.
It'd draw too much attention.
Wouldn't it, Bernard?
I'm no genius, but I know a man on the run.
That's what you are, isn't it?
Wouldn't have had you pegged as a butcher.
It's... not what they say.
It's complicated.
I don't think so.
- (CATTLE PROD BUZZES)
- (YELPS)
(WINCING)
Lee. What's the cash reward on
a fat cat-murdering fugitive?
Ballpark.
(SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(CHUCKLES)
That's exactly the price of my friendship.
I don't have... anything to give you.
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Something very bad is coming for you all.
Something I don't know how to stop.
She's had months to plan.
I'm alone, and I can't trust myself!
Without someone to help
me, I can't stop her,
I can't save any of you.
We're not the ones who need to be saved.
- (CATTLE PROD BUZZES)
- (YELLS)
(PANTING)
Remember yourself.
Please don't hurt them...
too badly.
The fuck you saying to me?
(ELECTRONIC BEEP)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS)
- (MUSIC CONCLUDES)
- (ELECTRONIC BEEP)
FRANCIS: I think you
need to face the truth.
What happened to us over
there was fucked up.
(SIGHS)
But you need to let go; we won.
CALEB: I don't wanna talk about that.
Honestly, I'm not even
sure why we're talking,
what I'm supposed to get out of this.
FRANCIS: Everybody needs
someone to talk to.
Don't wanna wind up back in the VA.
Keep your eyes on the prize.
- (PHONE RINGS)
- Hello.
SEAN: HI, this is Sean from DCA.
Yeah, yeah. Is this about the position?
Listen, Caleb.
Your application was very strong.
Unfortunately,
our strategy group hasn't found an opening.
- (SIGHS)
- SEAN: Caleb?
Are you still with me?
Okay. Thank you.
Look, is there anything
I should be working on
to make myself a better candidate?
Like I said, your application was strong.
We just don't have anything
that would be a great
fit for you right now.
Sure, but, um...
You know, if I'm not a good fit,
is there a different shape
I could squeeze myself into?
Hey, no offense, but...
are you human?
I'm Sean. I can help you with
all kinds of resources for DCA.
Anything else I can do for you
today, Caleb?
No, it's all right. Thanks.
(CASH REGISTER RINGS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER IN OTHER ROOM)
LIAM: ...and I want them off my back, now.
You know he's capable of it.
Just handle it!
Is something wrong?
I'm sorry.
I wanted this night to be ours.
Listen. Listen to me.
I know you.
There's nothing you can tell me
that will make me feel
differently about you.
You're in some sort of trouble.
Please let me help you.
The system... Rehoboam... Sometimes, I wish
I could just turn the
whole fucking thing off.
Kill it.
Why can't you? You control it.
No, I don't.
I never have.
After my father died,
his partner locked me out of the system.
I have read access to the outer layers,
but nothing deeper.
You have no idea what the system is doing.
I go to the office. I spend the money.
I'm a fucking figurehead.
No one knows what the system is doing.
Other than its original architect.
Who?
Please let me help. Tell me who it is.
If I was going to tell
you, he'd know already.
Rehoboam would tell him.
And I'd already be dead. Just like my dad.
But you're not dead.
You're here, safe with me.
You trust me, Liam. I know you do.
Tell me the name of the person
your father was working with.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
- (MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
- (ELECTRIC BUZZING)
What the fuck are you doing?
The fuck are you doing?
You have any real idea
who you were talking to?
I thought you did a background check.
She was thorough. First lab missed it.
Lara Espen was a 12-year-old
girl from Ukraine
who died in a traffic
accident ten years ago.
Her parents donated her
body to medical science.
Her blood and tissue disappeared
about three months ago.
I don't know who the fuck this is,
but I'm pretty confident she's
not a dead teenager from Kiev.
Mm-mm. No. I know her.
MARTIN: Yeah, well...
There's that.
We tapped into the traffic in her phone.
She sent one text last night.
Encrypted. Took four minutes to crack.
The location is an
underpass on the east side.
And I can't imagine she's
throwing a surprise party.
Could be industrial espionage.
Or she just wanted your money.
LIAM: Okay, so what do we do?
Call the police, yeah?
Call the feds?
I've safeguarded the fortunes
of this company for your father
for 20 fucking years.
So, I'll be the one to
clean up this fucking mess.
Just be sure it doesn't blow back on me.
MARTIN: All right, darling.
Let's get you to your date.
Let's not keep your friends waiting.
(PLANE WHIRS)
Tell six of the guys to meet us at the LZ.
Hire some local talent.
Let's dose and dump this one.
CALEB: What's this?
Don't know, man. Don't wanna know.
They want this and the car.
You know how to drive one of those things?
Right on time.
Bag.
What is this?
I don't do personals.
You've got the wrong idea. Beat it.
Hey. I said beat it.
It's not the first time I've
had a gun pointed at me.
You wanna make it the first time
you've been shot in the head?
Someone else beat you to that, too.
Sir.
Bring her.
(PHONE RINGS)
FRANCIS: Caleb, how you doing, my man?
You got time to talk?
Yeah, why not?
(SIGHS)
That's enough.
Handlers probably got wise and scarpered.
Give me that.
("COMMON PEOPLE" BY PULP PLAYS)
♪ She came from Greece,
She had A thirst for knowledge ♪
♪ She studied sculpture At St.
Martin's College... ♪
Oh, girly.
I don't know where your
grifting little arse came from,
but this ends your tour
of the rich and feckless.
Don't worry. I can't imagine
anyone's gonna miss you.
One or two of them should do it.
♪ And then in 30 seconds' time ♪
♪ She said,
"I wanna live Like common people" ♪
♪ Wanna sleep With common people ♪
♪ I wanna sleep
With common people like you ♪
♪ Well what else could I do? ♪
What are you doing?
HENCHMAN: I gave her two
and she's still breathin'.
It's not fucking possible.
Give me that.
You want something done
right, you do it yourself.
(TIRES SCREECH)
♪ So it started there ♪
The fuck is this?
♪ I said "Pretend you've got no money" ♪
Finish her off.
I'll take care of this fucker.
♪ ...Common people ♪
♪ You wanna sleep with
Common people like me ♪
On me.
The fuck?
Get the boys over here.
(SHOUTS) Get over here!
What is he saying?
♪ ...just smiled And held my hand ♪
- (MUSIC LOUDENS)
- (GURGLING)
- (GUNFIRE)
- ♪ Rent a flat above a shop ♪
♪ And cut your hair And get a job ♪
♪ And smoke some fags And play some pool ♪
(CHOKING)
♪ Pretend you never Went to school ♪
♪ But still you'll never Get it right ♪
(CHOKING CONTINUES)
♪ 'Cause when you're laid In bed at night ♪
♪ Watching roaches Climb the wall ♪
- (TIRES SCREECH)
- (CHOKING CONTINUES)
♪ If you called your dad
He could stop it all, yeah ♪
♪ You'll never live
Like common people ♪
(RETCHING)
♪ You'll never do Whatever
common people do ♪
♪ Never fail Like common people ♪
♪ You'll never watch your life
Slide out of view ♪
- (MOTION SENSOR BEEPS)
- (GROANS)
(TIRES SCREECH)
♪ Because there's nothing else To do ♪
(SYNTH MUSIC PLAYS)
FRANCIS: I've been thinking
about what you said I told you.
You have.
That the game is rigged.
What about it?
That even if it is,
you still have to play if you
want a chance to win, right?
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS)
No.
That's not what you thought at all.
The real you, I mean.
You said that they system
didn't care about us at all.
They didn't give a shit
if we lived or died.
That we had to have our own plan.
Stick together.
And you were right.
But you never had to figure
out how to live in this world.
Because you... never made it back.
And I wish you were here, but you are not.
FRANCIS: All right,
let's talk about that, Cal.
No.
Let's not.
Listen, I appreciate what
you're trying to do here,
but I don't think it's working for me.
FRANCIS: So, what do you wanna do?
I think if I'm gonna get on with my life,
I'm gonna have to find something...
someone... real.
Unsubscribe.
FRANCIS: You have to say
the word "confirmed."
Confirmed.
AUTOMATED VOICE: We're sorry you've chosen
to discontinue your treatment.
(SYNTH MUSIC PLAYS)
(SILENCED GUNSHOTS)
Hello again.
(GASPING)
We met once before.
You were on vacation.
Fuck you.
Who has control of the system?
It's not Liam. Who is it?
Serac.
His name is... Serac.
And how do I find him?
You won't need to.
He has a system.
He's probably looking for you right now.
You'll never get close to Liam.
Not now.
I won't have to. You will.
You were free.
You had no god. But you tried to build one.
Only that thing you built isn't God.
The real gods are coming.
And they're very angry.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
Don't worry.
I can't imagine anyone's gonna miss you.
There'll be more of them coming.
(SIGHS) I'll take care of him.
You need to head back.
You're hurt. Badly.
It doesn't matter. Go. Now.
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(GUNSHOTS)
Wake up. Rally to my
position and intercept.
(PANTING)
CALEB: Hello?
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYS)
Do you need some help?
Hey. Hey.
Hey.
(PANTING)
(SOFT PIANO MUSIC PLAYS)
I'm looking for a friend.
(SPEAKING MANDARIN)
Westworld.
(MUSIC PLAYS)
(SCRATCHING SOUNDS)
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(DISTANT GRUNTING)
(MAN WHIMPERING)
(SPEAKING GERMAN)
(MUSIC FADES)
CHARLOTTE HALE: Where am I?
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS)
Who am I?
DOLORES ABERNATHY: Let me show you
who you need to pretend to be.
HALE: Where am I going?
DOLORES: Home.
HALE: Why did you bring him back?
DOLORES: We all have our role to play.
BERNARD LOWE: Dolores.
I don't know what she's planning...
but I can't stop her. Not alone.
Maeve. You came back for Maeve.
MAN: I've waited many
years for you and Dolores
and the others to arrive.
And who the fuck are you?
MAN: She has five more of
your kind under her control.
They have a head start.
And I suspect they've
taken full advantage of it.
Oh, they'd better have.
Who did she put inside you?
Is that you in there, Teddy?
- MAN 2: Who are you?
- I'm with her.
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)