[theme music playing]
My name is Hannah Grose.
The year is 1987.
Dominic is dead.
Charlotte is dead.
Rebecca and Peter are dead.
I'm dead.
Yes.
I want to help them.
But you can't.
No.
- And why is that?
- I'm slipping away, Owen.
I can feel it, even now, and…
I don't want to slip away.
I want to stay here, with you.
But you can't.
[melancholy music playing]
[Hannah] No, I can't.
Here.
Right here, this moment.
"What a curious and charming man,"
I thought.
Oh, it had been so long,
I'd forgotten that feeling, but…
I looked at you, and…
I almost forgot myself for a moment.
God knows I've tried not to think of you.
Very hard, but I…
I've thought of you often.
Thinking about the places we would go
if we were ever to leave Bly.
[chuckles] Where we'd settle.
You'd open your restaurant.
Make me taste
all those wonderful recipes you created
in that beautiful,
maddening mind of yours.
[Owen chuckles]
[Hannah sniffles]
I always think
that I would very much like…
to spend the rest of my days with you.
Listening to your dreadful puns,
holding your hand, and…
I loved you, Owen.
I should have told you.
What a life we could have had.
Oh, Owen, wouldn't it have been wonderful?
Huh?
[sniffles]
I prefer it here.
This one.
This day with you.
I know, love.
But I suppose…
Well, you have to warn me, don't you?
You have to help me.
I thought I was.
Out there.
You must help me out there.
You must help all of us out there.
In here, I'm you.
This isn't me.
This is just you.
You have loved me…
so I'll always be here.
But you don't want me to be hurt.
Nor the kids.
If I leave, I don't know
where I'll go afterwards and, I'd be...
Be brave in death, Hannah.
We both know you're not so selfish…
to remain hidden in a memory.
[inhales sharply]
[unsettling music building]
- [frightening music playing]
- [Dani choking]
[Flora, screaming] Stop it!
Stop it!
Flora! Get inside!
[Hannah] Now hide!
[frightening music continues]
[whimpering, choking]
Let her go.
Now!
Stop!
[Hannah groans]
[gasps]
[chokes]
[Hannah grunts]
[ominous music playing]
[feet clattering]
[sinister music playing]
[choking]
[Dani grunting]
[music intensifies and subsides]
- [eerie music playing]
- [footsteps squelching]
[Flora panting]
[Flora] Please.
Let her go.
Please.
[jarring thud]
[thud]
[ghostly echo]
♪ We lay my love and I ♪
♪ Beneath the weeping willow ♪
[Viola humming "O Willow Waly"
in ghostly voice]
[choking]
[Dani, weakly] Flora.
[croaking] Flora!
[squelching footsteps approaching]
[Flora panting]
Miss Jessel!
Help me!
Miles! Help me!
I gave you your freedom…
- [Flora, screaming] Miles!
- …and you're letting it drown.
[Flora] Help me!
Help me!
Miss Jessel!
- [car door opens]
- [suspenseful music playing]
[Henry] Hey!
Uncle Henry!
Put her down!
- [screaming] Help!
- Come on, you put her down now!
I said put her down.
- [Viola screams hoarsely]
- [Flora screaming] Uncle Henry! Help me!
You're killing him!
Help! Stop it!
[Flora screams]
[poignant music playing]
[screaming] Help!
Uncle Henry!
Help!
[suspenseful music playing]
[engine powers down]
Is that Henry's car?
[Hannah gasps]
Not here. Not-Not here.
Owen, Owen, what are you doing here?
Th-This is gonna sound insane,
but we both had an awful dream,
and we just drove, and…
The lake. They…
- They need you at the lake.
- [Dani screams distantly] Flora!
[music surges]
[Flora] Help! [panting]
Help!
- Help me! Help me!
- Shh.
[Flora] Please, help me.
It's okay, sweetheart.
You won't feel it.
Okay? I'll… I'll feel it for you.
I'll just tuck you away one last time.
Go ahead, love.
You let me handle this part.
- Let me in.
- [emotional music playing]
Let me in.
It's you.
It's me.
It's us.
[eerie static]
Mummy.
There, my darling.
It's all right.
[water sloshes]
Owen!
Go!
- [Jamie] Dani!
- [Owen] Henry, hey.
[storyteller]
Owen tried to breathe life into Henry,
who hovered between life and death.
Soon, Flora would find herself
dream-hopping endlessly at Bly.
And it would have all gone that way
had not the au pair,
in that critical moment,
said what she said.
Something she did not entirely understand,
but something she felt, in her bones.
She had to try.
It's-It's you! [panting]
It's me!
It's us!
[emotional music continues]
[panting]
[Jamie screaming] Dani!
[Dani panting]
[echoing softly] It's us.
[music intensifying]
[music stops suddenly]
[somber piano music playing]
[Rebecca] Do you feel that?
When he checks the well…
please tell Owen I'm sorry.
Tell him I love him.
And the rest, well…
it's just...
[Henry gasping, coughing]
I'm so sorry, Miles.
I'm sorry.
[water splashes]
[gasping] It... It's us. It's us.
- [Flora whimpering]
- No! It's okay.
[hysterically] It's okay. It-It's okay.
It's okay. It's... It's o... It's...
It's okay.
Shh.
Okay.
[Dani gasping]
- Okay.
- It's okay.
[storyteller]
The au pair invited Viola into herself,
and the invitation had been accepted.
In that instant, the spell
that Viola had cast over Bly was broken…
Flora!
Uncle Henry!
…and all of the spirits
trapped in her gravity were released.
[Miles] Uncle Henry!
Miles!
Oh…
I'm so sorry, kids.
I'm so very sorry.
[Owen] Hannah, where's…
Where's Hannah?
[somber music continues]
[Owen panting]
[stifled sob]
[storyteller] The next day,
Owen assisted five men from town
while they gently lifted
the housekeeper's body from the well.
It was assumed she died accidentally.
An unfortunate stumble.
[broom sweeping]
In the days that followed,
a calm settled over Bly Manor,
for the first time in centuries.
The very air was different, lighter.
All that had once been trapped
on the grounds was now gone…
to some other place.
[Henry] Your father…
taught me how to do this.
He had a trick for it.
For a lot of things, actually.
My favorite…
was when he taught me how to sew patches
onto the knees of my trousers.
Daddy knew how to sew?
Oh, very well, in fact.
- [tender music plays]
- Mm-hm.
[Flora] Will you teach me
how to sew patches onto things?
[Henry] If you like.
Do you have any other stories,
Uncle Henry?
About your father?
Yes, I do.
A lot of them.
And your mother, too.
I'll tell you all the stories I've got.
[storyteller] After the housekeeper's body
was taken from the well,
some in the village said that the cook
rode with her all the way to the coroner.
And there,
he insisted on cleaning her himself,
which he managed with a soft towel,
soap scented with lavender,
and the greatest of care.
He stayed at her side
until she was buried,
and he loved her the whole way.
I am told, and I believe,
that he loves her still.
- [knocking on door]
- [Jamie] You about done up here?
I got distracted.
[Jamie] That's all right. I'll help you.
What's wrong?
[breathes shakily] I don't know.
Dani.
[sobs softly] I feel her.
In here.
It's so quiet, it's so quiet, but…
she's in here.
And this…
part of her…
that's in here, it isn't…
peaceful.
It's quiet, but…
it isn't…
peaceful. It's…
rage.
And I have this feeling
like I'm walking through this…
dense…
overgrown…
jungle…
and I can't really see anything
except the path in front of me.
But I know…
there's this…
thing…
hidden.
This angry, empty, lonely beast.
It's watching me.
[melancholy music playing]
Matching my movements.
It's just out of sight…
but I can feel it.
I know it's there.
And it's waiting.
[ominous music plays softly]
She's waiting.
And at some point…
she's gonna take me.
[breathes shakily]
Do you want company?
While you wait
for your beast in the jungle?
[Dani sniffles]
Do you want company?
[Dani sighs]
[sniffles, sighs heavily]
[Flora] Will you visit us?
Depends on where you're going.
Uh, America, I think.
Well…
I can do that.
I think that's where we're, uh…
where we're gonna go.
First, for a little while, at least.
Then where?
Well, uh…
that's the thing about adventures,
you're not meant to know.
- [whispers] That's half the fun.
- [all chuckle]
For you.
[tender music playing]
- Are you sure you wanna give me this one?
- You must have it.
It's you.
Thank you, Flora.
Well, uh, good show, boss.
[chuckles] Take care.
- Yeah.
- Be safe.
Oh, well…
I suppose I…
I don't know how I will ever thank you.
[sighs]
I'm so glad.
You have each other now.
I know. [chuckles]
It is right.
I…
Well, I'm just so goddamned lucky,
aren't I?
And so are you, Miss Clayton.
Where would we be, we wretched people…
without the generosity of our betters?
And luck.
[exhales loudly]
You all right, Poppins?
Yeah.
[engine turns over]
[Jamie] If we keep driving north,
it looks pretty rural.
There's lots of green.
Maybe in a few weeks
we could take the train.
Get to Vermont around Christmas.
[Dani] Mm.
Snow could be nice.
You'll laugh, but, uh…
part of me's wanted to go since I saw
White Christmas when I was a kid.
[chuckles]
- Doesn't have to be Vermont.
- No, it's not that.
Snow sounds nice.
I just…
I don't think we should plan,
you know, Christmas.
It's a ways away.
One day at a time.
Yeah, no, I know. I'm-I'm sorry, I'm just…
- Just being...
- Realistic?
It's all right.
One day at a time is fine by me.
As long as those days
are with you, Poppins.
One day at a time is what we've got.
It's what everybody's got
when you get down to it.
[storyteller] The days turned to months,
the months to more,
and before the au pair knew it,
a year had passed.
A trip around the sun,
and she was still here.
She was still her.
- [Jamie] Have something for you.
- Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Is that a moonflower?
They're really rare, you know?
I've got a problem.
Or rather, we've got a problem, Poppins.
Oh, no.
You see…
I'm not sick of you.
At all.
I'm actually pretty in love with you,
it turns out.
[kiss]
[Jamie] Mmm.
[kissing, chuckling softly]
[storyteller] One year became two.
[speaking indistinctly]
And from two,
it spread into an endless time,
so it seemed.
[uplifting music playing]
Three…
four, five years would pass.
And there was peace.
- Twenty-five thousand kroner?
- No.
- Twenty-five thousand dollars?
How did dollars get into this?
[storyteller] At long last,
deep within the au pair's heart,
there was peace.
And that peace held for years,
which is more than some of us ever get.
[ominous music playing]
[melancholy music playing]
[Jamie sighs in frustration]
How many years in this kitchen?
My cooking is still shite.
- What happened there, then?
- Found it on the street.
Wanted to save it.
Give it here, then.
Want me to keep stirring?
Yeah, see if you can salvage it.
What is going on here?
Well, there's your problem.
Your roots have been…
- Dani, why is there a...
- Here's the thing.
You're my best friend.
And I love my life.
And I don't know
how much time we have left,
but however much it is,
I wanna spend it with you.
And I know
we can't technically get married,
but I also don't really care.
We can wear the rings, and we'll know.
Okay? And…
that's enough for me.
If it's enough for you.
I reckon that's enough for me, yeah.
[laughs]
[kissing]
[Jamie sniffles]
- I love you.
- [Dani] I love you, too.
[laughs]
[Jamie sighs happily]
[upbeat jazzy music playing]
[cork pops]
[Owen] This is the best news.
I'm so happy for you both.
- Cheers, mate.
- Thank you.
Owen, this place is so beautiful.
Thank you.
Yeah, I'm, uh…
I'm happy with it.
We have a lot of regulars now,
which is nice.
They'll come in,
and I'll have their order ready.
There's something in knowing you, uh…
you made a place
people like to come back to.
- Yeah.
- Nice.
[Owen] Yeah.
And no one's, uh, lodged
any complaints about the name?
- Okay.
- [Jamie laughs]
Okay, it does get the occasional eye roll.
But I'll never forget
how badly it annoyed her
until she finally had to laugh,
and nothing was better
than that woman's laugh.
Yeah.
To Hannah.
Hannah.
[Owen] Mm.
- [Dani] Mm.
- You heard from Henry recently?
- Uh, I check in every now and again.
- Merci.
We haven't spoken to the kids
in ages, though.
- [ominous rumble]
- But, hey, they are growing up
and getting out into the world.
What kid wants to chat
to a couple of old people, eh?
- [melancholy music]
- You all right?
Yeah, yeah, I'm good.
I, uh, try to go when I can, you know.
Actually, uh, they all came here
a few months back, on holiday.
Back across the pond on an adventure.
Henry, Miles, Flora.
Flora's boyfriend.
Flora's got a boyfriend?
She's 12.
[Owen] She's 17.
- Yeah.
- Christ.
And fully smitten.
Henry is terrified.
Thank God he's sober now,
or he'd drink himself into a grave.
So, they're all happy?
Yeah.
[Dani] Mm.
It's interesting, though.
The way they talk about Bly.
You talked about what happened?
No. I mean, that's what's interesting.
They don't remember anything about it.
What?
Nothing?
No. Well, just the kids. Henry still…
remembers all of it.
But I mentioned Hannah,
and Flora asked me
who I was talking about.
- It's been this way a while, turns out.
- [Dani] So…
Well, if they don't remember Hannah,
they don't remember…
So, they've just forgotten it all?
They know they used to stay at Bly
when they were children.
Said they recognized Hannah's picture,
but only as the woman
that used to stay there with them.
The details, the specific moments, the…
the fear of it all
that we were so afraid would infect
the rest of their lives has just…
faded away.
And all that's left is the shape of it.
Bly was their summer home.
They used to live there
when they were children.
Do you think Henry will…
tell them?
Would you?
I mean, by the signs of it,
they're thriving.
I'd say…
just let them be.
Let them live their lives
the way they should.
Without anything hanging over them.
They deserve that.
We all do.
[water running]
Are we gonna talk?
I'll take that as a "no."
[ominous crescendo]
- [dish crashes]
- Jesus!
What's going on?
- Are you okay?
- [breathing shakily]
What happened?
I saw… I saw her.
She's there.
What did you see?
Her.
[gasps]
[whispering] I keep seeing her.
Okay.
- Right.
- [faucet squeaks off]
[water gurgling]
Okay.
- It's gone.
- It's gone?
- Is it?
- It's okay.
We're gonna be okay.
- You can't think the worst.
- Jamie.
- We don't know what this means. We…
We can have so many more years together.
Dani.
We can have so many more years.
We'll keep an eye on it,
and it'll be fine.
[panting]
Okay?
It's gonna be okay.
I'll do the washing up from now on.
Yeah?
You're shit at it, anyway.
[Dani chuckles]
- [sniffles]
- [chuckles]
Oh, baby, come here.
[kiss]
It's okay.
It's gonna be okay.
Well, the queue was shite,
but I've got it.
Our union is officially civil.
We'll marry again when we can.
- [water gurgling]
- It looks like that's enough for now.
Dani.
Dani?
[ominous music playing]
- [faucet squeaks off]
- Dani. Dani.
[gasps shakily]
Dani.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
Okay.
[whispers] Do you see her?
I only see you.
I'm sorry.
- All the water, I didn't realize.
- It's okay. It's okay.
Water is easy to clean up.
[sniffles]
I'm so tired, Jamie.
I know.
It's like every day
I feel myself fading away,
but I'm still here, and…
Hey.
- I don't really understand how that is.
- You're still here.
You're here.
It's like I see you right in front of me…
and I feel you touching me…
and every day…
- [melancholy music playing]
- …we're living our lives,
and I'm aware of that…
and it's like I don't feel it all the way.
I'm not even scared of her anymore.
I just stare at her, and…
it's getting harder and harder to see me.
Maybe I should just accept that.
- No… No, no.
- Maybe I should just accept that and go.
No.
Not yet.
- Jamie…
- Look, it's fine.
If you can't feel anything…
then I'll feel everything
for the both of us.
But no one is going anywhere.
Okay?
You're still here.
[sobs softly]
What if…
[sobbing]
…I'm here sitting next to you…
but I'm just really her?
One day at a time.
[rain pattering]
[ominous music slowly building]
[water gurgling]
[music intensifying]
[fades to silence]
[melancholy music playing]
[breathing rapidly]
[storyteller]
The au pair knew the moment had come.
The beast had lurked indeed,
and the beast, at its hour, had sprung.
And she could not risk
the most important thing,
her most important person.
- [sniffles]
- Not for one more day.
And so, the gardener found herself
back at Bly Manor one last time.
[birds chirping]
[music building emotionally]
[sighs heavily]
[inhales sharply]
[water splashing]
[storyteller] The gardener said the words
she'd heard those years ago.
- She willed it with everything she had.
- [muffled screams]
You, me, us.
Us.
"Take me with you,"
she cried in her heart.
"Take me.
Drag me down like you did the others."
But the lady in the lake
was different now.
[muffled screams]
The lady in the lake was also Dani.
And Dani wouldn't.
Dani would never.
In fact, no one would ever be taken again.
And no one has been taken to this day.
[gasps, screams]
[whimpering]
[panting]
[storyteller] For the rest of her days,
the gardener would gaze into reflections,
hoping to see her face.
Her own lady in the lake.
She'd leave her door open at night,
just a crack,
should she ever come back.
Waiting for her lover to return.
[Jamie sighs heavily]
[storyteller] Years would go by,
and as she slept underneath the water,
the au pair's memories would fade.
Like Viola before her, like the children,
she, too, would forget her past.
She would know nothing of the gardener,
nothing of their life together.
[fire crackling]
The details,
the specific moments would all fade away.
More time will pass, and…
the water will wash away
the delicate features of her.
Of her beautiful, perfect face.
But she won't be hollow, nor empty.
And she won't pull others to her fate.
She will merely walk the grounds of Bly,
harmless as a dove,
for all of her days.
Leaving the only trace of who she once was
in the memory
of the woman who loved her most.
I'm sorry. [chuckles softly]
I told you,
the story wasn't exactly short.
[guests chuckle]
My God.
So, is it true?
Which part?
[guest] I mean…
if I were to fly to England,
and I were to visit Bly Manor,
I may…
get a peek of this lady in the lake?
No.
I expect if you were to fly to England,
you would find no such place by that name.
If you were to find the manor, though,
perhaps you'd see her.
Though, no way to know
when she's awake or asleep.
Christ, is that the time?
Big day tomorrow.
Best get some rest.
Hm.
[groom] All right. Shall we?
I think I'll stay here a moment.
[groom] You okay?
[bride] I'm perfect.
Just enjoying the fire.
- All right. I love you.
- I love you so.
- Good night.
- [groom] Good night.
[bride] He's the silliest.
But, damn, if I don't love him the most.
That's how it should be.
I liked your story.
I'm glad.
But I think you set it up wrong,
in the beginning.
Is that so?
Yeah.
You said it was a ghost story.
- It isn't.
- No?
It's a love story.
Same thing, really.
Well, if you go on to retell it,
make that change up top for me.
Something on your mind?
No.
[chuckles] Not really.
I just keep thinking…
about that silly, gorgeous,
insane man I'm marrying tomorrow.
I love him.
More than I ever thought
I could love anybody.
And the crazy thing is
he loves me the same exact amount.
We got lucky.
Sometimes when I'm sitting next to him,
in that easy silence…
[crying]
…you only get with your forever person,
who loves you as much as you love them,
I start getting really, really terrified…
that he's gonna…
before I do,
and then what am I supposed to do?
How am I supposed
to just live a life that he's not in?
[sighs] Sorry.
I don't know what's happening.
[sniffles] I'm a mess. [laughs]
No, you're not.
I cry all the time, for no good reason.
You shouldn't be thinking
of losing each other at all.
Don't let that hang over
your happiness right now.
Enjoy that easy silence with him.
It is rare, what you've got.
But, when the time does come,
years and years from now, mind you…
[bride chuckles]
…it will be hard every day,
and it won't get easier.
But…
[sighs] …eventually, after some time,
you'll find little moments,
little pieces of your life
that remind you of him.
And they'll be silly and dumb,
or they'll be sad,
and you'll cry for hours.
But they'll still be a piece of him.
And you'll hold them tight.
It'll be like he's here,
with you.
Even though he's gone.
Now, you have a big day tomorrow.
A happy day with your silly,
gorgeous, insane man.
- [sniffles]
- You should sleep.
Thank you.
I feel like I should hug you.
That's all right.
You know…
it's funny.
I thought you might be making it up
just off that name.
That name?
But, then, I figured,
"How could you know that?"
It's a funny coincidence, I suppose.
My middle name is Flora.
Is that right?
Huh.
Good night.
[footsteps receding]
[sighs]
["I Shall Believe" by Sheryl Crow playing]
♪ Come to me now ♪
♪ And lay your hands over me ♪
♪ Even if it's a lie ♪
♪ Say it will be all right ♪
♪ And I shall believe ♪
♪ I'm broken in two ♪
♪ And I know you're onto me ♪
♪ That I only come home ♪
♪ When I'm so all alone ♪
♪ But I do believe ♪
♪ That not everything
Is gonna be the way ♪
♪ You think it ought to be ♪
♪ It seems like every time
I try to make it right ♪
♪ It all comes down on me ♪
♪ Please say honestly
You won't give up on me ♪
♪ And I shall believe ♪
♪ Open the door ♪
♪ And show me your face tonight ♪
♪ I know it's true ♪
♪ No one heals me like you ♪
♪ And you hold the key ♪
♪ Never again ♪
♪ Would I turn away from you ♪
♪ I'm so heavy tonight ♪
♪ But your love is all right ♪
♪ And I do believe ♪
♪ That not everything
Is gonna be the way ♪
♪ You think it ought to be ♪
♪ It seems like every time
I try to make it right ♪
♪ It all comes down on me ♪
♪ Please say honestly ♪
♪ You won't give up on me ♪
♪ And I shall believe ♪
♪ I shall believe ♪
♪ Please say honestly
You won't give up on me ♪
♪ And I shall believe ♪
♪ I shall believe ♪