[theme music playing]
[distant seagulls]
[girl]
So you have to wear them forever now.
Forever until you die?
Mom says they make me look extinguished.
She probably said "distinguished."
It's like fancy.
Let me try.
Oh, wow.
You're blind.
- Can you even tell it's me?
- Of course I can.
I see you every day.
- [woman in distance] Kids, dinner!
- You can stay for dinner again.
I should go home.
No, really, you can stay.
My mom says you can stay anytime.
I think she wishes she could swap us.
[chuckles]
Then you'd have to live with my mom.
[Dani chuckles]
Wow.
You like it?
Yeah, absolutely.
You're beautiful.
["All Through the Night"
by Cyndi Lauper playing]
Are you ready for this?
[sighs]
I think so.
We have to get through this,
then they'll leave us alone for a while.
♪ …feel the same
Without saying ♪
[knocking]
♪ We have no past ♪
- ♪ We won't reach back ♪
- [guests cheering]
♪ Keep with me forward
All through the night ♪
♪ And once we start, the meter clicks ♪
♪ And it goes running
All through the night ♪
♪ Until it ends
There is no end… ♪
[man] It was a dare. She dared me…
to kiss her, and so I did.
And then Kyle tells me that kissing
is how you get a girl pregnant,
- so…
- [guests chuckle]
…I panicked. I-I was ten years old,
my mom's gonna kill me,
Danielle's mom is gonna kill
the both of us.
I-I have to make this right.
So…
the very next day,
while we were walking to school, I…
get down on one knee,
and I asked her to marry me.
- And she turned me down.
- [guests laughing]
She says, "We're too young."
And, so, I said…
"When is old enough?"
And, um…
well, over the years,
I kept asking and asking.
Now, we're still pretty young,
but I think we are old enough
to know what we want,
and what I want is to be the man
that gets to be with this girl,
this beautiful, amazing girl,
for the rest of our lives.
Danielle, thank you
for daring me to do it. [laughs]
I can't wait.
- [guests chuckling]
- That's all I wrote.
["Higher Love" by Steve Winwood playing]
♪ Bring me a higher love ♪
♪ Bring me a higher love… ♪
[woman] Dani, honey, are you having fun?
- Yeah. Yeah, I'm just a little tired.
- Yeah.
Eddie says you've been so busy at school.
Yeah, there's a couple of kids
that just need a little extra help.
Come with me for a minute.
I've got a surprise for you. Come on.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, so, one thing I've always loved
about you, Danielle,
you always seem to spot the kids
that need you the most.
You'd better take care
of yourself as well, you know.
Save them all if you can,
but put your own oxygen mask on first.
Edmund says the same thing.
All the time.
Here, come here.
This is just a... a…
I don't know, it's a silly thought.
It might be a bad idea.
Um, but…
[whispers] Oh.
I, um…
I remember the first time I met you.
You were just the sweetest little thing.
And you said,
"Good morning, Mrs. O'Mara.
I'm Danielle, and I'm gonna be
Edmund's new best friend."
[both laugh gently]
You always knew your mind. Always.
[chuckles]
So, if this doesn't feel right,
I expect that you will tell me.
I trust you will.
I always hoped I'd have a daughter
I could give this to.
I'm so proud of my sons,
but I don't think this would suit
any of them.
[both laugh]
Well, maybe Carson. [chuckles]
Anyway, come, let's see.
I mean, we'd have to take it in,
of course,
and, um… well, take it up, probably.
Um… But, well, let's just…
see.
Okay.
- It's beautiful. I, um…
- [sighs with relief]
I don't know what to say.
Oh…
Just say…
"Good morning, Mrs. O'Mara."
[party music continues in distance]
- [sighs]
- [jarring crescendo]
[footsteps approaching]
[knocking on door]
[Jamie] You decent?
Come in.
[Dani] Oh!
You look…
I can scrub up when I need to.
Funeral starts at four.
- Owen said we should get there early.
- Okay.
It's a…
[clears throat]
It's quite a dress.
Yeah, it's the only thing I had in black.
I-I hate it.
Does look a bit like you're trying
to scandalize the village.
Can't say I fault the general principle.
- I just don't want to let Owen down.
- [Jamie] He won't mind.
Honestly, you don't have to go
if you don't want to.
Really?
He said as much.
Was pretty clear.
Okay. Yeah.
That's a relief, actually. I, um…
I had a funeral in my own life.
Not so long ago.
And I feel like this is, um…
Hey, Poppins.
It's your day off.
I promise, I don't need you to be my date
to Owen's mom's funeral.
- [both chuckle softly]
- Okay.
Okay.
Then, can you help me get this thing off?
Blimey. [clears throat]
No, seriously.
- [Jamie chuckles]
- The, uh… the zipper.
Right.
[takes deep breath, clears throat]
- Thank you.
- [upzipping]
[ominous thud]
[gasps]
Did I pinch you?
No, I'm sorry.
[eerie music playing]
All right.
- Well, I'll be back in a few hours.
- Okay.
And if I find out
you've not been relaxing,
- there will be serious consequences.
- [chuckling] Okay.
Yeah.
[door creaks shut]
[Flora humming "O Willow Waly"
in distance]
[humming grows louder]
[rubbing sound]
Oh.
- Hello, Miss Clayton.
- Hm.
I thought you were off to town.
For the funeral.
No.
No, I decided to stay home.
I don't like funerals either.
Hm.
So, what you up to down here?
Grave rubbings.
Wow.
I wanted to finish them all
before the end of the season.
Hm.
- [Flora] Miss Clayton?
- [Dani] Mm-hm?
[sighs] Will Owen's mom be there?
- Where?
- At the funeral.
I suppose so.
My mom and dad weren't at theirs.
They were far away when they died.
They had to bury empty boxes.
But we had to pretend anyway.
And I thought that was quite silly.
Well…
…you know,
your parents loved you so, so much that…
…in a way, they'll always be here.
They're not here.
I'm sorry, Miss Clayton.
They're really not.
I've looked and looked. But…
we can pretend
if that makes you feel better.
Oh. No.
Okay, now. Come along, sweetie.
Your pants are getting wet out here.
[Flora giggling]
- What?
- [gigglng continues]
What's so... Hey! No!
Mrs. Grose,
my trousers got wet in the graveyard,
- and Miss Clayton said I wet my pants.
- [Hannah] Oh!
Because in America,
"pants" mean "trousers."
[laughing] That is funny.
She said I wet my pants like a baby.
[Hannah chuckles]
Oh, Miss Clayton,
let me do one for you.
You haven't seen this.
I'll do it in blue, to match your eyes.
- Mm.
- It will be splendid.
[chuckles] Okay.
I, uh…
I guess you didn't make it
to the funeral either.
Oh, no, not my cup of tea,
the church in the village.
I haven't been there since…
God…
since I was married.
Hm.
I had nothing but respect
for Owen's mom, but…
she was long gone.
Dementia is a savage thing.
Jamie said that Owen said it was okay
if we missed it.
No, yeah, that's true.
[sighs] I pay my respect in my own ways.
He understands that funerals
are for the living.
It's up to the living to decide
what they can and cannot bear.
[Dani] Hm.
[Hannah] Right, you. Come along.
Let's get some supper started
for you children, shall we?
Mm-hm. Me and Miles will help.
I can chop things up.
[Hannah]
Oh! I'm not letting you chop things up.
- [Flora] Aww.
- [Hannah] Ohh.
[storyteller]
The au pair found that she lit her candle
not in remembrance of those that she lost,
but to atone for the moments
she didn't remember them.
Those most recent moments
where she'd even been happy
to have forgotten them.
[somber music playing]
I thought you said you were making
our favorite for dinner.
I didn't say it was your favorite.
It's Owen's favorite.
But Owen isn't here.
- Hey, you lot.
- Hello.
- [Hannah] How was it?
- Oh, you know, just a barrel of laughs.
Any chance for a brew?
Yeah, I'll make tea.
[Hannah and Jamie] No!
I'll make it.
Can you, uh…
make sure these two
don't chop their fingers off?
[Jamie] Owen did his best.
Almost no one even remembers how she was
when her mind hadn't gone.
Hate to say it,
but, on some level, it must be a relief.
For Owen, I mean.
Uh, did he, um…
Did he seem relieved?
No.
Didn't seem much of anything.
Shell-shocked.
I'd be relieved, though.
Losing yourself like that.
Being worn away a little bit every day.
Good Christ.
Just shoot me.
Put me out my misery.
It's not fair on anyone.
I don't think fairness
comes into it, dear.
[Jamie] Hm.
[chuckles softly]
[Hannah] That's right, butter.
[Hannah speaking indistinctly]
[eerie music building]
[ominous thud]
[Dani gasps]
Poppins, you all right?
Yeah.
[laughs nervously] I-I'm fine.
I need a…
I need a minute.
[eerie music building]
[music intensifying]
- [music crescendos]
- [Dani gasps]
[gasping] I th... Oh, my God.
Jesus.
What happened?
I thought he was Peter Quint.
Which is ridiculous.
I'm much better looking.
Hey, stand down, Poppins.
Oh! Oh, my God.
I am so sorry, Owen. Uh...
It's actually quite impressive.
No damage done.
- [Dani panting]
- Owen, you prat.
What are you doing leaping out
on innocent Americans?
You're meant to be at a funeral.
Uh, I just needed to leave,
so I got in the car,
and I didn't know I was coming here
un-until I arrived and, well,
I should… I should go, shouldn't I?
- I should go back, 'cause...
- Supper's, uh…
almost done.
You should eat.
I'll bet you haven't eaten.
Mrs. Grose,
how did you know Owen was coming?
She's been making your favorite.
[Hannah] Come on.
Let someone else cook for you
for a change.
[melancholy music playing]
[Owen] Oh, she gave me a heart attack.
[Dani breathing shakily]
[dramatic crescendo]
["Mad About You" by Belinda Carlisle
playing in background]
[woman] God, Dani, look at you.
- I should've kept my dress.
- [Mrs. O'Mara] Hm.
I think I burned it.
Bad memories, bad marriage.
Luckily, Danielle does not share
my taste in men.
Well, lucky for Edmund, okay?
I mean, he's the lucky one
in this equation.
And I'm happy to say, he knows it.
You've got great shoulders.
You know that?
Thank you.
You should wear your hair up on the day.
Show them off.
[Mrs. O'Mara] Karen, come on.
[Karen] Did you let Mike see you in yours?
- [Mrs. O'Mara] No, but...
- Danielle's father helped pick mine out,
and look how that turned out.
I don't think you can blame that
on the dress.
♪ You and I… ♪
[liquid pouring]
[Flora] Mrs. Grose says shepherd's pie
is your favorite…
[whispering]
…so I wanted to bring it to you,
because you're my favorite.
Thank you, sweetheart.
- Hannah, this is pretty great.
- [chuckles]
I remembered what you told me.
Half a teaspoon of Marmite in the gravy.
You can taste it.
Yeah, my, uh…
My mom used to make this
when she had to go away for work.
It would keep for days in the fridge.
Sorry, still recovering.
I was attacked, you know.
Right at the front door.
I'm so sorry.
[Hannah] Hey, you leave her alone.
She can't help it.
She's American.
They're essentially savage people.
[Flora] Will you be going away now, Owen?
Now you don't have to
look after your mom anymore?
- Why? Are you sick of me?
- No!
Admit it, you're all sick of me.
I bet Mrs. Grose can't wait
to get me out of her hair.
That's right.
I'm far too old to be putting up with you
loitering around my kitchen all day.
No, she likes you.
[whispering] Really.
[normal voice] Mrs. Grose, tell him!
Just eat your dinner.
[clears throat]
You're not dying, you know.
[melancholy music playing]
[Owen] What do you mean?
When Mum and Dad died,
I thought I was going to die too.
I was sure of it.
But then I thought…
…what if I was already dead?
But nobody else knew,
and I was walking around dead.
But everybody could see and hear me.
That was dreadful.
It only felt like dying…
…because actually, I was still alive.
You have to be to feel that way.
I wasn't dead.
I was just really, really sad.
But then I learned a secret.
I didn't even need to be sad anymore.
What secret?
Dead doesn't mean gone.
So…
you don't need to be sad.
- Miss Clayton?
- [Dani] Hm?
I think I ought to be allowed
a glass of wine.
[Dani] Mm.
You know, I disagree.
You're all having some.
Anyway… Peter let me have wine sometimes...
For pity's sake.
Will we ever hear the end of Peter Quint?
My mum used to water mine down.
Yeah, gave me half a glass.
My mom too.
Except without the water.
[Owen chuckles]
They do that in France
for the little kids.
[yells] I don't want it watered down!
I want an actual bloody drink!
- [tableware clatters]
- Uh-uh. No!
[ominous music playing]
Good night, Owen.
[Owen] Good night.
Come on. Both of you.
[footsteps receding]
[Dani follows]
You know…
I do like that young woman.
[creaking]
[eerie music playing]
[Flora] Miss Clayton…
…please don't move things around
in my doll house.
Oh, I...
I have a very particular system.
I'm sorry.
[Flora] Oh…
You've got Peter.
Flora.
Yes?
Have Miles or you…
…seen Peter Quint?
Since he left.
Maybe you…
let him into the house.
Look, I'm not angry.
I'd just like for you
to tell me the truth.
No.
Of course not.
We don't let him in the house.
That's not how it works.
- What are you looking at?
- [gasps]
I-I'm sorry?
You do that, a lot.
You look over my shoulder.
What are you looking at?
I don't know what you mean.
Well, that was quite the display,
wasn't it?
What was?
Miles, you and I are a lot alike.
Are we?
Yeah… We are.
In one of the biggest ways people can be.
I didn't have parents growing up either.
[melancholy music playing]
My dad died…
when I was about Flora's age.
And my mom…
…was alive, but, um…
…she wasn't really there anymore.
So, a lot of the times,
I had to be my own parent.
The kids like us…
…like you…
…and me…
…and Flora…
…we're special.
We grow up faster than other kids.
Hm.
And even more special…
we really get to choose the grown-ups
that we keep in our life.
Well, mostly, anyway.
I suppose that is pretty special.
I'm saying this 'cause I want you to know
that I understand.
When you talk a little bit
more grown-up, or…
you wanna act like the grown-ups,
I understand.
I was the same way.
You lost somebody too.
I did.
I've lost people a few ways in my life.
But…
wow!
Miles, you've got some great grown-ups.
Some great people here
to choose for your family.
If you want to.
Good night.
We're all outside, and you're joining us.
[Dani] Hm.
[Owen] Oh, there she is.
Dig in. Some of this wine
hasn't seen daylight
- since before you were born.
- [Dani] Huh.
[Owen] Hannah, give her a bottle.
Hannah.
- Hm?
- [chuckles] Where did you go, love?
I'm so sorry.
I, um… I've been drifting lately.
Quite a bit, I'm afraid. [chuckles]
[light classical music playing]
- Thank you.
- Hey.
- [Dani biting]
- Easy.
- Oh.
You're gonna hurt yourself.
[chuckles nervously]
I'm sorry. I-I… I keep trying to stop.
Look, I know it's been…
it's been a lot.
You always hear that planning a wedding
is one of the most stressful things
you can do.
But you're doing great.
And I just wanted
to give us a night where…
we don't have to talk about any of it.
Uh… Actually…
Eddie, I was thinking
we could just tone it all down.
Maybe just…
I don't know, I don't think
we have to go so… crazy with it.
Y-Yeah, I thought
you wanted a big wedding.
I-I…
If you don't,
that's all perfectly well and fine.
I…
thought I wanted it.
I wanted…
to want it.
But it's just so expensive,
and…
so much…
to organize.
So many people to let down...
Y-Yeah, no, easy. It's dumb.
For a second,
I thought you were gonna say
you didn't wanna get married at all.
Eddie.
I can't.
What did I do?
- Nothing.
- What didn't I do?
- It's not like that.
- Well, then, what's it like, Danielle?
[sighs]
[sniffles]
Thank you.
[somber music playing]
This makes no sense.
I should have said something sooner.
- Yeah, you think?
- I didn't wanna hurt you… or your mom.
Or your family.
And then it was just what we were doing.
- Jesus Christ...
- I just…
thought I was being selfish.
That I could just stick it out,
and, eventually, I would feel
how I was supposed to.
You didn't wanna hurt me, huh?
And…
I love you.
So much.
Even still.
- It's just not... I don't...
- Fuck you, Danielle!
How... W-Why are you doing this to me?
I, um…
I don't... Eddie…
Okay. Yeah.
- Eddie.
- No, let me go.
- Eddie!
- Let me go.
- I'm sorry!
- Jesus, have you not... You've done enough!
[Dani, sobbing] I'm sorry.
Eddie! Eddie!
- [screaming]
- [tires screeching]
[ominous music playing]
[gasping breaths]
Eddie!
[breathing shakily]
[gurgling breaths]
[fire crackling]
Oh, damn it! Fallen soldier.
Owen, be a hero, pass us a fresh bottle.
[Hannah] Oh, I love a bonfire, I do.
Reminds me of being a little girl again.
Mind you,
I do appreciate the adult beverages.
[Jamie] You know, in the old days…
I mean, the really old days,
they used to build giant bonfires
at this time of year.
And talk about the people they'd lost.
Toss in offerings
to drive away evil spirits.
- Old bones, mostly.
- [Owen] I remember.
[slurring slightly] That's why
they call it a bonfire, isn't it?
As I was sayin',
that's why it's called a bonfire.
From the old English, meaning "bone fire."
Build a pile of old bones
and burn away the shadows.
Because from here on in,
the shadows get deeper…
…the nights get longer.
We're heading into the dark,
and we have to hang onto each other.
So we can only carry so much.
So…
anyone got any old bones to throw?
All right, I'll start.
[sniffs]
[melancholy music playing]
[Hannah sighs]
Rebecca.
Rebecca Jessel.
Oh, my God, it's been almost a year.
A year focused on the wrong person.
But, wherever she is,
she's still worth ten of that man.
I won't say his name.
She was brilliant.
She was beautiful.
And she was punished for it.
I don't know why brilliant young women
are always punished.
Rebecca.
All right, my turn.
[clears throat]
Lord and Lady Wingrave.
Dominic and Charlotte.
They were good people.
Old-fashioned…
kind people.
And their kids really miss them.
Nothing can fix that.
Not ever.
But here's Dani Clayton.
She's a bit of a weirdo,
but she's a lot stronger than she thinks.
And if anyone can bring Miles and Flora
back to themselves,
she can.
I'm glad she's here.
I think they would be too.
[sniffs]
What about you, Poppins?
Um…
No, thank you.
That's all right.
No, you... you don't have to.
So…
my mom.
Margaret Sharma.
She was 67.
Except sometimes,
by the end, she forgot that.
Called me by my dad's name,
or her brother's.
You know, I tried to pretend
that I didn't know
who I was supposed to be.
They didn't say
any of that at the funeral.
They wouldn't. They just…
…smoothed it over.
Made it nice.
So, they left out all the bad stuff.
And all the good stuff.
They didn't say how funny she was.
How she would…
wink at you
from across the breakfast table.
She had a sweet tooth.
And a dirty laugh.
And she loved me…
so hard…
it hurt.
Sometimes.
No matter what I did.
She was gone long before she died.
And I miss her.
She was my anchor.
And then I suppose she was my…
…burden.
Christ.
She seemed so small,
at the end.
But still so…
…heavy.
And I…
And all I could do was just…
let her hang onto me
until it was time for her to let go.
And soon I'll let her go, too.
[ominous music building]
- [hospital machines beeping]
- [indistinct chatter]
[inaudible]
[melancholy music playing]
[gasping]
[sobbing]
- [dramatic clang]
- [gasps]
[screams]
[breathing shakily, whimpering]
[bell tolling in distance]
[man] I'm so sorry.
[woman] I'm so sorry.
[man] Thank you.
I'm so sorry, Danielle.
He was a wonderful young man,
and you were a lovely couple.
[Dani] Thank you.
Forgive me.
[distorted] You're doing so well, honey.
[echoing] I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
[ghostly echo]
[distorted] You made him so happy,
right till the end. I hope you know that.
You're being so brave, honey.
I'm really proud of you.
[frightening creaking]
[abruptly] Excuse me!
[sobbing breaths]
[melancholy music resumes]
[sniffles]
I'm sorry.
Hm.
[storyteller] The au pair was tired.
She had been tired for so long.
Yet without even realizing
she was doing it,
she found herself taking her own advice
that she'd given to Miles.
She'd chosen someone
to keep close to her,
that she could feel tired around.
Chosen someone who might help her
burn away the shadows.
I'm not gonna ask if you're all right,
'cause I don't like being lied to.
So, what's wrong?
I thought I saw…
Peter Quint.
- But it wasn't?
- No, of course not.
It's not the first time I've…
seen things that…
aren't there.
So, what else?
Well…
I, uh, I…
I guess I…
…told you about my fiancé…
earlier, didn't I?
Oh, you did.
Yeah.
I was, uh…
hoping we'd, uh, get round to that one.
Yeah.
We were…
We were engaged, and he... he died.
He died and I, uh…
I sometimes, I… It's like…
I see him.
I've never told anybody that.
I'm…
…so, so sorry.
We were about to break up.
We, uh…
I'd broken…
We had broken up.
I'd broken up, I guess.
Right before.
I mean, right…
…right before.
Jesus, Dani, the same day?
Yeah.
Is he here now?
No.
[Dani sighs]
Good.
'Cause, you know,
I'll sort him out for you if I have to.
Oi…
dead boyfriend!
Give it up, mate! It's over!
Seriously, Poppins.
How are you still standing?
Think I'm crazy?
I think you're surprisingly sane,
considering.
[sniffles]
[Jamie] Look…
I know what it feels like…
to feel like you can't find your...
You sure?
Yes.
[emotional music playing]
[ominous thud]
[terrified gasp]
Okay.
Right. [clears throat]
- So… [awkward chuckle]
- I don't know what to…
- I don't know what to say.
- Just forget about it.
It's my fault. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, just…
- Jamie.
- You were just telling me.
Literally telling me
that you weren't up for this.
Just…
Let's…
Let's get back.
Uh, another night, maybe.
Another time, maybe.
[storyteller] But what the gardener
didn't yet understand
was that the au pair
had been telling herself
- to wait another night…
- [knocking]
…another time…
…for years and years.
[knocking continues]
- [Mrs. O'Mara] Oh, oh, hi, Danielle.
- Oh.
Uh, y-you've not been answering
your phone, so I thought I'd come around.
Oh, I'm sorry, Judy, I, um…
Uh, it's, it's, um…
- It's been a bad time.
- Oh, of course.
Honey, I'm... I… I'm worried.
People say
you're not taking care of yourself.
You've got to eat.
I brought some lasagna.
- Oh, my favorite.
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
- No. [laughs gently]
I-I brought something else, too. It's…
Um…
I… [stammering]
I think it's silly, sort of, but…
I thought you might like
to have these.
[eerie music playing]
Oh, uh…
No. Judy, I-I'm sorry, but I...
Really? They were in his things
that came back from the hospital and…
I can't stand to look at them.
I couldn't bear to throw them away,
so I thought…
- Please.
- Okay, of course.
Thank you.
Danielle…
I hope you know that you're still
a really important part of this family.
I hope you know that I mean that.
Come here, come on.
Ohh…
Oh, my sweet thing.
[car approaching]
Okay, um, I-I actually have some stuff
I need to get done.
- Oh, sure, of course. Um…
- Yeah.
Please, please come by for dinner,
any night.
- Okay, I will.
- Okay.
Real soon.
Lots of love.
Okay. Uh, bye-bye now.
Bye, sweetheart.
[somber music playing]
Say it with me.
Hannah Grose in Paris.
You and me, while we still can.
[Jamie] So sorry to interrupt,
but I'm turning into a pumpkin.
Come on, Owen, time to go home.
Oh, it's about that time.
Well… [clears throat]
I'll-co-hol you later.
[Hannah] God, even for you.
Drive safe.
[Jamie] I know the road. We'll be fine.
It's all good.
Christ, the state of you.
[Flora] Miss Clayton?
[frightening musical swell]
Miles!
[sniffs]
[Miles] Miss Clayton!
What the he...
What the heck are you doing down here?
Fl-Flora had a nightmare.
[Dani sighs]
Okay, let's get you two back to bed.
Not just yet.
I'm quite frightened.
It was a horrible dream.
Well, you should be in bed.
Not now, I won't.
[sighs]
What happened?
There was something horrible
and loud in the wardrobe.
Mm-hm.
Moving from in there to under…
A creature!
A creature under my bed.
And it knew my name.
And it was reaching out,
and it knew my name.
And it said it wanted to do awful things.
And it had bones for hands.
That sounds awful.
It was my mum.
[eerie music playing]
I am so…
sorry, Flora.
That sounds like an awful dream.
Well.
Let's get you two back to bed, okay?
Just a minute.
I don't want to just yet.
I was so scared,
but I'm feeling better already.
Just…
a-a few minutes more.
Just a minute, really.
In... in fact,
c-could I have a glass of milk?
[Dani] Of course.
[melancholy music playing]
I'm sorry.
No.
It's okay, okay?
There's nothing to be scared of.
- Quite right.
- Yeah.
Good night…
sweet girl.
[ominous music playing]
[sighs] Talk about this in the morning.
[somber music playing]
[ominous music plays]
[music intensifies]
[eerie music building]
[Dani sniffs]
[melancholy music plays]
It's just you and me, then.
Hm?
[fire roars]
[wind whistles]
[closing music playing]