[theme music playing]
[gentle music playing]
[woman]
We lay my love and I…
[insects chirping]
…beneath the weeping willow.
[water gurgling]
[gasps]
[woman] But now alone I lie…
…and weep beside the tree.
Singin', "O willow waly…"
…by the tree that weeps with me.
Singing, "O willow waly…"
…till my lover return to me.
[water gurgling]
[dinging]
[man] Can I have your attention, please?
You'll get to your meals momentarily,
but first…
the bride has asked me to speak.
I thought she was joking!
Why invite such catastrophe
upon your own wedding?
- [guests chuckling]
- [man] But, as she explained,
"No, heavens, no. Not the wedding,
the practice meal."
The rehearsal dinner, for God's sakes!
I must claim my right as a slightly drunk,
completely jet-lagged Englishman
to well and truly speak my mind.
Because I want to warn you all,
you young people
have absolutely no idea
what you are letting yourselves in for.
Oh…
Here's a horrifying statistic.
Did you know
that almost half of marriages these days
do not end up in divorce?
[guests chuckling]
That means there's a strong probability
that you two get to watch each other die.
And that's the preferred outcome.
To truly love another person
is to accept that the work of loving them
is worth the pain of losing them.
And that's it.
That's all.
And if that scares you
as much as it scares me,
then I say run.
Go off and do drugs on a beach in Bali.
Devote yourself to a life
of the mind. Run!
Run while you still can. You're young,
you're strong. The world… [fades out]
[bride] No, I'm serious,
- we actually refused to stay here.
- She refused.
[female guest 1] I didn't know
staying here was even an option.
[bride] There's three suites
in the castle,
- and Jack wanted to stay here…
- [Jack] Just one night.
…before we left for the honeymoon.
Just tomorrow. Just after the reception,
so we could just stumble upstairs.
[bride] But I said,
"No way, not after those stories."
[female guest 1] Wait, just the stories?
- You didn't see her?
- No! God no, I didn't see her.
If I saw a dead woman, a dead nun,
no less, crying in the corners,
- we would not be getting married here.
- Okay, it's just a story.
This place used to be a convent for, like,
a few decades in the '40s.
It's part of the sales package.
They can charge a few hundred extra
for the ghost story.
Look, I love a good ghost story,
I just don't want to sleep in one.
[female guest 2]
We honeymooned in Ireland.
They kept telling us
to look out for Seamus,
the stable boy.
- Oh, Seamus.
- [guests chuckling]
[female guest 2] They said his head was
crushed in where a horse had kicked him.
[bride] Ghost stories are worse
when there's a kid.
[female guest 2] Adds a little something,
doesn't it? [chuckles]
I have a story.
Well…
…it isn't really my story.
It belongs to someone I knew.
And it's not exactly short.
Well, it seems we have time enough, and…
wine enough.
Why not?
All right, then.
A ghost story.
Again, this story isn't mine,
but it is full of ghosts of all sorts.
And if a child gives the effect,
another turn of the screw…
…what do you say to two?
The teacher was, by choice,
a solitary young woman.
Come up to London in trepidation
to answer in person an advertisement…
…placed by one Lord Henry Wingrave
regarding his young nephew and niece,
who were in need of an au pair.
A full-time position, it said.
Live-in, at that,
in his old family home in Essex.
A great good place,
alone in the country.
[cars honking]
Miss Clayton, is it?
Oh, call me Dani. Hi there.
Please, have a seat.
- You're a teacher?
- Yes.
Or I was.
Fourth grade.
In the States.
Mm-hmm.
Been in England long?
[sighs] About six months.
Six months? During which time, you've…
Well, I've…
[in British accent]
…fallen quite in love with London.
God.
Tea? Coffee?
[without accent] No, thank you.
Haven't quite mastered tea yet.
I'm used to it coming in a pitcher.
Full of ice cubes…
…and lemon wedges, and…
Well, it's a whole different thing here.
[Henry] Yes, it is.
You've no previous experience
as an au pair.
Well, I…
I've quite a bit of experience
with children, Mr. Wingrave.
In a classroom,
but this is a full-time, live-in position.
I know, that's actually why
- I responded to the ad.
- The children are wonderful.
Exceptional, really,
my niece and my nephew.
Exceptional children, as I said.
But challenging, both.
Miles, my nephew, is back home
from boarding school early.
He needs structure,
discipline more than ever, I fear.
Mm-hmm.
Well, can I ask why he was sent home?
- Spring session shouldn't end...
- You'd be expected to tutor him
so he doesn't fall behind.
In that respect, your classroom experience
may actually be of use.
The same with Flora,
my niece.
You'd tutor her as well.
Your ad mentioned the position
was in the countryside?
In Bly,
my family's country house.
The children are used to Bly, they…
spent summers and holidays there
with their parents,
before they passed.
It's a great good place, the manor.
There are few others on the grounds.
A cook, groundskeeper.
They stay in town.
There is a live-in housekeeper,
but the children…
would be your responsibility
and yours alone.
Don't call on me
unless it's an emergency.
I'm extraordinarily busy.
I understand.
You know,
one of my more unique assignments
at my school
was specific
to some of our highest-need children,
- one of whom had actually lost their par...
- What's the catch?
I'm sorry?
The catch. You're what?
Thirty?
Mid-twenties?
I wonder…
What's the catch?
You're younger than most
who'd apply for this sort of thing.
What makes a woman of your age
want to give up her life
to take care of someone else's children?
A life in America, at that.
Full-time as well.
It seems odd… to me, to be frank.
Hm.
It seems odd to me too.
The listing, I mean.
A full-time position
in a beautiful country manor
to two exceptional children.
But I saw your ad six months ago.
When I first arrived in London.
And I have seen it every month since.
Seems to me an easy position to fill.
At least as you've described.
So, I suppose you're right.
What is the catch?
That really is the question.
[rock music playing in background]
Thank you.
[cars honking in distance]
[Henry sighs]
Alright, James?
[clears throat]
I know I didn't get the job,
and that's totally cool.
But that was the most awkward
job interview of my entire life.
So, I think we should toast to it,
Mr. Wingrave.
Or do you prefer it in your tea?
[Dani] So…
you can tell me now, right?
I'm honestly so, so curious.
About what?
The catch.
- [chuckling] Oh, no.
- No, come on!
Well…
…imagination, I suppose.
No one wants the job.
Oh, come on. No one?
We did find someone for a while.
Last summer.
A promising young woman.
The children liked her.
Mm-hmm.
And then, she… [sighs]
Well, I-I suppose she died.
It was her own fault, to be blunt.
Her choice, to be blunter,
but she died on the grounds.
People are superstitious,
especially in the country.
So, now it's a story.
These small children in that huge house
with their dead parents,
and now, their dead governess.
[sighs]
Never mind the parents died abroad.
Never mind the governess took her own…
So, yes, the story precedes the job,
- at least at all the agencies.
- [Dani sighs]
Now, no one wants it.
Superstition…
imagination.
What about you?
What was your catch?
I, um…
…couldn't be at home anymore.
Have you ever taught a classroom
of 25 kids?
- No, I absolutely have not, I'm afraid.
- [Dani chuckles]
Well…
you take to them.
You love them.
Even the worst ones. [laughs]
You just do.
And you try to help…
…but there's just too many of them.
[chuckles]
And too little of you.
So, you just…
The ad said two children.
I figure I don't know the specifics,
but I know how to handle kids.
Maybe I can make a difference.
I could. I could make a difference.
A real difference.
With just two. [chuckles]
Then I noticed the position was…
full-time, live-in.
And then it clicked.
They've lost someone.
Now, I understand death.
I know what loss is.
[breathing heavily]
[Dani]
I'm gonna be in England a while longer.
Quite a while, actually.
I got a job.
Yeah, I-I got a trial position,
at least to the end of the summer.
But it could go on for quite...
No, I know. I know it's longer
than I said, but I got a job.
- I'm not.
- [somber music playing]
I'm not running from anything,
and it hurts me when you say that.
You know it hurts me when you say that.
Anyway…
…you can reach me
when I get to the house.
I'll call you… when I have the number.
I love you, Mom.
[music intensifying]
- Uh, Miss Clayton?
- Yeah.
- Owen.
- Hi.
- Pleased to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Let me get... Let's get that.
- [Dani] Yeah. I have some bags.
No worries. Thank you.
Thank you.
[somber orchestral music playing]
[car thudding]
Oh, uh, sorry about that.
Country roads.
How long was I out?
Oh, a while.
Are you still on American time?
Oh, no.
I just haven't got much sleep lately.
Ah.
Well, hostels aren't terribly restful.
I mean,
you'll find it much quieter out here.
- [Dani] It's gorgeous.
- Is it?
What?
I can't tell anymore, personally.
Uh, I was born in Bly.
The town, I mean, not the manor.
I escaped for a bit.
Spent some time in France.
- What?
- Studying to be a chef.
Yet, here I was,
just thinking you were a driver.
No, no, no, only sometimes,
when Henry asks me.
- [Dani chuckles]
- Frankly, I'm a rubbish driver. [chuckles]
But not a bad cook, turns out.
Why'd you come back?
- From France?
- Family.
And this job pays the bills,
while I'm here.
- [Dani] Mm-hmm.
- And it keeps me close.
Well, there are worse places to be stuck,
believe me.
I've actually never liked Bly.
The people here, most of them,
they're born here, they die here.
The whole town
is one big gravity well.
And it's easy to get stuck.
[Dani sighs]
God, is that…
[Owen] Like I said, plenty to love.
Can I get out
and walk the rest of the way?
[insects chittering, birds chirping]
[girlsinging in distance]
♪ Singing, "O willow waly" ♪
♪ By the tree that weeps with me ♪
♪ Till my lover returns to me ♪
[Dani] Oh, what a beautiful song!
What song?
- The one you were just singing.
- [gasps] You're Miss Clayton!
You must be.
Oh, and you're so pretty.
I told Miles you'd be pretty.
How perfectly splendid!
You must be Flora.
I hope I didn't startle you.
- Not at all. You're expected.
- Oh.
I'm just so, so pleased you're here.
- [Dani chuckles]
- And Mrs. Grose will want to see you.
And Miles.
- [Dani] Mm-hmm.
- And Owen, and Jamie.
You know, I've met Owen.
When did you meet Owen?
On the car ride up.
Now, what's that?
Oh, this.
Just a silly thing, really.
Just a moment.
[soft piano music playing]
- What a gorgeous lake.
- Oh, you mustn't.
It really is just a smelly old pond.
And, you know, there are leeches in there.
Horrid little things, like vampire slugs,
and the nastiest beetles.
Who needs that old pond, anyway?
There's so much else
that's so much better.
It really is perfectly splendid
to meet you.
- [Dani laughs]
- Miles!
She's here! She's here!
And she's even prettier than I imagined.
This is her!
Hi, Miles.
So pleased to meet you, my lady.
- [kisses]
- Oh, well, what the gentleman.
And this must be Mrs. Grose.
- Hi!
- I'm sorry, um…
Goodness, I wa... I was miles away.
I'm Dani.
Oh, it's a pleasure to meet you.
Hannah Grose.
Well, I-I see you made it in one piece.
- Yeah.
- Was the journey okay?
Oh, it was perfect.
- Oh, wonderful.
- Yeah.
Yes, that... that Owen is a fine young man.
- Good sort. [chuckles]
- Mm-hmm.
Right, well, um,
let... let's find our way inside.
I'm sure Miss Clayton
is eager to see the house.
- Oh, yes.
- [chuckles] Right, well, come along.
- Now...
- You can call me Dani.
Nonsense.
Children, you will call her Miss Clayton,
like we agreed.
[storyteller] Her first look at Bly
yielded no discomfort,
no foreboding.
It was exactly as Lord Wingrave
had described.
A great, good place.
And it yawned open to welcome her home.
[door creaks shut]
This is the foyer,
and it's perfectly splendid.
- It's beauti...
- Come along!
This is the kitchen,
and it's perfectly splendid.
And this is Owen.
He's the cook,
and he's splendid.
- [Dani] Mm-hmm.
- Perfectly.
Hello, everyone.
Hey again.
Hi!
Hi, Flora.
- This way.
- [Dani chuckles]
[Flora] The paintings are all original,
which means they're painted by hand,
and they're perfectly splendid.
This is the classroom.
It's…
…quite boring.
These are the lovely stairs,
but you mustn't run on them.
If you fall, you can injure yourself,
and the stairs are not forgiving.
Not forgiving in the least. Do you see?
Mrs. Grose says
they're brutal on the knees…
- Oh.
- …but I don't have any issues.
- [laughs gently] Gorgeous!
- [Hannah] It is.
A great good place.
Heaven for the children.
But mind the stairs,
they're brutal on the knees.
[Dani chuckles]
And this is where our parents
used to live.
We don't go in there anymore.
[Flora] We don't go in there anymore.
It's all covered up.
[Hannah]
This room is closed at the moment.
And covered up. But underneath it all,
it's all just perfectly splendid.
[Hannah]
Let's leave Miss Clayton to freshen up.
[Flora] Of course.
But then we must show her
the statue garden.
She'll see it all eventually, Flora.
We'll see you after you've settled.
And once you have,
we'll have to show you the rest.
[Hannah] Flora!
[Flora] Coming.
[giggles]
Oh!
I'm sorry. May I come in?
Yes. Of course.
Perhaps knock from now on.
Of course.
I just wanted to say
how happy we all are that you're here.
And to give you this.
Not much, I know.
Just a little something
to make you feel more welcome.
Thank you.
It's very pretty.
I'm just gonna finish up here
and see you in a few minutes, okay?
Of course.
Thank you.
[teapot whistling]
[Dani] I hope it's all right.
I haven't quite figured out tea yet, so…
Mm. It's fine, dear.
- [Miles] Mm.
- [Owen] Dinner is served.
- [gasps theatrically] Wow!
- [Owen] There you go, mate.
- [Miles] Thank you.
- Owen makes the best dinners.
He made me
a macaroni-and-cheese sandwich once,
which was divine.
So, what brings a young American like you
to England?
And Bly of all places.
Oh, you know,
just wanted to see the world.
- [Hannah] Mm-hmm.
- And what do you think of it so far?
- Um, Bly? Or the world?
- I want to go to Australia.
Or Florida, because it's almost my name.
- [Hannah chuckles]
- That's right.
- It's just so gorgeous here.
- Yeah.
I know I keep saying that,
but there's no other word.
- I could think of a few others.
- Oh, hush now, Owen.
- He likes to wind me up.
- She likes being wound up.
Aren't you joining us?
Oh, uh…
Um, not tonight, sweetheart.
I've got to go home to my mom.
Disappointing.
You sound just like her.
Is she feeling better?
Much.
Better every day, I reckon.
All right. [sighs]
Good night, you lovely young lady.
And good night to you, too, Flora.
[Hannah] Ugh, heaven help me, this man.
Enjoy.
So, he lives with his mother?
[sighs] Lives for her, more like.
That's why he came back from Paris.
- [Dani] Mm.
- She took ill. Quite ill, I've heard.
- I'm sorry.
- Yeah.
He said she's getting better.
Yeah, better every day.
He says that, but he leaves earlier
and earlier these days.
He used to stay every night for supper.
Maybe she feels well enough to eat,
so he has to get home in time
to cook for her.
I'm sure you're right, sweetheart.
What? You're not gonna eat?
Oh… Oh, well, yeah.
- I'll have it later.
- [Dani] Okay.
[whispering]
I'll give you some pointers.
Thank you.
[Flora] I wish to look like a gnome.
A bubble gnome.
[chuckling]
Well, you're sure getting there.
[Flora giggles]
What?
It really is very silly, isn't it?
[Dani chuckles]
Yes, you're a very silly girl.
Where did you get that?
- What?
- The butterfly clip.
Oh…
Um…
Miles gave it to me.
He shouldn't have done that.
Why not?
Because it doesn't belong to you.
Who does it belong to?
- Miss Jessel.
- Who's that?
The other one.
- Before you.
- I'm…
I'm so sorry.
I…
I was wrong. It's actually fine.
Can I get out now?
Can I play with my dolls?
Yeah. Fifteen minutes, okay?
[ominous music plays]
[mirror squeaks]
[Dani sighs]
You know, I've gone
to every kind of school you can think of.
Have you?
Even a boarding school once, like you.
I know how hard it can be.
It's not so bad.
Well…
…you're home now, aren't you?
Look, you can talk to me
about whatever you'd like.
About school.
Anything that happened there.
I promise, I've heard it all.
It's very kind of you.
Good night, Dani.
Good night.
You know, Mrs. Grose seems to think
you should call me Miss Clayton.
Didn't you like it?
I'm sorry?
The butterfly.
Oh, I… [clicks tongue]
[sighs]
You know, Flora…
was a little upset, I think.
She's always a little upset.
Whether she admits it or not.
But she's so, so glad you're here.
And so am I.
Well, thank you for making me feel
so welcome.
[Dani] Bedtime!
- And I'm finished.
- [Dani] Mm-hmm.
Perfect timing.
Is that me?
Why, no, silly. You're you.
It's just a dolly.
Touché.
[gentle piano music plays]
[Dani] Who are all these?
[Flora] Why, they're dolls, of course.
[Dani chuckles]
You, miss, have a lot of dolls,
and we're going to learn
how to pick them all up
before we go to sleep, okay?
[Flora] Put her back.
She stays…
there.
And you're all tucked in.
And it's time for bed.
It's just lovely that you're here.
Thank you, Flora.
But you have to promise me something.
Of course.
You have to promise me
that you'll stay in your room.
Don't leave your room at night.
Stay in your bed until morning.
I don't think I can promise that.
But it's certainly a good rule
for you and your brother...
But you must.
Okay.
At least for tonight.
Now get some sleep.
[crickets chirping]
[storyteller]
The night found the au pair restless.
It was as Flora had said.
The rooms were larger at night,
as though the house itself
had inhaled deeply
as the sun disappeared,
expanding as it held its breath
for the morning.
That sense of expansion
wasn't only indoors, either.
Gazing out, she found that the terrace
and the whole place,
the lawn and the garden beyond it,
and all she could see of the park,
were empty,
with a great emptiness.
An emptiness that called out
to be explored.
[chilling musical swell]
[clicking]
[sighs]
[creaking]
[chilling musical swell]
- [teapot whistling]
- [gasps]
[sighs]
Tastes good to me.
[crickets growing louder]
[sound intensifies shrilly]
[Dani] What a beautiful day.
[birds chirping]
Well, I'll never get tired of this place,
I swear.
What's the matter?
[Flora] I'm very cross with you.
[Miles] Miss Clayton!
Come see what I found!
You left your room last night
even though you promised you wouldn't.
- Miss Clayton!
- [Dani] How do you know that?
You've got to stay in your room.
Come and see!
- Why?
- So she doesn't see you.
[Dani] Who?
The lady.
What lady?
- The lady in the lake.
- [Miles] Flora.
Flora, look.
Miss Clayton…
- Look!
- [Flora screams]
[Miles laughs quietly]
Look, I've been a teacher
for nine years, Miles.
That's almost your whole life.
[tender piano music plays]
In all that time, a lot of kids have tried
to scare me in a lot of different ways,
and you know what I learned?
I'm a lot braver than people think.
Including me.
[Miles] I wasn't trying to scare you,
Miss Clayton.
I knew you wouldn't be frightened.
Did you?
Of course.
I knew that about you right away.
Hm.
Is that something you used to do
at school?
Play pranks?
Tricks.
I never quite saw the point of tricks.
Your uncle told me a little bit
about your problems at school.
You spoke with my uncle?
Well, of course. He hired me.
Did he ask about us?
All he did was talk about you two.
He misses you both.
Very much.
No, he doesn't.
Of course he does.
Shall we give him a ring and ask?
[storyteller] The au pair's heart ached
for the boy's pain.
But, like the very weather at Bly,
his moods proved quick to change.
As sun, clouds, and rain would appear
without hint or warning,
so, too, did the children's moods.
As though time and nature held…
secret laws…
just for them.
- [music and birdsong fade into silence]
- [Dani's breath echoing]
[haunting whoosh]
[birdsong resumes]
[Owen] There she is.
They got away from me.
[phone rings]
[Owen] No, I'll get it. You have a seat.
Relax.
If that's even possible.
Hello?
What's for lunch?
- Bangers and mash.
- Hello?
Hello?
Flora, don't.
[Dani chuckles]
- [Miles] Who was it?
- Oh, don't know. They hung up.
- Again?
- Another one?
Oh, we've had some, uh, prank calls.
- Probably just a wrong number.
- Thank you.
[Hannah] You're welcome.
- [Owen] Miss Clayton.
- Mm.
Thank you.
[storyteller] The gardener
did not even introduce herself
to the new au pair.
She barely acknowledged her at all.
Simply treated her
as if she'd always been there.
The others in the room
just assumed they'd already met,
which, if she were honest,
was how the au pair felt
when she first saw the young woman.
So, who decided it was a good idea
to feed these wee gremlins?
[Flora] We're not gremlins!
- We're very good children.
- [Miles] Hm.
Oh, is that right?
See, I'm not so sure.
Owen, what do you think?
[Owen] Oh…
It's hard to say.
I'm gonna have to get water on them
to be sure.
Mm.
- Like this?
- [Flora grunts]
[gardener laughs]
There you go.
- [Hannah] There you go, dear.
- [Owen] You're a star. Thank you.
Was there somebody…
working on the grounds today?
Maybe a repairman or something?
No, I don't believe so.
'Cause I saw a guy,
on the parapet, on my way in.
On the parapet?
Yeah.
- Can't imagine.
- [Owen] I've not been up there.
[Hannah] Well, why would you?
Are you sure you saw someone up there?
[Dani] Absolutely.
I waved, he didn't wave back.
Well, we do get ramblers sometimes.
People that wanna have a look
at the gardens.
They take liberties,
but if one made it onto the parapet...
They can't get up there,
not without going through the house.
The only way up there
is through the old wing.
And where don't we go?
[both] The old wing.
You must have imagined it, dear.
- You're not gonna eat anything?
- Oh, no, I already ate.
Just here for the company.
You must try this.
[Hannah] Flora, don't.
[birds chirping, insects chittering]
[quiet, unsettling music plays]
[Dani gasps]
Oh…
Did you... Did you find anyone?
- No.
- [Hannah] Oh.
I didn't.
But…
I did find some…
I'm sorry. Am I interrupting you?
[chuckles awkwardly]
Oh, no. No, not at all.
What did you find?
Ah.
It's Flora.
- Ah, Flora, Flora…
- I've seen a few of these.
Well, you can't judge them.
Not after what they've been through.
Mr. Wingrave told you about their parents,
I'm sure.
- Only that they passed.
- Mm.
Two years ago, now.
Miles was only eight. Flora, six.
[Dani] Mm.
And that's enough bad luck
for two children to bear,
but then to think…
what came after.
Your... your predecessor.
- Miss Jessel?
- Yeah.
Rebecca.
God…
Rebecca. Poor Rebecca.
She was…
She was a bright young thing.
She was ambitious, intelligent.
Kind of heart.
But…
…there was a man.
Which really is the only thing
that can bring down a woman like that.
All the world's vices
in disguise of its graces.
Anyway, the less said about him,
the better.
You know he skipped town?
With a tidy sum of Henry's money
and the poor thing's heart.
Stole a lot, that one. Sticky fingers.
And to see her
in the days leading up to it.
So broken.
So empty.
She was gone long before
she waded into that lake.
Oh…
Flora found her.
And Jamie found Flora.
To hear her tell it…
Rebecca's body in that water.
Face down.
And little Flora just…
…stone-still…
…staring.
And I…
To think I used to cringe
when I heard the children…
running through the house,
screaming and kicking up a fuss.
But in the weeks
after Miss Jessel there…
Silence, it never felt so terrible.
And now…
Now, when I hear them…
cry, or… [sniffles]
…scream, or yell…
God, it's the most beautiful sound
in the world.
- I'm so sorry.
- [Dani] No.
- It's all right.
- Oh, God, look at me.
[sighs]
Oh…
It's a talisman.
A tiny game of Flora's
to keep us all safe.
Us.
God. My God, these children.
Both of them
trying in their own way, I think.
[Dani] Mm.
[inhales deeply]
You know, I should head back.
Owen and Jamie
will be leaving for the evening.
But I'm happy to watch the children
before bed if you'd like a moment.
Wh-What are the candles for?
The dead.
There's more of them than I'd like,
the older I get.
I'm sorry.
Oh, God, no need. [sniffs]
I have been, and I remain,
a very happy woman.
[Dani laughs gently]
[somber orchestral music playing]
[insects chittering]
Good evening, Miss Clayton.
Time for bed.
Is it?
I shouldn't think so.
No more games, Miles.
Do you like games, Dani?
Not at bedtime.
[Miles]
It's the best time for games, really.
[Flora] Stop being weird, Miles!
He's so weird sometimes.
[Dani] And you…
sweet thing.
Imagination.
I love…
your imagination.
And everyone in this house is so lucky…
that you're using yours to keep us safe.
Just promise me…
that when you're keeping us all safe,
that you keep yourself safe first.
And no going on the parapet.
Okay.
You really are, you know?
I'm what?
Perfectly splendid.
[Dani chuckles softly]
Good night, sweet girl.
Oh…
I'm sorry!
You know, you need to make sure
that you pick these up.
I would hate to break…
Where would you like her tonight?
In the house or under the dresser?
[Miles] Miss Clayton?
[Dani sighs]
I was just about to tuck you in.
There's an electric fan
in Flora's cupboard.
I cannot sleep without it, I'm afraid.
That... that's right.
My cupboard.
Would you fetch it for me?
I'm awfully sorry.
Oh…
Sure thing.
Well…
here you go.
She can sleep with you tonight.
Okay, let's look.
Hmm.
- I don't see it!
- [Miles] It must be under some clothes.
Okay.
- [door slams]
- [lock clicks]
Guys.
I said no games.
Open up!
Open the door!
Open it!
- [lock rattling]
- [Miles] I'm trying!
Miles!
[Miles] I'm trying!
Flora!
[Flora] It's stuck. We're really trying!
Okay, it's not... it's not funny.
Open the door.
[Flora] We'll have to find the key.
It really is stuck.
- We're very sorry!
- The key is in the lock, Flora.
Turn the key.
- [door rattling]
- [Miles] It's not! We can't find it!
I'm being serious.
Open the door!
[door stops rattling]
[ominous music playing]
Miles!
Flora?
Open the door!
[door rattling]
[yelling] Open the door!
- [pounding on door]
- [Dani yelling] Open the door!
[screaming] Open the door!
[panicked breathing]
No!
Open the door!
Guys!
[Dani screams]
[panicked whimpering]
[screaming] Let me out!
Let me out!
[Dani crying]
- Let me out! Let me out!
- [pounding on door]
Let me out! Let me out!
[Dani pounding on door, whimpering]
[insects chirping]
[door unlocking]
- [Dani gasps]
- [Miles] I'm so sorry.
We're dreadfully sorry.
[breathing heavily]
Bed!
It was an accident.
Now!
I am sorry.
- Please, don't be cross.
- We'll talk about it in the morning.
[sniffles]
[sighs]
[door creaks shut]
[sobbing softly]
[sighs heavily]
[sniffles]
Were you outside?
[footsteps creaking]
- [insects chirping]
- [footsteps descending]
[panting heavily]
[somber orchestral music playing]
[closing music plays]