[theme music playing]
[sipping]
[knock at door]
The post is here.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
[footsteps recede]
[pensive music playing]
[sighs]
[storyteller] Lord Wingrave greatly
preferred the confines of his office
to the comfort of his London flat.
He trapped himself there,
day and night tucked away in his work,
in his nightly routine,
until he was entombed in it.
Until there was no room left
inside of him for anything else.
Until he felt…
- most like himself.
- [footsteps approaching]
For better or worse.
[receptionist] Miss Clayton phoned.
And?
Just an update.
Wanted to report about the children.
And how are the children?
She says they're well,
but she's a bit concerned,
and that she's happy to elaborate,
if you'd like to schedule a call.
Says there's some things,
nothing alarming she says, but…
some things you may want to hear about.
No need.
I'm happy the children are well.
Of course. [inhales deeply]
Have a good weekend.
[receptionist] Uh…
Thank you.
[sips]
[door opens and closes]
[sighs]
[ominous music playing]
[sniffs]
Scotch or bourbon tonight?
Scotch it is.
[haunting music playing quietly]
[opens bottle]
[exhales slowly]
[sighs]
[frightening clicking]
[music intensifying]
[dramatic crescendo]
[exhales]
[motor roars]
[Dominic] Charlotte!
Charlotte!
Too late?
- [Henry] You're on time.
- I'm on time?
- Yeah, she's close but not yet.
- Thank God for that.
Charlotte, I'm here!
I… I don't think she cares much
right now, to be honest.
She's early.
She's quite early.
It happens, doesn't it?
I'd never have left
if I'd thought she'd be this early.
Well, you made it, you're fine.
I'd never miss the birth
of my own daughter.
[panting] I'd never.
Why not the hospital?
It was faster
to have the doctor come here.
This early,
you should take her to a hospital.
A hospital is two hours away.
The doctor was 40 minutes away.
- Miles?
- He's fine. He's asleep.
Okay.
- I'm here, darling.
- [Charlotte groaning]
Here's my girl.
My girls.
How are my girls?
[whimpers, screams]
[panting]
[pensive music playing]
[screams]
[Charlotte continues screaming and crying]
[birdsong]
[unsettling hushed sounds]
[knocking on door]
[Jamie] Don't usually see you
this early in the a.m.
Uh…
Yeah, well, I-I knew… um…
I know that y-you start early
on Thursdays.
[Dani] So,
I thought I'd bring you some coffee.
You Yanks and your coffee.
You might like it.
Cheers.
- [spits]
- I'm not the best at coffee, either.
- [chuckles]
- [Jamie] Ahem.
How's your week been?
It's been okay.
Yeah, um…
The kids have been
a little strange, lately.
Everything's been a bit strange, really.
And no Owen.
No you.
[Jamie] Mm. [clears throat]
I seem to see less and less of Hannah.
She just…
goes out, I guess.
By herself.
Sometimes, I just turn around,
and-and she's gone.
Sometimes, people just need to be alone.
Did you wake up just for this?
No.
You just waited for me to come back.
I-I knew that you were coming back
today, but…
no, no particular reason.
Are the kids awake?
Um, no. No, they're asleep.
So, you just got up with the sun.
And you're, uh…
tiptoeing around the kitchen
making awful coffee by yourself,
just to come say hi at six in the morning,
for no particular reason?
Poppins, you flirt.
Fine.
I-I… I don't like the way we left it.
And how did we leave it?
Wrong.
And-And I wanted to…
I wanted to start doing something right.
So, I thought I'd start with coffee.
Are you sure about that?
Because every time
I think you might be sure,
you've got this irritating habit
of jumping back,
like you've just seen a scary bug.
Maybe that's best, really.
I like you.
But I also like my life the way it is.
Nice and boring.
[scoffs]
Yeah, I-I wouldn't want to disrupt that.
[in forced Cockney accent]
Gotta keep things proper borin',
'aven't we?
[Jamie snickers]
[in normal accent]
Look, there's-there's a pub in Bly, right?
There is.
Would you want to get a drink?
Away from the house.
Away from all this.
That could be kind of boring, right?
Could be dreadfully boring.
Okay, so I could ask Hannah
to watch the kids one night.
And you and me…
could get a boring, old drink…
in a boring, old pub…
and see where that takes us.
You know I live above that pub, right?
I told you that already, didn't I?
Got a little flat.
Right above the boring, little pub.
[eerie music playing]
Flora?
[eerie music plays]
[Dani] Flora!
Flora, Flora!
Hey, hey.
Hey.
What are you doing?
I don't feel good.
How long have you been out here?
I just woke up.
I don't know.
[suspenseful crescendo]
- [music stops abruptly]
- [birdsong]
[soft thud]
[Flora] Hello?
Miles?
Is that you?
[quiet creaking]
[creak]
Wait!
Who are you?
Did you hear me?
I'm Flora.
[ominous shrill sound]
[Flora screams]
[screaming] Mummy, Mummy!
[panting]
- [whimpers]
- [unsettling music playing]
Mummy!
What is it?
There's someone in my room.
A little boy.
Oh, Miles!
- For God's sake.
- It's not Miles.
It's not. It's…
Uncle Henry?
Oh.
- Hello, Flora.
- [Charlotte chuckles awkwardly]
What are you doing here?
I didn't drive back
to the city last night.
Uncle Henry slept over.
In one of the guest rooms.
And I was just saying good morning
just now.
[Charlotte] Yes.
And I-I just heard you say
there was someone in your room.
Come! See, quickly!
You see? No one there.
Not now,
but there was.
There definitely was.
And stop saying there wasn't!
All right, all right. There was.
There was a little boy, you say?
Little, like me.
Oh, surely no one is as little as you.
[Charlotte chuckles]
Well, if there is a little boy,
and you're the only one who can see him,
perhaps he'd like to be your friend.
No, there's something wrong with him.
His face isn't finished.
- Oh, no.
- [Charlotte chuckles]
He doesn't even have a mouth.
Well, I should think
he would be a very good listener.
And there's almost nothing
more important than that in a friend.
[Charlotte] That's right.
And if he can listen, perhaps he'd love
to hear some of your stories, Flora.
But… how can he be my friend
if… he can't tell me his name?
Well, perhaps you could give him a name.
You could give him
a whole story of his own.
Uh, I had a friend
when I was your age, too.
In this house, in fact.
He was a soldier,
and I was very afraid of him,
until I gave him a story.
Was he happy when you gave him one?
Oh, he was.
So, maybe I could do that.
Give him a story.
That's my sweet girl.
When's Daddy coming home
from Scotland, Mummy?
Uh…
U-Um…
Soon, my love.
This is strange.
It is?
I think…
because…
Well, I suppose it's because I'm too old.
Isn't it?
Yes, I expect that's it.
I feel like I should be littler.
Well, you should be five years old,
in fact.
You were five years old
when this happened.
[Flora] So,
why aren't I five years old?
I'm not five years old,
I'm eight years old.
Why is my age all wrong?
You know why, don't you?
Because this is a memory.
That's right.
[Flora] I've been tucked away again,
in another memory.
You have.
This is happening more and more,
isn't it?
It is.
[Flora] I keep getting tucked away
in one memory or another,
and, then, I start to realize it,
and it'll be over as soon as I…
Wake up.
Hey.
Hey. [chuckles softly]
Hey, you just…
You just nodded off there.
[chuckles]
You just, um…
What... What happened?
[sighs] I don't know.
I'm sorry.
I'm having a bit of a moment.
Oh, it's all right, we…
We, uh…
we just wanna make sure that you're okay.
What were you doing?
[Dani] We were talking.
We were, uh, talking about the walk.
Your-Your walk last night.
And, uh…
And you just, um…
Well, it-it looked like y-you fainted,
but, uh…
are you okay now?
I'm quite tired.
I'd like to go back to sleep.
But to dream…
not a memory.
Dream, this time.
[Dani] Okay.
Okay.
[knocking on door]
It's Miss Clayton.
Said Flora's been sleepwalking.
- And she's all right? [sighs]
- I'm not sure.
If she's all right, that's all.
If she isn't?
If she isn't, then why isn't she calling
a bloody doctor?
[quietly] Yes.
- [drops pen]
- [sighs]
[clocks ticks quietly]
[sighs quietly]
[distant siren wailing]
[line ringing]
[Flora] Flora residence.
Well, hello, Flora.
It's Uncle Henry.
Hello.
How are you doing, darling?
I-Is your mother…
What about Mummy?
Well, I mean to say, uh…
have you seen that little boy again?
Oh, no, not yet.
Oh, well, that's fine, isn't it?
Now, are you working on a story for him?
I'm trying.
But Daddy says he's a type of mint.
I'm sorry?
He says he's a type of special mint.
And that's all.
A fig mint, he says.
- In my imagination.
- [Henry laughing]
Well, you-you tell your dad
even "fig mints" need a story.
Tell him yourself.
Dad, Uncle Henry's on the phone!
What?
Hang on.
He says fig mints need stories, too.
- [sighs]
- [Dominic] Thanks, sweetheart.
What's this, then?
Hi, you're, you're back.
I am. Just for a bit.
Flew in last night,
last flight out of Glasgow.
Spur of the moment thing, but, uh…
But don't worry about the case.
- I'm heading back tomorrow.
- Uh, well done.
I-I'm sure the children
are beyond thrilled to see you.
How did you know?
Know what?
That I was back.
Or were you... Why are you calling?
I was…
I was looking for you. I…
I tried Glasgow,
and I couldn't find you, so…
I thought Charlotte would know
if you'd swapped hotels.
No, no, I'm still at the…
Well, anyway, you found me.
What's happening?
Well, I've…
Well, I've answered
my own question, actually.
In the time that we've been… talking,
I've sorted it out.
Oh, well.
Well done.
Sure.
Safe travels.
[footsteps receding]
[Henry sighs]
Fuck.
[sighs heavily]
[ominous music playing]
Don't know who you're trying to hide from.
Might as well come in.
[alter ego] So…
we decided on Scotch and bourbon tonight.
[chuckles] And the '62, at that.
Are you sure we can still afford it?
After Peter robbed you blind.
Hardly blind.
What's a quarter mil?
And Miles' money, after all, not yours.
I replaced all of it as…
You know this.
Don't know why I bother
explaining myself to you.
You know everything.
Oh.
She's likely asleep by now.
You'd get the cook again,
or the housekeeper.
Or that cute little American.
The calls are spooking them.
You know it.
The Scholarship Society.
[scoffs] Well, they should know better,
shouldn't they?
[laughs]
They've had years to figure it out.
The receptionist could handle this.
This… and all his correspondence.
I'm perfectly capable.
She could send out a notice of death,
and stop the incoming mail.
Could send a dozen.
Could send a notice
every time something comes in
without ever bothering you with it.
You wouldn't even need to know it.
I'm perfectly capable.
Hm.
You insist on handling it
so that no one does,
because every time you send out
a notice of death,
the world where you can pretend
your brother's still alive
gets a little bit smaller.
Doesn't it?
I'm not pretending a fucking thing.
Well, then take down the address
on this envelope,
and draft a notice of death
for Dominic Wingrave,
and put it in the post.
[Henry sighs heavily]
[drawer slides open]
[drawer slams shut]
[chuckling]
[sighs]
- [insects chirping]
- [footsteps creaking]
How is she?
She slept all day.
[Hannah] Hm.
[sighs] No fever, though. I keep checking.
Poor thing must be exhausted.
[Dani] We-We missed you this afternoon.
Where did you run off to?
[Hannah] Oh, um…
I'm not…
Well, I suppose I was around.
[scoffs] God, what does that say about me?
I can… can hardly remember this afternoon.
[Dani] If she's the same tomorrow,
I'll call the doctor.
- Yes. Yes, that sounds about right.
- I called Henry, but…
he didn't call back.
I… don't understand. I mean…
how could a person…
They're his only family.
Henry's not exactly himself anymore.
Not really, I mean…
he hasn't been for a long time.
[sighs] Ever since Charlotte and Dominic
went on that blasted trip.
Well, I suppose none of them came back.
I mean, Charlotte and Dominic,
obviously, but…
neither did Henry, if I'm honest.
Oh.
All three of them just…
[splutters]
gone.
Are you coming down?
In a bit.
All righty.
[quiet, unsettling music playing]
[Owen] We can go…
Like, we can go this weekend.
It's Patrick Swayze, come on.
- Yeah, in concert.
- [Hannah muttering indistinctly]
You're still here?
- Oh, yes.
- Oh, yeah, had to wash up.
Besides, I was asked to stay behind.
[Dani scoffs]
Now, who would ask you to do that?
[Owen clears throat]
[Jamie] Don't touch that.
You'll just desecrate it.
[laughs] Hey, I, uh…
I thought you left a while ago.
Made it halfway home,
and I thought, "Rough day.
Maybe Poppins
might fancy a little boredom."
What do you say?
- The kids, I...
- Already taken care of.
[Hannah] I've got things handled here.
You, uh…
You go and enjoy yourselves.
- Uh, we have things handled here.
- Yes.
Any nightmares, bogeymen,
or monsters under the bed
will be dealt with swiftly and fairly,
in an impartial court.
[Dani laughs]
Come on.
- [rain pattering]
- [animal howls]
[Dani] Where, uh…
Where are we going?
Are you taking me out here to kill me?
[Jamie] Keep talking, I just might.
So, uh…
there's not many secret spots,
even on grounds this big.
- But this one… special.
- [Dani] Wow, that's beautiful.
- You planted that?
- Yeah.
It's a moonflower.
Bloody hard to grow in England.
[Jamie clears throat]
Yeah, but…
worth it.
[Jamie] Is it?
Isn't it?
This plant only blooms two months a year.
And only at night.
Each bud, only once.
These flowers will be dead by morning,
and tomorrow night,
new buds will bloom, and then they'll die.
In three weeks,
this entire plant will be dead.
And in the spring, I'll have to plant
a whole new moonflower.
That's a lot of work
for a flower that only blooms once.
That's what people feel like to me.
Exhaustive effort.
Very little to show for it.
All of them?
All of them.
Even you.
Even me.
Especially me.
So, I figured I'd save you some effort.
[night animals calling distantly]
[Jamie] Skip to the end.
Take a shot.
Why not?
So, here goes, okay?
[Dani] Mm-hm.
Okay.
[emotional music playing]
Mum was Louise.
Dad was Dennis.
Dennis met Louise when she was 18.
He was 24.
Total surprise, a year later,
my brother Denny.
And me, less of a surprise, I guess.
Dad starts working in a coal mine.
It's, uh, more money.
Slightly more,
but he's barely home now,
and Louise, well…
Louise is home with the kids,
but she's basically a kid herself.
A kid with two kids,
and a husband 600 meters down.
So, she does what kids do.
She plays.
So, Dad's underground,
and Mum's under some bloke, and…
the thing about a coal mine…
Well, the thing I think about most
now I'm older…
No plants down there.
No life at all.
See, these men…
We send them down into this dark mess,
digging for something dead.
So… dead that it's now lumps
of dead things,
so old and lifeless
that they will literally burn,
and that was his life.
While she did
whatever she could to feel alive.
All that death,
that dark, powdery death
is all over his face,
his hands, his fucking lungs,
when he comes up.
There's not a leaf, not a branch,
not a flower in his world,
and when he finally
climbs out of that grave,
finally climbs back
to the land of the living…
they laugh at him.
They laugh because the whole town knows
that the new baby,
my little brother Mikey, isn't his.
So, Dennis buries his head in the soot,
and they… [chuckles]
…praise him for his loyalty,
while they mock him for a cuckold.
Louise, on the other hand,
call a spade a spade,
and they call my mum a whore.
Call the daughter one, too,
bully her at school, on the streets.
Even makes its way home.
Little Denny piles on,
tries to save his own skin
by blaming all the females in the family,
and in '67, Louise bolts.
She splits,
and I come home from school to find Mikey…
alone…
screaming his little head off.
He's still a baby,
and he doesn't understand
what he's done wrong.
I try and take care of him.
But I'm just a kid.
Kids can't raise kids.
I forget things.
Like watching over a pot when it boils.
So, one day there's an accident.
Social Services gets involved,
and we're split up.
Dad did his best.
He spent so long underground, didn't know
what to do with a kid, let alone…
three kids.
So, he disappeared into the dirt.
Then, it was foster care.
Just a bunch of stale, perverted men
with bitter wives,
hoping to make a few quid
by taking care of the local trash.
I left for London pretty soon after that.
[sniffs] Got myself
into all sorts of trouble there.
Wound up serving a couple of years.
And it's there I start gardening.
Busy work for idle hands.
But I fucking love it.
Love it.
And it's so clear then…
how people…
aren't worth it.
But plants…
you pour your love,
and your effort,
and your nourishment into them…
and you see where it goes.
You watch them grow,
and it all makes sense.
So, yeah.
[scoffs]
Everyone is exhaustive.
Even the best ones.
But sometimes…
once in a blue goddamned moon, I guess…
someone…
like this moonflower,
just might be worth the effort.
Look, I know you're struggling.
I see it.
I know you're carrying this guilt around,
but I also know that you don't decide
who lives and who doesn't.
I'm sorry, Dani, but you don't.
Humans are organic.
It's a fact.
We're meant to die.
It's natural…
beautiful.
And it all breaks down and rises back up,
and breaks down again,
and every living thing
grows out of every dying thing.
We leave more life behind us
to take our place.
That life refreshes and recycles,
and on and on it goes.
And that is so much better
than that life getting crushed,
deep down in the dirt,
into a rock that will burn
if it's old enough.
So much better to see the leafling…
and flower.
We leave more life behind
to take our place.
Like this moonflower.
It's where all its beauty lies, you know.
In the mortality of the thing.
[emotional music continues]
[Dani sighs]
[Dani pants softly]
[clock ticking quietly]
Oh, dear.
What are we going to do about this?
I don't know.
I truly don't know.
[unsettling music playing]
[soft growl]
[Peter grunts]
Is that all of it?
- One more piece in the car.
- Okay, I'll grab it.
[Charlotte gasps]
Oh, my God!
What have you done?
I found a gentleman in Sussex
who makes these.
It's, well…
- It's close enough, I suppose.
- [Charlotte scoffs]
Couldn't match it exactly, obviously.
Oh, she's going to lose her mind.
[gasps]
I'm sorry I won't make the party.
Hopefully, this smooths it over.
Oh, she's six.
She'll only notice the presents.
[Henry chuckles]
Not here.
[Henry] Hm.
- [footsteps approaching]
- [Henry] I'll get the last of it.
Uh, perhaps we could hide this
in the study until the party.
[Charlotte] Sounds good.
Darling, look what your brother's brought.
It's terrific.
I'm sorry I can't make the birthday party.
You know how it is.
- I'll call you when I get to Berlin.
- Sounds perfect.
[door opens]
[door creaks shut]
[somber music playing]
[rain pattering]
[footsteps descending]
[Charlotte gasps, laughs nervously]
Oh, my God!
What…
Whatever are you doing here
just sitting in the dark?
I just wanted something small
before going to sleep.
Extra energy.
It's going to be a blitz in the morning.
All those extra children running around.
You should get some rest as well.
Are you coming to bed?
[Dominic] Flora's birthday…
got me thinking…
what a strange night that was.
[Charlotte] Was it?
I don't remember much.
Beauty of childbirth.
We're supposed to forget, they say.
A chemical in the brain, in fact.
It's the only way
we'd ever have another one.
She was so early.
She was.
Right.
And I was so surprised.
But for a baby that early…
she wasn't nearly as small as I expected.
Math didn't work, did it?
I don't know what you mean.
I mean, that if she wasn't early,
if she was actually right on time,
that math wouldn't work.
She kind of had to be early, didn't she?
Or else it would mean
she was conceived in August.
While I was in Russia.
Six years.
Took me six years to do the math.
I suppose I didn't want to, did I?
I was gone an awful lot, wasn't I?
Lonely…
a house this size…
just you and Miles.
Lonely.
Do you love him?
[sighs]
[sniffles]
[storyteller]
The au pair could not remember
the last time she'd slept this well.
And she thought perhaps she never had.
[quiet, unsettling sound]
[Dani sighs]
[unsettling music playing]
[Dani] Flora!
Flora! Flora, what are you doing?
Where am I?
What's happening? Are you okay?
Were you sleepwalking again?
I don't…
I don't know.
I think I was tucked away again.
Okay, come on. Let's go inside.
Why does this keep happening?
[ominous music playing]
[music fades to silence]
[sniffles]
I'm terribly sorry for the trouble.
I was just going on a walk.
I didn't mean to alarm you.
Let's get some breakfast, shall we?
I'm positively famished.
[Dani chuckles]
[somber music playing]
- [door opens]
- [footsteps approaching]
[clears throat]
[clears throat louder]
I'm sorry to interrupt.
Miss Clayton called, again.
- I think maybe you should...
- Is anyone hurt?
Do they need an ambulance?
No, I don't think it's that simple.
Jesus, I told you!
[yells] I'm unavailable
unless someone is hurt!
[Henry sighs heavily]
[sighs]
Goddamn it.
Fine!
[exhales]
Fine.
Get her back on the phone.
[unsettling music playing]
- [men speaking indistinctly]
- [objects shuffling]
[Henry] Hey.
What's all this, then?
Just put those in the car, will you?
You keep the office, is what this is.
What are you talking about?
I don't want to see any of this,
ever again.
How stupid you must have thought of me.
How fucking stupid.
- I-I don't...
- Babies rarely adhere to a schedule, Dom.
But listen,
and this is the important part.
She's my daughter.
In every way that matters.
When she skins her knee,
calls out with a nightmare…
it's me.
First time some asshole
breaks her heart…
I'll be there to console her.
And when she asks her father
to walk her down the aisle…
me, not you.
Do you understand me?
She didn't tell you?
Well, look at that.
I get to be here when the penny drops.
I've been thinking.
I've been thinking
about what the right word must be.
And I keep getting stuck on "banished."
It's close.
It has teeth.
But not nearly enough.
And it'll do for now.
You're banished, little brother.
You're banished from my house.
You're banished from my wife, my children.
Banished.
You don't have a brother anymore.
Or a niece.
Or a nephew.
Nobody.
Just yourself.
And yourself, Henry…
your real self…
he's an evil shit.
A grotesque little demon, isn't he?
I pity you.
'Cause you have to live with him.
You have to live with yourself.
And he's a shit, grinning,
fucking monster.
Isn't he?
[door slams]
- [Flora] How far away is India?
- [Charlotte chuckles]
It's further than "I'll miss you,"
but closer than "goodbye."
I know what you're thinking,
but you shouldn't worry.
It's going to be fine.
It's just a few weeks, my darling.
[Flora] Can I come with you?
A couple of weeks is a terribly long time,
and I don't want to be here all alone
with Miles and Mrs. Grose.
Hm.
Ah. Here we are.
This is called a talisman.
I used to make them.
Well, sometimes I still do. Old habits.
I've made them
since I was your age, really.
[Flora] What does it do?
Well, it protects people,
and it keeps them happy.
[sighs] It's happening again…
isn't it?
What?
I'm not really here.
I'm too old.
It's like…
the math doesn't work.
That's right.
I'm tucked away again in another memory.
Tucked away safe.
I miss you, Mummy.
[Charlotte whispering] Oh…
My darling.
[in normal voice]
You should probably wake up now.
[ominous music playing]
[eerie swish]
- [Owen] Remember these? Was in the spring.
- [Dani] You remember.
[Dani and Owen laugh]
How can you have two helpings?
- [all chuckling]
- Look at him go.
[Flora] You've… You've…
What are you doing?
[Dani] Flora!
Hey!
You're eating dinner without me.
W-What?
- Wh... Flora, what?
- You already ate, in your room.
- Owen made you soup.
- It was some of my best work.
I don't remember that.
Told you she wasn't herself.
She seems fine.
But weird.
I don't like this game.
It's okay.
I don't like it!
- [phone rings]
- [Dani] Probably your uncle.
Everything's gonna be okay, Flora.
Don't-Don't worry.
Hello?
- It's another freaking prank call.
- [line disconnects]
[sighs]
[alter ego] Do you really think
she'll answer one of these times?
[scoffs]
It's getting sad.
[phone hangs up]
I don't imagine
there's much in it for you.
One in ten times you call,
she might answer.
You might hear her say,
"Flora residence."
Unlikely.
[snickers]
In the meantime…
[laughing] …they think you're some pervert
breathing into the phone.
Just a crank.
Pathetic, really.
[knocking on door]
Here we are again.
Well, it's not real,
but you probably should get it anyway.
[footsteps approaching]
[sighs]
I'm sorry to come by.
Uh…
Well, I-I was nearby, and…
[sighs]
I wasn't nearby.
I made up a story. I don't have long.
What are you doing in here?
Oh, I was…
[sighs]
I don't rightly know. [laughs]
I'm sorry.
Flora.
I'm so sorry.
I should have told you.
I should have done
a lot of things differently.
We're leaving tonight.
India.
For a few weeks.
Retracing our honeymoon.
I see.
I wanted to say goodbye.
- Charlotte.
- I mean it.
I'm going to make this work.
My husband, my family.
I needed you to hear it from me…
why I'm going on this trip.
I can fix it.
But I couldn't leave without…
I love you, Charlotte.
I know.
[crying]
There's a lot more to it than love.
A lot more to it.
[Charlotte sniffles, breathes heavily]
[footsteps receding]
[unsettling, ethereal music playing]
[alter ego]
Jumping ahead, if you don't mind,
to my favorite part.
No, please.
That hurts. That really hurts.
I want to see it again.
- No.
- The night we met.
[phone rings]
- [alter ego] Come on.
- [sighs]
[alter ego] Answer it.
- No.
- [ringing]
[alter ego]
But you have to. You know that.
- I don't want to.
- [alter ego] But you always do.
Come on, there's nothing to be afraid of.
You know who it is.
It's the British Consulate in India.
No, please.
They have terrible news.
- Please.
- There's been an accident.
[ringing continues]
[sighs]
[ringing]
[Henry sighs]
[clears throat] Hello.
Yes, speaking.
I'm sorry, could you repeat that?
[sniffs]
[inhales sharply]
What sort of an accident?
Oh…
Well, surely, they're all right.
[inhales sharply]
[breathes heavily]
You're wrong.
[clears throat]
You're mistaken.
[exhales]
[pants]
[whimpers]
[pants, cries out]
[panicked breaths]
[ominous music playing]
[screaming]
[sighs]
[sniffles]
[panting]
[alter ego] That wasn't so bad, was it?
[exhales heavily] It was hell.
Every time is hell.
No.
That wasn't the worst of it.
Not even arranging their funerals,
or burying those empty coffins.
No.
Hell was having to call Bly,
having to break the news,
and having her voice
be the first one you heard
when she picked up the phone.
Her little voice saying…
[Flora] Flora residence.
[Jamie] Sleep talking, sleepwalking.
She's having a rough time of it.
Yeah.
Yeah, I…
I don't know what else to do.
So, yeah, I think I'm gonna take her
to a doctor in the morning.
She needs a psychologist.
We have mandated therapy inside.
I hated it.
Didn't think it would do anything.
My assigned psychologist, Tamara,
she was relentless.
A dog with a bone, that woman.
So, I started talking just to shut her up.
After a month, I realized
I was sleeping through the night.
Wow.
Yeah.
You might be right.
[sighs]
I'm gonna go.
Oh.
I should change my clothes, at least.
[laughs]
Well, um…
y-you could…
come back.
- Tonight?
- Yeah.
Tonight.
I don't know, Poppins.
I don't know, you've got your hands full.
[sighs]
Well, I'm gonna be up all night
checking up on her, anyway.
Good night.
Just good night.
There are other nights,
and there will be other nights.
You promise?
[Jamie chuckles]
[Dani laughs gently]
- Promise.
- [Dani] Mm.
[sighs] Fuck it.
This again.
Disconnected.
Phone trouble?
[Henry sighs]
[ominous rumbling]
Phone's disconnected.
So?
So, it shouldn't be. It wasn't earlier.
I'm sure it's nothing.
[ominous rumble, drone]
- What are you doing?
- Going.
- What?
- I'm going to Bly.
- [ominous boom]
- [scoffs] That's insane.
It's a three-hour drive,
and you've been drinking all...
Well, for two years, really.
- That's no reason.
- [ominous boom]
[sighs]
What's the point? The nanny has got this.
You couldn't do anything, anyway.
- I have a terrible feeling.
- [ominous boom]
Oh, well, that settles it.
I haven't had a feeling like this since...
So, you'll go to Bly, then?
They'll be so happy to see you.
And maybe you can tell
those little kids to their faces
exactly how their parents died.
And you can tell them
why they were taking that trip
in the first place.
[ominous boom]
Hello?
Wait!
There you are.
Don't be scared.
[somber music playing]
I'm sorry I was scared before.
That was very rude of me, but…
I thought I'd give you a story.
You poor boy.
I'm so sorry about your face.
Here.
Try this.
There.
There you are.
Now, let's come up with a story…
just for you.
I've done it again, haven't I?
I'm tucked away again in another memory.
Because the night I did this,
the night I gave you a new face,
I was only just five years old.
Wasn't I?
Why do you keep doing this to me?
Just tell me.
Why do you keep pushing me aside?
Miss Jessel.
Come on, now.
No more.
I don't like this game.
Stop hiding from me.
I want to talk to you.
[suspenseful music playing]
I'm very cross with you.
But why?
Everything is just fine.
- It's perfectly...
- It's not.
I'm tired of being tucked away.
I'm tired of forgetting things,
and I'm tired of acting strange.
And of Miles acting strange.
What's the matter with Miles?
Miles is perfectly splendid,
except when he isn't.
Isn't splendid?
Isn't Miles.
[Flora sighs]
No.
Don't do that!
You mustn't keep doing that.
Get back here and let me see you!
What are you doing to me?
- I…
- [door creaks open]
[Dani] Flora?
[frightening music playing]
Flora.
Come here.
[Flora] It's okay.
It's only Miss Jessel.
Shh, shh, shh.
Miles!
- [frightening boom]
- Well…
this is awkward.
Miles!
[music intensifies]
[music fades into silence]
What?
Flora. Flora!
No, Flora! Flora!
[footsteps pounding rapidly]
Flora!
Flora.
[suspenseful music playing]
Flora, where are you?
Flora.
Flora, we gotta go.
Come on.
I'm sorry.
[frightening musical swell]
- [thud]
- [music abruptly stops]
[closing music playing]