Ah!
What's up, Hondo?
You guys got nothing on me.
- You killed a cop.
- Allegedly.
And then you bragged about it.
So arrest me, sweetheart.
All right? You got nothing tying me
to that nigger friend of yours.
Okay, why don't you see
if you can make it stick?
No. You killed our friend.
We're not gonna arrest you.
What are you talkin' about?
You're right,
we couldn't make it stick.
You're fucking cops, okay?
Arrest me.
See any badges?
You're the fuckin' sheriff!
- Allegedly.
- Oh, fu...
Where do you go?
What do you mean?
It's like...
You can't even look at me.
It's nothing like that.
You know, maybe you
should really think about
getting a new place.
It has a certain
old-school charm, no?
No.
Well, you can't beat the rent.
I mean, I get that this
isn't a relationship,
and I'm fine with that.
I have to go to work.
You could at least hire a
cleaning service or something.
I don't like people
touching my things.
- Your things?
- Yeah.
- These aren't your things.
- Okay, time to get up.
This is where Sugar's
old crap goes to die.
Yeah, this coming from the girl
who lives in an Airstream.
You just seem like somebody who could
use a friend is all I'm saying.
We're just two adults
having sex in a motel room.
You know what?
Fuck it.
Come here.
Great sex.
Always room for improvement.
- Hey, Carrie, you're early.
- I couldn't sleep.
Order up.
Eggs Benedict, hold the sauce.
Man, you guys.
- Take the back five, okay?
- You got it.
Who had the eggs Florentine?
You want some eggs?
No, thanks.
You hear that?
What?
Quiet.
- You missing Job?
- No.
I'm just sayin' how
nice and quiet it's been
since you got back from your little
trip to New York last month.
You got a problem with quiet?
On the contrary.
I'm gonna miss it when it's gone.
Yes?
In regards to the
matter we discussed,
you should come down
to the basement.
- Now?
- Yes.
Is he ready to talk?
Looks like you two
made quite a night of it.
I know, I know.
Burton's interview style
can be a little rigid at times,
but he's very precise.
These cuts will all heal.
You just make sure you live
long enough to let that happen.
Do you understand?
Good.
Now, has Jim Cage been supplying
Philadelphia with molly?
Yeah.
And he's been selling
to Frazier exclusively?
They cut your prices.
He's got the whole
territory locked up.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Wait!
Please.
Please help me.
That's not really my thing.
Stay the fuck away from me!
Fruit platter and
oatmeal with soy milk.
Egg white omelet.
Hi, Carrie.
How are you?
How are the kids?
Everything's great.
Thanks.
Eggs over easy.
Side of bacon, crisp.
Thank you.
I give her a lot of credit.
It can't be easy, huh?
You okay?
Yeah.
- Mr. Proctor.
- Sheriff, Deputy.
Charging me with
unlicensed firearms.
That was the best you could do?
Just getting the ball
rolling till I can charge you
- with the Longshadow murder.
- I'm sure you are,
but thanks to you I have
an airtight alibi, don't I?
You had me locked up, remember?
The way I see it, a guy like
you, I'll get another shot.
Yeah, but your track record
isn't exactly giving me
much cause for concern.
See you around, Kai.
I still come in every day
expecting to see Emmett there.
Yeah, me, too.
Hey, morning.
- Hey.
- Raven.
Uh...
Listen, I know that I...
have some pretty big
shoes to fill here.
- Huge.
- Yeah, yeah, I get that.
But all I did was answer an ad.
I'm sorry.
This can't be easy for you.
It's not, but it gets my
family off the reservation.
And I gotta tell you after
working six years for KPD,
it's great to be working in an
actual functioning police station.
Functional. That's us.
Hey, Hood, you got a minute?
Uh, yeah. What's up?
Hondo file.
Medical examiner said
they're not gonna send out
for ballistics on the bullets.
They're prioritizing, I guess.
And I...
And I canvassed the area.
No one seems
to have seen anything.
So, basically,
the official consensus is
three anonymous shooters
did the world a favor
and nobody's gonna
lose any sleep over
a dead neo-Nazi
with multiple priors.
- So...
- Sounds good to me.
Okay.
Something else?
Are you even fazed by this?
- We executed a man, Hood.
- He killed one of us.
I know that.
I understand.
You've done this sort
of thing before?
What?
Killed a man?
No, executed him.
Brock...
You'll be okay.
Now let's go.
Let's just not
make a habit of it, okay? I...
Does Father know that we've
been meeting like this?
To what end?
You don't think
he'll join us, do you?
But you would think at one
point he'd want to know
what became of his son.
Let's be honest, Kai.
Who you've become is exactly
what he is afraid of.
How is my granddaughter doing?
She's fine.
Hit him!
The fire trials
are a sacred Redbone tradition
to prove yourself a worthy leader.
Times have changed
and the Redbones
must change with them.
Wrong.
Sheriff's Department.
Billy. Billy.
You have to press
that interface button first
in order to pull the call
off Alma's switchboard.
- Thanks.
- Got it?
- Yeah.
- Time and experience, son.
Interface.
- There you go.
- Sheriff's Department.
Deputy Lotus stepped away for
a moment. Can I help you?
Do you see him now?
Are all your doors locked?
Can you check them for me, please?
And tell me your address.
Got it.
Okay, we're on our way, ma'am.
Okay, we got a prowler call.
Lady said there's a guy
hiding in her shrubbery
- in her backyard.
- Whoa.
Is it 63 Oakwood Lane?
Yeah. How'd you know?
Time and experience, son.
I'll get it.
- We should both go...
- No, no, I need you to stay here
and hold down the fort, all right?
Times have not changed.
We are still being
raped and plundered
by the white man
like we have been
for 500 years.
What exactly is it you think
we're going to celebrate?
You left, Chayton.
I'm in charge.
- I understand.
- Do you?
I don't want to fight you.
I don't want to fight you, either,
but that's how we do it unless
you see another way, Chayton.
You could just step down.
Would you?
Ah!
- Had enough?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- We done?
- Yeah.
We are here, all of us,
to fight in a war
that we will never win
because it was lost
by our people centuries ago.
We will never
reclaim our country.
But I've come back because
I'd rather die fighting
than to live like a slave
in my own land.
It's time we took
something back.
Hello?
Another prowler, huh?
Gotta stop it with
these prowler calls, Emily.
All right?
Look, what if I was out
when Billy Raven took that call?
Who the hell's Billy Raven?
- New deputy.
- Oh.
- Poor Emmett.
- I gotta get back.
Just have a drink with me.
- Em, I'm on duty.
- You're always on duty.
That's why we got divorced.
No, we got divorced because you
were fucking Elliot Granger.
I was fucking Elliot Granger
because you were never home.
Classic chicken
and the egg debate.
Just sit with me.
Please?
I just get lonely sometimes.
Well, maybe you shouldn't
drink alone at night.
Done.
To us.
Yeah.
How's everything?
How's... How's work and...
You don't have to make
small talk with me.
Come on.
Stop it.
Stop, Stop.
Damn it, Em. I just wanted
to make sure you were okay.
Then make me okay.
Damn it.
Fuck me.
Harder.
Oh!
Did it hurt?
I mean, at first when they jab you
with the needle it hurt a lot,
but, I don't know, after a while
you just kind of get used to it.
Kind of like my life.
Did your dad
find a new place yet?
Yeah, he's renting
this shitty little apartment.
It's pretty depressing, actually.
Are he and your mom,
like, talking?
Sometimes, yeah.
The whole thing
is just so fucked up.
I bet they freaked
when they saw your tat.
They're way too caught up
in their own bullshit
to pay any attention to me.
I know where we can get some
premium bud for, like, 50 bucks.
- You have 50 bucks?
- Tapped out.
No shit.
You're always tapped out.
Bite me.
I have an idea.
Holy shit.
It's like a stoner's Toys "R" Us.
All right, guys.
Guys, come on.
Come on!
Doing a little late-night shopping?
You two, head home now.
Consider this your last warning.
Is he joking?
You guys, just...
Just get out of here.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, I'm fine. Just go!
Hey!
Leave the stuff.
So, you wanna be a thief now?
A little piece of advice.
It's harder than you think.
Your first mistake was your numbers.
Every extra person increases
your chances of getting caught
and you had three people
on a one-man job.
It's not a great start.
Come with me.
You see an alarm
on the door, window?
Nope.
So how did I get here so fast?
See that little white box up there?
It's a sound sensor.
You break the glass,
that triggers a silent alarm.
Ten seconds later,
my office is on the radio,
here I am.
Your only option with glass
is a cutter.
So this is it?
Jackpot
- How much you got?
- Thirty-seven dollars.
Wow.
See, the register is also
connected to the alarm.
So you would've been better
to take the whole thing
and open it when you got clear.
Although, if there is
any real cash left overnight...
it's gonna be in the safe,
which is also
bolted to the floor.
So unless you know
how to crack a safe...
No?
Well, then there's
really nothing in here
worth getting arrested for.
Unless, of course,
that was the point.
You think I wanted to get caught?
Self-destruction
runs in the family.
A little soon
to be making daddy jokes,
don't you think?
You never know until you try.
To your health.
I don't know what you've
been up to, but...
I just had sex with my ex-wife.
Again.
I know, I know, I know.
But you know what?
I know what you're gonna say
and you've never
been divorced, so...
Hey, look,
I wanted to tell you...
we took care of Hondo.
Oh, man, we made him pay
for what he did to you.
I doubt you'll be running in
the same circles up there
or wherever, but...
if you happen to run
into him, that was us.
I know, I know, you probably
have some Bible verse
about leaving revenge to God,
but, you see, Emmett,
sometimes you cannot wait
for God to put the world to right
because while you're waiting,
the world just keeps
going to shit.
And when you have a guy
like Hood leading the charge,
well, God's just gonna
have to move a lot faster
if He wants to keep up and
you can tell Him I said that.
I miss you.
Cheers.
What are you doing here?
I stopped by to see the kids,
found them here alone,
so I decided to stay
and have dinner with them.
- Where's Deva?
- She went to bed hours ago, Carrie.
- It's past midnight.
- I had to work late.
You know, somehow I don't
think you were at the diner.
Well, you know, a lot of single
mothers have to work two jobs.
This has to stop.
Let's not do this.
Isn't the whole point of getting a
divorce so we don't have to fight?
How can you not realize
that you are risking
the well-being
of your children?
What is it with you? Some sort
of addiction or something?
You would know.
I'm sorry.
So you and Mom way back when.
- Yeah.
- But not anymore?
- No.
- How come you left her?
I mean, she was pregnant.
She should have found you.
- She should have told you.
- No, no.
It wasn't her fault.
There was no way she
could have got to me
without putting herself, and you,
in a lot of danger.
Then after she met your father,
she did what was best for you.
The point is
why don't you take
it easy on your mom?
She lied to me my whole life.
No, she tried to keep you safe.
She left everything.
Her whole life.
Gave it all up.
Everything.
She did that for you.
When did you know about me?
The first time I saw you.
You came here for her?
But I stayed for you.
- Hi, Dad.
- Hey, I saw you go to bed.
- Woke up.
- Deva?
- This is not okay.
- Yeah, tell me about it.
Where'd you find her?
She was just out
with some other kids.
Yeah, well, thanks
for bringing her back.
Yeah.
Have a good night.
Hood.
You know, Carrie promised
to tell me everything,
but when it came to you...
...nothin'.
Whatever your secrets are,
they were worth breaking
a promise to her husband.
You ended my marriage.
Please...
...leave me my daughter.
I don't care who made her.
I'm her...
I'm her father.
I'm asking you, please.
This is what we took in
last night.
And if you click here, you can
see the same day last week,
last month, and last year.
You click here,
you can see what each girl
is bringing in.
Okay.
Anyway, I think this is enough
for tonight.
Why don't you check on the club?
I'll finish up
a few things here.
Proctor had his hands
in Longshadow's pockets.
One thing leads to another.
Now Longshadow is dead.
We'll be coming
for you, white girl.
You...
...and Proctor.
Soon.
Come on, come on. Let's go!
Who the hell is that?
This is a United States
Marine Corps vehicle.
Step aside...
TOC, kilo-one-niner. Taking hostile
contact on Pondfield 15. Requesting...
We don't have time to wait
for backup. Get us out of here.
Motherfuckers.
Just got
a report of shots being fired
on Pondfield Road.
Pondfield Road,
that's near Camp Genoa.
- Could be running exercises.
- Not without notifying us.
Siobhan, we're close by.
We're on it.
Jackson, you okay?
Jackson, answer...
Got him.
Come on, let's go!
Move it, move it!
Alma, we need backup!
EMS, we got multiple casualties!
Repeat, multiple casualties!
Are you worried
about the Indian?
He knew.
How could he know?
They would naturally
suspect my involvement.
Who pulled the trigger
is not important to them.
It seemed pretty
important to him.
You know, I'm gonna
put a guard in the house.
Anywhere you go,
Burton will go with you.
That Indian won't
get near you again.
- Morning, Sheriff.
- Morning.
- How can I help you, sir?
- Who's the CO here?
Colonel Stowe, sir.
Okay, well, I need to see him.
You have an appointment
to see the colonel?
You just told me his name. How
could I have an appointment?
No one gets on base
without authorization.
There were four Marines killed
on the road earlier today,
about eight miles from here.
- I'm sure you heard about it.
- Yes, sir.
Well, this is
a homicide investigation.
That's my authorization.
- Sheriff Hood.
- Colonel Stowe.
I've been expecting you.
Not according to
your men at the gate.
They were just
following protocol.
This way.
Hey, Colonel.
Let me just start
by saying how sorry I am.
It's a tragedy.
Nine tours in
Iraq and Afghanistan between 'em,
and they get killed demilling an
antiquated base
in Banshee, Pennsylvania.
I have no idea how I'm gonna talk
their families through that one.
Colonel Douglas Stowe.
So you're shutting the place down?
We're basically clearing
house for all the contraband
that gets shipped
out of the war zones.
Guns, valuables,
drugs, you name it.
And cash.
Your tax dollars at work.
Whether we're buying guns off the
streets to keep them from the Taliban
or sending out soldiers with
briefcases full of money
to pay off informants.
We've got half of Afghanistan
on the damn payroll.
The money we don't use
has to be inventoried
and sent back to the Fed to
be wasted in the next war.
Right.
You don't agree?
I don't like war.
But when you ask me to fight,
let me fight.
So the four Marines
who were killed,
they were transporting cash?
No, we don't move
cash in trucks.
We contract armored
vehicles for that.
Those were mostly confiscated
automatic weapons.
AKs and M4s headed to a Fed
facility to be destroyed.
Great, so now the Redbones
are armed like the Taliban.
I'm sorry, the Redbones?
The guys who jacked your truck.
They're a tribal gang
from the reservation.
Do you have a list of everything
that was in those crates?
- I do.
- Great, well, if you could
just have one of your people
print that out for me, then...
Sheriff Hood,
I appreciate the visit
and the fact that
you and your deputies
tried your best
to stop these people.
But the moment they killed my Marines
and stole government property,
this became a matter
for the military.
NCIS will lead the investigation
with the FBI and the BIA.
Now, that's a lot
of fuckin' letters,
and the last thing you want
is be getting caught up
in the middle of it.
That's true, but those guns may
end up on the streets of my town.
And if they do,
you feel free to shoot back.
We got four dead Marines here.
No one's gonna have the patience
for a small-town sheriff
who thinks he knows better.
Okay.
Thanks for your time.
Captain Murphy here
will show you out.
Thanks again for coming by.
You don't look like a Marine,
Captain Murphy.
Sugar here.
You know that one big job
we've been looking for?
Well, I think I found it.
- Do tell.
- The Marine base, Camp Genoa.
They're moving cash
by the truckload.
- Millions of dollars.
- If they're moving
that kind of money,
they're still gonna have
- military-grade security systems.
- Yeah.
If only we knew someone
who could hack
into the military network.
It's been 25 minutes.
You should be in by now.
You try working with a motherfuckin'
hand cannon in your face.
This here is the New
York Stock Exchange.
There's a lot of moving parts.
Well, then, make them
move a little bit faster.
The trick ain't gettin' in.
The trick is gettin' out without
anyone knowing you've been there.
That's of no concern to me.
- There.
- That's it? You're in?
Oh, no, that's just the signal.
Signal? What signal?
Damn it, he got
the fuckin' money!
Go get him.
- Have you seen me run?
- Bullshit!
Shit!
Bollocks.
Fuck me!
Now is not really a good time.
Everything okay?
How'd the Fat Al thing go?
Up in fuckin' smoke.
You know, I'm actually
starting to believe in God?
And I'm thinkin'
that motherfucker hates me.
Yeah, well,
I got something might cheer you up.
I highly doubt that.
What the fuck, Job?
Hold on.
- Is this all the money?
- Motherfucker sat on his own grenade!
Damn.
I ain't coming back
to Pennsylvania.
I just had eyes on eight to ten
million in unwashed U.S. dollars.
I hate you.
You know that?
I fuckin' hate you.
I see you met
the Duck Dynasty guys.
Yeah.
Don't worry, I'll sanitize
the booth when they leave.
Here you go.
What can I get you guys to eat?
How about a deluxe burger
and your phone number?
- I don't have a phone.
- That's all right.
We don't have to talk.
You're gonna want
to move that hand.
- How's that?
- Yeah.
- Does that feel good?
- Sure does.
Yeah?
- Hope it was worth it.
- Worth what?
How do you want
that burger cooked?
Hi.
So what happened?
- He grabbed my ass.
- So you broke his nose?
Do you really think you're the
right person to be lecturing me?
Yeah, 'cause right now I'm
the only friend you've got.
So I'll ask you one more time.
What's going on with you?
I'm a fucking waitress.
I'm getting divorced
and my kids look at me
like they don't know me anymore.
And I'm getting groped
by inbred freaks.
Fucking look at me.
Go home.
I'll clean this up.
So this is the one, huh?
Yeah.
I don't know.
A military base?
Sounds risky.
Anything worthwhile usually is.
And it's being decommissioned.
What about Job?
He said he'd think about it.
I don't think he's coming back here.
Look at you, Sugar,
already trying to cut me out.
Is that your driving outfit?
Yes, it is.
And fortunately it's also my
"don't take any shit" outfit.
So whatever it is
you thinking about sayin',
swallow it and pour me
a fuckin' whiskey.
If I start drinkin' now,
maybe I'll be drunk enough to
handle this town in daylight.
Gentlemen...
Camp Genoa.
You know,
my whole way over here,
I just kept thinking,
"I can't believe I'm coming
back to this shithole
to mix it up with
the fuckin' Marines."
Well, it's not the Marines
I'm worried about.
- It's the mercs.
- The mercs?
You didn't say nothing
about no motherfuck-
What kind of mercs?
Well, the bad kind.
I'd say ex-Navy SEALs
if I had to guess.
I don't believe this shit.
What is it with you?
Is it a death wish?
Is that what it is?
Because if it is,
why don't you go out
and get yourself killed?
Why do you always want
to get me killed with you?
- It's a lot of money.
- It's fucking soldiers with guns.
Big fucking guns.
We ain't talking
about rent-a-cops.
We ain't even talkin'
about real cops.
We talkin' about
fuckin' commandos.
- They'll never see us com...
- Uh-uh, nope!
Tell me about the money.