Previously on Revival.
Who's ready for a holy war?
You have authority to
smoke out every reviver.
Tag them and track them.
It works during Shark
Week, and it'll work here.
She used to be a person.
Now she's a reviver.
I'm a reviver, Wayne,
so maybe we can keep
my registry off the books?
Stop dodging me.
I want answers.
That's not mine.
Gentleman needed to replace
his wife's wedding ring.
That asshole lied to me.
I'm done playing it safe.
You with me or not?
I don't need you.
He was in my house. That's
beyond crossing the line.
How many drug-related
offenses do we have?
You shake up the can, you'll
have to deal with fizz.
You still play poker with
that piece of shit Irish cop?
I need to get back
over the border.
-I know what you did!
-I took you
from the bridge, but
I didn't kill you.
Help! Somebody help!
Speed up!
Oh, Dana.
Somebody help!
-What do we know? Anything?
-Dana fired two shots at... Hey!
Uh, Dana?
Cypress family?
There has been significant
internal bleeding.
Thankfully, the bullet seems
to have missed any
of the major organs.
If she makes it through
surgery, we'll keep her sedated
for 24 hours to monitor.
When can we see her?
Could be a few more hours.
Yeah.
I got to go work on
this case. You, uh...
You call me when
she gets out, yeah?
Wait. Dad!
Sorry. I can't.
Please. Please.
Okay. What happened?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Um, um.
Please,
she wasn't here.
Please. She wasn't here.
Please.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Just keep, uh, just
keep me posted.
So I understand there are
no discernible footprints
on the path. The two bullets
that went through our
victims are still missing.
The nine-mil shells you found
are both from Dana's weapon.
But that's it. Huh?
What's the working theory?
Listen, sir, I'm not sure
I'm supposed to be talking
to you about this. Okay?
Brent, I'm the sheriff. All
right? And it's my daughter.
I know. And I know
you Cypresses like to
bend the rules some.
My daughters are
my life. Okay?
And if you think
that for one second
you're going to keep me out
of the loop on any of this,
you better wake up and give
your head a shake, son.
Yeah.
Uh, okay, well...
Well, it's hard to say.
It could have been multiple
shooters, but, uh...
But what?
Well, the most likely scenario
is that Dana drew her gun.
They tussled for it, and
both of them got shot.
I'm sorry, but that's where all
the current evidence
is pointing to.
So, keep looking.
Find me some physical evidence.
All right? Expand
the search perimeter.
Get something that backs
that up because I think
that someone else was
here doing the shooting.
-Oh.
-Any crackpot theories
on why she was here
in the first place?
Uh, no. We're still piecing
that together. Yeah.
I'm gonna talk to our
witness. Ask if...
The doc? I'll go with you.
Wayne, listen,
I will keep you in the
loop as much as I can,
but we got to at least try to
keep appearances here, you know?
Yeah.
Do you own a gun?
Uh, no. Why? Why
would you ask?
You're our only
conscious witness,
and our two victims have
gunshot wounds, so...
Um, because I was, uh, I
was there on a date, sir.
Hm.
She was investigating
something, then, was she?
I, I don't know.
Um, she got a text from someone
and that redirected us
there, to the woods.
Oh. What did that text say?
I don't know.
I didn't think it was
any of my business.
So, you charged into the woods
trying to be the hero, huh?
What did you see when you got
in those woods, Dr. Ramin?
And, um, I saw...
There was a man, um...
-Mr. Weimar.
-Weimar?
Weimar, yeah. Did
Dana say anything
when you got there,
when you saw her?
Did she say anything?
Uh, no, sir.
Dana's a pretty chatty
person, you know.
Even in a bind, so...
No, sir.
You didn't see any
suspects running away
or anything suspicious?
-Nope. It would...
-No.
-It was me, Dana and Mr...
-Mr. Weimar.
Mr. Weimer. And he, uh,
yeah. There was no one else.
Hey. Dana's out of surgery.
Okay, um,
station at the door. Yeah?
I want to know exactly
who's coming and going.
-Okay.
Okay, Dr. Ramin,
let's go over this one
more time, shall we?
Um, okay.
Hey, mind if I,
uh, if I come in?
Coop, can you go sit with Fitzy?
I want to speak to
Ibrahim for a sec.
Dr. Sheppard, line one.
Hey, buddy.
Uh...
This is a lot.
What did you say in there?
Just what I saw,
okay. I didn't...
Except for you.
I know, uh,
I know Dana'd do
anything for you,
but I don't know you,
okay, and a lot of this
isn't making sense,
so I just need you to, uh,
just-just tell me what
happened out there.
I don't know.
Okay, then how...
how did you all end up
in the woods together?
Uh, was that you? Was
that you who texted her?
No, no. I was there
confronting Aaron
and Dana just showed up.
Okay, then who
shot her? Em, huh?
Was it that Aaron guy?
Did he set this all up?
No, no, he couldn't
have. Look, the truth is
is that Aaron and I have
a bit of a history, okay?
So I was there confronting
him, but when I got there,
he was already scared of
something, or someone,
and told me to leave,
but before I could,
his body...
His body just jerked
forward and he fell into me
and he was dead just like that.
Someone shot him and
then Dana showed up
and before I could warn her,
Someone shot her, too.
And then I took her gun
and I shot back and I hit him.
But it wasn't enough
and he got away.
I am so sorry that you have
been brought into all of
this and have to lie for me.
I'm not... I'm not
lying for you. I'm...
I'm lying for Dana.
But I'm a really bad liar,
okay? I suck at it and I just...
I'm so bad, and,
um, I don't know.
If the police keep going and
they keep asking questions,
I might crack, okay?
I'm sorry, I might...
I'm not good...
I'm not good at any of this.
I will figure this out.
Okay?
Trust me.
I'm a Cypress.
Shit.
It's still in me.
But who would kill
Mr. Weimar and shoot
Dana? I'm worried.
It's okay, sweetheart.
We're working the case now.
We'll have answers soon.
Rogers, I need the
coroner's intake exam
the minute it lands on
your desk. Thank you.
You do know I'm capable
of more than paperwork?
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah. Please.
Dad, I wanna help.
Look, you should know.
There is a working theory that
Dana is the one at fault here.
How? She was shot, too.
Sorry, boss. Lester
wants a word.
Not now, Lester!
Go on.
But what does this
mean for Dana?
You're still investigating
who shot her, right?
Like, Dad, what's going on?
-Martha, please!
I can't right now.
I have to focus.
All right, look:
Now you gotta keep
this to yourself, okay?
The evidence presently points
towards Dana as the one
who did the shooting and that
ain't good for Dana, okay?
But I know there has
gotta be more to this
and I'm going to keep digging
until I find out what it is.
How would you go about proving
that another gun was involved?
Both the victims were shot
through and through, okay?
So that means that those bullets
could've gone 600 or so
feet in any direction.
How would you go about
finding a missing bullet?
We've already swept
the area for hours.
But if you find this bullet
you could break the case.
Find the bullet and the shooter.
-Yes, and we'll sweep again.
-Sheriff.
-Once more tomorrow afternoon.
Get out! Now! I said no!
-Okay, okay.
-He escaped! Sorry, boss.
Is this, like, a 1:00
pm situation, or a 4ish?
You stay out of it, okay?
Now that's it. No
more questions.
I have got a killer
to find so, please,
close the door on your way out.
Thank you. I love you.
And tell Lester I'm sorry.
Okay.
Reviver subject Myles Miller,
male, 43 years old on loan from
the Mountain Bay
County Penitentiary.
Please strip, Mr. Miller.
They gotta be
watching while I...?
Yes, ma'am.
You just be sure
to tell the judge
I been on my best behaviour.
Will do.
Careful with those.
Ow!
Ah.
Oh.
-We're good.
-Monsters.
You know how embarrassing
that was for her?
To have that mark in her ID?
Notice on our door?
That bother her or you?
Why do you gotta
be such an asshole?
I'm doing this for
your own good, Ken.
She's a reviver.
A good one! And my wife!
Look, I get it, okay?
But what happens when Diane
or one of the other ones
snaps again?
I have to look at
the big picture.
You think she'd do that?
This is the woman that
brought you casseroles,
helped around the house
when Patty was sick.
Who helped watch little Martha.
The old Diane? Of course not.
But she's gone, Ken.
And we don't really
know for certain yet
who's taken her place.
I know you better
than anybody, Kenny.
And I know if you
weren't so close to this
you'd see it the way I do.
You know what I see?
A man who thinks he
gets a free asshole pass
because his wife died.
When the truth is
you and I both know
you were an asshole
long before that.
Now, I told you before,
I'm not going down this
road with you again. Okay?
So, you better tread softly
when you talk about
Patty and my family.
Diane is my family. Give
me the same damn courtesy.
Now you of all people
should understand
I am the sheriff. Okay?
I have to think about everybody.
I have an obligation
to this town.
I can't let you have it one way
and everybody else
have it another!
But what if it was somebody
that you loved was a reviver?
Would you still do it?
Yes.
You're a nasty piece of work,
considering that you got one
daughter in anger management
and another suspected of murder.
It's clear that the
last piece of goodness
in the Cypress family
died with Patty.
Say it again.
I dare you.
Go ahead, Wayne,
give it your shot.
You know, you might
have the governor
and a few good folks
in this town fooled,
but I know the real you
and I'm making it my
mission to make sure that
you don't get re-elected.
You'll never wear a badge again.
Mr. Mayor.
Don't say a goddamn word
unless you've found
Dana's shooter.
That's what I thought. Now
I gotta get back to work.
You busy yourself somewhere else
doing something else, okay?
You got it, Chief.
Hey, you can push
me just so far.
Are you okay?
-Not really.
-Hm.
Hm.
Well, whatever you gotta
say, you could say it.
It's about Aaron.
Aw, Dude...
Look, I get that
professor shit can be hot.
I do, but you can really
do so much better, Em.
He's dead.
Shit.
Shit, well, I guess
don't kick him now.
-No.
-What the hell even happened?
I don't know. He was
dead when we found him.
You found him dead?
Wait, what do you mean by we?
Me and Dana.
What the hell is
wrong with you two?
Look, I need your help because
whoever shot Aaron shot Dana.
She got shot too?
I need you. Please.
Look, I don't know
who else I can ask
or who I can trust.
I don't know, dude.
This is so whack.
Come on. Just do it already.
Yep, just gonna...
Okay.
I can't look.
I can't look!
Ugh, the blood. The blood!
Oh my... God.
It is not that bad!
Okay.
No. What? No. What
the... We are not making
a Caesar salad here! Look,
I can't get the right angle,
so I need you take off
those gloves and just...
-Ai-ya-yai.
-Pull it out with your fingers.
Come on! Dude, it's
healing. Let's go!
Oh my God, oh my God,
oh my God, oh my God,
oh my God, oh my God, oh my...
Ooh!
I got it!
And now for the hard part.
The hard part?!
This is me.
I might not know
why it happened.
But I'm no longer
sad that it did.
Thank you, Wanda.
Anyone else have anything
they'd like to share?
Go ahead, Damon.
I used to think God had a plan.
And then I died. And
now I'm alive and, uh...
I guess it feels like
something's missing,
like there's a real emptiness
inside me. It's lonely.
And if God does have a
plan, is this really it?
Maybe this is a second
chance. Your opportunity
to live with intention.
Ah, what have we here? Nella.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
God-fearing woman helping
some legion of demons?
Have you no soul?
-Get out of here, Blaine.
Leave these poor people alone!
People?
People bleed and then
die. These are not people.
You're but another
consort of demons
standing amongst the damned
as they're just walking
on this path. It's wicked.
Now you should be
thanking your God
that we are all here to
rescue you from what's coming.
She said leave!
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah. Yeah, I know that smell.
It's pagan rot.
You're one of the
damned going to Hell,
so you should be taking
a good look at me because
I'm going to be
sending you back.
Hey! Don't hurt him.
Oh my God. Are you okay?
Sorry, I...
I didn't realize
my own strength.
Oh. Mm.
We're coming for you.
Starting to show their
true colours, boys.
Gentlemen, help him up.
Shit, you're strong!
Never mind that.
We're going to go over
this one more time.
-Okay.
-You're the distraction.
Me?
Not again.
No problem. Love
helping the ladies.
You know us.
Those lug nuts are
so hard to turn.
Yeah, if you go on
Reddit, lefty loosey,
it actually explains
it's a myth, so...
-Oh.
-You go on Reddit?
Once you get Randy out,
that's when I go in.
I need to get Aaron's blood on
the bullet because, you know,
DNA? So I need
to find his body.
Once I find his body,
that's when I will put
the blood on Aaron's bullet,
so that when the police find I,
they think that the
bullet went through Aaron.
And since the shooter shot
Aaron, Dana, and I all,
once they find the
bullet they find
the shooter who shot Dana.
What the hell?
What are you doing in here?
You should be out there.
You're the distraction!
Randy's barely got
one lug nut off.
He's a creep. I told
him I had to piss.
Oh, that would've
been a lot easier.
Careful!
You throw up and your DNA
is all over the place.
I'm at a dead end, Danes.
I need your help with this.
I want to get whoever did
this but the leads are shit.
You know, I wish to hell
you'd have come to me
if you were in trouble.
Yeah, well, I'm
sure it's my fault.
Your mom always said
I was too hard on you.
I just had to be sure you
were on the right path.
You gotta come out of this.
Oh, uh, Sheriff, Sheriff.
I, uh, I got more information
on, uh, Mr. Weimar.
Yeah, uh, it appears he was,
um, choked before he was shot.
What about the GSR results?
Are they still missing?
Well, that was an
honest mistake, um...
You know Randy?
Yeah, well ever since that man
woke up in his incinerator,
he's been a little bit
all over the place.
Do you have anything of merit
that you want to
share with me, Deputy?
Yeah, I'll just
get into it. Uh...
The last text that, uh, Aaron
Weimar sent before he, uh,
before he died was to Dana.
Yeah, it, uh...
"Go to the woods behind Pacer's.
I'll tell you what
really happened."
Okay, what's taking you so long?
You said they're coming
in the afternoon,
which could be any minute now.
I know, I know.
I just need it to be perfect.
They need to find the bullet,
but not think it was moved.
I'm going to have a lifetime
worth of trauma for this.
Okay, if this is
your worst trauma,
you've lived a very
privileged life.
What?
I toss it I compromise
the scene, right?
You do listen.
Hm.
Oh my God.
My God, Dana's awake!
-Oh my God. Shit.
-Oh, shit.
Testing shows no phosphate
or nitrate present
in the water samples
from Moore Creek.
This rules out
The usual cause of rapid
algae bloom formation.
We still need to test all
known elements and pathogens,
but for now my theory remains
Moore Creek is ground
zero for Revival Day.
Hey. Just the man I
wanted to speak to.
Good. If it's about
what happened to Dana
'cause that's all
I want to hear.
-I already talked...
-Look...
-...to your deputy about it.
-Maybe you missed something.
Think! All right?
Are you sure about the
direction of the gunfire?
You know, maybe you
saw a strange car,
or heard someone else there?
Oh...
You did see something
else, didn't you?
What aren't you telling me?
Nothing? I just...
What the hell is...?
Hey.
Get it out!
Get it out! Please!
Please!
This.
Note that we increased the
dosage by five milligrams.
-Get it out! Hurry! Please!
-Let me get this out.
I got you. I got you.
You're okay. Okay? Okay. Okay.
You're okay. You're okay.
Hey. What are you...
What are you doing?
We're giving him crotalase.
You're giving him snake venom?
No, we were testing more
extreme ranges of pathogens
to see if we could
get the sheriff
the answers he needs.
And your hypothesis?
Crotalase could
slow cell division.
-What does that mean?
-As you can see,
it dramatically slows down
reviver healing properties.
Yeah, but this, this,
this is inhumane.
Wasn't the intention.
After revivers showed
unnatural strength under duress
we decided to try this option.
So they are dangerous?
No. We cannot jump
to conclusions.
Which is why we rely on science.
Now that we know that we
can slow revivers down,
all we have to do is just
change the dose and then
maybe we can figure out
what started this
whole revival thing
in the first place.
Starting here.
Here. With torture?
No, with discovery.
No! This is not
the way, Sheriff.
You know what can happen if
this gets into the wrong hands.
Look, take a beat, Doc.
I won't let that happen.
Look, good work, okay?
And while I want to
keep everyone safe,
this is good intel,
but let's step back from
this direction of
inquiry for a while.
Copy?
Copy.
All these years trying
to get your respect
all I had to do was get shot.
How you feeling?
Like I got hit by a Mack truck.
Lose a fight with a razor?
Shut up. I like it.
How long was I out?
Twenty-four hours, give or take.
Oh, God. Poor Coop. He
must have been so worried.
We all were.
He's okay, though.
He's with Nella.
-Did they find who did this?
-Not yet.
But they have Fitzy stationed
at the door just to be careful,
but, Dana, what were
you doing out there?
I could ask you the same thing.
You were right about Aaron.
He was on the bridge that night
and somehow his ring
was inside of me.
He was lying, so I really
thought that he killed me
even though he swears
that he didn't.
Em...
did you kill Aaron?
God, really...
wanted to.
And I almost did.
But I couldn't.
And I didn't.
-Good.
But whoever shot him,
shot you. I even
fired back at them.
Do you... Do you think that
they were there for Aaron
and maybe you just got
caught in the middle?
I don't know but
I'll figure it out.
What if...
I was the reason
that you nearly died?
Come here.
I just don't know
what I would have done
if I lost you, too.
I'm not going anywhere, okay?
Okay.
We'll figure this out.
Together.
I think it's time I
start taking care of you.
How are you going to do that?
I have my ways.
Consistent with the
injuries of the victim.
Who we looking at now?
We're working on it.
I'll, uh, I'll let you know
as soon as we know something.
JP.
Have you talked to Lester yet?
-What is it about this time?
Well, I think you're going
to want to hear this.
Apparently he saw
someone suspicious
the night of the shooting.
Goddamn people always
traipsing through
my woods. I keep telling
you but you don't listen.
So then the other night,
I'm out walking my
dog, Chuck, like usual,
and I hear two shots.
Then another two.
That's four in total.
Then this man, all in black
with one of those
black ski masks,
which they should not
be selling on account of
they're the mask of choice
for said perpetrators.
-Lester, get to the point!
-All right, Sheriff.
Okay. Yes, sir.
So, this black-ski-masking fella
goes tearing across the
east side of my property
like a bat out of hell right
toward Stone Bridge Road.
He was wearing those pants
with all them pockets,
I think tactical boots and one
of those small flashlights.
I believe it was a Fenix TK16.
Maybe a Klarus XT2CR.
Like this?
Well, yeah. Exactly.
Of course, those
3100 lumen ones,
they have about
400 yards of throw.
Most people cheap out
with the 250 lumen ones.
Brent!
Hey, Lewis, come over here.
Lester saw the shooter.
It's a cop.
-Uh, what?
-Yeah.
I want you to run ballistics
on everybody's firearm,
including yours.
Okay, yeah. Um, well, I'm
gonna need yours, too.
All right.
Now, I want you to check
their lockers, okay?
Their vehicles. Work and
private. Evidence logs.
We're gonna need a clean
chain of evidence here
without you, so...
-That's why I'm telling you
to do it because I'm not
doing it myself! Okay?
Yep. All right. I get it.
Sheriff, please. Please.
Good. Yep. Um, Fitzy,
Rogers? Let's go, all right?
I got more.
Yes, we all know you
have a moral objection,
but that doesn't mean you can
refuse an official request.
Yes, I can. That's why
they call it "request."
Request denied.
-Since it was the sheriff
who asked for the
CDC's assistance
and he isn't here
to say otherwise,
I am inclined to let Dr. Morel
continue with her
line of investigation.
As head of the Wausau
project, I firmly disagree.
-Ibrahim, let it go.
-You heard the sheriff:
He doesn't want
your kind of help.
If we're going to talk,
let's make sure that the
whole class can hear.
-Sorry.
-Now, Dr. Ramin,
I'm not sure how things
work with the CDC,
but in Wausau, you
are an interloper
and obstructing the
sheriff's mandate
and defying my order
is unacceptable.
Well, then, we
are at an impasse.
No, we're at a
leadership change.
Wait. If you just
talked to the sheriff,
if you just talk
to him, you could
just figure this whole thing...
-No need.
You can surrender all your
samples and data to Dr. Morel.
She heads the Wausau
project as of today.
You answer to her now.
-What?
-Thank you, ma'am.
I appreciate your support.
Don't let me down.
I'll give you a second.
Hm.
This brave soul
proved himself
worthy to our cause.
His sacrifice deserves
a great reward.
Our rock, our fortress,
grant us everlasting light!
grant us everlasting light.
Our rock, our fortress,
It's time for you
to get branded.
Become one of the flock.
Go in. Give your hand
to the guiding light.
May it burn away your sins
and become one of us.
Our rock, our fortress...
Behold!
His ascension.
Our rock, our fortress,
grant us everlasting light
Our rock, our fortress...
It's a colouring book.
I'm, like, a grown-ass woman.
Uh, yeah. The, the, I
thought the candy could
be for you and then...
-Oh.
The colouring book and
everything else, uh,
maybe for Cooper.
It's really nice. Thank you.
Yeah.
Glad you're here.
Yeah. Yeah, me, too.
Thank you.
Listen, I get that
I asked you to lie.
And I know that
that's a lot. I know.
And you didn't question
it and that says a lot.
But I want you to know that...
I can't tell you
what's going on,
but I promise you
it was for a good reason
and I'm really sorry for
putting you through that.
Thank you for
protecting my sister.
Yeah. It's... It's okay.
Well, I mean, this part of
my day, believe it or not,
turned out to be just
okay in a good way.
-Really?
-Yeah, yeah.
No, I just said that and
yeah, it did, it did.
Well, I've only been
out for 24 hours.
Fill me in. What happened?
-No, I'm not going to do it.
Dump my problems on... No.
-Oh, come on!
-You're in a hospital bed.
-Honestly, this is
the last time you'll get
my undivided attention.
I promise you that. So
just shoot your shot.
Oh!
Pick a different
choice of words.
Anything else.
Oh, well, uh, I...
I may not have a
job for much longer.
What? Are you leaving Wausau?
Not if I can help it. Um...
Why? Would you be...
Would you be sad?
Well, I'm just
thinking, you know?
I was just... I was just
wondering, maybe, uh,
well, I would love another date.
But, uh, no guns this time.
Hm.
Well, you did bring
me candy, so...
♪ Because you believe in me ♪
You can turn darkness into day!
It's a powerful thing to say
Because you believe in me
You can make
everything go my way
The feeling of...
-Brent!
-Ow!
God, didn't take you
for a flowers guy.
Oh, those were, uh, left
at the nurses' station.
Guess not everyone in town
wants you dead after all.
Yippee-ki-yay.
So, uh, some news you'll like.
We found the bullet
that killed Aaron
and your gun wasn't a match.
Yeah, no shit.
But you'll never
believe whose was.
McCray.
-McCray?
-Yeah.
Why?
Who knows why McCray does
any of the stuff he does.
And you will never believe
what we found on the guy.
What the hell?
Is that a foot?
♪ Because you believe in me ♪
♪ You can turn
darkness into day ♪
♪ It's a powerful feeling
knowing you love me ♪
♪ Because you believe in
me I can make anything... ♪