All right, hold on.
I got the turn up here.
Oh! How cool was that?
That was way cool!
- My turn.
- Sorry, that's not allowed.
I just signed
15 pages of forms saying
- you gotta rideon the back.
- I don't see any lawyers around.
- You know that's not the point.
- No.
You just wanna keep
all the fun to yourself.
Come on, Dad!
You go over 15, we're pulling
over, all right? I mean it.
- You're the best.
- All right, get on there.
- Put on your goggles.
- Okay.
- Ready?
- Got the clutch in?
All right, that's my boy.
Adam, you're going too fast,
slow it down!
I mean it, you're going too fast.
Slow down!
Adam!
Let go of the throttle!
Adam! No!
What've you got?
Sixteen-year-old, status post,
ATV crash,
40% burns on his body.
Nasotracheal intubation.
Start a bag of lactated
Ringer's, wide open...
- Will he be okay?
- We'll be with you when we can.
Get him out!
Wait, wait, wait!
I'll start fluids.
Let's go get him hooked up.
Watch the line.
- Been looking for you.
- Been avoiding you.
Burn Unit can handle it.
If they could handle it,
they wouldn't be asking for you.
- Is that a journal?
- Friend wrote an article.
In Hindi?
They have a cutting-edge
neuroscience program in India.
It says so right on the cover.
Kid's heart rate's messed.
Tachycardia
can be explained by the burn.
I assume
the Burn Unit knew that.
His potassium's low.
Which can also be explained
by the burn.
Except I'm sure the Burn Unit's
pumping him with fluids
which means his potassium
should be going up, not down.
Could be amphetamines.
Or bacteria
lunching on his heart.
Or cardiomyopathy,
or some other very bad thing.
He needs an EKG.
Okay, no skin, no EKG.
Is he even
gonna survive the burn?
What, you got
a date or something?
Forty percent of his body.
If the Burns Unit
can prevent an infection,
his body will regenerate
maybe 10%,
surgeons will do 20 or so grafts,
six months in this room,
he'll end up with a series of nasty
scars, maybe some pain,
but he'll live.
Unless his heart shuts down
'cause we can't figure out what's causing
the low potassium and tachycardia.
We need help from a Belgian doc
named Einthoven.
He's dead.
While he was alive, he invented a little
dittie called the Galvanometer.
Where do we get one?
Go to any electronics store
that's been open since before 1905.
There's a good chance they've got one
in a corner in the basement.
We need an audio-visual setup
for the lecture hall.
- What for?
- For the lecture.
- What lecture?
- Dr. Weber's lecture.
- Who is Dr. Weber?
- A neurologist, I think.
The memo was from you.
- Where is my assistant?
- She left.
- When?
- Wednesday.
- Seriously?
- Well, the temp agency sent someone,
but she got lost.
Well, when she gets here,
fire her.
Oh, yeah.
- Did you issue this memo?
- Look at that.
Congratulations.
The patient that has been in a
coma for two years and counting
is still in a coma.
This is not my signature.
I don't know
anything about this guy.
I'm supposed to introduce him?
Have lunch?
- The coma patient has a migraine?
- Oh, no, no, no.
No, I gave him medication
to prevent a migraine.
That's a migraine.
Increased flow velocity
in his cerebral arteries.
I did subsequently give him
nitroglycerin, which could possibly...
You induced a migraine
headache in a coma patient?
I gave him a little headache, similar
to the one you're giving me now.
Have you even read
an ethical guideline?
Well, it would be wrong to try out a
new migraine prevention medication
on someone
who can actually feel pain.
- Did you sign this?
- Yeah.
We can talk later about
the appropriate discipline.
Because of the burn,
we can't perform any of our
normal tests to see what's wrong.
So we're going to try
a Galvanometer.
It picks up a pulse
in the wrists and the ankles.
Hopefully it'll tell us why
his heart rhythm is abnormal.
- What have I done to him? I...
- It was an accident.
All right? So...
He's got all these burns
and now there's something
wrong with his heart?
We're trying to figure out if
the two are somehow connected.
- Had he been sick lately?
- No, nothing.
Anything unusual
with his behavior?
- Had he been tired a lot?
- Nothing.
He was great, he was happy, he was
just having a great time, and then...
If he was experimenting with
amphetamines or cocaine...
No.
We gave him some pot
about a year ago, to try...
It was just once.
We thought if we took the mystery
out of drugs and alcohol,
the less he'd experiment.
We'll know more
after the tests.
It looks like
they're gonna electrocute him.
Plug it in.
You plug it in.
Fine. Give me the cord.
Works.
Prominent U waves.
No inverted T wave.
No ischemia.
Q wave normal.
That's not good.
Okay, turn it off. Turn it off!
- What's happening?
- What is that?
The seizure's getting...
Can't you stop that?
Who electrocuted my patient?
- He had a seizure.
- He wasn't electrocuted.
What does the seizure tell us?
Move.
What are you looking for?
Same as you are, love, acceptance,
solid return on an investment.
Differential diagnosis. Go.
Could be epilepsy
or seizure disorder.
Not with the tachycardia. It
could be a virus in his brain.
Your specificity's impressive.
Adrenoleukodystrophy.
Could be MS.
The seizures could be caused by
plaques and lesions on the brain.
Well, let's find out which.
Get him an MRI.
No nuclear imaging!
He wouldn't survive the move to Radiology.
MRI and CT scan are both out.
Okay, lumbar puncture will tell
us if his proteins are elevated,
at least we can exclude MS.
We can't do
a lumbar puncture either.
You're cramping my exits.
Don't tell me,
no skin on his spine.
We'd be inserting a needle into an
area that's teeming with bacteria.
If he doesn't have a brain infection
already, we'd give him one for sure.
There's no other way
to look at a brain.
Transcranial
Doppler Sonography.
She said "brain",
not "pregnant woman's uterus."
They do sound alike. I used one
to look at a brain this morning.
Why didn't you take the patient
to Radiology, get an MRA?
Obviously
I was doing something illegal.
Using nuclear imaging
would have raised questions.
You're not gonna get a diagnosis
of MS from a sonogram.
Not definitively,
but patients with MS
have more reactive neurons
in their occipital cortex.
Okay then.
Thank you for all coming
to today's lecture
by Dr. Phillip Weber,
who is our guest today
at our hospital
to talk about headaches.
Dr. Weber is at the Weber Center
for Pain, that makes sense.
Weber, Weber.
So please welcome Dr. Weber!
Thank you Dr. Cuddy.
I suppose I should tell you a
little bit more about myself.
I went to school in Virginia.
You've never been to one of
these things in your life.
- Who is this guy?
- No idea.
What's with the outfit?
Sudden chills
and light sensitivity.
Inexplicable.
I received my medical degree
at Johns Hopkins University,
where I studied under
Brightman and Gilmar...
Hmm. He must be good.
You went to Hopkins, and studied
under Brightman and Gilmar.
Shh.
Helped me win the Doyle
Internship at the Mayo Clinic.
You were supposed
to get the Doyle Internship.
This guy's Von Lieberman? The guy who
got you thrown out for cheating?
The dean threw me out. Von
Lieberman just ratted on me.
This guy's name is Weber,
not Von Lieberman.
I call Weber Von Lieberman,
way eviler.
Shh.
1D receptors have improved the
acute treatment of migraines,
to this point...
So what's the plan?
You gonna wait until he bends
over and make a fart sound?
I'm not here about the past.
He's a bad scientist.
Well, you cheated off him,
how bad can he be?
He got the answer wrong.
Are they trying to wake him up?
They can't do that, right?
He'll be in too much pain.
Don't worry, he's still under.
But the brain never completely
sleeps, it's always working.
Controlling your heart rate,
breathing, temperature.
The eyes
respond to visual stimuli.
Blood flow increases
in certain areas of the brain
and we can track that
with a sonogram.
With MS, blood vessels are more
reactive, so flow is faster.
If Adam has an infection,
there'd be swelling, which
would constrict the arteries.
And the flow would be slower.
Chase.
Near the subarachnoid space.
Data from control subjects were
analyzed of a two-way ANOVA
with status and side
as within-subject factors.
You stalked this guy for 20 years
just for this shot to humiliate him?
I'm trying to learn.
Vessels without
significant rebound...
He doesn't even know
what that means.
You're gonna interrupt him,
aren't you?
If I have a question.
And what's that
gonna accomplish?
Why can't you just enjoy this? Why
can't you just be happy for me?
You have got to find less debilitating
outlets than humiliating people.
I hear bowling is more fun
than stalking.
But I'm better at this.
If "P" is less than
point-zero...
Blow a ton of money
on a plasma TV.
We found a subarachnoid bleed.
Bleed in the head
isn't causing seizures.
It could be. 10% with damage to
cerebral cortex have a seizure.
Or bacterial meningitis.
- Viral encephalitis?
- There's no way to tell without...
Shut up!
Excuse me.
Not you.
You know, if my lecture is
interrupting your meeting, I can wait.
As your people say in India.
Appreciate it.
We'll figure out why later.
Fix the bleed or he dies.
Talk to you in a couple hours.
I'm in the subarachnoid space.
- Can you get it?
- Think so.
Put the probe back where it
was so I can see the wire!
We're looking for the bleed
in...
Look when I get there, I'm flying
blind without a contrast CT here!
And with a p-value
of less than 0.001,
we have strong statistical evidence that
this drug prevents migraine headaches
without daily administration.
Excuse me, Doctor.
He knows his field
better than you do.
It's always been my understanding that,
unless you follow a daily regimen,
no drug can prevent a migraine.
That's why they call it
a breakthrough.
That's why
you call it a breakthrough.
No, the pharmaceutical company
sponsoring my clinical trials
also hails it
as a breakthrough.
I'm sure your wife
and lawyer do, too.
Is there anybody who doesn't
stand to make a fortune from it
calling it a breakthrough?
Who are you?
Just a lunatic
who desperately needs a hobby.
How exactly
do these studies work?
Do you give this drug
to a bunch of people,
and if they don't get a migraine,
you go, "Voilà, my drug works"?
Excuse me, miss?
Do you have cancer?
Wow! Mango juice
prevents cancer.
Perhaps I should have taken my
medication before this lecture.
We had a very specific control
group, chronic migraine sufferers.
I don't have time to go through
all the math right now,
- but the incidence was dramatically...
- Sure, in India.
Two plus two
equals five there, right?
Do I know you?
I know your math skills.
They blow.
Touché.
You sound very familiar.
Why did you publish it in an
obscure journal in India?
Why not publish it in really, really
cool head cases of South Philly?
Neuroscience New Delhi
is a respected journal.
Yeah. The guy running Slurp N' Gulp
tells me it's one of the best.
Get a hooker, anything.
See, I'm thinking that publishing
studies is probably the easiest way
to get a pharmaceutical company
to give you a reach-around.
And choosing a journal that no one
can actually read, well, that's...
That's shrewd.
- I know I know you.
- Sure you do, Dick.
The name's Philip.
My bad. Something to do
with your face.
I always think
your name is Dick.
- House?
- Here.
Medical school was 20 years ago.
Give it a rest. Grow up.
Yeah. You were always the grown-up.
Do the responsible thing, tattletale!
- You cheated!
- I cheated then, you're cheating now!
Your drug doesn't work.
Oh, yes, you would like to believe that
because it plays right into your fantasy...
- I tested it.
- Oh, really?
What are your parameters?
Where's your study?
Room 2134.
- One patient?
- The coma patient?
You haven't changed a bit.
You took shortcuts in med school,
you're taking shortcuts now.
You cannot test this
on an abnormal brain.
That's so close-minded. He's
not abnormal, he's special.
Cerebral cortex
atrophies in coma patients.
You need live,
conscious people.
You don't know everything,
House!
Something
that disrupts brain function.
Plaques are perfect. Interrupt
neuronal communication.
- MS?
- No, MS is complicated.
I think this is more basic. It's
just tachycardia and seizures.
How much longer the Burn Unit guys
gonna keep him in that thing?
Lecture's over, let's go.
House wants to...
Adam's waking up.
Get the anesthesiologist
in here now.
He's in pain.
That's not pain.
Need some help in here!
Adam had an orgasm.
What? You mean,
while he was sedated...
What's wrong?
I'm having a migraine.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I was right.
I'm gonna knock you out
for a couple of hours.
No, I got work to do.
Just give me sumatriptan
for the pain
and verapamil
so it doesn't recur.
I heard the patient had fun
in the hyperbaric chamber.
Yeah.
Gotta schedule me
some time in there.
Weber's meds
aren't even legal in the U.S.
It's legal in India.
I was disoriented.
Moving around is a bad idea.
Hey, if you feel chest pain,
you need to let me know.
Verapamil can cause
congestive heart failure.
Nothing can hurt my heart.
Hey, you're gonna feel some dizziness.
Definitely gonna be constipated.
Differential diagnosis
for getting off.
Is he gonna be okay?
No. Something's seriously wrong
with him.
Differential diagnosis
for ejaculation.
Don't make me say it again.
We're not stalling,
we just don't know.
Then guess.
- Could pain medication cause an orgasm?
- I wish.
Maybe pain caused the orgasm.
You get a tattoo, the brain releases
endorphins which create pleasure.
Most people don't orgasm
from a needle prick.
Well, Chase has a point.
The brain is like a huge train
station, if the switches...
You're the neurologist,
talk for me.
If sensory information got misinterpreted
by the medial forebrain bundle,
it's possible for bad to feel
good, and good to feel bad.
He's a lucky kid. Let's not
fix him until the burns heal.
So what attacks
the medial forebrain bundle?
Infective neuropathies,
vasculitic neuropathies...
Krabbe's disease,
metachromatic leukodystrophy.
All very bad things.
No way to look for any of them
in his condition.
Could be an infection.
I said infection
about eight seconds ago.
You listed
some brain infections.
But what if it's just a regular old
infection festering in the burned skin?
Pus on his arm isn't causing
problems in the forebrain.
He's on 20 different medications
to manage his pain, his heart,
how often he urinates.
His brain is like a waiter
that's got too many...
Hey, hey. I do the metaphors.
The brain is stressed.
An infection elsewhere
could put it over the edge.
So we just wait for his burns
to heal to see if you're right?
If you're wrong, he doesn't
have that kind of time.
Dominic Larrey.
He another dead doctor?
He's Napoleon's
Surgeon in Chief.
Cleaned a lot of battle wounds.
By amputating legs.
And with bugs.
Maggots are implanted
directly into Adam's burns.
Maggots, they eat dead people,
I...
Maggots eat dead flesh.
Only dead flesh.
So they're perfectly suited
to clean wounds.
They also kill the bacteria
that thrive in injured tissues.
Dr. Jekyll, I presume.
They found a half-eaten sheep in the zoo.
The police wanna ask you a few questions.
I need something
to wash it down.
Coffee? Bad idea.
- You're better off with water!
- Coffee's closer.
Foolproof plan, by the way.
Either his meds would work,
and you'd be in psychic pain
because Von Evil is gonna be rich.
Or they wouldn't, and you
get to be in agony all day.
Perfect lose-lose situation.
Very you.
- I had to prove...
- You've proved nothing.
Right. This isn't a migraine.
Yeah. "Dear New England
Journal of Medicine",
I took this guy's drug
and still got a headache.
"Thus, scientifically proving
that my arch enemy is an idiot."
You just wanted the pain.
Meds are supposed
to prevent migraine.
You get distracted by pain.
Leaves less room for the things
you don't wanna think about.
Like the Flyers sucking,
or the price of gas,
or the fact that you pushed the
love of your life out of your life.
God, I wish the pain
would go away.
Next time you need to get your mind
off her, stick a needle in your eye.
It's less annoying to the rest
of us when you can still walk.
Did you sleep here?
Lower.
Do you want a pillow?
Not softer, lower.
Frequency of your voice
is grating.
You should've been better
by now.
I'm super.
Patient?
The maggots
did great for the burn.
But the brain waves
are still all over the map.
Which means your regular old infection
isn't causing his brain dysfunction.
Which means there's
an underlying condition,
which means we've gotta
get inside his head.
Do a lumbar puncture.
We've already established
that we can't get a lumbar...
C2, C3.
No. No. No way.
I only saw a cervical tap once,
and that guy got paralyzed.
Ask the parents if they prefer to have
their son in a wheelchair or dead.
Something's causing his brain
to lose control.
Eventually it'll shut off.
We need to do a lumbar puncture
to get some of the fluid in
his spine so we can test it.
You need us to sign a consent?
I have to warn you.
There's a serious risk
of paralysis or death.
Are you saying
we shouldn't do this?
You have to do this.
Then why are you telling us
what can go wrong?
- I just think you should know...
- Either you're cruel
or this clipboard is a way
for you to cover your ass,
- in case you cripple our son.
- This isn't his fault.
No, it's not. It's yours, that's
what you keep telling me.
My son is lying in there
half-dead,
I am just trying to find a way
to get through this.
- I'm sorry.
- Yeah, I know.
Needle.
- It's not going in.
- Don't force it.
I'm going one space higher.
It's too close to his brain
stem, it'll herniate.
- You're gonna paralyze him.
- You're not helping.
His blood pressure's spiking,
stop.
I can get it.
He's 180 over 120,
he's gonna stroke.
I'm in the space.
Give me the vial.
He doesn't have MS
or an infection.
His proteins aren't elevated?
Wrong protein. IgM, not IgG.
Elevation was probably caused
by the bleed.
What if there was tingling in his
extremities prior to the crash?
- How can you still be on MS?
- I gotta be on something.
Something's interrupting his
neurons' chitchat, like lesions.
We can't scan for them.
The only test we can do, we
just did and it was negative.
He has no tingling,
no numbness.
And you read his history, parents
didn't say anything about...
What about Adam?
We can't look into his brain, but
you want us to read his mind?
Good point.
Yeah, you can finish
the sponge bath in a minute.
They're just re-doing his dressings.
He's out, he's fine.
I didn't page you to put him out.
I paged you to wake him up.
Why are these lights
so damn bright?
Thank you.
Come on, I need to talk to him.
House, you can't wake up a burn
victim to play twenty questions.
- It's torture.
- He won't remember.
- He's gonna be in extraordinary...
- God, you're good!
You're putting me to sleep.
I know he's gonna be in pain, I know
you disapprove. I'm his attending.
Wake him up.
Oh, my God!
- I'm Dr. House.
- It hurts!
It's gonna get a lot worse,
so answer fast.
Before the accident, did you experience
any numbness or tingling in your fingers?
You got burned, it's healing,
I need an answer.
It really hurts!
Any tingling
in your arms or legs?
You gotta do something,
I can't...
Adam, you gotta listen to me,
did you feel anything?
I pissed in my pants
and then I don't remember...
- Was he okay?
- Get everyone in my office.
Where you going?
Kid's screaming gave me a headache.
I gotta take an aspirin.
House, you okay?
We've been waiting for you.
I'm hallucinating.
Hallucinations with migraines
are pretty uncommon.
- What did you see?
- I saw music.
Sensory deception
makes no sense.
You took something.
The kid's
fighting for his life.
Hey, you find him?
He was hallucinating
in the locker room.
He okay?
He's feeling no pain,
he's high.
Vicodin high?
Past that. He's seeing sounds.
Took something.
Why is it so dark in here?
It's a beautiful day outside.
Open the shades,
let the sun shine in.
It's nighttime.
- It's still Tuesday, right?
- You look better.
- I took something.
- Mind if I ask what?
Little of this, little of that.
I know
what's wrong with our patient.
He's depressed.
- He told you that when you woke him up?
- Nope.
He told me he pissed his pants
and blacked out.
That's not diagnostic of depression.
Lack of appetite, isolating yourself.
Uncontrollable urination and blacking
out are good predictors of what?
Seizure.
Which means the seizure he had
when you tested his heart
- was at least his second seizure.
- So what?
Depression and seizures
aren't correlated.
No, but you know what is?
Depression
and anti-depression medicine.
Tox screen was clean.
Yeah, but you know how much
crap he's got in his system
for dealing with those burns.
The guy could have the Spanish Armada
floating through his bloodstream
and we wouldn't know about it,
till they started firing cannons.
Antidepressants have been known to cause
seizures in kids, but not orgasms.
This is a brain in trouble.
This is a brain
with too much serotonin.
Serotonin affects mood, appetite, it
doesn't cause the brain to shut down.
Antidepressants fake brains into
thinking they have more serotonin
than they actually do.
Every ten million or so cases
sets off a chain reaction.
Produces too much,
enough to fry itself.
If Adam has Serotonin Storm,
it's deadly.
But treatable. Cyproheptadine.
Unless he doesn't have
Serotonin Storm.
He could just as easily have too
much dopamine as serotonin,
but if it's dopamine, the
cyproheptadine will kill him.
Where are you going?
Gonna talk to the kid again,
he seems nice.
You can't.
Why? Did he say
he doesn't like me?
Anesthesiologist
told the parents what you did.
Everyone's a tattletale.
Is your son depressed?
- No. Who are you?
- I'm Dr. House.
Oh, you're the idiot
who thought...
I heard him screaming
all the way down the hallway.
If I didn't wake him up, I wouldn't
have learned what caused the crash.
He had a seizure.
This wasn't my fault?
Well, if he hadn't had the brain
problem, he wouldn't have the burns.
On the other hand, if you
hadn't put him on the ATV,
he also
wouldn't have the burns.
You can debate your personal
responsibility after I leave.
I need to wake him up again.
I need to know if
he's taking antidepressants.
He's not.
- He's the happiest kid I know.
- But you don't know, do you?
He's my son.
That's sort of my point.
At 16, they'll tell anyone
anything, except their parents.
Adam talks to us
about everything.
Yeah, I know
about the pot and the cocaine.
There was never... Cocaine.
What...
Are you sure?
Are you having him followed?
He told us
when he got drunk at a party.
when he started having sex.
At 16? Way to go.
He told us when he
cheated on a math test.
He told us when his
girlfriend cheated on him.
- He doesn't hide anything from us.
- But if he was depressed?
He'd tell us.
We don't judge, he's not
depressed, we're sure.
"Bet his life on it" sure?
Just hypothetically.
Yeah.
Okay.
Kid's happy.
Happy, happy, happy.
Then we're back to where we started.
Seizure disorders.
Seizure disorders
aren't causing orgasms.
Vascular malformations?
Would've seen it
on the sonogram.
Hepatic encephalopathy?
Liver enzyme tests were normal.
- Where are you going?
- Take a leak.
What are you doing?
You can't come in here,
you're not sterile.
Don't touch our son,
we told you...
Seriously, millions of
bacteria, microbes on you.
He'll die of sepsis.
If you go in there...
I think
he's gonna wake him up again.
I know he is.
House, you can't do this.
Oh, if I had a nickel for every
time I've heard that. Relax.
Are they gonna sue us?
If I'm right, I save his life.
If I'm wrong,
he's dead no matter what I do.
Either way, how much
have I really hurt them?
Leave him alone!
You're not sterile.
Do you wanna kill the kid?
- Give me the syringe.
- No pain, no gain.
Hey, you gotta stop this.
They're right.
- He's not depressed.
- Yeah, sure.
I'm not letting you go
till you give me that syringe.
What's that on his wrist?
A burn.
- Why on his wrist?
- Why not on his wrist?
His back, his torso, everything's a mess.
His forearms are clean.
- Except right there.
- So what?
It's a perfect circle.
So a drop of burning gasoline fell
on his wrist, a screw from the ATV.
Maybe.
- Why are you torturing him?
- Does your son smoke?
I'd kill him.
So, he can talk to you about sex,
crack, anything except cigarettes.
He has a cigarette burn
on his wrist.
Also a fading nicotine stain
between two fingers.
Bad news, your son has a
filthy, unhealthy habit.
Good news, he's trying to quit.
Bad news,
the quitting's killing him.
Good news,
I can cure him. Bad news...
- Nope, that's the end of it.
- Quitting smoking can kill?
No-smoke meds
are antidepressants.
The crappy ones
you get over the Internet
are loaded with whatever
antidepressants they can get cheap.
And since Mommy and Daddy obviously
didn't take him to a pediatrician...
Sorry, I was wrong
about him being depressed.
Treat him.
Hey!
Did you drop acid?
- Why would I do that?
- To annoy me.
Or maybe because
you're miserable,
or because
you want to self-destruct.
Pick one.
How about because LSD acts on
serotonin receptors in the brain,
which can stop
a migraine in its tracks.
I'm just saying
that's also a possibility.
- How did you know about it?
- Cameron is worried about you.
I told her that LSD lasts up to 12 hours,
if you were functional, she must be wrong.
Either that or I also took a
whole bunch of antidepressants,
which short-circuited the LSD.
I'm just saying
that would also explain it.
Thank you for ruining
my clinical trials.
Pharmaceutical company's
shutting me down.
- You're kidding. Really?
- How could that surprise you?
You sent them an email
complaining about my math,
telling them about your stunt.
I didn't know
people actually read emails.
Delete button's
so conveniently located.
So what's next?
You gonna follow me my whole life?
- Torture me?
- Why would I do that?
You waited 20 years to do this.
What's next?
Break up my marriage?
- No. We're even.
- Right.
Oh, thanks for setting me up.
Eye for an eye,
LSD and antidepressants.
Everything in balance.
Buddhists call it Karma. Christians
call it the Golden Rule.
Jews call it...
I don't know, Rabbi Hillel
said something poignant.
Universe
always settles the score.
- Does it?
- No.
But it should.
Do you think you'll ever be able
to look at him and not blame me?
Yeah. Will you?
I'm Paula.
- Hey, Paula.
- How you doing?
You work over at the college, or
are you full-time over at the...
I'm looking for a distraction.
You don't need to talk
to do that, do you?