Gosh! I guess he got away.
Can Baby Shoes come out to play?
Come on! Hands on your head.
Climb out.
I can't climb out
if my hands are on my head.
Just keep them where I can see them,
man. Come on.
- You high, popo?
- Yeah, man.
Catching morons makes me high.
Lift your shirt up by your collar
and turn around.
Would you look at that?
Dude's got a weapon.
All right.
You have the right to remain stupid.
Watch the gun.
Anything you say will be
completely incomprehensible.
- Seriously, man! Careful!
- Seriously, man? Seriously?
Does your mama know what you do?
Oh. It's sweet. Your dad's proud.
- You made the local paper.
- For my article.
Give it a rest. You read
what he wrote in the margin?
"Our friend Lazarus sleeps,
but I go that I may wake him up."
Yeah. He's not proud of me,
he's proud of Jesus.
Everything I do right is God's work.
Everything I do wrong is
my own damn fault.
Cop with a sense of humor.
Differential diagnosis.
Guy's in the ER, bleeding on everybody.
- Drugs?
- He's a cop.
Good point. How about drugs?
Tox screen was clean.
He did, however, get hit by a bullet.
Just mentioning.
- He was shot?
- No, somebody threw it at him.
I'm thinking trauma. He got
bullet fragments lodged in his brain.
According to Baby Shoes,
the cop was laughing before he got shot.
- Baby Shoes?
- The guy who shot him.
Reliable witness.
His name is Baby Shoes.
How bad can he be?
The fragments are in the wrong part
of the brain to cause euphoria,
so let's expand the search.
Factor in the cough
and the cloudy lungs.
Why are we ignoring
the elevated heart rate?
Because he's in shock.
What if the heart was already fast
before he got shot?
You mean after the foot race?
He's giddy.
Indicates a blockage of oxygen.
Carbon monoxide gas would elevate
the heart rate,
cause coughing
and impair neurological functions.
- He got CO poisoning outdoors?
- Yeah.
All 'cause those bastards
didn't ratify Kyoto.
Or he got CO poisoning indoors
and then moved outdoors
before he'd inhaled enough
to make him drop dead.
Test his arterial blood gas.
If his carboxyhemoglobin levels
are higher than 15%,
stick him in a hyperbaric chamber.
You go check the cop car for gas leaks.
If it was the cop car,
his partner would be sick.
Maybe she is, but just doesn't have
as good a sense of humor.
Also, check his personal car,
his work, home.
I'll check the precinct.
The blood test confirmed you have
low-level carbon monoxide poisoning.
We're putting you inside
a high-pressure chamber that...
You don't really care, do you?
Do you live near a gas supply?
Yeah, me. After, like, a huge enchilada.
Anything toxic you have at your home?
Any paint solvents, anything unhygienic?
No. No, I keep a pretty clean home.
If you have trouble breathing,
you can press this button
and the chamber will decompress.
- Like this?
- Not now. If you have trouble.
- It's broken.
- All right.
If you have problems,
we'll push it for you.
Muscle contracture.
- How bad does it hurt?
- Not at all.
Looks wild, though, huh?
Your brain's not getting enough oxygen.
You're losing motor function.
- We should start this right away.
- Should I be scared?
No, you probably have a
carbon monoxide leak in your place.
We have a guy there checking things out.
Sounds okay.
- How about the gas intake valve?
- Looks great.
It's down in the furnace room.
Your system's fine.
If you had a carbon monoxide leak,
half the force would be sick.
Then why are you here?
I was wondering
if you could do me a favor.
Yeah.
I've got a disability.
- These are speeding tickets.
- A lot of emergencies.
He's feeling better now,
but you never know.
I'll see what we can do.
Where does your partner sit?
The place is a cesspool, but I don't
think I need to test for anything.
Nope. Waste of time.
- You know about the marijuana?
- I've heard rumors.
The cop's acting high
because he is high.
- He's got...
- Legionnaires' disease.
It's a good thing Joe got shot
or the whole precinct would have gotten
wiped out. Anarchy on the streets.
It takes 48 hours to test
for Legionnaires'.
But only two seconds to recognize
that the symptoms fit
while staring at the rancid,
unchanged water of an AC unit.
Marijuana explains the high carboxy,
the cloudy lungs and the happiness.
Pot doesn't explain the fact that he's
gotten worse since he was admitted.
Why don't we agree to disagree?
Actually, why don't we agree
that you'll disagree with me
while treating him for Legionnaires'?
It's not as pithy, but...
I feel a lot better.
The meds are working.
Heart rate's normal.
COHb levels are down. No fever.
Take some deep breaths.
You seem disappointed.
I'm glad you're feeling better.
- You got a problem with cops?
- Please don't talk.
In my experience people who just don't
like cops have a reason...
I need you not to talk.
No rales.
These clouded areas
of the upper lobes,
they're the infiltrates we found
yesterday.
- They're not there anymore?
- They're clearing up.
You had Legionnaires'. Now you don't.
So, you didn't find anything
at my place?
Nothing medically relevant.
So there's nothing I need
to worry about, then?
Not this time.
What are you doing?
I want to make sure
he sees what's involved.
What we found was fairly advanced.
These cloudy areas here and here,
these parts of your lungs
simply weren't functioning.
But they're okay now, right?
Everything's okay now.
I'm fine.
You're blind.
I bumped into something.
That doesn't mean I can't see.
- I'm sure this is frightening, but...
- What's Doctor Cameron wearing?
Dark blue pants, white shirt,
black shoes.
Almost,
except for the pants, shirt and shoes.
You're blind.
He really thinks he can see?
He can physically see.
His brain just can't process it.
- No chance this is a practical joke?
- No way.
Anton's blindness indicates
damage to both occipital lobes.
It must be from the trauma.
Bullet fragments just happened
to hit the same spot in both lobes?
A stroke could cause Anton's blindness
and euphoria.
Officer Krupke is clotting in his brain.
Start heparin to thin the blood.
Find the clot and yank it out.
The clot would be at the top
of the bilateral vertebral arteries.
Great. Chase,
stick your fingers in there
and grope around until you find it.
Oh, wait.
When you turn him into a vegetable,
then there's going to be
frivolous lawsuits.
You know what would be better?
Contrast MRI.
Do we have one of those?
You can't do an MRI.
If the bullet fragments are magnetic,
they'll move and rip his brain apart.
Well, let's flip a coin.
Heads MRI, tails he dies.
Police-issue Kevlar vests don't have
the ceramic plate insert
that would shatter a bullet.
They would catch it.
So, the bullet shattered on its own.
Meaning Baby Shoes was using
.38 caliber hollow points,
which unfortunately are ferromagnetic.
It's just so cool that you know that.
We could do an angio
to find the clotting.
Waste of time.
The skull creates too much artifact.
We'll never get a decent view.
- It's the next best thing to an MRI.
- And a waste of time.
- An angio might show...
- Oh, God, it's a coup!
Fine, go do your angio.
When you're done wasting your time,
meet me down in the morgue.
We're going to snake a catheter
into your femoral artery
and up into your brain
so we can check for clots.
Keep this on throughout the procedure,
unless the pot's
already made you sterile.
I have a stressful job. You got no idea.
I grew up with cops like you.
One part bully, nine parts hypocrite.
- What is wrong with you?
- Just having some fun.
- The man is sick and scared.
- The man's a crooked cop.
Maybe you should take yourself
off the case, Foreman.
You don't have to like someone
to be their doctor.
Hey, how you doing there, buddy?
Just sit still
and we'll have you back out there
scaring the crap out of people
in no time.
Happy?
- What did the angio tell us?
- What are you looking for?
I called my mom. She didn't pick up.
What did the angio tell us?
That Foreman should be off this case.
He's a neurologist.
Unless you think the patient's
optic nerve is in his spleen.
He doesn't like cops.
Foreman, policemen are our friends. If
you and I ever get separated shopping...
- I was just busting the guy's chops.
- See?
He was just busting the guy's chops.
Foreman is essential
to solving this case.
Medically, what did the angio tell us?
There appears to be some clotting,
possibly around the circle of Willis.
Based on the progression of symptoms,
the clot is growing.
We need to cut into...
Saying that there appears to be clotting
is like saying
there's a traffic jam ahead.
Is it a ten-car pile up, or just
a really slow bus in the center lane?
And if it is a bus, is it
a thrombotic bus or an embolic bus?
I think I pushed that metaphor too far.
Angio can't tell us
that kind of information.
Oh, so you're saying
it was just a waste of time?
It gave us some information
without killing him.
You don't know that an MRI will
kill him.
The bullets have a ferrous base!
Little tiny pieces trapped in his head.
They're not going anywhere.
Maybe it's worth attempting surgery
to remove the fragments.
Surgeons say inoperable
and the patient's on blood-thinners.
Other than that, perfect plan.
- You got a better plan?
- Much.
The bullet's identical to the one
that Baby Shoes popped Joe with.
Let's see how magnetic it is.
Did anybody hear a...
I shot him. He's dead.
The bullet split into four fragments.
No exit wounds.
I only used a half-load of gunpowder.
It won't be exactly precise comparing
the locations on an X-Ray to an MRI.
How unprofessional was Foreman?
Ask him yourself. He's right here.
Worse than usual.
Better than you.
He berated Joe for being a bad cop.
Berated or humiliated?
I'm not sure.
I didn't have my thesaurus with me.
One implies that he took pleasure in it.
I want to know if it was repressed
black anger or just giddiness.
You think I'm sick?
I think that an appropriate response
to watching your boss shoot a corpse
is not to grin foolishly.
The fact that I've grown bored
by your insanity is proof of nothing.
Doctor Foreman,
Doctor Chase requests your assistance.
I can't even imagine the backwards logic
you used to rationalize
shooting a corpse.
Well, if I'd shot a live person,
there's a lot more paperwork.
Then it won't be a problem for you to
stand beside the casket at the wake
and explain why a cancer patient
has a bullet hole in his head.
The man donated his body to science.
Yes, it's a tragedy.
If I hadn't shot him, his body could
have spent the next year
letting first-year med students
use the carpool lane.
- He's set.
- Do not turn that on, House.
You're mad
because I put a bullet in his head.
At worst, all I'm doing now
is taking it out.
My bad.
They have to shut down the magnet
to fix it.
MRI is going to be out of commission
for at least two weeks.
Oh, it doesn't matter. We obviously
can't use it on this patient.
No, but there are other doctors
in this hospital and other patients.
That helps explains how they can afford
all the fancy equipment.
I'm sure not pulling my weight.
Is doing nothing an option?
I'm just saying, maybe the clot will
break up on its own.
- The giddiness seems to have gone away.
- The blindness hasn't.
- Echo his heart.
- Looking for what?
The problem is obviously neurological.
The clots are in his brain.
The source of the clots may not be.
Do a complete
transthoracic echocardiogram.
Maybe we get lucky. Maybe the clots are
coming from his heart.
- Heart's clean.
- Where else could we look?
We could ultrasound his legs,
look for a DVT.
I need you to move over.
Joe, are you okay?
Tachycardia. Heart rate 150 and rising.
Saline wide open. He's bleeding out.
House wanted to thin his blood.
He sure did a good job.
BP's crashing. He's going into shock.
Intracranial bleeding.
We need to relieve the pressure.
We need a surgical team.
- Foreman, get out!
- Boy, is he screwed.
We clot his blood, he dies.
We thin it, he dies.
Am I the only one who finds this funny?
Oh, man!
I'm not sick!
Did you hear the one about the guy
who bled into his brain
and had to have a hole drilled
in his skull to relieve the pressure?
Hilarious.
Someone laughs, they're dying?
That's absurd.
But not funny.
If I'm not sick, all you're doing
is locking me up with the source.
I'll get sick, prove you right.
If you're not sick, it's not contagious
and you've got nothing to worry about.
If you are sick, the two of you are
staying in here until we find out why.
So you might want to make friends
with the pig.
The good news is
I can finally get my MRI.
No, you can't! You blew up the machine!
Not the portable one, chuckles.
Chase and Cameron are bringing it
to scan your non-bullet-riddled head.
- Where are you going?
- To the office. Got work to do.
Eat your meals, take your temperature
every half-hour
and any meds I command you to take.
- So I'm just a regular patient now?
- No.
You get your own thermometer.
Check your blood.
Anyone with an elevated sed rate gets
to be Foreman's new roomie.
- He should be a part of this.
- He's a patient.
- He's not irrational.
- He's not objective.
He's got the most motivation to get
this diagnosed.
Right. You're not even friends with him.
Why would you care?
There is an area of increased T2
attenuation in the cingulate cortex.
- Kind of mushy.
- Cingulate cortex controls emotions.
This mushy spot explains the euphoria.
Question is, what's causing the mush?
A question you might want
to ask a neurologist.
Foreman is a selfish jerk,
but he's a neurologist
and he's the only one who's been in that
apartment.
This is why he shouldn't be here. You
wouldn't call him a jerk if he was here.
If you think he screwed up at that
apartment you'd keep it to yourself.
- No! I...
- Well, we'll never know.
As long as he's not here,
he's just like any other patient,
which means we can dump on him
all we want.
What's eating the selfish jerk's brain?
West Nile
or Eastern equine encephalitis would...
Test Foreman's blood.
Given that he's the only one who got it,
person-to-person transmission is less
likely than some sort of deadly toxin
that Foreman picked up
in the guy's home.
Who wants to go next?
You're ready to sacrifice yourself for
a guy who doesn't consider you a friend?
He's just a patient, right?
It's the job.
Hey.
You don't have to go anywhere.
Joe's apartment is
right downstairs in the lab.
Foreman brought back
samples of everything.
What was that, "Who wants to go next"?
Some kind of test?
Don't worry. You made the right call.
Foreman stumbled
into whatever it is without knowing.
And he's way smarter than you are.
Ow! Damn, Chase!
- You suck at this.
- Sorry, it's this damned suit.
I can do it myself.
And I'll throw that out.
What'd the MRI show?
I can't be a part of the differential
and I can't even know
what the differential is?
You'd have told any other patient
what you found out.
MRI showed a lesion
on your cingulate cortex.
What's the thinking?
Toxins are in the lead,
viral's a distant second.
Do you think the lesion could be
an abscess?
It's just a small, soft area.
More mush than anything.
Was there inflammation in the lining
of the ventricles?
There was an increased signal there,
yeah.
- What are you thinking?
- Staph infection.
Toxins lead to neurodegeneration
which causes the lesion.
- Not without a fever.
- The cop had a fever.
Mine could be coming.
I could have got it directly from him
or a dirty dishtowel at his place.
Give us Ommaya reservoirs.
Deliver linezolid directly
into our brains, and we're cured.
Samples tested negative for toluene,
arsenic and lead.
What about the blood?
Negative for West Nile
and Eastern equine.
We have to go back to Joe's apartment,
get more samples...
No one goes back to that place
until we know what we're looking for.
Get some of that cop tape,
stick it over the doors and the windows.
I'll take all the HAZMAT precautions.
The chance of infection is
next to nothing.
Yeah, I was never that great at math,
but next to nothing is higher
than nothing, right?
- It's not your fault he got sick.
- But it would be his fault if we did.
We should get a sample directly
from Joe's brain.
We can't do a biopsy.
There's too much edema from the bleeding
because you gave him heparin.
I don't think this is the time to be
pointing fingers.
I didn't give Foreman any.
You want to give Foreman a brain
biopsy?
Come on. Really, who doesn't?
This could be a simple staph infection
causing neurodegeneration.
Without a fever? Not a chance.
- Joe had a fever.
- He also had Legionella.
The mush might be forming an abscess,
and since there was inflammation
of the lining of the ventricles,
it makes sense.
The staph releases toxins,
causes neurodegeneration,
- causes the lesions.
- This is a waste of time.
We should put an Ommaya reservoir
in Foreman's brain
and start administering antibiotics...
If I'm going to be arguing with Foreman,
I may as well do it directly.
Kernig's sign, negative.
Brudzinski's sign, single positive.
Patient Joe Luria,
distal and proximal arm contractures.
Duration four seconds.
Staph infection most commonly presents
on the skin.
Most commonly?
You want to treat me
like any other patient, do it.
But the House I know
never uses phrases like "most commonly."
- You're not laughing anymore.
- No.
You think that's a good thing?
Sort of doubt it.
Staph would be in your heart, lungs,
spleen, liver or kidneys
before it gets to your brain.
Your organs are clear. It's not staph.
The infection could be limited
to a brain abscess.
Which I would have seen in your MRI.
Sign this so that I can take out
a piece of your brain.
Let me see the MRI.
- There was no abscess on the image.
- Let me see it, then.
I liked you better when you were jolly.
MRI was taken over an hour ago.
That soft spot could now be an abscess.
If it was staph you'd have a fever,
which you don't.
101.6.
What idiot gave you that?
Put the Ommaya reservoir in my skull
and treat me for the staph.
Triangle.
This one?
Circle.
Next.
Foreman, why aren't you answering?
Is there a problem?
- Square.
- Tell me your date of birth.
Is that House? Yeah.
- Next?
- Square again. Why is he here?
Because my neurologist is
having surgery.
I thought I was just another patient.
You didn't believe that crap, did you?
Date of birth.
The Ommaya reservoir is inserted
in the parietal lobe.
My spatial recognition is the issue,
not my memory.
Oops. Did you say Ommaya?
I could have sworn you said biopsy.
Hey, I'm just messing with your head.
Mother's maiden name, please.
Get out of my temporal lobe, House.
Hello?
Are you awake?
They told me somebody was sick like me.
I'm up.
Your voice...
Aren't you my doctor?
Not anymore.
You're the guy who doesn't like cops?
Yeah.
Can you see?
- You can't?
- Not a thing.
You've been blind a while.
The fact that you're aware of it now
could be a sign of improvement.
It hurts so much, doesn't it?
I'm okay.
It's going to hurt.
The morphine barely takes the edge off.
I'm going to die, aren't I?
You die, I die.
It's not going to happen.
Why not?
Are you just too stubborn to die?
They took a piece of my brain.
Whatever is wrong with us, they'll find.
Do you believe in prayer?
Not really.
Neither do I.
My dad always prays.
So does mine.
Do you want to try it?
Try praying?
Okay.
- How is he?
- Still dying.
Well, you've almost mastered
another skill, though. That's good.
We have Foreman's biopsy results.
Non-specific signs of inflammation.
That's it?
I also swabbed for staph. Negative.
He's not even a carrier.
Well, at least Foreman was wrong, too.
Yeah, there's that.
- Can I go to Joe's apartment now?
- No.
Go back to the lab and start retesting
all the samples that Foreman collected.
- For what?
- Everything.
Bacteria, toxins, fungus,
anything that likes to feast on brain.
- That's thousands of...
- Better hurry.
Cameron, suit up.
You're going to monitor Foreman.
He's on to hand contractures.
He'll be at Anton's blindness soon.
Run hourly checks,
because when he does go blind
he won't be able to tell us.
We'll use the data to construct a
timeline
so we can see how far behind Joe he is.
Why are you still here?
You're being cautious.
You're being common.
When you don't give a crap...
How many of your guys have caught
cancer from their patients?
Let me know when that happens,
then we can have this conversation.
It's just another case, huh?
I'll bet you can even have unprotected
sex with your cancer patients
without catching a damn thing.
Boy, I wish I had your job.
Biopsy showed nothing.
How can it be nothing?
You cut out a piece of my brain.
It's nothing personal.
We just didn't find anything.
Can you up his morphine, for God's
sake?
He's already maxed out.
20 milligrams per hour.
- What about toxins?
- Everything was negative.
There was a cupboard above the stove.
Did you see it?
I didn't check all the food,
but could be listeriosis.
I didn't go back. Follow right.
Who did?
House said we shouldn't go.
Too dangerous.
The answer's got to be in that
apartment. Not going is too dangerous.
- I'm sorry.
- You're thankful.
If House would've pointed at you instead
of me, you'd be the one in here.
Tell me when you can see the light.
It's your job to go back! You're
a doctor! You go where the disease is!
Say when you can see the light.
I'm dying and you're sitting here
measuring how fast I go?
- Tell me when you can see the light.
- My vision is fine!
- Your left-side periphery is reduced.
- It's fine! I'll prove it!
Ow! Son of a bitch!
Now we're both exposed.
You got two choices.
You can go tell House what just happened
and get your own cot brought in here,
or you can go back to that apartment.
You save me, the cop and yourself.
It's not SSPE.
I checked your past vaccinations against
Joe's. No batch matches.
Did the blood show antibodies
for Coxsackievirus?
Guys, can you please shut him up?
- He's over his limit on morphine.
- Where's Cameron?
She said she had some stuff to do.
Said she'll be back soon.
What are you doing?
Foreman!
Imagine being constantly reminded
of the pain you're about to be in.
I can't take it!
Just stop it! Stop it, stop it, stop it!
Mainlining morphine into his carotid
could stop his heart!
So could pain-induced
stress cardiomyopathy.
Either the morphine kills him
or the pain does.
You're condoning this?
I'm certainly not going in there
to stop him.
I'm going to make you feel better.
Joe has a new symptom.
Hyperalgesia.
The infection's spreading
into the pain center of the brain.
Make it stop! Make it stop!
His brain is telling him
that his whole body is in pain.
Because of the location,
painkillers do nothing.
Suit up. Put the guy in a coma
before the pain kills him.
What if he used cedar wood
to hide the pot smell?
Aureobasidium fungus could grow there.
- Did you find any cedar wood anywhere?
- No, but maybe...
Maybe what?
Maybe somebody could go back,
take a second look?
And why aren't you pissed off
that Cameron's playing hooky
while your life hangs in the balance?
Why doesn't anyone listen to me
anymore?
- I decided you were wrong.
- God, you're weak.
Guy steals your article,
tells you you're not his friend,
and you still want
to risk your life for him.
Foreman broke my skin
with a tainted needle.
- Wow!
- Yeah.
God, you're weak.
The guy tried to kill you.
First thing on my list of things to do
would be to stab him back, shoot him.
I've got a gun in my desk.
The last thing on my list would be
to lie to my boss about it,
and then give the bastard
everything he wanted.
I'm not here for Foreman.
I'm here to save myself.
Even with a needle stick, your chances
of infection are pretty slim.
That's why you're wearing a suit.
You wanted to be here.
He just gave you the excuse.
What does that guy have to do
to make you hate him?
Give me the bag.
- Mildewed dishtowel.
- To re-test for staph.
What is that? Mouse droppings?
Hamster droppings. Could carry Toxocara.
It'd explain the blindness.
Now that I recognize as oven crud.
Could be meat with Trichinella.
It would explain the high fever.
What's with the rye bread?
Mold could be responsible
for ergot poisoning,
which could explain the contractures.
- There are three loaves.
- So?
You're going back in there.
A guy who lives on take-out pizza
does not buy three loaves of rye.
That's looking too far into the future.
Unless he cares about
something a lot more than his diet.
- Are you on the roof yet?
- Yeah, I'm here.
- I don't see any birds.
- Whistle or something.
Do that "come hither" thing.
They came that fast
because it's their behavior pattern.
Joe's been feeding them.
Now look down.
Do you see a river of pigeon turd?
No. There's barely any.
It's not weird, it's cheap.
Joe's a guy who looks for the easy way.
Probably been stealing cable
from his neighbors.
Why not steal fertilizer
from rats with wings?
You see a shovel or a dust pan?
I found a scraper. It looks used.
Sitting on a bucket.
A bucketful of pigeon crap,
the perfect home
for Cryptococcus neoformans.
Yup.
Fungus enters the brain
through the sphenoidal sinus,
where it dances its triple threat
of happiness, blindness
and intractable pain.
Let's hope this experience teaches
our cop a lesson.
Don't cut corners
when you're growing your pot.
See you back home.
I was there.
I should have found it.
Yeah, you could have saved us
a lot of time.
Get me a flush of ampho B
and flucytosine.
I'll start us both.
I was waiting for lab confirmation.
I haven't heard from House yet.
Look at his EEG.
Theta band's been increasing steadily
since we put him under.
The guy's unconscious,
but still in pain.
Theta bands could indicate
at least half-a-dozen different things.
One of which is pain.
The fact that he's no longer screaming
makes us feel better,
not necessarily him.
Chase?
How's Cameron?
She's not giddy.
Fever's down. White count's improving.
Has she said anything to you?
You mean, like, "I completely understand
why Foreman did what he did"
and I hold no grudge?"
What I did, did save my life.
Get in here and help! Forget the suit!
He's tachycardic. Wide complex.
Looks like V-tach.
- It's not Cryptococcus!
- What?
House was wrong.
The samples were negative.
- What is it?
- We don't know.
Give him the amio.
- Do we have any more leads?
- That was our lead.
- Foreman!
- This isn't doing anything.
Foreman, he's in V-fib!
- No good. Hit him again.
- Come on, man. Come on, Joe.
Hit him again!
Give him an amp of epi.
Nothing.
He has multiple system failure.
Foreman!
Foreman.
Time of death?
No!
Time of death...
12:26 p.m.