Hey!
Dr. Sebastian.
Two pallets of antibiotics
for tuberculosis.
We've got six pallets
worth of patients.
Stoia Tucker needs a math lesson.
I'm headed back tomorrow.
Hey! Hey!
Come on, come on. Come on,
kids, let the truck through.
Move those boxes quick, quick. Let's move!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Let's go! Let's go, man! Hurry!
I've got some very special medicine here.
It's from Hershey, Pennsylvania.
One per person. One per person.
Let's calm down, kids.
Wait, wait.
Help! Help! Dr. Sebastian!
Come quickly!
My son, he fell. He fell on this log.
We were just waiting for his friends.
I got no breath sounds
on the left. Give me that.
Yeah, he's gonna be okay.
The fall didn't cause
him to drop a lung.
The lung caused him to fall.
TB chewed it up.
He'll be lucky
to live another year.
This is Sarni. I picked up the
tab for the back brace myself.
The funny thing is,
is that the brace cost more
than the medicine
that would have prevented her
from needing it.
It's your medicine.
All of the antibiotics
that we need are right here
in your warehouses,
in your factories.
- We provide over 10,000 doses a year.
- Which is not enough.
You know we'd love to do more,
but our hands are tied.
New car, Jerry?
I saw it on the way in, looks beautiful.
Don't make this personal.
All the way from Germany, too. I
know that's a lot of red tape.
I'm not like you. I'm not
ashamed of making a living.
And I know you didn't become
a chem major for the money.
Now, you want the same things
that I want. You just...
You have to... You just
have to push a little...
You have to push
a little bit harder...
- Harder for it.
- Sebastian?
Call 911.
Is he okay?
Isn't someone here a doctor?
Selling subscriptions? I heard
20 and you get a new bike.
Dr. Sebastian Charles collapsed during
a presentation at Stoia Tucker.
Really? Crushed under the weight
of his own ego?
Wow!
Is there nobody you admire?
Well, there is this gal I met in Nam who
could blow out a candle without using...
He thinks it's TB.
Good thing he's not the syphilis expert.
- He wants a second opinion.
- Second to his own. Okay.
- It's not TB.
- What is it?
Oh, you want specifics?
Lemma, big Knicks fan.
You've never had an episode
like this before?
No. He died last month.
Stupidly tried to share
his meds with his cousin,
and they only had
enough for one.
Dr. House,
I'm Sebastian Charles.
Patients aren't usually
part of the diagnostic process.
Well, I'm a doctor.
Listen, I know you guys
don't make a lot of money...
I wrote your people a check last month.
Oh, well. Write us another one.
- Talk to Chase. He's rich.
- My dad, not me.
Every minute
four people die of TB.
Wow!
How can you sleep at night?
There's people dying in Africa
of a disease that we cured over...
Yeah, I know.
I saw the concert.
Seriously. Let's see, you sleep six
hours. That means every night you kill
1,440 people.
I guess you got to get
some sleep, but come on.
If you'd stayed up another 10 minutes,
you could have saved 40 lives.
Do you send notes to the
families in the morning?
That's gonna take
at least 10 minutes.
So that's another
40 dead, another 40 notes.
Why don't you go wrack yourself
with guilt in your own room?
No, thanks. I'll stay.
I'd like to hear the differential.
Dr. Cameron, tell the doctor why it's not
a good idea for the patient to be here.
He's an immunologist
and a TB expert.
That'll be very useful
if we need somebody to say the words,
"I think it's TB".
What is that?
Oh, that. I'm sorry,
that's my body powder.
It's the only thing I've found
that works in the Sahara.
I'm kind of used to it.
I don't even notice it.
Who thinks it smells like
an elephant-dung smoothie?
It smells okay to me.
That is exactly why the patient
shouldn't be in the room.
If you can't tell a man
that his cologne makes you want to puke,
how are you gonna tell him
that he's an idiot?
He's not an idiot.
Sure, you say that now,
while he's in the room.
Look, I don't have time for this.
It's TB.
Nope.
The symptoms are too varied.
Well, if you haven't seen 10,000 cases,
I agree that's what you'd think.
I told you he's an idiot.
- You said you wanted a second opinion.
- No, actually,
my backers
wanted a second opinion.
Yeah, doesn't look good if you drop dead
while wearing your shoe sponsor's logo.
It's TB and I'm not dying. I'm
gonna want you to plant a PPD
and induce a sputum
to confirm the TB.
Imaging studies will
determine the progress,
and I think we should probably
take a CT scan of my lungs
- just so that nobody second guesses us.
- Wouldn't want that.
Hello? No,
I'm feeling much better.
Well, what you can do is,
you can get your board to approve
the increased
med shipments that... Sorry.
No, don't, don't, don't try.
No, don't do your best.
Just get it done, okay?
That's Stoia Tucker, and they're
the nice pharmaceutical company.
I'm sorry,
but it's against hospital regs.
Oh, I need the phone.
Why don't we focus on getting
you better right now?
- What'll you do, throw me out?
- No, just the phone.
Sorry. We've got an emergency.
Got to go.
- There's a phone in your room.
- Yeah, I figured that there would be.
Right. I just thought...
It's not like the hospitals
you may be used to in Africa.
I don't know what the
facilities were like, so...
Thank you.
You're welcome.
And thanks for that check.
I should go.
The nameless poor have a face,
and it's a pompous white man.
Yeah, what a jerk, saving
all those lives like that.
What's the emergency?
I can't remember
how to do "walk the dog".
The guy's sick, maybe dying.
And you've forgotten all about
doing a differential diagnosis.
- You just sent us off to test him...
- Well, I had to get him out of there.
Now we can all sit around
and call him an idiot.
- Who wants to go first?
- He's right.
Tuberculosis could present
hundreds of different ways.
Well, by that logic, everyone in
the hospital should be treated.
Not everybody in the hospital has been
exposed to it for the last 20 years.
TB takes years to kill you.
Two weeks ago,
he was perfectly healthy.
Now he's got a whiteboard
full of symptoms.
What about something metabolic?
Welcome aboard
the Good Ship Ass-Kisser.
Nice day for a sail.
Pucker up, me hearties.
It's not metabolic. Kidney, liver and
thyroid are all normal. No diabetes.
- What about his heart?
- Obviously big as all outdoors.
Abnormal heart rhythm. Wave
forms show PR variability.
It's subtle, but it's there.
You think it's his heart?
Sick sinus syndrome?
Loose throttle. Sometimes beats
too fast, sometimes too slow.
- Causing him to pass out.
- It would account for the episode.
I'll put him on telemetry, do a
stress test and an echocardiogram.
Treat him like every
other hospital patient.
I want to see that pious, body-powdered
tush hanging out of his gown.
Could you give me a hand
with this thing?
I don't recall asking for a
stress test or an echocardiogram.
What are you gonna do,
walk out?
Corporate sponsors
aren't gonna like that.
I need your forearm.
What's House thinking?
Sick sinus syndrome.
Well, that's a lot
more serious than TB.
Is that a PPD?
If it changes color
in the next 48 hours...
Yeah, if House doesn't think it's TB,
why would he have you test for that?
Just covering
all his bases, I guess.
Uh-huh.
He doesn't seem
like a guy who does that.
We have you scheduled for a 10:30 echo.
Good for you.
Every minute that we refuse
to love one another,
another puppy
cries another tear.
You're just mad because he's closer
to a Nobel Prize than you are.
And yet I've nailed more Swedish babes.
Crazy, crazy world.
It's not just a trip
to Stockholm, you know.
It comes with a cash prize.
Seriously?
No wonder everybody's
going after that peace thing.
He cures thousands
of people every year.
You cure what, 30?
McDonald's makes a better hamburger than
your mother because they make more?
Oh, I see.
So you hate him because the lives he saves
aren't as good as the lives you save?
Yeah, that's the reason.
Nobel invented dynamite. I
won't accept his blood money.
The top of my head's
killing me.
We spent a week doing
"top of head" in anatomy.
I know just where it is.
- That is not the top of my head.
- Close enough for clinic.
Your sinuses are clogged.
Judging by the scratches on your
hands, I'm guessing a new cat.
It was my mother's. She's dead.
You keep a dead cat?
No. My mother's dead.
Poor cat. You're allergic.
We can control it
with antihistamine.
- One pill a day.
- Pills?
You don't like to swallow.
Not surprised.
Forget the pills.
We'll give you a nasal spray.
Steroids?
Is there something else
you can give me?
Well, if you live
by the river, I've got a bag.
Hey. Stress test was normal.
- But his EKG was not normal.
- Echo's normal.
Two for you, one for me.
We need a tiebreaker.
Echo and stress tests are more reliable.
Tilt table tests.
That never works.
I'll bet you
a week's clinic duty it does.
You're on.
You like this guy?
You always tell us our opinion
of the patient's irrelevant.
Medically, it's irrelevant.
It says something about you.
You figure anybody who gives a crap about
people in Africa must be full of it?
Yes.
There's an evolutionary imperative why we
give a crap about our family and friends.
And there's an evolutionary imperative why
we don't give a crap about anybody else.
If we loved all people indiscriminately,
we couldn't function.
So the great humanitarian's
as selfish as the rest of us?
Just not as honest about it.
Well, you also always tell us
motives are irrelevant.
Dr. Charles, your heart's handling the
changes in orientation just fine.
No pauses on your EKG.
And House drives in for
the lay-up and no, rejected!
- What does this knobby thing do?
- I'm within protocol range.
You're not gonna
get a different result.
The way I figure it is, this
could show you problems at six,
imagine what it'll tell you
if you crank it to 10.
- House, is that you?
- Does it go to 11?
Would you stop? You lost. I'm scheduled
for clinic duty Thursday and Friday.
All right, I'm beginning
to feel nauseous.
Would you turn the damn thing
off before you break it?
Okay, I'm getting dizzy.
I can't see
and I'm gonna pass out.
- I win.
- At those speeds, astronauts throw up.
I'm not talking
about the nausea.
- The test revealed the problem.
- Yeah? House is insane?
- What he just did...
- Abusive and unprofessional.
If he hadn't done it, we
wouldn't have seen the problem.
You've got
an abnormal PR interval.
It could be dangerous, possibly fatal,
particularly if you're in Africa
away from advanced medicine.
I'm gonna need a pacemaker?
You're scheduled
for surgery this afternoon.
We'll be able to maintain
your pacemaker from anywhere.
You just need to get yourself to
a phone line every few months.
Better yet, you could join me
at one of my clinics.
- I'm kind of spoiled.
- Well, we'll get you a hut with a view.
- Do you like sand?
- I meant medically.
- No PET scans, no MRis...
- This is ridiculous.
- Dr. Charles...
- I know. I know. Hospital regulations.
Darling, have a seat. Come on.
You're smart. You'll adapt.
- We're going up or down?
- Basement.
All right.
You might even find that without
the technological crutches,
you become
a better diagnostician.
My heart
can handle this, right?
So far, just carnival rides
have set you off.
When you meet these people,
it changes you.
We should
talk about it over dinner.
Are you asking me
to Africa or on a date?
I can ask you halfway around the world, I
can't ask you to a restaurant a block away?
- Well, one's a job, and the other's...
- Yeah, hospital regs.
You can't date patients, right? I wouldn't
wanna risk your precious objectivity.
You haven't answered
either question, by the way.
You don't think
objectivity's important?
I think doctors like House
cling to objectivity
like a three-year-old to a blanket.
Don't get too worked up.
Stay calm. Stay cool and maintain
the correct perspective.
The only flaw in their argument is that
when you have millions of people dying,
the correct perspective is to be
yelling at the top of your lungs.
- Sorry. My head is killing me.
- Here, sit on the step.
So, are you gonna go out
with me or not?
Your heart rate's normal.
Yeah, of course it is.
It's one flight of stairs.
I'm gonna be fine.
Hand's a little...
Call a code,
second floor stairwell!
- You were wrong.
- Hey, I have feelings.
I'm trying my best.
Isn't that enough for you?
- The abnormal EKG was real.
- It's not sick sinus syndrome.
Thank God we found out before
we put the pacemaker in.
And thank God you dragged him into a
stairwell to get his heart racing.
We were taking the stairs. They
keep them in the stairwell.
The guy's a selfish jerk.
Why would you...
Why would you say he's selfish?
Because he's been talking to Foreman.
No, I haven't.
I'm just giving my opinion.
This kind of altruism
doesn't just naturally...
Excellent briefing.
Hey, the guy's still sick.
Can we talk about that?
Now, headaches point to
a neurological problem.
Acoustic neuroma.
A brain tumor causes dizziness,
loss of consciousness,
messes with breathing
patterns, heart rhythms...
Get an MRI.
Hello?
Oh, I'm sorry. I'll be right down.
No problem.
I'll do an extra hour
to make up.
I'm late for my clinic duty.
Here, go be me
for a couple of hours.
Explosive diarrhea, fever,
it's probably the flu.
Wow. You're good.
You a Harvard boy?
- You're not Hill, Oliver.
- No.
Carter, Cecelia.
They put you in the wrong room, Cecelia.
- Mrs. Carter.
- Sorry.
I'll just be
a few more minutes.
Don't take these in order,
everything falls apart.
I have cancer.
I felt a lump.
- I'll go get a nurse.
- Yeah, see you in an hour or two.
Lie flat.
Lift your left arm up
and under your head.
- Right there?
- Yeah.
I felt it this morning.
Oh, my cousin
had the same thing.
It's nothing.
We should check it again
on your next cycle,
but you really don't have
anything to worry about.
That's what they told Donna.
- She was dead in six months.
- Listen, the edges are smooth.
It has mobility. It has all
the earmarks of a benign...
Why should I believe you?
Because you're trying
to rush me out of here?
The risks of a false positive
on a biopsy outweigh...
Either you do the biopsy,
or I talk to your superior.
Which is it, Dr. House?
- I'll arrange the biopsy.
- Thanks.
- He asked me out.
- I'm shocked.
I'm shocked when patients
don't ask you out.
He also asked me
to come to Africa.
Boy, he moves fast.
I think the two questions
had two different objectives.
Do you like him?
Good-looking single guy,
genius doctor,
- cares about the world.
- I take it you said no.
- You think I'm that hung up on rules?
- He's not House.
There's nothing there.
Yeah, there is.
Did I ask you to plant a PPD?
It was positive. He's got TB!
Well, of course he's got TB. The guy's
been in the jungle for 20 years.
If he tested positive for pinkeye, would
you think that was his big problem?
I did a test. It was positive.
Why is that a problem?
Because now he's got
the big red target on his arm,
the stubborn jerk thinks he's right.
He won't let us do any more tests.
Well, maybe he's not
the only stubborn jerk.
I did an LP, too. Low glucose, and
he has an increased sed rate.
- Everything screams tuberculosis!
- Not everything!
If any of the symptoms are caused by the
TB, it would throw off our diagnosis.
You're right.
We gotta treat the TB.
Who knows?
Maybe he'll just get better.
You'd like that, wouldn't you?
So, it's TB, but not TB?
- I'm complicated.
- The guy does know tuberculosis.
- If he says it can manifest...
- The guy's not even a real doctor.
- He's a human telethon.
- Is that your problem with him?
You see hypocrites every day.
Why is this guy so special?
You think I have a hypocritical
attitude to hypocrisy?
The problem is, there are 26 letters in the
alphabet and he only uses two of them.
He treats thousands of
patients with one diagnosis.
He knows the answer
going in. It's cheating.
So it's all because he's one
of them useless specialists?
Oh, did I hurt the big-time
oncologist's itty-bitty feelings?
You're a big help to patients
who actually have cancer.
- Other times you're just annoying.
- You've outdone yourself.
I'll say. My salad's covering
a free T-bone steak.
Cecelia Carter, remember her?
Last week they said it was
mystery stew. They owe me.
She was just in my office crying
because of the way you treated her.
That doesn't sound like you.
Then it probably wasn't.
I get that you like
to shock people,
stun them out of complacency,
out of stupidity.
But this woman thought
she had cancer.
She had a lump in her breast. What
were you trying to accomplish?
Let me ask you something.
If this were another doctor,
if the patient were complaining about,
let's say, I don't know, Foreman,
you'd just dismiss this as the paranoid
bitching of another paranoid bitch.
- And file it under "P" for...
- Paranoid?
Am not.
- You're right.
- Good.
Apologize to her before the
end of business today.
- What did you do to Ceci?
- I have no idea.
Just the salad today.
Big breakfast.
Hey.
Levofloxacin?
You have
a resistant strain of TB.
Wow, you just
walk right in with these.
That's what we doctors do.
We write down the name of some
medicine, and someone gives it to us.
You know, there's parts of the world where
you get knifed walking around with this.
I mean, the regular stuff
is bad enough,
but the treatment
for the resistant strain?
They get $6 a tablet for that.
And I take it for two years.
Streptomycin.
Now, that's two grand.
Ten grand, cure one person.
I had a patient in Djani once.
It was a mother,
had three little boys.
She had resistant TB.
She couldn't afford these.
She couldn't afford bread.
We gave her
the regular stuff, but
- no surprise, she died.
- Sorry.
I'm not taking these pills.
Because she couldn't get them,
you're not gonna take them?
- That's insane.
- Why?
- 'Cause I'm better than her?
- Because letting her die was wrong,
but letting you die
is just as wrong.
Maybe I won't die.
Maybe somebody will pay a little
more attention to my story.
He figures
the pharmaceutical companies
need something big
to force them into action.
This'll get a lot more media play
than 1,000 African villagers dying.
So, he won't take the pills.
- Newsweek's calling you.
- And he won't agree to any more tests.
He has his diagnosis.
See what happens
when you don't listen to me?
Maybe millions
of lives get saved.
Yeah. That's my point.
Increased heart rate,
night sweats,
loss of consciousness. Besides rough
sex, what do they all have in common?
- T...
- It's not TB!
His autonomic nervous system?
- We know that it's not a brain tumor.
- What else could be eating his nerves?
Fabry's. Autonomic
dysregulation syndrome.
Shy-Drager syndrome. It doesn't matter.
He won't let us test him.
In my opinion, Dr. Sebastian
Charles is an idiot.
Yeah, you can quote me.
C-U-D-D-Y.
Sebastian is refusing
life-saving treatment.
He's refusing TB treatment.
You don't think he has TB.
- Ergo, you should care less.
- He won't let me test him.
And what do you want me to do about it?
Hold him down.
Have you apologized
to Cecelia Carter yet?
Trust me, she doesn't
wanna hear from me.
Look, the guy
is killing himself!
Am I the only one who realizes
this is a bad thing?
If he was a Christian Scientist refusing
meds, we'd have 18 attorneys...
You're putting on makeup.
That's not a good sign
for my side, is it?
Sebastian has called
a press conference for 3:00.
He's asked me to be there to confirm
the diagnosis and the prognosis.
You are as big
a media whore as he is.
Of course I am. It couldn't possibly
be that I think he's right,
and that I'd like to be a small
part of what he's doing.
Oh, whores can like the sex.
Doesn't mean they're not whores.
And with that eye shadow, I
am totally screwed, aren't I?
Totally.
How you feeling? A little weak.
You're having a good day.
The symptoms will quickly focus
more and more on your lungs.
You'll find it difficult to talk
and eventually breathe at all.
I think I know what I'll have
to look forward to.
I know.
I just came to ask if you'd be
willing to accept any treatment.
No, if you're trying to scare me into...
No. Palliative treatment.
Narcotics.
Fentanyl patch, morphine drip,
whatever it takes.
We can make your last days
fairly comfortable.
And if you have another
good day, maybe dinner.
Thank you.
You want Third World treatment?
You got it.
- Boy, is it hot here in Djani.
- What are you doing?
What am I doing?
Putting everything
on the floor of the hut.
What's the magic box
with the moving pictures?
- You think he's a hypocrite?
- Hypocrite? No.
Everybody in Africa's got cell
phones and running water.
This thing just will not flush.
Do you really think that if you come
in here and make it a little hot,
make it smell a little,
that I'm just gonna fold and abandon
everything that matters to me?
Lousy sanitation
over there, too.
You are not the same as them.
Your life is not the same.
And you're cheapening everything they're
going through by pretending you are.
I am the same. I'm not special.
You can't demand to be treated
like any Third World sick person
- and call a press conference!
- They treat me special!
That doesn't mean I am.
And what kind of selfish jerk
wouldn't take advantage of that fact?
It's all preventable.
Stoia Tucker makes medications
right here in New Jersey.
They have warehouses full of the stuff.
There's more than enough to go around.
So if I can get them,
why can't Lemma?
Why can't Quesmo?
And why can't Sarni?
Another person just died.
Where is your outrage?
No, I have no intention
of martyring myself.
I'm just putting myself...
Sure, they're dying,
but it's got a great beat.
Must be hot as hell under those lights.
- Yep.
- Hey, why the page?
- He okay?
- He's in a coma.
I need you to
apologize to Ceci, Cecily.
- Mrs. Carter? For what?
- For whatever I did.
- You didn't do anything.
- That has been my position all along.
His chestx-rays are negative, so
he's not contagious at this point.
His condition
is currently stable.
Do you ever notice how all the
self-sacrificing women in history,
Joan of Arc, Mother Teresa,
can't think of any others,
they all die alone.
The men, on the other hand,
get so much fuzz it's crazy.
It's an unfair world.
House, she was scared and unreasonable.
Insulting a woman
with breast cancer,
that's a move best left to the pros.
Frankly, you don't have the chops.
I didn't insult her! I did the
unnecessary biopsy like she wanted.
It was negative
like I knew it would be.
What'd you do, call them perky?
You are years away
from mad skills like that.
I need you to apologize.
Cuddy's only doing this
because she thinks it's you.
Welcome to the world.
Everyone's different, everyone
gets treated different.
And you try fighting that,
you wind up dying of TB.
What are you doing?
Testing the patient's
autonomic nervous system.
Of course.
His internal heating
and ventilation should be off.
He shouldn't be able to sweat.
That's why he's got
that awful body powder.
Take it away, crank up the heat,
stick him under the lights,
he can't cool himself. He
should be turning bright red.
The picture's fine.
Yeah.
I'm asking Stoia Tucker
to save these lives,
millions of lives,
including my own.
Dr. House, I would appreciate
it if you left us...
Get that out of my face.
What are you
trying to prove, House?
Dr. House, I would appreciate it
if you left the room while...
He's sweating like a pig.
It's 100 degrees in here, House,
because you turned up the thermostat.
Did they hear me?
The media, did they listen?
- He's disoriented.
- They have to hear me.
- His arteries are clamping down.
- I want everybody out of here now!
Get the crash cart.
He's having a cardiac arrest.
- Get it set up.
- All right.
Get them out!
Everyone. I want
everyone out of here now!
Clear.
Come on, Sebastian.
I've got sinus rhythm.
That is not TB.
Compelling television.
- Do whatever tests you want.
- I want to treat you for TB.
Dr. Cameron found low sugar
in your cerebrospinal fluid.
- It's a classic finding of TB.
- Oh, now you think TB's the problem?
No.
If TB caused
cardiac arrest on a hot day,
your work in Africa would be even
more futile than it already is.
Can you get
to your point, please?
That whiteboard in my office, we're
up to about a dozen symptoms now.
Cardiac arrest, clearly not TB.
CSF sugar clearly is TB.
The rest of them
could go either way.
Unless we know which ones are
which, I can't diagnose you.
I'll take any other tests or treatments
you might want to prescribe.
So you're not special,
but TB is.
People die of TB because we let them.
It's our choice.
People die of malaria because we let them.
They die of dysentery. They...
- No, TB's my disease.
- You own a disease?
Well, I'm sorry I missed
the IPO on dengue fever.
Look, I know I have a way about me, and
I know I piss a lot of people off.
And a whole lot more
I just annoy.
But you're the first person
that I've ever met
who I think is actually
annoyed by what I do.
Do you think I'm not saving any
lives, or is that a bad thing?
Right now, I'm just trying
to save your life.
Or do you just have
a problem with hope?
You know, the difference between
our jobs is not numbers or styles.
It's that I know I'm gonna fail.
Even if I save a million people,
there's gonna be another million.
You couldn't handle that.
I think you resent
anyone who can.
Can't we just agree that
you're incredibly annoying?
Take the pills,
or I'll let you die,
do an autopsy,
call my own press conference
and make sure the world knows
that you didn't die of TB.
Corporate sponsors will be disappointed,
but they'll find another disease.
Why would you do that?
Because I'm just a mean
son of a bitch.
So, we still have to explain PR
variability, syncope, headaches
and
low sugar?
- That was classic TB.
- Apparently not.
- You rerun the test?
- Yeah.
- This is good.
- Good? This is bizarre.
"Bizarre" is good.
"Common" has hundreds of explanations.
"Bizarre" has hardly any.
What else could cause
low CSF sugar?
I get to ask the questions.
I've found you look a lot smarter asking
questions than dumbly not answering them.
- High insulin levels in his blood.
- They'd have to be very high.
Okay, very high
insulin levels in his blood.
How could he get
high insulin levels?
We've checked daily blood
sugars, all normal.
See how smart she looks?
'Cause she asked the question.
And it's not glucagonoma
because he has no rash.
It's not self-induced
because he's not an idiot.
And it's not a tumor because the
CT and the MRI were both negative.
Which just leaves tumor.
Why do you do this? Why do you ignore
what I say like I'm not even...
Small tumor.
Really, really tiny.
So small we can't see it.
Nesidioblastoma.
An abnormal growth of the
insulin-secreting cells in his pancreas?
That only intermittently
secrets insulin...
In response to stress,
like if, I don't
know, if someone
accidentally puts the
mechanical bull on 11.
Easily removed by surgery.
Except if it's so small
we can't see it,
how are we even gonna
prove it's there?
She asked, looking clever.
Just start hacking away at his
pancreas until he gets better?
How do you prove something
exists when you can't see it?
Does God exist?
Does the wind blow?
- We know because the leaves move.
- Look for effects.
You should look the other way.
- There's Cuddy with your patient.
- Dr. House!
Dr. House has an emergency.
- We can't avoid her forever.
- Eventually she'll die.
You sure she doesn't
have breast cancer?
We think you have a tumor.
Easily removed surgically. We're
gonna poke it with a stick.
- And if there's no tumor?
- Nothing happens.
Splenic artery, it's a
hard left off the celiac.
If there is a tumor?
What usually happens when you
poke something with a stick?
Pokes back.
He's stuck in the
superior mesenteric.
I knew we should have
stopped for directions. Men!
I'm there.
We're gonna inject calcium
into your pancreas.
The beta cells
will release insulin.
If there are too many beta
cells because of a tumor,
your blood sugar
will drop precipitously.
How do we know
it won't go too low?
Fingers and toes crossed.
Go ahead.
Glucose is holding
steady at 75.
- No leaves rustling. Blow harder.
- I already gave him one amp.
Well, I guess now would be the time
to give him more than one amp.
Fifty. It's starting to drop.
- Forty-five.
- I think my arm's shaking.
I'm gonna start him on a glucose drip.
He's gonna seize.
Not yet.
- It's continuing to drop.
- Not fast enough.
- He's seizing.
- We've got to reverse this.
He's at 40, 38, 35.
Push an amp of D50.
You want to kill the guy?
We're back to 40.
Congratulations.
You have a tumor.
Are you gonna go out with him?
- Is that any of your business?
- Nope.
I don't think so.
Two days ago, you were holding his hand.
What's changed?
He practically lives in Africa.
There's no future.
On the other hand, maybe there's
too much of a future now.
You weren't attracted to him because
he was prepared to die for a cause.
You were attracted to him because
he was actually doing it.
- Right. It's that simple.
- That was simple?
I put a label on him and go from there.
Everybody does it.
We are who people think we are.
People think he's a great
doctor, so they give him stuff.
- He is a great doctor.
- The reality is irrelevant.
I'll prove it.
People who know me see me as
an ass, treat me as an ass.
People who don't know me see a
cripple, treat me like a cripple.
What sort of selfish jerk wouldn't
take advantage of that fact?
Oh, my goodness. Are you okay?
Yeah. I am so sorry.
It was completely my fault.
It's nothing. I'm fine.
Well, I'm very relieved.
I feel terrible.
- Please don't worry about it. I'm fine.
- You sure?
Okay.
How's everything?
I'm gonna go.
My foot's killing me.
- What did you do to...
- It was nothing. It was all my fault.
Yeah, listen.
Bogale, relax, okay?
I'm gonna be back on Tuesday.
Tell Sarni I'm gonna bring her
a new brace. All right.
- Just in case.
- You get them?
Six-months' supply.
Should fix you right up.
I'll see you when you
come back for a refill?
Yeah, I'll see you
in two months.
You gonna give them away?
Well, you know how these things happen.
You leave a bag on the airplane,
you drop some pills
down the drain.
I have an idea. You could bring
me the refill in Africa.
I don't think so.
You actually like working for House?
You find this satisfying?
There he is.
- It's good to see you. Dr. Sebastian.
- Thank you.
Thank you. I appreciate that.
I appreciate the support.
It's not about the kids
dying every eight seconds.
It's about the media stroking,
adulation, the pats on the head.
That's your problem
with him, isn't it?
Look at him.
Loves it, eats it up.
Yeah, the man actually
enjoys what he does.
Listen, I saved his life.
That means I get credit for every
life he saves from here on out.
I'll make sure Stockholm knows.