[upbeat music playing]
What made you wanna be a rabbi,
like, in the first place?
The goal was to be in the NBA,
but, you know, that's all political.
[Joanne laughs]
Come on, I'm serious.
You know... [chuckles]
It's funny. I get a little self-conscious
telling you this.
When I was little,
I was a pretty nervous kid.
Bit of a scaredy-cat, if you will.
And the world seemed like a very chaotic
and... and unsafe place to me.
And when I started paying attention
to the lessons in the Torah
and, uh, was exposed to the rituals
and the traditions,
it allowed me to view the world
as a much safer and more meaningful place.
And I knew from a very young age
I wanted to spend my life
trying to help keep it alive.
That's a great answer.
It was either that
or all my mom's influence.
Anyways, excited to meet her?
I'm excited to meet both your parents.
Good. They're really important to me.
I want it to go well.
Now you're making me nervous.
Don't be nervous.
Is it true what they say
about Jewish boys and their moms?
I mean, we're pretty close.
You don't still
kiss your mom on the lips, do you?
No. I mean, that's gross.
[upbeat music playing]
I was fine. Not nervous at all.
And then Noah freaked me out.
That's trash. That is trash.
These are trash.
- Mm. Trash.
- Yep.
- Trash.
- Okay.
Tra... No, Mom. This is a jury summons.
You have to respond to this.
Oh, I can't.
I always side with the accused.
And don't worry, sweetheart.
You know,
I loved meeting your father's parents.
It was easy-peasy.
Because they were both dead already.
Well, that's lucky.
I just... I don't wanna screw it up.
I like Noah so much,
and it's a really important step
to meet his parents.
And I don't know if we can be together
if they don't approve.
Did you know he asked me
if I'd consider converting?
To Judaism?
For my religion.
Oh, that's fun. Is it? I don't know.
I don't know either. I don't even know
if I believe in organized religion.
Oh, preach.
[sighs]
Once again, you haven't given me
any advice I can use, so I'm gonna go.
- Well, no, no. Oh, no.
- [Joanne] I love you.
- Bye.
- No, you can't go. You can't go.
Why not? She's got a life to live.
Oh, no! Come on. Hey! No, stay.
Let's talk some more about religion.
- Help me. I asked you to stay focused.
- Remember...
Is that her fucking car parked outside?
You guys are unreal, okay?
- Like, seriously?
- I had to.
I feel awful when you two fight.
I mean, I can feel
my uterus ripping in two.
- What?
- Morgan is dead to me.
Oh, okay.
I don't know if I'm gonna be able
to record the podcast with her,
knowing that our listeners
won't be able to trust
a word that comes out of her mouth.
What makes you think
I wanna do the podcast
when every story you tell
puts our audience to sleep?
Okay? It's like, nobody cares which
aluminum-free deodorant you like the most.
- I'm sorry, was that a diss...
- [Morgan] Yeah.
...or just another lie?
I can never tell with you.
You know that I'm not a liar, right?
- Oh, of course, honey.
- Thank you.
But you have always been
a bit of a storyteller.
[chuckles] Remember back in fifth grade
when you told everyone
that I was in Wham!?
- I do.
- Oh, I loved that one.
I am just trying to help you,
but you refuse to accept the fact
that Noah lied to you, okay?
- The truth is going to come out.
- Get your finger out of my face.
I'll put it wherever I want.
Deal with that.
Okay, I can't stay here anymore.
I have a date tonight anyway
with one of the guys that I met
on the "desperate dating" apps.
And he happens to be
a hot, professional baseball player
for the Pittsburgh
team.
I dated a baseball player once.
Most erotic time of my life.
Wow, thanks a lot.
[Joanne] I honestly cannot believe
you did that.
[phone ringing]
[phone chimes]
Hey, what's up?
[Morgan] Hey, I need to...
Why are you hiding in the bathroom?
Oh, I get it. You don't want
your wife to hear us talking.
What? No. All right, yeah.
So I just haven't told Esther
that we're friends yet.
Why are you calling me?
Okay, so, um, what's the deal
with Noah and Rebecca?
- Are they talking again?
- What do you mean?
If I tell you something,
I need you to swear
you're never gonna repeat it to anyone.
- Not Noah, not Esther, like, nobody.
- [Sasha] 100%.
I just need to let you know I've never
successfully kept a secret before.
Keep that in mind before you tell me.
Okay. Okay.
Well, so I ran into Rebecca last week.
Oh, okay, that is juicy.
Yes. I talked to her.
Well, Julie talked to her.
Okay, who's Julie?
[Morgan] I'm Julie,
but Rebecca didn't know that.
She basically told me
her and Noah are getting back together.
What? No way. No. Noah would have told me.
He tells me everything.
I'm like his rabbi.
[sighs]
Although, what if
he's hiding that from me?
God, that's a hard pill.
I don't know, but get to the bottom of it.
- Let me know what you find out.
- [car beeps]
And don't mention my name.
Okay. All right.
I will, but you can't mention my name.
Sorry, why would I mention your name?
I don't know. You said it,
and it felt like I should say it back.
Okay, bye. Thanks, weirdo.
Bye, talk later.
[phone chimes]
[toilet flushes]
[buoyant music playing]
What's that?
A gift I thought you could give my mom.
- Noah. No.
- Well?
- Wanna tell me what's in the box?
- Absolutely not.
Please let me do my thing, okay?
I'm an excellent gift-giver.
- Okay.
- Trust.
[doorbell chimes]
You ring the doorbell at your own house?
You don't just walk right in?
Without announcing ourselves? Are you...
- What's...
- Sorry.
Okay, deep breath. I got ya.
Ah! Welcome.
- Hey, hi.
- Hi. Hi.
- Hello.
- [Noah] Hey.
[Noah's mom] Here's my baby.
- Oh, hello. Hi.
- Here's my baby.
[both] Mwah!
[Noah] Hi.
- You feel too thin.
- Good? No, swole.
And you must be the famous Joanne.
Ah, guilty. I'm happy to sign an autograph
if you'd like, Mr. Roklov.
- [chuckles] Please, call me Ilan.
- [Joanne] Thank you.
Mom, this is Joanne.
Joanne, this is my mother, Bina.
It's a pleasure to meet you, Bina.
Please, call me Mrs. Roklov.
- Okay. Um, I brought you a gift.
- Yeah.
Oh, thank you. How nice. Heavy.
- [Noah] It is.
- Is it food?
- It is.
- Come on in.
- Should we take it to the kitchen?
- I love to eat.
- Yeah.
- We all love to eat.
Well, I hope you like it.
I... I was very excited about it.
It's, um, spoiler alert,
a custom-made charcuterie board
that I had designed for this occasion.
[Bina] It'll be perfect for lunch.
Oh. Oh! Uh... [clears throat] Is this pork?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no. That's prosciutto.
- Uh-huh.
- Prosciutto is pork.
What?
Come on.
I thought prosciutto
was fancy Italian beef.
- [Ilan] I wish.
- Vera, dear.
Uh, please throw this in the trash.
Oh, hold on, Vera.
Uh, is it possible that we could maybe
just eat, like, around the pork?
- The berries are so fresh.
- Mm-hmm.
Thank you, my dear. But you see,
it's already been all tainted by the pork.
Uh, Joanne also brought you this.
- What?
- [Noah] Yeah.
[Bina laughs]
Now, this is a beautiful gift. Thank you.
- [Sasha] Hi!
- You're welcome.
Sasha, Esther,
look what I got from your brother.
I'm pretty sure prosciutto is beef.
No, it's definitely pork,
but it's beautiful.
Kids, thank you.
That's just so thoughtful.
- [Noah] Hey!
- [Esther] Hey, buddy.
- Where's Miriam?
- At bat mitzvah tutor.
Our little girl's big day is coming up.
- Yeah.
- Can you believe?
I've never been to a bat mitzvah before.
It sounds so fun.
It's gonna be a very important day.
Yep, it will. You know, they get boring.
You wouldn't wanna come.
- I think the hora gets pretty lit.
- It's a beautiful simcha.
Yeah, but they're mostly...
Thank you both. It's mostly boring.
Mom, I'm gonna give Joanne a tour.
I'd love that.
Sasha, dear. I would like you
to mix us some drinks
while I put away
this lovely gift that my son gave me.
Uh, yes.
How about a very large glass of wine?
Red would be great.
No. We do not serve red in this house
because there have been incidents.
- It was Esther both times.
- Okay. Thanks, everyone.
White is just fine, then.
Esther, sweetie, would you please
cut up some of the cucumbers?
- You talking to me?
- Uh-huh.
- In your kitchen?
- [Bina] Mm-hmm.
- And you're not being sarcastic?
- No, sweetie. I trust you.
You know what you're doing.
[gentle music playing]
Well, all right.
Yeah. Don't fuck it up.
No, I won't. It's just cucumbers.
How could it be ha... hard?
[Noah] And now for the best part
of the tour, my old bedroom.
- Oh wow!
- Right?
- Wow, wow, wow!
- Right? Yeah. As you can see, I was cool.
- Um, this is a canopy bed.
- Yep.
This was the bed you wanted
when you were 17?
No, but, uh, my mom picked it out.
And when she bought it, then it was here.
- Ah.
- Yeah.
You never told her
it wasn't what you wanted?
Uh... I didn't wanna hurt her feelings.
I love that you protect your mom,
but it's okay to push back sometimes.
You could've been sleeping
in a race car bed.
I would've killed for a race car bed.
[Noah groans softly]
So when you brought girls up here,
you just hooked up under this canopy?
Oh yeah. They loved it.
We'd hook up there.
We'd hook up above it,
below it, beside it.
- No, there's never been a girl in here.
- There's ne...
- I'm your first?
- Mm-hmm.
- Welcome to the canopy.
- [Joanne] Wow!
It's all part of my plan.
Brunch is ready.
[quirky music playing]
And that bed is meant for one.
- That's why no girls.
- Sorry.
Can't believe I'm finally
the good daughter-in-law
now that Joanne's around.
The power's kind of, like, intoxicating.
Do you think Joanne's gonna stick around?
Rebecca and Noah are completely done?
Why would you even ask that?
I don't know. It's just something I heard.
From where? What do you mean you heard?
Nothing. I mean, I didn't hear it
like in, you know,
like a real sense of hearing.
It... It's just that, like, I heard it
in the sense that it was like
a psychic vision
or a premonition or something.
You know how that happens sometimes?
Babe, do you know
what's actually really funny?
Okay. Rebecca saw the dumb sister.
Pretended not to know who she was.
And told her just, like, a bunch of lies
about her and Noah just to fuck with her.
It's amazing.
My God. Women are scary.
Hey, hey. You need to promise me
you are not gonna repeat that.
Yeah. No. No, no, no. Of course not.
That's just like...
That's just really juicy information
that people would kill for,
and I'm just not gonna
do anything with it or tell anybody.
Okay. Great.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Bina] So here we are.
Yep.
It's okay.
[music fades]
Wow!
Everything looks incredible.
- Doesn't it?
- Thank you.
- [Joanne] Yeah.
- You gotta try my mom's famous pâté.
- Oh.
- She makes it from scratch.
- Oh, okay.
- Try a little sample of that.
It's chopped liver.
- Mmm.
- Right?
Wow!
I can smell it from here.
That is so good.
So tell me,
Joanne, what exactly is your religion?
Well,
I guess, um, religion was never
really anything I grew up with.
We celebrated Christmas,
but that was the only holiday
I can ever remember
my parents getting into.
And your parents
are divorced now, isn't that right?
No, they're separated.
Uh, but it's probably permanent
since my dad is gay.
Ah.
- Esther, could you pass the fruit, please?
- With pleasure.
Mm. And this is
what your, uh, your podcast is about?
My gay dad? No.
Sadly, I think that one's been done.
- Ah.
- Um...
It is about sex and relationships
in the modern world.
And this is how you make money?
Talking about what you do
behind closed doors with sex and men
in front of the whole world?
I mean, people actually pay to hear this?
Yeah. That's how I make money.
Uh-huh.
How do you make money?
Oh mama!
- Mmm. Mm-mmm.
- [sighs]
Who seasoned these cucumbers? Fabulous.
Well, I was... busy raising children,
which I know is not as important
as talking about all my former lovers
for public consumption.
Honestly, it's embarrassing.
No woman should act this way. Airing...
Mom, enough.
You'll excuse me.
Oh my God!
I am gonna remember this moment
for the rest of my life.
I would like to officially invite you
to Miriam's bat mitzvah.
Being around you
makes me look like a goddamn angel.
Well, I'm gonna go talk to your mother.
- I will.
- Whoa.
This is between her and me.
Actually, I wasn't really
gonna talk to her.
I'm gonna take a little nap.
It's okay.
[tense music playing]
[gasps]
How dare you
come into my kitchen unannounced?
How is that prosciutto?
Is it good?
- No one will believe you.
- [Joanne] Mm.
Food's getting cold, so...
Think I'm gonna head back in.
Joanne.
You're not gonna believe
what I walked in on.
Don't listen to a word she says.
She was trying to clean the kitchen
while we were still eating.
Can you believe that?
My girl, Bina.
Don't worry. She gave me permission
to call her that.
And, Bina,
you have such an amazing family.
Which I expected,
seeing how you raised Noah
to be the extraordinary man he is.
Let me get your chair.
Just want you to be comfortable.
[exhales happily]
Mmm, this is delicious.
[whispers] What is happening?
I have no idea.
[tranquil music playing]
- Should I check on Dad?
- Don't bother, sweetheart.
He wakes up at 6:00.
We'll eat another meal,
and then he'll fall asleep.
Somebody ate all the prosciutto
off the charcuterie board.
What?
Oh yeah. That was me.
Um, I'm sorry,
I couldn't help myself. [chuckles]
I hope you can forgive me.
But it was in the trash.
Yeah. Yes.
And I... I fished it out of the garbage,
and I ate it.
Like a raccoon.
Joanne, you're so remarkable.
How is it that you are not married?
Um, if I'm being real, probably... [exhales]
...I'm a hopeless romantic.
I just haven't found
the right mother-in-law yet.
[chuckles]
Mom, are you all right?
You having a stroke?
No, I'm laughing because Joanne is funny.
[Bina laughs]
Is this the tone of your podcast?
Like, if I were a guest,
what would you do?
My sister and I would start
by putting you at ease.
Um, like, Esther,
pretend you're my sister.
Oh! Yeah. Sure, I'll be whore number two.
- Esther, language.
- No, it's an inside joke.
- Would you stop it?
- Never mind.
So, first, my sister and I,
we talk a little bit about ourselves.
And then we ask the guest
to tell their stories.
I have a story.
Oh yeah. Mom's a storyteller.
And there's always a lesson.
[Bina] Thank you, dear.
When I was a young woman,
I went to New York City
for the first time.
I was with my grandmother.
The weather was awful.
And so, of course, what happens?
She catches a terrible cold.
So I had to get vapor rub for her chest.
I went to the first pharmacy I saw
at 51st and 6th, but they had nothing.
So I go back to the hotel,
and Grandmother was asleep.
So, with nothing to do,
I go down to the lobby,
and there is a bar.
Anyway, Frank Sinatra got me drunk.
And then he stuck his thumb in my mouth.
- Oh. Wait, what?
- Oh!
What was the lesson?
Keep your mouth shut around Frank.
Well, you being the bad one
was short-lived.
Sorry, I'm so likable.
Hey, um, any chance
I can rescind that bat mitzvah invite?
Having you there
isn't benefiting me anymore.
Oh, no. I'll be there.
Well, I tried.
Honey, don't forget the rugelach!
[Sasha] I got it!
- [Esther] Bye, guys.
- Bye. I haven't eaten in 20 minutes.
Text your sister,
see if she'll come to dinner with us.
- No.
- Come on. I hate that you're in a fight.
- What are you fighting about?
- Nothing.
She's just a lying bitch
who's trying to get
in between me and my bubala.
- How do you know Morgan's lying?
- [sighs]
If you knew the situation,
you would get it.
Okay, well, I don't.
Okay, bye. Bye, Mama.
- See ya.
- Bye, Sash.
- Thank you for a lovely day.
- [door closes]
Sorry I raised my voice.
- That was wrong.
- It's okay.
Joanne, it is so nice to know you.
Right back at you.
And you have
to give me the recipe for that pâté
because I can still taste it.
It's just chopped chicken liver.
Mmm.
- [Bina] Bye, my son.
- [Noah] Bye.
To be honest...
[door opens]
...I like you so much more
than I thought I would.
Oh, that's sweet.
[whispers] But you're never gonna
end up with my son.
[rock music playing]
♪ God, it's brutal out here ♪
♪ I feel like no one wants me
And I hate the way I'm perceived ♪
♪ I only have two real friends
And lately I'm a nervous wreck ♪
♪ 'Cause I Iove people I don't like
And I hate every song I write ♪
♪ And I'm not cool, and I'm not smart
And I can't even parallel park ♪
♪ All I did was try my best
This the kind of thanks I get? ♪
♪ Unrelentlessly upset ♪
♪ They say these are the golden years
But I wish I could disappear ♪
♪ Ego crush is so severe
God, it's brutal out here ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Just having a really good time ♪
♪ Got a broken ego, broken heart ♪
♪ God, I don't even know where to start ♪