Previously on From...
I hear their voices.
Sara, just tell me
what you did.
I left the door open.
I have Sara tied up in
the basement of the church.
Tell me you're joking.
That girl may be the key to
unlocking all this.
That girl may be
the way we all go home.
Let's take a walk.
We have to turn around!
We can't be here!
Stop the bus!
Everyone lease return
to your seats!
Bad things are gonna
happen if--
Stop the goddamn bus!
Everyone on, right now.
You're gonna get people killed,
you realize that?
Hello?
Where are you?
Is this Jim?
Your wife shouldn't be
digging that hole, Jim.
You ever wonder
if Abby was right?
What if it's all
just a dream?
Aah!
My blood is your blood now.
Who was in my room?
- Sorry?
- Someone was in my room,
and they took something.
Uh, I think I saw Jade
and the Matthews boy
up here last night.
You are not
listening to me.
No, I am listening,
and I'm telling you
to fuck off.
Residents don't carry guns.
That's the rule.
Well, uh, rules change.
The wires aren't
connected to anything.
They were just dangling
from the ceiling.
Tabitha, we have
so much to talk about.
I saw something
that wasn't there.
What?
I saw two children
standing in the middle
of the road staring at me.
Hello? Someone down here?
Hi, Kenny.
And right through here
we have the common area.
And downstairs you'll have
a nice big room all to yourself.
Come on in.
No.
I don't like it here.
It's too sunny.
I-I want to go home.
No, no, Dad.
It's okay, look.
Um, this place
is really nice.
And, look, there's
a perfect little spot here
for us to play chess.
We stay here together?
I'll give you folks
a few minutes, okay?
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Look, Dad.
Mom and I are gonna
be right down the street.
You know? And we'll
come here every single day.
But it's really, really
important for you
to be somewhere where you
can't open the door at night.
Dad, what happened last night...
It's safer this way.
No.
I go home now.
Uh, I'll go get
the rest of the stuff.
Kenny.
Sheriff Boyd, hey.
Everything all right?
Yeah, we were just, uh,
we're getting my dad settled in.
I heard you had
a scare last night.
Those things were knocking
on the door, they're--
He was convinced that, uh,
that his brothers
were outside.
Right.
My mom tried to stop him
but, uh, he-- he pushed her.
It was, uh...
Yeah, man, it's--
It's hard.
First time seeing
your parents struggle, huh?
Yeah.
You know, this place...
...there's not a lot
holding it together.
You know,
everyone is scared and confused,
but a thing
I learned in the army,
it always helps to
have people to look to--
people who seem like they know
what the hell they're doing.
That's really all
I'm trying to do here.
Seems like you're doing
a really good job.
I could use some help.
Wouldn't mind having
a deputy watching my six.
What do you say?
You think?
I think, right?
Uh, yeah.
I mean--
Sheriff Boyd!
I have to show you something.
Can it wait?
I gotta--
No, no, no.
Um, I have--
I have to show you now.
" plays]
♪ When I was just a little boy ♪
♪ I asked my father ♪
♪ "What will I be?" ♪
♪ "Will I be handsome?" ♪
♪ "Will I be rich?" ♪
♪ Here's what he said to me ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ Whatever will be will be ♪
♪ The future's not ours to see ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ What will be will be ♪
♪ Now I have
children of my own♪
♪ They ask their father ♪
♪ "What will I be?" ♪
♪ "Will I be pretty?" ♪
♪ "Will I be rich?" ♪
♪ I tell them tenderly ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ Whatever will be will be ♪
♪ The future's not ours to see ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ What will be will be ♪
Hey, I was gonna
make some tea.
You want some?
Are you okay?
Hey.
Yeah, I'm fine.
It happened again, didn't it?
You saw something.
I need you to watch
Ethan for a minute.
I need to talk to your father.
Mom, you can tell me.
I know. I know.
Yes, it happened again.
I saw something,
but, listen, I'm fine.
And you're fine, right?
- We're good.
- Yeah.
I just need to talk to Daddy.
- Okay.
I'll be right back.
Where's Mom going?
Uh, she--
Oh, Christ!
Are you people
living here now?
Our house collapsed.
Well...
at least you had one.
It's not my fault you broke it.
Hey, take it easy.
We finally get rid of
those three smelly hippies
from Colony House
and now we got you people!
Still wanna go see Victor?
Yeah.
When I came down earlier...
...she was here.
Give us a minute, okay?
What?
I need to talk to her.
In private.
Wait for me upstairs.
Please, Kenny.
I got this.
All right.
I'm glad you're okay.
Yeah, that's debatable.
I got about a thousand
questions for you.
What happened to you?
After you pushed me
in that tree?
Where'd you go?
I followed right behind you.
And?
And then I was here.
So you--
You been here since
the other night?
I didn't know what else to do.
Where did you go
when you went through?
That's a...
How did you know?
How'd you know
what that tree was?
A little boy told me.
He was standing up on the ridge,
wearing all white.
He said that Nathan was right,
that we made
this place angry,
but we'd be safe
in the tree.
So, this little boy, that's one
of the voices you hear.
No.
No, this was different.
- I think--
- Jesus.
I think he's trapped here
like us,
that he wants to help,
but he's not sure how.
No shit.
Look, I am glad
you're back.
I am. I am.
But you being here,
that's a shitstorm
waitin' to happen.
We need to figure out
how to handle this.
You know
what you have to do.
We're not talkin'
about this.
Boyd, it was always
going to end like this.
You knew that when
you brought me out there.
There's no way I can
ever live here again.
Hey.
Just sit tight, okay?
I gotta talk
to Kenny.
Just sit tight.
Boyd?
You didn't tell Kenny,
'bout what happened
that night at the clinic.
No.
What is going on?
Look.
Now, I'm just gonna say
this as plainly as I can.
Okay, Sara is uniquely
connected to this place.
Something here has
communicated with her.
Communicated how?
She hears voices.
Ye-- I know,
I know how it sounds.
Believe me.
When Father Khatri came to me--
Father Khatri knew?
Father Khatri
locked her up in the basement.
Apparently Nathan had come
to him
earlier in the day,
he was worried.
Thought she might do
something to hurt someone.
So, Father Khatri
questioned her,
and what he found proof of
is that something here
is talking to her.
Using her like-- like--
A pawn.
He figured if something
here is using her,
if she really is
connected to this place,
then we can
use that to understand
what this place actually is.
Okay, I don't-- So, what?
She's just been downstairs
since Father Khatri died?
No.
I took her with me
into the forest.
Jesus, I--
Look, hey,
when push came to shove,
she's the reason I made it back.
That girl downstairs
saved my life,
and I know,
I know she did bad things.
Horrible things!
But this place, Kenny,
it can make you think you're
doing them for good reasons.
She killed her own brother!
She tried to kill
a 9-year-old kid!
Yes, I know!
Do you? Because you lied.
You lied to everyone!
You lied to me!
Yeah, okay, okay.
Okay, you're right.
And I know that what
she did is unforgivable,
but, listen, when she
killed those people--
People?
It was just Nathan.
No, I mean, yeah.
She almost with the--
with Ethan--
You know what
I'm talking about, right?
Kenny!
Boyd.
What's gonna happen
when everyone finds out?
When Jim and Tabitha
and Ethan's
whole family finds out?
Yeah, okay. Well...
- We'll handle it.
- She's dangerous.
Boyd, she belongs in the Box.
Okay, well,
she's not dangerous.
Not anymore.
Okay, would you
still be saying this
if it was Ellis that
she almost killed?
She's not goin' in the Box.
If we really wanna
figure this out--
Hey, she's not going
in the goddamn Box, okay!?
No one else is going
in-- into the fucking Box!
Oh, okay.
I, uh... I-I-I need some air.
I gotta...
Boyd!
Boyd.
I can't--
Boyd! Boyd! Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey!
Hey! You okay?
Guys, come on!
Jeez!
Hey.
Hey, slow down.
Not too long, okay?
Okay.
Hey, you.
Guess it's laundry day?
I'm just trying to get things
back to some sense of normal.
I never got to congratulate
you on the engagement.
- Oh.
- I'm really happy for you guys.
Well, in that case,
maybe you'd consider
being one of
my bridesmaids.
What?
Ellis doesn't wanna wait.
We're gonna--
We're getting
married here.
Oh my God. Seriously?
Right?
But I mean, it's--
Well, I would be honored
to be one of your bridesmaids.
Why, thank you kindly.
I saw the new guy outside.
Elgin, yeah, he's, uh--
I think he's having
a rough time.
Maybe I could talk to him?
Really?
Yeah.
It was nice having
people do it for me.
Hi.
What do you want?
I was worried
about you.
I'm glad you're okay.
Well, I'm not very
happy with you.
Can I come in?
I don't know.
Are you gonna
steal anything else?
I told him not to.
I said you wouldn't like it.
Well, you should've
said it louder.
My mom said
you helped her.
Out in the forest.
She's a nice lady.
You're lucky to
have a mom like that.
What are you drawing?
New stuff.
What kind of new stuff?
Things we saw.
You and my mom?
Yeah. Yeah.
Where did you guys go?
You should go now,
'cause I'm pretty busy.
Well...
Please just go!
I found these in
the storage closet.
I thought you might like them.
I'm sorry I made you mad.
Okay.
Bye.
Hey.
You're Elgin, right?
Yeah. Julie?
Yeah.
How's your dad?
Uh, he's pretty beat up.
Kristi, the doctor,
she's trying to get him
to take it easy for a bit.
You been here a while?
Uh, not that long.
Kinda feels
like a lifetime.
Look, I know you probably have
tons of people telling you
they're here if you wanna talk,
but I'm around
if you wanna talk.
Believe it or not,
it actually helps.
I appreciate that.
Hey, what's going on?
I thought you--
I wanna go home.
Okay, well, ca--
I think that's my cue.
It was nice meeting you.
Likewise.
Hey!
Ethan, wait up.
Good.
And then we'll
do the other hand.
I'm telling you, I'm fine.
I'm just tired, that's all.
Oh, given your
vast medical training
I guess there's nothing
to worry about, then.
Now press up as hard as you can.
Good.
What about spider bites?
I got spiders on me
when I was out in the forest.
Uh, yeah.
Let me take a look.
Let's see.
- There's one here.
- Okay.
And then there's...
They don't look swollen
or inflamed, which is good.
Uh, but do you wanna
tell me about this?
What? It's nothing. I just--
Boyd!
I just scratched it
on a tree branch.
It's, um...
it's not infected,
but keep it clean, okay?
Yes, ma'am.
Those tremors,
have they gotten any worse?
They come and go.
I'm dealing with it.
Have you noticed any
symptoms other than the shaking?
Such as?
Visual impairment,
muscle stiffness--
- Nope.
- Depression?
Kristi, everybody here
is depressed.
You know, I remember my--
my dad, he got--
It started to mess
with his mind at the end.
Yeah, I don't think that's
anything that you need
to be worrying about right now.
Cognitive impairment
with Parkinson's
doesn't happen until way
down the line, if at all.
Why? Is there something?
No. Just-- Just curious.
I'm telling you, I'm fine.
Fine.
Okay, but you need
to rest, okay?
In your condition,
you can't afford to be
putting any extra stress
on your body right now.
Boyd, what's going on?
Nothing! I'm sorry.
The idea that
anybody here could avoid
putting extra stress
on anything is just--
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
This is great.
Uh, not a good idea. Okay.
- Just sit, okay?
- Come on!
For fuck's sake,
there's literally nowhere
in this town I can be alone.
Wait a second.
You're the bus driver, right?
I'm sorry.
It's been a long day.
Stay as long
as you want, all right?
I'm just gonna...
That boy.
He said to me,
"Turn around."
He begged me.
I didn't listen.
When?
What?
When did he ask you
to turn the bus around?
Was it before
or after you saw the tree?
After.
Oh, well, then
you were already screwed.
Apparently,
it's once you see the tree,
that's when everything,
you know.
Yeah, I wouldn't
spend too much time
kicking yourself
for that part.
Those people.
They got on my bus.
It was my job to get them
where they were going.
All right,
tell me something.
Does your pity party
come with music? Hm?
Will you be serving
finger sandwiches?
Look, it's not
your fault!
Okay?
I mean, if you wanna
feel like shit, fine,
but feel like shit
'cause your life is fucked.
Don't carry around
a bunch of guilt thinking
that you ruined
anybody else's.
Besides, no offense...
...they were riding a bus.
Their lives couldn't have been
that great to begin with.
It was a bad joke. Sorry.
You know I wasn't even
supposed to be driving that day?
I took that job
to pay for my degree.
Last month I finally
paid off my tuition.
I was all set to hand in
my notice and I thought,
why not stay a few extra weeks?
Put aside something extra
so I can treat myself.
Take a little trip
and celebrate.
I deserve
a little reward, right?
Is this what I deserve?
I sold my company
right before I got here.
Finally achieved the one thing
I worked my whole life for.
To getting what
we deserve.
Mm.
Ah, it doesn't get easier.
Yeah.
Jim?
Hi.
Hey.
I'm sorry,
I didn't hear you come in.
Who are you?
I'm Marielle.
I was on the bus.
Oh.
Don't worry, I'm a nurse.
I was just helping
Kristi inventory the supplies.
Um, I'm looking for my husband?
Jim?
He left a little while ago.
Thank you.
This go other storage.
Okay.
Jim.
What are you doing, honey?
You should be resting.
We need to talk.
Okay.
Over here.
Take, take more.
Take more. Yeah.
Jesus.
I laid down there all night
thinking I was gonna die,
and I just kept
asking myself "why?"
Why did that road
lead us here?
What the fuck is
the point of all of this?
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
you can't just take this stuff!
It doesn't belong to you!
Hey! You go! Now!
Fucking people.
Fucking vultures.
Did you know Kristi's
fiancée was on that bus?
What?
Yeah.
And what you said about
the wires not being connected?
That's not possible.
No, no,
I'm telling you--
Oh, no, it's not that.
I know, I believe you.
It's just that there
is no way that...
When we build
a new rollercoaster,
we design it to do things
that seem impossible,
because the more
impossible it seems,
the stronger the reaction you
get from the people riding it.
I know how this sounds,
but what if...
...what if all this was designed
just to see how we react?
I mean, what if this is all some
kind of fucked-up experiment?
The radio worked.
No.
We made contact with someone.
So, then why is
everybody just standing--
'Cause they don't know.
Right as the storm
was coming in,
just as we were about
to wrap things up,
I heard a voice. A man.
That's why I came
running back here.
He-he warned me, Tabitha.
Or threatened me.
I don't know which,
but he knew my name,
and he said
you shouldn't be digging,
and then just like that,
our house collapsed.
You think someone's
watching us?
All I know is--
Honey.
All I know is
someone got on
the other end of that radio
and they talked to me.
Over there.
Did anyone else hear it?
The voice on the radio?
It's your move, Boyd...
but I gotta say...
your options
don't look great.
This ain't real.
You're not here.
You wanna talk about
what can and can't be real?
That's the part
you wanna focus on?
Yeah, I don't know.
I got a little mystery boy
sending people through
magic trees in the forest,
my hand's
not shaking anymore,
but now I got fucking worms
underneath my skin.
So, yeah, yeah, maybe that's
the part we should talk about!
Or... how 'bout we talk about
what's really on your mind?
How exactly are you gonna tell
Kenny that Sara killed his dad?
She didn't kill him.
She opened the door.
Potato, pot-ah-to.
You think Kenny's gonna
be interested
in the minutiae of exactly
what happened?
Let me ask you something.
What benefit is there
in Kenny knowing?
That you lied to him.
You betrayed him.
- I didn't--
- You found out the truth
about how his father died.
You not only spared the life
of the person responsible,
you gave her your trust,
your friendship.
All this was
your fuckin' idea!
Oh, come on, Boyd. Really?
It's poor form
to blame the dead.
He'll understand.
I did what I had to do.
She was valuable!
She--
She may still be valuable!
Oh, yeah,
she may very well be of value.
Which is why you need to
keep your fucking mouth shut.
I mean, of what value is
the truth to Kenny right now?
What, you think he's gonna be
better off once he finds out?
Or will you simply be relieving
the burden of your own guilt?
Oh, man.
Somehow you being dead
made you more of an asshole.
Leaders sometimes have to
make tough decisions, Boyd.
You of all people know this.
What, you wanna be
everyone's friend?
Go be the new bartender.
Apparently there's a vacancy.
But if you wanna
lead these people home,
sometimes you have to
make a shitty decision.
I tried telling you this before,
you didn't listen.
Listen to me now.
I'm not gonna lie to him.
What was that thing Ellis said?
'Bout that thing
that everyone holds onto?
That's what you are
to Kenny now.
You're the father
Kenny no longer has.
What do you think happens
when you take that away?
Broken people don't
survive here, Boyd.
It's not a good time, Jim.
You know why I'm here.
To thank me for
looking after your kids
when you ran off
like an asshole?
We need to talk about
how we're gonna handle this.
Handle what?
You heard the voice
on the radio.
I know you did.
Get the fuck in here.
I'm gonna put this
as delicately as possible.
How fucking stupid are you?
What?
You wanna know if
I heard something?
Yeah, I heard it.
I heard
some spooky motherfucker
warn you about your wife
20 minutes before
your house collapsed.
That means that there are
people out there who can see us.
And what part of you
thinks that that's a good sign?
Do you realize what happened
here after you ran off?
The fucking lights exploded.
One of my people
almost went blind.
If there really
are people watching us,
they sure as shit
aren't helping us.
What do you think
they'll do if they find out
we know about them? Huh?
And that's assuming
it was actually a person
on the other end
of the line.
There are things
around here that walk
and talk just like us,
until they walk up to you
and rip your fucking guts out.
How do you know
it wasn't one of them?
- I--
- I am not saying ignore it.
But you already
got people's hopes up
with your goddamn tower.
All the more reason--
To keep our fucking
mouths shut.
Until we know more.
Where's the radio?
What?
What happened to the radio?
It's in the back.
It got a little
busted up during the storm.
All right.
Do me a favor and don't do
anything until I tell you--
Hey!
What the fuck are you doing?
Oh, fuck.
- Hey, calm down.
- Fuck!
Don't tell me to
fucking calm down!
You don't touch my shit!
Understand me?
Hey.
What's going on?
He went through my bag.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Okay, look, if this is
gonna work, you're gonna--
Enough! All right? Enough!
Now, this only works if
he stays out of my shit. Period.
We have a way
of doing things here.
That's good for you.
I got a way of
doing things, too.
You touch my stuff,
I will smack
the fucking shit outta you.
We clear?
Good.
Boyd said you saved his life.
It-- it wasn't me,
it was, um...
It's hard to explain.
He said you hear voices.
He said that that's why
you tried to kill Ethan,
and how you
ended up killing Nathan.
How does a voice
inside your head
convince you to do
something like that?
I mean, wouldn't your first
thought be
that you're losing
your mind
or that maybe
it was a bad idea?
You don't understand.
So help me understand.
Because I really
wanna believe
that Boyd is right
about you.
I wanna back him up,
but people are gonna freak out
when they find out about you.
And that doesn't just hurt you.
That hurts Boyd.
You understand?
And I cannot
let that happen.
So, help me.
Please.
Sara, I always thought
of you as a friend.
And my mom...
my mom adores you.
My mom always
thought of you as, like,
the daughter that she never had.
Convince me that you don't
deserve to go in the Box.
I can't.
Do you think
I want this?
Boyd gave me a chance...
that I didn't deserve.
I'm grateful
to him for that.
I'm glad
I got to help.
But now I'm back.
And I have done things
I can't undo.
We can help!
We can help make
people understand.
You know,
we can do that.
Sara, this town is
so hard on everyone,
and I know you thought
that you found a way to...
I know that it was horrible,
I know that
it was unforgivable,
but if we can
make people understand
why you did
the things that you did,
- maybe we could, you know--
- Kenny!
Stop.
There's something
I need to tell you.
You okay?
I heard about
the fight.
He'll come around.
They always do.
Not this one.
I know his type.
Everything's a personal attack,
a goddamn battle.
Well, maybe...
Maybe we change
the rules a little bit.
Just ease up on
the communal sharing. Maybe we--
Maybe we just give him a whole
wing of the goddamn house!
That's not what I mean.
I mean, it doesn't help--
Oh, fuck this!
Whoa, what are you doing?
I'm gonna have a chat
with our little friend.
Donna!
Get up.
What?
Get your shit.
You don't like the rules here,
you can live somewhere else.
Get the fuck out of here.
Jesus!
Get the fuck up!
Okay.
You wanna tell me
where we're going?
You'll see.
Come on.
- Come on!
- I'm coming.
Well, I don't want
people staring at it
when they're eatin'.
Can't say I blame you.
Welcome to your new home.
What?
Hop on up.
Now, this here is the talisman
from the Matthews house.
They won't be
needing it anymore.
What you're gonna wanna do
is hang it on the window.
And you wanna make
damn sure it stays there,
because if it falls down at
any point during the night
and one of those
things gets inside,
it won't matter if
you have a dozen of those.
If they're on the floor at
that point, they're just rocks.
You done swinging
your dick around?
You made your point.
No.
No, see,
I don't think I have.
You don't want anyone
looking through your shit, fine,
but I'll be motherfucked
if I let you hurt
any more of my people.
You understand that?
You really don't
get what's happening here.
Even after
everything you've seen,
you still can't process the fact
that this is actually real.
Now, seeing as you
don't strike me as
the brightest
of fucking bulbs,
I'm gonna bet that it
takes you longer than most.
So now you get to live here.
No shades on the window.
You get to see
everything that's happening.
Every night those things come.
There really is no way out.
Best of luck.
Excuse me?
Sheriff Boyd, right?
Yeah, sorry, I don't, uh--
Tillie.
Tillie. Hi.
- Hi, yeah.
- Hi.
I was on the bus.
Yeah.
This, uh, wasn't exactly
my preferred destination.
I understand you yourself
had a bit of an adventure.
Yeah, I did. I'm sorry.
You'll have to excuse me.
I need to go
speak with my deputy.
You won't find him in there.
I just saw him heading
towards that medical building.
I, uh...
...went to look for
you at the church.
You know,
before we came here...
...I don't think I ever once
remember seeing my mom cry.
I'd see her mad.
I'd see her stubborn.
I'd see her frustrated.
And now every
single night...
...I hear her sobbing
in her room,
because she's convinced
that it was her fault...
that if she had
been here with my dad...
that he wouldn't have
gotten out of the basement...
...and he wouldn't have opened
the door to let those things in.
But he didn't
open the door, did he?
No.
You knew.
I found out
the night before I left.
Kenny--
Don't.
Don't fucking touch me!
I was going to tell you.
When exactly were you
planning on telling me?
She's going in the Box.
No.
She's going in the fucking Box!
Kenny--
She killed my dad!
They tore him to pieces
and you knew!
You fucking knew!
Kenny, please, Kenny.
Li--
You watch your own fucking six.