♪ Shoobie-doobie-doobie-
doobie-doo-wop-wop ♪
♪ One fine day ♪
♪ You'll look at me ♪
♪ And you will know
our love was meant be ♪
♪ One fine day ♪
♪ You're gonna want me for your girl ♪
♪ Shoobie-doobie-doobie-
doobie-doo-wop-wop ♪
♪ The arms I long for will open wide ♪
♪ And you'll be proud to have me
right by your side ♪
♪ One fine day ♪
♪ You're gonna want me for your girl ♪
♪ Shoobie-doobie-doobie-
doobie-doo-wop-wop ♪
♪ Shoobie doobie doo wop ♪
♪ Though I know you're the kind of boy ♪
♪ Who only wants to run around ♪
♪ I'll be waiting and someday darling ♪
♪ You'll come to me
when you want to settle down, oh ♪
♪ One fine day ♪
♪ We'll meet once more ♪
♪ And then you'll want the love
you threw away before ♪
♪ One fine day ♪
♪ You're gonna want me for your girl ♪
♪ Aah-aah ♪
♪ One fine day ♪
♪ You're gonna want me for your girl ♪
♪ You're gonna want me... ♪
Isaac.
Isaac!
What's wrong?
- Isaac's gone.
- What?
Someone's been in the house.
Isaac!
I'm sorry
you had to go through that.
Standing in the road screaming his name.
You were still there?
I was worried about you.
Nothing compares to the fear
of losing a child.
The questions that must thunder
through your head.
Is he alive? Is he in pain?
I wanted... I wanted to help you.
I wanted... I wanted to tell you.
Tell me what?
I never touched your son.
You said you would tell me the truth.
You said if I came here,
you would explain everything.
I'm explaining.
No.
You're full of shit.
We know it was you.
They know it was you.
Based on what evidence?
You were obsessed with Isaac.
You...
his name was all over your, uh, plans.
He's a... he's a special boy.
What the fuck does that mean?
Don't leave. Don't leave.
Please, please.
Don't let him bait you.
That's why you interrupted us?
- You need a break.
- No, I need an answer.
By rights, you shouldn't even be in there.
- If he tries something...
- He won't.
If something happens to you.
It won't.
Ravi, it's okay.
I'm okay.
Take a minute.
And when you go back in there,
I'm coming with you.
He won't like that.
Good.
Ravi, thanks.
I haven't done anything.
You trusted me.
Not a lot of people would have.
I'm just... I'm glad it was you.
I'm glad you got assigned the case
and not someone else.
I'm not.
Miss Chambers...
let's talk downstairs.
Do you mind if I record this?
We've activated child rescue alert.
With any luck, we'll have Isaac's picture
on every front page by the morning.
We've got roadblocks,
officers going door to door.
And we're checking local CCTV.
Whoever this man is,
he's not gonna have anywhere to hide.
I can promise you that.
Is he gonna...
I'm sorry?
Is he gonna hurt him?
It's her job, it has to be.
Some psycho had his kid taken away
and now he's just returning the favour.
Maybe, we've got people
looking into old cases.
Disputes, grievances,
if there's a link, we'll find it.
Will you?
'Cause her name was written on his wall
and you didn't do anything about it.
We were looking for Lucy Chambers.
That's not your name, not on paper.
It's not an excuse,
it's just an explanation.
We were too late.
And I can't tell you
how sorry I am for that.
But right now,
our best chance of finding Isaac
is to identify the man who took him.
You knew one of his victims.
Shane Fisher.
What about Harold Slade?
He should kill himself.
I'm sorry?
Harold Slade.
Harold Slade is dead, Miss Chambers.
Are you saying you knew him?
I don't know.
She's in shock and you're not helping.
You should be out there looking for him.
We've got people looking, Mr Stevens.
If we ID the suspect, we can make sure
they're looking in the right places.
Do you need to take a break?
Now, these aren't easy to read but...
Isaac's name comes up several times.
What does it say?
We think this one says,
"Isaac is unbound."
Well, what's that supposed to mean?
He might be quoting scripture.
In the Bible, Isaac was bound
to a sacrificial altar by his father.
That's Isaac's watch.
Why...
why has he drawn Isaac's watch?
You're sure this is his watch?
It was here, it was in this bag.
No chance
he could have been wearing it?
No, he never wore it, right?
It doesn't work anymore.
Anything else missing?
Not that I can see.
Why would he take his watch?
That has to mean something, doesn't it?
If he just wanted to hurt him,
he wouldn't take something like that.
It's the press office again.
Okay.
I'm gonna need a recent photo of Isaac.
Clear, high res.
If it's okay with you,
I'd like to get his face
on TV, social media, newspapers,
but everything else
stays between us for now.
What do you mean?
Harold Slade, Shane Fisher,
we don't want that connection
going public, not yet.
Why?
If we keep the story
focused on Isaac,
we have a better chance of finding him.
You okay over there?
Sylvia, is it too hot for you?
Shush.
We're watching the quiz.
These girls haven't a clue.
It's Henry VIII.
See? Told you.
You didn't know.
You let me know
when you're ready for your pudding.
- What's for pudding?
- Apple crumble.
Nah.
I missed that one.
Is there anything else
you need me to do while I'm here?
Butterfly.
No. Oh.
Oh.
It's butterfly.
She doesn't know.
I'll stick it on for you.
No, don't change the channel.
It's all right, I'm just popping it on.
We asked which of these insects
is also the name of a swimming stroke.
You're saying mosquito?
I'm afraid the correct answer
is butterfly.
So that means Stacey steals the jackpot
which now stands at £720.
See? Told you.
Butterfly.
She didn't know.
Thirty-two comments,
two likes, one wow,
fourteen sad faces.
Sad faces.
Fuck, I hate Facebook.
What you doing?
Working.
Seriously?
Come on.
Well, what else am I supposed to do?
You can go to bed. Come on, come on.
- Whatever you're doing, it can wait.
- It can't.
- Yes, it can. Come here, Lucy.
- Mike.
- Come on, come on.
- Yes, you can. Come on.
- Mike. stop it. Stop.
I don't know what to do.
Hey, it's okay. All right.
Okay.
Shh.
It's okay.
Come on. Let's just go to bed, eh?
Mike.
- Mike.
- What?
What are you doing here?
Our son's missing.
Oh, so he's our son now?
You don't love him,
you don't spend any time with him.
- Okay, yeah, all right, Luce.
- No, no, no,
you don't get to do this.
You don't get to comfort me.
What happens if he walks
through that door right now?
What happens then?
Are you gonna wrap your arms around him?
- Are you gonna tell him it's okay?
- Luce,
I am scared just the same as you are.
No, you're not, not like me
because I love him and he's gone.
And it's not your place
to hold me and say,
"Oh, let's go to bed,"
like it's your bed because it's not!
I do not need that from you right now!
Okay!
Fuck.
I'll sleep in the living room.
No!
Just go home.
Please.
Fucking hell.
Nick?
What are you doing here?
Working.
Well, trying to.
This bloody thing keeps crashing on me.
You left
the evidence room unlocked.
Yeah, sorry.
Everything all right?
Don't think I've ever seen you
in here before 8:00.
Someone took a kid.
We're in the first 24.
You really think I'll be having a lie in?
That's not what I meant.
You know, Bella didn't think
I'd make detective.
Says I couldn't spot a pattern
in a pair of curtains.
Sometimes I think she's right.
We're relying on your brain here.
So tell me, what am I missing?
No real link between the victims.
Different crimes, different motives.
Case could be ten years old at least.
There's no pattern, Nick. It's just chaos.
Well, here's someone else
to add to the chaos.
Fly tipping report.
Someone's been dumping their crap
in the ravine there.
Report says it's been going on for years,
they never caught the bastard.
But then a couple of weeks ago,
a ranger spotted a car and called it in.
Description's consistent
with our red Nissan.
Who followed up?
Courtney and Dorse.
Wasn't a hell of a lot to go on but...
You said...
You said, right that some of these...
- some of these could be maps.
- Mm.
Well, this one here
matches the road configuration.
You see that line there that sort of vein?
- Mm-mm.
- And the shading.
Well...
that's the woods, isn't it?
Or am I seeing things?
If you are,
then I'm seeing them too.
I'm sorry,
I don't know why I came here.
Uh, I... I saw we had an appointment and...
I just got in the car and drove.
That's okay, it's okay.
You have to trust the police, okay?
And honestly, the best thing
you can do for Isaac right now
is to take care of yourself
so you can be there for him if he...
If they find him.
When.
Oh, um, I know something.
Harold Slade, I... I...
I read his name in the paper
and I remembered it.
I know that that name
means something to me.
Or maybe you just want it
to mean something.
Please don't do that.
I didn't come here for therapy.
So why are you here then?
You want the name Slade
to mean something so you can act.
You can help.
Being powerless in all of this
that... that is the scariest thing.
When you heard Slade's name,
you wanted to feel a connection.
But it's... it's more likely just déjà vu.
We have two ears, two eyes,
a right brain and a left brain.
And when one half of the brain
processes information
faster than the other.
We are experiencing
and remembering the moment
at the same time.
Which is why we sometimes feel like
we've done something before,
or we think we recognize a stranger.
Harold Slade has a violin
above his stairs in the hallway,
so which side of my brain
is telling me that?
It could have been something
you overheard,
or saw on the news,
or maybe something the police told you.
I...
Maybe it was another memory
that you have linked
with the idea of Harold Slade.
I know him.
I know that I know him.
I have to tell the police.
Tell them what?
Lucy, what do you think they're gonna say?
Have you slept?
Uh...
You need to go home and rest.
I'm here if you need me
and anything I can do to help.
Temazepam?
Sorry?
A few years ago,
I had a prescription for temazepam,
but it didn't, um...
didn't stop me waking up.
But it... it... it helped me
settle down again.
You're right. I, um...
I really need sleep.
I need to clear my head.
Temazepam won't help clear your head,
trust me.
Oh, you said you could help me.
So help me.
Some of this stuff is old.
Really old.
Serial killer, serial fly tipper.
It's a gateway crime.
See, first off,
you dump a washing machine in some woods.
Then you stab a couple of people.
And the next thing you know
you're... you're snatching kids.
Sorry.
I might have been wrong before
when I said there was no link.
What if there is?
What if it's her?
Lucy Chambers?
She's Chloe Fisher's case worker.
- Yeah.
- Isaac's mother, obviously.
Her name was written
on the suspect's wall.
And she might have known Harold Slade.
Oh, she doesn't know what she knows.
She's unstable as you would be.
But if she does, if there is a link
then she connects every victim.
Except for Jonah Taylor.
And what? What about this lot?
What are you trying to tell me
that... that that's her old fridge,
and that, that's a pair of
her old curling tongs?
- Nick?
- I'm just saying.
Can you smell that?
It's a dog.
Debs?
What're you doing?
It could have been us.
Did you lock the back door?
Nobody's getting in this house.
They'd have to get past me.
Go away.
Leave me alone!
Oh!
Oh.
Pack of cigarettes, please.
What kind?
Don't care.
- That's twelve ten, love.
- Thanks and a lighter.
You starting up again?
First time.
Shit.
Oh.
Hello?
Hi.
Are you all right?
Miss Chambers?
It's been over 24 hours.
I know.
We spoke to your husband earlier.
I'm afraid there's been no update.
Nothing concrete.
Mm, he's not my husband, not anymore.
Okay.
Um, can I ask you a question?
Yeah, of course.
Are you religious?
Uh, no, not really.
What do you believe in?
I don't know.
Science, I guess.
Logic, patterns.
What about the other stuff?
Other stuff?
Ghosts...
uh, fate, miracles, luck...
love.
I've never seen a ghost.
Have you?
I don't know.
Sorry, I know it's really late.
I probably woke you up.
No, no, you didn't.
I wouldn't mind if you did,
but you didn't.
Thanks.
- Detective Dhillon.
- Yeah.
Can I ask you one more question?
Uh-huh.
Did Harold Slade
have a violin above his stairs?
Sorry I'm a bit late.
Sylvia why is the door open?
Sylvia?
Oh, you don't have to turn it off.
Oh, Harold loved Tchaikovsky.
Well, it's very beautiful.
Is it?
I still can't hear it.
I was going to take him
to see Swan Lake for his birthday,
in Prague.
I booked the tickets without him knowing,
but I think he suspected.
Couldn't get anything past him.
Well, you know what he was like.
How did you know him?
Sorry?
My husband he...
he never mentioned you.
The rowing club.
My... my son was on the team.
We couldn't make the funeral so I just...
I just wanted to pay my respects.
What's your son's name?
Isaac.
Isaac, and he's in the rowing club?
He was, he used to be.
- We moved.
- Really?
- When was that?
- Last year.
This is really embarrassing
could I use your loo?
Uh, yes, I... I suppose so.
- Sorry.
- That's all right.
Um, upstairs third on the right.
Okay.
Dogs name was Milo, a Doberman.
Forensics tell us
he was probably run over.
We've contacted the owners,
they don't know anything
just that he's been missing
for a few days.
Other than that
nothing out of the ordinary.
As you know we impounded the Nissan
over two weeks ago
with a flat tyre and a buckled wheel.
We have to assume the suspect
has another means of transport.
So, first priority
is to identify the new car
so that we can track it down.
We've hidden some cameras
in the woods where the dog was found.
Working theory is he comes and goes,
so he'll be back.
Miss Chambers.
Write this down,
Turnpike house,
Paintmoor Lane, North Tamford.
I think Harold Slade had a pseudonym
and he... he used it
to buy a... a property near here.
I'm gonna send you
some pictures, um, documents.
What documents? Where are you?
They were in his safe.
His safe?
I knew the code 1812.
It was 1812 like the overture.
I'm sorry I'm not sure
what you're telling me.
He should have killed himself.
Who, who should have killed himself?
Slade had secrets.
Look, I don't know what this is.
I just know it's important.
Um, Turnpike House, Paintmoor Lane.
I will meet you there, okay?
Hello?
Miss Chambers, I need you
to stay away from that house.
Have you got the address?
Read it back to me.
Turnpike House,
Paintmoor Lane, North Tamford.
- Good. All right. I'm heading there now.
- No you're not.
Listen to me, you need to take a breath,
go home and let us do our jobs.
We can...
shit.
Ellen, what's up?
What? What do you mean? Where is she?
Oh, fuck.
Not today.
Fuck it.
Ellen, listen to me.
No, you don't need to call the police...
because I know where she's going.
Mum...
what are you doing here?
Oh, God, you're freezing.
We need to get you back, okay?
- Will you come with me?
- Mm?
Oh, God, I can't do this today, I can't!
If you can't stay put
you will have to live somewhere else.
Do you understand?
I'm not chasing you up here again.
You look like my daughter.
Yeah, I know.
You were the one on the telly.
Talking about those girls.
Mum, please, please
let's go back to the car.
I think...
you must be a very good person.
Will you sit with me?
And watch the ghosts.
Why here? Why do you come here?
It's beautiful.
Yeah.
Oh.
Oh, my darling.
Don't cry.
What's wrong?
You can tell me.
Oh, somebody took Isaac away.
He's gone.
Who's Isaac?
My son.
Mum, they've taken my boy away.
It's okay, you'll find him.
You haven't given up.
That's what you said, on the telly.
You remember, don't you?
I've never been on the telly, Mum.
I don't want to go.
I know.
But we have to.
I'm sorry.
Ready?
I can do it.
Right, let's get you warmed up.
Oh, that's lovely.
Are we going home?
Not yet.
Who'd buy a place like this?
Well, it's a fixer upper.
Could be nice.
Gut it, do it up.
If you got the time and the money
you could turn the profit.
Doesn't explain the fake name of course.
If this was Slade's,
no one knew about it, not even the wife.
I've got pictures of the deeds.
If we tie this to the case we can get...
a warrant.
Need a warrant anymore?
Nick.
Premises was insecure.
Could be an imminent risk.
Reasonable grounds.
I'll take a look upstairs.
Did you find anything?
Flurane.
Flurane?
What's flurane?
Anaesthetic.
Anything upstairs?
No.
Just a couple of rats.
You know they say you're never
more than six feet away from a rat.
You're thinking of spiders.
Am I?
It's a common misconception.
Rats aren't that prolific.
How often do you actually see one?
Nick?
It's the boy's watch.
I've been here before.
Where are we?
It's all right Mum, just stay in the car.
So what do you want to do?
Call it in.
Get forensics out here,
dog unit, everyone you can.
You sure that's a good idea?
I mean if he brought the boy here,
maybe he'll come back.
Miss Chambers.
What have you found?
You shouldn't be here.
Tell me what have you found?
Miss Chambers, I need you to get
in your car and go home.
- Show me!
- You can't be here right now.
Don't touch me!
Oh, my God.
Where is he?
Make the call.
Let's go outside.
Isaac.
Isaac!
- Miss Chambers.
- Isaac!
We've searched the place.
There's no one here.
What about in there?
Where?
There.
Help me move this.
How did you know this was here?
I...
Yeah, we're gonna need
at least two to three search teams
and a dog unit.
Looks like the boy was here.
Yep.
ASAP.
Oh, God.
Miss Chambers, go upstairs.
Lucy!
Go upstairs, now.
Get Detective Holness.
Tell him...
Tell him to come down here.
I see you.
There.
I found you.
I'm not supposed to be here.
Well, neither am I.
Neither am I.
Come on.
Good boy.
There she is.
Detective Dhillon, you look well.
How did he get away?
Isaac?
You had him and you let him escape.
See this is what bothers me, Mr Shepherd.
You told me you're very good
at what you do.
But if what you do is taking children...
It's not.
Not usually.
Maybe every ten years or so.
What happened to Jonah Taylor?
Is he alive?
I certainly hope so.
Where did you take him?
You've got me on four counts of murder,
life in prison.
What good would a confession do me?
Clear your conscience.
My conscience is black.
Nothing's gonna change that.
I'm not here to tell you
what you want to know.
I'm here to tell you...
what you need to know.
What do we need to know?
I was there the day Isaac disappeared.
You know that.
I was watching you.
I saw where you hid the spare key.
I let myself in.
Searched the boy's room.
Why?
Research.
What were you looking for?
Confirmation.
And I found it.
Then your ex-husband showed up,
smashed the glass in the kitchen.
I was gone before you
and Isaac arrived home.
But I stayed close.
I heard the commotion.
So, tell us what you saw.
What I saw...
If you didn't take Isaac, who did?
No one.
No one?
I don't think anyone took the boy.
Well, he didn't just vanish
into thin air, did he?
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
♪ You're gonna want me for your girl ♪
♪ One fine day ♪
♪ You gonna find me good young girls... ♪
House hasn't fallen down yet
so that's something.
It's not a supporting wall.
We'll see.
No, it looks great babe.
Cheers.
Start in the attic tomorrow.
You're not serious?
What?
Can't you sit still for one minute?
What do you think I'm doing now?
What is it love?
Lee, what?
Take Meredith downstairs.
Come on, love.
He's not supposed to be here.