Why are you doing this?
I didn't do anything.
I know you didn't...
but you will
if we don't make you better.
We can change it.
We can change you, Connor,
but I need you to help me.
I don't like killing...
but I've done it before,
and I will do it again if I have to,
do you understand?
Now get in the chair.
Just had word from St Michael's.
A 17-year-old kid
tried to kill himself last night.
Overdose.
He confessed this morning.
You were right.
This was retaliation.
Just one kid?
Seems that way.
One other dealer stepping up,
Aiden Stenner.
Stenner?
You know the name?
Yeah.
Yeah, I know the name.
Fuck.
You don't have to do this.
Yes, I do.
♪ I know so many people ♪
♪ Who think they can do it alone ♪
♪ They isolate their heads ♪
♪ And stay in their safety zones ♪
♪ Now what can you tell them ♪
♪ And what can you say
that won't make them defensive? ♪
♪ I know there's an answer ♪
♪ I know now but I have... ♪
Can you see them?
The birds.
Well, they're not real.
You can see them, you can hear them
but you can't touch them,
don't bother trying.
Oh, don't mind him.
That's just Roger.
He can't see you or me,
but he keeps me company, don't you?
You old shit.
Oh, love, you're holding on, aren't you?
I lost my grip...
a long time ago.
You wait. Wait, wait there.
This is real.
Squeeze it.
See?
No more birds.
Okay. Mum,
it's time to put your shoes on, come on.
Lovely manners, your boy.
- What's his name?
- Isaac.
Mum, he's your grandson.
He didn't cry
when he was born, did he?
Er, come on. Let's get you in the car.
Where's Ellen?
She's in the other room.
Do you wanna say goodbye?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
I'll see her later.
She brings me dinner.
Oh, no,
you won't be here for dinner.
You're gonna live somewhere else now,
do you remember?
What? What are you saying?
Shush, shush.
Can't hear myself think.
Are you off Sylvia?
Well I don't smell off.
Oh, I'll have macaroni cheese for dinner.
Is that all right?
I'll see what I can do.
See what you can do?
All right. Come on, Mum.
Isaac.
Hypnotic, isn't it?
I had hypnosis once.
Didn't work.
They think all brains are susceptible.
You know?
How familiar are you with psychotherapy?
Not at all.
Never needed it.
Well, it's a team sport.
So I'm very glad you're here for Isaac.
Yeah.
I didn't abandon him
if that's what you're thinking.
She kicked me out.
You know, I said some things
that I didn't mean.
Maybe I did mean, um...
at the time.
How long have you been separated?
Nine months.
It wasn't supposed to be
a permanent thing but, you know,
it's hard when your kid is, erm...
well, like he is.
She ever talk about me?
These sessions are about Isaac.
No, no. I know.
I know, I know.
But I'm his dad, you know.
Sorry, I know... I know you have...
you have doctor-patient confidentiality
or whatever you call it.
We do.
Sorry. We're late, sorry.
Sorry, we're late. Sorry.
That's okay.
We were just getting to know each other.
- Yeah.
- Thanks for coming.
Oh, it's okay.
Oh. God.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
Okay.
So I thought we could start today
with a bit of a game, all four of us.
What do you think, Isaac?
All right, let's have a look,
shall we?
Escape from Anxiety Island.
Are you okay, Isaac?
Dr Play Bunny's Stress Maze.
Isaac?
Hey, what have you got there?
Where did you get this?
Grandma.
Oh, you shouldn't have this,
it's not yours.
Give it back.
Well, it doesn't belong to you,
sweetheart.
I want it.
Why do you want it, Isaac?
- Give it back!
- Okay.
Don't talk like that.
You never talk like that.
Okay. Give me a cuddle, it's all right,
it's all right.
Okay.
Yeah.
♪ The folks will wonder
'bout the wedding ♪
♪ They won't listen to a word you said ♪
♪ Gonna take
your mama out all night ♪
♪ Yeah, we'll show her
what it's all about ♪
♪ We'll get her jacked up
on some cheap champagne ♪
♪ We'll let... ♪
Hey!
- Hiya.
- Hey, Debbie.
You all right?
Meredith ran out
in front of the car again.
Oh, you are joking.
Meredith Warren, get here now.
Oh, no, she's not here, she...
Did you run in front of Lucy's car?
Don't lie, when was this?
It was...
I'm sorry. I think I made a mistake.
- What?
- Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Lucy.
You saw her, right?
Ravi.
Hey, can you give this
to Detective Dhillon?
Careful it's hot.
Thank you.
You're sad.
Yeah.
Yeah, I am.
I'm very sad.
Do you wanna go and play for a minute?
Come on, go and play on your trampoline.
I need to talk to Detective Dhillon.
Oh.
Is this my fault?
- How could it be?
- I asked you
to find Aiden Stenner.
I should've just left it alone.
- But you were doing your job.
- Was I?
The night of the storm...
that man
was going to kill Aiden Stenner.
- You don't know that.
- I remember it.
I know it didn't happen,
but I remember it.
And it's just as real as any other memory.
You think I'm nuts?
No, I don't.
I think you're...
What? Clairvoyant?
Lots of people claim to know the future.
Make a lot of money from it.
No. This is not like that.
I can still see his body lying...
his eyes staring at nothing.
I didn't know
I was trading one life for another.
You weren't.
There were no trades or bargains.
It's just chaos.
Maybe some people
understand the chaos.
And we stopped him
from killing Aiden Stenner,
and then he told
you someone else was going to die.
It wasn't just someone.
Where did you get that?
Isaac gave it to me.
He's a sweet kid.
They think I should take
compassionate leave.
And what do you think?
I think I should do my job.
Whatever that man is, he's a murderer
and a kidnapper and God knows what else.
He thinks he's righteous.
What makes you say that?
I know him.
I've never met him.
I have never seen his face,
but I know him, Ravi.
Gideon Shepherd?
Hello, Gideon.
Oh, my God.
- Lucy?
- Gideon Shepherd.
- What?
- That's his name.
I just woke up and it was there
in my head, like, I always knew it.
Hold on. Who are you talking about?
The man we're looking for,
his name is Gideon Shepherd.
Ravi?
I'm sorry. I don't understand
what you're telling me.
He's real.
I looked him up.
Gideon Shepherd disappeared in 1967,
age nine,
after stabbing his father to death.
What makes you think this is him?
I don't think. I know.
I remember,
like I remembered Slade and Aiden Stenner.
- Lucy.
- Listen to me.
His mother died five years ago
in Sterling,
but he's got a younger brother, Malcolm.
He's a surgeon and Facebook says
he lives in Cheltenham.
Do you think you could get me his address?
You can't just harass some nobody
because of a cold case from 50 years ago.
But he's not a nobody.
He's the... he's the brother of the man
who abducted my son.
And I didn't call to ask your permission.
Then why did you call?
To see if you wanted to come with me.
Put some music on if you want.
It's a long drive.
We shouldn't be doing this.
Well, nobody asked you to come.
You literally asked me to come.
No, I didn't. I just gave you the option.
That's not what Nick would say.
Sorry. 10:00 and 2:00,
I forgot you're a policeman.
It's okay.
I'll let you off with a caution.
Oi!
What are you doing?
Nobody wants a smoky bride.
- I'm nervous.
- You're addicted.
Oh, come on. You don't even smoke.
Today's a very big day for me.
I'll have you know.
Lots of pressure.
Come on.
No more smoking.
Time to get married.
You okay?
Yeah. Sorry.
- Eyes on the road, Chambers.
- Uh-hmm.
Why couldn't Mum take me out?
Because she's busy
and she's a terrible driver.
- I'll tell her you said that.
- Fine.
Then you'll have to teach yourself
to drive, because I'll be dead.
Now, focus.
Cockpit drill.
- Hmm.
- What's first?
Make sure it's in neutral.
Before that?
Eat a jelly baby.
- Why?
- Sugar.
Helps you concentrate.
Okay.
Let's try that.
Oh, great.
Who is this?
Malcolm Shepherd?
That's me.
DI Ravi Dhillon.
My friend and I would like to ask you
some questions, if that's okay with you.
What's this about?
Can we talk in private?
Do you paint?
Er, my daughter.
As in my daughter paints.
I don't paint my daughter.
You know what I mean.
Is there anywhere to sit down?
No.
You could have that stool.
I meant for you.
He's dead, isn't he?
I'm sorry?
My brother,
you're going to tell me he's dead.
No.
Not as far as I know.
What's this about then?
Are you still in contact
with your brother?
Not exactly.
What do you mean not exactly?
Well, I haven't seen him,
not since he disappeared.
But a few years ago he started calling,
leaving messages,
and I think he was watching us.
What makes you say that?
Same car, out in the lanes,
into the drive.
We told the police but they said
there was nothing to go on.
Was it a red Nissan?
- How do you know that?
- Lucky guess.
When's the last time you heard from him?
My birthday.
When was your birthday?
Three weeks ago.
1:23 AM?
He only ever calls
in the middle of the night
because he knows I won't answer.
Hi, pal.
I don't know if you even listen
to these messages,
I must've left you a hundred by now.
I don't know if you'll hear
from me next year.
I hope so.
I hope one day you'll pick up the phone
and talk to me.
Tell me that you understand.
But I know you never will.
It looks like you've got a good life and
that's... that's... good enough for me.
That's why I did it.
So you could live.
You were the first one I saved.
If you are listening,
then happy birthday,
enjoy 58.
Take care of yourself.
I'm gonna need to hear that again.
Hello?
Isaac.
Waiting for my mummy.
Ms Rogers.
We can't go outside on our own.
Isaac?
Who are you talking to?
The man with the glasses.
Knock, knock.
Hello?
Er, Mike.
Isaac's dad.
Oh. Right. sorry.
I'm Ms Rogers.
Yeah. His mum asked me
to come pick him up.
She said that she called the office.
Did she?
Let me just check that.
They probably sent an email.
Sorry. I know it's awkward,
but it's policy.
Yeah, that's... I understand.
Ah, here we go. Mike. Sorry.
- Can you confirm your surname?
- Stevens.
That's the one.
Sorry about that. Had to be sure.
It's no problem.
Will Isaac's mum be dropping him off
in the morning?
It's just I'd like a word.
You can talk to me, if it's about him.
It is.
It's nothing,
just that he's been drifting more.
I know that's understandable
after what happened but it's...
it's...
He freaks you out, don't he?
No. God, no. I'm not saying that.
No. But he has been having conversations.
- Uh-hmm.
- Talking to people who aren't there.
Yeah. Yeah. He does that, yeah.
Yeah, Lucy's mum's got schizophrenia,
for what it's worth.
Of course, that don't explain
why he can't feel any pain.
You know, he burnt his hand?
- Uh-hmm.
- Yeah?
Apparently, you're not allowed
to call a child a psychopath.
That's what I read.
Neurodiversity can be hard to diagnose
at a young age.
Neurodiversity?
Ah. Well, I guess we'll just...
see what happens
when he gets older, eh?
He may surprise you.
Or murder me in my sleep.
Sorry. That's... that was a bad joke.
Erm, nice to meet you, Ms Rogers.
Yeah. Yeah. You too.
Could you send me that recording?
I really can't.
It's evidence.
Are you serious?
I could be in a lot of trouble already.
Well, can I listen to it
one last time?
Hi, pal.
I don't know if you even listen
to these messages.
I must've left you a hundred by now.
I hope...
one day you'll pick up the phone...
Stop, stop, stop.
Back.
Hi, pal.
What is it?
- There's a train close by.
- I don't know if you listen
to these messages.
I must've left you a hundred by now.
I hope one day you'll pick up the phone.
- Maybe.
- No. I used to live by a train line.
Trust me, I know that sound.
So he's by the tracks.
Doesn't exactly narrow it down.
No. There's not many places
a train sounds its horn.
Tunnels, level crossings.
If we assume he's still in the area, say,
a hundred mile radius,
not many trains passing those points
at 1:23 in the morning,
give or take a couple of minutes.
It's worth a try, I guess.
All we need is a railway map
and a train schedule.
That's some good work, Detective Chambers.
Sorry.
It's okay.
I'll, erm, I'll send you the recording.
Amazing.
Hello?
Hey.
Having fun?
Yeah. Learned all about football,
haven't you, mate?
Hey.
Cuddle for Mummy.
Where were you?
Lost track of time. Sorry.
Yeah? Lost, er,
lost track of time where?
Just had some errands to run.
What does it matter?
It doesn't. Why is it secret?
It's not a secret.
I just don't want to tell you.
That's what a secret is.
Has Isaac had dinner?
Er, yes, yes.
Eaten like a prince, this boy.
He's had sausage pasta,
just like we used to make.
There's, erm, there's some left
in the pot if you want some.
Yeah. And then I gave him some ice cream.
Hope that's okay.
We don't have any ice cream.
Er, I bought him
some strawberry ice cream.
That's his favourite, is that right?
What?
I was in Cheltenham.
In Cheltenham?
With Ravi... DI Dhillon. We...
er, we're working
on something together.
You... you're working on something
with the police?
The man that took Isaac...
is called Gideon Shepherd.
We spoke with his brother today.
I'm sorry. What?
He gave us a lead.
A lead?
Lucy, this guy's... this guy...
this guy's a serial killer.
What are you thinking?
I'm thinking I need this to end.
- I need it to be over.
- It is over.
We've got our son back.
He's safe.
That's all that matters.
What?
Nothing.
Just... tell me what it is
that would make this better.
Whatever you want me to do, I'll do it.
You want me to, erm,
hunt him down on the street?
'Cause I will.
I've got an old BB gun in my garage.
I just want everything
to be normal again, Mike.
Can you do that? Can you make it normal?
You're not normal, Lucy Stevens.
That's why I love you.
But if that's what you want,
I will try.
Great.
Sausage pasta it is.
If your mum asks,
I gave you strawberry ice cream, okay?
Okay.
Good boy.
Oh, my God.
Take me through it again.
Look, I know it's flimsy.
I just want you to hear yourself.
The logic is sound.
Best-case scenario,
this is the man that murdered
Shane Fisher and Harold Slade.
This is the man
who abducted Isaac Stephens,
and Jonah Taylor,
and fuck knows how many other kids.
Worst-case, it's not him...
but you catch a murderer
who's evaded arrest
for more than 50 years.
It's win-win.
- Okay.
- Okay, what?
Okay. I'll pass it up to MCS.
So it gets buried in someone's in-tray?
I'll mark it as urgent, okay?
But I need you to get out of here.
- Nick wouldn't have wanted this for you.
- Oh, fuck you.
I'm sorry.
Slam the door on the way out
if it makes you feel better.
Hi.
I think I found him.
There's an abandoned repair yard
outside Melwood.
Fits with the timings on the message.
You were right.
So what now?
My boss said he'll pass it on
to Major Crimes.
What does that mean?
It means we're on our own.
You're gonna do something?
He kills people, Lucy.
He kills people and I know where he is.
I can stop him.
No. You... you can't.
You're gonna get hurt.
People are already getting hurt.
No one's gonna act on this unless I do.
- Ravi.
- I'll keep you updated.
Ravi, please listen...
Come on. Come on. Come on. Please.
Are you okay?
This is so stupid. Why am I nervous?
I have to walk into a room,
say some words, kiss him,
and then walk back out.
- I mean...
- Gross.
What could go wrong?
Well, you could fart.
My aunt farted at the altar.
Apparently, it's all anyone remembers.
Thanks, Rhia.
Are you sure you still want to marry him?
I mean, he did wet the bed
until he was eight.
Yes, you have mentioned that.
And his favourite film
is Beauty and the Beast.
He says it's Goodfellas
but it's Beauty and the Beast.
Save it for the speech.
Your funeral.
For the record,
I think you're making a huge mistake.
Thanks, mate.
Love you.
Gross.
- Okay.
- Uh-hmm.
Turn it off please.
What's your name?
Connor.
Connor what?
Connor Lawson.
How long have you been here,
Connor Lawson?
I don't know.
We have to go. Come on. Quickly.
Get as far away from here as possible.
Go. Now.
You in here, Dhillon?
I wasn't gonna kill him.
That wasn't the plan.
But you shouldn't have come.
I've had this fight before.
You won't win.
Dhillon, listen to me.
I can't let you stop me
but I can let you live.
Just stay down. Stay down.
Leave me alone!
I'm sorry.
Ambulance.
- Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot. Ow.
- Are you okay?
Yeah. That is hot. Don't touch that.
That's because it's been in the oven
for eight hours.
It's because you need new oven gloves.
We need new oven gloves.
Do you need a hand?
Er, no, no.
You stay there. I got it covered.
Hi.
What are you doing tonight?
Mike's cooking dinner.
Why?
He's still refusing a lawyer.
- Has he said anything?
- Nothing.
Three days and hardly a word.
Er, are you still in hospital?
They let me out. Good behaviour.
He asked to see me.
He said he'd explain everything,
but not to me, not to my colleagues.
He said he only wants to talk
to Lucy Chambers.
Lucy?
Yeah.
How quickly can you eat dinner?
Are you gonna sit down?
What's funny?
Nothing. Sorry. Nothing.
You ever been in this room before?
No.
But you feel like you have?
Why would I?
Déjà vu.
They say it's like a short circuit
in the brain.
Your sense of a moment plays
through your memory centre.
Makes you feel
like you've experienced all this before.
Jesus.
What the fuck do you want?
You should have listened.
I wish you'd listened.
I could have stopped the chaos.
But now you blame me.
You blame me because that's easier
than blaming yourself.
Blaming myself for what?
What happened after the storm.
I never met your partner
but I read his obituary.
He seemed like a good man.
I'm not trying to goad you.
We all have people we care about.
Who do you care about?
Your brother maybe?
We spoke to Malcolm. Did you know that?
He seems like a good man too.
Makes me wonder how you ended up this way.
Same upbringing, same mother, same father.
You left your brother messages.
Malcolm's got nothing to do with this.
You leave him alone. You understand?
- You leave him alone.
- You said you did it for him.
Was Malcolm the reason
you murdered your father?
My father was the reason
I murdered my father.
Did he do something to Malcolm?
- Did he hurt him? Was he cruel?
- You've got absolutely no fucking idea...
- what you are talking about?
- Why did you murder him, Gideon?
Because he murdered me first.
What did you say?
All right.
You might want to record this.