Previously on Prison Break:
- What are the charges?
- Attempted murder.
He's also arraigned for the murder
of his mother and his stepfather.
Don't look at me like I'm some con.
You're as crooked as scoliosis.
I don't get caught.
This is as far as you go.
- Come on, bro.
- You and I, we're not bros.
When were you planning on
telling us about the money?
- What money?
- Five million dollars...
...that Westmoreland
planted in the desert in Utah.
I found Steadman.
I'm with him now, Linc. He's alive.
What? You found Steadman?
Oh, my God.
My hand has been in that box
for hours now. It is dying.
- I can promise you nothing.
- Story of my life.
- And these?
- The keys to a car that's waiting for us.
- A couple hundred yards.
- That a two-of-us or a five-of-us?
- That's a two-of-us.
- We got company.
How did he know?
MAHONE. It is only a matter of
time before we know everything...
...that is in Scofield's head.
Where he plans to run to,
how he plans to get there.
So when the time comes
that he does get there...
...we'll be waiting for him.
Canadian and Mexican
border patrols have the mug shots.
BORTAC's on high alert.
See if we can get Mexican border patrol
to set up checkpoints 50 miles in.
The warden over at Fox River
called, asked to be kept in the loop.
- What should I tell him?
- That he's no longer in it.
That info that you asked for
is on your desk when you get in.
Thank you.
What's the plan, man?
No bars on these
doors. Do what you like.
With what?
We're supposed to be in Mexico,
sipping on margaritas...
...waiting for the heat to dip.
That was the plan.
See? they just used us to dig, right?
We're gophers.
- Where's Michael?
- He'll be here.
Okay. You know what, Sucre?
Maybe you and I should go and get that
$5 million, know what I'm saying?
- It's sitting there in Tooele, ready to get.
- You wanna stay, shut your mouth.
- You've got one more time to touch me.
- Guys, chill.
- What?
- Hey!
Relax.
Honey, are you sure
you packed everything?
Yummy.
Mm.
Our photos are in the paper.
They're all over the news.
Yeah, and you didn't see that coming?
- What's so funny?
- The two of you. Cracks me up.
Here's to amateur hour.
- What do you say?
- Yeah, yuk it up, funnyman.
Last supper, boys.
This is the part where we say goodbye.
It's not much.
It's enough to get you started.
- Hey...
- No.
- I'm not telling you where Fibonacci is.
- Well, I didn't ask.
I only ask for a quarter
for a phone call.
Make four.
Thank you.
I wonder what happened
to the other guys.
They all had a head start.
Except for T-Bag.
Yeah, he was bleeding pretty bad.
Think he's dead?
Are you done?
- No, I still have to clean it.
- But you're done?
Yes.
It's time to move.
We got everything we need.
Just a quick stop in Utah
and then we're off to Mexico.
L.J. has a hearing today
to determine if he gets tried as an adult.
I can get him.
- It's not the right time.
- When will it be?
After we go to Mexico.
After we're off the news.
They framed him for a double homicide.
Soon as he loses his hearing,
they're gonna ship him out.
So today in the courthouse
is my only chance to get him.
They took Veronica.
They're not gonna take my son.
I know.
I would never leave L.J. behind.
But we can't do this now.
There's no plan in place.
Believe me, I know that courthouse.
I've been there more times
than I can remember.
The person guarding him's the bailiff.
He carries Mace and a stick.
So you're gonna bum-rush
the courthouse. That's your plan.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
Y'all, we're headed out, man.
Well, good luck to everyone.
- Stay out of trouble.
- Yeah.
This is it, papi.
- I hope you find the girl, buddy.
- She's all I have.
I'll die trying.
- Good luck.
- Yeah, you be easy, man.
Maybe we'll see each other again.
You never know, Michael.
You never know.
Tell me everything you know
about the courthouse.
- You get any sleep?
- Couple hours.
Eight of them.
I still can't believe it.
Exhibit A why you don't let women
work in the military or the police force...
...especially inside a male prison.
Because look what you get.
Dr. Sweetcheeks leaves the door open
for Scofield...
- ...and here we are.
- Sounds like there's more to the escape--
If Tancredi doesn't leave
her office door unlocked...
...those eight dirtbags
would be in the SHU right now, okay?
- Bottom line!
- Brad.
- Any update?
- None.
They were last seen
at that cemetery in Oswego.
- We'll get them.
- They'll get them.
- It's been handed to the FBI.
- Doesn't mean we can't work it.
It does, actually.
- You and I are pulled off the pursuit.
- Why?
We're going to find out shortly.
We have to report to DOC headquarters.
- I will meet you there.
- Sir, we can get these guys.
- Give me a couple days and I swear I--
- Brad.
We've got to go.
No family with Patoshik? Nothing?
Yeah. Until about four
years ago, when he killed them all.
Updated rap sheet on Apolskis.
Take a look when you get a chance.
You have to use the key
that we keep in the grill because that's--
Man, I'm so sorry.
It's my bad. My bad, bro.
I'm sorry.
"Scott Kolbrenner."
It's this one here.
Don't touch the radio.
Hi. I'm with the Des Moies Herald,
I'm covering the L.J. Burrows hearing.
What time's that start today?
Come on.
Thank you. Three o'clock.
The hearing lasts a half-hour max.
He'll be taken down to Transport Bay
at 10 till to catch the 4:00 van.
How do we get close to him?
Well, when I was locked up, I had
nothing to do except study the briefs.
Nick Savrinn's bar number
was on the front page of every one.
We wanna talk to L.J., we--
- We pose as one of his attorneys.
- Yeah.
Hogwash. That is absolute hogwash.
Please answer the question.
How was Scofield able
to have exclusive access to you...
...pull a shank on you
and bind you to your chair?
The warden of the penitentiary.
I trusted him.
Obviously, he betrayed that trust.
Officer Bellick...
...is it true that almost all the inmates
who either escaped or tried to escape...
- ...worked in Prison Industries?
- That's right.
Why did these inmates
have so much time...
...to dig a hole in the floor
of the guards' room...
- ...while working Prison Industries?
- I can answer that.
If any of you
have ever worked a day in a prison...
...you would know
since an inmate gets 19 cents an hour...
...some are bound to drag their feet.
Officer Bellick...
...is it true you sold the right to run
Prison Industries to the highest bidder?
- No. Who the hell told you that?
- This is unbelievable.
While we're wasting time in here,
there are eight convicts out there--
Were you employed at Fox
River as a correctional officer, Mr. Geary?
- Yep.
- Yeah...
...until he was fired
for shaking down inmates.
That'll be your last outburst, officer.
Were you aware of any arrangement
Officer Bellick had...
...with any inmate
regarding Prison Industries?
Yeah, he sold it to John Abruzzi.
John Abruzzi,
who is one of the escaped convicts?
Yep.
We'll get other C.O.'s to
substantiate this if we have to...
...so I'm giving you one chance
to get in front of it.
Did you sell Prison Industries
to John Abruzzi?
Yes or no?
- Yes. But at no time was I aware of--
That'll be all, Officer Bellick.
That will be all.
Warden, you and Officer Bellick
can step out into the hallway.
We'll call for you
when we've reached a decision.
I'm gonna get some coffee.
Well, I did my best
under the circumstances.
The good news, sir,
is you had the hand iced...
...so I was able to restore blood flow
and the bones are pinned.
However, I recommend
you get medical attention ASAP.
Meanwhile, some aspirin. It'll help
thin the blood and avoid clotting.
Antibiotics, some painkillers.
I usually tell the owner of the dog,
cat, whatever...
...to coat them with peanut butter
so they're easier to chew.
- But obviously, in your case--
- You did one hell of a job, doc.
Well, thank you.
Well, it's okay for you to leave now.
Oh, I'm leaving.
- And you're not.
- What?
- You heard me.
- Look, sir, I haven't seen anything...
...and I won't tell anyone.
You know, I fell for
that bill of goods once before.
Never again.
- Sir, I swear to God I will tell nobody.
- You would.
And I would die in prison.
- Please, please, please.
- Shh. Shh.
Now, you did me a solid,
so I'm gonna return the favor.
This can go down humanely
if you don't fight.
But if you pull a stunt like that again,
it's gonna get inhumane right quick.
Your call.
But one way or another...
...I am putting you down, doc.
- Lincoln Burrows Jr.?
- Yeah.
In here. You got a visitor.
You must be L.J.
Agent Mahone, FBI. Thank you.
Please.
I'm assuming you've heard.
Yeah.
I have to tell you,
what your dad and uncle pulled off...
Very impressive.
I've been doing this 14 years...
...and most escapes can be attributed
to dumb luck or brute force.
The level of planning and sophistication
that went into this one...
...and eight guys got out...
I really do, professionally speaking...
...have a lot of admiration
for Lincoln and Michael.
Cool. Now we're buddies.
What do you need?
Help me bring them in peacefully.
I don't know where they are.
- I don't know where they're going.
- There's another way you can help.
- How?
- Go on TV.
I can have a camera crew down here
in a half an hour.
You know what, man?
The murder charge they put on my dad...
...the two murder charges
they put on me...
...everything's been a setup,
coming from way up top.
So the fact that you work
for the government...
I got nothing to say.
I'll give you the same advice you'd get
from the guy working at the deli.
Start thinking about yourself now.
In fact, the sooner the better,
because no one...
...not your father, L.J., not your uncle...
...is going to do your time.
And at 16 years old,
you're looking at a long stretch.
How much time you get,
where you serve it...
...who your cellmate might be.
You need to start thinking
about yourself now.
I want your dad, I want your uncle,
and I'm willing to deal.
Don't wait and let someone else
get the reward.
What's up?
Hey, man, you look familiar.
Did you rush Sig Ep last semester?
- Sig what?
- Sig Ep.
- No.
- Next in line.
Where to?
Utah.
How we doing here?
Nothing until tomorrow.
All right, yo, I got 45 bucks.
How far will that get me?
Nick Savrinn. Bar number is 56437.
I got a call time with my client,
L.J. Burrows.
- Hello.
- Know who this is?
Yeah.
Yeah, Nick Savrinn.
How you holding up?
Doing what I can do.
How about you?
I'm worried about you.
- Sorry about what you're going through.
- Thanks.
Word is after this hearing, because of
my dad being so high-profile, they're--
They're shipping me to an adult facility
in Kingman, Arizona.
Yeah, well,
hopefully that ain't gonna happen.
You hear from Veronica today?
She didn't show up. They gave me
some court-appointed clown.
No, I haven't heard from her.
Hey, this fed came by
and talked to me today.
Yeah?
He wanted me to help try
in getting my dad to turn himself in.
Well, knowing your dad,
I doubt that's gonna happen.
Listen up, this is real important.
- All right.
- On the third, look out for Otis Wright.
You got that?
On the third, look out for Otis Wright.
Until then, keep your head up.
- What?
- Just remember that.
I'm gonna do everything I can
to get you out.
Hey, Nick.
If you talk to my dad...
...tell him no matter what, I love him.
- Hey.
- Did you get him?
- Let's do this.
We got one more stop.
There is a belief in my religion
which I know to be true...
...and it applies to everyone,
Hindu or not.
The acts we commit in this life
determine where we go in the next.
And he who commits evil
can never hope for eternal happiness.
Never been a goal of mine, doc.
I'm more a here-and-now type.
I'll tell you something I know is true.
The Indians here,
the tomahawk variety...
...some of them believe--
Well, used to believe, before most
of them were slaughtered.
--That when a warrior
kills another in battle...
...he absorbs
that fallen warrior's spirit.
So this isn't the end for you, doc.
You're with me now.
And how are you doing this fine day?
Uh...
I'm great. How are you?
Couldn't be better. Anything
in particular I can help you find?
Just looking. Thanks.
Well, if you need any assistance,
just give a holler.
- How are we this fine day?
- Great.
- Can I help you find anything?
- I'm good, thanks.
Hey, we gotta go.
- I just need to pay up.
- Now.
How are you today, officer?
Yeah, they were right...
Well, they were right back here.
We can make it
to the courthouse on foot.
You don't understand.
Everything is in that car.
Forget the damn car.
We don't have time.
Come on, man, let's go.
- Hi.
It is the finding
of this panel, Warden Pope...
...you'll be docked two weeks,
placed on three months' probation.
Officer Brad Bellick...
...will be terminated,
effective immediately.
Mr. Bellick, you can retrieve whatever
belongings you may have from Fox River.
That'll be all.
I've worked at Fox River
since I was 18 years old.
Being a C.O. is my life.
And we appreciate that.
We could've saved a lot of time
if you would've just told us...
...that this was gonna be a railroad.
- That'll be all.
- There is only one person responsible...
...for this escape.
His name is Michael Scofield.
It's not Officer Bellick. It's not me!
But you need a fall guy, fine.
But you're not gonna be
just taking Officer Bellick's job.
Because even though I am not proud
of many of his actions...
...it will be a cold day in hell when
I turn my back on one of my own men.
I quit.
That will be all.
If this thing doesn't work out and
you end up going back to Fox River...
...I ain't coming to get you.
I mean, you are the brains
and I am the brute.
Seriously, Michael,
you don't have to do this.
Let's go.
We're good.
You got a call from Nick Savrinn
earlier today. What was that all about?
He's my attorney. That's privileged.
That's odd, because Nick Savrinn
was found dead in his apartment...
...an hour before that call came into you.
L.J., this is important.
- . All right.
- On the third, look out for Otis Wright.
You got that?
For someone who's convinced
the government is capable...
...of so many underhanded things, you
sure are playing fast and loose with me.
What are you gonna do, throw
another fake murder charge on me?
- Who's Otis Wright?
- I have no idea.
I think you do. And if you don't tell me,
after you're convicted...
...I will be in that courtroom when you're
sentenced, and I'll hang you out to dry.
Take it to the bank.
Yeah, put me in touch with
the prosecutor in the L.J. Burrows case.
I want a meeting.
On the third, look out for Otis Wright.
Until then, keep your head up.
Otis Wright.
- Let's go.
- Hold on.
- Move it.
I'll escort the boy.
Otis Wright.
Otis elevator on the right.
What is he planning?
Keep it in the holster
and no one gets hurt.
Keep it in the holster.
All right. L.J., hit stop.
He's coming with us, so just stay cool.
Stay cool.
Hey, buddy, give me his gun.
Hey, hey.
L.J., give me your hand.
Thattaboy. Come on.
Hey, back off. Back off. Back off.
You're not shooting anybody.
Neither are you.
Give yourself up and your kid can walk.
That's the only way he's getting out
of this place. It's the only way.
Dad.
Dad!
- Dad, you gotta let me go.
- No.
Dad.
You gotta let me go.
Up there. Scofield is in the building.
Take him.
You guys, go. Cover that way.
Scofield and Burrows are in the building.
Come on.
- Freeze!
- Don't move!
- Truck.
- Stop or we will shoot.
Stop!
Two suspects heading south on Liberty.
Bradley?
Yeah, Ma?
What are you doing home so early?
Well, I had to take...
...my personal days, you know,
before they went away.
Shouldn't you be looking
for the convicts?
Well, they got somebody else
doing that, Ma.
You okay?
I'm good.
Okay.
Whoa.
All right.
We should break
a bottle of champagne across its bow.
If you're intending to get this home
for your anniversary tonight...
- ...I wouldn't recommend it.
- No.
Listen, I want you to know, I...
Well, I feel very fortunate
to have met you.
I'm breaking out.
And you're gonna make sure
my brother goes with me.
Thank you for calling AutoStar, Dr. Gudat.
- Am I pronouncing that correctly?
- Uh...
- Dead on.
- How can I help you today?
I need directions.
- Where to, sir?
- Utah.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Are you Scott Kolbrenner?
I am, yeah.
You must be Debra Jean.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Yeah, same here.
I was almost ready to leave
when you called.
No one else responded.
I guess there's not a lot of Utah people
out here. Are you from there?
No, I just, you know...
I'm headed out there
to collect an inheritance.
- My grandpa died.
- Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
It's all right.
He went out with his boots on.
So where's your stuff?
Uh... I mailed it yesterday.
Mailed it? I've never heard of that.
You don't wanna lug it around.
Plus, I got a boy who works for UPS.
So he hooked it up.
So you wanna bounce?
Okay. I'm parked out front.
Bradley?
Yeah, Ma?
They just announced the rewards
on the TV.
- What reward?
- The convicts.
For the convicts.
The ones who escaped.
- How much?
- A hundred thousand dollars apiece.
Three hundred thousand for the animal
who killed President Reynolds' brother.
Every whacko in the country's
gonna be after those bums now...
...wouldn't you say?
Police!
Step out of the vehicle
with your hands up.
- We gotta move.
- I can't.
Oh!
Oh, my God.
I failed him.
I sure hope you packed a lunch.
It's gonna be a long ride to Arizona.
Move your ass.
Get men in all the area hospitals.
Wherever they are, one's bleeding good.
Which means they either come to us
or they die.