Previously on Prison Break:
A very credible witness has just come
forward and he's willing to testify.
He'll corroborate everything
you've said about this conspiracy.
Who?
How much do you know
about Sona, Mr. Kim?
Only what I've been given clearance on.
There's been a change in strategy.
- How much further would I have to go?
- For this you only have to go to Panama.
- I didn't know you'd be here.
- You e-mailed me, said T-Bag was here.
- It's on the website.
- I didn't write on no website.
- This is looking more like a setup.
- He's got Maricruz locked away.
Either I help him get the money
or she's dead.
Freeze, Bagwell!
Theodore Bagwell. He's the one
you want for that dead chick in there.
Sucre, you better pull it together.
Oh, God!
Go get the money. Please.
Who you fooling?
You ain't gonna kill me,
Mr. Michelangelo.
You ain't got it in you.
- Linc?
- Hello, Michael.
What do you want, Alex?
Bring me the money. Bring me the boat.
You are out of your mind.
We have something
the other person needs.
Your brother for your plan.
Five minutes. That's what you have.
I didn't kill that man.
I'm getting you out of here.
I got three Weeks.
MICHAEL.. Just have a little faith.
I did everything I could.
I know you did.
Señor.
- Chicle?
- No.
Soda? Beer, my friend.
Spleef? Magic mushrooms.
Burst your brain, split it wide open.
I'm your man, man.
Magic Mystery Tour,
right here in this box.
If I don't got it, I can get it.
Beat it.
So you gonna do the right thing?
Right for who, Alex?
You've lost, Michael.
That's what you've done here.
You'll lose a whole lot more unless
you tell me right here and right now...
...you're gonna bring me the money,
you're gonna bring me the boat.
And you'll just let my brother go.
Yeah.
Just like you let Tweener go
and Abruzzi and Haywire.
Things are different now.
- Really?
- Yeah.
The people I was working for,
they kind of, uh, sold me down the river.
Now I just wanna go out to sea.
That's funny.
I'll have to remember that one.
I face more prison time than you.
Sort of jumped ahead of you a few
spots on the public enemy list.
You're my way to freedom, Michael,
and I'm yours.
We both know
what the other one's capable of.
Let's treat each other with respect here.
No games, no bluffing.
Just two guys
doing each other a favor.
What do you say?
Where are you?
Mira Flores shipping docks,
just outside of Panama City.
It's a big warehouse
right on the water.
That's a long ways.
It'll take me at least 24 hours
to get there.
Well, then, I'd get moving.
How's it feel being on the run?
- I'll survive.
- Not if they catch you.
They'll send you to the chair.
You think that's ironic?
It'd be justice.
Mr. Kim. Alex Mahone.
Call me.
Oh, justice will be served.
What I'm about to divulge to you
will in all likelihood get me killed.
- Actually, I guarantee it.
- Then why are you doing it?
Because this was supposed to be
about country, about loyalty...
...about what's right, but it wasn't.
Because I wronged people
who should not have been wronged.
Those orders were given
by Caroline Reynolds...
...who was vice president at the time.
Acting on those orders,
I planted evidence.
I procured a body, I lured Lincoln Burrows
into that parking garage that evening...
...under the auspices of a different hit.
From the ground up, we framed him.
Perfect.
See, Lincoln Burrows gets executed,
people forget about Terrence Steadman...
...the controversy surrounding him
and the presidency.
And nobody ever knows
about the Company.
Yes, which is a shadowy cabal
of corporations...
...that pretty much influence everything
that happens in this country.
But I fail to see how any of this
is relevant to Sara Tancredi...
...and the fact that she aided and
abetted, that she jumped bail.
She did so because she feared
for her life, which was appropriate...
...as I had orders to kill her.
Hey.
You still in the magic business?
- What's your name?
- Chaco.
It's all here.
Everything Mr. Kellerman said
is corroborated in these documents.
In light of this evidence,
my question, I guess to you...
...is whether your time
and resources are best spent...
...in pursuing charges
against Dr. Tancredi.
No. My office will drop all charges
effective immediately.
But, Your Honor, I would like
to devote my time and attention...
...in prosecuting this man,
Mr. Kellerman.
Officer.
I literally don't even know
what to say to you.
It was good knowing you, Sara.
- Yeah?
- Where are we?
I'm in Panama. Nice place.
Good weather. Cool breeze.
Where are we with the brothers?
When you get them, I wanna
come down there for confirmation.
I suggest you get on a plane.
By the time you get here...
...I'll have Scofield and Burrows
where you want them.
And then this whole thing is over.
Sara, it's me.
It's a strange thing...
...leaving a message for someone
you know is never gonna get it.
I can only assume the worst...
...so this'll be the last message
I'll leave for you.
I just wanted you to know
that I made it.
But it's no good without you.
Anyway, remember when I...?
Remember when I told you
about those 50-cent beers...
...in Baja at happy hour?
Well, they're even cheaper down here.
And if by some miracle
you do get this...
...I need you to listen close.
Sara. Sara, I suggest
we get you out of here.
It's gonna be a media circus outside
and it'll only get bigger. Let's go.
Sure.
Larger unexpected fireworks at the trial
of Dr. Sara Tancredi in Chicago today.
New testimony has implicated
that former President Reynolds...
...was complicit in the falsification of
her brother Terrence Steadman's death.
The fallout from all this,
the purported killer...
...Lincoln Burrows, who's led
the country on a nationwide manhunt...
...will be exonerated of all charges
effective immediately.
Oh, my God, Bruce.
Lincoln's a free man.
Michael left me a message.
Okay. My God. Um...
He doesn't know.
He's still planning on running.
Uh...
Come on, Michael. Come on,
come on, come on.
Let me do the intro.
Fine. Then I'll do the talking.
Okay, I gotta go to him.
- What's that, about 3000 miles?
- It is.
We're gonna have to swing by my hotel,
and you'll have to get me to the airport.
He's gotta know he doesn't have to run.
What he's doing is gonna get him killed.
The stars are finally aligning, sir.
Mahone's got Burrows.
Scofield's on his way.
I will make it happen.
I am going down there myself.
Uh, I assume we both know
which one that is.
I will call you when I get down there.
I just-- I want you to listen
really, really close, okay?
- Alex, Alex, slow down.
- Okay, okay, fine.
We talked about getting back together,
about giving it another shot.
Yes, and I said that maybe we could.
- Alex?
- What about Columbia?
- Cartegena?
- Go there?
Well, you got summer break
coming up, don't you?
- Same with Cam?
- Yeah. But--
Listen, I'm not far from there
right now...
...and I was thinking, why not just stick
around and have you guys come down?
I mean, you always wanted to go,
didn't you?
- Visit the homeland?
- Yes, but you didn't.
Yeah, but I do now.
Uh...
Yeah. I mean, I suppose I could,
we could maybe do two weeks...
...at the end of the summer, or--
- Is that a yes? That's a yes, right?
- Yes, yes.
Great coffee, great beaches,
wildlife parks for Cam and--
Look, it might not work out.
You've gotta be prepared for that. I--
It can't be like it was before.
It will never be like before.
I know what's important now.
I know what matters.
Well, I guess I could look online.
I don't know. I should go.
Just come be with me, Pam.
Be with me.
Hey, you got nothing
to worry about, okay?
It's you I'm marrying.
Señor Gonzales.
U.S. Embassy operator.
I'm looking for a friend.
A missing American friend.
He could be in the hospital.
He could be in jail.
Name?
Bellick. Brad Bellick.
Hey! Hey, do I get
to call my lawyer or what?!
What are you, savages down here?
I get to call my lawyer or something.
Freaking banana benders.
Finally! That's him!
That's the guy. He's the one
that killed that girl. Good job, guys.
Hey. Hey, aren't you gonna
release me now?
Hey.
Hey!
- You're busted.
- Am I?
- Where's the money?
- Pretty Boy's got it.
He's out there with a royal flush, and
you're in here with a busted straight.
- That hardly seems right, does it?
- Your hand don't look much better.
Maybe I got an ace up my sleeve.
You know something I don't?
You should rest your leg, boss.
I was told we could make a deal.
You're a long ways from home, boy.
There ain't no deal for you here.
You haven't heard
what I have to offer.
A guy looking like you do,
coming here?
Only thing you offering is jail time.
I'm not a cop.
Check online.
Type in Michael Scofield.
That means nothing to me.
Could mean a hundred grand.
This takes longer than 30 seconds,
you're in the canal.
Bait for the catfish.
Hey.
You just gave me a hundred thousand
reasons to turn you in.
That's true.
I guess I'll just have to give you
a few more not to.
You know I'm innocent.
- Yeah, probably.
- And yet you don't care.
I don't care about anything
other than getting my life back, no.
Your wife know who you really are?
Hey, you know how it is.
Good men doing bad things
because of circumstance.
I'd call her back if I were you.
Tell her to forget you were ever born.
Oh, you would, would you?
Stop the cancer
from your life spreading to theirs.
Cancer of my life?
I wouldn't be begging her to meet me
in this third-world dump...
...if it weren't for you and your life.
There's no way out of this for you.
For any of us.
For me, there is.
- How much of it you spend?
- A hundred thousand. Two.
Of course, down here,
be more like a million.
Be Louis XIV for a sum like that.
The Sun King of Panama.
You ain't gonna be seeing
much sun now.
Hmm. I don't know.
You know, Bagwell, out of all
the guys, all eight of them...
...you were the guy I was hoping
would go down in a blaze of gunfire.
Why don't you give me
your best shot? Finish the job.
Maybe I will.
That Siamese cat smile just makes me
wanna open you up that much more.
It's Cheshire. Cheshire cat smile.
I'm free?
Hey.
Hey, what the hell is this?
Hey, wait, wait a minute.
What about him?
He's the one that did it.
What's that mean? Buena suerte?
What does that mean?
Good luck.
Bellick.
Bellick!
Where is my Maricruz?
Where is she?
You wanna know where she is,
find a way to get me out of this!
Get me out of here!
Sucre, get me out of this! Get me out!
Maricruz.
Michael, that's a beautiful boat.
Just promise you'll change the name
when you take it.
I don't think my mother
would have approved of you.
Consider it done. Come on.
- Uncuff me.
- No, not yet.
So is this the part
where you go back on your word?
Hands up, hands up.
No.
As of now, they want you alive.
Why?
That's a good question.
Figure it out some day, on your
own time. Where's the money?
- Cut him loose.
- No.
Come on, Alex.
You already got the boat.
- Show a little good faith.
- The money.
I want--
- Yeah?
- I'm here. Where are you?
I'm inside the warehouse.
I'll be right there.
Here we go.
- Hello?
- Hello.
- You speak English?
- Yes, sir. Can I help you?
- Yes, yes. Mira Flores docks.
- Everything all right?
- Yes. There's been a murder.
- Are you in danger?
A well-dressed Asian man
has just been shot by two Americans.
- We'll send a car right away.
- Come. Yes, come.
So you kill him and frame us.
Why?
So everyone will leave me alone.
Because that's all I want.
That, and the money.
- It's not gonna happen, Alex. Let him go.
- Give me the money.
- Let him go.
- Give me the money!
I am dumbfounded.
Well, don't be shy. They're all yours.
You said you'd have them right
where we wanted them.
This isn't right where we want them.
Well, that's your job now.
- Oh.
- This is as far as I go.
Or is it something else?
Another reason we're all here?
Like that.
- Like a double-cross.
- Yeah, just like that. Say goodbye.
Great minds think alike, eh, Alex?
Okay, come on, come on.
Once seated, your four-piece
will be mounted to the floor-mount.
During transport,
do not speak to either I, myself--
I know the drill.
Get in.
- So, what have we got, 30 minutes?
- Yeah, something like that.
- Why didn't you take the freeway?
- Rush hour.
- Oh, hell.
- What?
- The engine light just came on.
- It just got serviced at motor pool.
Yeah. We've gotta pull over
just to make sure.
All right, I'll check it out.
In the French Resistance, it was
a high honor to face a Nazi firing squad.
- Thought I told you to be quiet.
- Meant you did your job.
The highest honor was to smile
when they shot you.
Took you long enough.
Lake Gatun. Eastern canal.
Approaches to Cartegena.
Twenty-seven-fifty.
What's that crossing take?
Two days
if you're under full sail all the time.
Good time of year to be down here.
No storms. Nothing.
Had enough storms recently.
- Enjoy it. It's a beautiful crossing.
Ha-ha. I plan to.
This boat here. Who does it belong to?
Señor?
We got a call that this boat was used
in some illegal trafficking.
It's the wrong boat, pal.
You can check it if you want to, but--
- Hey, you can't just go to--
- Hey, this is Panama, friend.
Get acquainted with the law, huh?
- I--
Coca.
Yes, I definitely think you need
to get acquainted with it.
Chico.
Well, I...
- You think they got him?
- It's a pretty singular boat.
That's a lot of coke to be
carrying around. If you were at the helm--
I'd be doing some serious time.
Ten years, minimum.
Yeah, you would. We lost the boat.
At least we got dead man's money.
It's our ticket
to the rest of our lives...
...minus what I'm sending
Westmoreland's daughter.
Hey.
- You showed up.
- We had a deal.
- That's my brother.
- Hey.
This way.
So we get out of here
and we never look back.
We never look back.
I wanna thank you, Michael,
for everything.
You're welcome.
It's the best I could do
with the money you gave me.
That'll work.
- She's very pretty.
- She'll get us where we need to go?
Not the boat, señor.
So I got your message.
Thank God I found you guys.
Thank God is right.
Michael, Lincoln's free.
What?
Uh, it's all over the news.
Paul Kellerman came forward.
And he had everything documented
and he made a full confession.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
- Everything?
- Everything. All charges.
Whoa.
What a...
Man, what a-- No more...
It means you don't
have to run anymore.
What about Michael?
Uh, a friend of my father's
is getting into it...
...but he's pretty confident
that under the circumstances...
...nobody's gonna pursue you on this.
I need a drink.
I'll go see what I can find.
Here.
Help me out of this.
We did it, Linc.
- We did it.
- Yeah.
No.
You almost did it.
You want the money?
Take the money. Take it.
You think this is about the money?
Pocket change? Like 5 million?
Then what is it about?
My brother's been exonerated.
The president stepped down.
We're not a threat anymore. It's over.
You may be done with us, but that
doesn't mean we're done with you.
- The police are on their way.
- This started with me.
- Let my brother go.
- Oh, that's sweet, that's sweet.
You don't hear that much anymore,
that sort of fidelity in families.
Two brothers who will go to the ends
of the earth for each other.
Too bad only one of you will survive.
No!
We gotta go.
My men have orders to fire if you
don't come out with your hands first.
Murder is not something that we take
lightly here on Panamanian soil.
So come on out of there
and there will be no more deaths.
Michael, I took a man's life.
Don't think about that now.
You and I have got a date, remember?
Two limes and a couple of beers.
Don't forget that.
This is your last warning.
Give me the gun.
I took a man's life.
We're gonna walk out of here together
and tell them exactly what happened.
No, look at me, look at me,
look at me.
Now, we're gonna tell them
what happened.
- Okay.
- We're gonna explain everything.
And I'm gonna do
whatever I can to help you.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
Now, give me the gun.
Here.
You ready?
I love you.
I love you too, Sara.
- Okay.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
- All right.
- Come on.
Don't move!
I'll shoot!
- Michael, what are you doing?
- Nobody moves! Nobody!
- You sacrificed everything for me once.
- No.
- No! Don't move!
- No, I won't let you do this.
Michael. Michael!
Now it's time to say thank you.
It was me! It was me!
- I did it!
- He's done nothing wrong!
- He's innocent!
- I did it! It was me.
- He's done nothing wrong.
He hasn't shot anybody,
he hasn't hurt anybody. Michael.
Michael, tell them the truth!
Michael! He's done nothing wrong!
Hello?
Hey, it's me.
Oh, getting impatient. Reminds me
of when we were in college.
Did you buy the tickets yet?
No, I'm still looking.
Don't.
- What?
- Forget about them.
Forget I ever existed.
- Excuse me. You speak English?
- Yes. Can I help you?
Yeah. I'm looking for a woman.
Sara Tancredi.
She was brought in to give her
statement, then released.
You just missed her.
Sara!
Oh, God.
I thought you'd never show up.
Okay, when am I getting out of here?
That's the thing.
There's been a hiccup.
A hiccup?
Look, you guys got me.
You got me fair and square
in Mexico, all right?
I did what you wanted me to do. Now
it's time to cut me loose like we agreed.
Getting caught wasn't part
of the agreement.
I got caught running your setup.
Being your bait.
Now, I got you Scofield down here.
I got you what you wanted.
You got caught, Bagwell.
Wait. Where you going?!
Where you going?
I got you what you wanted!
I got them boys down here!
I did what you told me to do!
Do you hear me?
I did what you told me!
This is as far as we go.
General.
I trust this is a safe place to speak.
It's Scofield.
They got him.
Scofield back in the pen.
Gotta be honest,
I didn't think we'd see it happen.
You know he's gonna break out.
It's in his blood.
That's exactly what
we want him to do.