Don't you wanna go
down the slide? It's so fun!
- Someone's waiting, sweets.
- You can do it.
Come on, go down the slide. Go.
Whee!
Margo?
- Daddy! Help!
- Erica?
- Get me out of here!
- Hold on. I'm coming.
Help!
My god!
Her name is Tara foley.
She was also a nanny.
But we really didn't know her that well.
Do you know of anyone who
would've wanted to hurt her?
I can't imagine. She was so nice.
Milo, we don't eat grass!
Have some seaweed.
Well, there was that creepy guy.
What creepy guy?
Some weird guy who had
been hanging around the park.
As a mom, it's my job
to anticipate all the ways
somebody could die at a playground,
but stuck in a slide?
- Missed that one.
- Morning, all.
- Morning.
So, Dr. Forzan, what have you got?
Well, it looks like the victim
died of an epidural hematoma
due to a blow to the
head by a heavy object.
She was attacked in the slide?
I don't think so.
Judging from the shape of the slide,
the location of the wound,
it's my belief that the
victim was struck elsewhere
and tried to escape her assailant.
She was hiding, lieutenant.
Time of death?
Around 10:00 P.M.
There doesn't seem to be any cctv here.
I'll have Lynn check.
Any guess as to the murder weapon?
It's hard to say.
We'll test the wound
for particulate matter,
but an injury like this could've
come from any number of things
if it was swung hard enough.
I'll have forensics do a wide sweep.
They're gonna have a hell of a time.
There's no place more
laden with bodily fluids
than a playground during flu season.
Got a lead. The victim's
name is Tara foley.
According to Tara's fellow nannies,
a suspicious man who seemed
particularly interested in Tara
was seen hanging around the park.
Any one of them manage to
take a photo of this person?
Unfortunately, no.
Okay, that dinging's gotta stop.
- Morgan.
- What? I'm detecting.
See? Eight unread messages
from someone named Brett Lewis.
"Tara? Tara! You're late. Where
are you? Tara, answer me now."
The last one's a voice memo.
Tara, you're now an hour and a half late!
You better have an airtight excuse
because this is unacceptable!
That would appear to
be her employer. May I?
No emergency contact listed.
No one listed as mom or dad, either.
What? God, it just keeps getting sadder.
This poor girl. All alone in the world.
Spent her last few
minutes terrified for her life.
You can tell by her ballet
flats that she was nice.
Okay, we have to find that man
who's been hanging around the park.
Daphne, oz, go through Tara's phone.
See if you can find any pictures
she may have taken of him.
And look for next of kin.
Boyfriend, girlfriend,
anyone who can tell us
more about Tara and her life.
- Yep.
- Yeah. You got it.
And Morgan, karadec, we
may not be able to talk to family,
but let's at least start by
talking to the one person
she worked for every day.
Find out what he has to say for himself.
You got it, boss.
What murderer leaves someone
an angry message after killing them?
The smart one.
Adam karadec, LAPD.
I'm afraid I've got
some bad news for you.
Poor Tara.
This is such a shock.
So how long had Tara
been ward's nanny?
About four months.
In that time, she'd
become part of the family.
You know, Brett, you seem
pretty angry in your messages.
I mean, did you have a
strained relationship with Tara?
No. Not at all. I'm just a
stickler for being on time.
I wouldn't have yelled
at her had I known...
Can you tell us about
Tara? What was she like?
Oof.
Tara was a sweet girl, you know.
She was quiet and loving,
and liked reading historical fiction,
and watching tiktoks of dance protégés.
Sorry, I'm just trying to
give you everything I know.
Outside of working for us,
she lived a relatively solitary life.
That would explain the lack of an
emergency contact in her phone.
Had Tara mentioned anything
out of the ordinary to you recently?
- No, nothing I can think of.
- No.
Wait, the... there was...
There was that guy
that kept following her.
Tara complained that she
kept seeing the same guy.
He'd show up wherever
she was. Park, coffee shop.
He was often reading a
French magazine or newspaper.
And he had a limp.
I know where to find this guy.
There's only one news stand
that sells French newspapers in la.
And it's across the street
from a perfect stakeout location.
Wow. You really love this diner?
My god.
This is so good. You gotta take a bite.
Eat from the other
side. I didn't touch there.
Morgan, we're on a stakeout.
A key to a good
stakeout is being discreet.
You worried I'm gonna pull a Meg Ryan
and fake an orgasm or something?
That would attract
way too much attention.
I can fake yours, though. Watch.
Impression over.
That's, hilarious.
- That's our guy.
- Really?
Yep. Yeah. It looks like
he's headed this way.
- In here?
- Yeah.
Where did he go?
Okay, he went up there. You stay here.
Okay.
Okay!
Hey, Morgan, it's safe to...
Well, I could tell by
your confident footsteps
that the coast was clear.
Well, it turns out
that our stalker is actually a pi.
Charles lavoie,
aka Chuck the canuck. Former LAPD.
Used to be a detective
in the traffic department.
Just a warning, the guy is a lot.
Okay.
I apologize about the pastrami smell.
You'll get used to it.
Hey, Chuck.
Adam karadec.
I'll be damned.
- And you got married.
- No.
Morgan gillory. We work together.
Anyway, karadec and I came up together
as detectives, you know.
- We were always neck and neck.
- Is that right?
Until I was forced to retire early. So...
Well, Chuck was shot in the line of duty.
- My god. What happened?
- Yeah.
My firearm did discharge
itself whilst in its holster
during a routine traffic stop
causing my metatarsal to shatter.
You shot yourself in the foot.
I shot myself in the foot.
Okay. Hey, can I take a
look at this newspaper?
Yeah. Sure.
Le devoir, from Quebec.
This is the French newspaper
that Tara saw her stalker reading.
What's this all about?
What do you know about Tara foley?
Everything.
- Did you know she was murdered?
- Almost everything.
I had no idea. Poor girl.
Who hired you to follow her?
I place a high priority
on client confidentiality.
But an even higher one on friendship.
- I was hired by the lewises.
- Her employers?
Ward's parents. It's getting messy.
They wanted to know if I saw
anything out of the ordinary,
but I found bubkes.
Did you take any pictures?
Tons.
I shoot raw, my man.
It's my favorite part of the job.
Do me a favor, Chuck. Bring
these photos to the station tomorrow.
Yeah. Happy to.
Karadec.
- Nice to meet you.
- You too.
Poor girl.
Why did you stop following Tara?
I was canned.
The client wasn't happy with the results,
which is what they always say
when they don't get what
they were hoping to find.
What were they hoping to find?
They thought the nanny
was mistreating their son.
We didn't expect to see you again.
We didn't expect to be back.
You think we hired a private investigator
to follow Tara?
I'm sorry, but we most certainly did not.
Well, we might have.
What?
Brett, why did you
hire a pi to follow Tara?
I was a nervous wreck
ever since the ordeal
we went through with
our last nanny, Rosa.
What happened with Rosa?
I'm a member of the 90049
parents' Facebook group.
That's the Brentwood zip code.
Six months ago, I see a
post from a concerned mother
describing a horrific event at the library,
where an unattended child
wandered out of the library
and almost into the street.
When I read the description of the child,
I realized it was ward.
It was terrifying.
Yeah, that is a
nightmare. What'd you do?
We asked Rosa about it,
and she ultimately admitted it.
We had no choice but to let her go.
But what does this have to do with Tara?
We hired Tara, and
everything was going great.
Ward loved her.
But then we see another
post in the parents' group.
This time about Tara.
And this time from several mothers,
all saying that Tara
was endangering ward.
We debated whether to believe it.
The post about Rosa was true.
But we talked to both ward and Tara,
and determined that the accusations
against Tara had to be made up.
Ward lit up around Tara in a
way that he never did with Rosa.
And Tara seemed to be
taking excellent care of ward.
I couldn't let it go. I'm sorry.
What did this pi even find?
Nothing.
Can we see these negative
posts about Tara, please?
Sure. I took screen grabs of everything.
Here you go.
This car in a gal seems to
be all up in your business.
Well, car in a is the one who alerted us
to Rosa's misconduct.
Yeah. And then it looks
like she turns on Tara.
Did you reach out to car in a?
I messaged her, but she said
she didn't have any more information.
If you'll excuse me, I gotta stand up.
These pants only have about
a ten-minute sitting time limit
before they become a
permanent part of my body.
So, Jeff, you were totally confident
in Tara's care of ward.
Completely. She was wonderful.
Where did you even find this guy?
The Internet.
I can't believe you hired a pi.
Well, my guess is he wanted
eyes and ears on the outside
since you guys are all
covered on nanny cams in here.
What? Nanny cams?
I used to rely on a very kind
but very senior gentleman
to watch my kids, and
I wanted to make sure
that he wasn't literally
falling asleep on the job.
So I looked into my surveillance options.
You've got the nanny cam clock,
tissue box, picture frame, energy drink,
which I found confusing,
the nanny cam fake toolbox.
Ultimately, I couldn't afford any of them.
But I'm finding that Brett
went with the plant, globe,
and the adorable spy robot.
There's a nanny cam in the north pole?
We're gonna need that footage.
- Where were you two last night?
- We were here all night.
Can anyone corroborate that?
- We were on a video call.
- With who?
Lamar Nichols, our couples counselor.
All right. We'll be in touch.
Well, I'll have Daphne
look up carina's address,
track down the other parents
who posted about Tara.
We need to get to the bottom of
this 90049 parents' Facebook group.
Yep.
You know why most
foods are cooked at 350?
The maillard reaction,
a chemical process
by which the sugars are browned
and produce pleasing flavors.
But I think the sweet
potato fries call for 425.
Crap. You're right.
Agh! They rejected me.
I'm trying to infiltrate a
private online parenting group,
so I can chat up some people
who are bullying our victim,
but it seems like they sniffed around
and figured out that we don't exactly live
within the city limits of Brentwood.
We don't even live close enough
to have the same weather as Brentwood.
By the way, my classmate Finn is having
an 11th birthday party
soon, so I'll need a gift.
Awesome! What do you wanna get him?
Ava, what's a good gift
for a boy's 11th birthday?
Ava, do you have any ideas?
Hey, phone face.
Hi. Your brother's talking to you.
I don't know. Elliot's
the only fifth grader here.
Hey, I was super into
legos when I was 11.
My favorite was a toy story 2 set
'cause I had a big crush on Jessie.
You did? I could totally see it.
With her cute pigtails,
and your eyes just
popped out of your head
and your jaw dropped to the floor.
Hey, hey. She seemed nice.
Why don't you go grab your
tablet and you can pick out a set.
Okay.
- Text me again.
- Okay.
That's you when you first saw Jessie.
Did you change your text
tones to say "awooga"?
Only for the texts from you.
I can't believe you.
Me neither.
Hey! You wanna go
through Tara's phone?
That's all you.
Yeah. This place still smells
like cheap floor wax and the scared urine
from the suckers we put away. Whoo!
You must be Chuck.
You got me.
Did you bring the
photos for the foley case?
Indeed I did. Yep. All 1,500 of them.
Yeah, karadec wanted me
to walk you through them.
You know, identify all the key players.
But first, I need a chair
with solid lumbar support.
There she is. I slipped a
disc between my l2 and l3.
You know what? I got Tara's phone.
You tear it up with Chuck.
Okay.
Seems like you have some
personal photos mixed in here.
All my photos are personal.
Are you on any of these,
online parenting groups?
Absolutely not.
Don't need some
self-righteous mom telling me
I don't love my kids if I
don't cut their cucumbers
into little smiley faces
before I cram 'em in their lunch box.
Yeah, I would never take you as the type
to anthropomorphize vegetables.
That is the kindest thing
you've ever said to me.
"Warning from a concerned mom."
Ward's new nanny, Tara,
is cruel and neglectful.
Last Tuesday, she grabbed
his arm so hard he screamed.
Then Thursday, she
yelled at him to stop crying
"and left him stuck on the
top of the play structure."
I didn't write that.
It sure seems like you did.
And a bunch of other ones just like it.
I mean, why don't you
take a second look?
Didn't write it.
That's pretty good, but I didn't write it.
Didn't... no, you know,
I did write this one.
Which one?
"At the library on Wednesday afternoon,
a dark-headed boy wearing
galoshes and a conductor hat
was unattended for 15 minutes,
crying and calling for a Rosa.
He ran out the front door
and would've gone into traffic
had it not been for a
quick library staff member.
Finally, Rosa showed up with no excuse.
"If this is your nanny, she is dangerous!"
Exclamation point.
Okay, so you got Rosa fired.
No, I didn't get her
fired. I reported an issue.
In my line of work, safety is Paramount.
I'm a vp of a commercial real estate firm.
It's very demanding.
Usually, child care falls
to my husband, Mark.
But I had the day off,
so I was able to take
our daughter to the library.
Now, I don't know all the... the kids
and the nannies like my husband does,
'cause I'm not around during the day.
So I had to post on Facebook
to let the parents know
what had happened.
My point is, is that I
tried to do the right thing
and it bit me in the ass.
How so?
Well, after I wrote that post,
I was eviscerated in private messages
saying I ruined a woman's career.
Said I needed to check
my privilege. It was...
It was ridiculous.
They wouldn't be saying
that if it was their kid.
Exactly. Okay?
So I just said screw this
and deactivated my account.
- Where were you two nights ago?
- I was working very late.
I have a big, big presentation coming up.
Look, I'm sorry that
this nanny, Tara, is dead,
but I didn't know her.
Well, the initial search
of Tara's apartment didn't
turn up anything of note,
but I wanna go back again
now that we know
more about our suspects.
Hopefully, we'll find some answers.
Talk to me, daph.
Tara has someone saved in
her phone as "little sketchy."
- The texts are intense.
- Little sketchy?
I'm sending them to you now.
I think we may have an
actual stalker on our hands.
Any luck tracking down the other people
who wrote negative posts about Tara?
Still working on it.
Thanks, daph. Bye.
Ooh-Kay! Here we go!
My forever love, why do you forsake me?
"My heart knows not its beat
if it can't echo that of yours."
If I don't see you soon,
"I don't know what I'll do."
That was three days ago.
She never wrote back.
Tara's apartment.
Seems pretty neat.
Still feel kinda weird about
you parking in her spot.
All right. Let's do this methodically.
I'll start with Tara's
desk, and you start...
By making a huge mess.
Look at this.
Tara was religious. Drawer
dump already paying off.
And we got overdue bills.
Notice of a rent increase. Tara
may have had money trouble.
This is interesting.
She knew car in a was
harassing her online.
Well, she may have feared for her life.
She kept pepper spray in her nightstand.
Well, we got a lawyer's number here.
Cleo, Phillips, and Strauss.
Hi, I was wondering if you could tell me
if Tara foley is a client.
I'm afraid we can't
divulge client information.
Right.
Well, who might I speak
to regarding a stalker?
I'm sorry, sir, we're
an immigration law firm.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Well, that's strange.
Morgan, look at this.
The night she was murdered, she
was planning on going to church.
Yeah, I'll have hoffy find
out if anyone saw her there.
Still nothing that
points to Brett or car in a
or gives us an idea of
who little sketchy was.
Ew.
Morgan. Don't.
By all means.
Let me parse through the
trash piece by piece like a lady.
I mean, at a certain
point, just treat yourself
to the full-size bar.
Bingo!
"Sunday night poetry slam."
Based on little sketchy's
overly wrought rhyme scheme,
I bet we could find the guy here.
And today just happens
to be... Sunday fun day.
Where is Ava? She's ten minutes late.
Ooh! I forgot to tell you.
Our prime delivery came with
Finn's birthday present in it.
Just ordered it yesterday.
It's already here.
Actually, I don't need it after all.
Turns out I'm the only kid
in class Finn didn't invite.
What? That's gotta be a mistake.
It's not.
I promise.
Well, this sucks.
Hey, I still think it's just a mistake.
But if it's not, you're
keeping that present
'cause you're a wonderful
kid and you deserve it.
There you are. Where have
you been? I gotta go to work.
Can you put that down, please?
You have actual people in the room.
I'm just being polite and thanking Ryder
for dropping me off.
Ryder drives?
Most 26-year-olds do.
Not funny.
Not the night and not funny.
As if I couldn't be in a worse mood,
I gotta go to a poetry reading.
Tara, Tara!
You're gone with the wind.
I'm left heartbroken,
beaten and chagrined.
Goodbye, Tara-saurus.
Who's sore? Us.
Who's dead?
You.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
We need to talk.
I'm detective karadec,
this is consultant gillory, with the LAPD.
We're looking into the
murder of Tara foley.
Good.
I know who killed her.
Bryan schlotzky is on
his way in for questioning.
You know, I can't stress enough
the importance of
hand-to-hand combat training
in our line of work.
I could show you a few moves.
Can't believe you brought Chuck
the canuck back to our precinct.
Well, you gotta admit,
it's fun to watch oz squirm.
Daphne, any luck
finding the other people
who posted about Tara on
that 90049 parents' group?
Still looking. It's a needle in a haystack.
There's so many moms
named Megan out there.
I think we might have
someone else to consider.
Mark, carina's husband.
Mark's in a lot of these
photos. He and Tara seem cozy.
And in this one, he's wielding a bat.
That could cause a hematoma.
Can you go back one?
Tara's wearing Mark's sweatshirt.
Well, how do you know?
It's got the old supersonics logo on it.
Supersonics. Fast food joint.
No. Former NBA team based in Seattle.
In 2008, they moved to Oklahoma
and played under a different
sound-themed name, the thunder.
I think Mark was from Seattle.
On their mantle, I saw a family photo
of them standing at the space needle.
In the distance, you
could see mount rainier,
and in the foreground were
the arches of lumen field.
Daphne, pay Mark a visit.
Find out what the real nature
of his relationship was with Tara.
Got it. Oz, can you print these for me?
Yeah.
And it would appear that little sketchy
has arrived for his interview.
Ooh.
Give me one sec, real quick.
- Hello?
- Hi, this is Jean Anne,
Finn's mom, returning your call.
Hi, Jean Anne. Hey.
Listen, I think there's
been a misunderstanding.
See, my son Elliot believes
he's the only kid not invited
to your son's birthday party.
Finn made the guest list.
It's a small group, and he and
Elliot don't know each other that well.
That's an easy fix.
Why doesn't he come over
tomorrow for a playdate?
Tomorrow? I guess that could work.
Perfect. We'll see Finn then. Great, bye.
Motherhood has made
me so understanding.
How did you know Tara?
Tara was my babysitter.
Where were you the night Tara died?
I was outside her apartment complex
blasting a love song through a speaker.
Can anyone confirm that?
Several of the tenants
were quite frustrated
with my act of devotion.
At the poetry reading,
you said you knew who killed Tara.
It was Mark.
A dad at the playground.
He started horning in
and made Tara cut me out of her life.
But Tara would never
be with a married man.
So he killed her.
Hi. Mark?
Daphne forrester, LAPD.
Is there news about Tara?
Not exactly.
Can you tell me why Tara
was wearing your sweatshirt
in this photo?
I guess she was cold?
Looks like you two were pretty close.
We were.
Ward and my daughter,
Ruby, were playground friends,
so I got to know her pretty well.
You know, she didn't have any family,
so I was there for her,
gave her advice when I could.
Was it more than friendship for you?
What? No!
No. I love my wife. I'm devoted to her.
Tara was a friend.
Okay. Where were
you the night Tara died?
Here, hosting book club.
We were reading Liz Gilbert's big magic.
Wait, actually, you know what?
You can ask anyone in my book club.
We're called the "Lou reads."
Except "read" is spelled
I can guess.
Is that your bat?
This?
Yeah, it's for wiffle ball.
It's plastic. Totally harmless.
See?
You're doing great!
I have actual race cars if you
wanna do a tactile thing later.
I've got freshly opened cookies.
Do you have anything
without refined sugar?
Let me go look.
Gosh. Imagine being
there in the summer of '56
when art ingels invented the first go-kart.
Dude! You made me lose!
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to.
You really suck the fun out of everything.
You know, I'm only here
because my mom made me, right?
You're just a weirdo who can't shut up.
That's why you're not
invited to my birthday party.
Hey, Finn.
I'm taking everybody to
knott's Berry farm next week,
and you're not invited.
I sure would love to bring you along,
but they got a "no turd kid" policy,
so I guess we'll just have
to miss you on this one.
Why don't you grab your
stuff and go sit on the porch
and wait for your mom.
Bye! Thanks for coming.
I kind of blacked out. How bad was it?
What just came out of my mouth?
Bad.
It was all bad.
I'm so sorry I forced a playdate.
Finn does not deserve a friend like you.
I know it's hard to be different.
But listen.
You are fun, no matter
what that little jerk says.
I'll believe it when I see it.
I don't know. One of
them thinks he's not cool,
and the other one's
basically divorced herself
from our family.
If she's not with her boyfriend,
she's constantly texting him.
Yep.
I'm so sorry, Morgan,
but this too shall pass.
And then something
even harder will come up.
Good. Thank you so much.
Honestly, this foley
case is driving me nuts.
We are missing something. I can feel it.
I do too.
Brett's couples counseling
alibi checked out.
Although, he may have
hired someone to kill Tara.
Look into his financials.
You might wanna see this.
Tara's with the other nannies
in a lot of Chuck's photos.
They might've known each
other better than we thought.
I mean, they did spend
every day together.
Our main suspects all have alibis,
not all airtight, but still.
Go back to the nannies.
Find out everything
they know about Tara,
anything we may have missed.
- Yeah.
- Oz.
I remembered that boxing
combo is lethal if done correctly.
- I'm actually heading out.
- We'll talk about it later.
- Morgan, you and I should tag along.
- Yeah.
Karadec, you wanna
play some handball?
- Soon as I get back, bro.
- All right. Whoo.
Remember the good old days, Selena,
you know, when you could
arrest a perp in the morning
and then take him out for a
beer in the afternoon, you know?
When everybody wasn't so
sensitive about everything.
Darius!
Come here, please.
I wanted to ask you
about the Tara foley case.
Chuck, I think you better excuse us.
You want me to get
the Chuck out of here.
My hourly rates are too high.
Thank you, Chuck.
You are a lifesaver.
I hope I didn't pull you
from anything urgent.
Nope. Just snagging a cup of the
good coffee you guys have up here.
But I do have an update.
The toxicologist report on
Tara foley came out clean,
and we found no evidence of
defensive wounds on her body.
Which means when she was
attacked, she didn't fight back.
She was taken by surprise.
Or she knew her attacker.
Seems like it.
We're hoping you can tell
us a little more about Tara.
She was nice. Almost too nice.
She didn't know her worth.
I hear she was working
for ten dollars an hour less than we do.
And with no benefits.
Poor thing.
An extra ten bucks an hour
would help with those overdue bills.
This job is easier if you work together.
Coordinate. Only one nanny
needs to bring a soccer ball.
That sort of thing.
But she didn't take us
up on our offers to help.
You know, the saddest part is,
she might still be
alive if she was a joiner.
Joiner? What do you mean?
Well, the night that she
passed, I was house-sitting,
so I had these girls over to just hang out.
She could've been with us.
But instead... God rest her soul.
The only one she was
friends with was Mark.
Bet his wife didn't like
that. What was her name?
- Carina.
- Right. Carina.
You remember that fight?
What fight?
His wife show up one day
and scream at Tara and Mark.
Tara look really frightened.
Carina's motive just
got a whole lot clearer.
- She was jealous.
- Didn't she have an alibi?
She said she was working late,
which was confirmed by
the security log at her office.
Anyone can jump a turnstile if
they wanna avoid scanning their ID.
Or they don't have money for the Metro.
Wanna sneak into a
Brandi carlile concert.
Just for example.
- Karadec.
- Hey, it's Daphne.
You know those other moms
who posted negative things
about Tara in the
Brentwood parents' group?
- Yeah.
- They don't exist.
Don't exist?
Their profiles appear to be fake.
So somebody who hated Tara
created fake profiles to drag her?
Yeah, we're about to go talk
to somebody who fits that bill.
Thanks, Daphne.
So, we need to be keeping
an eye on sustainability,
as our clients value...
Tell us about the heated argument
you and Mark had at the park, please.
Did it have anything to do with
Mark's relationship with Tara?
What? No. Are you...
Are you suggesting I
was jealous of Tara?
Well, jealousy is a common motive.
You wouldn't exactly
be rewriting the playbook.
I wasn't mad about Tara.
I was mad about our deck.
Mark had one simple job.
Just order the wood for our new deck.
And out of all the types of wood,
do you know which one he ordered?
Alaskan spruce.
Everyone knows that Alaskan
spruce shrinks end-grain.
Okay? And causes serious
problems when it gets wet.
Right. I know that, but I'm not everyone.
You are the only real person
we can link to the
negative posts about Tara.
All the other profiles were fake.
Did you maybe create them
to upset the young woman
that your husband was so close with?
My god. Look, I told you,
I never posted about Tara.
Only Rosa.
I took my daughter to story
time at the library one time, okay?
As a working mother,
that is a special opportunity
to hang out with your kid
in the middle of the day.
And while I was there,
I happened to see something awful,
so I said something.
And then it backfired
and I deleted my account.
Hang on. Hang on.
What time is story time?
Noon.
All the comments
about Tara were posted
between 12:00 and 1:00 P.M. story time.
It's basically a time
when caretakers get
to take a little breather
because the kids are
otherwise occupied.
And who would want to
infiltrate a parent group
where the subject is trashing nannies?
The nannies!
They were in that group
under fake accounts.
They bullied car in a off of Facebook
when she came for Rosa,
and then, once Tara was hired,
they scraped her old
profile and made a new one.
They posed as car in a
and other concerned parents,
and they reported Tara.
But the other nannies liked Tara.
Did they? I've been on the outside
of the mom clique enough times
to know when people
are being nice to your face
but judging you behind your back.
When people like Tara come
in and work for less money
and no benefits, they devalue our job.
She didn't abide by the nanny code.
Tara wasn't welcome.
She replaced our friend.
Those nannies resented Tara.
She threatened their very way of life.
Not to mention, they were
loyal to the woman she replaced.
- Rosa.
- Or should we say sporty spice?
Each of the kids had a spice
girl sticker on their lunch box.
Which was clearly for the nannies,
'cause what three-year-old
gives a "zig-a-zig"
- about a 30-year-old band?
- Band?
Except there was one spice girl missing.
Sporty spice was tucked
away in the back of the shelf
in Brett and Jeff's house.
Tara didn't want to use that lunch box
because the spice girls stickers
were the original five nannies' thing.
And Tara was on the outs.
So you think all the nannies killed Tara
because they were
mad she replaced Rosa?
Nope. Oksana did.
And you know this because...
Because of the capitalization
conventions in the Russian language.
In the post that car in a
admits to writing about Rosa,
she capitalizes the day of the
week that the incident occurred.
But in the post that car in
a denies writing about Tara,
the days of the week are lowercased,
which would only make sense
if you were a native Russian speaker.
Because in Russian, you
don't capitalize days of the week.
But even if oksana
was bullying Tara online,
using fake accounts,
that doesn't mean she killed her.
Well, of course it does.
'Cause of the way she crossed herself.
You guys aren't up-to-date
on the great schism
between eastern
orthodoxy and catholicism?
- Okay.
- Not totally.
Okay, in 1054, there was a huge fight
between western and eastern churches
called the great schism.
And this resulted in a few
fundamental differences
between how each church does things,
one of those differences being
how members cross themselves.
Okay, now this is ringing a bell.
Catholics use five fingers,
and they cross forehead, chest,
left shoulder, right shoulder.
Orthodox christians cross
themselves using three fingers,
forehead, chest, right
shoulder to left shoulder.
Now, when we were
chatting with the nannies,
I saw oksana cross herself in
the eastern orthodox manner.
How does oksana's religion
mean she killed Tara?
Another result of the great schism
is that the two sides
use different calendars.
Catholics use a gregorian calendar
introduced by a pope in 1582.
Orthodox christians still
use a Julian calendar.
Basically, it means they
celebrate the same holidays,
but certain holidays
fall on different dates,
much to the chagrin
of the little Greek girl
whose easter bunny comes
a month after her friends got
to eat all their cadbury eggs.
- I love those.
- Girl, same.
So good.
You can go back to work now.
Now, do we know what
religion Tara foley was?
- Catholic?
- Catholic!
We found a rosary.
That's classic catholic.
But don't forget what I
said about the calendars.
How could we?
On Tara's calendar, she
had marked down a date
for the exaltation of the
cross, September 27th.
But catholics celebrate that on the 14th.
So she wasn't planning
to go to her church service.
She was going to oksana's.
Tara had figured out
that oksana was the one
who was bullying her, and that explains
the number for the immigration
lawyer we found in her apartment.
Identity fraud is a crime that
can get your visa revoked.
Tara knew that by making
fake profiles on Facebook
and pretending to be car in a,
oksana was putting her visa in jeopardy
and she could be deported.
Exactly.
Tara knew that oksana was gonna be
at the Russian orthodox church that night.
Which is a block away from the park.
After the service, Tara
confronted oksana.
Oksana freaked out and
bashed her in the head.
She thought she'd finished
the job, but she didn't.
Tara was out of sorts, afraid
that oksana would follow her.
She went to the park, hid
in the slide, where she died.
Were you with oksana the
night Tara was murdered?
- Yes.
- Can you tell me what you did that night?
My employers were out of town,
so I just had a girls' night in.
We had some drinks, went in
the hot tub. Oksana made dinner.
- Then watched a movie.
- Everyone left around 1:00 A.M.
Well, thanks. Super helpful.
We're just gonna go ahead
and check the nanny cams.
They don't have nanny cams.
Well, the whole point of a nanny cam is
that you don't tell the nanny.
- Oksana wasn't there.
- Oksana's a very scary lady.
She made us lie. Oksana
swore it was an accident.
I can't believe you found
nanny cams and didn't tell me.
I was bluffing.
Sneaky spice.
Your friends turned on you.
They said you forced
them to provide your alibi.
We know that you are
the one who killed Tara.
That little bitch threaten me.
Said she's gonna have
me sent back to Russia
for creating those posts.
After everything I sacrifice to get here.
After the persecution my family endured.
Tara had no idea what going
back would mean for me.
That's why I pick up that rock!
You could have just
promised to stop bullying her.
I couldn't take risk.
I would always be
looking over my shoulder.
I choose prison here over
going back to Russia any day.
And so you have.
I gotta go do something.
You guys play. Have fun.
Hey. There was a
time you would've killed
to go to the playground.
Well, it's because Ava would
make me puke on the spinner.
It was fun.
But we're different people now.
You wanna play over there?
Okay, go. You can go over there.
Don't go too far!
- Hey, Jeff.
- Hey.
Thought I might find you here.
Well, it hasn't felt right
to hire a new nanny yet.
I'm so relieved that
Tara's killer is behind bars.
Tara deserved that, at least.
Well, now that the case is closed,
there's something I
thought you might like.
Wow.
I never got to see this, you know?
Their everyday together.
That is... that is the heartbreaking thing
about being a working parent
that... your kid has all these experiences
that you are just not a part of.
Your main focus when
you hire a caretaker is
that your child will be safe.
But your hope is that
your child will be loved.
And ward was loved by Tara.
And I knew that.
But now I get to see it.
Race you to the spinner.
- Wait! Come on!
- Come on!
- Get on!
- Wait up. Okay, I'm on. I'm on.
Whoo!
- Come on.
- Okay.
You're going so much faster than before!
Yeah!
Ava, you're going to make
me lose my lunch! Don't stop!
Whoa!
Yeah? I'm gonna make you
puke up yesterday's lunch too!
Wahoo!
Whoa! Whoo!