Official LAPD business. Keep my
baby close. This won'Őt take long.
What exactly
are you doing?
Helping the cops solve cases.
- We'Őre really doing this, huh?
- We'Őre doing it.
- You know this woman?
- I'Őm his partner.
- We'Őre not partners.
- Non-romantic partner.
We'Őre not partners.
She'Ős actually
just a consultant.
We work on cases together
in a partnerly fashion.
Morgan did good work
on this case.
Did you tell her that?
I obsess over
every little problem I see.
My mind is constantly
spinning out of control.
Which makes it impossible
to hold a job, relationship.
I'Őm Tom. Janitorial staff.
- Are you asking me
out on a date?
- I think I am.
When I agreed to take this job--
I promised to look into
your missing ex.
Roman Sinquerra.
A month before he went missing,
Roman was cited
for painting a mural
in an unauthorized location.
Back then, the area was a hotbed
for criminal activity.
- Roman wasn'Őt a criminal.
- Well, then I'Őm wondering
if he saw something
in the area he shouldn'Őt have.
Honey, your father
loved you so much.
- That'Ős why he left?
- It'Ős more complicated
than that.
Whatever.
I don'Őt even remember him.
- If he could be here--
- I'Őm glad he's not.
I know how early it is.
You want a spot for us
and our kids or not?
Will you just put on some shorts
and get down here?
Help!
So, I gotta be honest.
I haven'Őt been on
many breakfast dates.
Mmm. Yeah.
Maybe 'Őcause they suck.
- Oh, that'Ős great. Yep.
- You don'Őt. You don't suck.
I'Őm glad you're here.
I just feel bad that
this is all the time I have.
My life is kind of insane.
It'Ős not ideal, I know.
Okay.
So, what'Ős your ideal date?
Oh. Um...
- Well, there'Őd be
a cocktail involved.
- Great.
And maybe just dinner
with an adult
where I'Őm not worried
about waking kids up.
Hey, I can be that adult.
Plus, didn'Őt you say
your kids were away
with your ex this weekend?
They are, but I am on call
with the LAPD.
And every time I'Őm on call,
they seem to call.
Okay, this is what
we'Őre gonna do. Let'Ős hope
that crime takes a holiday.
And I'Őm gonna keep
Saturday night open for you.
- No, you do not need to do that.
- It'Ős too late. I just did it.
- Just canceled all my plans.
- Just now?
Just now. Plus, I don'Őt wanna
celebrate alone.
What are we celebrating?
You remember
that whole hostage situation?
- Oh, yeah. Yeah.
- I got shot. Yeah.
How'Ős that going?
It'Ős going good.
Just finished my rehab.
I'Őm as good as new.
- And I'Őm also
a pretty good cook.
- Really?
Yeah. I almost said great,
but I'Őd rather under-promise
and over deliver.
Oh, look at that.
They'Őre calling.
Saturday night?
I have a good feeling about it.
- I like the optimism.
I really do.
- Mmm. Enjoy your day.
- You too.
- Go solve crime.
Thank you.
Am I good here?
You always park like this?
You wanna try
gliding this big boat
into a tiny spot, be my guest.
Seriously though,
am I gonna get a ticket?
- No.
- You know what you should do?
You should get me, like,
a universal parking pass.
Like a citywide permit,
you know?
Something I can hang
from my rearview,
or a sticker would work.
Consider it done.
You'Őre a terrible liar.
Thank you.
I'Őll start
walking it off right now.
Hey, Oz. What do we got?
Unidentified female. Late 20s.
- Blunt force trauma to the head.
-  Mmm.
Lifeguard was just showing up
for their shift.
Heard a woman yell for help
and ran over to perform CPR.
She was alive at the time
but barely.
When the EMTs arrived,
they took over,
but she didn'Őt make it.
Time of death
was called at 8:32 a.m.
About half an hour ago.
We thinking accident
or foul play?
We started canvassing the area.
So far, no eyewitness account
of anyone matching
the woman'Ős description
have turned up
in the last couple of hours
at local businesses.
And I don'Őt think
she was planning on swimming
in these clothes.
Plus, there'Ős nothing
at the crime scene indicating
what caused that head wound.
- Ah, so we'Őre
looking at a murder.
- Maybe.
- Give me your watch.
- Why?
- Just g-give...
- Okay.
- The paramedics
didn'Őt detect a pulse?
- Right. That'Ős why...
Wait. What are you...
Because there was
no detectable pulse at the time.
She'Ős still alive.
Hey, get those EMTs
down here now!
How is that even possible?
It'Ős called the Lazarus effect.
You never heard of it?
Lazarus from the New Testament?
That'Ős the guy.
He was raised from the dead.
And as a reward,
he has a medical anomaly
named after him.
It'Ős the spontaneous return
of circulation after failed
attempts of resuscitation.
So, it'Ős like a miracle?
No, it'Ős medical.
How'Ős our Jane Doe?
Hospital said
she had a skull fracture.
She should be out of surgery
in a few hours if all goes well.
The moment she'Ős up,
I want us there. See if
she can identify her assailant.
What about forensics?
Trace amounts of metal
found in the head wound.
I'Őm thinking our weapon could be
a hammer or something.
Hey, guys,
I think I ID'Őd our Jane Doe.
Heather Wallace. Twenty-seven.
Graduate student at UCLA,
according to her boyfriend,
Morris,
who filed a missing person'Ős
report last night when she
didn'Őt show up for dinner.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
- Is that her?
- That'Ős Heather.
How long were you together?
Only a few months.
He'Ős a little older
than Heather.
A little?
I was shopping at Abbot Kinney
when she asked me
for directions to the canals.
I walked her over there, and...
and we just clicked.
I'Őm sorry,
can I get one of those?
Morris Jardine. Fifty-seven,
lives in the Palisades.
Founder of a leisurewear company
he sold last year.
Looks like he did quite well.
And where were you last night?
I was at home, picking out tile.
I'Őm putting in a new pool.
I was frustrated.
So many choices.
Mosaic, glass, porcelain.
I wish that I was better
about not losing perspective.
I was in a bad mood
because of pool tiles.
I thought that was
so important, and now...
She'Ős in the hospital
fighting for her life?
I wanna like this guy,
but I don'Őt.
I'Őm with you.
Something feels off about him.
How about the fact that he
hasn'Őt asked to see Heather yet?
- Lieutenant.
- You talked to UCLA?
Uh, yeah. But there'Ős
no record of a student
named Heather Wallace.
So, I ran
our victim'Ős fingerprints
and got a hit from when she
applied for a real estate
license two years ago.
"Penny Hall."
If Penny gave Morris
a fake name, then she definitely
had something to hide.
And maybe after he found out,
he attacked her on the beach.
I'Őm no detective, but seems like
figuring out who our victim is
would help us figure out
who wanted to kill her.
Have an address?
We do. You and Karadec
go find out if Morris
is lying to us
and why Penny is lying to him.
Here we are, 11D.
Penny'Ős my favorite tenant.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, I offered her
an upper unit when it opened up.
She wanted to stay after
what happened to her boyfriend.
What happened to her boyfriend?
Well, he died.
Murdered, I think.
Morris Jardine, white guy, 50s?
No, that doesn'Őt sound right.
A young guy, about her age.
His name was Marcus...
No, Lucas. Lucas Phillips.
Yeah, sweet guy.
Poor girl stayed in
for weeks after that.
I do hope she'Ős all right.
Thank you.
This must be Lucas.
Morris never mentioned
anything about Penny
having an ex who was killed.
But if she didn'Őt trust him
with her real name,
she probably wasn'Őt
telling him much.
Do you have any idea
how much this bag costs?
I have absolutely no idea.
A lot.
You know,
I think Penny got scared
when her ex was killed.
Tried to stay off
the killer'Ős radar
by using a fake name.
But whoever killed her ex
finally caught up with her.
Uh, these are
very expensive shoes
for a person who lives
in a crappy part of town.
Well, then. Maybe we have
a sugar daddy situation
gone wrong.
Not with those credit card bills
on her counter.
This doesn'Őt make any sense.
You'Őre right. Morris wasn't
paying for the clothes
or the bags. She was.
Well, that'Ős strange.
Penny is paying 2,500 bucks
a month for a billboard on PCH.
Billboard for what?
We'Őll certainly find out.
You'Őre right. This is weird.
Penny lives here, except for
any one of her outfits
would pay my mortgage
for an entire month.
That'Ős not to mention
the handbags or the shoes.
Why does a woman
hide her identity,
date a rich guy
while going into serious debt
trying to keep up appearances?
Could have something to do
with that.
So, our victim was investigating
another victim?
It was a cold case. And Penny
was pulling out all the stops.
Oz, do the honors.
She did this?
It'Ős Lucas Phillips,
Penny'Ős boyfriend,
found dead two years ago
just after the Fourth of July.
Detective Clark Boding
worked the case.
Yes, I remember. He was
really upset about that one.
Remained unsolved
when he retired.
Now, the police reports
suspected Lucas
was robbed on the beach.
Poor guy died
from blunt force trauma
just after 10:00 p.m.
- Just like Penny Hall.
- But we know Penny
wasn'Őt robbed.
Otherwise, that diamond necklace
would'Őve been long gone.
Exactly. I don'Őt think
the motive for Lucas'Ős murder
was robbery either.
The killer just wanted us
to believe that.
So, it'Ős looking like Lucas
and Penny were attacked by
the same person.
What'Ős with the rice?
Tiny pieces of rice
found on Lucas'Ős hair.
No one found
an explanation for it.
Yeah. Nor for the antifreeze
in his nose.
Yeah. No, I saw that,
but rice? How does somebody
get rice in their hair?
I mean, where was this guy?
At a wedding?
I doubt that milling rice
was his idea of a good time.
- Just saying. Make a note.
- Noted. What else we got?
For the two years
prior to his death,
Lucas worked as a tennis coach
at the Marina Azul Beach Club.
So, do we think Lucas'Ős killer
is part of the beach club set?
Uh, Detective Boding interviewed
at least a dozen people
from the club.
According to his investigation,
their alibis check out.
Well, Penny didn'Őt think so.
There are
club members all over her board.
And her receipts show
she went there a lot.
If you can'Őt afford a membership
to the club...
Date a member.
Morris. So, we know Penny
came up with an identity,
bought clothes to blend in,
then started going with Morris
to do her own investigation
into the death of her boyfriend.
Which probably means
either Morris found out
and filed
a missing person'Ős report
on his own victim...
Or whoever killed Lucas
wanted to silence Penny 'Őcause
she was getting too close.
Go find out which.
Okay, but why would you think
that they wouldn'Őt let you in?
I'Őve worked
in these kinds of places,
and we didn'Őt let me in.
Huh.
Uh, there'Ős Morris.
Looks like he belongs
on the campaign trail.
Tracks for a place like this.
Can I help you with something?
Yes, we'Őre investigating
a crime in the area.
Who'Ős in charge here?
That would be Mr. Wilson.
But I'Őm afraid I can't
let you past the main foyer.
Yeah, you guys have
a strict dress code?
I'Őm sorry, but yes, we do.
- And I'Őm not passing it?
- I'Őm afraid so.
Club rules state no denim,
no shorts and no graphic tees,
but we can offer you a blazer.
- Oh. A blazer. Do you hear that?
- Yeah.
Hang on though. What about
my car and my bank account
and my kids in...
in public school?
I guess what I'Őm asking is
how much does this blazer
actually cover?
Like, is it a magic blazer?
My grandfather founded
the Marina Azul Beach Club
in 1974.
He bought 20 acres
of beachfront property
for less than I paid
for a year at grad school.
- It'Ős very nice.
- Yeah, our members
seem to think so.
Oceanfront dining,
poolside cafŽ,
ten tennis courts.
We'Őre not here for the tour,
Mr. Wilson.
Did you hear about
the young woman that was found
a mile down shore?
No, no. We have a private beach,
so we don'Őt really mingle
with the public.
Different crowd.
Edward.
Yo. Ross wanted
to switch the cab
with his favorite merlot,
but I thought we agreed
the 'Ő95 was garbage.
I'Őm with the guests, Blaine.
This is Blaine, our head of
guest services here at the club.
I'Őm also his brother,
which Eddie likes to,
uh, leave out.
Are you... You a new member?
Nope. You recognize her?
Yeah. Yeah, maybe.
Uh, what'Ős her name?
She'Ős...
She'Ős with Morris, right?
Yes. Have you seen her talk
to anyone recently?
Sorry, guys, I meet a lot of
members'Ő girlfriends,
but I don'Őt really keep track
until one'Ős wearing a rock
and they wanna rent the place
for a wedding.
You guys must remember this one.
- Oh, they do.
- Yeah, that'Ős, uh, Lucas.
He was a tennis instructor here.
He was very popular.
It'Ős a real shame.
Anything else?
Not really. It'Ős been
a couple of years, man.
Hmm.
You know what?
I'Őm gonna give you my card.
You give me a call
if you remember anything.
I tell you what,
if I think of anything else,
I'Őll just call 911.
Of course they'Őre brothers.
Very handsome. Very smug.
Very unhelpful.
I'Őm gonna try to get a warrant
so we can take a look
at their personal profiles.
Yes. Thank you. I can take that.
- Yeah. Burn it.
- Ah.
- How'Őd you get that black eye?
- Oh, I'Őm fine. Thank you.
- Did a member do that?
-  No.
It wasn'Őt one of ours.
Yesterday, a gentleman
on the beach was trying
to sell some illegal goods.
Got him off the property,
he landed one on me.
Did you get
this gentleman'Ős name?
Cameron Smith, aka Swizz.
Two priors for assault,
one for possession,
one for public nudity.
Club attendant
says he'Ős out here
at the same time every day.
And if he was kicked out
of the club an hour before
Penny was attacked,
then he must'Őve been
in the area.
But what does he have to do
with what happened
to Lucas and Penny?
Maybe nothing,
but if Lucas was killed
because of something
that happened in the club,
and this guy was
selling drugs to its members,
he had to know something.
- Here'Ős our guy.
- You sure?
Pretty sure.
You comfortable over there?
Matter of fact, I am.
Help yourself.
So, why y'Őall being
so nice to me?
Are people not normally
nice to you?
In general, no. But maybe I
haven'Őt done myself any favors.
Shouldn'Őt have to.
People should still be nice.
Did you know Lucas Phillips?
Found dead on the beach
a couple years ago?
How about this?
What about her?
His girlfriend at the time.
You know her, right?
She'Ős clinging to life
after being hit in the head
and dumped on the beach.
She barely had a pulse
when we found her.
Did you see her last night?
There'Ős a detective
out in that bullpen
doing a track and trace
on your phone right now,
so you might as well
just tell us the truth.
Especially if you didn'Őt do
anything wrong.
Besides assaulting a valet guy,
which I could arrest you for
right now.
Have you seen her recently?
- Yeah, I saw her.
- And?
And all I did was tell her
to stop coming around
acting like I'Őm the one
that killed Lucas.
I don'Őt like
being accused of things
that I didn'Őt do.
That girl wouldn'Őt let up.
At about what time was that?
I don'Őt know.
Like, 9:00 o'Őclock. Just before
I went to the beach club.
I know it looks bad, okay?
But I wasn'Őt selling drugs
on their beach.
I was just trying to get
in the club to see Blaine.
He'Ős been dodging me for weeks.
Why is Blaine dodging you?
'ŐCause he still owes me money.
I'Őm sorry,
Blaine owes you money?
See? That'Ős the problem
right there.
You folks spend all your time
judging guys like me,
but never shine the light on
all those privileged-ass people.
Maybe we will.
But first we'Őre gonna
go talk to Penny.
Because she just woke up.
Penny, hi.
I'Őm Detective Karadec.
This is Morgan,
she'Ős assisting me on your case.
Hi. Glad you'Őre back.
It'Ős good to be back.
Yeah, she'Ős feeling much better.
Uh, Morris, would you mind
giving us a minute?
Of course.
I can'Őt believe he's still here.
He didn'Őt even know
my real name until yesterday.
Hmm.
Penny, tell us everything
you remember about last night.
I was responding
to one of the calls.
- From your billboard?
- Yes.
But this one seemed legit. It...
They said they saw
the attack on Lucas.
So, I went to meet them
at the beach.
And then what happened?
I... I felt something
hit me from behind.
The next thing I remember
is waking up in the water.
I didn'Őt even see their face.
I just want all this to be over.
Well, the good news is
that'Ős why we're here.
Thank you. But I should'Őve
never gone this far.
But I had to know
who killed Lucas.
Yeah. It sounds like he was
a pretty special guy.
One of a kind.
That'Ős a really
beautiful necklace.
He gave it to me
the week that he died.
Um, Penny, we may
have to reopen Lucas'Ős case
to find out who did this to you.
Was there anything about
the days leading up to his death
that stuck out to you?
I'Őve gone over it
a million times in my head,
but I could never find
anything concrete.
What about the beach club?
We spent a little time there.
Can you tell us
anything about that?
Lucas loved it.
The job, the people.
I thought
the whole idea of it was weird.
What do you know about Blaine?
We saw that you had
a picture of him in your closet.
Lucas and Blaine
had some nasty run-ins.
One was so bad,
Blaine suspended Lucas.
Said if there was
another problem, he'Őd fire him.
I tried to get to him,
but it was hard,
because he is well-protected
by his brother.
Well, I think that
about does it for us.
Penny, we'Őll make sure
we leave one of our officers
here with you
- while we keep investigating.
- You rest. Continue to heal.
We'Őre gonna go find out
who did this.
I hope you'Őre right.
I know my brother.
He wouldn'Őt hurt anybody.
You sure about that?
Because everyone
we talked to says
he just plays by his own rules.
Blaine'Ős not perfect,
but I know he can explain
all this when he gets back.
- And when might that be?
- I don'Őt know exactly.
Can I ask you
a serious question?
Did you rob
an airport gift shop?
What? No.
Each year, Blaine and I pick
a different country to visit.
We'Őve been doing it
since we first traveled
the Mediterranean as kids.
You gonna arrest me for that?
Well, if your brother
murdered one person
and tried to kill another,
and you'Őve been protecting him,
I will absolutely arrest you.
I would do anything
for my brother, and I have,
but we'Őre talking about
murder here.
Getting him through rehab,
that'Ős one thing, okay?
Covering up
his money troubles, sure.
But what you'Őre suggesting,
it'Ős insane.
And Blaine,
I'Őve been there to help him
through the lowest of lows,
and now he'Ős through the fog.
So, I really don'Őt
appreciate you standing there
and accusing him of something
I know he didn'Őt do.
I can appreciate that, but we
still need to talk to him.
He was checking in with
his sponsor a few hours ago.
Feel free to come back.
Oh, we'Őll be back.
I think Morris is out.
Blaine is clearly dodging us.
A meeting with a sponsor
shouldn'Őt take this long.
Yep, I agree.
But I might have someone
just as interesting
for us to talk to.
Who?
Her.
Oh, I love your necklace.
Oh. Thank you.
My husband
had it custom-made for me
to celebrate
our tenth wedding anniversary.
Oh. Do you wanna guess
how many diamonds?
You go ahead.
I'Őm guessing 120 diamonds
for 120 months of marriage.
That'Ős right.
One of a kind, he said.
Just like me.
Corny, I know.
I mean, I guess it'Ős not corny
if you mean it.
- Did you say
it was one of a kind, though?
- Yeah, because we just saw one
that looked exactly like that.
We did. We did, right? Except
that one was real diamonds.
This one'Ős moissanite.
Sorry, I'Őm not familiar.
Oh, you'Őre about to be.
Yeah, sodium carbide.
It was discovered by
French scientist Henri Moissan
in a meteor crater in 1893.
Nowadays, they'Őre lab-grown,
but that makes them
a great alternative
to mined diamonds,
and you can barely tell
the difference.
They'Őre more ethical,
better on the environment,
certainly more economical,
and their
double refractory properties
makes them throw rainbows
whereas diamonds throw white.
Who are you guys?
The ones investigating
the attack on this young woman.
You recognize her?
I'Őm sorry,
I don'Őt know who that is.
What about her boyfriend, Lucas?
I gave the real one to Lucas.
Why would you give it to him?
Should we just ask
your husband about it?
Shelby Havertz
was having an affair
with the club'Ős head of
guest services, Blaine Wilson.
And Shelby'Ős
not just any member.
Her husband
is on the city council,
which means if he found out,
club'Ős liquor license goes away.
Lucas found out about
Shelby and Blaine.
Shelby didn'Őt want
her husband to ruin
her boyfriend'Ős business.
Yeah, so Shelby gave Lucas
her expensive necklace
to keep him quiet,
and bought herself
a cheaper replica.
And then Lucas
gave the real diamond necklace
to Penny.
Now, Blaine didn'Őt think Lucas
would keep quiet. That'Ős motive.
Where'Ős Blaine now?
We'Őre waiting on confirmation,
but supposedly with his sponsor.
Uh, is this about the rice?
No, it'Ős about his shorts. Look.
His shorts are wet,
but his hair'Ős dry.
But if he was killed
at 10:00 p.m.,
wouldn'Őt his body be
on the beach all night long?
- Yes.
-  Well, okay.
The problem is,
high tide happens
around here twice a day.
Once in the afternoon,
once between 1:00 and 2:00 a.m.
So when they found his body
on the beach in the morning--
He should'Őve been
totally soaked from the tide,
but he wasn'Őt.
Either we have
the wrong time of death...
Or Lucas didn'Őt die
on the beach.
I think Lucas
was killed somewhere else.
For all we know,
he could'Őve been stuffed
inside a suitcase.
Probably by somebody who waited
until the beach would be empty.
His body was placed there
by the killer
sometime after high tide.
Which means we have to find
the actual crime scene.
Daphne, where we at with
the Lucas Phillips cold case?
Sending all CCTV
for Carbon Beach
and surrounding areas
on the day of Lucas'Ős murder
back to the team for review.
And everyone'Ős clear on
what we'Őre looking for?
Anyone moving a bag
that could have a body inside.
Detective, I need you and Lyons
to double-check
the alibis of everybody
on this board, please.
On it.
I don'Őt care if they want
a statement. The answer is no.
Talk to me.
Well, now that we'Őre looking for
a completely different
crime scene,
I think we should circle back
to a few of these people
one more time.
-  Which ones?
- It'Ős too soon to tell,
but we'Őll zero in.
Oz is going back over
all the forensics now.
Only 15% of cold cases
get solved. Less than ten
after two years.
Yeah, we have our work cut out
for us, Morgan.
That'Ős why
we'Őre digging in, right?
I know. I just wish I could see
what I'Őm missing.
Don'Őt be so hard on yourself.
You just figured out
Lucas'Ős body was moved.
And if we find
where he was actually killed,
- it could lead us to--
- To who actually did it.
Yes, I understand that.
But are we really
spinning our wheels looking for
a two-year-old crime scene?
And Daphne'Ős gonna spend
the next 18 hours doing what?
Looking for a car
that drove near the beach
that maybe had a dead body in it
that we wouldn'Őt be able
to see anyway?
Morgan, it'Ős time well spent
if it gets us somewhere.
Even if it takes days or weeks--
Or months, or even years.
Yeah, I'Őm well aware.
Yeah, that'Ős what we do.
Review evidence with fresh eyes.
I will eat and sleep here
if it means finding something
on Lucas'Ős body
that came from
the real crime scene.
That sends us to a new location.
A new location sends us back
to one of those suspects
on the board.
I mean, we weren'Őt looking at it
through the right lens before.
We are now,
because of you.
Is this
your first bullpen speech?
Out loud, yeah.
Very inspiring.
So, what do you think?
That maybe Lucas was attacked
in a kitchen or a restaurant.
Yes. We can'Őt forget
about the rice.
Look, we'Őve been
burning it at both ends.
Let'Ős regroup and hit it hard
in the morning, shall we?
Morgan.
I know why this case
is hitting a nerve.
I feel your frustration.
Look, I'Őve kept my commitment
to digging deeper into Roman.
- But I need to know
that you'Őre really--
- It'Ős not just about me.
In many ways, I had moved on.
My daughter thinking that
she was abandoned by her dad?
That'Ős gonna hang over
every moment of her life.
Okay. Go home.
I'Őll see you tomorrow.
Lucas and Blaine
had some nasty run-ins.
I would do anything
for my brother, and I have.
I don'Őt like
being accused of things
that I didn'Őt do.
Hi, it'Ős me.
I can see that.
I just texted you a menu.
Do you like Chinese?
Would you like to come in?
Does anybody live here?
Ooh, is that a blue rose?
Love those.
You know they don'Őt grow
out of the ground like that,
right? People make 'Őem.
Hmm.
The Italians
believe they represent
a longing for the impossible,
or a relationship that can'Őt--
Morgan, my apartment is not
a case or a crime scene. So...
Okay. Got it. Um, okay.
This is what I was thinking,
and feel free to kick me out
or tell me to shut up
or whatever,
but I kind of knew
you'Őd be here working on this,
and I can'Őt seem
to shut it down either,
so I thought that maybe we--
You'Őd just swing by uninvited
in the hopes
that together
we might find something
that helps with the case.
Yes.
I like it. Let'Ős get started.
Oh. Great.
- What?
- I just...
If I don'Őt eat something soon,
I'Őm gonna pass out.
So, if you could
just check out the menu.
- Yeah.
First of all, I don'Őt understand
what'Ős going on with
the antifreeze, right?
- That doesn'Őt make any sense.
- Can you make it make sense?
So, look. Take this.
Baby, I can never tell
How do you sleep so well?
How are you gonna
look at that face and tell me
that you don'Őt hate this face.
No. I hate that face,
but we cannot prosecute a face.
Did you see
how tall his hair was?
I don'Őt trust that.
But then you wake up
For the sunrise
You know
You don'Őt gotta pretend...
- I will look through...
- I already looked through
all of those.
Don'Őt you
Just wanna wake up...
Mmm. Right here,
we'Őve got a flimsy alibi...
- Mm-hmm.
- ...a bad attitude
and, uh, a bruised ego.
- So, that'Ős motive.
- A bad mustache.
...babe, I think it'Ős great
But while in this world
I think
I'Őll take my whiskey neat
My coffee black
And my bed at three
You'Őre too sweet for me
-  There you go.
- Maybe this was a mistake.
The pop by or ordering Chinese?
- Both.
- Well...
...we are gonna solve
this thing, Gillory.
I can feel it in my bones.
They teach you that
in the academy?
Feeling things in your bones?
I'Őm just saying.
I wouldn'Őt bet against us.
I like the confidence.
You know who else would like
that confidence? Tom.
Tom cooks.
Wanted to cook me dinner.
He asked about last night,
but we are still working
this case.
So, I don'Őt see that happening
anytime soon.
It'Őll happen.
Do you want it to happen?
Yeah. I think I do.
Her name was Lucia.
When I proposed,
she made that for me.
Meh. It'Ős for the best.
She deserved to be with a man
who wasn'Őt more in love
with something else.
This.
I'Őll see you later.
See ya.
- She'Ős back.
- We gotta go. Now.
- Go where? Why?
- I'Őll explain it all in the car.
But I know who killed Lucas.
And how do you know
it was Edward?
Okay. So, in the late 1870s,
a man named Erwin Perzy
was trying to develop
an ultrabright light source
for a surgical lamp.
But what he accidentally
ended up inventing
was the snow globe.
Snow globe?
Morgan, there are
a dozen officers
racing down PCH right now.
Why are we talking about
snow globes?
Because a snow globe
was the murder weapon.
- I think that'Ős a bit of a leap.
- Just stay with me, okay?
Throughout history,
they'Őve tried
tons of different things
to make the snow
in snow globes float:
Wax, soap, sand, bone fragments,
metal shavings, sawdust,
and last but not least...
Rice.
And the trace amounts
of glycol found in
Lucas'Ős nasal passages...
Antifreeze.
Antifreeze is what they put
into snow globes to keep
the liquid from freezing.
So you think Edward used
the snow globe to kill Lucas?
I do. Do you remember
when we were in his office?
They had all those souvenirs
from their world travels.
Edward was talking about
that one fancy trip
to the Mediterranean.
That'Ős Italy, Greece,
France and Spain.
I saw souvenirs
from Italy, France and Spain.
I did not see
a souvenir from Greece.
The snow globe.
That'Ős right.
Here'Ős what I think happened.
I think Lucas
had had it with Blaine.
The affairs, the drugs,
the fraud. He had to go.
But Edward was never gonna
turn his back on his brother.
So when Lucas came to Edward
and gave him an ultimatum,
fire Blaine or he spills
all of his secrets,
Edward killed Lucas to protect
his brother and the club.
- But then there was Penny.
- The case was cold.
She was the only one
keeping it alive
because she was obsessed with
solving the crime.
And Edward was obsessed
with covering it up.
You do realize, Morgan,
this is all circumstantial
unless we can get Edward
to confess.
Great. Let'Ős go do that.
On me. Moskowitz, Kingston.
West exits now.
- Got it.
- Copy.
- Morgan. Please remember--
- Yeah. I hang back.
You go first.
How could I forget?
Everybody,
out of the building right now.
Let'Ős go. Nice and slow.
- Excuse me.
What the hell is going on?
- Where'Ős your brother?
- My brother? Why?
- Where is he?
- In our office.
- Thank you.
Edward?
He'Ős on the run.
Suspect is on the move.
I need all exits covered.
He'Ős on foot heading west.
Morgan, we gotta get you
someplace safe
until we lock down the area
and get Edward into custody.
Come on.
- Karadec?
- What?
I think I know
where he'Ős heading.
Edward, come on down.
It'Ős over.
You'Őre right.
It is over.
Hey. Just hold on
for a second, okay?
Let'Ős talk about this.
You were just looking out
for your brother.
The way you have been
your whole life.
What do you think'Ős
gonna happen to Blaine
if you step off that ledge?
Edward.
Ed, she'Ős right.
Don'Őt do this, man.
Look, you'Őre all that I got.
I need you.
I'Őm gonna be okay.
All right. Let'Ős go.
Take care of yourself.
Well, I told you
we'Őd solve this one.
Look at you being right
about something.
Ha.
Looks like I'Őll be able
to make that date
with Tom after all.
You want a ride to his place?
No. You can just
drop me off at my car.
I got a few stops to make.
Wine?
Well, wine, but Penny.
I wanna be the one to tell her.
Hmm.
Hey.
It was Edward. We got him.
When you'Őre ready,
we'Őll fill you in
on everything, okay?
I know it doesn'Őt
bring Lucas back,
but I hope that at least--
Now... Now I know.
Yeah.
Thank you.
You'Őre welcome.
Why is that so funny?
I don'Őt know.
I just can'Őt picture you
in a high school band uniform.
- Why not?
- That'Ős actually a lie.
I can very much picture it.
I just don'Őt think
you want me to.
Hey, I was very, very good.
Second chair clarinet.
And those wind section kids
were very competitive.
Any chance you still have
that uniform? I wouldn'Őt
hate it if you threw it on.
Whoa. Slow down.
That'Ős good.
Mmm. Thank you.
They'Őre called torrijas.
It'Ős actually a family recipe.
Well, then, please thank
your entire family for me.
I will.
You don'Őt know
my last name, do you?
Hey, I could tell you,
but I don'Őt...
I don'Őt wanna rush this.
I really appreciate that.
- It'Ős--
- Flores.
I see what you did there.
Mm-hmm.
I hide it well,
but I'Őve got a lot going on too.
There were some changes
in my life that I had to make
that I probably should have made
a long time ago.
It cost me
some relationships that I'Őm
still trying to repair.
Don'Őt worry I'Őm not gonna
unpack it all for you
and ruin this amazing night,
but, um...
The point is...
life is messy,
especially when
it gets to our age.
I'Őm so much younger than you.
I just like being around you.
It'Ős as simple as that.
So, I'Őm thinking...
that if we keep it that way,
then, I don'Őt know,
maybe the chaos around us
starts to feel
a little less chaotic.
Maybe.
You'Őre still picturing me
in band, aren'Őt you?
I mean, not 'Őcause I want to.
It just won'Őt go away.
I get it.
- Sorry.
- No, go ahead.
Hey, Lieutenant.
If a child
A child cries
Would you not forgive them?
Why don'Őt you close that?
Yeah, I might seem so strong
Yeah, I might speak...
Okay. I'Őm here.
Morgan, when someone'Ős
been missing as long as Roman,
it'Ős hard to find anything
besides some old impound files
and the diapers he bought
the day he disappeared.
I understand.
That'Ős why it's taking me
so long to find anything useful,
to find someone to talk to
who might know something.
What are you saying?
I'Őm saying that
when I started digging into
every aspect of Roman'Ős life,
tracking where he was going
in the days before
he disappeared,
I came across a guy.
Someone Roman met with
more than once.
Did you get a name?
Gio Cornforth.
Ring any bells?
No. I have never heard
that name before.
What do we know about him?
Clean record.
No digital footprint.
But I did find out that Gio
is known as a concierge.
Not the kind normal people use.
He procures
certain items for individuals
on both sides of the law.
If Roman was dealing
with a guy like that, then,
let'Ős just say,
it begs a lot of questions.
So we'Őre working on a plan
to get him here.
Set up an interview.
Get some answers.
This Gio sounds like
a hard guy to find.
He is.
But you found him, didn'Őt you?
I did.
When did you do all this?
In the shadows
when no one was looking.
And that'Ős how it stays
until we know a lot more
than we know now.
Okay?
Okay.