[in Yiddish] Time for the four questions.
Come on, dear.
You were so excited for this.
"Dear Father,
I'd like to ask you four questions.
Dear Father,
I asked you the four questions.
Now please give me an answer."
"And the answer is:
we were slaves to the pharaoh in Egypt.
And the Lord took us out of there.
And if He didn't take
our forefathers out of Egypt,
then we and our children
and our children's children
would still be enslaved
to the pharaoh in Egypt."
We tell ourselves the story of Passover
to remind us of our suffering.
Not only from the Egyptians.
But also the inquisition,
the Chmielnicki uprising, the Pogroms,
the Nazis.
May their memories be erased.
In every generation,
they rise up against us.
When we trusted our friends and neighbors,
God punished us.
When we tried to wear their clothes
and speak their tongue, God punished us.
When we forget who we are,
we invite God's wrath.
It's why we are all sitting here now.
Now we accept who we are.
And that is the only way
to be free.
[sentimental music playing]
[Esty's grandfather continues praying]
[sentimental music continues playing]
[Esty breathes heavily]
[sighs]
[whispers Yiddish prayer]
[guests praying in Yiddish]
[baby gurgling]
[woman cooing]
[woman] Isn't he cute?
He's very cute.
If you ever want to talk,
let me know.
[baby crying]
At the beginning, it was hard for me, too.
But now I've got five and six on the way.
Thank God!
[Esty] I'm so happy for you.
[baby continues crying]
[in English] I'm sorry...
[in Yiddish] I need some air.
[baby continues crying]
[melancholic music playing]
Yanky!
I have something to tell you.
[Yanky] You left me alone
with your entire family tonight.
Sit down!
My mother says we can't go on like this.
Like what?
We have to change something.
Your mother told you that?
I want a divorce.
A divorce?
She says you'll never
be a good wife to me.
- But...
- We finished once!
Only once.
It always hurts you.
It's always something with you.
And I'm still young enough to remarry.
What else can I do?
You're asking me?
Has your mother
already called the matchmaker?
Has she?
Calm down!
Fine!
[shouts] God help me!
[suspenseful music playing]
Where were you?
So a Jew is stranded on a desert island.
A ship shows up to save him.
He shows the captain around.
The Jew points out a house he's built
and says, "That's my synagogue."
They walk around
and the Jew points out another house.
"That's the other synagogue," he says.
The captain is confused and asks him,
"You're only one guy,
so why do you need two synagogues?"
The Jew says,
"Oh, I never go into that one."
You stink like an ashtray.
- [Mike in English] They read the review...
- [Ahmed] It's gonna be a... two-plus?
[Mike] A two-plus...
From one to five, or from one to ten?
Esty!
What a lovely surprise!
No worries.
Your secret is safe with us.
Which secret?
[both chuckle]
- Mike's just made coffee. Have a seat.
- [Mike] Yeah.
Thanks, but... Have you seen Dasia?
No, I think...
Yeah, I think she already left for school.
Do you think I can get my things
from her room?
Of course.
Thank you.
I'll be back in a minute.
[Moishe exhales]
[in Yiddish] So I found Esty.
What?
Where?
Exactly where I told you she'd be.
That's impossible.
Leah Mandelbaum said she'd call me
if she heard anything.
That woman is a deviant, Yanky.
Why would you believe anything she said?
Why would I believe anything you say?
Who is that?
[Moishe] Who do you think?
[sentimental music playing]
Who's she with?
[Moishe] Ask her yourself.
How do I make this bigger?
[in English] Audition?
[in Yiddish] That letter was addressed
to Leah Mandelbaum's apartment.
[Ahmed in English]
So, are you ready for your audition?
No.
When is it?
Tomorrow morning.
9:00 a.m.
Well, that gives you exactly
23 more hours to panic.
Coffee first, panic later.
Okay?
Well, much more importantly,
what are you going to wear?
This...
[Ahmed] Okay.
But add some lipstick.
It looked great on you last night.
[Robert] Hi.
Good morning.
- Hungry?
- [Robert chuckles]
Do you still want to do...
what we talked about?
- Because I just saw...
- Yes, yes.
Yes, please.
May I ask
where you're taking this young lady?
Uh-uh.
You'll see.
Did you tell him about me?
Of course. He's a really nice guy.
Oh, hi, Esty. Nice to meet you. Come in.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
Yes...
[Malka in Yiddish] Mommy!
They had nice cherries
at Mr. Silverman's for 50% off.
We can bake a pie for tomorrow.
Mommy?
Malky,
my heart...
[Malka] What's wrong?
- What is it?
- [Esty's grandma moans]
Hold on to me.
- Hold on to me.
- [Esty's grandma moans]
Mommy, hold on to me.
[footsteps running upstairs]
[Yanky in English] You lied to me.
I know she's here.
[Leah] She's not!
[Yanky] Then where is she?
I know about the audition.
[shouts] Tell me the truth!
Where is my wife?
[Leah shouts] Stop it!
[both breathe heavily]
[Yanky cries]
[sobs] I'm sorry.
[Yanky crying]
[Yanky breathing heavily]
I asked her for a divorce.
Why?
Because I didn't think
she could get pregnant.
But then she did.
Esty's pregnant?
That's why you're chasing her, isn't it?
That's why the rabbi
sent your cousin after her.
I have to take her home.
That's my child she's carrying.
What else can I do?
Ask Esty what she wants.
[tires squealing]
[Esty panting]
[Esty yells]
[Esty yelling]
- [Esty whimpers] No!
- [woman in German] Do you need help? Hey!
[Esty shouts]
[in Yiddish] Don't touch me!
God's watching you.
Me?
Both of us.
And what does God think of you, Esther?
Who is this person?
[in English] Igor,
say hello to my cousin's wife, Esther.
I don't think you properly met.
[Igor] Shalom.
[Esty in Yiddish] Don't touch me!
Go!
Sit.
What are we doing here?
Do you know Mr. Auerbach?
From the bakery?
[in English] Is this a trick question?
[in Yiddish]
Of course I know Mr. Auerbach.
He was born here.
What?
On this playground?
[Moishe] More or less.
There was a building here before the war.
It was bombed.
He was born in the building.
[in English] In 1932.
[in Yiddish] His parents got him out
on the last train to Rotterdam.
He made his way alone to England
and then to New York.
Everyone else was rounded up
on the street over there...
and taken away and killed in the camps.
Mr. Auerbach never saw his parents again.
That's a terrible story.
But Mr. Auerbach now has 13 children
and 30 grandchildren...
And a thriving bakery in Williamsburg.
Because he got out of this place!
This place is full of Jewish souls, Esty.
The souls of a million dead!
You want to raise a child
among all these dead?
The dead are with us anyway, Moishe!
It doesn't matter where we live.
You think my grandma doesn't eat
every single meal of her life
with the souls
of her dead parents and siblings?
No.
But thanks to your selfish ways,
now she's got another soul to feed.
Yours.
- [in English] In the kitchen?
- You shouldn't have!
[in Yiddish] How's your mother?
Not good. The doctor says
she's had a series of heart attacks.
But she wants to stay home.
She refuses to go to the hospital.
Let me know if we can help.
Thank you.
[in English] By the way...
[in Yiddish] Yanky's found Esty.
Did he tell her my mother's dying?
Of course not.
He has enough to worry about, chasing
down his crazy wife in a foreign country!
[in English] It takes two.
[in Yiddish]
Esty didn't ruin the marriage alone.
[Moishe] What will you do here?
With no skills, no money,
no experience, no contacts.
The world is a scary place.
You still have
a little cash in your pocket.
Your body is still warm from the meals
Yanky provided for you.
Give it a few months.
Talk to me when you're cold and hungry,
a world away
from anyone who ever cared for you!
I'll still have my mother.
Your mother?
The one who abandoned you
to wipe old peoples' asses
halfway around the world?
You think she'll welcome you
and your baby
into the home she shares
with her non-Jew lover?
No, Esty.
You've made your bed.
And now you're all alone in it.
Eventually, you'll come crawling back
to the community, of course.
But then it will be too late.
Things will never be the same.
What is that?
Come back now, Esty.
Or you'll always be
the Jew who lost their way,
waiting for God's final judgment.
There is one other way out.
Moishe.
Put it down!
Foolish girl.
I'm not going to shoot you.
If you don't come back,
you'll do it yourself.
[Esty breathes nervously]
[melancholic music playing]
[Vivian in English]
So, tell me everything.
How are you?
Pregnant.
But isn't that what you wanted?
Not like this.
This is America, Esty.
- You can make your own decisions.
- Williamsburg is not America.
You don't know the rules.
The rules are imaginary.
The eruv wires around the neighborhood
aren't electric,
there's no moat around the kingdom
of Williamsburg filled with crocodiles...
Their power is just in your head.
The Talmud says...
If not me, then who?
If not now, then when?
[Vivian] What is this?
Documents from my mother,
proving my right to German citizenship.
So...
will you help me?
[Esty] Hello.
How are you doing?
Good.
Um...
- This is my...
- Jewelry?
- Yeah.
- [man] Right.
All right, let's see what we've got here.
Two pearl necklaces, diamond earrings,
and pearl earrings?
How much for all of this?
I can give you 2,000 on consignment,
or 1,300 if you want the cash up-front.
I'm in a really tight spot here.
Is that really all you can do?
You, me, and everyone else, right?
Tight spots are my specialty.
All right, I'll give you 1,500 cash.
That's all I can do.
Okay.
[door buzzer sounds]
[Leah in German] Hello?
[in English] It's Esty.
[Leah] Esty?
[door buzzer sounds]
What happened?
Oh, Esty. Come, come inside.
[Esty breathing heavily]
[Esty sniffling]
[Leah] Oh, my God.
Okay...
- Can I take this?
- No, no.
[Leah] Okay, don't worry.
Don't worry.
- [Leah exhales]
- [Esty sniffling]
He chased me.
He wants to take me back to Williamsburg.
Moishe?
Did Moishe give you this?
- Did he follow you here?
- You know Moishe?
There's always a Moishe.
They would do anything, say anything,
to make you believe
you will not survive in the outside world.
But he's right.
I'm pregnant,
and I have no money, no education.
I have nothing to give this child.
You're its mother.
You'll give it your love.
Like you gave me yours?
- I don't even know what mothers do.
- I'll help you.
[Esty] Stop it.
- I promise I'll help you.
- I said, stop it!
No,
I won't stop.
This is the first time in 15 years
I get to speak to you without a chaperone.
No Malka, no Babby.
Listen to me.
I love you, and I'll help you.
- You left me.
- [Leah] No, I didn't.
You left when I was three,
and Babby and Malka had no choice...
You were taken from me.
- That's a lie.
- [Leah] No.
No, it isn't.
Look...
I was married off at 17
to a man in a foreign country.
Nobody prepared me
for living with your father.
It was...
impossible.
But then I had you,
and a friend helped me
find an apartment for us.
For us?
[Leah] Yeah, you and me.
Those few months were...
[sighs]
They were beautiful.
Until the rabbi sent his guys
to terrorize me, his Moishes,
calling, turning up
in the middle of the night.
And then they sent their lawyers,
and then I was out of my league.
I lost you in court.
And not a day went by
where I didn't think about you.
[sentimental music playing]
[prays in Yiddish]
[Yanky breathing heavily]
[melancholic music playing]
[paramedic]
How long has she been lying here?
[Esty's grandpa] I don't know.
- I found her like this and then I called.
- [paramedic] Does she take medicine?
- Our daughter always brought her medicine.
- [paramedic 2 in English] Charge 150.
[defibrillator whirring]
[paramedic 2] Clear.
Charge 190.
- [defibrillator whirring]
- [paramedic 2] Clear.
[heart monitor beeping slowly]
[defibrillator thumps]
[melancholic music continues playing]
[heart monitor flatlines]
[sighs]
[Esty's grandpa prays in Yiddish]
I have to make some phone calls.
[Esty's grandpa
continues praying in Yiddish]
[Leah] Nina.
- [Nina] Hmm?
- [in English] Come and have a look.
Beautiful.
Oh, that's a good idea.
It's perfect.
- I want to warm up first.
- [Leah] Okay.
I'll see you there?
Thank you.
[breathes heavily]
[takes a deep breath and exhales]
[sighs]
[in Yiddish] Slob.
[Robert in English] What took so long?
- Hey!
- [Robert] It's about to start.
Yeah, let's go.
[sentimental music playing]
[inhales deeply and exhales]
[footsteps approaching]
[chattering]
[Karim] Morning.
Thank you for giving me this opportunity.
Good luck.
[Sosena in German] Super! Wow.
[in English] My name is Esther Shapiro.
I'm from New York.
Miss Shapiro will be auditioning on piano.
Song...
Song?
- Yeah.
- [Ahmed whispers] Is this you?
Do you know about this?
Such a late change is very uncommon,
Miss Shapiro.
[Esty] I know.
And if you don't allow it, I understand.
[Karim] What will you be singing?
[Esty inhales and clears throat]
"An die Musik."
By Schubert.
Do we have anybody here
who can play that immediately?
Oh, actually...
I asked someone.
[Esty clears her throat]
[Karim] Whenever you're ready.
["An die Musik" by Schubert
playing over piano]
[in German] ♪ You champion of art ♪
♪ In how many awful hours ♪
♪ Where I was snared up ♪
♪ In life's vicious cycle
All those wretched hours ♪
♪ You have my heart... ♪
[Leah in English] You won't
mess this up for her. Understand me?
[in German] ♪...into a better world ♪
[in Yiddish] She belongs with us.
The baby, too.
[in English] You're not the only one
that can make threats.
[in German] ♪...into a better world ♪
[student in English] Yeah...
Good morning!
Get out.
[piano music continues playing]
Can you tell us why you chose this song?
My grandmother loved it.
It was our secret.
Why a secret?
[breathes nervously] Well, um...
I come from a community
in Williamsburg, Brooklyn...
where women are not allowed
to sing in public.
Why not?
A woman performing loudly among men
is considered to be immodest.
Even seductive.
Tell us a bit about your education.
[Esty] I went to school until I was 17.
[professor] But you have had
no formal musical training?
[Esty] I didn't have access
to proper training of any kind.
But for the past three years,
a musician living in a building
that belongs to my grandfather
gave me piano lessons
in exchange for rent.
This was also a secret.
I mean,
my husband knew, but...
he didn't approve.
[professor 2]
Miss Shapiro, how old are you?
Nineteen.
The piece you chose
is really better for soprano voices,
not mezzo sopranos like your own.
Maybe there's another piece
you could sing?
- [Karim] Miss Shapiro?
- [Esty] Hmm?
Have you prepared another piece?
It would be nice
to hear something different.
Okay.
[inhales deeply and exhales]
[sings in Yiddish]
[chattering]
[Mike in English] It's crazy.
[Yael] I didn't even know
she could sing at all.
[students chattering]
[Ahmed] Yeah.
[Yael] The second song...
I've heard Yiddish songs before.
But that was...
Don't keep your fan club waiting.
This is my...
mother.
[Ahmed] Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
- [Leah] Hey.
[Esty] Yanky?
[in Yiddish] When did you get here?
Just in time to hear you sing.
Your hair...
Everyone can see it.
You won't believe it,
but it's fashionable here.
I get it.
On the road there is a different Torah.
What?
[sentimental music playing]
[casino worker in German] Fifty.
[in English] Call.
Call.
[in Yiddish] I didn't know
you could sing like that.
You don't know
a lot of things about me, Yanky.
I don't even know
a lot of things about me.
We can discover those things together.
[casino worker in German] One hundred.
[in English] Raise.
[in German] Two hundred.
[in English] Call.
All in.
[Yanky in Yiddish]
This is where I'm staying.
- Come upstairs.
- No, Yanky.
I don't think that's a good idea.
I want to show you something.
Is this some trick Moishe cooked up?
Moishe?
No.
[in English] Showdown.
Set.
[in Yiddish]
I saw this and thought of you.
No. Yanky, please!
No gifts.
Come on.
Open it.
It's beautiful.
Thank you.
[Yanky] Listen...
I know about the baby.
It's a miracle, actually!
That's true.
Come home with me.
We'll be a family.
It's everything we always wanted.
- Esty...
- Is it?
Today,
when you sang that song,
I was reminded of our wedding.
We were so happy that day.
I was happy because I thought marrying you
was the beginning of a new life.
- But instead...
- We'll start over again!
You asked for a divorce.
It was the biggest mistake of my life.
Not just that...
Everything will be different
now that we have a child.
- It's not that simple.
- I know!
You were unhappy all the time.
I told myself
something was wrong with you.
But nothing
is wrong with you.
You're just different.
You said it yourself when we met.
So...
I can't go back.
Yes...
Yes, you can.
You'll see.
I can be different, too.
- Stop! Yanky!
- You don't believe me?
Stop!
Yanky, stop.
[cries] No.
[Yanky sobs]
[Esty moans]
- How about now?
- [Esty sighs]
Will you stay with me now?
[whispers] It's too late, Yanky.
Don't you understand?
It's too late.
Esther Shapiro.
Will you stay with me now?
We'll be back for that baby.
[Moishe laughs]
[sentimental music playing]
[chattering]
[child laughing]
[child in German] Mummy...
[sentimental music playing]
There she is.