I've dedicated myself to pursuing
not only the obvious offences,
but the hidden ones.
Cosette!
I'll find her.
If we were to part with her,
we'd want some compensation.
Are you my papa?
If you want me to be.
Marius Pontmercy, my grandson.
Let me spend some time
with my little boy.
Never! He will be brought up
to curse your very name.
Mon pere?
There was a man called Thenardier,
he saved my life.
If you ever meet him,
you do the best you can.
This man is Jean Valjean.
I beg you, care for this child.
Police!
He will never get away!
You may stay here
but you will be able
to see the child everyday.
Look at Marie Claire,
she can't wait until Friday.
What's happening on Friday?
Well, she's leaving, of course.
Oh, I didn't realise it was so soon.
Don't you wish you could, Cosette?
I don't know.
All the pretty dresses and parties.
Dancing and falling in love!
And getting engaged!
And doing that.
- Jermaine!
- Well, I'm only saying.
Look. That's my cousin.
Isn't he handsome?
I'll be seeing him on Saturday.
Oh, poor Cosette.
Why poor me?
You're going to be a bride
of Christ, aren't you?
Look.
Such a shame, you're
far too pretty for that.
Girls!
No more chatting!
Oh!
Father, not too tight!
You'll squash all the breath out of me.
Why? Are you such a fragile
little thing then?
You forget your own strength sometimes.
Forgive me.
I just cherish our
Saturday afternoons so much.
Come on.
What is it?
Come on, speak.
Am I really going to take the veil?
Well, that's what we discussed
with the abbess and Sister Simplice.
Have you changed your mind?
No.
I don't know.
I'm sorry, please don't be cross with me.
I could never be cross with you.
It's just I've seen nothing
of the world yet.
You have seen the world.
The inn at Montfermeil and that family.
Lies, violence, cruelty,
that's the world.
I don't believe it's all like that.
I thought…
I thought we'd found a home here together
where you could grow up
and I could grow old.
And you could grow old
and I'd die here and…
…we'd never be separated.
I'd be locked away…
…and I don't want that.
The police force of Paris
has established a standard of excellence
that is an example for the rest of France
and the world.
I call upon Inspector Javert
to accept the medal of honour
for his exceptional achievements
as a thief-taker.
It's a great honour, sir.
Reflects well on us all.
I can take no pleasure in it.
Not while that man is free.
Beg your pardon, sir, what man?
You know the man,
Pierre Madeleine, Jean Valjean,
whatever else he calls
himself now, that man.
Well, that's one man out of hundreds.
That was a decade ago.
- He may have been dead for years.
- No.
No.
I am convinced that he is still
alive and here in Paris,
laughing at us.
I shall never be at peace
until he is back in chains.
Monsieur.
Thank you, young man.
I've seen you at Mass, haven't I?
Yes.
Monsieur Pontmercy, isn't it?
Marius Pontmercy.
My name is Mabeuf.
Could we speak a few moments?
I used to watch a poor man who came
here regularly to see his child.
It was the only way he could,
because of a family arrangement.
Little boy knew nothing of it.
There was a rich old father-in-law
who threatened to disinherit the boy
if the father made any contact with him.
So, the father always stayed
behind that pillar there.
I'd watch him gaze at his son and weep.
Poor man so adored that child.
It's a very touching story, monsieur.
He was one of Napoleon's
bravest colonels.
His name was Pontmercy.
Your father.
"Saved ten Cossacks and
saved the life of his corporal."
"27 bone splinters extracted
from his left arm alone."
And listen to this one.
"A ship carrying General Guibert
"ran into a hornets' nest
of eight English ships.
"Rather than flee or hide,
Sub Lieutenant Pontmercy
"ran the tricolour up the flag staff
and sailed proudly past."
I never knew.
You lied to me.
You told me lies about my father.
I am your father.
Don't talk nonsense.
I have discovered that my father
was a humble and heroic man
who died forgotten
and neglected because of you.
I never knew him because of you.
And I never knew him and never wanted to,
or any of his kind.
They were all villains, murderers,
revolutionaries and thieves,
all of them.
Traitors who betrayed their king.
Then I say down with the King.
What did you just say?
I said down with the King.
Young man, I see that you
and I cannot remain
under the same roof any longer.
Get out!
I never want to see you again.
Now what have you done?
He… He'll be back
with his tail between his legs,
you… You mark my words.
I fear for you.
The world outside has changed.
There is anger and unrest in the streets.
What about that police officer,
the one who came here?
Thank you for your concern, sister.
I've everything prepared.
Is it really ours, Papa?
Come and have a look inside.
This is Toussaint.
Mademoiselle.
Bonjour.
A piano!
- Thank you.
- Monsieur.
God, look at this place.
Well, better apologise and
make your peace with Grandad, then.
- No, I shall never go back there.
- Look.
- Bonjour, mademoiselles.
- There you go.
- All home comforts.
- You're disgusting.
Yeah, I know.
Right, why don't you get settled in
and come and have a drink
at the Cafe Musain later?
Thank you, Courfeyrac,
you're a good friend.
Just the thing for a studious young man.
What is it you're
studying at the university?
Law, madame.
Well, then, you'll understand
that as the principal tenant
I am empowered
to see that you behave yourself.
No young ladies in your room
except by special permission.
Of course.
Thank you.
I'll leave you to settle in now.
- Bonsoir, monsieur.
- Bonsoir.
Bonsoir, monsieur.
Marius!
Yes. How are you?
Here he comes.
Large as life, our very own
pet royalist, Pontmercy.
Let me introduce you to these fellows.
Grantaire, Enjolras, Bossuet.
I have to say, first,
I'm not royalist any more.
What are you now then?
I'm a Bonapartist and a Democrat.
Now, that's a step
in the right direction.
Napoleon was a defender of the Republic
before he made himself Emperor.
Well, have a drink.
Yes, have a lot of drinks.
I say down with all nations
and down with all kings.
What about emperors?
An emperor is just a king
by another name, only worse.
I won't have it.
Napoleon made this country great.
He brought reforms through his conquests.
What a joy to serve
under such a man as that.
What could be greater?
To be free.
I want to be a citizen of the Republic,
not a subject of a king
or an emperor.
One day we'll all be fighting
to the death about that,
on one side or another.
And what side will you be on, my friend?
Psst, monsieur.
Monsieur, over here.
Look through the peephole.
Do you want to see more, monsieur?
No, I…
Show's over.
Nighty-night.
Papa, what was my mother like?
Don't make me speak of it.
She was one of my workers…
- …and I dismissed her.
- What for?
For nothing, for…
…concealing the truth.
What truth?
About you.
And after that,
she fell into poverty and…
…she was ill and…
…I tried to make amends,
but it was too late and she died.
So, now you see why
I want to protect you.
I don't want you to suffer
in the way that she did.
So were you planning
to keep me locked away here?
No, no, I…
Yes, Papa, this isn't
what we discussed at the convent,
or did I misunderstand?
You don't know what
the world is like, Cosette.
You've said that before
but I want to see for myself.
I'm lonely here, Papa.
It was better in the convent.
At least I had
the other girls to talk with.
All right, all right, I understand.
Tomorrow we can go
to the Luxembourg Gardens.
Oh, thank you, Papa!
Papa, I need new clothes.
Everyone looks so smart here.
If you say so.
Papa!
- Now, Monsieur…
- Fauchelevent.
Monsieur Fauchelevent,
it has been quite a pleasure
for me to dress your young friend.
My niece.
Well, yes, your niece, of course she is.
Such a lovely figure, it would be a shame
not to show it off,
I'm sure you'll agree with me.
Mademoiselle, come. Come, come, come.
There.
Turn, turn.
Do you like it, Papa?
Papa, that's so charming.
Er, I preferred you in
your old one, but if it pleases you.
Men, what do they know?
Shall we show him the others?
What about…?
Give me some of those letters.
Monsieur, s'il vous plait…
- Mademoiselle!
- Merci, monsieur.
- That's for you and
no-one else, all right?
Tres genereux.
Thank you.
It's not mine, it's my father's.
Oh…
Forgive me.
What's your name?
Cosette.
Marius Pontmercy.
Well, thank you again.
My pleasure, delighted
to meet you, mademoiselle.
Goodbye.
There was no need
to go running after him.
Who was that?
Oh, I don't know, just a young man.
Papa, what's the hurry?
It's turning chilly, I want to get home.
What's the matter?
My wrist, it's sore,
you were holding it so tightly.
Forgive me.
Here, let me kiss it better.
Why did you get into such a state?
Cosette, you have to understand
not everyone you meet
has your best interests at heart.
But nor is everyone
I meet a villain, surely?
No, but there are plenty
of young men about,
pleasant enough in manner and appearance,
whose sole aim in life
is to debauch young women.
Debauch, what does that mean?
To…
To lead them astray.
Well, I don't think Marius was that sort.
How do you know his name?
Well, he told me his name
and he asked me mine.
- What's wrong with that?
- And you told him?
- Yes.
- You told him your name?
He didn't mean any harm.
What makes you think you know that?
You know nothing of the world.
Because you want to protect me
from knowing anything.
I'll tell you one thing,
we won't be going back
to the Luxembourg Gardens for a while.
This place is like a prison.
You have no idea what a prison is.
Oh, come on, get that down you, huh?
Un… Deux, trois…
Any better?
I'm worse, if anything.
But does anybody else know
a better cure for love?
Revolution.
Come on, soldiers who spilled
their blood for France
are living as beggars.
I mean, your own father,
a hero, died a pauper.
Look at the slums, look,
look at the children starving,
while a fat king sits on the throne.
Paris is a tinderbox,
it'll only take a spark to set it off.
That's it.
Put your passion into
the fight for freedom,
then once the regime has withered away,
equality for all.
We can all take turns
on that nice girl of yours.
He's joking.
I apologise, truly, sincerely.
I have felt what you are feeling now.
An emptiness and despair.
We must struggle, we must
overcome these feelings.
How?
We could take him to the
Chaumiere at Sceaux.
You know, the place where all
the lost women can be found.
- You might even find yours there.
- Excellent idea.
We will all go.
You can count me out,
I've got better things to do
with my time, and so should you.
Count me out too.
No chance. You're coming,
even if we have to drag you.
Gah!
Come on.
Just stop.
Excuse me. Sorry.
Cosette!
Do you want me? For you,
I make a special price.
No, no, sorry.
Dommage.
Who'd have thought to find you here?
Get out of here,
you good for nothing whelp!
All right, I'm going.
All right, monsieur?
- Kiss it.
- No!
- You know you want to.
Oh, monsieur. Kiss it.
I was thinking of walking
out to watch the sunrise.
Thought you might like to come with me.
To the Luxembourg Gardens?
No.
Make ready. I'll wait for you.
Why this place, Papa?
There's something I wanted you to see.
What's that?
Papa, who are those men?
They're convicts.
From the prison hulks.
Can they really be men?
Yes, they're men.
They're men like me.
Cosette.
I think if I crossed paths with
one of those men, I would die,
just from looking him in the face.
What are you doing here?
What do you want?
It's a bit chilly in here.
Can I get in with you?
No.
I've got a letter for you.
Really, who from?
My dad.
Give it here.
- Jondrette. Is that your name?
- Sometimes it is.
He says your family
is starving. Is that true?
We don't eat often, monsieur.
Go fetch my purse. There, on the table.
Here. I can spare that much.
You don't have to.
He tries it on with everyone.
It's for you, not him.
Here.
Thanks.
How do you live in this place?
I live like this.
Get what I can, how I can.
I go out in the evenings and
sometimes don't come back at night.
Do you know what I mean?
Five francs! A shiner!
You're a star! Are you sure?
- I'm sure.
- What a gent.
Merci, monsieur, mille fois.
Au revoir, monsieur.
This is too stale for
you now. Can I have it?
Thanks.
You know what?
That Monsieur Marius is a gent.
I knew that letter was a good one.
It wasn't your letter that done it.
I done it. I told him my tale
and he took pity on me.
He likes me, Monsieur Marius.
- Did he do you, then?
- No, he's not like that.
- He's all pure at heart.
- Come here.
Come here, there's a good girl.
- What have you got in that hand?
- Nothing.
- Come on, open up.
- Show your pa what you've got.
That was for me, not you.
Argh!
Thieving whelp. You're a thieving
old bugger! I hate you.
Any more of that and
you'll really get one.
- I'm not scared of you.
- Oh, yeah?
All right, you've been a clever girl.
Just don't get above yourself.
Scum, the lot of them, swanning
around in their golden coaches.
What about me, eh?
Eh?
Suffering here in squalor.
Get him here. Can you do that?
Eponine, Azelma?
The old fellow with the young daughter?
Yeah, that's the one. You said
he looked like a soft touch.
And don't come back without an answer.
Oy!
Those terrible men.
To think of the things they must
have done to be punished so.
Why did you take me there?
Was it because you were angry with me?
- No.
- Did you want to frighten me?
No, no, Cosette, no. I…
Monsieur, Mademoiselle.
My poor father has written you a letter.
Please read it and take pity on us.
- A letter for me?
- He knows you're a kind man.
You have nothing more than this to wear?
No, sir, this is it.
I know the house.
We'll come. Tell your father
we'll be there later.
Pa will be so happy when I tell him.
- Papa.
- What?
I don't think we should go.
Why not?
That girl, I just have
a bad feeling about her.
Her family needs help,
Cosette, and I can give it.
You wish to know what the world is like,
well, you can come too.
They're coming.
Ah! Douse the fire, Rosalie.
You, light candles.
And you, break a window.
Well, go on! Put your fist
through it! Go on!
Monsieur, monsieur, s'il vous plait.
Merci, monsieur.
Oh, Azelma!
Don't cry. It'll only
make him more angry.
No, no, no, on the contrary, on the
contrary, bawl the place down.
We want him to see suffering.
You, in bed. That's it, that's it.
Aw, good girl, keep quiet.
Aw!
Go on.
Brave girl.
Monsieur. Mademoiselle.
Oh, welcome, welcome, sir,
to my humble abode.
Oh, and your charming
daughter too, come on, come in.
Come on.
I brought you some clothes, monsieur.
Some woollen stockings, blankets.
Oh, my angelic benefactor
is more than generous.
A thousand thanks, kind sir.
No, no, no, I wish, I wish woollen
stockings could pay the rent,
but I thank you, with all my…
Papa.
I see you're much to be pitied, monsieur.
Fabantou.
Did you not sign your letter Genflot?
My name is Genflot-Fabantou.
Of course.
You see, monsieur, all
I have to cover myself
is this chemise.
And my wife's sick, and my daughter
injured.
And six months rent in arrears.
That's 60 francs.
If it's not paid by tonight,
we're all out on the street.
Once I was a respected man,
and then one day, a man came
and stole my daughter from me.
Oh, if I could meet that man again,
I'd have something to say to him.
Do you know what I'm saying?
Oh, Mademoiselle!
It's such a shame for such as one
as you to be exposed
to such unpleasantness.
I have five francs about me.
There's people in the city
that would pay a lot
more than that to see you, I'm sure.
- I'm taking my daughter home.
- Don't forget your coat, Monsieur.
I'm leaving it. It's yours.
I'll return this evening at
six o'clock with 60 francs.
Noble sir, we'll be expecting you.
Don't forget this.
Cosette.
Are you going back there to that man?
Excuse me.
I have to go back,
to get him out of our lives.
I won't let him hurt you.
Rue Plumet. Oui, monsieur.
Oh!
Oh, you're down in the dumps.
What's the matter?
You brought them here, didn't you?
The old man and the girl.
Yeah, what about it?
So you know where they live.
Well, I don't know
the actual house, Monsieur Marius.
But you could find out
for me, couldn't you?
Depends. What do I get?
Anything you want.
Well, anything for you, Monsieur Marius.
But he may not live very long,
the old man.
What do you mean?
My dad's up to no good. Got to go.
Ah, evening, monsieur. All right?
Oh, if you hear a bit of noise
later on, don't worry,
we're having a little
party for a few friends.
- Bonsoir, monsieur.
- Bonsoir.
Right, tonight's the night.
He thinks he can get away with 60 francs.
He's got millions stashed away.
We'll put the screws
on him and get the lot.
You two, clear out,
I want you out of the way.
- What, her with her bad hand?
Fresh air will do it good. GO ON, HOP IT!
Get off. Go on.
Did you recognise him? Him?
The man who took the girl.
Oh, my God!
That horrible fine young lady that looked
at my girls with pity in her eyes?
Her, has to be.
I would give her a good kick in the
guts with my clogs on, I would.
Yeah, well, you may,
my dear, with my blessing.
I've got a couple of pals coming
round and we'll have some fun
with them, and then we'll take his money.
All of it.
And then what?
I think we'll have to do him in, my dear.
The Gorbeau Tenement, you say?
Yes, you know it?
I do.
Take these.
Go home, hide in your room, keep watch.
Let them carry on for a while.
We have to apprehend them in
commission of a crime.
You say you're a lawyer,
you'll understand that.
I'm a law student, Inspector.
Well, you'll just have to do.
When it's gone far enough,
fire a shot, in the air.
Are you frightened?
Er, I'm a little nervous.
Well, everything depends on you.
Six o'clock, you say?
- Right, all set?
- All set.
Right, well, I'll warm this up a bit.
For our friend, eh?
Hail Mary.
Right, this is it.
Oh, I knew you wouldn't let us down.
God bless you, sir.
Where's the child that was injured?
Her sister's taking her to the doctor.
We thought it best.
Children, more expense,
they're a hole in your wallet,
aren't they, eh?
Here.
That should cover your rent
and your immediate expenses.
There's more where that came from.
Paris is not the right place
for you and your family.
You should move to the countryside.
I can help you with that.
Yeah, that's very…
That's very thoughtful
of you, monsieur, certainly.
I'll certainly consider your kind
offer, but do you like paintings?
Well…
- Who is he?
- Just a neighbour.
As I was saying, if you like art,
I have a painting I might be induced
to sell to the right buyer.
Just neighbours.
Now feast your eyes on this.
A masterpiece by my own hand.
Depicting Sergeant Thenardier,
the hero of Waterloo.
And where's this hero now, eh?
It was I, Thenardier, who saved the
life of Colonel Pontmercy,
and never had so much as a word
of thanks for it,
and you were the bastard
that stole my little girl.
Seize him, boys! Tie him down.
Gah!
I'm a reasonable man. I don't want a lot.
200,000 francs should do it.
You wouldn't want no harm to come to
your pretty daughter now, would you? Eh?
Is that what you call her?
My friend Montparnasse
could slip up behind her
in the park and cut her throat.
I'd slit yours, too, for two sous.
You dare to threaten my Cosette.
Grab him!
Ow!
You think you can do
anything to impress me?
Look!
What?
Ah, ah!
Now do your worst!
Grab him!
Come on!
Hit him in the face!
Take them away. Lock them up.
Put down your weapons and surrender.
Don't touch my mum!
Attacking an officer?
The man you lured here. Where's he?
- Tell me!
- He's not here.
Shame you missed the real prize,
Inspector!
Two got away, sir.
Seen you before.
You're that student my
sister is sweet on.
Gavroche, son and heir.
There's nothing to nick in here,
if that was what you were thinking.
- I'm not a thief.
- Aren't you? I am.
No-one's going to help you, you've
got to help yourself, don't you?
Well, I'm off.
Where will you go?
Don't worry about me.
I've friends all over this place.
So long, monsieur.
Hail Mary, mother…
Papa! Papa!
Papa!
Now, old friend, you and I are
going to have a little talk.
And you're going to tell me everything.