[Ballard] Previously on Ballard...
[Chastain's wife]
He knew he got it wrong, Renée.
He overheard Olivas joking
about sleeping with an ex-partner.
But it was the way that Olivas said it.
It was like he had crossed a line
with this woman.
He tried to assault me at a party.
Jake can feel what he wants about Ballard.
If she's bungling the investigation,
I need to know.
Yesterday on the Pearlman case,
this was our list.
Today, we have narrowed it down
to 378 blue Ford vans.
Gonna be near impossible
investigating potential corruption
without stepping on a land mine.
So we should just ignore it?
[Ballard] This doesn't work
unless we're all on the same page.
You need to start trusting me.
We got a hit on that dummy bullet?
Guy's name is Javier Fuentes.
He's actually still in county.
- Who is he?
- He's a coyote for the cartel.
A ring of cops is running hot guns.
They take 'em straight off the streets
and sell them to the cartel for big bank.
The gun. Who gave it you?
It was definitely a cop.
LAPD. White dude, 40s.
Here are six candidates.
This guy, Anthony Driscoll.
He's got more than a few complaints
against him for excessive force.
[Javi] That's him right there.
If you find him,
I bet you find the others.
I would kill for the experience
you're getting in Cold Cases.
I'm shooting for detective
in a couple years.
[Driscoll] So...
[sighs]
...tell me about your new girlfriend.
You don't intentionally
make their fries soggy.
- Ever. And if you do...
- [waitress] Hi there. Hibiscus margarita.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, of course.
- And then, an old-fashioned. Yeah.
- Thank you.
So I'm working on getting
another medical certification.
Hoping it'll speed things along
in the EMT program.
- That's exciting.
- [Aaron] It's been tough
- juggling classes with work.
- Hey, baby.
- Where are you going?
- [waitress] Uh.
I'm also back around later.
But, uh, pretty soon,
I'm gonna be able to get on the truck.
- I hear the first...
- [waitress] No, I...I...
[patron] Come on.
- [waitress] I've got to go to the bar.
- Whoa, hey. What's up?
[patron] Can I get a kiss?
- I love you.
- Okay. Love you too.
- [sighs] Nothing. I... [grunts]
- [Aaron] Are you sure?
You seem a little out of it.
Is everything okay?
[Ballard sighs]
I'm sorry. I just, uh...
These cases. I-I feel like
I'm seeing bad guys everywhere.
- Peekaboo.
- [laughs]
[sighs] Oh, uh...
This too.
- It's okay?
- Sure.
Now you be a good boy for your mom now.
Okay.
All right.
Thanks.
[line ringing]
Not a bad break. I must say it myself.
- Mm-hmm. All right. Watch this.
- [chuckles]
Okay, hold on one second.
Hey. Uh, sorry, I meant to reach out.
Hope you're not getting distracted.
Nah.
Never that.
You sure?
'Cause I shouldn't have to call you
for an update.
Where we at with things?
Hey, it's all good. I'm in like Flynn.
Okay, lover boy. Take what you want.
Just make sure I get what I need. Quickly.
Otherwise, we'll have to get creative.
Okay. [chuckles] Okay. Don't get crazy.
Don't make me.
What's up?
Here.
Let me show you something.
Okay.
Okay. Ready?
Mm-hmm.
You're an expert now?
Oh, I got a few tricks
up my sleeve. Uh-huh.
- Widen your stance a little bit.
- Mm-hmm.
- Elbow down just a tad.
I like my way better.
- Well, I can't argue with that.
- Mm-hmm.
["I'm Hung Up On You" playing on radio]
[song stops]
[tense music plays]
[car lock beeps]
[person] Hey, Tony.
[chuckles] Good to see you.
You're late.
Mama told me to never arrive empty-handed.
- Chunky Monkey.
- [thumping]
Van's loaded up outside.
- Ah.
- It's got all the toys.
[thumping]
Like water into wine, Jesus.
- You, uh... You mind if I say hi?
- Go.
[both chuckle]
[muffled grunting]
[Driscoll sighs]
- I can't help you.
- [cries]
[Driscoll] I'm just the delivery guy.
[inhales sharply, grunts]
Today, it's guns. Yesterday...
- Yesterday, it was you.
- [breathing shakily]
But I'm not complaining.
You were easy money.
[sniffs] What they do with what I deliver?
Now, that's none of my business.
Just like whatever you were snitching
about was none of yours.
[muffled cries]
- You shoulda kept your mouth shut.
- [muffled screams, cries]
Always a pleasure.
- You need a ride?
- Thanks.
I got one.
[birds chirping]
[alarm clock ringing]
[ringing continues]
[sighs]
[Ted] It's like the Van Show around here.
We're still running 'em down.
Um, not the most exciting part of the job.
Yeah, not the most productive either.
Well, I... Until a better lead comes along,
this is the one we're mining.
Waiting for one to come along
isn't exactly a great look, Rawls.
- Good morning.
- Oh, hey.
Detective Ballard.
Rawls was just catching me up
on the strides you're making.
Yeah, I bet he was.
You know, it's just a lot of man-hours
devoted to these vans though.
Are you sure you're not putting
all your eggs in one basket?
A blue Ford van was spotted at two
murders that we related to Sarah's case.
So, yes, I'm confident
we're pursuing our best lead.
Mmm.
You know, the success of this new unit
could be a critical component
to Jake's upcoming election.
We'd really like to see Sarah's case
closed before the ballots go out.
Oh, yeah. Well, wouldn't that be nice?
Except my investigations don't run
on your political timeline.
They don't run at all
without Councilman's influence.
How about a weekly check-in moving forward
to make sure we're all on the same page?
Sure.
Great.
I look forward to
working together more closely.
It's not looking good.
Fifty vans down and they're all dead ends.
- How many are left?
- Four. But they were all scrapped.
That's why they got pushed
to the bottom of the list.
We can still check out the prior owner.
See if they have any overlap
with our victims.
But any hope of physical evidence?
That's out the window.
- Damn it.
- No, don't listen to him.
I actually think one of these
could be promising.
- Promising how?
- [Colleen] It's number 53 on the list.
My husband and I were married
on May 3rd. 5, 3.
- Oh, boy.
- [Martina chuckles]
What?
I am just following my gut.
Isn't that what you people do?
She's not wrong.
- Colleen.
- Van number 53 was scrapped in 2009.
But before that, it was registered
to a woman named Jenny Garrison.
- She lives in the valley.
- All right. I'll pay her a visit.
You guys dig in on the remaining three.
If I have to start over on this case,
I need to know sooner rather than later.
Do you mind if I go with?
Let's go.
Three vans left. One for each.
One.
Two.
Where is Laffont, anyway?
He's missing all the fun.
["Canon and Gigue in D major" playing]
You are in luck.
I'm whipping up a batch of baby Bundts,
and I need a taste tester.
A batch of baby Bundts?
- Mini Bundt cakes.
- [scoffs]
Then why not say that?
[stammers] My affinity for alliteration
is a gift whether you recognize it or not.
Just taste it.
Hmm?
- And this is--
- Lemon lavender.
I know. You weren't expecting it.
That is an elevated flavor profile
right there.
Mmm. And maybe a little less lavender.
- I mean, you're almost there, babe.
- [grunts] No, no, no.
- You are almost there.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. Less lavender it is.
I got it. Hmm.
What are you working on anyway?
You haven't brought a case home in ages.
And certainly not one this color coded.
- Just a pet project...
- Huh.
...that requires more space and quiet
than the office allows.
Oh. [chuckles]
Well, I like it.
It's nice having you home.
Back to the lab
to address your aggressive note.
[phone buzzes]
Yello.
How's it coming?
It's coming.
I've been retracing Driscoll's steps,
working backward
from the time he resigned.
But at a certain point
his footprints disappear.
Well, the guy went undetected
in the LAPD for years,
so he certainly knows
how to cover his tracks.
No doubt.
Let me keep digging. I'll call you.
We are running out of road
on both these cases.
So I'm really hoping
one of these vans pays off.
Something on your mind?
Were you and Olivas close?
We were friendly.
I didn't know him very well.
Certainly not well enough.
You guys were partners.
What was that like?
It was good.
[sighs]
- Jenny Garrison?
- Yeah.
We've got some questions
about a van you scrapped in 2009.
My ex-husband, Mike, took off
with that van nearly 30 years ago.
You should be asking him.
We'd love to,
if you can tell us where to find him.
Wish I knew.
He ran off with someone. Another woman.
I haven't seen or heard from him since.
Any chance you know this woman's name?
Side Piece Denise.
Denise McKenzie.
She was a singer
at that Mormon choir in Utah.
Latter Day Saint, my ass.
Why didn't you ever report the van stolen?
Look, Mike was an abusive prick.
If that van was the price for my freedom,
I got off cheap.
What is this about?
Well, we believe that
your van has been spotted
at several crime scenes
that we're investigating.
The quickest way for us to confirm
if your ex-husband was involved or not
is through DNA.
Are these rapes we're talking about?
Oh, my God.
Did he kill someone?
Ma'am, we are not at liberty
to tell you that.
He did, didn't he?
- I knew he had it in him.
- [Parker] Ms. Garrison.
Do you have any of his belongings
from back then?
I might.
[stutters] I gave it all away.
The only trace I have left of him
is the one good thing he gave me.
My daughter.
Actually, a cheek swab from both of you,
and we'll be able to run it and--
No. Uh, things
are, uh, delicate with Trish.
Ma'am, we're going to need to talk to her.
She's been dealing with the fallout
of her father leaving her all her life.
She's just gotten sober.
She's barely holding down a job at Costco.
I am not gonna jeopardize all that.
Something tells me
Trish doesn't stay out of this.
Not a chance. We're getting that DNA
whether her mom likes it or not.
[landline rings]
Cold Case tip line. Martina speaking.
Yes, yes we do.
[inhales sharply] Uh-huh.
Okay.
Oh, your great uncle did it.
Mm-hmm.
Um, can you spell his name for me?
I will pass this along to a detective.
Thank you.
[mouthing] It never ends.
Guys, I just saw our furry friend
in the break room.
Friend is a strong word.
And not one we use for no damn rat.
He's a mouse. And I think he's nesting
in the conference room.
What, the mouse is back?
Time to bring in the Borax.
No. Let me get some traps.
The catch-and-release kind.
Or the other kind.
Colleen thinks the mouse
is nesting in the conference room.
Time to clean that out. [sighs]
Did you get Trish Garrison's address?
DMV's not current
and mom's still stonewalling.
Damn it. We need that DNA.
I just found out Denise McKenzie
has been missing for the last 28 years.
What?
- Holy moly.
- [Ballard] Yeah.
Her parents reported her missing
in Salt Lake City in 1997.
No mention of Mike,
which means that they probably
didn't know about the relationship.
Gives a whole new meaning
to running away together.
Assuming she ran away with him at all.
If he is our killer,
she could be his first victim.
Did, uh, Jenny say
that Trish just got a new job?
- Costco.
- Find her.
Anything new on Mike?
Any crossover with Sarah?
He pulled quite the disappearing act.
After '97, there's no phone records,
no credit cards, no tax payments.
Sounds like he doesn't wanna be found.
So that makes this van our best lead.
[sighs] Okay.
Contact the NICB. Get a detailed
report of its history, all right?
Call me when you get it. I'll be back.
Looks like number 53
may be lucky after all.
[chuckles]
[Laffont] This looks like Driscoll
took a three-month vacation, right?
But once I started looking into it,
I found a slew of articles,
including a huge piece in the LA Times
about a major takedown
of a local drug ring.
This gap coincides with that takedown.
And get this.
"The investigation relied heavily
on undercover LAPD officers
who were part of a task force
run by the DEA."
So if Driscoll was
a part of that operation--
We could find some
of his criminal contacts.
Or corrupt cops.
Let's talk to the lead agent.
- Oh.
- Don't.
Trust me.
- We're out, babe.
- Okay, bye.
[officer] Parker?
Trish Garrison?
Thanks for coming in.
What's this about?
Why don't you come take a seat.
[whispers] Thanks.
I knew my dad was a deadbeat,
but this is crazy.
Sometimes people aren't
who we think they are.
[scoffs]
And one of the victims was Sarah Pearlman?
I heard about her.
If I open this door, I... [sighs]
I might not like what I find.
Believe me, if there was any other option,
I would not ask you to do this.
I think, uh...
I think wondering would be worse.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
[phone rings]
- Hey, how'd it go?
- [Parker] Trish was a champ.
Even called her mom.
I mean, the woman gave me an earful,
but she's gonna let me swab her too.
Hell, yeah.
Now, I'm headed to take this sample down
to Forensics myself.
After what happened to that bullet,
I'm not taking the chance
any more evidence goes missing.
I hear that.
Hey, tell Darcy if she moves this
to the front of the line,
I'll be her best friend.
[Parker] Will do.
It's definitely in there. I'm telling you.
Marble was barking like crazy.
[grunts]
Thanks.
Agent Trejano?
Detectives Ballard and Laffont. LAPD.
- Thanks for fitting us in.
- Yeah, sure thing. How can I help?
We had some questions
about a task force you ran in 2018.
- Had a lot of our guys undercover.
- Oh, yeah. Great White.
That was a big one.
Do you remember
a detective named Anthony Driscoll?
Yeah, sure I do. He was integral.
He made 13 arrests.
Brought in a huge haul of fentanyl.
Yeah, we did a lot of good.
Could've done more.
How do you mean?
Well, we took down the big fish in LA,
but we were aiming for the sharks
across the border.
- Great White.
- [in Spanish] Tiburón blanco. Yeah.
It was the cartel bosses
that we really wanted.
- They slipped through.
- How?
Informant. They screwed us.
Eh, it was actually Driscoll
who cultivated the source.
He said he would tell us everything
we needed to know
if we would just get him out.
He had a girlfriend and a kid.
He just wanted a new life.
Do you happen to remember
the informant's name?
I-something.
Ibanez?
No. Ibarra.
- Luis Ibarra?
- Luis Ibarra.
- That's him.
- Uh-huh.
Boss, you're gonna want
to check this shit out.
Just, uh, before we go,
whatever happened to Ibarra?
How did he screw you?
He got cold feet.
Disappeared back to Mexico.
And you know that for sure?
Driscoll did. Yeah.
After the dude ghosted him, he
followed him all the way down to Jalisco.
Back across the border
until the trail went cold.
Ibarra's never surfaced since.
Hmm.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Yeah.
[Parker] Wow.
And Trejano didn't have any suspicions
on Driscoll?
No. Ibarra was gonna flip on the cartel.
So instead of protecting him,
Driscoll took him out.
Easy work given that
he was Ibarra's handler.
Yeah, well,
that's one way to handle things.
Yeah. Ibarra never had a chance.
So twisted. Killing your own informant.
Driscoll's either incredibly reckless
or he thinks he can't be touched.
Or both.
The DEA didn't bat an eye at his story.
He must think he's Teflon.
He's not. We just have to find our way in.
[sighs]
Then we grab him.
Rattle his cage. See what he gives.
That's risky.
Yeah. But if he's the first domino,
we gotta make him fall.
We only have one shot at this guy.
We can't bring him in
unless we have some leverage.
So first off,
we have to nail down Driscoll's
whereabouts the day Ibarra was killed.
How do we manage that?
Figuring out where he was
on a random day five years ago?
The past is always present, my friend.
Let's dig in tomorrow.
I better get home
before Leo starts baking again. [sighs]
What he is doing is criminal.
- [chuckles] Good night.
- [Parker] Good night, Laffont.
So...
I've been thinking, you know,
since you told me about Olivas.
Reexamining things.
Seeing things in a... [sighs] ...new light.
- Yeah. Been there.
- Yeah.
Part of me just wants to leave it alone.
But, um... [sighs]
...something tells me
wondering might be worse.
[sighs] Why don't you come to my place?
Tutu made ribs.
We can talk there.
Okay.
I mean, incredible.
It fell right off the bone.
- Years of practice.
- [chuckles]
[chuckles] Believe it or not, this one
went vegan for a while. Drove me nuts.
You kidding. You love cheese.
I do.
[Tutu] Yeah. [sighs]
Imagine her mood after a month without it.
I nearly kicked her out of the house.
Would assume so. [laughs]
I think I'm gonna take Lola for a walk.
Thank you.
And no swimming after dark, you.
[Ballard, Parker chuckle]
- Lola.
- [Lola barks]
- Bye, baby girl. Good girl. Come on.
- [whines]
[Tutu] All right. Let's go.
How long you've been living with her?
Um... [sighs]
Gosh, I think it's two years now.
I'd just gotten out of a relationship,
and it was supposed
to be a short-term thing,
but then it just really worked.
I'm lucky to have her.
[chuckles]
So, you said
you were reframing some things.
Yeah.
Just wondering.
How did he get you alone?
Oh, boy.
We were at a bar.
Friend had made detective,
so we were celebrating.
- Excuse me.
- [hip-hop music playing]
[Ballard] We were having a great time.
Here you go.
Olivas was bringing me drinks.
Doubles.
He said it was the smart move
because the bar was mobbed.
Come on.
Gotta toughen you up. [chuckles]
You got it. [chuckles]
[Olivas] Mmm.
- Mmm.
- Okay.
- [coughs] I'm getting used to it. [laughs]
- [Olivas] Okay. Okay.
[Parker] That is no joke.
[Ballard] The drinks really hit me hard.
And so I went to the bathroom
to splash water on my face...
[sighs] ...and he followed me in.
He said that he wanted to see
if I was okay.
[hip-hop music playing]
[Ballard] When I pulled out my phone
to call an Uber...
he tried to take it from me.
- [sighs]
- [Olivas] Hey. Hey.
[stammers] What are we doing?
[scoffs] Do not waste your money.
- I will get you home any time.
- [chuckles]
[Ballard] Said that he would
take me home himself.
[Parker, Olivas chuckling]
I told him that it made no sense
to drive all the way to Malibu.
When he couldn't convince me...
the whole nice guy act just disappeared.
[sighs] He slammed me into the door...
[inhales sharply, exhales]
Oh, I fought him.
[breathes shakily]
And it wasn't easy,
because he was dead set
on getting what he wanted.
But I finally got him off me, and I ran.
Straight out the door
into my partner, Chastain.
[scoffs]
Everything in RHD went downhill
from there.
[inhales sharply, exhales]
[sniffles] A lot of that sounds...
[breathes shakily] ...really familiar.
[sniffles, sobs]
How did I not see it? [whimpers]
[cries]
[sighs] All this time.
[groans] All this time.
[sniffles] I thought, you know, I... [cries]
I didn't do enough.
I thought maybe I did too much.
I gave him mixed signals.
I don't know what I thought.
I just...
[sighs] I thought it was on me.
[Ballard]
I heard in therapy once that, uh...
"If you're assaulted by a stranger,
you don't trust the world.
But if you're assaulted
by someone you know,
you don't trust yourself."
[Parker breathes shakily]
You said that...
...most of it sounded familiar.
What was different?
- [Olivas] Watch your head.
- [Parker chuckles]
[door closes]
[sighs]
Hey, I got you, partner.
[Parker breathes shakily]
I let him take me home.
[sobs]
[sobbing continues]
[sniffles]
You didn't let him do anything.
[phone buzzing]
Tell me something good. [sighs]
[Laffont] I don't think
I can help you there.
I just looked into the GND logs
on the day Luis Ibarra died.
Anthony Driscoll was signed out
to Division 106 that day.
The son of a bitch was in court.
Wait a minute. Cops claim court
like schoolboys claim stomachaches.
- Remember that time you--
- I was not gonna miss Rihanna in Vegas.
Well, look,
before we let this guy off the hook,
let's make damn sure he was
actually in court that day.
How are we gonna do that
without raising flags?
Even asking the court liaison feels risky.
I have an idea.
Ooh. Someone's glowing this morning.
- Thank you.
- [Colleen chuckles]
Who's the guy?
Just 'cause I woke up in a good mood
does not mean a boy is involved.
Whatever.
I was just agreeing.
But...
[whispers] ...maybe this time
there is a boy.
- [whispers] Ooh. Details later.
- Yeah.
- [phone chimes]
- Oh.
Guys. I heard back from NICB.
Jenny Garrison's van was crushed in 2009
at a place called R&T Scrapyard.
I knew this van would take us places.
And where's it taking us exactly?
Encino. That's where the scrapyard is.
We should go while traffic's light.
Encino? Ugh. I'll swing by on my way home.
Nope. I did the digging.
I'm going with you.
If Mike's our killer,
we need a lead on him.
And so far, this van's all we got.
[groans] Great.
This takes me back.
Do I wanna ask where?
Carolina Crusher.
Winter Nationals, uh, 2005.
[Ted chuckles]
[chuckles] Oh, hang on.
You're into monster trucks?
I contain multitudes, Ted.
We're looking for anything you might have
on a vehicle that was crushed here
back in '09.
Yeah. We just need copies
of any relevant paperwork.
Or-Or better yet, email.
Save those trees.
[chuckles] What?
That's where all the old records are.
Knock yourselves out.
[video game beeps]
You have got to be kidding me.
[Colleen] Good heavens.
It'll be a miracle if we find anything
in this trash heap.
Where's your sense
of wonder and curiosity?
No. Not... Not...
Not in a place that looks like this.
Come on. You... You like to fish, right?
- What's that have to do with anything?
- When you fish,
you throw out a line
and you see if anything bites.
Sometimes it does,
sometimes it doesn't. [chuckles]
But someone who enjoys it
likes it either way.
That's why it's called fishing,
not catching.
[sighs]
Oh, okay.
- [blows] Oh.
- Jeez. God.
[attorney] And how does this witness list
connect to the conspiracy Javi gave you?
Well, he didn't give me anything
that would make my case, so I'm looking.
Looking for?
All right, fine.
But I want it on record that getting you
this witness list is me doing you a favor.
Noted.
For real, Ballard.
If you're not gonna tell me what's up,
then what's in it for me?
What? I got you a boba.
If I find what I'm looking for,
it could help your client.
[gasps]
That's it? Did you find the name?
Nope. Which is exactly
what I was hoping for.
[scoffs]
- Driscoll's back on the board.
- [Laffont] How?
I just reviewed the LA County witness list
for the day that Driscoll claimed
to be in court.
His name doesn't appear anywhere.
No subpoenas. No testimonies. Nothing.
He fabricated an alibi.
This guy fucking killed Ibarra.
I know it. [sighs]
[Ted] Okay, let's see.
[groans]
[groans, sighs]
- [Colleen] Okay.
- [Ted] So... [mutters]
I found it.
I found our van.
Not a lot to go on here.
Your negativity
is bad for your health and mine.
Van was towed here
from a storage facility on Oxnard.
- Come on.
- Oh, you wanna go there now?
- Oh, you bet your behind I do.
- [chuckles]
- This is our first nibble.
- You and your rabbit holes.
This is where the magic happens.
We get a lead, catch a break,
run into a dead end.
This is where we figure it out.
[chuckles]
[partner] This is dope.
This definitely beats getting dispatched
to check on barking dogs.
Dogs?
Seriously?
"To protect and to serve."
Hmm. No wonder you wanna make detective.
One day soon.
Sarah's case is the main reason
our unit's even here.
Well, I hope the guy gets
what's coming to him.
- If we find him.
- When you find him.
And your John Doe case?
Where the hell did you even start when
you didn't know the victim's identity?
Well, actually, it was my idea that led us
to figure out who he was.
Damn, girl. [chuckles]
Well, maybe you could teach me
a thing or two.
It didn't lead us anywhere though.
We found the gun, but it led us to a guy
with an airtight alibi.
Still.
I'm impressed.
[chuckles]
[line ringing]
[Parker, on voice mail]
It's Zamira. You know what to do.
- [voice mail beeps]
- Hey, Parker. It's Ballard. [sighs]
Just calling to check on you,
see how you're doing.
Uh, big news on the Driscoll front,
so give me a call back, all right?
[mouthing] Bye.
[cries]
[grunts]
[screaming, crying]
[screams]
[breathing shakily]
[car approaching]
Some day, we're gonna make such
a mess of this place, we'll all be gone.
It'll go back to the coyotes.
What do you got for me? [sighs]
- Case is dead in the water.
- You sure?
They got no leads, no suspects.
Whole department's bankrolled
by that city councilman,
the one with the dead sister.
That's what they're focused on.
Wow. [sighs] You are sure.
You're young,
maybe you don't know how this works.
But they're right outside,
looking for cracks.
I'm telling you. I don't think
there's anything for us to worry about.
You're asking your friend questions,
being nice about it. I appreciate that.
[stammers] I'm not a monster.
And I see the appeal,
believe me. Pretty face.
The guys we work with...
they don't care about that.
They don't care about being nice.
One of them is up here talking to you
instead of me.
[tense music plays]
They might want you to twist her arm
a little more, or they might want me to.
Like I said, I'm not a monster. [sighs]
But I also do what they tell me.
And she may not be so pretty then.
But it's not gonna come to that, right?
You won't let it.
[car door opens]
[car door closes]
[car engine starts]
Um... Okay. Our records do show a van
was towed in 2009 from unit E36.
Belongs to a Mike Garrison.
Uh. Wait. Wait. Uh. Belongs?
He-He still uses it?
Uh. [chuckles]
Lucky duck locked in an old rate.
Paying a third of the rest
of our customers.
[gasps]
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
We-We hooked a big one.
[sighs]
Uh, Ballard. Um... [stammers]
We're gonna need a warrant.
[tires squealing]
She's on her way.
She'll be here any minute.
So you keep saying.
It's nice of you to join us, by the way.
Oh, I don't miss the fun stuff.
[sighs]
Seriously, I got a family.
It's time for me to go.
Which means it's time for you to--
[car approaches]
- [manager sighs]
- [car door closes]
Got a couple of black-and-whites
standing by.
Hey. I got your text.
- Glad you made it.
- [manager sighs] Follow me.
Did we get anything new on Garrison?
Like an address?
Uh, no such luck.
Apparently, the unit's paid for in cash
via drop box, once a year.
Yeah. I asked about the cameras.
They roll over every 30 days.
[Laffont] Well, let's hope
he came by recently.
Ooh. This feels big.
[manager] Here it is. Locker 36.
It's because you followed your gut.
[chattering on radio]
[sighs] Let's cut it.
Here we go.
[breathes shakily]
[Colleen] Oh, dear.
What do you think are in these?
[Laffont] Could be anything.
Photographs.
Body parts.
Holy shit.
It's Laura Wilson's.
They're like little coffins.
This is sick.
[tense music plays]
It is.
And it stops here.