[Ballard] Previously on Ballard...
[Berchem] You have 72 hours.
Find something meaningful
or this case goes to Homicide.
[Hopkinson] So, serial killer, huh?
You got a name?
[Ballard] I found a closed case from 2008.
The victim was strangled in her bed.
The family reported
a gold bracelet missing from the scene.
We found that bracelet...
[breathes heavily]
...among our killer's souvenirs.
The victim's boyfriend was convicted,
but he always claimed innocence.
If we reopen this case,
we might find a link
between the women and the real killer.
And we could
potentially free an innocent man.
Mike and Denise were found
within a ten mile radius near Crestline.
So she was the target.
Mike was an obstacle.
Luis said that we could trust him.
- You should've kept your mouth shut.
- [muffled screams, cries]
Always a pleasure.
You need a ride?
Thanks. I got one.
[Ballard] Ibarra was gonna flip
on the cartel, so Driscoll took him out.
Driscoll's either incredibly reckless
or he thinks he can't be touched.
[Driscoll] They got no leads, no suspects.
You're young,
maybe you don't know how this works,
but they're right outside,
looking for cracks.
Like I said, I'm not a monster.
[both grunting]
- I got it.
- [Aaron] Are you sure about this?
He's gonna die!
[Aaron] Make a vertical incision
a half inch deep to create an opening.
Push the tube into the incision until
you feel it go through the trachea wall.
[Ballard breathes heavily]
- [inhales sharply]
- [screams]
No!
- [grunting, panting]
- [Lola barking]
- [radio chatter]
- [siren wailing]
[detective, distorted]
Did you know this man?
Ma'am, look at me.
Sorry, I'm gonna have to ask you again,
did you know this man?
Yeah.
[detective] You're gonna have to
speak up now. I can't hear you.
Her throat was compressed in the attack.
She'll be hoarse for a while.
Yeah, I knew him.
Help me out with something.
Who pulled out the trache? Him or you?
You gonna read me my rights now?
Hey, buddy. An ambulance is waiting.
Let's pick this up tomorrow.
We're gonna need her clothes.
This is not my first rodeo.
You'll get her clothes
once she's changed at the hospital.
Come on, let's go.
You okay?
Everything's gonna be fine.
[whispers indistinctly]
[ominous music plays]
[ambulance engine starts]
Let's go!
[siren wailing]
[shutter clicks]
Thank you.
[grunts]
- What the hell happened?
- News said someone tried to strangle her.
No. It's, uh... [stammers]
...related to the John Doe case.
- What?
- How?
[sighs] Uh...
[sighs]
Probably hard to know
since it's under Sheriff's jurisdiction.
Right. They're very territorial.
[sighs] Can we go see her?
I don't think visitors are a good idea.
Detective Laffont? Some Detectives
from Homicide are here. They want--
Hey, Tom.
- Greg?
- [Parker] What the hell?
Sorry to intrude.
Okay. Hey.
- Whoa, whoa. What's going on?
- [Ted] Hey, hey, hey. What the hell?
You didn't have to.
Believe me, it was perfunctory.
You look like hell.
What happened?
- You know what I know.
- Bullshit.
How come you never told me an ex-cop
was a suspect in your John Doe case?
I just didn't get a chance.
It all came together so fast.
But when I get back to work,
I'm going to--
About that,
Homicide is taking the Pearlman case.
So those are "I'm sorry" flowers,
not "get well" flowers.
They're taking the John Doe case too,
but it sounds like that one closed itself
when Driscoll pulled his trache.
[inhales sharply] Any more bad news?
I'm gonna put a protective detail on you
until we sort all this out.
No, no, no.
Driscoll's dead. I don't need a detail.
It wasn't a question.
Fine. I get to pick the team.
Once you're cleared by the doctors,
you can call Metro and make arrangements.
But take a few days.
[grunting]
Hey.
- Hey, Ballard.
- Hi.
Got you staying at the Sand Dollar Motel
until this all blows over.
Sounds lovely.
Appreciate it.
He a friend of yours?
One of the few.
Okay, room 210.
We'll be here if you need us.
Thanks.
So, Laffont dropped by my crib last night
sometime after 1:00.
He gave me a phone. A dead ex-cop's phone.
Said you wanted me to dump the data.
Did you?
Before I answer that,
what the hell is going on?
I can explain,
but first I gotta figure out how to get
that phone back in the chain of custody.
Already took care of it.
Working with Mo on a need-to-know basis.
I need to know.
I need you to fill me in.
Who's Anthony Driscoll?
[sighs] He murdered a John Doe,
one of my cold cases.
And then I find out
this guy's running guns and drugs
between the Zacatecas Nuevas cartel
and the LAPD.
Jesus, Ballard.
Yeah. And he must've been in deep
because he chose to pull his trache
rather than get arrested.
Doesn't sound like a cartel hit,
the way he came for you.
Strangling's not their style.
No.
My guess is he was on his own.
[scoffs] If this was a cartel hit,
we wouldn't be sitting here
right now talking.
I'm sorry.
I pulled you into some deep waters.
Uh... Story of my life.
I did dump Driscoll's phone.
Found a bunch of numbers,
probably burners.
So we'll have to chase 'em down
the old-fashioned way.
Follow the pings, put faces to numbers.
And I still cannot believe that
you took a cell phone from a crime scene.
- I was gonna give it back.
- [chuckling] Yeah.
Oh, man. I'm beginning to like you
more and more. [laughs]
Jesus.
[sighs]
[groaning]
[phone ringing]
Laffont. [clears throat] What's up?
[Laffont] Just checking on you.
How you doing?
I'm fine,
it's just my voice is driving me crazy.
How's the team holding up?
Not well.
You give any thought
what you're gonna tell them?
[sighs]
Everything.
Why didn't you tell us?
I shouldn't even be telling you
at this point.
Well, at least now we know
who's outside the circle of trust.
No, this is so much bigger than trust.
This puts all of you in danger.
They went after Javier Fuentes
the same day Driscoll went after me.
And I know
that's not the job you volunteered for.
So if any of you want out, I understand.
[chuckles] Okay.
No more secrets.
Circle of trust.
Let's get back to work.
[stammers] Get back to work on what?
They took both of our cases.
Right. I don't know that yet.
But I'm gonna figure it out.
[reporter 1]
Hello, this is KCAL News doing a story--
[reporter 2] This is ABC7 calling--
[reporter 3] Detective Ballard.
Mike Suffolk with the LA Times--
Hello. My name is Lillian Lee.
I saw you on the news.
I'm running out of hope.
My son, he was killed.
His name is Raehyun. Raehyun Lee.
I call the detectives,
but they no longer call me back.
I want my son back.
I fear he will never rest in peace
because they never found his body.
I found our new case.
Who's in?
Box was a mess.
My guess is the original IO pegged it
as a gang killing and called it a day.
Gonna be a heavy lift.
Yeah. Are you sure about this?
There's no body. Just a pool of blood
in the alley behind Ray's apartment.
Maybe you ought to go home.
Rest for a couple days.
No, I'd rather work.
I'll go crazy licking my wounds.
Honey, lemon, ginger.
Soothes the vocal cords.
[sighs] Thank you.
A green Ford Fiesta was spotted
on security footage leaving that alley
around the time Ray disappeared.
No plates, which seems "gang-y."
But the vic's cell pinged once after that
up in La Cañada.
Which seems considerably less "gang-y."
But it says here that Ray was affiliated
with the Asian Gs.
Hmm.
They had Koreatown on lock in 2018.
Seven years later, territory's shifted.
Maybe somebody will talk.
Mmm. I don't know.
I mean, gangs
in my neighborhood can hold a grudge.
And people tend to keep their mouths shut,
even years later.
We still have to try.
So, Martina, Colleen,
will you draft some flyers
with the car info and the victim's photo?
Push it out on LAPD socials.
Rawls, Parker,
will you post those in the neighborhood?
I mean, it's a long shot, but it's one
the original investigator never took.
- Let's go talk to Ray's mom.
- Mm-hmm.
Right thing to do,
expanding the circle of trust.
But you did leave out the part about Bosch
and the cell phone you swiped.
I'm working up to it.
The team needs to focus on this new case.
[grunts] The team needs to?
[scoffs] We could use a win right now,
don't you think?
But, uh, why this case?
I don't know.
Something in the mother's voice.
[sighs]
They never found my father's body either.
Oh, shit, I spaced.
- What's up?
- It's Lancaster prison.
I was supposed to go visit
Jorge Ochoa today.
Oh, the guy doing time
for one of our serial killer's murders.
Detective Renée Ballard. [clears throat]
Yeah, I know. I'm sorry.
Can you get me another appointment ASAP?
Thank you.
Lancaster hasn't gotten the memo
it's not our case anymore.
I guess not.
I know he's gone.
I just want to bury him, so his soul can
get to where it needs to go.
He wanted to play baseball,
even scouts came to watch him play.
But then he had an accident
on his friend's motorcycle.
They put a metal plate in his shoulder.
No more baseball.
After that, he had different friends.
Rougher boys.
But even God's favorite
was a fallen angel.
Ray, was no angel, Mom.
He was in a gang.
Did it to take care of us,
but he was into some bad shit.
[speaks Korean]
Um, Ray's brother, Jun.
I'm sorry,
but if you wanna know the truth, Mom...
police need all the facts.
He's right, we do.
So I read in the case file
that Ray got into an argument
with another boy at school
a few days before the shooting.
Marcus Jeong. Yeah.
Him and Ray were friends,
till they weren't.
- Do you know what happened?
- [Jun] I was just a kid.
Marcus has twin face.
Two-faced, Mom.
[Lillian]
I told the detective to go look at him,
but because Marcus doesn't dress
like a bad man...
Marcus wasn't in a gang.
And the cops thought it was a gang thing.
So they moved off Marcus.
And then they pretty much gave up
altogether.
Well, we're gonna do everything we can
to find out what happened, okay?
[scoffs] Mm-hmm.
[speaks indistinctly]
- I think it worked out there pretty well--
- [Ballard] Marcus Jeong?
Detective Ballard, Detective Laffont.
We wanted to talk to you about Ray Lee.
Yeah, um, Kate, I'm gonna...
I'ma catch up with you. Yeah.
[Marcus] He tried to jump me
into the Asian Gs.
He was recruiting me hard,
and I-I felt the pull, you know?
But I had people on my side.
My mom, my teachers,
the counselor at school.
All trying to keep me
on the straight and narrow.
But when Ray got killed, look,
that was a big reality check.
It's just, what can happen
when you're in that life.
I got it together quick after that.
Can you tell us about the fight you had
with Ray, the week he disappeared?
It's become like one of those urban myths,
you know?
We just had some static.
About what?
He thought I was stringing him along
about joining up,
but it got blown way out of proportion.
People started talking
like it was this cage match.
And then this video started circulating.
Wait, what video?
Some kid uploaded cell phone footage
of the fight.
My mom had a lawyer friend
get it taken down a couple of weeks later.
Didn't want it hurting my prospects.
Sure looks like things worked out
for Marcus.
Maybe at Ray's expense.
Let's see where he was
the day that Ray disappeared
and then maybe Colleen can dredge up
that video he was talking about.
Mm-hmm. Hey.
I am calling an audible.
- You look exhausted.
- Laffont.
You're going back to the hotel.
[stammers, sighs]
Get some rest.
Handcuffs if necessary.
[sighs]
All right, Burner Boy is back there,
seven o'clock.
[Bosch] Another blue-suiter.
I don't know him.
I'll call in the shop number,
see who signed it out.
Man, Ballard and all these cops.
What's she gotten into?
Some bad shit, brother.
[coughing]
[sighs]
[sighs, chuckles]
[gasps, breathes shakily]
Oh, honey.
[groans]
I'm okay. I'm okay.
- Oh, baby.
- I'm fine.
[phone buzzing]
Huh? [pants]
[groans, sighs]
I thought you told me to get some rest.
[Laffont] I did.
Uh, but I'm calling early
because we got a lead.
A witness replied to the flyer we put out.
No way.
[chuckles] Way. Surprised me too.
He lives up in Montrose,
just west of La Cañada.
That's where
the vic's cell phone pinged last.
Rightio.
He said he was heading out
on an early hike
up Colby Canyon
on the morning in question.
Saw someone coming out of the hills
in jeans and a hoodie,
all dirty, wearing work gloves.
He drove away in a green Ford.
Okay, but why would somebody remember
all these details seven years later?
I am so glad you asked.
I am now going to read his statement,
word for word.
Ahem.
"I got there and realized
there was no pit toilet at the trailhead.
I just finished my coffee, so...
Anyway, I found some bushes.
And I'm in the middle
of doing my business...
[Laffont, witness]
...when someone came out of nowhere."
They came down right through there,
and my dog went crazy,
pulling on the leash.
I got my pants around my ankles,
so I go ass-over-teakettle into the dirt.
Anyway,
when I saw the flyer about the green Ford,
it was the first thing I thought of.
It was right over there.
[dogs barking]
[officer] Found something!
That's him.
[ominous music plays]
- [sighs]
- Ballard.
Check it out.
[music intensifies]
[Lillian praying in Korean]
[in English] Amen.
[sobs]
Did you find a gun?
Were there prints?
Yeah, we're processing the gun now.
In Colby Canyon?
Look, Jun, I know you want to help,
but you gotta let us do our jobs.
Same thing the cops said seven years ago.
Jun, look what she's done.
She helped put your brother to rest.
Just 'cause they found the body, Mom,
doesn't mean this is over. [huffs]
[footsteps recede]
I'm headed to Lancaster in the morning
to go talk with Jorge Ochoa.
[breathes deeply]
Do... Do you think you can--
Have Firearms fast track the gun?
I'm on it.
[softly] Thank you.
[clears throat] Also, uh... uh...
See if Colleen has made any progress
on the video?
First thing tomorrow.
You know, I never put it together,
what happened to your dad.
How it drives you.
You could always stay with us.
Leo would love to have you.
- [chuckles]
- And Tutu.
Especially on Bachelor night.
[scoffs, laughs] Aw.
[chortles]
And leave all this?
[Laffont sighs] Hmm.
Thank you for the offer.
But it's... it's not the motel.
It's just not home.
Mm-hmm.
[phone rings]
Hey. What's up?
You talk to Ochoa yet?
[Ballard] No, not yet.
I'm on the Sierra Highway.
I'm about 40 minutes out.
Any news on the gun we found
with Ray's body?
Uh, Firearms Freddie says it was
registered to a Ms. Christa Fortson.
Any connection to Marcus or Ray?
Not according to Ms. Fortson.
You spoke to her?
Uh, she has an early shift at Denny's,
so I swung by there and got a short stack.
Said she bought a bunch of guns
back in the day
for an ex-boyfriend gang member.
- Ah, young love.
- Yeah.
He'd dole 'em out to his buddies.
Any chance he wants to tell us
which buddies?
Not likely.
He's dead.
And Ms. Fortson's alibi checks out.
Great. Swing and a miss.
Yeah. Talk soon.
[groans]
[gate buzzer sounds]
Sorry I didn't make it in the other day.
[Ochoa] I'm not going anywhere.
That's Elena's.
Your fiancée?
Are those your initials?
Yeah.
Where did you get this?
In a storage unit that belonged to the
person who actually killed your fiancée.
What do you mean? Who?
I don't know that yet, Jorge.
But I think you're innocent.
I need to hear it from you though.
I am. I am. I told my lawyer that.
He said the DNA was too hard to explain.
He wanted me to take a plea,
but I was never gonna do that
because I wasn't guilty.
So you went to trial?
The jury didn't believe me.
Then I had no more money to fight.
I loved Elena.
I'd never hurt her.
She gave me one too, with her initials.
It said, "Mi Vida, E.C."
They took it when they arrested me.
She got promoted at her job,
and she was so proud.
But it meant long hours.
We'd be apart more.
So she bought these with her own money,
so we'd have each other.
Always.
Look, I don't know, Ballard.
The DNA's a killer.
[Ballard] Well, it's not foolproof.
She was Jorge's fiancée.
Of course they slept together.
Yeah. Says the woman
with a probable concussion.
[scoffs]
[documents rustle]
This gold bracelet
belonged to his fiancée.
Her name was Elena Cervantes.
You know where I found it?
In the storage unit
of a serial killer I'm investigating.
And why didn't you lead with this?
Because I was testing your faith
in me, Damani.
- [chuckles]
- And you failed, by the way.
You in?
[sighs] Yeah, I think I am.
Good. This guy really deserves someone
who's gonna dig down.
Well, I'll get the shovel.
- How's Javi?
- He's hanging on.
You got any idea who came for him?
Mmm, not yet.
I'm working on it.
- I'll be in touch.
- Yeah.
[copier clattering]
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey.
Hey.
You got to treat her nice.
[copier whirring]
Thanks.
What's all this?
I've got someone working
on an age progression for Ibarra's kid.
- Gael?
- Yeah.
I called Missing Persons,
but they're taking too long,
so I went to DCFS myself.
You know, asked for every kid
around his age.
Figured I'd look for a match. I just, uh...
I didn't realize there'd be so many.
It's really got its hooks in you, huh?
Gotcha!
I found it. Marcus's video.
His lawyer did a good job burying it,
but I found a snipped daisy chain.
- The Internet never forgets.
- [keyboard clicks]
- You get back over here.
- [grunts]
[crowd clamoring]
[clamoring continues]
Back off! Get off of me!
[teacher] Marcus. Get out of here. Now!
All right, show's over.
[student] Come on, Mr. Kim. Let 'em fight.
Wait, freeze it. I know that name.
[mutters, sighs]
Nathan Kim. He's a teacher at the school.
Original IO interviewed him,
and he said the fight wasn't a big deal.
That it was blown out of proportion.
- [Parker scoffs]
- Same thing Marcus said.
Why did Mr. Kim play that down?
For his benefit or for Marcus's?
Let's find out.
Stay on Gael.
Let's go, Rawls.
[Ted] How long do you think
Berchem's gonna keep this detail on you?
[Ballard] Until he decides
I'm not in danger at home.
[sighs]
You know, I could upgrade your protection.
Put some of my private sector guys
on your house.
Ex-Green Beret. They worked the Oscars.
Sounds a little fancy for me, no?
It'd be free of charge, of course.
That is within our budget.
Can I think about it?
Sure.
Hey, hang on. Laffont is texting.
Apparently, Marcus was at a swim meet in
Bakersfield the day that Ray disappeared.
He broke the record
for the 50-meter freestyle.
Great. So he's not our guy.
Doesn't look like it.
Let's go talk to Mr. Kim.
- [crowd clamoring on video]
- [Mr. Kim] Get out of here. Now!
[clapping] All right, show's over!
[video ends]
Pretty heated in this video, Mr. Kim.
And rough with Ray, considering
he was one of your former students.
I know. It's not a good look.
This gang thing, it... gets to me.
I grew up in this neighborhood.
Used to ride my bike all over,
never once locked it up.
And at some point, things changed.
[sighs]
All the work I do in the classroom,
it goes down the drain
the second these gangs start promising
them quick money and some street cred.
Is that what was happening with Marcus?
He had so much promise.
But I could just see him
at this fork in the road.
I mean, look at Ray. He was exactly
where Marcus was just a few years before.
And I lost that fight with him.
And he ended up dead.
You think Ray died
because of his gang affiliation?
I know he did.
He had a long list of enemies
by the time he died.
You remember who was on that list?
Seven years ago. [sighs]
Man, I talked to the detective back then.
There was a kid named Ashton Reed.
Eddy Fortson was another one.
Victor Cabrera.
Did you say Fortson?
Yeah. He was a student in my class.
Any relation to Christa?
That was his sister. Why?
[scoffs]
Gun that killed Ray
was registered to Christa Fortson.
Well, didn't she have an alibi?
Yeah, she did.
Which makes her brother our best bet.
Hey, if this ain't about
the child support, then what is it?
Murder, Eddy.
[stammering] Oh. Uh... I mean...
[Ballard] Ray Lee.
He was shot multiple times
with a gun registered to your sister.
And we know you had beef with him too.
Ray who? I-- I don't know a Ray.
Well, you went to school together, Eddy.
I went to school with lots of people.
[Ted] You were both on the baseball team.
You rode together to away games.
Your sister told us
about the guns she bought.
She buy one for you too?
We're processing that gun
right now for prints.
We find yours, Eddy, you'll be
paying child support from prison.
[chuckles]
Yeah.
Christa gave me that gun.
But it wasn't because
I wanted to kill no one, okay?
I was getting messed with at school.
You mean bullied?
Christa told me I could use it,
flash it around,
get the upperclassmen to ease off me.
But it wasn't a week
before someone stole it from my locker.
Sister was pretty bent.
You've been to Colby Canyon?
Colby Canyon? No, what's that?
A hiking trail, up the 2.
That place.
Never been. No, no.
Only the four-point-whatever's got to go.
- What do you mean?
- From my school.
One of the teachers took all
the smart kids once a year
for bonding, trust falls,
all that kind of shit.
What teacher?
I don't know. What's his name? Mr., um...
Mr. Kim.
Yeah.
I never made the cut.
[Ted] Gotta go back and talk to him again.
[Parker] About what?
All we have is a hunch
and the word of a former student.
We're gonna need more.
Yeah. Well, we're not
gonna get anything this late.
So, first thing in the morning,
we start from scratch on Nathan Kim.
Good night.
Hey, Rawls.
If that offer for security still stands,
I'll take it.
Oh. Yeah.
Consider it done.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
Appreciate you.
Hey. Wanted to get this all cleaned up
before you got here.
[sighs] Thank you.
I see you upgraded your protection detail.
Pretty impressive.
I got some help from a friend.
- Is Tutu home yet?
- [phone buzzing]
Outside with Lola.
Hey, Colleen. What's up?
[Colleen] You know I can't help myself.
So... [chuckles] ...I did some digging
into Nathan Kim's vehicular history.
Turns out, his mom owned a green
Ford Fiesta at the time of Ray's murder.
No way.
Do we know where it is now?
Donated to charity
after she passed in 2021.
I'll call tomorrow morning
as soon as they open.
If we can find the new owner,
maybe there's some
physical evidence left behind.
Yeah, it's a big if and a big maybe,
but it's worth a shot.
Nice find, Colleen.
Now put your laptop away.
Copy that.
[gasps] Hi, baby girl.
Aw. [grunts]
- Ah! [grunting]
- Oh, sorry. Here.
Uh...
[sighs, pants]
Thank you.
- [grunts, sucks teeth]
- Here, here, here, here, here. Come here.
Are you ever gonna tell me
about that tattoo?
[sighs] Yeah.
After my dad died, I was alone.
My mom was already long gone.
[inhales sharply]
I fell in with some... some people, and it...
[sighs] Anyway, it wasn't good.
I was really messed up.
[clears throat] So I got this.
You know, I figured even if I was lost,
that maybe he could watch over me.
I love that.
Oh, gosh. [grunting]
You've been so good to me.
It's easy to be good to you.
These last few days...
something's kinda snuck up on me
in all the chaos.
When you called that night,
realizing you were in trouble,
it made me think...
[chuckles]
Hmm.
[phone buzzing]
- [phone beeps]
- I'm on my way in.
Get ready to love me.
Uh, okay.
We found the donated Ford.
And with the current owner's consent,
FSD is processing it as we speak.
No shit?
And we hit the jackpot,
'cause nobody ever wiped the GPS data
off the nav.
Guess where Nathan Kim was
the night Ray died.
Colby Canyon?
You love me, right?
- Hang on. I got another call.
- [phone beeps]
- Detective Renée Ballard.
- [Lillian] Jun is gone!
He said one of his teachers
killed Ray. Mr. Kim.
I don't know what he's gonna do.
All right, I'm headed there.
- [siren wailing]
- [engine revving]
[police chattering on radio]
[Laffont] Black-and-whites got here first.
They saw a young, Asian male
barricaded inside.
- They called SWAT.
- Shit.
[sighs] We gotta move.
Rawls, you're coming with me.
Laffont, Parker, watch the back.
[doorknob rattles]
Rawls, get a crowbar.
- Jun?
- [Jun] Go away!
- [Mr. Kim] Please, do something!
- [Jun] Shut up!
Jun, it's Detective Ballard.
- [Mr. Kim] Do something.
- Shut up!
Jun, put down the gun and walk
towards the door. We got this guy.
He killed Ray, and nobody did anything.
Colby Canyon.
That's where you take the smart kids.
Same place you buried my brother!
[stuttering]
I don't know what you're talking about.
Bullshit! You're lying.
Tell him what you did, Nathan.
You're crazy. I didn't do anything.
We have the evidence. We have your car.
You don't have time.
[shrieks] Okay, okay.
I didn't want to hurt anyone. I-- I just
went there that night to scare him.
- You took a gun!
- Guns are all he understood.
I didn't go there to kill him.
But think about it,
how many kids did I save?
- Shut up.
- [Ballard] Jun?
We have everything we need, Jun.
All right? I told you I wouldn't quit.
Put the gun down, all right?
Let us come in there, do our jobs.
We got him.
Put the gun down.
Come on. Help us.
- [sobs]
- Put it down.
[gun clatters]
Jun, come to me.
Come to me, come to me. Turn around.
On the ground. On your knees.
[handcuffs clicking]
- [Mr. Kim yelps]
- No!
[both grunt]
[Ted] Don't move! Don't move.
- Stay where you are.
- [officer shouts]
- I got him, I got him, I got him.
- [Ted] Come on! Hands behind your back!
[groans]
- [Mr. Kim whimpers]
- I'm sorry.
[panting] I know.
Spoke to the DA.
I explained to her about Jun,
and she's gonna push for a low term.
His poor mother.
Well, at least she has answers now.
Sucks it took so long.
Well, that's because the original
investigator was looking for a bad guy
that looked like a bad guy.
Sometimes they just look like us.
What do you say, you put this one
on the shelf too? The Ibarra case.
Definitely as good as closed.
Oh, um, one sec.
Um, a little more work to do.
You wanna put it up?
You went through hell with this one.
No. That's your case.
[phone buzzing]
Hey, Harry.
They traced another number
from Driscoll's cell phone.
I wanted you to see it for yourself.
- Kids, where are you going?
- Hey, hey, slowly, slowly.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.