[Ballard] Previously on Ballard...
So what, you running this thing now?
[Olivas] Keep doing your jobs
and the money will keep flowing.
I'll make sure the cartel knows
it's business as usual.
We traced another number
from Driscoll's cell phone.
I wanted you to see it for yourself.
Wow. Wow. [chuckles]
[siren wailing]
- LAPD. Olivas, hands up.
- Hey, easy.
You got no idea what you've done.
[Berchem] I bet it feels good. Knowing
what you've been through with Olivas.
Surprise. You used to love
watching your dad build his boards.
[Ballard] He died when I was 14.
Surfing accident.
Tutu in there thought it would be
cathartic for me to build his board.
[Parker] You know, everything's coming
up Cold Case unit.
You can feel it, right? Like
something big's coming around the corner?
[Laffont] November 2000.
Sawtelle. Check it out.
Naomi Bennett was assaulted?
- She was a victim.
- A victim who survived.
[gasps]
[Berchem] This is huge.
She could ID your serial killer.
These men may or may not
have been involved in your attack.
Can you tell me
if you recognize any of 'em?
[Naomi] It's number four.
Tom, it's him. Gary Pearlman.
The Councilman's dad?
We found a living victim.
Rawls, where are you?
I stopped by Jake's place.
I'm with his dad.
- No, Gary!
- [gunshot]
[gasps] Rawls?
[sirens wailing]
[police officers chattering]
Any sign of the shooter?
No, ma'am. Car's in the garage.
Must've left on foot.
Lock down this neighborhood.
No one goes in or out.
- We're all over it.
- [chattering on police radio]
How bad is it?
[paramedic] He's hanging in,
but we've gotta move.
No. Oh, no, Rawls. Goddamn it. [sighs]
Where is your car?
Where is your car, Rawls?
[Ballard] You hang in there, okay?
[chattering on police radio]
Pull up DMV registration for Ted Rawls.
Put out a crime broadcast on his BMW ASAP.
Suspect is Gary Pearlman.
He is armed and dangerous.
Copy.
[phone rings]
[Ballard sighs]
- Laffont.
- Um, what's the news?
[Ballard] He's hanging in,
but he's lost a lot of blood, Tom.
They're putting him
in the ambulance right now.
Any sign of Gary?
No, but I think he stole Rawls's car.
We're putting out a BOLO.
I need you to coordinate with Metro.
Get Naomi somewhere safe until this guy
is in custody. I need her on lockdown.
[Pearlman] Hey. Hey. Hey.
- I gotta go.
- Is that my dad?
- [Ballard] Jake. Jake.
- Is that my dad? Is he okay?
- Stop. Stop.
- What are you doing?
- What are you doing here? Where's my dad?
- Stop.
Jake, it's not your dad. It's Rawls.
What?
These murders we've been investigating...
they were committed by your father.
- What? No. No, that can't... that can't be.
- Yes.
It was Gary all along.
No.
He killed Sarah. He killed all of them.
- [breathes shakily]
- I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
- No. No.
- [siren wailing]
I want the major case
management system running
before the hour's up.
Willis, you're heading it.
Make sure we have canvas teams
pulling video in Pearlman's neighborhood
and start interviewing
potential witnesses.
I want Cyber up on...
Cooper. Take him to my office.
I want Cyber up Gary Pearlman's
bank accounts
on his phones,
his email, his social media.
And I wanna find Ted Rawls's car.
Right now, that's the best chance
we have of locating Gary.
4 Series like that should come
with GPS tracking. I'll get into it.
Coglin, have one of your people
talk to Jake.
Get a list of friends and family
his father might seek out.
- Places he might go.
- Copy that.
Sir, I'd like to be the one
to talk to him.
Captain, no disrespect to the detective...
I've built a rapport with him.
Sir, my team runs these drills.
We know what we're doing.
And I know these cases,
and I know the people involved.
- If the lieutenant would like to--
- Detective Ballard.
Coglin, I want her with Jake.
- Yes, sir.
- [Berchem] All right. Let's get to it.
You wanna tell me
what the hell happened with the DNA?
You ran Sarah's weeks ago. Why didn't we
get a familial match to the killer?
The only thing I can think of is that
Gary is not Sarah's biological father.
- You think the wife had an affair?
- She could have.
I've got a volunteer working it right now
with Darcy to confirm it.
Make me your first call.
[sighs] Yes, sir.
You get Naomi squared away?
Yeah. Parker's taking her to a safe house
in Hollywood. She is pretty freaked.
I bet she is.
- [sighs]
- You busy?
After Mom died,
he, um, folded in on himself.
And all their friends
were hers anyway. [sniffles]
He's got nobody. Except me, I guess.
So you can't think of anywhere
he may have gone?
Places he talked about?
You know, I found her that night.
Sarah.
[mournful music playing]
Got home from a friend's.
I thought everyone was gone.
It was so quiet.
I went upstairs.
Her door was open and...
God.
He must've heard me pull up
and that's why he went out the window.
Wasn't five minutes later
before he came through the front door
like he just got home himself.
[Pearlman sighs]
I looked up to him. He came to my games.
He helped me with homework.
He gave me advice.
[sighs]
I mean, none of it makes any sense.
How can... How can he be this...
this monster at the same time?
- [Nelson] Hey.
- Hi.
You talk to Jake?
He's in rough shape.
It's good that you're here.
Have you heard anything yet?
No. I'm on my way to the hospital now.
If there's anything I can do...
Thank you.
- [phone buzzes]
- [sighs]
Colleen. How's Rawls?
Uh... [sighs] Last I heard, in surgery.
But I haven't seen the doctor in a while.
Okay, I'm on my way to you.
Okay. Hey, listen, I heard from Darcy.
That palm print on the windowsill
in Sarah's bedroom,
it definitely belongs to Gary.
Jesus.
And, uh, Jake
and Sarah don't share paternal DNA.
So mom had an affair. What a mess.
What about Gary? Any news on where he is?
[Ballard] Not yet. But we'll find him.
I just... I can't believe it was him.
He seemed like such a nice man.
[elevator dings]
I gotta go.
Call me if there's any updates.
Lewis is covering this area of quadrants.
He's gonna upload. You two split it.
- Captain.
- Whatever you get,
- let me know immediately.
- Excuse me.
I know that the assumption is always
that the suspect is going to run,
but I don't think Gary Pearlman
is going to do that.
Why wouldn't he?
You know we found a woman, Naomi Bennett,
that he left for dead back in 2000.
So?
So based on what I know about him, I don't
believe that he would leave her behind.
Sir.
Explain.
She's not just a loose end.
The guy wants to rabbit.
There is no doubt in my mind.
I agree. He wants to run.
But there's a part of him,
the part that killed all those women,
that won't let him do that.
The fact that Naomi is still out there
and she's alive means that... she won.
I don't think he'll walk away from that.
- I'm sorry. This is just a complete--
- Just wait a second, goddamn it.
Say you're right, then what?
What would you have us do?
Make sure he knows that somehow.
How do we do that?
- Put me on the news.
- What? Like this isn't already a circus.
- Captain, we need to focus our resources...
- Sir, let me tell him
what he's leaving behind.
And then maybe, I don't know,
but maybe he will reveal himself.
I hope you brought a change of clothes.
[sorrowful music plays]
The diligent work
of the LAPD's Cold Case unit
uncovered a mountain of evidence
that Gary Pearlman left behind,
including, most recently, a living victim.
A woman who survived to tell her tale
and to ID him.
Now, with the full force
of the department focused on locating him,
we are confident Gary Pearlman
will be in custody very soon.
When we count the casualties
this man left behind,
it's not just the women he murdered,
and their families who suffered,
but his family suffered too.
And with that, I know that Jake Pearlman
would like to say a few words.
Dad. Please. Just turn yourself in.
Anything you do now
is only gonna make it worse.
Please, do the right thing and cooperate.
They got a location on Rawls's BMW.
Yeah. A block away from Union Station,
where people go to leave the city.
MTA security has Pearlman
on camera entering the building,
but they lost him in the crowd.
He could be anywhere.
- Hey, can you bring up that track...
- Yeah, well, I need...
Come on, I need a name. I need a name.
[Coglin] San Francisco, Phoenix,
Bakersfield, San Diego.
And those are just
the train tickets that he bought.
He also bought two bus tickets
and a subway pass.
According to his credit card company,
he rented a car too.
I want your team coordinating
with MTA, Greyhound,
Amtrak, Budget Rent a Car, whatever.
Follow each lead down,
however long it takes.
- One of them is gotta lead us to him.
- Yes, sir. SIS is on it.
Sir.
If we need more context on Pearlman,
we'll reach out to you. Understood?
[Parker] What's going on?
He's in the wind.
Damn.
You good?
Yeah. Let's just get to the hospital.
Bet you're happy now. Huh, Renée?
Now that IA bought whatever bullshit
that you sold 'em.
It's not bullshit.
You ruined my husband's career.
Olivas made his own choices.
No. You did that.
You lumped him in
with all those dirty cops.
Zamira, you know.
You were his partner. He's a good man.
Janet, there are--
Why don't you go to the hospital first?
I'll meet you there.
Right. Okay.
How could you do that to our family?
You don't need to believe me, all right?
But if you wanna know the truth...
Captain Berchem will tell you everything.
Take care of yourself.
[phone buzzing]
Sir, I just got to the hospital.
[Berchem] Ballard,
a woman was found in the trunk of her car.
Alive, thank God.
But she works at the Robeks
in Union Station.
Pearlman car-jacked her.
That's how he got out of there.
Where's the car?
Authorities found it
near the Mexican border in Arizona.
They're flagging him with Border Patrol,
but Gary probably crossed hours ago.
We missed him, Ballard.
Yeah. Okay, thanks.
[melancholy music plays]
[no audible dialogue]
[mournful music plays]
Surprised to see you in your blues.
Figured he would've liked it.
[Ballard] Some people might assume
that Reserves are outsiders.
Not full sworn, not brothers in blue.
I think they're as blue as the rest of us.
Maybe more so.
Because they don't do it for the pension.
They certainly don't do it for the salary.
They do it because they're part of
the world that they're trying to improve.
And Rawls... Ted.
He wanted to make a difference.
And he may not have been full-time sworn,
but he was no tourist.
And when you lose a guy like that,
you don't just lose the man.
You lose the justice that he was
gonna chase down too.
So we have to go out there
and chase it down for him.
Ted...
you were an important part of our team...
and you will be missed. Dearly.
He thought I was still angry with him.
He knew you wouldn't always be.
How you doing, Ballard?
Hey.
What is it?
I can't stop thinking about this guy
at my dad's funeral.
One of his front teeth was missing.
Anyway, he told me later that morning
that it was actually my dad
who knocked it out.
They were 18. Got into a bar fight.
Next day, my dad shows up at the pier
for this new gig on a long-liner.
And guess who he's working with?
- Gap-tooth guy. [chuckles]
- [chuckles]
They thought for sure one of them was
gonna go overboard by the end of the day.
But you know how it goes.
Small boat, big ocean.
Friends for life.
Yeah.
I guess you're not coming
back to Homicide.
No. I think I'm good where I'm at.
[car approaches]
[Pearlman sighs]
It's quiet around here.
After hours.
How you holding up?
Not even sure I've really processed it.
Uh...
His records were a mess,
but I think I got everything.
Thanks for putting all this together.
There are still victims
we haven't ID'd yet,
so this could help us do that.
Some of this could even lead us to him.
Yeah. Good.
[sniffles]
You know, all this, um...
who he is... [stammers] ...I just
can't wrap my head around it.
I feel like...
like I'm in one of those Escher drawings
where everything holds together
but nothing makes sense.
It's ironic, you know.
I pushed for all this to get closure
and some peace.
I got everything but.
You gave that to other people though.
Other families that were hurting.
You have to remember that. It matters.
I hope so.
[sniffles]
[sighs]
Hey, do you mind if I take a few
of his things with me?
I can have Hastings
bring it to his family.
That'd be nice.
[chuckles]
He, um, called me on his way
to my house that morning.
He was angry with me.
He was coming over to have a word.
About what?
He thought it was pretty messed up how
you got blindsided in that news interview,
and he thought we were crazy to think
about replacing you.
[sighs]
I've, uh, decided to suspend my campaign.
Not like I had a chance
after all this, so...
But, um, I want you to know that
you'll still have friends on the council,
even after I'm gone.
[sighs] I appreciate that.
Thank you.
Hey. Um...
When you do find him,
if you can, bring him in alive.
[phone buzzing]
[sighs]
Hey, Tutu.
[Tutu] Just wanted to say hi,
see how you were doing.
I'm fine.
I'm just working. [clears throat]
How's it feel?
[sighs]
Quiet.
And a little weird, to be honest. His
protein powder is still in the break room.
Mmm. When are you coming home?
I think now's a good time.
I'll pack up and head out.
- [clears throat]
- Good. I'll chill a couple.
Like the sound of that.
[chuckles] Love you.
Yeah, yeah.
[switch clanks]
[generator whirring]
[door opens]
[footsteps]
- [gunshot]
- [Ballard grunts]
[grunts, panting]
[gunshots]
[Gary] You really think you're gonna walk
away from this, Renée?
Huh?
We both know how this ends.
[handle rattles]
[both grunting]
[grunting continues]
[shelf bangs, crashes]
[Ballard yells]
[grunting]
- [Gary screaming, groaning]
- [hammer cocks]
- [panting]
- You bitch!
[groaning, whimpering]
This is Detective Renée Ballard.
Ahmanson Training Center.
Advise responding units code 4,
suspect's in custody.
I need an RA for a male, white,
approximately 70 years old,
suffering from a pretty messed-up hand.
[groaning continues]
You know, I knew she was one of them
the minute I saw her face.
Standing at the counter,
going on and on with the salesgirl.
I'm sorry. You said she was one of them.
Who is them?
A certain kind of woman.
Uppity, selfish, not ladylike.
You said she was talking
to the salesperson.
Yeah. At the jewelry store.
She had just gotten a promotion,
and, uh, she was going to put everything
on hold for this job.
Marriage. Kids.
I was doing him a favor, you know?
She wasn't the marrying kind.
We'll come back to that.
We didn't connect any,
uh, souvenirs to Sarah.
I guess you had plenty around the house.
[Laffont] She seemed like a nice girl.
Honor roll, cheerleader...
[chuckles] ...theater club.
How did your daughter fit the pattern?
She wasn't my daughter.
But I raised her anyway, like she was.
Because I-I believe in family first.
And yet she dared
to accuse me of infidelity.
That night?
She found some things in my truck
and she thought I was cheating
on her mother.
She found your souvenirs. The lipstick.
She thought you were having an affair.
She had no idea that--
She shouldn't have been looking
through my things.
[Bosch] That's enough.
He cop to all your victims?
The ones we've ID'd, yeah.
Laffont's working the other three
unmatched souvenirs we have left.
What about Laura?
He give you anything new?
Only that he killed her because
she wasn't gonna make his coffee anymore.
Come again?
Laura was a barista at Gary's local spot.
She was nice to him. She talked to him.
He liked her
until she landed the commercial,
and then he said that she,
uh, was no longer humble,
she was bragging about getting the role,
and that she didn't have to
pour coffee anymore.
[sighing] Just... He was upset
that she was leaving him behind.
Let me guess.
All goes back to his childhood.
Mom left when he was eight,
dad took it out on him pretty severely.
Told him he was the reason.
And the world gains another psychopath.
Looks like he really
did a number on this place.
Caught me by surprise. I thought he'd go
after our living victim, Naomi,
but I had the psychology right.
Just the wrong target.
Probably a good thing
you don't actually think like a killer.
[chuckles]
Glad you got the bastard though.
Even after all those years
of haystack blown over the investigation.
Well, the past is always present, right?
Renée, let me tell you something.
Anyone ever takes me out,
I hope you catch the case.
That's a high compliment, coming from you.
What about your conspiracy case?
Olivas and those other shit-bird cops.
Well, it's with the DA's office now.
They're keeping me
at arms length, of course.
I should know more when I see you next.
Ah. Here's everything I got
on Laura's case.
It's a long list of casualties
with this guy.
Yeah. It is.
[knocks on cabinet]
Till next time.
[sighs] You got back late last night.
Yeah. I went out with the team.
We needed some time to be together.
It's beautiful.
You gonna finally take it out?
How could I not?
He'd be proud of you.
["Only the Strong" plays]
♪ Only the strong survive ♪
♪ Only the wrong relive their lives ♪
♪ We've been here a thousand times ♪
♪ Wish I could go back and find ♪
♪ Letters I wrote you in my mind ♪
We're gonna need more shelves.
♪ Perhaps I could unknot us
from this awful bind ♪
[sighs] Thank you.
Take care. I'm proud of you.
♪ Love is a sickness cured by time ♪
♪ Bruises all end up benign ♪
♪ I hope that you can change my mind ♪
♪ Had to leave this crying all behind ♪
♪ I hope that you don't think
that I'm unkind ♪
♪ So somebody told me,
only and only ♪
♪ Only the strong will survive ♪
♪ Only the strong survive ♪
♪ And I won't write a woman
with a man on my mind ♪
♪ Hope that didn't sound too unkind ♪
Hola, mi amor.
♪ Just struggling to figure out how ♪
♪ Only, only, only, only ♪
♪ Only the strong can survive ♪
♪ Hope that you can change my mind ♪
♪ I had to leave this crying all behind ♪
♪ I hope that you don't think
that I'm unkind ♪
♪ So somebody told me,
only and only ♪
♪ Only the strong can survive ♪
[music ends]
[Bosch] Renée! Renée!
- Hey.
- Hey, Harry. What are you doing here?
I reached out to my friend
in the DA's office,
asked about your conspiracy case.
Tell me.
Goes before the grand jury next week.
Charging six officers.
- Six? I gave them seven names.
- I know.
They're gonna kick Olivas.
He's gonna walk. Sorry.
So, I want you to be
on that two o'clock call with the mayor--
Chandler. Why isn't Robert Olivas
being charged with conspiracy?
Give us a moment.
How did you know?
The evidence my team collected
indicated he was higher up
than any other officer we gave you.
Then I believe you've answered
your own question.
He made a deal?
With what? What did he offer?
Conspiracy cases always require
an insider who's gonna flip--
We gave you Manny Santos.
Manny is low-level. We needed more.
Olivas raised his hand.
Of course he did.
And you had to take the easy way.
I know, given your history
with Detective Olivas,
that you might feel--
My history?
He told us about the issues between you,
which you should've shared from the start.
My history has nothing to do with the fact
that he's committed serious crimes.
Detective, you're not seeing
the bigger picture here.
No, I'm seeing it. Pretty damn clear.
Parker, shit's gone sideways
with Olivas. Call me back.
What the hell, Ballard?
What are you doing here?
You snake! You don't care who you hurt
or who you leave behind!
You always get away with it! Always!
Calm down, Ballard. Don't be so upset.
You think the world is fair,
but it's just not.
And it's not my fault either.
I just know how
to make the most out of it.
I'm gonna be fine. I'm gonna weather
all of this because I always do.
But you... you're gonna spend the rest
of your career in that basement,
clawing to get out.
[scoffs] You know,
I've been where you are.
Certain that the wind's gonna blow
in my direction.
But what you don't know
is the whispers have already started.
You're gonna be toxic in the LAPD.
They're gonna wipe your name
from everything.
Where's your wife, by the way?
She take off already?
Took the boys with her?
You've got me to thank for that.
I put her in touch with Berchem.
Give me a reason.
[sighs]
My career may be in a basement,
but at least it's not in a fucking box.
[items clatter]
[sighs]
Who could he possibly have to trade?
I don't know.
We'll probably find out in a year or two,
when everything comes to light.
But at least he doesn't have
a badge to hide behind.
Bet you wish I never knocked on your door.
Nah.
I mean, don't get me wrong,
it kills me that he won't get an ounce
of what he deserves,
but... at least I'm not alone in all this.
- [cars approaching]
- [siren blares]
[dog barks]
- [Ballard] Can I help you?
- Detective Renée Ballard?
- That's me.
- [phone chimes]
You're under arrest
for the murder of Detective Robert Olivas.
What?
Ballard, somebody shot him. He's dead.
[dog barks, growls]
[stammers] Uh, can you hold on
just for one second please?
- You... You don't need to...
- [handcuffs click]
[no audible dialogue]