[Ballard] Previously on Ballard...
Bosch's guy pulled 14
numbers off of Driscoll's phone.
All burners. We traced one of them
directly to Olivas last night.
[Ballard] Number ends in 0666.
[Martina] Manny Santos.
My boyfriend.
He was getting texts from Olivas.
Manny Santos? Hey!
No!
[Ballard] You're burned, Manny.
You're just the only one
who knows it right now.
Don't you wanna keep it that way?
My name is Officer Emmanuel Santos.
I'm cooperating of my own volition.
I was a part of group of cops
across the LAPD that colluded
with the Zacatecas Nuevas cartel.
You don't call me, Manny. I call you.
- What do you want?
- [Ballard] I just wanted to see your face.
[officer]
LAPD. Put your hands on your head.
[Abril] Does the cartel has my son?
We are going to keep looking for him.
You said that there was
a video of Luis with Gael.
I narrowed it down to seven kids
who could be a match for Gael Ibarra.
These are the addresses where
each one first entered the system,
but this one was surrendered at
a firehouse six blocks from the Sunbeam.
[Ballard] The connection between
these victims is behavior.
What if our killer was punishing these
women for stepping out of their place?
It's lipstick.
It was found under
Sarah's bed like she dropped it there.
That's not Sarah's. That's Othella.
It's a brand for Black women.
There was no analysis
done on the lipstick inside.
If it wasn't Sarah's, then whose was it?
Results on the lipstick?
Yep. You were right.
Lipstick wasn't Sarah's.
Original IO only swabbed the outside.
Darcy tested the actual lipstick.
Got a sample, and a hit in CoDIS.
Hell yes.
DNA matched a woman named Naomi Bennett.
In the system for a 2003 felony.
Naomi Bennett. Arrested in 2003
for a hot prowl in Sacramento.
- Hot prowl?
- A burglary with an occupant inside.
Naomi broke into the home of a woman.
Twenty-six years old.
Living alone,
asleep in her bed at the time.
Sounds like one of our victims.
What if our killer wasn't a solo act?
Hmm. You think this Naomi
person may be working with him?
- Could be.
- Female accomplice?
It's not that uncommon actually.
Gerald and Charlene Gallego, Myra Hindley
and Ian Brady, the Ken and Barbie killers.
Okay, Reddit.
- [grunts]
- All right. Deep dive on Naomi.
Every database we got,
forwards and backwards from '03.
Get creative.
Flag on the play. The serial killer's
accomplice theory doesn't hold.
November 2000. Sawtelle. Check it out.
- Naomi Bennett was assaulted?
- Strangled in her home. Left for dead.
November 2000.
That was five months
before Sarah Pearlman's murder.
Naomi Bennett wasn't an accomplice.
She was a victim.
A victim who survived.
[gasps, cries]
This is huge.
She could ID your serial killer.
That's what we're hoping.
Thing is, she's in Madera.
- Madera?
- It's a cow town. Central Valley.
I did check.
The department plane is available.
That's not happening.
Just get Madera PD
to set up a virtual interview.
You want me to re-traumatize
an assault victim on Zoom?
And then try to extract
25-year-old details from her?
Good point.
Have a nice drive.
Right. [sighs]
On the corruption case, DA's office
wants written statements from your team.
Are you hearing anything else from them?
Case is strong.
Indictments should be
coming in the next week or two.
I bet it feels good.
Knowing what you've
been through with Olivas.
But Renée, he's well liked.
So, just keep your head down.
Copy that.
Hey, Parker. Pack a bag.
Meet me at the Ahmanson. We leave in 45.
Whoa. Renée Ballard.
J. Edgar. It's been a while. You good?
Trying to be.
Heard you're breaking
the Sarah Pearlman case open.
Turned a cold murder hot?
- Heard from who?
- Mutual friend.
[chuckles] I'm glad, Ballard.
- I'm glad you landed on your feet.
- Mmm. Jury's still out. [scoffs]
I don't know. I'm hearing rumblings.
Y-You close this big one,
they might bump you back to Homicide.
[chuckles] How many department
rumors turn out to be true? Come on.
Well, this one has legs.
I'm crossing my fingers
'cause I could use a new partner.
Yeah? Who they got you with?
They got me with Tomlinson,
and I kid you not,
this guy spends all day checking bitcoin.
[both chuckle]
Stay out of trouble, Renée.
[inhales deeply, sighs]
I cannot believe you got
Berchem to approve the plane.
- Well...
- Well?
He didn't. Hope you like a road trip.
- I guess.
- [phone buzzes]
- As long as you let me DJ. [chuckles]
- [chuckles]
- What? News on the corruption case?
- No. It's Laffont.
He just got approval to go see Gael
and collect his DNA.
We might actually
reunite this kid with his mom.
[scoffs] You know, everything
is coming up Cold Case unit.
Look, I know we took some bad
beats, but you can feel it, right?
Like something big's
coming around the corner?
You sound like Colleen.
[chuckles]
Okay, sounds good. Will do.
That was Ballard.
She said that the DA's office is
requesting written statements
on the Manny Santos case,
so while we wait for her and Parker...
- Written statements?
- Letters make words. Left to right.
[scoffs] Can you put that thing down?
No, I mean, statements about what exactly?
- Well, let's ask the expert. Detective.
- [Laffont grunts]
The DA's office
wants statements about the--
Oh, uh, I heard.
Um, detail your actions
during the investigation. Be specific.
Stick to your own POV.
It'll be different for each of you.
[scoffs] Homework.
You okay with that?
Uh, yeah.
[clicks tongue]
I think I'm gonna enjoy this.
- Especially the ending.
- Just stick to the facts.
And if you need any help...
[sighs]
- Hey. Everything okay?
- Yeah.
I got Gael's DNA.
Oh, that-that's a good thing. Isn't it?
Yeah, Darcy's gonna run it,
but it's just the foster home.
I mean, it's a caring place,
but they're under-resourced.
Even when, uh, the system is working,
it's not working well enough.
[clicks tongue, sighs] It's a shame.
[sighs] God, I hate this part.
Ms. Bennett? I'm Detective Renée Ballard.
This is Officer Parker.
We're with the LAPD.
We'd like to ask you some questions.
About?
November 2000.
[sighs]
All of them are dead...
And-And I'm-I'm the only one.
I know.
It's a lot to process.
[inhales shakily]
That was decades ago and I could
barely remember any details back then.
The detectives,
they would ask me questions,
but it's like my mind didn't want
me to remember. [inhales sharply]
I-I don't know how to explain it.
I understand.
I do.
But the smallest detail could help us.
We'd like to show you some things.
See if they spark your memory.
[grunts, sighs]
I don't know. [sighs]
Actually, you know, why don't we, um...
Why don't we give you the night?
And we can speak to you in the morning.
Okay?
Yeah.
You had a feeling?
Now who sounds more like Colleen?
I know.
But I could tell
that she was boxing us out.
[sighs] Sometimes you only get one shot.
[Ballard] Yeah, but it can take time.
You know. You've been through it.
[sighs]
I still can't believe we got him.
- [clears throat]
- Oh, boy.
Well, I don't know what
business brings ladies like you
to this fair part of the country,
but God bless capitalism.
- [both chuckle]
- [chuckles] Work trip, am I right?
- You sure are, cowboy.
- I knew it.
Let me buy you a round.
Uh, we're still in the middle
of this one actually.
Oh, come on. All work and no play?
Is that it?
- Let's have some fun. [laughs]
- [laughs] Oh.
Oh, don't you worry.
I got a permit for it.
- Ah.
- And, uh, I know how to handle it.
[chuckles]
- Fastest hands in the west, I bet.
- Like Billy the goddamn Kid.
[chuckling]
So, how about it?
Yeah, we're just finishing up
our wings and...
Tired of tipping back beers? Hmm?
Well, what if I could get
my hands on something to, uh... [sniffs]
...light up the night a little bit?
- Catch my drift?
- [chuckles]
- I think we do.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
- [chuckles]
- Oh. Um...
- You know what?
I got a permit for mine too.
- Right. [chuckles] I, uh...
- Go on now.
- Just gonna... Okay.
- Get.
[Ballard laughing]
[sighs] Sometimes it's just too fun.
[sighs]
I don't wanna move too fast with Naomi.
She's got that assault buried so deep,
we could lose our chance
if we don't tread carefully.
I don't know.
What if we do the opposite?
[knock on door]
- Good morning, Ms. Bennett.
- Good morning.
Look, I'm-I'm so sorry.
I-I stayed up all night racking my brain,
and I really wanna help you,
but there's nothing to tell.
- I've moved on. Thank you.
- Naomi.
[sighs] Look, hear me out.
I know this is hard.
But the reality is we need you to do this
for all the women that he's hurt,
and all the women that he could hurt.
[inhales sharply]
It's not that I don't want to.
I just can't.
Yeah, because you're too far from it.
It's like you said,
your mind won't let you.
Maybe that'll change if you go all in.
Come back to LA with us.
Wait? Come back to LA?
Maybe if you go back and you
immerse yourself, it's a way to remember.
[breathes deeply]
[sighs]
[inhales sharply, sighs]
[breathes shakily] Wait.
Is that...
That's how we found you.
Wow.
[sniffles, sighs]
[sighs]
Everything fell apart for that girl.
[inhales sharply]
Can you tell us more?
Um...
[sniffles]
Um, after what happened, I, um,
I just left, you know?
I thought getting away would help.
I started drinking.
And then, I couldn't drink enough.
The first time I tried coke,
I was like, "Thank God."
But eventually
that wasn't enough either, so...
[sniffles]
After that, um, I got arrested.
The burglary in '03?
I tried to break into
my friend's house, and, ugh...
that was my rock bottom.
That was the end of
a nosedive that all started with him.
[inhales sharply]
Things were good before that.
So, it's like,
I look at this girl and I just...
It just crushes me, you know?
[swallows] When you say "good"?
[inhales deeply] I was happy.
I had my own place.
I'd been grinding through beauty school...
[sniffles] ...for years,
and paying my own way.
And then I finally,
finally got a chair in a salon.
And I was like...
Man.
I mean, I skipped to work every day.
It might not seem like much, but...
But it was everything to me.
[sniffles, sighs]
Two months before Naomi was attacked,
she landed a chair at Jolie in Mar Vista.
That sounds familiar.
Like Elena's promotion,
or Laura Wilson's commercial gig.
But for that to motivate
our guy to go after Naomi,
- he'd have to know about it.
- Exactly.
So look for anyone with proximity.
Friends, family, employees at the salon.
Uh, employees at
the Jolie strip mall. Anyone.
Councilman Pearlman.
Everything all right?
Things are turning nasty,
with the election coming up.
My opponent... [sighs]
...wants to make my connection
to the Cold Case unit a central
campaign point against me.
- Guys, I am working as fast as I can.
- And we recognize that.
But we have another ask.
I'm setting up an interview with KTLA
to get in front of the narrative.
- And we want you to--
- No.
We want you to join Jake on camera.
Hell no. You came here to talk politics?
- I-I have a million--
- We wanted to meet in person.
- Talk it out.
- Bullshit.
You knew that if you called me,
I'd hang up on you.
Okay, just t-try to think
big picture here, Ballard.
It's not just Councilman's
political career that's on the line.
It's his influence.
What's this?
Everything about my relationship
with Manny. Right up to his arrest.
And why are you giving it to me?
Make sure it's thorough. Professional.
I don't want anything to screw this up.
Oh.
I'm sure Laffont probably--
Laffont's too nice to be honest.
You lack the tact to be polite.
Okay then.
- Hey, Ballard.
- [Ballard] Hey.
- I found, uh, something.
- [phone buzzing]
Back in 2000, there was a hot wings spot
at the Jolie mall,
right next to the salon.
Had an employee named Casey Robbins.
- Casey Robbins have a record?
- Oh, no. Something more than that.
[inhales sharply] In 2000,
Casey Robbins lived in Palms
on Jasmine Avenue, just north of Venice.
One of the same blocks
that another victim,
Josie Culver,
canvassed for Hillary Clinton.
Josie Culver knocked
on Casey Robbins's door.
He has a connection to two of our victims?
- That's something, all right.
- I told ya.
Can you get a photo of him from 2000?
[sighs]
[sighs] Naomi, I know it's been a long
time, but do you recognize this man?
[breathing shakily]
Um, I'm not sure.
[stammers] I still can't picture his face,
but I'm trying.
Don't worry about it.
- It's okay.
- Thank you.
Where's Casey right now?
I couldn't find a current on him.
But found his mom. Woodland Hills.
All right.
Rawls and I will go check it out.
You guys cross reference every victim
with this guy Robbins, all right?
This is our angle.
Rawls.
[scoffs]
What?
The shit women have to
deal with is messed up.
[sighs] I just...
I read Martina's statement.
And... [stammers]
...everything that happened to Naomi.
I mean, all-all these cases.
Yeah. It's not ideal.
And you're expected to date
under these circumstances. I mean...
Honestly, what's that like?
I mean,
I guess it's like getting on the 405.
The traffic sucks,
but you still gotta get across town.
[chuckling]
What about you?
D-Dating wise.
Oh, you mean my foundation?
What?
Oh. Ted Rawls's Foundation
for Hungry Single Women.
It's our mission to feed
any hungry single woman
at LA's finest establishments,
drinks included, for four dates,
give or take, until we amicably part ways.
Jesus, Ted.
[chuckles, sighs]
I mean, I date. I...
I haven't been
in a relationship in forever.
Psych 101 probably says
that you can't have my dad
and come away with
a winning approach to love.
I don't know.
Maybe I'm part of the problem.
Well, at least you're rich.
[both chuckle]
Yeah.
Yeah, I could believe
a serial killer grew up here.
[scoffs] Yeah.
Only one car.
- Why don't you check out back?
- Uh-huh.
- Hi.
- You're here about the dog then?
- The dog?
- You're a little early.
Don't just stand there.
[sighs]
[gasps] You're a cop.
I love Law & Order.
"You have the right
to remain silent." [chuckles]
You know, after the apocalypse,
all that will be left
are cockroaches and cop shows.
And that will be just fine by me.
You live alone?
Oh, I did, till my son moved back in.
Casey.
He's a real mama's boy.
[Ballard] Is your son here right now?
[stammers] No?
No. He stepped out.
Do you mind if I use your restroom?
I just had too much coffee on the way in.
Uh... [stammers] ...sure.
Sure, if you're brave enough.
You go right ahead.
Thanks.
[knocking on door]
[Casey's mom] You okay?
Hope you didn't fall in.
"Right to remain silent." Oh.
- [sighs]
- Well, come on now.
Let's get what you came for.
Uh, actually,
I just realized that I need--
[Casey] Mama?
Oh, dear.
There you are, sweetie. Hi.
Who the hell is this?
- She's the woman about the dog.
- That woman canceled.
Who the hell are you?
She's a cop.
- Got a badge and everything.
- Yeah. I think I should get out of here.
That's a good idea.
"Anything you say can
and will be used against you."
Step aside.
Step aside!
- Step--
- Everything good in here?
[Ballard] Rawls.
Do you want to get the car started?
Get animal services over here,
and call SIS.
That creep doesn't go
anywhere without a shadow.
Looked like a horror show in there.
Think he'll consent to a search?
He doesn't have to.
- I already got his DNA.
- Oh. [chuckles]
- Hey, now. [chuckles]
- [Ballard] Hey.
Tutu? Wow. I mean, it's...
It's 9:30.
A perfectly respectable time for mimosas.
[chuckles]
This new lead sounds like
a cause for celebration.
Maybe. Under normal circumstances.
And how would one
describe current circumstances?
Well, if I solve this serial case,
there could be a move
back to Homicide in my future.
And that's not a good thing?
[stammers, sighs]
You like where you are.
[sighs] You know, I think I might.
Even more reason to celebrate.
I'll get the glasses.
- [chuckles]
- [phone buzzes]
Goddamn it.
[sighs]
- Hey, what's up?
- [Ballard] Hey, Parker. Casey's a bust.
The toothbrush sample didn't match
the DNA we got from the palm print.
No.
[groans] I know we were
supposed to take a morning off,
but I need you to get Naomi
into a black and white.
It's time for her to go see the apartment.
- You sure she's ready for that?
- I mean, she has to be.
[stammers] Okay. We'll meet you there.
Frack! You know what? I can't.
I gotta go meet Pearlman and Hastings
to prep for this stupid interview.
[sighs] You know what?
- You go. Take Laffont.
- You got it.
- No notes. Great job.
- Really?
[Ted] Actually, one note.
That guy was an asshole.
Uh... Uh, wait. Two notes.
You know you deserve
better than that, right?
Okay. Good.
- Good morning.
- [sighs]
- How'd you sleep?
[sighs] I'm not sure that I did. Uh...
[grunts] Well, unit's currently empty,
so we can take all the time we need.
Okay.
- [breathing heavily]
- The memories are there.
Just let them surface.
[breathing heavily]
It's weird.
Smells the same.
[inhales deeply, exhales deeply]
I'd only been here a few months.
My first place by myself.
[inhales deeply, sighs]
Uh... That night, I, uh...
I had drinks after work with
a few friends from the salon, and...
and then I came home, not too late.
Do you remember anything being off
when you got home?
[sighs]
No.
[floor creaks]
That creak.
[stammers, breathes shakily]
I used to step over that creak.
[breathes shakily]
But that night, I heard it and I knew
somebody was in the apartment.
- [breathing shakily]
- [floor creaking]
Where were you? When you heard it?
[breathing shakily, stammers]
I was...
I was asleep.
In bed.
There.
[breathing shakily]
There was a dresser on that wall.
Used to be... [stammers] ...a fan there.
What's that sound? It was after, uh...
Was it after? [gasps]
[gasping]
I remember when he was...
[breathes shakily]
There were people outside.
They were laughing.
[sniffles] His, uh...
[cries] His eyes.
[breathes shakily] I remember his eyes.
They were brown.
You're sure?
[breathes shakily] I'm positive.
Um...
[breathes shakily] Oh, God.
I can almost see his face.
[cries] And then it fades away.
[breathing shakily]
- Shit. Okay.
- Okay, okay. Don't worry.
Don't force it, okay?
This was really good, Naomi.
I just need a minute. [breathes shakily]
- Okay.
- I just... [breathes shakily]
Progress.
A little.
Just...
- I just hope it was worth it.
- Oh, she'll get there.
She's doing good.
I'll call Ballard, ask her to put in
a request for a sketch artist.
There are over 6,000
unsolved murders in this city.
Many of them involving
victims with families
who don't have the power to pull strings.
As the son of a blue-collar mom and dad,
I know what that's like.
And now with this unit,
I'm using my position
to fight like hell for all those
families waiting for answers.
But Councilman, what do you
have to say to those critics who say
you are funneling money into
solving your sister's murder,
while the city's crime and homelessness
problems spin out of control?
I'd say those critics
are misguided-- [stammers]
Councilman?
- May I?
- Please.
Cher, you mentioned funneling money.
[chuckles]
The Cold Case unit
has one full salaried employee. Me.
The rest of my team are volunteers.
We work in the basement of this building.
And yet we're still getting results.
Just last week, we closed a case.
Murder of a 19-year-old boy.
We arrested a killer who was
walking the streets for seven years.
Well, that's impressive,
but if Detective Ballard
is actually clearing cases like she says,
then why is it that your office
is in discussions with the police
commission about replacing her?
Well, I'm not sure where
you're getting your information,
but whenever we play with taxpayer money,
it's always important
to constantly reassess.
- Even if changes aren't necessary...
- What the hell?
First time hearing about it.
...just to ensure that resources
are properly allocated.
It was due diligence after the attack
at your house.
- That's all. A contingency plan.
- Then why didn't you say that?
There were also some concern about
the other case you were building.
- Against Robert Olivas.
- What?
It was suggested that there might
have been some personal motivation.
- Oh.
- We should've back channeled.
This was a mistake.
Oh, on that, I wholeheartedly agree.
Oh, gosh.
- [Ballard] Hey.
- Oh, hey. [clears throat]
- Please tell me you bought beer.
- I did, but, um...
- I... I told him he could come in.
- What?
But...
[sighs]
Hey.
Hi.
Sorry to swing by.
I wanted to talk to you in person.
Okay.
Um...
We...
We started this casually.
That was the agreement.
And it was good.
It was great. [chuckles]
But when you were attacked, and I was on
the other end of that call with you, I...
[stammers] It was awful.
I mean, it...
I was worried about you, obviously, but...
it was more than that.
And I realized...
I want something more.
[sighs]
I... [sighs]
I don't know what to say.
No, you don't have to say anything.
Because I know you can't give
something more right now anyway.
[sighs]
I can't let myself be a casualty here.
I'm sorry, Renée.
You're quiet this morning.
More than usual.
Everything good?
Brown eyes.
That's all we got so far.
She didn't give you anything else.
Okay, but she will.
Or she might.
You know, she was with
the sketch artist all morning.
Maybe there was some progress made.
We're putting her
through all of this again.
How much damage is worth doing to her?
If we don't even get what we need.
Come on.
You know sometimes it just takes
one thing to blow open a case.
Just one tiny thing.
And you know
that sometimes that thing never comes.
[radio chatter]
[Naomi] Good morning.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
- [sighs]
- How are you doing?
[groans] I'm fine.
But, uh, why're we here if the assault
happened in my apartment?
Because we're struggling, Naomi.
Ballard.
It's true that, uh, the picture we showed
you of Casey Robbins, that was a miss.
And we ran the list of employees
at the strip mall three times.
Nothing. So... [sighs] ...maybe being
back here will spark something.
Can you tell me which one the salon was?
[sighs] Um, my chair was by that window.
Do you remember any male clients
that stood out to you?
Jolie only serviced women.
Any coffee shops
or restaurants nearby that you'd go to?
I used to bring my own food.
[breathes shakily]
What are the chances of you
actually finding this guy?
I mean, if I can't remember.
Is there some other way?
[Parker] We're figuring it out, okay?
Don't get discouraged.
Why didn't she park in the lot?
That employee.
She didn't park in the lot.
Um, when I worked here,
the company that owned the mall
didn't allow employees to park out front.
So we had to park around the corner,
up a side street.
Can you show us where?
Let's find out who lived here
back in 2000.
If Naomi was parking here, she could
have been spotted on the way to work.
You know that building?
It was under construction back then.
Parker. Listen, I-- Naomi, thank you.
All right, guys, we're expanding our
search to the 1400 block of Ashland.
Naomi parked off-site, so there's a chance
she encountered our killer there.
All right. I'll look into ownership
records, divvy them up with Martina.
Okay. Hey, where's Rawls?
- Isn't he supposed to be here?
- He called.
Uh, said he had something
to do on his way in.
All right, well,
fold him in when he gets here.
- Laffont.
- Mm-hmm.
Naomi didn't recognize her attacker,
which means
he was on the periphery of her life.
Someone she never noticed,
but who noticed her.
Yeah. There was a real estate office
on the corner.
It was renovated in 2000.
I spoke to the owner and he said he was
gonna send me a list of sub-contractors.
Oh, he already did. Great.
I'm gonna forward this to you,
so that you can have a lo...
No.
No way.
What?
No fucking way. That, uh...
That's gotta be a coincidence, right?
Naomi, these men may or may not
have been involved in your attack.
But can you tell me
if you recognize any of 'em?
[sighs]
Okay. [breathes shakily]
All right.
[breathing shakily]
It's number four.
Definitely. Oh, my God.
[stammers] Oh, my God.
Naomi, are you sure?
[inhales heavily]
- Okay?
- Yeah.
[breathes shakily]
So?
Tom, it's him.
Who?
Gary Pearlman.
What?
The Councilman's dad?
Oh, my God.
Pearlman Electric was one of the subs
on the Landmark Realty build-out.
Gary watched her walk
to her new job every day.
To her new life.
[sighs]
She was on top of the world.
And he couldn't have that.
Why didn't anyone flag
a connection in the DNA?
There wasn't one.
I reviewed the results with Darcy myself.
We need Gary's DNA. Where's...
Where's Rawls?
I mean, she ruffles feathers. I get it.
But replacing her would be
a colossal mistake, and Jake...
He-He needs to know that.
[sighs] I'm sorry.
He said he'd be about 20 minutes.
- You don't mind me waiting here for him?
- [Gary] No, not at all.
You've really, uh,
changed your tune on her, haven't you?
Can I assume she's making headway
in Sarah's case?
Oh, yeah.
We found a living victim.
Can you believe that?
- You're... You're kidding.
- No.
No, killer left her for dead in 2000.
Wow.
So, uh, what has she told you?
I mean, did she ID the son of a bitch?
No, but it's been a lot of years,
you know?
A lotta... lotta trauma to wade through.
Yeah.
But Ballard, you know,
she doesn't waste an opportunity.
Speaking of...
- Yo, boss. What's up?
- [Ballard] Hey, Rawls.
Listen, I know this is gonna
sound crazy, but it's true.
Naomi just ID'd Gary Pearlman.
He's our killer.
- What?
- [Ballard] Yeah.
We need you back here. Now.
Uh...
Yeah. Yeah, I can work on that for you.
- Rawls, where are you?
- Uh, I...
I stopped by Jake's place.
I'm with his dad.
Um...
But I'll be back at the office soon.
It's all good.
- No, Gary! Wait! Don't--
- [gun fires]
[gasps] Rawls?
[pants] Oh, my God. [sighs]