One, two, three.
Oh, my God! What am I doing?
I can do this. I can do this.
- Ready? You ready? Ready?
- Go. Go. Go.
- Go!
- Jump, jump, jump.
Jump, jump, jump, jump!
- Is it cold?
- It's amazing!
- Come on, chickenshits!
- Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! You bitch!
I'm a bitch?
You new?
Sorry?
Why're you sorry?
Oh, I wasn't. I didn't hear you.
What's your name?
- Dr. Goodheart.
- For real?
For real.
What's your first name?
Brian. What's yours?
Evie.
If I pee in here,
it gonna throw off your measurements?
Leave him alone. You're scaring him.
Shut up.
Bye, Dr. Goodheart.
- Bye, Dr. Goodheart.
Bye.
Okay.
How long you been waiting?
- Just a couple minutes.
Mmm-hmm.
Oh, good God, no! You're no fun.
Yeah, I know.
- They up?
- Just Mom.
- Hey, Mama.
- Hey, babe.
- How was the sleepover?
- Great.
Did you get any sleep?
- You want me to lie?
- Yes, I want you to lie.
- Did you take your meds?
- Yeah.
Sorry.
What about choir practice?
You have a ride?
Mmm-hmm.
What?
- Ah. Wait for your father.
- I'm starving. Where is he?
- Still in bed.
- Oh, Jesus.
Why does he always sleep in this late?
Stop eating the bacon.
John.
- John.
- It really is amazing.
Shh.
Are you serious?
- What?
- Man, get out of bed.
- You gonna eat that bacon?
- Maybe.
- Maybe?
And what are the factors
influencing your decision?
Leave his bacon alone.
Girl, if you made more,
I wouldn't have to prey upon my children.
If I made more, your heart'd stop.
You can have some of mine.
Thank you.
I got an hour before I run my errands.
You wanna throw?
I have choir practice.
Maybe when I get back?
Oh!
You hear that?
- That's it.
- Please, not again.
- Look,shh.
- You're never gonna find it.
- Where was that?
- It was by the dishwasher, I think.
No, no, it's not by the dishwasher.
It sounded like it came
from the dishwasher.
- It's definitely not by the--
- Hey, if y'all keep talking...
I'm just saying
it's not by the dishwasher.
- Maybe it's in the ceiling.
- You're not gonna find it.
Uh-uh. I'm gonna find it.
Hey.
I got eggs and bacon.
There's a letter in there.
I'll take care of it.
- Hey, how you doing, sir?
- I'm good, I'm good. I'm in 121.
Okay, yeah.
You can go ahead and set up over there.
- Okay, thank you.
- Thank you.
Just a reminder,
you're now required to check in
before you set up your stall.
How are you? How y'all doing?
Just a reminder, you're now required
to check in before you set your stalls up.
Folks, please make sure your vendor number
is clear and visible at your stalls.
All right, folks. Two minutes.
We have two minutes till the first load.
Fucking frackers.
At least it adds to our mystique.
All right, first bus coming in, everybody.
First bus coming in.
- Thank you, Lord.
- Jesus.
- Thank you, Jesus.
WOMAN 'l: Hallelujah. Thank you, God.
- How much?
-It's whatever you wanna give.
This is a test?
No.
Your water, will it make us safe?
It's just a souvenir.
Church service
is just past the 18 marker.
Services are an hour
before the last bus leaves.
God bless you.
- Hey!
- There's a line.
- People are waiting here.
- I'll just be a minute.
How much is it?
Just $140, if you don't mind.
- Hey, John.
- Isaac.
Uh, didn't mean to interrupt.
No, it's all right.
We were just finishing up.
It's all right.
And you remember,
just after Thanksgiving, all right?
Thank you, Mr. Rainey.
Oh, oh...
You, uh, thirsty? I got lemonade.
Uh, sounds good. Thanks.
Big line.
Seems like business is doing good.
I... I hear you're renting out
your top floor.
Yeah, I filled all the paperwork out
with park services,
and they said okay.
Well, if this is gonna be
a two-family residence,
fire code says
upstairs needs a separate entrance
and its own exterior stairwell.
Oh, uh...
Yeah, I can get all that done.
I just need a couple weeks.
No problem. As long as it happens.
So, uh, let's do this.
Sorry?
Your thing.
Can you do me?
Oh, uh...
- You want a reading?
- Yeah.
A reading.
Okay.
Yeah, sure.
Uh...
You a lefty or righty?
All right.
Okay, try and focus all your energy
into your hand,
and, uh...
And rest your palm down into the paint
and then press down
as hard as you can on this here paper.
YUP-
Like that.
- Good?
- Yeah, yeah.
- You can lift it.
- Okay.
- Yeah. Got some Wet-Naps there.
- Thank you.
- Paper towel.
-It's a little messy.
All right.
- You got a good one.
- Oh, good.
You got a birthday coming up?
Yeah, day after tomorrow.
Oh.
Happy birthday.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
What?
- Nothing.
- No, come on. What?
Nothing, man.
I'm not getting anything off you.
Tell me.
Something bad is gonna happen.
To you.
Well, shit, Isaac.
That is not ideal.
Look, I know why you're here, John.
Yeah, listen, you and me
have known each other
since the third grade.
Now, in all those times,
you've never once mentioned to me
that you had superpowers.
I don't have superpowers.
Well, magic powers.
Come on, man.
It's just the two of us talking.
You and me.
Now, this...
It's all bullshit, right?
I don't know what you want me to tell you.
I want you to tell me the truth.
John, what I do
is real.
Ah.
Well...
I gotta respect that.
Now...
How much do I owe you?
No, man, it's on the house.
Uh-uh-uh.
$60 enough?
Hey, John.
Be careful.
Yeah, I sure will.
Ooh!
Knock, knock.
- What?
- Knock, knock.
Who's there?
Broken pencil.
"Broken pencil" who?
Never mind. It's pointless.
Come on.
Gentlemen.
- It's three.
- Two and a half.
- Two.
- Three.
Five.
Jesus, John.
What?
Five?
He's selling a lie,
and folks are buying it.
It's a five.
Whoa, whoa. Hold up.
- Leave the house, Isaac.
- Hold up. What are you doing?
Kitchen's over there. Gas stove.
Whoa, whoa, hey, hey!
What are you doing?
John, hold on! John, hold on!
I don't understand!
Oh, you understand.
Okay, okay, what do you want to hear?
This is not real. Okay?
This is all bullshit.
Please. You don't have to do this.
Please, John. Brother, don't do this.
Fuck you, man.
Nah, I ain't leaving.
I'm not leaving my house.
You're gonna have to kill me.
I'm not leaving.
You're gonna need stitches.
I can do it myself, or I can refer you
to a plastic surgeon in Austin.
I was born here.
I have a right to be here.
When did he start burning
people's houses down?
Tonight.
You were who you said you were,
you should've seen it coming.
Yeah, well, you tell your husband
I meant what I said.
Ain't no avoiding it.
Avoiding what?
- What are you doing?
- Shh.
Must be under something.
- You're not gonna find it.
- No, lam gonna find it.
- Well, at least it got you out of bed.
- Oh, ho-ho.
I got out of bed,
so I could join y'all for church.
Mmm-hmm.
"Mmm-hmm," what?
God damn it!
A reading from Thessalonians.
"Now we ask you, brothers,
"to give recognition to those
who labor among you
"and lead you in the Lord
and admonish you."
Yes. Yes.
"And regard them very highly in love
because of their work.
"Be at peace among yourselves."
Yes. Yes.
- "Comfort the discouraged."
- Yes.
-"Help the weak."
-"Be patient with everyone."
- That's right.
"See to it that no one
repays evil for evil to anyone.
"But always pursue what is good."
Yes!
MAN". That's right. That's right.
"For one another and for all."
- CONGREGATION:: Yes.
- Hallelujah.
This is the word of the Lord.
Yes!
We are the 9,261.
We are spared.
We are spared!
- And for that, we are grateful.
- Amen!
Thank you, Michael.
Just a reminder for y'all,
I'm up in Austin this week
getting my surgery.
So if you are so inclined,
ask of the Lord for competent doctors.
Yes!
And a powerful anesthesia.
So I'll miss a few sermons.
But just like my hip,
y'all will get a great replacement.
Met him doing some missionary work
down in Brazil.
- He don't know our style...
- That's all right.
...but he knows the Good Book.
Amen, amen.
Better than most.
Certainly better than me.
My friend, Matt Jamison.
Thank you, Reverend Massey.
I'm so grateful for your kindness
and for letting me be here.
I haven't had the pleasure
of meeting most of you yet.
We've...
My wife, Mary, and I
have only been here for a month or so.
Well, I'm a man of faith.
Amen!
But when I heard about this place,
when I heard about what happened here,
I'd be lying
if I told you I understood it.
Yes, yes.
But I understand it now.
Because you've shared your home with me,
I wanna share with you
what has happened to us, to Mary,
who, I was told by countless doctors,
would never recover.
MASSEY". Thank you, Matt.
We all know what
a truly special place we've got here.
Yes!
And I know I speak
for everyone here when I say,
welcome, brother.
- Welcome!
- Welcome, sister.
Praise Jesus.
Now, let us bow our heads
for a reading from the Gospel of Luke.
- So nice to have you.
- Thank you.
- Hi.
- Thank you, sir. Thank you.
John. So nice to see your face
in there today.
Hey, I'm not too bad.
Come on, now, Calvin.
You're gonna make the new reverend here
think I never come to church.
- John Murphy.
- John, nice to meet you.
Matt Jamison, my wife, Mary.
Uh... A pleasure, Mary.
Welcome to Jarden.
Now, where you two in from?
Mapleton, New York.
It's just outside the city.
- New York City.
- Ah, figured.
Yeah.
- So what were you gonna say up there?
- I'm sorry?
Well, right before
Calvin here cut you off,
it seemed like you were
about to share something about your wife.
On.
I was just gonna say that I felt a burden
lift off of us when we came to your town.
For the first time, in a long time,
we feel safe.
Well, there's no place in the world safer.
- Y'all take care.
- Thank you.
Sorry, I asked for the bacon
on a separate plate.
You got it.
I'll bring that right back for you.
Every time.
Well, it wouldn't be every time
if they'd listen, sweetheart.
"See to it that no one repays
evil for evil to anyone."
Any particular reason you picked that one?
I didn't pick it.
Readings are predetermined.
What is a Thessalonian anyway?
Someone from Thessalonia.
From Arkansas, right?
Bacon and eggs separated.
Appreciate it.
Jerry, come on.
Jerry, please. Do you have to...
Sorry, folks.
Enrique.
Perfect Strangers star
Mark Linn-Baker
departed on October 14, 2012,
but Hard 10 tracked him down
to this sleepy village
in the Chihuahua province of Mexico.
WOMAN". We know you didn't depart, Mark.
Why'd you fake your departure?
No comprende. No comprende.
WOMAN". We know it's you, Mark.
No Mark. No Mark esta.
Mark, tell us why you did it.
Tell us why.
Damn! Damn it!
They're gone,
but so much of them is still here.
You tried to move on,
tried to live a normal life,
but cannot let go
because you haven't known how.
Hey.
My spoon got stuck
in the garbage disposal.
I'm going for a ride.
Other people feed him, you know?
He likes Mom's cooking.
Back by 10:00.
Be safe.
You mail the letter?
Uh-huh.
Good night.
Get off me!
Hey, we just missed the bus.
- Sure, you did. Head down, sir.
- You've no right to do this.
- Ma'am, calm down.
- You can't keep us out.
- Calm down, ma'am.
- Fuck you, man.
This is fucking America. Argh.
You can't keep people out, man.
You're not special.
Fuck your fucking wristbands!
Hello.
Hi.
You wanna pray?
Okay.
- What's that?
- It's a pie.
- Where'd it come from?
- It was on the porch.
Is it for your birthday?
- I don't know.
- There wasn't a note?
Just a pie.
- What kind is it?
- Apple, I think.
- Looks homemade.
- Mmm-hmm.
You think someone's trying to poison you?
Look at your face.
You know, someone just moved in
the Dunbar house.
- A family. Mmm-hmm.
- Just now?
Seem nice.
You know, I think we ought to
invite them over for dinner tonight.
You're gonna work on your birthday?
Just being neighborly.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Saw you moving in. I'm John Murphy.
We're right next door.
Here. Welcome.
Oh, thanks. That's so nice. I'm Nora.
Well, I see you got your hands full.
No problem. I got her.
Did you bake this yourself, John?
No, ma'am, I did not.
And who's this?
This is Lily.
Say hello to Mr. Murphy, Lily.
Hey, Lily.
ls everything all right in there?
Fine, we're just moving in.
You know, chaos.
Of course. Well, I'll leave you to it.
Just wanted to invite y'all over tonight.
Having a little barbecue for my birthday.
That's so...
We don't wanna crash your birthday.
No, no pressure. Just drop by if you can.
Thank you.
'BYE-bye.
- Bye, Lily.
You ask them if they eat meat?
I told them it was a barbecue.
If they don't eat meat,
that would've been the time to tell me.
Violet wants to know
when she can pick me up.
Well, you tell Violet
that you will text her
as soon as I authorize you to do so.
Hello!
Sorry, we rang the doorbell,
but nobody answered.
We're back here. Come on down.
It's Kevin. You're John, right?
Right. Right. This is Erika.
- Hi. Hi.
- Hi, Erika. How are you? Nice to meet you.
Evie, Michael, introduce yourselves.
- How you doing?
- Michael.
- I'm Jill.
- I'm Nora.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- So we are early or...
- No, right on time.
Oh, I thought this was a birthday party.
It is. We don't have any friends.
- Who is this?
- This is Lily.
Well, hello, Lily.
- She's adorable.
- Thank you.
Is she adopted,
or did your mom fuck a black dude?
Evie!
You don't need that anymore.
You guys bought the house, right?
Yeah, but they said that we should
leave them on for a couple weeks
so the park rangers
don't bother us or something.
Your daughter is good with a baby.
That's gotta be nice.
She's not mine. She's Kevin's.
Oh, well, she's pretty.
So is he.
His secret is moisturizing.
So you have family around here?
- Sorry?
- In Jarden.
I figured someone must have
tipped you off about the house.
Real estate moves
pretty quick around here.
Oh, no, we were just in the right place
at the right time.
I have a brother, Matt Jamison.
He and his wife came out here
a couple months ago.
He's helping out the Baptist church.
You know him?
I just met him yesterday. Small world.
Cake looks good.
Well, she works the grill, I bake.
Now, what happened to your head?
I fell.
Uh...
- Can I put these in the fridge?
- Absolutely.
You want one?
Nah. I don't drink.
But help yourself.
Okay.
What?
What? What?
Oh, what were you looking at?
I was just looking at your couch
in the other room.
We had one just like it.
So I step on the carpet,
and I feel this squish.
I walk around the corner,
and trickling down the steps
like a fancy fountain is water,
but in my house.
So I'm walking up these steps.
And you know when you feel
like it's a bad idea,
but you do it anyway?
I open the bathroom door,
and this wave comes out.
A little one but a wave.
And this one is standing in the bathtub
with her arms out like Moses.
And this one's up on the sink
trying his hardest not to get wet.
And he just looks at me
with this serious face
and goes, "Evie wanted to know
what would happen."
Gets funnier every time, Mama.
- How old were they?
- Five.
And they're lucky they made it to six.
That must've been fun to come home to.
Well, I was in prison.
Yeah? Well, how long were you there for?
Six years, 119 days.
They think you're kidding.
Oh, sorry, no. I really was.
Travis County Unit.
Go ahead. Go ahead and ask.
What?
What I did.
It's what everybody wants to know.
- That's none of our business.
- What'd you do?
Attempted murder.
Mmm-hmm.
What happened?
Didn't try hard enough.
Shit.
Evie. Evie. Evie.
Come back, Evie.
Evie, come back.
Evie, come on, baby.
Evie, come back, baby.
- I went away?
- Mmm-hmm.
ERMA". Um, she has epilepsy.
This doesn't happen
unless she forgets to take her meds.
Sorry. I ruined your cake.
No, no, no, no. It's...
I burned it anyway.
Come on.
The pie! They brought us a pie.
It's on the kitchen counter.
Will you run and get it?
Yep. Yeah, I'll grab it.
Do you have any more candles?
Uh...
Let me check.
Babe, do we have
any more candles back there?
Whenever you need
an extra pair of hands,
you just bring this beautiful thing over.
You'll be sorry you said that.
Thank you.
Thank you so much for having us.
Thank you for stopping by.
I'm looking forward
to getting to know you better, Kevin.
Yeah, me, too. Bye.
Bye.
Uh, see you later.
Jesus.
- Don't open it till I'm gone, okay?
- Why not?
Because it's the greatest
present you ever got,
and I don't want you to make a scene.
Happy birthday, Daddy.
- Back by 11:00.
- Yeah.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
- Bye, sweetheart.
- Bye.
Seat belt.
Let's go.
John! John, wake up!
Holy... Come on!
Let's go.
Give me your hand.
Come on, come on. Watch out.
Michael!
Over here. Stay in the doorway!
Evie!
Where is she?
Hey, it's Evie.
I'm ignoring you,
but I appreciate your persistence.
Hey, it's 3:00 in the morning.
Call us right now.
- Now, did you text her?
- She's not responding.
Just call us, Evangeline.
We need to know where you are.
Uh, hey. John Murphy.
Is Evie there with Taylor?
Taylor didn't come home either.
Hello?
No, Mr. Trousdale. Violet's not here.
Yes, sir. Thanks.
- You sure?
- They swim out there sometimes.
- I don't know if they go out at night.
- You come with me.
You stay here in case she comes back.
She's never done this before.
She'll come home.
Let's go.
Hey, it's Evie.
I'm ignoring you,
but I appreciate your persistence.
Dad!
The water's gone.
Evie.
Evie!
English - SDH