Thank you so much for having us.
Well, thank you for stopping by.
I'm looking forward to getting
to know you better, Kevin.
Yeah, me, too.
Bye.
Hey.
Are you the new neighbors?
Uh-huh.
Welcome to Miracle.
Thanks.
Don't open it till I'm gone, okay?
Why not?
Because it's the greatest
present you ever got
and I don't want you to make a scene.
Happy birthday, Daddy.
- Back by 11:00.
- Yeah.
Bye, sweetheart.
Bye.
Seat belt.
_
Holy shit.
How long?
Were you dead?
Eight hours.
Is she still with you?
Patti?
No. She's gone.
Then it worked.
Did you bury me?
My grandfather told me to.
He's gone, too.
I'm sorry.
Where you went...
did he help you?
Yeah. He helped me a lot.
What was it like?
It was like a--
a hotel.
A hotel?
Yeah.
Did you see my sister there?
No.
I saw her somewhere else.
I've got to talk to your father.
How long you been up?
A while.
No coffee in the coffeepot.
What are you drinking?
You going to church?
Now why would I do that?
It's October 14th.
We go to remember.
I don't want to remember.
John, open it.
Open it or I will.
It's my birthday present and
I'll open it when I'm ready.
Wait!
What-- what is it?
She found it.
No, she didn't.
What?
The night she disappeared, I was here
when you and Michael
went to find her.
Chirped the whole time.
She must have caught another
one and put it in the box.
And why would she do that?
Because you wouldn't let it go.
Fuck you, Erika.
John.
What happened?
The print on the car
that Evie disappeared from...
Yeah?
You know how we told you
you'd waste your time
trying to match it
with folks in town?
You weren't.
Hi.
Uh, hey.
Who are you?
I'm Laurie.
Garvey. Who are you?
I'm John. I live next door.
Is Kevin home?
Uh, no, he's--
- What's going on?
- Oh, hey, Jill.
- I'm looking for your dad.
- Why? What's happening?
I just need to talk to him.
You know where he is?
No, but I'm sure he'll be back.
Are you?
What?
Sure he'll come back.
Oh, he's definitely coming back.
Print matched?
Indeed it did.
You want to talk,
we should go inside.
No, we probably should
talk somewhere neutral.
- Okay.
- Yeah, we'll give you a ride.
Everything's okay.
Stay here.
Everything's fine.
What are you doing with him?
Just listen to what he has to say.
I'll be all right. Stay here.
Where have you been?
Your dad's.
I thought I told you not
to go over there anymore.
I won't.
You going to church?
Go inside and get changed.
Jill.
You're gonna have
to talk to me eventually.
What did you just say?
I said you're gonna
have to talk to me.
- I have to talk to you?
- I know.
I know I deserve that and
I know that you're angry.
No!
You don't know shit.
I know that your father's not
doing very well right now.
He's got--
he's got some serious problems, Jill,
and I'm sure you know that, too.
I came back here looking
for your brother, okay?
And your father asked me to stay.
He asked for my help.
I'm not asking for anything.
Jill, this is your house
and if you want me to, I will leave.
I will leave right now.
He said that we should stay.
Oh, sorry.
Okay.
All right. Okay, sit tight.
I'm gonna find that feeding tube
and we'll get out of here, okay?
Bingo! Right where Matt said it was.
I'm just gonna change her
real quick, okay?
Okay. Okay.
How about some music?
You want some music?
Let's try this. Okay.
I know. I don't like that, either.
- Oh, that's better.
- She's staying at her sister's.
- That's better.
- She's not coming back.
October, it's always,
you know, hard for her.
I can't believe it's been four years.
Did you lose someone?
Our little girl, Emily.
How old was she?
14 months.
She was talking real sentences.
Before any of our friends' kids.
I bragged about it.
Well, that's what proud fathers do.
Can I ask what happened?
Why your wife left?
I want to have another baby.
And your wife?
She says it would hurt too much.
Now, I told her we could start over.
It's a new life.
It'll help us, you know, forget.
You know what, Andy?
I'm gonna have to side
with your wife on this one.
She's not ready.
That thing inside all of us,
that mechanism
that allows us to love,
your wife's, it's broken.
And a new baby's
not going to fix that.
But you know what can?
Jesus.
After all, he was
the original Departure, right?
Fix that, Jesus.
Yeah, it's okay.
Shh, shh, shh.
Nora.
What are you doing here?
Where's Matt?
Oh, my God.
Hi.
Matt.
Is this real?
This is real?
It's real.
Oh, God!
Oh, thank God.
Oh!
Are you all right?
I'm a little confused, but okay.
You have to take her back right now.
- What?
- Mary, listen.
You can't be out here. It's not--
you have to go back
to town right now.
Okay, let's go, then.
No, I can't.
You have to take her back right now.
It's not safe out here. The baby.
The what?
- You didn't tell her?
- I thought you would want to.
I'm pregnant?
Now, Mary, do you remember
the night you woke up, we, um--
- Had sex?
- Yes.
Of course I remember.
Well, you waking up, that happened.
This baby happened
because you were across
that bridge in that town.
Now, I'll get there soon enough,
but you've got to go now.
Tell you what-- I'm gonna feed Lily
and I'll come back in 10 minutes.
- Hey, Nora--
- 10 minutes, Matt.
And then I'll take her
back in, I promise.
- Okay, thank you.
- You're very welcome.
Hey, where'd you steal her from?
That's not your baby.
That's not her baby.
_
You know her?
She's your dad's girlfriend, right?
She sprayed me with a hose once.
I liked her.
Are you scared for them?
For your family?
There is no family.
Where'd you hear that?
I thought that's the point.
No, Tom.
That's not the point at all.
Family is everything.
Here we go.
Sorry, ma'am. Park's closed today.
Really? Why?
It's October 14th.
It's the anniversary
of the Departure.
It's a time for the townfolks
to be with themselves, reflect.
Reflect on what?
I'm sorry?
Well, nothing happened
here to the townsfolk.
It's kind of like a temple
closing down on Christmas.
Not really your holiday,
don't you think?
I'm sorry, ma'am, but
unless you have a wristband
or a dispensation form, I'm gonna
have to ask you to turn around.
I have 35 pounds
of plastic explosive.
Will that work?
What?
Whoa!
Stop! Someone-- Hey!
We have a runner on the bridge.
- We have a runner on the bridge.
- Go, let's go!
Let's go!
Stop!
Get down on the ground now!
I said get down!
Get on the ground now!
Get in there, cuff her.
We got an unauthorized
vehicle on the bridge.
Possible code blue.
I repeat, possible code blue.
Which one is yours?
What?
Well, they took your dog
when you got here, right?
Which one is he?
I know we're not here
to talk about my dog, John.
No, that's exactly
why we're here, Kevin.
You tell me where my daughter is
and I'll let you take your dog home.
I don't know where your daughter is,
but I know she didn't depart.
No? Well, what did she do?
She staged it.
She and her friends,
to make it look like--
And you know this how?
I saw her do it.
You saw her do it
and you waited all
this time to tell me?
I didn't remember until this morning.
What sparked it, this memory?
What do you want me
to tell you, John?
I want you to tell me the truth.
What made you remember?
I died.
I had a-- a problem.
Michael took me to his grandfather's.
He said he could help.
He gave me, like, a--
My son took you
to meet his grandfather?
Yeah, Virgil. He helped me.
No, Michael wouldn't do that.
Listen, man, he did.
I swear, man, he did.
Prove it.
The old man told me
what he did to you.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry. No one should ever--
Man, shut the fuck up. That's a lie.
He didn't do nothing to me.
You don't know shit.
All right, now--
look, let's stay focused, man,
because, see, I want
to make sure I get this.
Yeah.
You saw my daughter
pretend to disappear
and the only reason
you remember that today
is because you came
back from the dead?
I know you don't think
it can happen here, John,
but it did.
You're right, Kevin.
That can't happen here.
But I need you to explain me this.
Evie loved her mother.
She loved her brother.
And she loved me.
So why in God's name
would she do this to us?
I don't know.
Okay, well, take a fucking guess.
Maybe she didn't.
What?
Love you.
Who knows what goes
through people's heads?
You know, your daughter--
Hey!
- What's going on?
- John, it's Evie. Follow us.
What?
- Evie!
- John, you gotta get back.
No, you have got to let me through.
We can't. There's a
bomb in the trailer.
- What?
- Buddy, you gotta go back.
John, you gotta get back. The
trailer is rigged with explosives.
Why-- why would anybody do-- Evie!
What happened?
Can I borrow those?
It's the three girls.
What three girls?
The ones who departed.
_
No, no, no, no.
We won't be able to get back in.
They're gonna blow up the bridge!
There's a bomb!
Blow it up! Blow it up!
Blow it up! Blow it up! Blow it up!
♪ Our hearts were
pure, we knew for sure ♪
♪ A miracle ♪
♪ That God had spared our town ♪
October 14th.
Four years ago.
Everywhere else in the world,
they knew something had happened.
Yeah.
But we didn't.
No.
Not until the phones started ringing.
Till we turned on our televisions.
And we ran out onto the streets.
Found each other.
Yes, we did.
And everyone asked
the same question--
is everyone okay?
Is everyone still here?
Yes.
- And we were.
- Amen.
We were still here.
Amen.
We were--
Michael has asked to say a few words.
My mom tells a story.
A lot of you have probably heard it.
She says that there was water
trickling down
the stairs in our house.
And when she followed it up, she saw
that it was coming from the bathroom.
She opened the door and she swears
a wave just washed past her.
And there were me and Evie,
five years old
and an overflowing tub.
My mom says she asked
Evie why she did it.
And my sister said, "I just
wanted to see what would happen."
That's the story that you always tell
and everyone laughs,
even me and Evie.
She laughed to protect you, Mom,
because it's not the truth.
I'm the one who turned the water on.
I turned it on all the way
because Evie was crying so loud
and she didn't want you to hear.
She was crying because we didn't
know why our father was gone.
Or why he did what he did.
But she was crying so loud.
So I turned the water on
and I drowned her out.
Until she could pretend she was okay.
Nobody disappeared from here on
October 14th four years ago.
But they did before.
And after.
We are the 9,261.
We are not spared.
That's not your baby.
- She doesn't belong to you.
- Shut the fuck up!
It's okay.
That clock, what is that?
What's inside here?
Y'all just gonna blow yourselves up?
Whoo!
Y'all need to move back now.
Everybody move back.
- Back up. Ma'am, back up, please.
- Dad.
Sir, I want you to step back.
- Back up.
- Step back.
- Erika!
Everybody, back up.
Get off the bridge!
Erika!
Are you just gonna blow yourself up?
'Cause if that's what it is,
I'm not leaving
this bridge, Evangeline.
I'm not.
You're just gonna
have to blow me up, too.
Get out of my way!
It's empty!
It's empty! It's empty!
Oh, Lord!
Nothing. It's zero.
Okay, rangers, hold that gate.
Get away from the fence.
Everybody, back off.
Hold the fence. Hold the--
- Back off!
- Everyone, back off!
- Pull back!
- Right there.
There's too many of them.
Let them go.
Let them go!
Why are you doing this?
I don't understand.
_
We need to go now.
Okay, my car's over there.
We can pack--
- No, we're going in.
- Matt.
Mary, I need you to trust me.
We need to get you
and the baby back in.
Now is our chance. Do you trust me?
- Yes.
- Okay, let's go.
Matt, wait.
Wait!
She's not yours.
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
- Hurry up, hurry up.
- Hurry up.
Nora.
It's okay. You're safe.
Okay. Hey.
It's okay. You're okay.
Yeah, I know. I know.
I know. I know. I know.
Motherfucker.
Motherfucker!
Dad?
Can you hear me?
I'm not fucking doing this again.
Where are you?
Fuck!
- Hello?
- Mr. Garvey?
Yeah?
We're aware this isn't
your jurisdiction.
You're a police officer, right?
Uh, that's right.
Something terrible
is happening in the lobby bar.
Another officer, he's being attacked.
I think they're gonna kill him.
I'll be right there.
Yeah.
- - Thank you, thank you.
- Thank you very much.
You're all lovely people.
Who's next? Who wants to sing a song?
Who wants to spin the wheel?
An officer of the law.
Will you regale us
with a tune, Officer?
- No.
- I will. I want to.
All right, darling. Come on up.
The stage is yours.
♪ Just call me angel ♪
♪ Of the morning, angel ♪
♪ Just touch my cheek... ♪
What is this?
Sorry, do I know you, mate?
Of course you fucking know me.
We met on the bridge. You
tied a noose around my neck.
Oh, sure. I remember.
The uniform threw me off.
- Did you call me?
- Call you?
I got a call. There was a cop
getting attacked down here.
Huh. Only cop I see around
here is you, Officer.
Suppose this crowd could turn on
anyone if they can't sing for shit.
Just tell me what I
need to do to get back.
Why do you want to go back?
Because I have a family.
Because I love them and I--
Yes, you love your family.
It's not your time.
Still got so much to live for.
Oh, come on, be original, mate.
Why should you go back
and the rest of us--
Because I deserve to.
You deserve to?
Yes. Now tell me how.
I already did.
Excuse me?
If you want to get out of here,
all you have to do is sing.
I don't believe you.
Why not?
Because it's stupid.
Ah, the trial, it's beneath you.
It's not elegant enough. Too easy.
You pushed a little girl into a well.
You don't want to sing?
♪ Darling ♪
Who's next? Anybody?
You're right. Don't do it.
It's stupid.
How about you, Officer?
You want a turn?
Give it a whirl.
Oh, that's a great one.
Okay, the words are gonna
come up right there.
Will you start it?
♪ I'm sitting
in the railway station ♪
♪ Got a ticket to my destination ♪
♪ On a tour of one-night stands ♪
♪ My suitcase and guitar in hand ♪
♪ And every stop
is neatly planned ♪
♪ For a poet and a one-man band ♪
♪ Homeward bound ♪
♪ I wish I was homeward bound ♪
♪ Home,
where my thought's escaping ♪
♪ Home, where my music's playing ♪
♪ Home, where my love lies
waiting silently for me ♪
♪ Every day is an endless stream ♪
♪ Of cigarettes and magazines ♪
♪ Mm-hmm, mm-mm ♪
♪ And each town
looks the same to me ♪
♪ The movies and the factories ♪
♪ And every stranger's face I see ♪
♪ Reminds me that I long to be ♪
♪ Homeward bound ♪
♪ I wish I was ♪
♪ Home,
where my thought's escaping ♪
♪ Home, where my music's playing ♪
♪ Home, where my love lies
waiting silently for me ♪
♪ Tonight I'll sing
my songs again ♪
♪ I'll play the game and pretend ♪
♪ Mm-hmm ♪
♪ But all my words
come back to me ♪
♪ In shades of mediocrity ♪
♪ Like emptiness in harmony ♪
♪ I need someone to comfort me ♪
♪ Homeward bound ♪
♪ I wish I was... ♪
♪ Home,
where my thought's escaping ♪
♪ Home, where my music's playing ♪
♪ Home, where my love lies
waiting silently for me ♪
♪ Silently for me ♪
Oh, f--
Come here.
Come on.
Come. It's okay.
Come.
Thanks for waiting.
Come here.
Welcome to Miracle National Park.
Welcome-- welcome
to Miracle National Park.
Welcome-- National Park.
We're excited to--
Welcome to Miracle National Park.
We're excited to have you.
Within the boundaries of the park...
sits the town of Jarden,
a town with a unique history.
What are you doing here?
I live here now.
♪ Broken hearts
and shattered dreams ♪
♪ Like wreckage on the ground ♪
♪ The memory of those poor souls ♪
♪ Who were lost but never found ♪
♪ They shook their fists ♪
♪ And cursed the sky ♪
♪ Demanding explanations ♪
♪ No answers came,
no soothing words ♪
♪ Just silence and frustration ♪
♪ But in Jarden town
the sun shone bright ♪
♪ A miracle ♪
♪ The light of love poured down ♪
♪ It's a miracle ♪
♪ Our hearts were pure,
we knew for sure ♪
♪ A miracle ♪
♪ That God had spared our town ♪
Erika!
You in here?
Hey, John.
I killed you.
Nope.
Let me see.
Went right through me.
Hell, you--
you should have bled out.
Uh-huh.
It hurts.
Let me-- let me clean it.
Okay.
I don't understand what's happening.
Me neither.
It's okay.
Okay. Okay.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
What if there's nobody home?
Then you come over to my house.
You're home!