Previously on Prison Break:
Mr. Kim. Sara Tancredi. I'm on it.
- Pursuing her the best use of your time?
- It is.
- I'll let the president know.
- I contact the president.
I'll contact her.
No family with Patoshik?
- Nothing?
- Yeah.
Until about four years ago
when he killed them.
MAHONE. Fernando Sucre.
He was in Las Vegas around 2.
Out west.
Just like Bagwell and Franklin.
You know D.B. Cooper? The money's
in Utah and they're all going to get it.
You're one of them Fox River boys.
- Come on, you got the map?
- No. Someone else does.
Before I destroyed it, I committed it
to my photographic memory.
I have the information, you have
the manual requirements necessary...
...to unearth
Westmoreland's buried booty.
- Get in.
- Okay.
Should be dead ahead.
The bastards built over it.
It's gone.
We have to open up in 15 minutes.
- So? That doesn't matter. I dare you.
- I said no.
I dare you, please.
The ranch is gone, Michael.
Well, the five million might not be.
And you're gonna find it how?
What, you got a divining rod
tattooed on your ass?
I don't wanna hear anything
from you...
...other than what your photographic
memory spits out regarding that map!
You watch your tone with me, boy.
I will watch you get tossed to the side
of the road to fend for yourself, boy.
Because if you can't remember
where that silo was...
...you're worthless to us.
- Yo, fools, let me out.
- Shut up.
- The map!
- Okay, okay. All right, all right, all right.
Let me out, boss.
The ranch was in the center of a box.
Sheep Road on one side,
Kokosing Road perpendicular.
In the center of the property
was the ranch house...
...and the ranch house
was surrounded by trees.
Let me out.
Every tree here is a year old at most...
...except those.
Where's the silo?
Inside the trees,
I wanna say on the left...
...but that may have been a barn.
I remembered the best I could, gents,
but I didn't know this place...
...would now be smothered
in tract homes.
So, you know, I'm sorry
that I'm not Rain Man over here.
- Alex Mahone. How are you?
- Lyle Sands.
We've been briefed
on all the men at large.
The full force and resources
of the entire Salt Lake City Field Office...
...are at your disposal.
Thank you. Do you have the files
my office requested on D.B. Cooper?
We're pulling them now. And this is
the D.B. Cooper case from 30 years ago?
Correct. If I can get those files
immediately, I'd appreciate it.
Sorry, but I have to ask.
Aren't you here for the Fox River 8?
I am. And they're here in Utah
to get D.B. Cooper's money.
So how about those files, Lyle?
- Silo. Silo, silo.
- This is stupid.
- We're gonna get made out here.
- All right, shut it. I think I remember.
If I had to bet, I'd lay it all on the silo
being on the left of the ranch house...
...inside the trees.
No. It's outside the trees.
Right there.
You see those two trees?
They're shorter than the rest.
They were all planted
at the same time...
...but those two
didn't get as much sunlight.
Something was in their way.
The silo.
Our money should be right there,
under that garage.
You better be right, boy.
This isn't a high-end subdivision.
They slapped this place up overnight.
The silo's foundations
might still be there.
To save money, they probably
just laid the concrete...
...for the garage floor
right on top of it.
We'll dig straight down. If we hit
the foundation, we stay. If not, we go.
Let's do it.
Oh, man.
Ain't no problem that a screwdriver
to her temple won't fix.
People die all the time, boys.
Five million dollars
comes once in a lifetime.
Let me out of here.
Come on, guys.
Well, we gotta do something.
And it's not gonna involve
hurting anyone.
I got an idea.
First,
we're gonna need some supplies.
A hundred and 10 percent,
I do not agree with this.
Everybody's gotta
pitch in to make this happen.
But back in the big house,
the boy proved he couldn't be trusted.
Which is why we're doing it here.
If he gets caught in town,
he ain't got a clue where the house is.
Besides, you're the one
we can't turn our backs on.
I could have died in there, man.
Well, guess what.
I need you to do something.
I need you to do something for me.
I want my cut of the money.
Well, we'll talk
once you prove we can trust you.
What do I gotta do?
I want you to go back to that garden
center and get everything on this list.
And gas up the car.
And we'll meet you right back here
in an hour.
- All right.
- And, David...
...don't screw this up.
This ain't Fox River no more, man.
You're looking at the real deal now.
But I want my cut.
Be back in an hour.
Let's go.
Mistake.
Big mistake.
Oh, come on, now.
Am I glad to see you.
You walk here?
No, it's just a long story, man.
I thought you were meeting up
with your family.
I met a few roadblocks. And you?
Yeah.
Well, let me guess.
You're going to Tooele.
Yeah.
Well, looks like we're going
the same direction.
Hopefully, we're not too late.
Can I hitch a ride?
Hey, look...
...I'll make it worth your while.
We've got some good news, sir.
We got our first tip on Patoshik.
Spotted at a burger joint
in Cedar Grove, Wisconsin.
Hand it over to local
authorities for now.
The only thing we're working today
is Utah and D.B. Cooper.
Got it.
Lyle.
There's a guy listed as having
the only D.B. Cooper bill ever found.
- Harold Jenkins.
- Yeah.
D.B. bought gas from Jenkins...
...with a hundred
on the day of the hijacking.
We checked the serial numbers
and they matched.
You worked the case?
Fresh out of the academy
and nobody's cracked it yet.
What makes you think that these
escapees know where the money is?
Because they may have been locked up
with the real D.B. Cooper.
Jenkins from the gas station,
he still alive?
Should be.
He was only 18 at the time.
Well, let's go say hi to him.
We're sorry, that
call cannot be completed as dialed.
Please check the number
and dial again.
Do you have
updates on Sara Tancredi?
I assume that's why you're here.
Yes.
Scofield sent her a message
through the mail.
A phone number
that was disconnected.
You know, to be honest...
...I was expecting
to brief the president.
Yeah, about that.
Right now, as you can imagine,
Carolyn's quite busy.
She's always been busy.
I've been working with her for 15 years.
Paul...
...she's the president
of the Unites States now.
Yes, Bill,
and I helped to put her there.
Well, if you'd like for her
to remain in office...
...you'll take my advice and just stay
on the sidelines for now.
She needs to be completely insulated
from anything regarding Lincoln Burrows.
I wanna talk to her.
You report to me now, and only me.
Don't try and contact Carolyn again
without my approval...
...and don't show up here
unannounced.
Finish the job you were given.
Get Burrows.
If you're telling me the road to him leads
through Sara Tancredi, by all means...
...pursue it.
And once that's been accomplished
and this whole thing goes away...
...we'll go about transitioning you back
into Carolyn's life.
Now,
do you have anything else on Sara?
The president
has unwavering faith in you.
She wants you to go through
Senate approval...
...with your eyes wide open.
- So what are we up against?
- Key allies in the House and Senate...
...are Meyerhoff,
Barnwell and Sommerville.
- Counting on them to sway the middle.
- Who's the opposition?
Senators Blake and Killoren
have openly vocalized...
...their opposition to you as VP.
Any indication as to why?
Political payback for the president's vote
on the energy bill last month.
Took them by surprise
and they don't like surprises.
- Dad. Lance, this is my father, Frank.
- Pleasure to meet you, sir.
It's nothing to lose sleep over.
Frankly, the biggest issue
we have to address...
...are the charges
facing your daughter.
Governor, are you with me?
Absolutely.
Yo, just chill, dog. Listen...
...once we roll, we bounce out of town,
we'll drop a dime and they'll find you.
Just be quiet. Just chill, man.
Woody?
Where you at? Woody?
I need Sheriff Williams.
Yeah, I'll hold.
Woody?
Where'd you learn about electricity?
I used to steal copper wiring
from transformer boxes.
Then I'd sell them on the docks,
make a few bucks.
You were in school, of course.
I was just looking, pretty.
What's that old chestnut?
I can look at the menu,
doesn't mean I'm gonna eat.
We get in, we get the money,
we get out.
- That's it.
- No, absolutely.
We're good.
Now, it's just up to the kid.
- Did you get everything?
- Yeah. Yeah, I got it.
- What?
- Nothing. It's cool. I handled it.
- Whoa. Okay.
Check it. This fool came in the shop.
He was acting all shady,
he got a bad vibe...
...so he picked up his cellie phone, he
started to make a call, so I popped him.
- What?!
- I hit him with the shovel, man.
I didn't know what else to do.
I tied him up and I put him in the back
room with that other country hick.
- Here we go. Here we go.
- I came through, you gimp.
- Who was he calling?
- The sheriff.
Man, I don't know, dude.
It just set off so quick.
- Did the call go through?
- Maybe, man. I don't know.
Maybe? Did the call go through?
Yes, I-- No, I don't know.
I don't know, man.
Yo, but I got the gear.
We gotta move on this now.
Yes?
Sorry to bother you, ma'am.
Is your electricity out?
Excuse me.
I'm looking for a Harold Jenkins.
Right here.
Alexander Mahone, FBI.
I'm staying 50 feet
away from her at all times.
What the hell else does she want?
I'm not here about that.
- What are you here for?
- D.B. Cooper.
People still wanna
know about that guy?
Unbelievable.
You worked the gas station
in American Fork where he filled up.
Yeah. Normal-looking guy.
Barely said a word.
There were some discrepancies
in the statement you filed 30 years ago.
In the report, it's noted that you said
he filled up at 7 a. m...
...but on another occasion,
you said it was 7 p.m.
- Which was it?
- Both.
He gassed up twice?
Yeah.
Full tanks both times?
Yeah. Why?
A systems what?
It's a systems diagnostics test.
Footage from our gopher cam
picked up exactly...
...where your line was corrupted.
And who corrupted it?
- You guys?
- Maybe.
All I know is my supervisor called
and said he wants me and my crew...
...to get over here and fix that problem
double quick, double time.
So...
- ...you're not with the electric company?
- No, ma'am.
Now, feel free to call your company.
But I tell you,
all they'll do is send over some tech.
Maybe tomorrow, if you're lucky.
And he'll spend a whole day
trying to find the problem...
...and another day trying to fix it.
But we're here right now.
And we're ready
to turn your juice back on.
My juice?
That's right.
And...
...that's your crew?
Yes, ma'am.
Yeah, D.B. Cooper
was driving a 1965 Chevy Nova.
There's no record on file
that Cooper even had a car.
But Charles Westmoreland did
and the car registered to him...
...at the time was a 1965 Chevy Nova
with a 16-gallon gas tank.
Back then, a Chevy that size got
approximately eight miles to the gallon.
D.B. stopped at the station
in American Fork...
...and gassed up once early that day...
...and then came back later that same
night and gassed up again.
Why would a guy headed to Mexico...
...which is a straight shot south...
...drive off the main road
for an all-day detour?
- The money.
- Exactly.
Cooper, Westmoreland,
jumped out of a plane with $5 million.
But Westmoreland didn't have the money
on him when he was arrested.
He ditched it before he got caught.
Give me that magic marker.
From American Fork,
he couldn't have gone further...
...than 64 miles in any direction.
I want everything you've got
in that perimeter.
Those cons
are in one of these towns...
...and if there's so much as a cat
missing in one of them, I wanna know.
The defective cable runs
right beneath your garage.
We're gonna have to dig up the floor
to get to it.
Well, who's gonna pay for this...
...and what about the cleanup
and the repair?
Well, the company will cover all costs.
We'll just dig a small trench.
Once we're finished, we'll re-lay
the cement. It'll look as good as new.
How long is it gonna take?
One way or another,
we'll be out of here today.
Really need to get started, ma'am.
Wouldn't want a pretty little thing
like yourself sitting...
...in the dark tonight, now, would we?
Well, that depends
on who I'm sitting with.
Touché.
Fine. It's okay, y'all go ahead
and do whatever y'all need to do.
Jeanette,
the noise might be substantial.
You might wanna take
in that tennis game after all.
Oh, no, it's too hot for that now.
Plus, I gotta keep an eye on you all
and make sure you don't steal anything.
Ma'am.
- How are you?
- Good.
All right, where's Tweener?
He's next door
plugging in the extension cord.
- We're gonna have to cut up the cement.
- Yo, we gots company.
What's up, snowflake?
Well, as always,
your timing is flawless.
- I don't follow.
- Well, let me try to explain it to you.
We're trying to run something here...
...and we can't have people
walking in off the street.
Oh, okay, so you want us to leave
and then you can just mail us the check?
Sucre, I know you trust me...
...and you know I'll cut you in
on that money.
But the two of you being here right now
jeopardizes everything.
I'm not going nowhere.
I want my share of the money.
Wait a minute, hold on, man.
Ain't we did this dance before?
You know,
I say I want in, you say no...
...then I threaten to tell somebody
about what's going on here.
And then you decide to play nice
and then we're one big happy family.
Why don't we just stop wasting time,
all right?
Thank you.
Damn, man, you still alive?
And kicking, homeboy.
How'd you find us?
Man, if I can do rapid deployment
of satellite communications...
...for Uncle Sam all over the world--
How are you guys doing?
Who are you? Who are they?
I had to call my supervisor.
He sent them right over.
This job is a top priority.
They want to get this done as quickly
and as efficiently as possible.
Well, Jeanette, like I said,
there's a lot of work to do...
...and it's gonna be noisy.
Oh, drinks. I forgot to ask.
We're good. Thanks.
Yo, man, this is not good.
We got her up in our grill
checking in on us all the time.
The boy is right.
And since I can't dig,
I'll volunteer to keep her occupied.
You don't touch her.
Who are you, Sister Mary Francis?
I know how to play nice.
I'll be watching.
Billy? Is that you?
Billy, is that you?
Yeah.
Thank you kindly.
Well, now,
how did you get out of working?
Union rules.
One crew member
always has to supervise.
- Oh.
- I'll check on them in a bit.
Lemonade?
Hm.
Little more ice?
Yeah.
And I like mine with a little oomph.
But since you're on the clock...
...I guess you can't join me?
Just two fingers.
All right.
It's been a while.
Yeah?
Whiskey
always makes me feel irascible.
I don't know what that means.
But I do like the sound of it.
Are you wearing Angel perfume?
I am.
Ah. Hm.
That reminds you of an ex, I take it.
Yeah.
Now, is that good memories...
...or bad memories?
Both.
Did you talk to Maricruz?
I don't wanna talk about her.
I gotta get some water or something.
Use the hose on the other side
of the house.
Sucre...
...down the road, if you're in trouble,
Europeangoldfinch.net.
It's what we can all use
to communicate.
Post a note on the message board.
- What's it called?
- Europeangoldfinch.net.
That's a bird, right?
I got something.
- It's the silo's foundation.
- Hells, yeah.
Thank you, Charles.
We just need to find the edge
and dig underneath it.
We'll get the money,
hit the back roads.
Uh, well...
What's wrong?
We got to stop in Tooele first
and gas up our ride.
I thought you already did that.
Man, when the garden center thing
happened, I just forgot, all right?
I want you to go back into town.
I want you to gas up that car...
...because I'm not driving around
with millions of dollars in the trunk.
- Do you understand?
- Man, why do I got to do it?
Okay.
I better check in on our friend.
You got it all the time.
Miss Tinsel toes.
Billy?
Yeah?
I made you a sandwich.
Peanut butter and jelly
with the crusts cut off.
Just like you like.
I'm so glad you came back.
I don't wanna say I told you so,
but that was just not the girl for you.
Where is that?
Where's what, sweetheart?
That painting.
It's Holland, where
I grew up. You know that.
- It's beautiful.
- Oh, there's no place better.
It's so peaceful...
...so protected from this crazy world.
Operator.
Hello, operator.
There's an intruder in my house.
Hello, ma'am? Ma'am, are you there?
Is anyone there?
Heard you had
some activity in Tooele today.
A bit. Don't see how it warrants
a visit from the FBI.
A stolen car
was dumped outside of town...
...belonging to a woman
from St. Louis.
- Am I getting that right?
- Yes, sir.
And then here, the owner's
girlfriend reports him missing...
...and then his buddy comes by
to check it out and he goes missing too.
Woody and Chet have been known
to drop everything...
...and go boar hunting
when the opportunity arises.
And they don't tell their old ladies.
I'll bet you my lunch money...
...there's nothing
amiss around here.
His dad will be showing up soon with
the keys and you can look for yourself.
Whoa, what are you doing?
Mr. Mahone.
They're here. Those escaped
convicts. They're here in town.
Who's there?
It's the police, ma'am. You okay?
Yes.
- Can you tell me what happened?
- There was this strange man.
I made him a peanut butter
and jelly sandwich.
I thought he was Billy.
And once the kids went to sleep,
we'd take a bath.
A long bath.
And afterwards, I'd just sit there
and watch her do her routine.
She'd rub her lotion on,
comb her hair...
...dress up in her nighttime fineries.
Oh, you're killing me.
She had this spot on her neck
right here.
Gave her goose bumps every time.
And that perfume...
My ex, he was an accountant.
He was really buttoned up.
It was wham, bam, thank you, Sam.
Well, shame on him.
Why did it end with that lady
you were talking about?
Just went our separate ways.
Do you know what I think
the best cure is for a broken heart?
Do tell.
Get back on the bike.
Whatever bike it is.
Amen to that.
Speaking of...
...could you do something for me?
I'm certain of it.
Come here.
Only, you have to be very discreet.
They don't come any discreeter.
You know that big guy?
The strong guy
that doesn't speak much?
Would you go in there...
...and ask him if he would like
to have a drink with me...
...after he punches out?
Please.
You've just been playing me
this whole time, haven't you?
Come on.
Don't be like that.
Would you just go in
and ask your friend?
Please.
- Hey, Dad.
- Sara, I've been trying to reach you.
Uh, yeah, I've been meeting
with my defense attorneys all day.
- You in Washington?
- Yeah, I'm coming back...
...on the next flight.
- I thought you're gonna be there awhile.
- No, plan's changed.
Sara, you remember that guy that I met
with you in your apartment?
I want you to stay away from him.
Who, Lance from my group?
Yeah, yeah, that's him.
He is not who he says he is.
I found out some other things too.
- What are you talking about?
- You were right.
- Sara?
- I gotta go.
Yeah, that's right.
Yeah.
- Yo.
- Just one second, sir.
Thank you.
- Can I help you?
- Just put 40 on three.
I'm sorry, what pump was that?
- Three.
- That one's been sticking.
- Okay. Then, I'll move the car.
- No. No, don't trouble yourself.
I'll have the mechanic come out
and pump it for you.
I've got a customer waiting on three.
- All right, I'll be right there.
- I'm in a hurry, all right?
Oh, he'll be right out.
Just one second.
Put your hands behind your head
and drop to your knees.
- Oh, God.
- Drop!
Where are they?
What? What?
Hey, man, one hand or not, I think
hillbilly needs to be up in here digging.
What you think?
Good man.
What the hell are you doing up here?
I'm sorry, Jeanette.
I just didn't see you downstairs.
I heard something.
- I apologize for barging in.
- Don't bother.
She's got the hots
for the big strong one.
I'm sorry, Jeanette.
We're gonna get back to work now.
I think y'all are done.
And I think y'all need to leave now.
We're almost finished.
No, I think you are finished, okay?
And I want you to leave my house now.
Sucre, check it out.
Cop.
Oh, thank God.
- Where you going?
- Oh!
- T-Bag, let her go!
- Oh, God.
She's our only way out of this, pretty.
Don't say a word, you old whore,
or I'm gonna cut your throat out.