Gather around, little friends!
Gather around and feast your eyes
on the amazing Pennywise,
the Dancing Clown!
Lively crowd.
- I'll wager it's even bigger tonight.
- Oh, you'll wager now, would you?
No more hanging about
with the card sharps.
I wish you could hear the way
they talk about you, Papa.
Papa, you make them so happy.
Yes, that's something.
That's good. That's good.
Now, what are you doing
back there, pumpkin?
I've been working on my face.
I wanted to surprise you.
My beautiful girl! Look at you!
Show me the bow.
Ladies and gentlemen!
For your amusement,
the Santini Brothers' Carnival
proudly presents
the first father
and daughter act in its history,
the Pennywise and Periwinkle Show.
Periwinkle?
That was Mom's stage name.
Yeah. Well, you can change it if you like.
No. I love it.
- Good.
- Papa, do you ever miss the circus?
Sometimes.
I miss the big crowds. Sure.
The roars.
One day...
the big tent
will come a-callin' again. You'll see.
But, this time, my act will be different.
Something new.
Something no one's ever seen before.
You. Now, wouldn't that be something?
Gather around, friends. Gather around.
Pennywise the Dancing Clown Show
will be on again
in about half an hour,
you don't want to miss it.
Go grab your mothers and your brothers.
Go grab your granny
and join the grand skit.
Damn it! It's all coming off.
All coming off.
Shit. Shit. Shit.
Hello?
Who's there?
Hello there, little fella.
What are you looking at? Show's thataway.
Scram.
The children seem drawn to you.
That's a strange thing
for a young man to say.
I can't find my parents.
Me neither.
They're dead.
Will you help me find them?
No.
Can't you see I'm busy?
What was that?
That's my mother.
Have you seen my father?
- He's just gone?
- Let's just take it easy.
We don't know exactly what happened.
- Are you sure it's his?
- Jesus. Right there.
- Who could have done this?
- I don't know anything
- until we find some trace of him.
- No body?
- Oh my word.
- I got folks combing the woods,
but it’s more than likely
something dragged him off.
- Oh God.
- I have no idea.
Boss, boss.
Found it in the woods.
Wolves, maybe.
They roam these parts.
Papa! Papa!
Hey, Reg. We got trouble.
Good evening.
Excuse the interruption, folks.
Now...
I'm gonna make this real simple.
Give us what we want, and we go away.
Norma? Norma Price?
You should be ashamed.
Go home. Now!
Go on.
What do you want?
Hank Grogan.
We know he's hiding here somewhere.
You hand him over,
and you can get back to your party.
No, no, no.
Seem you fellas got some bad information.
See, this here, it's just a rec facility
for military personnel only.
Well, then you won't mind
if we have a quick look around?
- Say we do.
- We're not asking.
- Look, I'm here.
- Daddy, no!
- Baby girl. Baby.
- No! No!
Look, I don't want no bloodshed over me!
I'll go. Just leave
these good people alone.
You're doing the right thing.
I don't think so.
Now, there's no need
for this to get messy, son.
Now, would you look at that?
We got guns too.
Ours just happen to be government issue.
I suggest you fellas leave.
Ain't nobody getting strung up today.
Put 'em down, boys.
Put 'em down. Put 'em down.
He's right.
This isn't the way.
Everybody out. Come on.
What are we supposed to do with you now?
You know they're coming back.
We got a truck out back.
Get him there, sneak him out.
- Fuck. They chained it shut.
- Is there another way out?
Check the back. Check the back!
Women and kids
in the middle of the room now!
Hey, call the guys on base.
I'll check the phones.
No, phone's not working.
Something's wrong with it.
Stay calm. Stay calm.
- Stay alert. Stay alert.
- Take care of yourselves, fellas.
- Do it!
- Something's going on.
- Stay calm.
- Watch out!
Get 'em out! Get 'em out!
Go, go! Check the back. Check the back.
- Reggie, go, go, go, go!
- Let's go! Hurry, come on! Come on!
Come on! Hey! Door's shut too!
Shit!
Hey, yo. I need ammo. Ammo!
Get down!
- Get in here!
- Down!
Go! Go, go, go! Move!
Don't go that way. They're on both sides.
Fuck!
Get down! Get down!
- Ronnie!
- Daddy!
Will, get up. Are you okay?
- You okay?
- I can't see anything!
- Ronnie! Will!
- Ronnie!
Daddy?
Where's my dad?
Please! Where's my dad?
- Daddy!
- I got you!
Let go of me!
My arm!
Rich! It's hot!
Hold still!
Oh my God! Oh my God! Oh my God!
Frankie! Frankie!
Frankie! Snap out of it!
Come on.
You got it. Get back.
Shit.
Dad! Where's my dad?
Hey!
Over here! Hey!
No, no, no.
Noreen. Over here.
Take my hand.
I know a way out.
Daddy! Will!
What's the matter?
Do I have face on my face?
Hey. It's okay. It's okay.
You're okay. You're okay.
I got you. We're gonna get you out.
Hello, Dicky.
What's the matter?
Seeing things?
I think they see you too.
Where are the kids? Show me.
It's time to go.
Not until I know Grogan's dead.
No one's getting out of there alive.
He's right. They're cooked.
Come on. Get in, get in.
- Down here now. Go, go, go!
- Baby.
What about Rich and Marge?
- The roof's caving in, boy!
- I got 'em.
- I'm gonna get them. Go on ahead.
- No! No!
Stop! Stop! Goddammit, I'll find them.
Get!
Get in!
Kids! Kids! In here! Come this way! Come.
Okay, get in.
Marge, come help me.
Come on, help me.
Help me!
Let's get in here.
It's the only way
we're gonna make it out.
- It's too small.
- There's plenty of room.
The roof is gonna fall! Come on, Marge!
Okay, okay.
There's not enough room for both...
- No!
- Marge-- Marge, stop!
No, Rich! Please, no!
Let me out! Please!
Marge, listen to me!
Let me out!
- Marge!
- Let me out!
Remember what you said?
About knights?
- What?
- Knights.
Who sleep with something by the bed?
Yeah.
Well, we don't just pee in pots.
We also protect fair maidens.
Remember the day,
that day all the guinea pigs
got loose in the hallway
'cause Robbie Mueller,
he broke into the science lab?
That was my first week of school,
and everyone went out to see it.
You came out of class
with a yellow sweater and a gray skirt
with a string tied to your finger.
You remember that?
You were so pretty.
I remember wondering, "¿Quién es esa?"
And you saw me staring and you said,
"Take a picture, it'll last longer."
You didn't say it mean or anything.
I didn't even know what it meant.
Later when I figured it out,
I remember thinking
what I should have said back.
"I wish I could."
I love you, Rich.
I love you too, Marge.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, come on. No, come on!
Guys, guys, wait!
Fuck.
No, no, no. No, not now. Not now! Fuck!
Come on. Come on.
Ingrid?
Hello, Stanley.
Is that you?
What are you doing?
What the hell are you wearing?
This is me, Stanley.
This is who I really am.
Black and blue is what you're gonna be
if you don't get back to the house
and wipe this ridiculous crap
off your face!
You hear me?
Hello, Papa.
What?
What the hell?
Who the hell are you--
I knew they would come
if they thought that he was here.
And there would be blood,
and-- and pain, and fear.
And I knew that you
wouldn't be able to resist it.
And you would come back.
And you would tell me that I was good.
Show me the bow.
Come to Papa.
Papa. Papa.
I love you.
You did good. You did very, very good.
Now, I'm going to sleep.
What?
Don't you worry.
I'll come back.
- No, no, no.
- I always do.
No. No, don't leave me. Please. No.
Don't abandon me.
You're not him.
Who are you?
Why, I'm Pennywise, your dancing daddy.
You are not my father.
- Yes, I am.
- What have you done with him?
I... I ate him.
But he still lives inside of me!
- No!
- Yes, he does!
Why, I... I can feel him right now, yes.
Stop.
- He's reaching out for his baby girl.
- Shut up!
Stop it! Shut up! Shut up!
Stop it!
Shut up!
Come to Papa.
Help!
Hey, hey. Are you okay?
Come on, dear. Are you alright?
Come on, careful. Watch your step.
Wait, wait.
All right, I'm good. Go.
Will!
Son.
Oh my God.
Son, you could have
gotten yourself killed.
I know. I-- I'm sorry.
- Are you hurt?
- I'm okay.
Mr. Hallorann, he got us out.
- Hallorann?
- Hanlon!
You all just hold tight.
I'll be right back, okay?
My dad. The woods.
Okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's just me. It's okay. It's all right.
- Leroy? Leroy?
- It's all right. Yeah. Yes.
You all right?
No. No.
I had to talk to one of 'em.
I had to.
The noise.
What's happening?
- It hurts like hell.
- Talking to you.
Look at our kind, brother.
What'd they do to us?
Gotta make it right.
Make it right--
- Dad.
- Baby.
We thought we should hide him
here just till you got here.
Are you hurt, Mr. Grogan?
No, I made it.
I'm just more worried
about the ones that didn't.
We gotta get him out of here.
- What if Dad sees?
- He knows.
Really?
Give me your clothes,
Mr. Grogan. If you don't mind.
Excuse me?
We need to help him.
We can help him
by getting his ass and ours back to base.
That... thing is still out here,
and I'm not inclined
to wait around to find--
It ain't here no more.
- What'd you say, Airman?
- Ain't here no more.
I could always feel it before,
but now it's like...
It's like a light went out. It's like...
Like this son of a bitch
just went to sleep.
Asleep or not,
the general's gonna wanna see us.
Seventeen dead airmen, more civilians,
not a goddamn clue where the pillars are.
- We are fucked, Major!
- Okay, Colonel. Okay.
No, no, maybe not.
I can help us find one of them pillars.
- What?
- Yeah.
How?
In that Indian kid's head, I saw it.
They put one of them pillars
where their war chief died.
I didn't know exactly where, but now...
Now we just gotta follow her.
Follow who?
Her...
What do we do about Hank?
I don't know, babe.
I'll think of something.
But for now, maybe you should
take him back to the house.
- Our house?
- Yes.
- Derry?
No one's going to look for him there.
- That thing--
- Dick seems to think
that this thing is asleep,
or hibernating, or something.
- Hibernating?
- Whatever the reason.
- Leroy, whoever did this needs to pay.
- That's not our job though, Charlotte.
How are you so calm?
- It's not our job.
- People died.
- Other than protect-- All we can do--
- Our son saw dead bodies, Leroy.
After this mission,
this place, all of this, it's done.
And we take our family
and get out of this town to safety.
The worst of all this shit is behind us.
I promise you.
Good morning, Derry.
It's 7:15 a.m. and this is
the news you can use.
Reports have begun filing in
about an electrical fire
that broke out overnight
at what fire department
spokesman Bob McCormick
described as
"an illegal colored speakeasy"
on the outskirts of town.
The blaze claimed scores of lives.
Among them,
the Negro patrons responsible...
Lilly, you've barely touched
your breakfast.
...along with several citizens
who showed up
to help treat the wounded.
Including beloved
local butcher Stanley Kersh.
Derry police also reported
including amongst the remains
the charred body of notorious
fugitive child killer Hank Grogan.
Way to go, boys in blue.
And rest in peace, Stanley.
No one could filet
a tenderloin quite like you.
Now here's Frank with the weather.
The Augury has passed.
Its feeding cycle is complete.
It sleeps.
How many died at the Black Spot?
Reports are still coming in,
but according to the coroner, 23.
And how many children
for the-- for the full cycle?
Seventeen. Seventeen young souls.
All those people.
And not a damn thing we can do
about it but watch.
It feels wrong.
We do as much as we can
for as many as we can.
Focus on the lives saved.
The ones protected because we
keep this thing in its cage.
Well...
See you shit-asses in 27 years.
Don't worry about him. I know.
- Where are we?
- Been at it since 0700 hours, sir.
If it's down there, we'll know soon.
- Where's Hallorann?
- In the tent.
- How are you holding up, Airman?
- The fuck it look like?
Sorry, sir. It's just...
the noise, sir. I'm sorry.
Why don't you head back to base, Airman?
Get some rest.
You did good.
So this friend of yours,
you really think she'll help us?
If anyone can get you
and your family outside Derry,
it's her. Trust me.
This is going to work.
Assuming someone will pick up the phone.
Come on, girl. Come on.
We'll just head there.
- You're not coming.
- No, I was gonna go to Lilly's
with Ronnie and Marge.
We thought it'd be better
if she heard it from us about Rich.
I don't think so, baby.
But Dad said the thing was asleep.
It wasn't that thing
that lit the fire last night.
This town is the monster!
You're not going anywhere!
And neither is Ronnie.
You sure this is necessary?
Unless you want my neighbors wondering
what a dead man's doing
walking down my driveway.
I mean, you think they'll notice?
I don't exactly look like Mr. Hanlon.
In this town?
Yeah, point taken.
Let's go. You stay.
I'll be back in an hour.
Lilly, sweetheart. You have guests.
Hey.
We needed to talk.
Last night, something happened.
We ended up heading
to the Black Spot without you.
The fire.
I heard about it on the news.
Are you--
- Is your dad--
- He's fine.
We're fine.
Will is okay. It's ju--
Where's Rich?
What?
No.
You okay?
He never did get one all the way
to Main Street, did he?
Found something!
Goddamn. Hallorann was right.
You can stand down, Major.
Stand down?
Colonel, we have orders
to take the pillar three clicks north.
Change of plan.
Pillar's going back to base
- for further testing.
- Wait.
The plan has always been to move inward.
Toward the center of Derry.
No, we pen this thing
one pillar at a time.
What you're suggesting,
it's like leaving the cage door open.
You heard Hallorann. The entity is asleep.
Now we can analyze the pillar's
physical properties.
See if Dick or the eggheads
can't use that data
to find the other 12 pillars even faster.
Relax, Major. We're in the homestretch.
You done good.
Charlotte?
You said if I ever needed a friend...
Why don't you two come inside?
Hank.
Rose.
The good news is the heat'll be off.
They already think Hank's dead.
I got friends in McGill up in Montreal.
They can get the Grogans set up
with fresh papers, all of that.
- What's the bad news?
- Gotta get him across the border.
Last I checked,
customs ain't all accommodating
to... dead people.
Just a line on a map.
Right?
Auntie!
We might have a problem.
Begin incinerator process.
Hold it right there!
Shut it down!
Shut it down! Now!
Take it out.
Take it out of there!
What the hell do you think you're doing?
You said we were just studying
the physical properties.
Orders are orders, Major.
Leroy.
Put the damn gun down.
Weapons down. All of you.
Now!
A word, please, Major?
I'm sorry I didn't tell you sooner, Major,
but OPSEC comes first.
You were on a need-to-know basis.
This isn't even about Russia, is it?
The greatest threat to this nation
is not from without, Major.
It's from within.
You see what's happening out there, Leroy?
Americans are at each other's throats,
and it's only getting worse.
Anti-nuke crazies,
the women's movement, race riots.
This country is slowly fracturing
into a thousand jagged,
ill-fitting pieces.
I am only trying to prevent
another civil war.
Americans have stopped
hearing one another.
They only want to fight
over who gets which piece of the damn pie
while the rest of the world eats us alive.
And the one thing
that makes people really listen is fear.
Listen? Or you mean obey?
I mean a nation of laws requires a system
where people actually follow them.
Anything else is anarchy.
You know that, Major.
You never planned to cage it.
You were always planning to free it,
to release it
in your own fucking backyard!
Look at this town.
What happened last night?
Horrific. But guess what?
The streets are calm today.
No rioting, no looting, no unrest.
The fear.
It settles on every living person
it touches like a fog,
like a goddamned anesthetic.
So you want to make America Derry?
At what cost?
How many dead fucking kids
along the way?
Fewer than die in car accidents
every single year!
We're soldiers, Major!
We accept collateral damage.
You are fucking insane.
And that's exactly what the IG officers
at DOD will say when I tell them
about this shit.
You'd be shutting the barn door
after the horse is already out.
Finish it.
Rescind the order.
Do it!
Put it down, Hanlon.
You may not realize it yet, Major,
but the actions you've taken today
may very well save this country.
You wanted to be a hero.
You did it, son.
Now go back to your quarters.
Make sure that man
does not leave this base.
Yes, sir, General.
- Hello?
- Hey, it's Ron.
Ron, I'm sorry.
My mom wouldn't let me out.
It's okay.
We all went over to the Standpipe,
just to get Rich's stuff and...
Hey, Ro-- Ron, it's okay.
- It's--
- No, it's not.
Nothing is okay.
I know.
I'm sorry.
I just can't get over
the fact that he's gone.
That he died like that. The way he looked.
The way he must have suffocated.
Lungs bursting like popcorn.
Making my mouth water.
What?
I can smell
his stinky, little, broken boy body.
Can't you?
Shut up.
- Shut up!
- I can't hear you.
I know who this is!
- You're not gonna scare me!
- Speak up, Willy boy!
- You hear that?
- I can't hear you!
I'm done being scared!
I can't hear you!