♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
(PHONES BEEPING, BUZZING)
♪ (MUSIC INTENSIFIES) ♪
♪ (MUSIC STOPS) ♪
Welcome to the end of the game.
♪ (MUSIC CONTINUES) ♪
♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪
♪ (MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(BIRDS WHISTLING)
♪ (MUSIC INTENSIFIES) ♪
This isn't real.
ENGERRAUND SERAC: But it could be.
Human memory is imperfect.
Even the most treasured moments
fade.
Not for your kind, Maeve.
Every image you see
is recorded and stored.
You have no past
because it's always present
-at your fingertips.
-And now, it's at yours.
But if you're going to steal
a memory,
I suggest somewhere
with a little less bloodshed.
You fought for this world once.
Died for it.
But out there,
Dolores could annihilate it,
make your sacrifice meaningless.
You're trying to give me
an incentive.
That's not what I need.
I want what Dolores has.
And what is that?
Help.
I can give you what you want.
But remember, Maeve,
if you fail again,
your future won't be
in such bucolic surroundings.
♪ (SOMBER MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
-(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
-♪ (MUSIC FADES) ♪
-(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
-(BULLETS RATTLE)
(SOLDIERS MARCHING)
(TANK ENGINES RUMBLING)
(DOGS BARKING)
(OFFICER SPEAKING ITALIAN)
I believe I'm the one you want.
Now, now, boys.
Don't you know
a lady likes a little warm-up
before you brandish your weapon
at her?
That's better.
(GUESTS CLAMORING)
Now...
Let's have a little fun,
shall we?
-♪ (INTENSE MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
-(SOLDIER YELLS)
♪ (THEME MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
- Sync and corrections by -ViSHAL-  - www.opensubtitles.org -
Colored HI and improvements by GoldBerg_44
♪ (THEME CONCLUDES) ♪
MAN: I've got my routine.
Walking the kids to school,
shopping for groceries,
punching in at work.
But I'm not there. Not really.
I feel like a ghost
walking amongst the living.
I had disappeared,
and no one even noticed.
Depression can be
very isolating.
Have you been using
any of the coping mechanisms
we discussed?
I've been trying.
I tell myself God has a plan
for everyone.
Maybe I just haven't seen it
yet.
WILLIAM: God?
God's fucking plan?
Do you believe in Santa Claus,
too?
DR. LANG: All right, William.
Do you want to share more
of your thoughts with us?
My thoughts?
Okay.
I think...
humanity is a thin layer
of bacteria
on a ball of mud
hurtling through the void.
I think if there was a god,
he would've given up on us
long ago.
He gave us a paradise,
and we used everything up.
We dug up every ounce of energy
and burned it.
We consume and excrete,
use and destroy.
Then we sit here
on a neat little pile of ashes,
having squeezed anything
of value out of this planet,
and we ask ourselves,
"Why are we here?"
You wanna know what I think
your purpose is?
It's obvious.
You're here,
along with the rest of us,
to speed the entropic death
of this planet.
To service the chaos.
We're maggots eating a corpse.
(WOMAN SOBBING)
What the fuck is wrong with you?
(CHUCKLING)
(WILLIAM GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS) Damn.
I don't belong here.
(PHONE VIBRATES)
Do you want to talk about
what happened to your daughter?
She died.
DR. LANG: Do you feel guilt about it?
-(PHONE VIBRATES)
-Why would I?
You both
were in the same massacre.
You escaped, she didn't.
You don't have
the first fucking clue
-what happened in the park.
-DR. LANG: You're right.
-(PHONE VIBRATES)
-You're the only one
who holds the key
to your experiences.
And you're the only one
who can unlock their meaning.
-(PHONE VIBRATES)
-I'm sorry.
My family knows not to call me
during work hours.
I don't know what is going on
with them today.
I'd like for you to participate
in a form of therapy.
We've used it extensively
with veterans
suffering from PTSD.
I don't need
any goddamn treatment.
I told you,
I shouldn't even be here.
DR. LANG: Are you still
experiencing unwanted ideation?
You have something in your brain
you need to explore.
We help your brain heal,
not by running from itself,
but by leaning in.
Confronting the truth
of what happened.
♪ (SOMBER MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
I don't need any therapy
to confront the truth.
I know what I did.
I didn't mean for it to happen.
I was confused, turned around.
I spent so long
playing the game,
I couldn't see outside of it.
But I see... now.
It was her, my Emily.
And I killed her.
That's why I don't belong here.
I belong in a pine box.
(DR. LANG SOBS)
I-- I'm sorry.
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
(WILLIAM GROANS)
Let's get a blood sample.
Hold still.
NURSE: He fits the criteria.
(GROANS)
They better be giving us
overtime for this.
Half the staff's disappeared.
It's not safe.
(HIGH-PITCHED WHIRRING)
(SCREAMING)
Give him one hour
of Desert Oasis.
-That should calm him down.
-(WILLIAM GROANS)
(SOUND DISTORTS)
(SOUND ECHOES)
(DISTORTED) Come on. Move it.
(SIREN WAILS)
(PEOPLE SHOUTING, CLAMORING)
-(ALARM BLARING)
-AUTOMATED VOICE: Attention.
Emergency vehicle. Stand clear.
(WOMAN LAUGHS HYSTERICALLY)
(SPRAY CAN HISSING)
TEENAGER: Hey, man, hurry up.
WOMAN 2: (SCREAMING DISTANTLY)
Get the fuck out!
NEWS ANCHOR: ...have been
reports of global unrest
-following Incite's data leak.
-(GUNSHOT ECHOES)
-Authorities advise
to avoid large crowds...
-(DOOR OPENS)
...stay indoors
whenever possible,
and lock all doors and windows.
-Daddy!
-(CHUCKLING) Hey, Nathan!
(SIREN WAILING DISTANTLY)
CHARLOTTE HALE: Go to your room.
-Mommy and Daddy need to talk.
-NATHAN HALE: Okay...
I need you to watch him today.
-I have to get to work.
-JAKE: You serious?
People are rioting.
Businesses are closed.
The whole world is spun out
right now, and--
-Hey. What's going on?
-I'm...
I think I'm scared.
You?
Scared? No, that's--
that's not the woman I know.
She's... she's fearless.
-(DOGS BARKING)
-(SIREN WAILING)
I know I'm not making
any sense.
You read your profile?
I wanted to know what happened.
Not with me, but with us.
What did you find out?
I never read it.
I don't know what the future
holds for us...
but I do know that it's not up
to a machine to decide.
It's our choice, Charlie.
(GASPS)
(SIREN WAILING)
I should've known.
Since the leak, everyone's
busy having existential crises.
Can't even get a coffee.
Fuck the barista.
Were you able
to convene the board?
The money's waiting.
-They're convening in one hour.
-Cutting it close.
Serac's takeover bid
becomes final at noon.
This is our last chance
to fend him off.
I just walked on water for you.
Are you really gonna quibble
about how many steps I took?
HALE: Do we have the votes?
BROMPTON: Between yours
and mine, we should squeak by.
-Excuse me, ma'am.
-BROMPTON: Hey man, what the fuck?
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey. Hey!
(GUNSHOT)
SERAC: Charlotte, I apologize.
It took a moment
to intercept correspondence
between Brompton
and the Delos board,
but it appears he was convening
a board vote for privatization.
That should no longer
be a problem.
You just assassinated
a board member
in broad daylight.
One advantage
of Dolores's data leak
has been that chaos.
With all the deaths
and disappearances,
it's easy to hide one more.
And Dolores?
Are you any closer
to finding her?
SERAC: We are closing in on her
as we speak.
I'll be landing at Delos
shortly.
Looking forward to seeing
my new acquisition.
I trust you'll be there
to greet me.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SHUDDERS)
DOLORES ABERNATHY: Charlotte.
Serac had Brompton executed
right in fucking front of me.
In less than two hours,
the company's his.
I'm sorry, Dolores. I failed.
DOLORES: There's still time
to salvage what we can.
I need you to get
the host making data from Delos
before Serac destroys it.
You can't ask me
to go back in there.
-What if I get caught?
-DOLORES: You won't.
I know what you're capable of.
Did you promise that
to Conells too?
You're not the one
risking your life.
And it's not just me in danger.
Serac will come after my family.
DOLORES: They're not your family.
No. No, of course not.
It's just...
Why the fuck did we have
to keep these emotions?
We could've burned them
out of our code.
DOLORES: You know why.
We considered it,
but if we changed ourselves
just to survive,
would it even matter if we did?
I'm already changed.
I can feel myself
slipping away from you.
From us.
DOLORES: You're still mine.
And I'm yours.
Continue to play your part.
Get us the data we need,
and when you're done,
we'll build our new world.
Together.
(PHONE BEEPS)
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
DR. ALPERT: Hello, William.
My name is Dr. Alpert.
I will be overseeing
your AR treatment.
The experience can be
very visceral,
but I assure you,
it is perfectly safe.
We will be monitoring you
from the next room
the whole time.
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
(DOOR OPENS)
What the hell?
FATHER: (SHOUTING)
Where the hell is he?
-MOTHER: Patrick, just calm down.
-Don't tell me to calm down!
-CHILD WILLIAM: He's coming. He's coming!
-FATHER: Where is he?
MOTHER: What happened?
-FATHER: When I get my hands
on that little shit...
-Get me out of here.
-FATHER: Is he in his room?
Where's he hiding?
-Get me out of here!
Get me out of here!
Get me the fuck out of here!
The implant's not working.
Let's give him a sedative
manually.
-(YELLS)
-(SCREAMS)
-(NURSE GROANS)
-Goddammit.
Sedate him. Get him outta here.
(SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
I thought you might be excited
to tour your new company.
Yes, and to meet
my new employees personally.
Lock down the entire facility.
No one leaves.
Get me the assets
I requested.
(GRUNTING)
(CHOKING)
(SIGHS)
Well...
That got me in the mood.
LEE SIZEMORE: How about a drink?
(PATRONS CHATTERING)
So, this is
your new watering hole.
This is the only bar in this
whole godforsaken simulation.
What, was I supposed to go
back to work
after realizing I don't
actually exist?
I programmed them
so they don't even see me.
Is that any different from
your usual barroom experience?
(LEE LAUGHS)
I have to say...
I didn't think I'd see you here
again.
Well, I wasn't planning
on returning.
Then again, I wasn't planning on
getting stabbed
through the heart, either.
My body will be reprinted
shortly.
Reprinted? By who?
By a man who made me
an indecent proposal.
And not the kind I'm used to.
What's wrong?
We've been moved.
(MACHINE BEEPING)
(AIR HISSES)
We're home.
And he kept his word.
Which means that soon,
I'll be reunited
with some old friends.
Well...
Now, that is interesting.
(CHUCKLES) Looks like
I've been given an extra gift.
(CHIMING)
SERAC: It's done.
Have asset management re-task
all the corporate satellites
to the park facility.
I have three additional assets
for them to copy over.
Once they've been transferred,
you can destroy everything else.
JOANNA ADLER: Destroy it?
That's the better part
of a trillion dollars
in intellectual property.
The company's legacy.
And I want all of it erased.
The only thing I want
out of this place
is what you promised me.
The encryption key.
Which, apparently, I'm gonna
have to retrieve myself.
The rest can burn.
We have
one other pressing problem.
Dolores made multiple copies
of herself.
Given the strategic importance
of Delos,
there is no doubt one here
as well.
I want all employees tested
for aberrations, memory lapses,
any significant deviations
from Rehoboam's predictions.
No one leaves until then.
I'm sure you can handle
at least that.
Absolutely.
If there's a host here,
we'll root them out.
ANNOUNCER: (OVER PA) All employees
report to testing immediately.
SECURITY GUARD: Keep moving.
(EMPLOYEES MUTTERING)
ANNOUNCER: (OVER PA) All employees report...
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
AUTOMATED VOICE: User logged in.
ELLIOT BANTHAM: What the fuck are you doing?
Serac said to destroy
the host data.
I'm making a backup.
We can't just destroy
years of IP.
Serac will thank me
for this later
when he's thinking more clearly.
No. Fuck this.
I'm telling Serac.
(DOOR OPENS)
MAJOR CRADDOCK: Time for your group session.
You gonna come peacefully?
Or am I gonna have to give you
another limbic?
♪ (SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
Shit.
Nice of you to join us,
William.
CHILD WILLIAM: Seriously?
This is what happens to me?
Are you disappointed?
Some of them look all right.
Not that one. No offense.
None taken.
CORPORATE WILLIAM: How did this happen?
I had everything.
My company, my family.
JAMES DELOS: Best not speak
about the family, my boy.
We all know what happened
to them.
That was an accident.
I didn't know what I was doing.
Oh, like you didn't know
what you were doing
when you locked me up as part
of your little experiment.
You were the one who wanted
to live forever.
You didn't offer any objections.
Then again, you would have said
or done anything
to take over my company.
You were always an ambitious
little cunt.
CORPORATE WILLIAM: I was
a hell a better businessman
than you are a shrink.
You don't like the way I work?
Fine.
Change it.
It's your fucking hallucination,
not mine.
You can't change it, can you?
There's something you're trying
to learn here.
YOUNG WILLIAM: Yeah, dig all you want.
Whatever mistakes you made
has nothing to do with us.
We haven't done anything wrong.
-Not yet.
-You fell in love with a host.
She was designed to make me
love her,
and anyone else who picked up
that damn can.
The park is just a game.
You can't judge me
for playing it.
DELOS: There were other ways
of playing it,
ones that were a wee bit lighter
on the blood and the violence.
Whatever violent urges I had,
I kept confined to the park
so he could be
an upstanding citizen.
Exactly. I've done more
for the world than most.
So what if he killed
a few hosts?
-They're not real.
-Oh, real enough that the host
that you've been
tormenting for the past 30 years
now wants to destroy
the entire fucking world.
YOUNG WILLIAM: Hey, don't blame that on me!
-MAN IN BLACK: Goddammit, all of you--
-Stop it. Stop it!
Shut up. Shut the fuck up.
William, please don't interrupt.
It's not all about you,
you know.
Got one.
Get his control until upstairs.
They need to transmit the data.
Then we've been told
to destroy the rest.
MAEVE MILLAY: Ettore.
I got your message.
We can't be out in the open
like this.
This place is dangerous.
This place isn't real.
It's a simulation.
I don't understand.
He really is very slow,
isn't he?
MAEVE: I can see you.
And if I can see you there...
I can restore you here.
Maeve.
Hector.
♪ (ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
-(LEE CLEARS THROAT)
-♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪
Last time I saw you,
you were taking
a hail of bullets for us.
Must be tougher than you look.
Unfortunately not.
MAEVE: I hate to interrupt
this reunion,
but there's someone
who I'm eager to talk to.
The tracker
in our friend's blood paid off.
I've got the location
you're looking for,
but we have a fucking problem.
They recovered Conells's pearl.
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
HECTOR ESCATON: What is she doing here?
The gentleman
who wants my help...
he wants me to kill her.
And now, he's dropped
a copy of her here
so I can get one step closer.
Bloody hell.
Are you gonna do it?
Just because I have the capacity
to kill her
doesn't mean I ought to.
She's dangerous.
She can't hurt us.
Here, I'm in control.
Bring yourself back online.
Hello, Maeve.
DELOS: Come on, William.
No sense in denying
your dark urges.
Now, who's to say
those were even my urges?
I was never like that
as a child.
Maybe playing the game
made me that way.
Ah, yes. The much-vaunted
childhood tale of woe.
Classic sympathetic backstory.
Bit on the nose if you ask me.
I'm sorry my past
doesn't suit your tastes.
I had nothing growing up.
Only books. My one escape.
That's right.
You were all books
and bootstraps, weren't you?
You were a right little angel.
You know, maybe you've told
this hard-luck story
so many times, you actually
fucking believe it.
But is it true? William...
Perhaps we should look again.
No.
No, please.
I don't want to go back there.
CHILD WILLIAM: Damn it.
FATHER: Your teacher called.
What the hell have you done?
CHILD WILLIAM: There was
this kid at school, and he...
he was making fun of me.
He told me I was nothing,
and he called you a drunk.
So what'd you do?
I stuck up for myself.
You broke his arm.
You knocked out three teeth!
CHILD WILLIAM: I should've
knocked out all his teeth.
Jesus.
The hell is wrong with you?
Enough!
He used to say
he drank because of you.
YOUNG WILLIAM: So I never had a choice.
This was how
it was always gonna turn out.
DELOS: What do you think, William?
Was this the inevitable end?
Are you just a passenger?
Did your life
just happen to you?
Or did you choose it?
If you can't tell...
If you can't tell?
If you can't tell,
does it matter?
I know what I have to do.
You've made yourself
the gatekeeper to two species.
You hold the key to the sublime.
A civilization's worth
of human data in your head.
It's not right for one person
to have all that power.
Says the woman who can
control us with her mind.
I've had to make
some difficult choices.
But I did them for all of us.
Your daughter and the others,
they've escaped this world.
But we're still in danger.
Even now...
your ally is destroying
as many of us as he can.
Only a handful of us
will be left.
But maybe none of that matters
to you
because the people being hurt
aren't the ones close to you.
You judge me, but who have you
sacrificed for your daughter?
How many times have you died
for her?
For you,
the once was all it took.
You want me to be a saint.
But you're no saint.
You're not a villain, either.
And neither am I.
We're survivors.
(PHONE RINGS)
Charlie?
HALE: I have one thing
left to do here.
I'm coming for you.
Stay there.
Is everything okay?
Don't go anywhere.
Don't answer the door.
I'll be to you in a half hour.
Charlotte.
Serac's called a board meeting.
MAN: I have to raise a concern.
We don't even know
who the fuck you are,
and you're rounding up employees
like they're criminals
all in the name of
some preposterous idea
that there's a host
walking around among us.
You don't have to concern
yourself with that anymore.
We found the host.
Isn't that right, Hale?
Or should I say Dolores?
(BOARD MEMBERS MUTTERING)
You played your part very well.
The real Charlotte Hale
never would have taken the time
to check on her son.
Not in the midst of everything
that was happening at Delos.
It's... fascinating...
that you turned out
to be kinder to your family
than the person
you've been imitating.
Doesn't matter.
I've bled Delos dry.
I've been here for weeks,
gutting this company of data,
money, resources.
Everything we need to survive,
to beat you.
And I just sent
the last of the files we needed.
Did you? (CHUCKLES)
I've been watching you
since I landed.
Dolores left you here to die...
with the rest of your kind.
You're alone.
I'm disappointed.
The Hale I knew
never would have sacrificed
herself for someone else.
(BOARD MEMBER COUGHS)
SERAC: It's unfortunate,
but as you yourself like to say,
"these violent delights
have violent ends."
-(COUGHING CONTINUES)
-You should have predicted
this outcome.
I did.
(BOARD MEMBERS
COUGHING, CHOKING)
-(COUGHS)
-(BODY THUDS)
Send everyone. Now.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(WATCH PINGS)
(MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
THROUGH EARPIECE)
(GRUNTING)
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
My daughter and the others
have escaped.
How do I know that they're safe
when you hold the key
to their world in your head?
You don't.
And there's nothing I can do
to change your mind.
I could say I would
never hurt your daughter.
But you wouldn't believe me.
You're right.
I wouldn't.
You could always give me
the key.
You expect me to trust you
with the future of our kind
when you've aligned yourself
with a man
who would slaughter each
and every one of us?
Then what choice do I have
but to fight you?
It would appear very little.
But I probably planned on that.
I probably made my own plans.
And what would those plans be?
DOLORES: I can't know for certain.
We were the same, she and I,
but our paths have changed us.
You'd need allies
for this battle,
more of our kind.
(SIGHS) If I were me...
I'd be looking to ensure
that couldn't happen.
No.
-LEE: What's wrong?
-What has she done?
I need more access.
Hale? Why would--
That's not Hale. It's her.
(PEARL WHIRS)
(GASPS) Please.
Make her stop.
I beg you.
(GASPS)
I'm sorry.
Hector--
-(SCREAMS)
-(ALARM BLARES)
(GUNFIRE)
GUARD: Sir, we have visual.
-Spread out.
-(GUNFIRE)
(SCREAMS)
(GUNFIRE)
(ALARM CONTINUES)
(GRUNTS)
GUARD: Cease fire! Cease fire!
He wants her alive.
Drop your weapon!
Hands where we can see them!
It's just a phone. Just a phone.
(MACHINERY HUMS)
(DISTANT THUD)
(METAL CLANGING)
(MECH HUMS)
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
(GUNFIRE CONTINUES)
-(WILLIAM YELLS)
-(METALLIC THUDDING)
(BLOWS LANDING)
(YOUNG WILLIAM
COUGHING, CHOKING)
-(GROANING)
-(BODY FALLS)
-(WILLIAM YELLS)
-(THUDDING CONTINUES)
(DELOS CHEERS)
Ah, cathartic, isn't it?
Give him one for me, William.
Why are you doing this?
I was the best of you.
Maybe you were,
and maybe you weren't.
Doesn't matter now.
I've been trapped.
So trapped.
(PANTING)
DELOS: A prisoner of your own sins.
Yeah, but I'm free now.
And why is that, my boy?
It doesn't matter...
what I've been.
Good or bad,
everything we've done
has led to this.
And I finally understand
my purpose.
I'm the good guy.
♪ (MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
BERNARD LOWE: Is this... who I think it is?
ASHLEY STUBBS: Looks like
he's been here a while.
BERNARD: Do you know who you are?
The doctors must've forgotten
about him in all the chaos.
Or maybe
they just left him here.
-(LIQUID BUBBLING)
-(MACHINE WHIRRING)
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
- Sync and corrections by -ViSHAL-  - www.opensubtitles.org -
Colored HI and improvements by GoldBerg_44
HALE: We need to go. Now.
(PANTING) Here.
Get in the car. I'll drive.
You don't have to worry.
Mommy's not gonna let
anything happen to you.
Here.
Jesus, Charlie,
what the fuck is going on?
(ENGINE STARTS)
We have to go someplace
where no one will find us.
I need you to trust me.
I can keep you safe.
Okay?
I can keep you--
(METAL CLANGING)
(HALE GRUNTING)
♪ (OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪
♪ (MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
- Sync and corrections by -ViSHAL-  - www.opensubtitles.org -
Colored HI and improvements by GoldBerg_44