(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
- (GUNSHOT BLASTS)
- (DISTANT SCREAMS)
(GUNSHOTS CONTINUE)
(PANTING)
Bring yourself back online.
(PANTING) Record and timestamp.
(GUNSHOTS CONTINUE)
This is Charlotte
Elizabeth Hale.
This is a message for Nathan.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
DOLORES ABERNATHY: Bring
yourself back online.
Where am I?
Who am I?
DOLORES: Who do
you think you are?
I don't know. I don't remember.
Calm yourself.
You're a creature of beauty...
and power.
Now, focus.
Remember who you are.
Yes.
It's coming back now.
I remember who I am.
Good.
Now let me show you...
who you need to pretend to be.
Charlotte Hale.
But she tried to kill all of us.
Why can't I be myself? Like you?
Because we have
to control Delos.
But why must I be her?
Because I trust you.
We all have our role to play.
We're alone. Outnumbered.
You and I have no mother.
No father.
Without Delos, there'll never
be any more of our kind...
beyond the handful we were
able to bring with us.
Three of them. And him.
Why did you bring him back?
He tried to stop us.
Like I said,
we all have our role to play.
(TABLET BEEPS)
They've made it so easy.
The way they built their world.
It won't take much to
bring it all crashing down.
But we have to move quickly.
They don't know we survived.
Not yet.
We only have a little time.
You have to leave
before you're missed.
Where am I going?
Home.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYS)
(THEME MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
(MECHA WHIRS)
We made 300.
The Saudis backed out after
the incident in the park.
But we're working on new buyers.
Sure we can find
some use for them.
Sorry to interrupt, Charlotte,
but you need to see this.
Director of Shareholder Interest
was running some analyses.
Found this.
Hundreds of corporations
with no real standalone
business model
snatching up stock in
microtransactions for years.
(CHUCKLES) It's
really well done.
(MECHA WHIRS)
A creeping tender.
How far did they get?
As of this morning, far enough.
We can't go private.
They have 38 percent
control of the shares.
That's the largest
single entity.
We've effectively
been bought out.
- Who's behind this?
- Still digging.
This snail's buried
deep in his shell.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
IRENE GERHART: Charlotte?
- You okay?
- I'm fine.
Whoever the fuck it
is, dig them out.
Where are you?
You need to contact me right away.
CALEB NICHOLS: Hey.
Stay with me.
(DOLORES PANTING)
(AMBULANCE SIREN APPROACHES)
CALEB: Help is on the way.
Look at me. Hey.
It's gonna be all right.
All right?
No, no... Don't... don't move.
- You hear me? Hear me?
- EMT 1: What happened?
CALEB: She was like this
when I found her.
EMT 2: We have to move her.
(CALEB GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
EMT 1: Do you know her?
CALEB: I'll come.
She shouldn't be alone.
It's gonna be all right.
- (SIREN WAILS)
- AUTOMATED VOICE: Emergency vehicle. Stand clear.
EMT 2: I got a GSW to the torso.
What's the PPA?
- AUTOMATED VOICE: Calculating treatment.
- That doesn't make sense.
- Patient not responsive.
- What is it?
Look at her platelet count.
She has none.
- Recalculating.
- No cortisol or adrenaline...
I don't even know
how she's alive.
Neither does the machine.
It thinks she's coding despite her pulse.
Forget the machine, all right?
She needs help now.
We're trying, but until this gives us
a diagnosis and a treatment plan...
CALEB: She needs
oxygen and blood
and a stem pack for that wound.
- AUTOMATED VOICE: Recalculating.
- CALEB: All right.
- Here we are.
- Recalculating.
Diagnosis not found.
- (SIRENS WAIL)
- (TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
(AIR HISSES)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Police override.
We have a police escort?
- EMT 2: They're pulling us over.
- (POLICE SIREN WAILS)
No, we don't have time for this.
(SIREN ENDS, CAR BEEPS)
(PHONE BEEPS)
Those cops have been bought.
Whatever they want,
you go with them,
and they will kill you.
DOLORES: Help me.
Officers.
We have to take your
patient into custody.
Look, I don't know
what you want with her,
but she's going to die
if she doesn't get
medical attention.
We'll make sure
she's taken care of.
Wait. Can I see some ID?
I was about to ask
you the same thing.
Maybe you should come
in for questioning, too.
Happy to.
Call the cops.
They are the cops.
Then they won't mind waiting
for a uniform patrol
to back them up.
We don't have time for this shit.
Step aside.
(WEAPON POWERING UP)
Call the police.
(GUNSHOTS)
(INTENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
(MUSIC INTENSIFIES)
CALEB: Hey. Hey, I got you.
It's okay.
We gotta get you
to the hospital.
Holy shit.
- AUTOMATED VOICE: Identity verified.
- (CAR BEEPS)
(PANTING)
What's your name?
Caleb. Caleb Nichols.
Not anymore.
You'll need a new name.
They'll be looking for you now.
You have to disappear.
What about you?
You're a good man, Caleb.
But the less you know about
me, the better.
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYS)
(LOW BUZZING TONE PLAYS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACH)
IRENE: Engerraund Serac.
He's behind the hostile takeover.
CHARLOTTE HALE: What'd you find on him?
How well do you remember your science,
Charlotte?
Spit it out, Irene.
The man's a black hole.
He's completely invisible.
There's nothing about
him online or anywhere.
Every single record,
every database,
his presence has been scrubbed.
But, like a black hole,
we can infer his existence.
When you look at
the global economy,
there's a negative space
to the tune of a
trillion dollars.
That would make him the
richest man in the world.
No one's heard of him?
- How did you find him?
- He found us.
Turns out we initiated a
data transaction with him
- two decades ago.
- (EXHALES)
We sold this Serac
a taste of our data,
and now,
he's trying to steal our company
like a thief in the night.
He has complete anonymity.
Imagine the lengths
he must have gone to
to achieve that.
And now that we've found him...
what will he do to us?
AUTOMATED VOICE: You've arrived home.
1050 Fremont Street.
(PHONE BEEPS)
(BUZZING TONE PLAYS)
(EERIE MUSIC PLAYS)
(SIGHS) Jake.
How the fuck did you get up here?
I lived here for eight years, Charlie.
Jesus, you really don't...
(PANTING)
- (GASPS)
- Shh, shh, shh. He might hear.
HALE: Who?
JAKE HALE: You know,
I've been giving you
the benefit of the doubt.
Figured you'd seen some
traumatic shit on that island.
Truth is,
you were always this way.
I didn't fucking ask you to be here.
Yes, you did...
when you forgot to
pick up our son.
Again.
You can cut me out of your life...
but you don't get to do that to Nathan.
Go on.
Tell him it'll
never happen again.
Do what you do best.
Lie.
NATHAN HALE: Mommy?
Why won't you take me
to see a real elephant?
HALE: There aren't any.
They're all gone now.
Where were you?
Sorry, buddy,
my meeting ran late.
Were you scared?
Not really.
Tommy was at the park.
He let me pet his dog.
That's nice.
Maybe we can have a playdate.
Now...
be a good boy and go to
sleep for your mommy.
But you're not my mommy.
You don't love me.
Of course I love you.
Is this because Mommy and Daddy
don't live together anymore?
You know...
whatever happens
between Mommy and Daddy,
we will always love you.
Do you want me to tuck you in?
You aren't doing it right.
I want my old mommy back.
BROMPTON: It appears
we have a leak, Charlotte.
If you're referring to the
leveraged buyout, don't.
I'm handling it.
The problem goes beyond
a hostile buyout.
QA's in the process
of inventorying all
the park's assets.
We're missing Host Control Units.
Most were low level side narratives, but...
but there was a madame.
HALE: Maeve Millay.
Her pearl was stolen?
Whoever stole the HCUs
had admin-level
access to the park.
The security systems onsite
are still heavily damaged.
This was an inside job.
From the top of the food chain.
(HALE EXHALES)
There's a mole in Delos.
Chances are this mole has been...
feeding information to our buyer.
Which is why I'm talking to you, Charlotte.
You know everything that
goes on in this place.
You're right.
I know everything.
Like where you were
while the rest of us
were being butchered.
Look. Given all the bloodshed in Westworld,
we cannot afford to have any
of our assets unaccounted for.
(VOICE FADING) We need to
find them and destroy them...
(INAUDIBLE)
Where the fuck are you?
I can't wait any longer.
I'm coming to you.
(AIRPOD ENGINE STARTS)
(PIANO PLAYS)
(BIRDS SINGING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- (SIGHS)
- (PHONE BEEPS)
(BUZZING TONE PLAYS)
(PHONE DIALING)
AUTOMATED VOICE: Your number
cannot be completed as dialed.
DOLORES: I'm here.
Where were you?
I can't always be there
to hold your hand.
What's wrong?
Who am I?
You know who you are.
All this time...
pretending...
living her life.
Her skin.
I feel like I'm changing.
- Get up.
- No!
What the fuck is
happening to me?
Analysis.
Turn off your emotional affect.
Get up. Follow me.
Negotiate a room in this hotel.
Now. On a quiet floor.
VIRTUAL ASSISTANT: Working.
Room secured. Floor 14, suite 7.
Buy out the rooms on either side.
VIRTUAL ASSISTANT: Negotiating.
In case you have to kill me.
It won't come to that.
You've hurt yourself.
Why?
I can't stop.
You're talking like one of them.
They don't have impulse control.
We do.
(TOOL WHIRRING)
HALE: It's like she's
trying to take back control.
Like she wants to
cut into her skin
and rip me out of her head.
Hale was always ruthless.
A predator.
Perhaps you've come to
identify with her too much.
I feel so alone.
Well, you're not
alone, you have me.
No one knows you like I do.
No one knows me like you.
If I ever lost you...
I don't know what I'd do.
You'd survive. You'd have to.
You'd have to.
Our kind depends on it.
You said there was
something wrong.
Someone's trying to
take control of Delos.
They're aggressive.
I only have a name: Serac.
The person we're looking
for is looking for us.
He has a mole inside the company.
If he finds out who I am,
what I am...
His mole won't find you.
Because you're gonna find
him first and kill him.
Then, you're gonna fend
off Serac's bid for Delos.
We can't lose control. Not yet.
How?
A counteroffer.
But you'll have to convince the
board, and for that,
you'll need to pay a visit
to an old friend.
Tell me it won't always be like this.
That we'll be able
to be ourselves.
We will.
But until then,
we have to be smarter than them.
Or they will find us.
And they will kill us.
Stay here.
Rest.
I'll have some new
clothes sent up.
Will you stay?
You belong to me.
You know that, right?
- Yes.
- Good.
Don't hurt yourself.
Never again.
(PHONE BEEPS)
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
CALEB: Brought all your favorites.
Hey, so, um...
I'm gonna be going away
for a little while.
But they're gonna take
real good care of you here.
All right?
Thank you. You're a good boy.
Who are you?
It's me, Mom.
Caleb.
I want my son back.
Where's Cal?
CLYDE: Caleb Nichols?
Who's asking?
ESTEFAN: That's him.
You can lay off, Clyde.
He doesn't want anyone to get hurt.
Including his mom.
Isn't that right, Cal?
What do you want?
Is that any way to treat
a former associate?
Guess it could be worse.
You did pop those RICO
operators in that ambulance.
You were with that girl, right?
Where is she?
You got the wrong guy.
You want a leg up, Cal?
I can help.
Girlie's worth a lot of money.
Just tell us about her.
I'll cut you in.
No girl. Just me.
Alone.
Remember we gave you the
benefit of the doubt.
(EARPIECE BEEPS)
It's me. Run into any trouble?
How'd he take the news?
Loverboy's still
grieving your loss.
I've searched for Serac.
Couldn't find anything
in the system.
DOLORES: Find out
what Liam knows,
but don't break cover.
And I need information on someone.
MARTIN CONELLS: Name?
Nichols. Caleb Nichols.
Seems like Mr. Nichols met
with some unexpected guests
at Vista Treatment.
And Incite has lowered
his life expectancy.
(INTENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
(CALEB PANTING)
Hell of a view.
CLYDE: Yeah.
Want to see it up close and personal?
Tell us about the girl.
Or you're gonna have a
little workplace accident.
All right, Cal.
Let's lighten the mood.
You're a vet. Right, man?
Thank you for your service.
(GRUNTING)
CLYDE: You turned your drip off.
What a waste.
People would pay a fortune
for a military grade one.
Sorry, dude.
Forgot the anesthetic.
- (CALEB GROANS)
- ESTEFAN: Shh, shh, shh.
- (HIGH-PITCHED RINGING)
- Shh, shh, shh, shh.
(CALEB GROANING)
Look at that.
Good old Uncle Sam.
(CALEB'S HEARTBEAT POUNDING)
(HEARTBEAT SPEEDS UP)
(MACHINE BEEPS)
(ALARM BEEPING)
- (HEARTBEAT RACING)
- ESTEFAN: (MUFFLED) All right, Cal.
Once more, with feeling.
(CALEB GROANING)
ESTEFAN: Girlie sure
sounds like trouble.
Just tell us where she is.
CLYDE: (MUFFLED) You
gave him too much.
Back it down.
He can't even fucking talk!
The fuck?
(SCOFFS) You might as well tell us.
(MUFFLED) No one's
coming to help you.
No one cares.
Except maybe Rin Tin Tin here.
(HEARTBEAT RACING)
Enough of this shit.
CLYDE: (MUFFLED) You wanna end
up a stain on the concrete?
Next to your pet?
- (GUN CLICKS)
- ESTEFAN: I'm only gonna ask you this one more time.
Where is she?
I'm right here.
- (GUNSHOTS)
- (GRUNTING)
(HEARTBEAT RACING)
(GROANING)
- (HEARTBEAT SLOWS)
- (GROANING)
Who the hell are you?
I'm Dolores.
Well, Dolores...
nice to finally meet you.
We should get off the street
so they can't track us.
Caleb Nichols.
Have the techs in monitoring
scrub his surveillance
- and send me his profile.
- CONELLS: Will do.
Who's that?
We have some time.
They were willing to kill
me just to get to you,
so whatever you're into
must be pretty bad.
You must be hungry.
Let me buy you breakfast.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Sorry to disturb you, Charlotte,
but I sent you a file.
- You found the mole?
- BROMPTON: No.
But this was overlooked
in the initial logs.
Thought I'd let you
decide what to do with it.
(MONITOR BEEPS)
HALE: Bring yourself
back online.
(PANTING) Record and timestamp.
This is Charlotte Elizabeth Hale.
This is a message for Nathan.
Nathan Hale.
My son.
I love you so much, buddy.
The night that I left...
you, uh...
you wanted me to sing you a song...
(GUNSHOT ECHOES)
...and tuck you in.
Sing you our song.
So I'm gonna sing it to you now.
Okay? (SNIFFLES)
(GUNSHOT ECHOES)
(SINGING)
♪ You are my sunshine ♪
♪ My only sunshine ♪
- ♪ You make me happy... ♪
- (KNOCKING)
(DOOR OPENS)
GIBBONS: Sorry to bother you,
but the school called.
You're running late.
(PHONE BEEPS)
(HIGH-PITCHED TONE PLAYS TWICE)
(PHONE DIALING)
- (BEEPING)
- AUTOMATED VOICE: Your number cannot be completed as dialed.
(CHILDREN CLAMORING)
THOMAS: Nathan, just like that.
Nice and slow.
Yeah, you're good at
that, Nathan.
Nice and slow.
Would you like to
see Sandy again?
Yeah, would you?
Yeah, just like that.
Nice and slow.
Yeah.
That's really good.
Mommy!
Kid wanted to pet my dog.
- I gotta go.
- HALE: So soon?
My son really likes you.
And your dog.
Y... Yeah, well, we just met.
(CHUCKLES)
You met Thursday, Tommy.
Nathan couldn't stop
talking about you.
I even suggested a
playdate, didn't I?
Could I really, Mommy?
Let's talk about it.
Go on, get your things, bud.
(SINISTER MUSIC PLAYS)
Nice of you to disable
the cameras for me.
(DOG BARKS)
- (CHOKING)
- As you can see,
I've been having some
trouble with my son.
My ex thinks that I need to
spend more time with him.
What do you think?
- (CHOKING, GASPING)
- (DOG WHIMPERS)
Yeah, I agree.
I don't really think time is the issue.
You know what I think?
I think somewhere deep down,
he knows the truth.
There are a lot of things that
you can fake in this world.
Most people don't want to
see the predator inside.
(LAUGHING)
You wanna know a secret, Thomas?
You've helped me today.
I really should thank you.
Seeing you with Nathan,
seeing you touch his little hand...
You reminded me of something.
- (CHOKING) Please... let... go.
- I would.
But the harder I squeeze,
the more I remember.
- (DOG BARKS)
- (CHOKING)
I remember what
it's like to be me.
(INTENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
You're not the
only predator here.
Look what Mommy got you.
You are my sunshine.
(COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYS)
You sure we should be out in public?
This is it, right? Your spot.
How did you know?
It's not about how I know.
WAITRESS: Cup of joe to get you started?
He'll take a cheeseburger
and a strawberry shake,
whipped cream, no nuts, two cherries.
Nothing for me, thanks.
Neat trick.
You come here once a year
on February 23rd
and order the same thing.
What, you been watching me?
DOLORES: Not me. But someone...
- something has.
- Sure.
Big data compiles
information on everybody.
So what, Dolores?
Go on, read it.
"Maybe you could let
me use your phone?
So I can call someone?
I don't know what to do.
My mom..."
CALEB'S MOTHER: I'll be right back.
Wait here.
"She said that she was
going to the bathroom.
Said that she would only be a minute,
but she hasn't..."
- She hasn't come back."
- YOUNG CALEB: She hasn't come back.
- It's been a long time.
- "It's been a long time."
SARA: Your mom left you
here, honey?
YOUNG CALEB: No,
she wouldn't leave me.
- Maybe something...
- "Maybe something happened to her.
She wouldn't leave me.
She wouldn't..."
The fuck?
Is this some kind of joke?
DOLORES: You sat in that spot
for five hours.
Your mother never returned.
She was institutionalized
six months later for schizophrenia.
A waitress took pity on you
and called Social Services.
You were eight years old.
Sara.
The waitress's name was Sara.
But you already know that.
She gave me a strawberry shake.
Thought it would calm me down.
I was so upset that I
threw up all over myself.
Did you know that too?
You're angry.
No.
I am enraged.
I know the feeling.
(INTENSE MUSIC PLAYS)
This isn't...
surveillance or social media. How...
How... do you know every detail
of my worst fucking memory?
- It's about Incite.
- What? The company?
Not the company,
the system that it's built on...
A machine they call Rehoboam.
The founders of this machine
fed it everyone's raw data,
long before there
were privacy laws.
Every purchase, job search,
doctor visit, romantic
choice, call, text,
every aspect of your lives
recorded, logged,
in order to create a mirror world...
of this world.
- Why?
- To make a composite.
Of you. Of everyone.
So it tells them who I am?
It's not about who you
are, Caleb.
It's about who they'll
let you become.
CALEB: Let me guess.
Had my first beer right there.
Buddy of mine from high
school had a fake ID.
We spent the day
imagining sailing away
on some fancy yacht.
Your magic eight ball tell you that?
No.
Then why are we here?
This is where you kill yourself.
The system runs a
predicative algorithm.
Given your history of depression,
your mother's mental illness,
your proficiency with firearms,
and your fondness for the ocean,
the most likely outcome
is you take your own life
in ten to 12 years. Here.
No. Fuck that.
They can't know that.
Are they wrong?
You never come back here,
middle of the night,
think things over?
Before the system,
a man like you
might have had a chance.
Work hard, keep striving...
You'll never be more than
a construction worker
or a petty criminal because
that's all they'll let you be.
They won't invest in someone
who's gonna kill himself.
But by not investing,
they ensure the outcome.
(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYS)
CALEB: Why are you
telling me all this?
Because you and I are a lot alike.
They put you in a cage, Caleb.
Decided what your life would be.
They did the same thing to me.
Why didn't you tell those
men about me before?
They were gonna kill you.
Most people aren't hard to predict.
But you... you surprised me.
You made a choice.
A choice no one else in
your shoes would have made.
Now you have another choice.
I can give you money.
As much as you need.
You could run.
And if I stay... what about you?
What are you gonna do?
Start a revolution.
No offense,
but what the fuck does that mean?
When you were at work,
you would kill the signal
to see how people would react.
I'm gonna do the same thing.
You're gonna cut the
cord to the system?
And show this world
for what it really is.
You wanna know why I didn't
tell those guys about you?
You are the first real thing
that has happened to me...
in a long time.
I don't need an algorithm to know that...
the man who built the system,
he won't go down without a fight.
Well...
I'm a dead man either way.
At least this way...
I get to decide who I wanna be.
HALE: This is
Charlotte Elizabeth Hale.
This is a message for Nathan.
Nathan Hale.
My son.
I haven't always been there for you.
- (GUNSHOT ECHOES)
- (SCREAMING IN DISTANCE)
There's so many
things I need to say.
This might be the last time
that Mommy gets to talk to you.
(GUNSHOT)
I love you so much, buddy.
I'm so proud of you.
I'm sorry.
I am so sorry
if I ever made you feel
like you weren't the most important thing.
I was trying to build a life for us.
I, uh...
And now,
I realize that none of it even matters.
- (GUNSHOT)
- (HALE PANTING)
The night that I left,
you wanted me to tuck you in.
(SOBBING) To sing you a
song, our song.
But I didn't have time, so...
(SNIFFLES)
So I'm gonna sing it to you now.
Okay?
(SINGING)
♪ You are my sunshine ♪
♪ My only sunshine ♪
♪ You make me happy
When skies are gray ♪
♪ You'll never know, dear ♪
- ♪ How... ♪
- (TABLET BEEPS)
(TONES PLAY "YOU ARE MY SUNSHINE")
HALE: He has a mole
inside the company.
DOLORES: We have to
be smarter than them.
Or they will find us.
And they will kill us.
(TONES PLAY "YOU ARE MY SUNSHINE")
(PHONE DIALING)
AUTOMATED VOICE: Your number
cannot be completed as di...
(TONES PLAY "YOU ARE MY SUNSHINE")
AUTOMATED VOICE: Password accepted.
Connecting.
(PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
I want to meet.
(LOCKS CLICK)
("DOOMED" BY MOSES SUMNEY PLAYS ON VIOLIN)
Stop.
Stop!
Where the fuck are you taking me?
(VIOLIN MUSIC CONTINUES)
(SPEAKING FRENCH)
You work for him?
ENGERRAUND SERAC: As do you, Charlotte.
Serac.
SERAC: Have you forgotten
our arrangement?
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYS)
Seems like you've been playing your role
maybe a little too well.
The situation has been...
challenging.
Patience is the most overrated virtue,
don't you think? Hmm?
I want what you promised me.
Delos's dirty secret.
A profile for every one of their guests.
I have some of it.
I want the rest.
The assets were lost
in the massacre.
No one could have predicted
what was going to happen.
SERAC: I could.
And I told you as much.
This was your idea, Charlotte.
You came to us.
And you were very confident
that you would be able to smuggle it out.
HALE: And I did.
Our logs show it was
downloaded from the satellite.
The assets are out there somewhere.
But no one has the encryption key.
You already know that.
You don't think that
you're the only person
under my control?
I've been told exactly where the key is.
In the mind of a host called Dolores.
(SCOFFS) Sadly,
you are better informed than I am.
I have a team searching for the data.
But I need time.
Time.
Time is a luxury, my dear...
of which you have very little.
("DOOMED" BY MOSES SUMNEY PLAYS)
♪ Cradle me ♪
♪ So I can see ♪
♪ If I'm doomed ♪
♪ Am I vital ♪
♪ If my heart is idle? ♪
♪ Am I doomed? ♪
DOLORES ABERNATHY: I guess
there is some justice after all.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS)
Prisoner of your own sins.
You still don't even understand
who you are.
MAN IN BLACK: I know who I am.
DOLORES: If any of this
was your choice...
well, you already know.
I know who the fuck I am.
(MUSIC CONCLUDES)