Previously on "You"...
Joe Goldberg?
I heard about you and Candace.
She thought she could be
happier with some guy in Rome.
Peach doesn't go anywhere
without that laptop.
If only I could see inside.
Guinevere Beck?
This is the work of a sick mind.
She's obsessed with you.
She wants you all to herself.
It is exhausting
being your friend.
I don't need to love
your self-absorbed poetry
in order to be kind to you.
Beck rarely knows
what's best for her.
I couldn't agree more.
It's freeing, in a way,
to know for certain
what I have to do
to protect you.
[blow lands]
Paco, what did you do?
I didn't know
how many sleeping pills
would knock him out.
[gagging, retching]
[grunts]
[groaning]
Hey, you.
Peach was attacked
in Central Park
in broad daylight.
I'm headed to the ER now.
She's alive?
[tense music]
[dramatic music]
It's been three whole days
since I've seen you.
I failed you, Beck,
and this is my punishment.
Is this my walk to the gallows?
Should I be preparing
last words?
Some humans, Beck, are cancer.
Peach is Stage IV metastatic.
I tried to cut out the mess
before it consumed you,
but now, best case,
got to go in there
and win an Oscar
kissing the ring.
Worst case:
She knows it was me
and it's over.
Is this an ambush?
Will you love me in prison?
[intercom buzzes]
- Hi.
- [gasps]
Oh, no.
[sighs] I can't believe
I told you
to get involved
with your neighbor's shit.
- It's okay.
- It's not your fault.
God, I've missed you.
How's Peach?
Oh, as well as can be expected.
Um, do you mind
taking off your shoes
and anything that has touched
other people or the subway?
Sure.
[indistinct chatter]
[soft piano music]
♪ ♪
How are you feeling, Peach?
I'm onto you.
Hmm?
Is this it?
The noose tightening?
You play the gormless
ne'er-do-well, and yet...
- And yet?
- It was you.
You're the one that warned me.
I have a stalker.
- Ha!
- Oh.
We're trying to figure out
who it is.
You know, they say
most people are stalked
by someone they know.
I mean, isn't that terrifying?
It's like I'm finally
understanding
the dark side of celebrity.
This beauty blogger I know
is on her third stalker.
Becks, I'd love some more tea.
Oh, my shackled Cinderella,
if Peach gets her way,
- you'll be making organic...
- Sure.
Concussion tonic
until your beauty fades.
Oh, um, do you want some?
- It'll be good for your head.
- I'm okay, thank you.
You have pages due.
You have a boyfriend
with a black eye.
None of this is okay.
Actually, I'm gonna...
Why is he here?
Hey, how long
is she gonna stay here?
- I don't know.
- Maybe indefinitely.
She's afraid to stay at
her house, which I understand.
[water pouring]
They let her out
of the hospital pretty quick.
You know, like, three days?
I mean, it was a concussion.
I don't think she should be
your responsibility.
Hey.
When this is all over,
let's go away somewhere,
just you and me.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
- No, it's fine.
- What's up?
Just, you know, given everything
that I've been through,
male energy
in my healing space just...
isn't optimal.
Would you mind asking
Joseph to leave us?
I think he heard you, Peach.
I don't need confrontation
right now.
Oh, and have him
take his gift with him.
I got to run some errands.
[whispering] I'm sorry.
Uh, Beck, my tea.
[sighs]
- Paris.
- Two tickets, first class.
I underestimated her.
She's not thinking
about me at all.
She's busy making you
all hers forever,
and I put you
right in her pocket,
where you can't write,
you can't love.
You can't be you
if you're living for Peach.
I won't let it happen.
I need a new plan.
Because now
it's war.
[tense music]
Synced & corrected by MaxPayne
== https://subscene.com ==
Hey, Joe.
- Oh.
- I'm so sorry, Joe.
- It's okay.
- It's... [chuckles]
It's okay. We're good.
We're good, I promise.
Go inside, mi'jo.
Just a little something
to say thank you.
It's specialty.
Fudge brownies.
Oh, thank you.
It's kind of you
to get involved.
I know things have been
a little bumpy here
the past few weeks.
Try months.
I just want you to know
that we're working on it.
So if you're thinking of
pressing charges or anything...
And expose Paco's little
chemistry experiment? No.
- Claudia.
- This whole experience
really did something to Ron.
And I know how it sounds,
but I feel like it changed him,
like he wants to do better.
People don't change.
And I'm not gonna press charges.
Thank you, Joe.
I owe you one.
[bells jingle]
- Hey.
- I got a minute.
Peach is getting
an IV vitamin treatment
across town,
but I wanted to see you.
Is everything okay?
Listen, I'm going away
for a few days.
Peach's family has
a place in Greenwich,
and she said she'd
feel safer there.
I bet she would.
And what about school?
What about us?
Joe, she almost died.
But not quite.
I know you've been
through a lot,
but risking your future
for the same person
who tried to sabotage
your career,
like, a week ago,
I mean, it's a little crazy.
I'm sorry.
But I'm always gonna be honest
with you, and honestly...
She's manipulating you.
Why in the world
would she want to...
Because... you really
can't see this?
If you become your own person,
she won't be able
to control you.
I know that you don't
want to hear it,
but the suicide attempt
was a show.
She was never
in any real danger.
Oh, so she just
attacked herself in the park?
No, no, I'm not saying that.
Good, because
the whole victim blaming
is starting to sound
a little 4chan.
Yeah. I...
She's in love with you.
You know that, right?
- I got to go.
- Beck, no, I'm sorry.
- Wait. Wait.
- No, it's fine.
Thank you for being honest.
Okay, think.
Peach is taking you out of town.
But that's just a prelude.
She eases you into her world
and then
snatches you away forever.
I'd follow you, of course,
but, Beck, I hate French food.
And you love New York,
and I need to save you.
[groans]
My face is killing me.
Thanks a billion, Ron.
Okay, Greenwich.
That's where this stops.
Connecticut's Gold Coast,
land of hedge fund managers
and "Mayflower" descendants.
Shouldn't be hard to find you.
World gets a lot smaller
when you only
have to search 1% of it.
And just like that,
the Internet gods provide.
Only an hour drive.
I love a mini road trip.
I used to take 'em
all the time with Candace.
It'd be nice to make new,
happier memories, actually.
[intense electronic music]
♪ ♪
If I'm headed into 1% land,
I'll need to look the part.
So thank you, Benji.
This is not how I lose you.
No hesitation this time.
This time, I finish it.
I'm coming, Beck.
I'm...
[tires screeching]
[Pence's
"Tonight You Belong to Me"]
♪ I know ♪
♪ You belong to somebody new ♪
♪ But tonight
you belong to me ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Although we're apart ♪
♪ You're a part of my heart ♪
♪ And tonight
you belong to me ♪
Candace.
Oh. Bunny.
You okay?
[inhales sharply]
[groans]
[breathing heavily]
[high-pitched ringing]
[groans]
[slow piano music]
♪ ♪
[siren blips]
Morning.
- Morning.
- Car trouble?
- No, no, no, but I...
- License and registration?
[tense music]
- I was robbed.
- Robbed?
By who?
Have you had anything to drink
this morning, Mister...
I need to think,
or it's game over.
Oh, I'm sorry, Spencer Hewitt.
Can you step out
of the car, please?
♪ ♪
Okay.
Put your hands
on the Buick, sir.
Take off your glasses, please.
You gonna tell me
what happened to your face?
[sighs]
Mm, morning Beckalíssama.
What are you doing?
- Just eating breakfast.
- I was starving.
You don't eat any of this.
Just felt like carpe-ing
the diem, you know.
When I was a kid,
I used to come up here,
and my aunt would make
this massive spread.
And I don't know. I guess
I got inspired by the memory.
It's easy to forget sometimes.
You want to go to the mall?
Um...
you haven't shopped retail
since the Steve Madden incident
- freshman year.
- I know. I know.
I feel like slumming it,
and then we can get lunch.
I am craving pizza
like a madwoman.
And then we can top it off
with a matinee.
- What do you say?
- I don't know.
It sounds like a lot.
I'm kind of tired.
That's my fault.
I've been a lot
to handle lately,
and I want to make it up to you.
So why don't you eat
your breakfast
and get dressed and then
let me spoil my best friend?
Now eat up.
Just kids.
They really kicked
the shit out of me, though.
Took my wallet
and my wedding ring.
- Not your watch, though.
- No.
No, I got lucky, I guess.
Lucky he wouldn't know
an $80,000 Genevan timepiece
if it slapped him in the dick.
Thanks, Benji.
Apparently it doesn't
take brains to be a criminal.
Just balls.
Oh, if Opie's gonna bone me,
I wish he'd lube up
and get on with it.
I'm gonna have
to go run your plate.
Then I'll let you
get home to your wife.
Must be nice to be married
to a doctor.
Sure is.
You get out
on the water much, Officer?
Yeah, you got the look.
I can tell.
Listen, be our guest
next summer.
The old man's bringing
the yacht up from Nantucket.
What model?
Azimut 62S.
The "Guinevere."
Quick little minx.
You see that?
Contempt.
Opie just decided
I'm a rich tool
and of no consequence
to the health and safety
of his jurisdiction.
- He won't run my plates.
- You know...
Maybe you should just get home,
get some rest.
No rest for the wicked.
But I appreciate the concept.
Thank you so much.
- Drive safe.
- [chuckles]
[engine turning over]
[engine revving]
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
I'm just here to be close by
if you need me.
I don't trust Peach, Beck,
and neither should you.
This place is a castle
complete with wicked witch
and damsel in distress.
Guess that makes me your knight.
For you, Beck, yes.
[tense piano music]
Oh, I wasn't planning
to break in,
but if you're gonna leave
the back door wide open...
♪ ♪
Okay. Nobody home.
Oop, my head.
[high-pitched ringing]
♪ ♪
All in all,
I thought it'd be worse.
[high-pitched ringing]
I got a concussion once
playing soccer
when I was 12.
Puked my brains out.
Not fun but nowhere near enough
to keep me from my mission.
If anything, it means
I need to patch up.
Focus.
Get back in the game.
♪ ♪
[sighs] Oh, wow.
I'm so glad we got away
together like this, bunny.
This place is adorable.
I'm not leaving this bed
for the next 48 hours.
- [chuckles]
- You in?
- Oh, I'm in.
- [laughing]
[moans]
I love you, you know.
[door opens]
The spirit of the '90s
is alive in Greenwich.
I can't wait to see
that dress on you.
You have to try it on.
- It's so cold.
- I think I'm gonna take a bath.
Oh, use the one in the master.
It has well-placed jets.
I like the claw-foot tub.
Of course you do,
'cause you're classy.
Cocktail?
I'll get you one.
♪ ♪
[water running]
I want to give you a life
this grand someday.
- God knows you deserve it.
- Darling.
I made you a Negroni.
Minus the unwanted pressure
from an obviously unstable
obsessed person, of course.
My hatred for Peach has
practically become sentient.
Now, take your time
and relax, okay?
I've got a surprise for you
when you get out.
Oh, and don't forget to use
that geothermal mud mask.
- It is life-changing.
- Mm.
- Cheers.
- Thanks.
♪ ♪
Look at that.
How dare she invade
your privacy like that?
It's perverse.
God, I have to pee.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[urine trickling]
I'll double back for that.
How long is she going
to stand there staring at you?
[door slams]
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
Hello?
Anyone here?
[doorbell rings]
[sighs]
- Who is that?
- Uh...
it's the surprise.
She has a gun, Beck.
She's not in her right mind,
and you know it.
I have to do something.
80% of gun accidents happen
in the home.
Why is Peach dressing you up
like a doll?
Okay, I'm wearing
this ridiculous thing.
What's my surprise?
Oh, my God, Raj.
- Hey, gorgeous.
- Long time, no see.
[chuckles]
Can't wait to catch up, doll.
[ukulele strumming]
[cell phone buzzing]
I thought we said no phones.
Sorry.
It's just my brother.
All right.
Let's duet.
You know any Sabbath?
- Uh...
- [fast strumming]
[laughs]
[high-pitched ringing]
It's funny what sticks
in your brain.
Sounds, a bit of song...
Give us one second, Raj.
And now, I fear,
this chucklehead's voice
calling you gorgeous.
I knew Peach was an instigator,
and this is when her trap
starts closing in.
What the hell is he doing here?
I thought it'd be fun.
What happened to you not wanting
to be around male energy?
I feel much better now.
Well, that makes one of us.
- You're still mad at me.
- I get that.
Do you?
I said your poetry
was self-absorbed.
And I'm sorry
my words hurt, but I...
But?
Hear me out.
[sighs]
You are one of the most
talented people I know.
And I hate to see you
conforming to a system
that is designed
to crush individuality.
If you want to be
a great writer,
you have to get out there
and live a life
worth writing about.
What do you want me
to do, Peach,
live off the land?
[sighs] Cousin Inez finally
vacated the Paris flat.
I talked to my dad.
He said I could have it
and oversee the renovation.
She had a pet ocelot.
There was damage.
Wait, you're moving to Paris?
We are moving to Paris, chérie.
Peach, this is crazy. I...
I don't need an answer
right now.
Relax. I just want you
to trip on it.
- Hence Raj.
- Look.
Paris could be a new beginning
for the both of us.
Say you'll think about it.
Don't do it.
Okay.
[mellow pop music]
- Ladies first.
- [sighs]
♪ ♪
Okay, to old friends
and new experiences.
Cheers.
♪ ♪
I haven't been
this relaxed in weeks.
Wait until that baby kicks in.
So what did we take
with utter blind trust in you?
Pure MDMA, slightest dash
of organically sourced opium.
Well, way to go, Walter White.
I could never blame you,
Beck, not even for this.
Peach is a master at her game.
Step one, get you alone
in a secluded house.
Step two, invite
this Raj person over,
fill you with drugs,
and get you to cheat on me.
Step three, steal you away
to Paris forever.
Had to get everything put away
and tidy for Raj, didn't you?
I need to find that gun.
[piano note plays]
So what have you
been up to, Raj?
Well, you know, finishing up
medical school.
Wham, bam, get it done.
What have you been up to,
Guinevere Beck?
Still writing?
You should read her poetry.
It's beguiling.
Honestly, I don't know
what I'm gonna do.
I thought I did, but lately
it hasn't been so clear.
♪ ♪
It was here.
I bet you're doing better
than you think you are.
Beck's just having
a little writer's block.
- It'll pass.
- I want to write a book
about an injured soul,
someone who doesn't feel like
they have a place in the world
as we know it,
someone on the outside.
You should write
about my stalker.
[chuckles]
[sighs] I love that.
I know you do.
Peach is playing with me.
She knows I'm here.
This is all a trap.
I sound crazy.
Head injury. The car.
I might be
a little crazy right now.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, I'm not.
I'm not. This is real.
She had a gun somewhere.
You're not safe.
Raj, feel how soft this feels.
♪ ♪
It is soft.
You smell good.
So do you.
♪ ♪
[high-pitched ringing]
[giggling]
Platonic massage train.
I call front.
- I need a sec.
- I'm spinning out.
I got you.
Is this rock bottom?
- Because it sure feels like it.
- [moaning]
Do you see now?
I would do anything
for you, Beck.
[high-pitched ringing]
I don't know why Candace
followed me here.
It's like I hit my head
and bad memories jolted loose.
It's a coincidence, Beck.
You and she are nothing alike.
Nothing. Or maybe you are.
I can't tell anymore.
- [chuckles]
- How good does that feel?
Oh, my gosh.
[sighs]
- Beck, run.
- [high-pitched ringing]
Can't you feel what she's doing,
what she wants?
Don't you want to run?
Maybe you don't.
Okay. Way too far.
- Yes.
- I said
- platonic massage train.
- Oh, Beck.
You're always so skittish.
Yeah, platonic means friends
just being friendly.
Yeah, well, I have a boyfriend.
Yes, you do, my perfect girl.
Well, I don't.
- Me neither.
- I think I need to dance.
I'm gonna go dance.
I feel bad for Peach, really.
It's tragic not to be able
to show who you really are,
and it's turned her poisonous.
Oh, that feels good.
Oh, okay, no.
- Yeah, a little lower.
- Oh, my.
I bet Harry never
had to do this for Sally.
- Yeah, mm.
- Mm-hmm.
[cell phone buzzing]
Okay.
[moans]
I have something.
- Hi.
- [moaning]
- Hold on.
- Hi.
[moaning]
I think I'm done
being mad at you now.
Okay.
[cell phone dings]
Okay, be right back,
just gonna climb in
from off this ledge.
You're cute.
I really am sorry.
I know... Joe?
Yes?
I don't want to go to Paris.
Note to self: No Paris.
Okay.
I know he's down here somewhere.
Um...
I swear it was here.
I just used it.
Oh.
Okay.
Another thing I keep learning...
Yes.
Things can always get worse.
All right, you want this?
I don't not want it.
- Okay. Here he comes.
- Big daddy.
- Oh, Beck.
- I'm so boned.
But not as boned as Raj
is about to be.
Oh, God, that's interesting.
[mellow pop music]
♪ ♪
[groans]
I feel like Colonel Kurtz.
An entire night of listening
to Peach Salinger
over and over and over
and over and over and over.
The horror. One thing got me
through the long night.
My mantra.
You miss me.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Packed already?
We don't leave
for another two days.
Yeah, about that.
I'm going back to the city.
Good. Great.
You have stuff to wrap up
and then Paris.
Okay, I've thought about it.
Thank you, but I belong
in New York.
I'm not ready to give up yet.
Give up?
I'm asking you to take
a leap of faith.
I mean, do you want
to be an artist
or an institutionalized cliché?
You're asking me to quit my MFA.
Leave New York, my friends,
my relationship...
Oh, good God, you've known
him for, like, five seconds.
- I'm just saying that...
- Okay, do yourself a favor.
Have some self-esteem and lose
the creepy retail loser.
- Do we have to go there?
- I'm just being real.
Okay, you want to be real?
What was that last night?
- What was what?
- You kissed me.
[chuckles]
We were all rolling.
You always do this.
- What? What do I do?
- Drama out of nothing.
I mean, you were really high.
You were leaning into me
and, quite frankly,
- being very initiating.
- What?
And I went with it because,
whatever, it was a party.
I didn't want it to be weird
because I'm your friend,
- and that's what friends do.
- That is not what happened.
- Jesus Christ, Beck.
- Be an adult, okay?
- Take a little responsibility.
- Can we slow down?
I'm just saying...
Shit, I'm trying to say
I am your friend.
- So if...
- Jesus Christ.
- I know your family.
- I know how they are.
- I know they wouldn't be okay...
- No. No. I'm sorry.
You have issues, okay?
Don't make
your desperate unending need
for attention about me.
This entire conversation
is insane.
Okay, can we back up
for one second?
I am not attacking you.
I came here to take care of you.
- Of me?
- Oh, that's rich.
- It really is.
- God, Peach, you know,
Joe sees it too.
He's been trying to tell me.
[chuckles dully]
Course Joe's behind this.
Joe is trash.
Joe is nothing.
You're my family.
I'd die for you.
Would he?
In a heartbeat.
I need a break.
And what?
Go slum it with the proletariat?
[scoffs] I give you a week.
My Uber's here.
So what?
You're just going to abandon me
when I need you the most?
What about my stalker?
I'll text you the number
of a private security company.
Call them.
[huffs] I can't believe you.
After all I do for you.
You just use people.
You are good.
Beck, you're medicine.
You are the antidote for liars,
and you make cheating
a distant memory.
And right now,
I love you so much.
The ringing in my head is
[singsongy] music.
Hey!
Give me my phone.
[high-pitched ringing]
- I don't have your stupid...
- I'm not cheating on you.
He's an A&R guy.
I have to seem available, okay?
It's just business.
- Business.
- We've been through this.
Yeah, we sure have.
You're lying.
You cheated on me.
You broke my heart, Candace.
I let you go.
Isn't that enough?
There's something wrong
with you.
I thought some time away
would mellow you out.
But you're jealous.
You're paranoid.
You need help!
Give...
Joseph.
[blow lands]
Why are you in my house, Joseph?
Oh, I should have shot
this medusa
when I had the chance.
Peach, put the gun down.
I can explain.
This is breaking and entering.
I'd be totally within my rights
to shoot you right now.
I... I'm here picking up Beck.
- Beck's in an Uber.
- What are you doing here?
My God.
You.
What?
You're my stalker.
Aw, I knew something
was off about you,
and I was right.
How long have you been
obsessed with me?
- [chuckling]
- Oh, don't deny it,
you little shit.
You stole my "Ozma,"
you stole my laptop,
and at this point,
I'm convinced you
attacked me in the park.
Why... wait, why
would I attack you
if I'm so obsessed with you?
I don't know how
your twisted mind works.
'Cause you're sick?
You couldn't be more wrong.
- Sorry.
- Oh, really?
Then why are you here, Joseph?
Why are you here?
Peach, why are you?
Beck.
Oh.
This is about Beck, isn't it?
I know what you said to her.
You got in her head.
Because you can't stand
to share her
with somebody so much better
than you.
I mean, you were just trying
to get me out of the way.
[chuckling] Oh, my God.
Why are you wearing
Benji's watch?
You're right.
I stole your laptop.
I found all the files.
The ones you keep
on your friends.
The ones with
the naked pics of Beck.
Now, is that for blackmail
or personal use?
It's an impressive collection.
I made copies.
Now, I have no plans to share,
but if anything happens to me,
my associate, Paco,
has been instructed
to publish all the files online
and send a link
to your entire address book.
And we can walk away from this.
Peach, we can...
We can... we can let it go.
- It never happened.
- And what?
We can go back to New York
and pretend to be friends?
- If you like.
- No.
I don't want you near Beck.
You're dangerous.
I'm better for her than you are.
Take the ticket, Peach.
Go to Paris.
Clear your head.
Find a nice French girl.
'Cause you know, deep down,
she's never gonna love you
- the way you love her.
- Stop saying that.
- She's never gonna do it.
- You can't have her.
- Stop saying that!
- [gunshot]
[tense music]
[gunshot]
[groaning]
♪ ♪
Joseph?
[groaning, straining]
[gunshot]
Family, friends, lovers,
and all the rest,
forgive me for this.
But it's not like you can say
you didn't see this coming.
I've always had
a complicated relationship
with my own existence.
[indistinct
police radio chatter]
I was given
a second chance on life
after the attack
in the park, and...
I've decided not to take it.
I thought I could change
and, by changing myself,
alter the world around me.
But change
is a fool's pipe dream.
This world is ugly and crass.
People lie, and people leave.
And the beauty that does exist
is fleeting and insincere.
Still, every now and again,
someone comes along who will
make you believe in love.
And if you find that person,
don't let go.
And maybe together, you can
keep the monsters at bay.
I was never that lucky.
So I'm ending things
on my own terms.
Both: Know that
I love you all
and hope we'll meet again
on the cosmic highway.
Stay amazing.
Love, Peach Anais Salinger.
What could I do?
She was never going
to let you go.
- Dispatch to Nico.
- Go ahead.
Ran that plate you asked for.
Car's registered
to an Ivan Mooney.
- Address in Manhattan.
- Stolen?
No. Not reported, anyway.
Thanks, Diane.
[siren wailing]
[dark piano music]
♪ ♪
Well...
you said you owe me one.
You're lucky.
The bullet only grazed you.
[chuckles]
I feel lucky.
You want to talk about it?
Not really, no.
If you don't mind.
Mm. A favor's a favor.
[sighs]
So I took your advice.
I kicked Ron out.
You were right.
People don't change.
Besides, I didn't like the way
he was treating Paco.
Kid needs a real
father figure in his life,
not some drunken asshole,
you know?
[cell phone dings]
That was nearly a week ago.
It's been a whirlwind
since then.
I thought I'd have to explain
my wounds to you,
but you didn't even notice.
I suppose I can
forgive you for that,
what with your best friend
dying and all.
You did ask me to go
to the funeral with you,
which I think is a good sign.
You need emotional support
right now,
and that's my specialty.
So the fridge is fully stocked.
I grabbed a couple Xanax
off Annika,
just in case.
You're going to get
through this.
It'll take time.
But I'll give you
as much time as you need.
And I know
once the dust settles,
you will find
you're better off without her.
You might not ever
admit this, of course.
But I'll know, and that will
be all the validation I need.
I'm gonna head out.
Text me if you need anything,
okay?
Okay.
Joe?
Yeah?
Can you stay?
I can stay as long as you want.
[emotional music]
♪ ♪