.
[bright tones]
- Previously
on "Good Girls"...
- You better give me
that money, bitch.
- Hey!
- [screams]
- Am I gonna make it?
- Here we go.
This is it.
It's go time.
- You saved her leg.
- I did?
- And how much of my cut
is from Cartier?
- All of it.
- What?
How'd you get insurance
to cover it?
- I tried to seduce
my therapist.
He straight up rejected me.
I want to get better.
- Friday at 8:30.
- I couldn't make as much.
- Why is that?
- The price of ink went up.
- You stole from a man
who blew a little girl's
brains out for fun?
- 10% off the top.
- What if he finds out?
- He won't.
[tense music]
- What's it say?
[percussive music]
♪
- You sure about this?
- ♪ Well, I'm going down
- ♪ Going down
a hard road ♪
- ♪ Just don't know
- ♪ Don't know where
I've been ♪
- Mm.
- Can I get you anything else?
- I think we're probably good.
- What didn't I order?
- Oh, let's see.
Chef's got an ambrosia salad.
- Bingo.
Mm.
- I'm really sorry, Leslie.
- Mm, yeah, thanks.
- Cop railroaded you good, man.
- Oh, yeah.
Lady Justice has got a real
Woodrow for guys like me, hmm?
[laughs]
- Some people
at the store were happy,
but they don't know you
like I do.
- Who?
- Jessie.
- Hmm.
Frozen foods?
- Mm-hmm.
And Marta.
- Seriously?
What's her problem?
- She saw you do
an impression of her
in front of the whole bakery.
- Oh, man.
Before I knew
it was a birth defect!
You know what?
[scoffs]
I can't wait to get out
of this hell hole.
All this woke culture.
- Ambrosia salad?
- Oh, yeah.
- Thanks.
- Dig in.
- I'm keto now.
- Oh.
Yeah, that explains it.
Your fingers look more regular.
- I'm really gonna
miss you, Leslie.
- [clears throat]
Listen.
I...
I need you
to do something for me.
- Name it.
You look great.
- You know what
they'll do to me.
You've seen
the documentaries, right?
- What can I do?
- Your sister still
got that shop?
[melancholic music]
- ♪ Come and take me home
- What do you think?
♪
- I'd add a scorpion
to the pentagram.
- ♪ I'm out in the woods
♪
♪ Said I'm lost
in the woods ♪
♪
♪ Oh
- ♪ Doda koo panga-ma
♪ Doda koo kala
♪ Doda koo panga-oo
♪ Kala shatini
♪ Doda koo panga-ma
- Okay, how many seats
in the House and Senate?
- Hmm, how many seats
on a plane, Josh?
- I have no idea.
- Exactly.
But you fly a lot more than
you pass bills in the Senate.
Am I right?
- Right.
I'm sensing
it's not the material
that's been the problem here.
- So do you have study buddies
over there across the pond?
- Oh, you mean a quiz chap.
- [laughs]
Yeah, yeah.
I've always been a lot more
chap than quiz, you know?
- Hmm, right.
Next subject.
- Josh Cohen.
- No.
- Come on.
You know everything about me.
- That's how this works.
All you, no me.
- Just, like, one little crumb.
Your middle name.
Twitter name.
Porn name?
- Huh, is that pineapple?
- That was mine.
- I just wanted a bite.
- Of my pizza.
There are four other slices.
- Well, I didn't want
a whole piece.
- Yeah, but my mouth
touched that one.
- I'm not following.
- Your mouth touched my mouth.
- I just wanted
to try the pineapple.
- We just kissed, my friend.
- We certainly did not.
- Oh, it is not so certain.
- We should do chemistry.
- Aren't we?
- Never mind.
- Okay, Doc.
You know, you could talk about
transference all you want,
but you just pizza transferred
your tongue into my mouth.
Hard.
And I don't think it was just
about the pineapple.
- I think we're
done for tonight.
- Mm-hmm.
You're the best quiz chap
I ever had.
- Hmm.
Do we look any different?
- Better.
- Older.
- Sexier.
both: [laugh]
- Happy almost anniversary.
- Oh.
- What, now look at this.
- Toaster's broken.
Had to microwave them.
- Mm.
- Harry tried to write a poem
about famous marriages.
- Where is that animal?
- It started
with Bert and Ernie,
and then he went back to sleep.
- Okay, well, we feel loved.
But go wake him up.
Get ready for school.
- Thanks, baby.
- Yeah.
- So what do you wanna do?
- What do you mean?
- Sara said she would babysit
if we wanna go out.
- You trust that child
in our house all alone?
- Okay, so here's
what it is, all right?
I'm gonna rent a Bentley.
- Oh, really?
- Uh-huh.
Convertible, ostrich seats.
- Okay.
- And I'ma drive you up
to Birmingham,
and we're gonna go have dinner
at the Townsend Hotel.
Hmm?
I think that's the place
they got the,
the bourbon that
nobody can get.
Like 70 bucks a glass.
Smells like a forest fire.
- Mm.
- We're gonna get that.
And then when the check comes,
I'ma charge it to the room.
- Oh, we're getting a room now?
- We're gonna get not a room.
Presidential suite.
- Ooh.
- And then, wake up,
breakfast in bed.
Home to the kids by noon.
[serene music]
♪
- You can't afford any of that.
- [sighs]
But we deserve it.
- Let's just go halfsies
on the new hot water heater.
- Hmm, nothing like
a good, hot shower.
- [sighs]
I gotta work anyway.
- Yeah, same.
- What if we
turn it lengthwise?
- It's a square, Annie.
- Is it?
Or is it...
A diamond.
- Okay.
- Take it easy
on my floors, okay?
- I need the practice.
- They're all she has left.
- So what are we gonna do here?
- I made a to-do list.
- That is a battle cry
if I ever heard one.
- [laughs]
She means business.
- Yo, Murderball.
You wanna park it
and join the conversation?
- I hear you just fine.
- Number one.
Gain back his trust.
- How?
- ♪ Softly
Just break it to me softly ♪
♪ Be straight with me
but gently ♪
♪ Tender before you kill me
♪ Pow pow
Bygone boy ♪
- And once we do number one,
then we move on to number two.
- What's number two?
- Get a cut of the money.
No skimming, no stealing.
We'll just earn it.
- Like we used to?
- ♪ What a joke
What a joke you make me ♪
♪ What's a queen to a joker
Tell me ♪
♪ What's a laugh
to a self-destructive me ♪
♪ What's a threat
to a death wish ♪
♪ You're so
♪
[air pump pumping]
- Oh, I talked to my mom.
The kids are great.
I think we should just
leave them there.
- Forever?
- Well, until
we figure this out.
Where are you going?
- I am going
to get our lives back.
- Well, you gotta look
that good to do it?
- You trust me?
[overlapping chatter]
Excuse me.
[electronic music]
♪
- Shouldn't you be
making my money?
- Just here having a drink.
Questions, notes, comments?
- So in sum,
we suck up to the gang leader
who we stole from,
and convince him
to pay us a living wage?
- Which we then use
to pay someone else
to blow his brains out?
- A professional.
Not someone who's gonna
wet himself in my car.
It's all I could come up with
at 4:00 a.m.
on an air mattress.
- Max has that cousin.
[scooter beeping]
- Makes sense on paper.
- Rough day?
- Mm, I've had better.
- Yeah, well, nothing
a good night's sleep won't fix.
- I'd have to have a bed.
- That's a problem.
- Well, the least of them.
- That right?
- I screwed up with my boss.
- Never good.
- I'm still valuable,
though, and he knows it.
And I only did it because
he works me to the bone
and doesn't pay me anything.
- What do you want, Elizabeth?
- Just what's fair.
- Ah, fair.
[laughs]
Yeah, I don't owe you.
It's the other way
around, remember?
- Can't we just go back?
- Well, that's up to you.
- What do you mean?
- Yeah, you gotta earn that.
- Okay.
- Yeah?
- I'll do anything.
- Anything, huh?
- Within reason.
- You still got that minivan?
- Why?
- I might got something
for you.
- My ottoman?
- [laughs]
NO.
[clears throat]
.
- [stammers]
Hey, where are my keys?
- How would I know?
- You know where everything is.
- Look in the fridge.
- I'm not an idiot.
Oh, and Dad is gonna pick
you up from school today.
I have some errands to run.
- Why'd you get in so late?
- I was in therapy.
- At 10:00 at night?
- Well, yeah, it was GED prep.
You know, it's--
Oh, by the way, there's pizza
for you for lunch.
- You had pizza
with your therapist?
- And a couple beers.
So what?
- He's your therapist.
- He's helping me.
It's like a,
like a study buddy.
- Like your last study buddy?
- Okay.
- But instead
of passing dummy algebra,
he got you knocked up with me.
- Have a great day
at school, okay?
- You had to drop out.
Got married, divorced--
- Love you.
- And here we are.
- This does not make you right
about everything, okay?
- Love you.
- Bye.
- I mean, that's
what it has to be.
'Cause we've already
delivered his drugs,
his money, his bodies.
- She even boned him,
for God's sakes.
- What does that have
to do with anything?
- And if he's trying to punish
us, which he most certainly is,
what is the one thing
we're all against?
- Microplastics in the ocean.
- Okay, the one other thing.
- The Rohingya crisis
in Myanmar.
- It's the GED.
She's trying to be up on stuff.
- Okay, why did we
march downtown
for three hours
in the rain last year?
- With the vagina hats on?
- That was for women, Annie.
We're not against women.
- What is every
sane person against?
- Oh.
both: Guns.
- Genetic cloning.
- Oh, I give up, I can't.
- Listen, it doesn't matter
what it is.
If we wanna get rid of him,
we're gonna do it.
- How do we even know
we're in the right place?
- Because the pin thingy
dropped here.
- It is a weird place
to deliver a bunch of guns.
- Maybe they're coming
by helicopter.
- Yeah, or some kind of drone.
- For all we know,
there could be a full convoy
barreling down the road.
- Nope.
Right up there.
[airplane whirring]
- Are you high?
- That's a commercial flight.
- Exactly.
Smart.
Hiding in plain sight.
- You think they're gonna land
a 747 in a wheat field?
- No, a cabbage field.
See, there's way more water.
You know, it's like when
they spray foam on the runway.
You know, it creates--
- For crashing.
- Exactly, but the package
still gets there
whether you crash the--
- Annie Bananey?
Annie Bananey!
[laughs]
Well...
Where do we go?
Let's get going.
This is the car.
Same car, I see.
You might have
to throw down some towels.
[horns honking]
- I mean.
- I know.
- I would have preferred guns.
- Grenades.
Cruise missiles.
- Anything else.
- And what is up
with the living hell
that is etched
all over his face?
- No, it's like
you can't do neo-Nazi
with Santeria and voodoo.
It sends a totally
mixed message.
- It makes sense actually.
- Dude, nothing
on that face makes sense.
- No, I mean the assignment.
'Cause we couldn't take care
of Boomer before,
so now he's gonna
take care of it.
- Why didn't he just have
somebody do it in prison?
- I mean, you know he's got
a whole network
of killers in there.
- Because he is testing us.
If we deliver this "package,"
then we're back in.
- Oh, God.
- Oh, they're looking for him.
- Hang a U-ey.
- Don't hang anything.
- Then what are we gonna say?
- That we didn't see anyone.
- What if they wonder
why we're out here?
- Just three moms out
for the day antiquing.
- Ew.
- What would you like us
to fake be doing?
- Berry picking.
- Fine.
- Way more believable.
- It's berry season.
- Hi, Officer.
- Afternoon, ladies.
- What's going on here?
- Some inmate started
a fire this morning
at Saginaw Correctional.
- Oh, my God.
- Yeah, it's still
a mess up there.
They think a few guys
may have jumped the wall,
so just taking precautions.
- Jeez, well
we appreciate it, Officer.
[radio chatter]
- Your kid's an Arctic Grizzly?
- Travel team.
Schedule's brutal.
- My son's a Bay City Penguin.
- Oh, my gosh.
That's so funny.
We're playing you
in the semi-finals.
I'm Beth, by the way.
Kenny Boland's mom.
- We'll see you on the ice.
[tense music]
♪
- [sighs]
Oh, it is hot in there.
Wait a minute.
That sign is in dollars.
- Well, yeah.
What did you expect?
- Loonies.
- What are you talking about?
- You're supposed
to smuggle me to Canada.
- Says who?
- Your gang leader.
- Okay, first of all,
he's not our gang leader, and--
- His guy on the inside said
that if I lit the fire,
my debt would be paid,
and he'd get me to Canada.
Why?
What did he tell you?
- Same thing.
- Oh.
- We just thought
you'd wanna pee first.
- [sighs]
Ooh.
[chuckles]
Well, man, I wish you would've
asked me five minutes ago
because it's a mess in here.
[groans]
- Oh, Jesus.
- You know what, though?
I am super horny.
Let me just...
[groaning]
- Oh, my God.
- Back--
- Ugh.
- Back in a jiff.
- Unbelievable.
.
- That is deeply stupid.
- It's Boomer.
- Talk about a lamb
to slaughter.
- To be clear--
- I know, I know.
- This is not Mary's
fuzzy, cute, little lamb.
- It's a dirty, mangy, feral--
- Serial raping lamb.
- If anyone deserves it...
- Sorry it took so long.
I've been in solitary
the past few weeks.
- Jesus, why?
What did you do?
- Well, it was more
what was being done to me.
- Can we please go?
- I needed time to heal.
- All right.
- They wanted to make sure I
could pass a solid, you know--
- Let's get back in the bag.
- Come on, move it.
- [stammers]
Oh, I need a favor.
- Are you kidding?
- Look, since
we're still stateside,
I wanna see Nana real quick.
- With that face?
You'll kill her.
- We're all going to
Saskatchewan in a grain truck.
I may never see her again.
And she's getting up there.
- Call her from the road.
- She's in a nursing home.
- Wait, what?
Since when?
- She had a bad fall.
- Well, what happened?
- I don't know.
No one was taking care of her.
I was locked up.
- No.
- He should say goodbye to her.
- She should say goodbye
to him.
- We have a job
to finish, Annie.
- And you-know-who
is not gonna wait.
- Manolo's good people.
He'll wait, right?
He's solid.
He's a solid dude.
- It is her last chance.
- [sighs]
One hour.
Thank you.
- All right, back in the bag.
Go on.
- Deeply stupid.
- You can't just
barge in here, okay?
Why don't you ask that prick
where he put his hands?
'Cause by the way,
he fully knew the rules.
- What's up, y'all?
- Do you mind staying outside?
- Hey.
Wait, are you sixth precinct?
I was 13th.
- 13?
Is that O'Brien?
Is he the captain there?
- Well, I heard he retired.
- I went to academy
with his son.
- Oh, great cop.
- [laughs]
- Will you please tell this guy
he can't just go
through our stuff?
- What's the problem, man?
- Dude said his wife's
earrings got stolen
at some birthday party.
- Don't you need, like,
a warrant or something?
- Well, that's really not how
it works for girls like you.
- [laughs]
- Why don't you bitches
take a seat?
- All right, all right.
Thank you, but I got this.
- Yeah, well, if you need some
help searching those lockers,
man, I'm happy to help.
- Stan--
- I said sit your ass down.
They're over there.
- You have a key?
- Oh.
Here you go.
Now I gotta tell you,
I was at that party,
and there were some
super shady people, so...
- Just keep an eye on them.
- Yeah.
- Why'd you leave the 13th?
- Oh, my man.
You know, the pay isn't
what it used to be.
- Tell me about it.
- Downside here is, what?
A heel to the face.
[laughter]
Hey, listen.
If you or any of the boys
wanna come down,
I'll hook you up
with some bottle service.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, man.
- Appreciate that.
- You got it, man.
All right.
- What the hell was that?
- That was me throwing him
off the trail.
- Our entire haul from
last night is in these lockers.
- You know what?
From now on, nothing but cash.
- I don't need it.
- Okay.
- Maybe we should just cool it
for a while.
- What do you mean?
- We almost got arrested, Stan.
- I can't do that.
- Well, I can't go to jail.
- [sighs]
Ruby and I, we're gonna
be married for 22 years
this Saturday.
- Is that the diamond one
or platinum?
- She wants a water heater.
- Hmm.
I think it might be leather.
- Yeah, I'm not gonna
give my wife an appliance
for our anniversary.
- As long as you got our backs.
- You know I do.
- Hi, what room is
Marion Petersen in?
I'm her grandson, Leslie.
- Let me call you back.
- He's asking where
the package is.
- We're not Amazon Prime.
- How long is this gonna take?
- Just tell him it's en route.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
What do we do?
- I don't know.
- Do we stay?
- Should we run?
- What is going on?
- She's dead.
A week ago.
In her sleep.
- I'm sorry.
In a place where 2/3
of the residents can't walk,
you put the ramp 1/2 mile away
from the main entrance?
What'd I miss?
Where Nana at?
- [whimpering]
.
- She lied, Annie.
- For months.
- And she chose him over you.
- And she's kind of racist.
- She's mostly racist.
- She was here because
she fell on ice.
- So?
- She was going to the salon.
- It could have
happened anywhere.
- I used to take her there.
- All right.
- Okay.
- Let's roll.
Hold Nana, would you?
She always liked you.
Here.
- What's this?
- Her final wish.
- Lake Okoboji?
- Yeah, that's where
she wants to be scattered.
By the waterfall.
- That's beautiful.
- That's three hours away.
- It's where she married
Grandpa John.
- We don't have time
for this, okay?
- No, I gotta see it through.
- Look.
She's a wonderful lady
and whatever,
but we gotta get you to--
- Canada.
- Yeah, right.
- I'm not going.
- Yeah, you are.
- No, I'm not.
- We don't answer to you.
- Yeah, we answer to someone
way scarier than you.
- Why does that guy
give a turd where I go, huh?
You know what?
Thanks for the ride.
You're off the hook.
- Uh-uh.
No way.
- Annie, I dig your new hair.
- Not really new.
- Well, I like that you
let the roots grow out.
Hey, hey.
- Beth.
- Hey.
Turn off the child locks.
- Beth, what are you doing?
- Give me Nana back!
- Get back in the bag.
- No, don't.
- Get back in the bag, Boomer.
- If we didn't have
enough reasons to go to hell.
- I swear to God this will be
her final resting place.
- Beth, don't!
- Oh, she's gonna go so well
with all this old people stuff.
- Please--
- Leftover prunes,
lots of wound care,
and honestly,
I don't know if this goo is
from sponge baths
or just straight up phlegm.
- No!
- Don't!
- You will never be able
to siphon her out of this ooze.
- Okay.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
- Put him in.
- We're not going
to Canada, are we?
- What's going on
with you and my mom?
- Sorry, who are you?
- How many other moms
see a kid shrink?
- Oh.
Hello, Ben.
- She thinks you care
about her.
- I, um--
I care about all my patients.
- So you drink beer
late at night with all of them?
- Well, most are in bed
by 8:00, so--
- Maybe you haven't gotten to
this part in your sessions yet
or whatever, but let me
break it down for you.
She's really into you, okay?
Like, the only reason
she's doing any of this stuff
is, like, to impress you
or something.
- Okay, look, it's natural
to worry about your mom--
- I just know her.
- Well...
Rest assured, we're trying
to work on these issues.
- Okay, but when she realizes
that you're "working on issues"
and not in love with her,
she's gonna get in bed
for three months,
eat a whole lot
of mac and cheese,
stop waxing,
stop paying the bills,
stop making my lunches.
And forget
about this GED thing.
- I, um--
I hear what you're saying.
- Good, 'cause if you don't,
I have ways to turn those
five star Yelp reviews
into one-ers.
- Yelp terrorist, eh?
- Freedom fighter.
- Definitely your mom's son.
Oh, but how are you
getting home?
- I rode my bike.
[somber music]
♪
- Is this it?
- Oh, God.
Oh, God.
Who's got Nana?
- I do.
- Sorry, who's talking?
- [sighs]
It's me, Boomer.
- Annie. Annie.
You gotta listen to me, okay?
I know you hate me.
But I also know
you loved my Nana.
- Just stop talking.
- She wouldn't have made it
as long as she did without you.
So I need you
to take care of her now, okay?
And do what
she wanted, okay?
Annie?
I need you to say "Okay."
Annie, can you hear me?
Can you hear me?
- Hockey bag in the trunk.
- Pop it.
- No, please, please.
Please, just--
Please say something!
Just, anything, Annie!
Waterfall, south
of the Makinac Bridge.
They got married at sunset.
- [stammers]
No, please, please.
Annie, I need you to promise.
Annie!
Please! Oh, please.
Okay, please, please?
- Stop.
- Whoever is carrying me,
I'll do whatever you want.
- You don't have
to do this again.
- We're all good now.
- It's basic management, right?
The best employee,
the most loyal,
they're the ones
who get a second chance.
- That's why you're back
on payroll.
12% off the top.
- I don't mean me.
- Guys, where
are you taking me?
Can someone just tell me
where you're taking me?
- Oh, him.
Yeah, I got
different plans for him.
- Ow! Don't throw
me around, at least, okay?
Could you be
a little bit more responsible?
[groans fearfully]
.
- ♪ Salt and Pepa's here
♪ Salt, salt, salt, salt
Salt and Pepa's here ♪
- Ah.
- ♪ Salt and Pep, Salt and Pep,
Salt and Pepa's here ♪
♪ Salt, salt, salt, salt
- ♪ Now, now, now, now
Wait a minute, y'all ♪
♪ This dance ain't
for everybody ♪
♪ Only the sexy people
♪ So all you fly brothers,
get on out there and dance ♪
♪ Dance, I said
- ♪ Salt and Pepa's here,
and we're in effect ♪
♪ Want you to push it, babe
♪ Coolin' by days
and at night ♪
both: ♪ Working up a sweat
- ♪ C'mon girls,
let's go show the guys that ♪
both: ♪ We know
♪ How to become number one
in a hot, hot show ♪
♪ Now push it
Ah, push it, push it good ♪
♪ Ah, push it
- ♪ Push it real good
both: ♪ Ah, push it,
push it good ♪
♪ Ah, push it
- ♪ P-push it real good
- Ah!
Happy anniversary, babe.
both: [laugh]
- Where did you rent this?
- Bought it.
- Wait, what?
- Club Hill, open for business!
[vocalizing]
♪ Ooh, baby, baby
Baby, baby ♪
♪ Baby, baby
Ooh, baby ♪
[sighs]
Happy anniversary.
- What is that?
- It's an upgrade.
- Real?
- 100%.
- Wow.
- What do you think?
- I think you're in over your
head at these private parties.
- Try it on.
- You coming up like that?
- Try it on, baby.
- No.
- No?
It doesn't feel right.
- 'Cause that matters now?
- You were just giving me grief
about how I slept at night.
- So?
- So why don't you
check yourself?
- Excuse me?
You opened this door.
- Swag money?
A professional karaoke machine?
That boulder--
- And then you opened it again.
You opened it again, and then
you bashed down the damn wall.
- One of us has to be good!
Why, hmm?
- What do you mean, why?
- All my life,
I've been swimming upstream.
Fighting it.
And you know what
that gets you?
That doesn't get you respect.
It doesn't get you a badge.
It doesn't get you
a proper wedding ring.
It just gets you tired.
And then you get washed
right back down again.
[Salt-N-Pepa's
"Push It" playing]
- Baby, I'm not wearing that.
- I'm not returning it.
- ♪ Baby, baby
♪ Ooh, baby, baby
♪ Ba-baby, baby
- ♪ Pick up on this
- How do I look?
- [stammers]
Like a girl?
- Hmm.
Anything on my teeth?
- Is that important?
- Very.
- Okay, well then,
a little right here.
- Here?
[clicks tongue]
Good looking out, Tim-ster.
[door unlocks]
- Annie.
- Ah.
Wish me luck.
Hey, so we can totally skip
the rest of government
because I watched this
mini-series last night
on John Adams, which was way
too long and extremely boring.
But it pretty much...
Covered everything.
Sorry, did I get
the wrong time?
- Before we get started,
I wanted to introduce you
to Lila.
- Hello.
- What's up?
- Lila's a teacher.
- Sixth grade.
- Very cool.
- And she's also American,
so she has a much firmer grasp
on your people's
sordid history.
both: [laugh]
- Oh, and by the way,
I think it's awesome that
you're getting your diploma.
- Oh, thanks.
- It's never too late.
- I thought you could use
a real tutor.
- I thought we were
making progress.
- Well, it's better this way.
Don't you think?
- I don't know what to think.
- Well, that's what
I'm here for.
He'll give you my number.
I'll see you at home.
- Okay.
- Bye.
- Bye-bye.
- Oh, okay.
All right, why don't we start
with what's
bothering you today?
♪
- ♪ Ba, ba, ba
ba, ba, ba, ba ♪
♪ Ba, ba, ba, ba
Chairs were on sale.
Just have to put them together.
I figured the kids could do it
when they get back.
Getting a jump, huh?
- Look at this.
- Is that our anniversary?
- No.
Valentine's Day.
Three years ago.
- Oh, with the sitter
who yelled at us
for coming home too late.
- We got sitter-shamed.
- Uh-huh.
We should shut down
more bars together.
Like, in general.
- Yeah.
We're real good at it.
- I can't remember the
last time I had that much fun.
- And you wore jeans.
- So?
- It wasn't that dress.
- I didn't need anything
from you.
- I really wish you did.
- It's just a dress, Dean.
- Well, I'll start
on the chairs.
[Erin Rae's
"As We Go Along" playing]
♪
- ♪ I can tell by your face
♪ That you're looking
to find a place ♪
♪ To settle your mind
♪ And reveal who you are
♪ And you shouldn't be shy
♪ For I'm not gonna try
♪ To hurt you or heal you
♪ Or steal your star
♪
- [laughing]
[crying]
- ♪ Open your eyes
♪ Get up off your chair
♪ There's so much to do
in the sunlight ♪
♪ Give up your secrets
♪ And let down your hair
♪ And sit with me here
by the firelight ♪
♪
- Third one this month
out of Detroit.
Labs came back.
Butyl acetate,
chromium oxide, and camphor.
Car paint?
- Or nail polish.
- Ew.
- It's a woman.
[ethereal music]
♪
[bright tones]