(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
Motherfucker!
- (GRUNTS)
- (SPLASHES)
I just got rid of the last.
Thank fuckin' Christ.
I drove up to Connecticut.
Good. The rump roast
went in down the shore.
So the barbecue over in
Sheepshead Bay... that still a go?
You know I'm not really sure
where the big guy left that.
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(BRAKES SQUEAK)
(ENGINE STOPS)
(GIGGLES)
This way, sweetheart. There's something
I need to get straight between us.
(BOTH GIGGLE)
Seriously, you look
beautiful tonight.
(CAR ALARMS BLARING)
(MOANING, GRUNTING)
(ICE RATTLING)
(CELL PHONE
BEEPS)
Yeah.
(EMERGENCY SIRENS WAILING)
It's done. Listen.
Gee, sounds like
a real weenie roast.
Hey, your friend the Shah
was walkin' in when it happened.
Him and some skifusa got
blown back on their keisters.
(LAUGHING)
...and last, transfer of the deed
to Jamba Juice.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
I'll meet you out front.
Listen, I just wanted
to apologize.
That night...
it's just I make it
a policy not to mix business...
No apology necessary, seriously.
Good, 'cause the truth is
I haven't been able to forget about you
and it ain't like
I haven't been tryin'.
So, you free for dinner?
Maybe?
Thanks, but I think I'll pass.
Congratulations
on the sale, though.
"Morning Sunshine,"
Benjamin Moore.
And we can do the borders
with the Disney characters.
Makes me nervous, this stuff.
We should wait to decorate
till after the baby's born.
Again with the superstitions?
Remember the penguin movie,
how you cried?
You sit on an egg for months,
one little thing goes wrong,
you're left with nothing.
Honey, I'm not Adrianna.
I'm healthy.
Our baby's healthy.
Stop worrying
and enjoy this time, okay?
I am. Let's just stop countin'
the chickens.
Any anesthesiologist, dial 5248.
Workin' man get off okay?
He was gone
by the time I got up.
Used to be he wasn't
home by the time you got up.
What's the matter?
Liz La Cerva tried
to commit suicide. Pills.
(SIGHS)
What'd she do that for?
Apparently she got a letter for Ade
from the Salvation Army.
- Ade's homeless?
- She made a donation every year
to feed the homeless
on Thanksgiving.
The letter set
Liz off, evidently.
Look, I gotta say I commiserate
with the woman, but...
She thinks her daughter is dead.
I told you I had another dream
about Ade in Paris.
A French policeman told me
she was dead and I had to tell her.
I know, Carm.
Pepe Le Pew...
Doesn't change the fact
that Adrianna is missing.
It also doesn't change
the fact that her mother's a bitter lush
- who can't accept reality.
- What reality?
That her daughter couldn't stand her
so she moved away.
That's what you
say to me two weeks
after our own daughter
moves away to California.
Oh come on, will you stop?
It's a different situation entirely.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
It's just...
it's just everything
all at once.
What everything?
The holidays are coming
and my spec house has gone to shit.
Well, A.J.'s got a job.
He's doing better.
You raised two gorgeous kids.
You got a husband
that loves you.
You made us a beautiful home.
Doesn't that count
for something?
Come on.
(TONY HUMMING)
Not exactly a Thanksgiving Day
classic here, Ed...
- (THUDS)
- (CHUCKLING)
The fuck?
Come on, cut it out.
He's already talkin'
like a real construction worker.
Yeah, funny. See how you like
working out in the cold.
Go check on the bird.
Bring back some onion dip too.
So how's your bird these days?
What the fuck
are you talkin' about?
Come on, clandestine
phone calls...
I know you got a new goomar.
- What can I say, huh?
- With a pregnant wife at home.
Your timing is
fuckin' priceless.
Playground's closed.
A man has his needs.
Good point. When Carmela had
her spec house,
I can't tell you how many nights
I had to fend for myself
while she was out lookin'
at bathroom fixtures.
So this new one... how come
you don't bring her around?
Honestly I would but...
between us, she's black.
- Oh!
- You're bangin' a shine?
She's hot too.
Classy.
Not that it
would matter to Paulie.
I'd still have to listen
to all his racial bullshit.
Yeah.
She would feel it too.
Hey, Uncle Paulie.
The fuck you doin'?
There's my girl.
Come here. Gimme that cheek.
(SMOOCHES)
I got your check.
She a doll or what?
Blanca.
Hi. I'm Anthony.
(CELL RINGING)
Yeah. I just did
your paperwork.
- You live in Jersey?
- Hello.
My urologist.
I gotta take this.
Soprano!
(MOANING)
(SIGHING)
I would've cleaned up
if you gave me a minute.
You started it.
Seriously, I'm sorry
it's such a pigsty.
I just work a lot and I'm a pig.
Gonna get a tree in here?
I come from Hanukkah people,
but it doesn't do a lot for me.
So Christmas Eve's
just another day to you?
Actually, we usually go to some
incredibly shitty movie.
There's nothin' else
to choose from.
Makes me worried
about my project.
- You ruined my dress.
- Save it.
Like Monica Lewinsky.
Show your friends
how hard you made me come.
Mmm.
What are we doing here, huh?
I don't know.
Can't stop thinkin'
about fucking you all the time.
How can you even like a person
who sleeps with a married guy?
Can we not talk about it?
I rushed in with her.
I thought I wanted it.
You do.
And you're not
giving it a chance.
You'll see eventually
you'll want kids.
It'll be good.
I don't want a family with her.
She's got no idea who I am.
She "doesn't understand you"?
As we know, Phil asked me
to arrange this meeting
after the fire in his wire room.
Correction.
You asked me to fuckin' attend.
- I agreed.
- Fair enough.
Now I won't call it
a sit-down because
of the inclement
negative implications.
Let's think of it as...
a meeting of minds.
Now for whatever reason,
certain incidents
have expired lately that in addition
to being dangerous
could have an adverse impact
on our respective bottom lines.
I know Vito's bottom was impacted
if that's what you're referring to.
Call him what you will, but you're
talkin' about one of my captains.
Captain?
The Good Ship Lollipop, right?
- Phil, please.
- Please, my ass.
The man was a fuckin' disgrace.
Well, before he came
out of the closet
he worked for me.
And he put
a lot of money in my pocket.
And yours too.
Talk about earners?
How about Fat Dom Gamiello?
- What about him?
- He's MIA.
A lot of people are concerned
for his well-being.
So what the fuck
would I know about that?
Well, as coincidence would have it,
he was last seen in New Jersey.
So was the Hindenburg.
Maybe you wanna look into that too.
Tony, please.
Phil.
We're getting off point.
I grew up in this, guys.
And I just lost
my friend, Rusty,
and for reasons
I will discern in time, believe me.
If there's one thing
my father taught me it's this...
a pint of blood costs more
than a gallon of gold.
My business,
all of our businesses...
this infighting's costing money.
I'm willing to move forward,
let the past be bygones.
- Fine with me.
- A wise decision
on both your parts.
Now what I'd love
to see is a truce.
Wipe the slate clean.
The no-shows, the wire room, Vito...
put it all behind us.
Yeah.
Your brother Billy,
whatever happened there...
- All right then.
- "Whatever happened there?"
- The shooting.
- God rest his soul, huh?
- I'll tell you what fuckin' happened.
This piece of shit's cousin
- put six bullets in the kid...
- Calm down, Phil.
...without any
provocation whatsoever!
- My cousin's dead.
- Fuck you!
Phil, we were making headway here.
I didn't mean to say...
Fuck what you meant, cocksucker!
Come on.
Jesus Christ, Carmine.
What the fuck?
Why would you possibly
bring that up?
(DOOR SLAMS)
He's holdin' the board,
looking the other way.
So the nail gun goes off, bam!
Right through the dude's cheek.
Oh, fuck.
- Passaic.
- What?
Where I live.
You asked me.
Right.
Why you ask me that?
You gonna come over, take me on a date?
Yeah, absolutely.
I got a son, Hector.
He's three.
Ah, that's cool.
You're gonna call me, right?
Hey... there's
only six numbers.
I left the last one off.
You wanna find me,
you're gonna have to work for it.
You have an
emergency call on two.
Oh my God.
Pop?
Guess who.
- That's not funny.
- Had to get your attention.
Well you had my attention. Now you're
wasting my time. I have to go.
Hold on. You got a warehouse
listed on Panama
that used to be a uniform supply.
What's the asking?
Three and a quarter.
Can I go now?
I was driving by.
I thought it had some potential.
But it's really
9,400 square feet
of leaky tarpaper roofs
and clotted galvanized plumbing
and no foot traffic to speak of.
Ease up on the hard sell there.
I'm thinking...
you get the seller to knock something
meaningful off the asking,
I fix it, you flip it.
Look, whatever happened, we did
make some money together, right?
- You serious about this?
- Oh, you never do shit like that?
I'll get back to you.
I was up for anything.
He signed the escrow papers
and I'm not sure what happened
but he... left.
It was so fucking humiliating...
and I was so worked up. I just
needed to smooth it out.
So there's the Cristal.
I mean it could've been
worse, given my history.
It could've been junk.
Julie, right?
- Julianna.
- Christopher.
I liked your share
in there, seriously.
I'm glad...
or sorry I guess.
Got a similar situation
with my job.
I really get that rush
when it's working.
I don't think I've ever heard you
share in there.
Not a judgment, by the way.
You learn as much from others.
I split my time at NA too.
Junk's another thing, huh?
Tell me about it.
- You look familiar.
- Pork store there, Satriale's.
Oh, right.
Wow, cool.
So I guess I'll see you.
Or maybe next week, here.
Wait. You wanna go
for coffee?
Well... okay.
Wanna follow me
to that dive on Sip and JFK?
(PANTING)
(PHONE RINGING)
For some people,
depression is a form
of forced introversion.
And in Lincoln's case,
it was extremely painful.
But it's out of that forced
introversion
- that comes the Abraham Lincoln...
- Where you been?
Linda Merola's.
...who's the successful president.
I left you a message.
The annual Christmas toy drive.
- How was it?
- It was nice. We gave an XBox.
So, Stan Klimik was there.
Ruth's husband?
He works for Kroll.
The private eyes?
He does their computers.
Anyway, I was
telling him about Ade
and he said we should
hire professionals
- to track her down.
- Carm...
It's not as expensive
as you might think, Tony.
He gave me his card.
Look, it's not about the money.
Did you ever think that maybe it's
an intrusion into Ade's personal life?
But what if she's
in trouble, Tony?
Stan said they had
this case once...
this guy ran out
on his child support.
He was a hiking enthusiast,
missing 12 years
and they tracked him down to a watering
station in the Mojave Desert.
(SLOW ROCK PLAYING)
Carmela's spec house? I need you to go
lean on that building inspector.
- Leave it alone, you said.
- Do it today, for all our sakes.
My wife needs a career.
Tony, hey.
Season's greetings.
Good holidays
to your family, huh?
Yeah, you too.
- (DISTANT SIRENS RINGING)
- (WATER DRIPPING)
Well, it's bigger
than I thought.
I got close with a developer who thought
he could do apartments,
some light retail, but we snagged
on some zoning issues.
Let me worry about that.
So who's this fiancé
you were telling me about?
Jesus, what the fuck
do you want here?
- Just move on, huh?
- I was confused, okay?
- I'm not now.
- What a coincidence,
'cause that's exactly
how I feel.
Take all the time you need.
Just stick it in the lock box.
(DOG BARKING)
(SIGHS)
It's only the latest draft.
Guy who wrote it...
I met him at a meeting.
JT Dolan, big user.
You can tell.
It's relentless.
Yeah, it's a work in progress.
I didn't mean it like that.
There's a lot in it.
Are you sure
about the title, "Cleaver"?
The Jerry Mathers connection?
Rules of success
for pictures like this?
One-word titles...
"Saw," "Hostel," "Cleaver."
But Michael... he knows
it's the boss right away?
You might want to make
more of a mystery out of it.
Maybe.
This boss,
he's a really rough...
is Anthony Soprano like that?
He's just a jumping-off point
for the character.
He's got some similarness.
Like he thinks everything's his.
But it's not.
I can't get into it
but there are some rules.
Thank you. Don't get into it.
I don't wanna know.
It's just weird, you know?
Being where he's been.
He hasn't been anywhere.
Nothing happened.
I told you that.
Don't matter.
He's been there in his mind.
Ugh. Fine.
You're right. Guy's got a lot more
on his mind than this.
Like whether or not to have
that third sandwich.
I'm not a fucking parking spot.
Ow.
Don't get me wrong,
I loved Dom more than anybody.
My point is we don't know
if Tony was behind this.
It was payback for Vito.
So why the fuck did they blow up
the wire room?
The balls on this prick.
To blow up a store...
you call that balls?
Balls is you look
a guy in the eye
while you jam an ice pick
through his lung.
I meant balls
as in "nerve," "gall."
I know what the fuck you meant.
Far as I'm concerned,
this is like 9-11.
Tony wanted
our attention. Fine.
He got our attention.
Now we wipe him off the planet.
You know that fat cocksucker says
I look like the Shah of Iran?
- Who does?
- Tony.
- I never got that at all.
- Fat piece of shit.
It's irrelevant, Phil.
But he's testin' you all the time.
And you keep indulging him.
You're right.
But whack a boss?
I won't do that.
- It's been done before.
- And it was wrong then.
Eye for an eye then, huh?
Pick somebody over there.
(TRAIN HORN BLOWING)
White trash motherfuckers
in Narcotics Anonymous...
fucking "Jerry Springer Show."
The fuck with
your whining tonight?
Listen... been involved
with this girl.
In there... that's
the place to share.
It's complicated.
Remember that real estate agent Tony
was dealing with? The Jewish one?
Fuckin' A. He planted
the flag. I'd back off.
No, he didn't do shit, she said.
He wanted to and
then never pulled the trigger.
Okay, it's touchy but okay.
I don't know if it's okay but fuck him
and what he don't know, you know?
So what's the problem?
She's in recovery.
Junk.
Her? Fuckin' movie
of the week.
Listen to me.
That last run you went on,
beginning with the feast? How hard you
had to work to get back from that?
Civilians... their bosses
find out they slipped,
they get a plane ticket
to Minnesota.
Tony will fuckin' mulch his roses
with what's left of you.
She's solid now.
Years sober.
We fuckin' met at a meeting.
- That never happens to me.
- That's all you got to say?
Schools of thought...
two of you together could be enabling.
Bad habits shared.
But it's more like
she knows how bad it is.
We watch out for each other.
She wouldn't even
let me have Red Bull. Seriously.
Well, that's the other school...
two are stronger than one.
I know I'm different with her.
Well, I guess we just
keep an eye on it.
You fuckin' lucky cocksucker.
- Another married man?
- I know.
And it gets worse.
I think he's connected.
To what?
- The mafia.
- No...
But... actually I know he is because
I was involved with his boss.
You ever hear of
Anthony Soprano?
I'm sorry, Jules. I don't even know
where to fucking start.
I know, I know.
The stupid thing is
he's sweet.
He's good to me.
I want you to listen
to this very carefully...
I'm your sponsor. I'm not judging you.
I'm not disappointed.
I am concerned and I'm here
to help you help yourself.
Unlike you, I've lived
in North Jersey my whole life
and those people
like his boss...
they are sociopaths.
Murderers actually.
I know, Ame, but I think you're getting
a little carried away.
Don't hug me.
On top of everything I'm getting a cold.
Cock...!
...sucker
motherfucker!
You shit asshole!
I hate you!
This man is so lame.
(RAP MUSIC PLAYING)
Shit.
- What's wrong?
- These assholes again.
They wake up the baby.
(KID LAUGHS)
Shh! My baby's
sleeping.
Why don't you come out here
and suck our dick?
Hey, what's this asshole's
problem?
My ex used to go down
and kick their asses, but...
(METAL CLANGING)
now they're back.
(BABY CRIES)
Okay, papi.
It's all right.
It's all right, baby.
(SIGHS)
(BABY CRYING)
Shh.
Fuckwads.
(RAP BLARING)
Look, you guys move.
Go hang somewhere else,
I'll give you this bike.
It's a Gary Fisher.
It's only a year old.
My parents gave it to me last Christmas.
All right.
(PANTING)
It doesn't bother you
that I'm younger than you are?
You know who was born
on your birthday? Jesse Ventura.
Who?
(SHE LAUGHS)
He's a famous politician.
I looked it up.
How do you know my birthday?
I did your W-4, remember?
The withholding?
You sure it don't
bother you I have a baby?
No, I love kids.
This is fuckin' ridiculous.
You're not goin' no place.
- I want to.
- We can watch a DVD.
I got the 50 Cent movie
down in my trunk.
They were giving it away
at the car wash.
Don't talk.
That's it.
You're fuckin' grounded.
Lie down.
I'm gonna go down the pharmacy,
get some Robitussin.
No! It's got
dextromethorphan.
What are you gonna do? Rip your
fuckin' lungs out? This is crazy.
You certainly seem very anxious
to get cough medicine in here.
I resent that.
Fuck it! It's over the counter.
How much shit could be in it?
Umh-um.
Maybe you could get
some valerian tea.
You put eight, nine,
10 tea bags in a cup.
- Fuck's that gonna do?
- It's equal to like taking a Valium.
- I didn't know that.
- Same chemical family.
Gotta have some cough
suppressant value, right?
Worst-case scenario,
it might help you sleep at least.
What do you think?
Valerian tea.
You have to go to
the health food store.
Jesus Christ, they didn't teach you
how to use a pair of pliers yet?
Oh it smells
all Christmassy in here.
Yeah.
(SIGHS)
Come on.
Oh, the Russos...
picture of their dogs.
It's sad with no children.
Oh my God!
The Building Department.
They're repealing the stop-work
order on my spec house!
"Construction
may begin immediately."
Tony, is this you? This is the best
Christmas present I could ever get!
Oh, I better return that vacuum
I got you then.
So, Christmas Eve...
besides the shrimp,
- I told DeSanto the cherrystones.
- Fine, good.
You sure? 'cause last year
you said the cherrystones were chewy.
The littlenecks then.
Jesus! Ebenezer Scrooge
over here.
So stop breakin' my balls
about clams. I don't feel good.
The Soft Scrub, lemon-scented.
You're cool as a cucumber.
Did I say I'm hot?
I got a tightness
in my chest up by the esophagus.
Well, you just had
a checkup, Phil.
Yeah.
Imagine the Christmas Marie
and the kids'll be having
after all that with Vito?
The DiBellas too.
Catherine's stroke?
Remember last year
at my mother's house?
Francesca Spatafore did that beautiful
solo of "O Holy Night"?
Vito accompanied her
on the piano?
I gotta try and take a shit.
Now, when one is having a heart attack,
the body releases proteins
that act as markers
which we would detect in the blood.
You don't show any, sir.
- So, his heart is fine?
- Yep.
- (SIGHS)
- Jesus Christ.
Mr. Leotardo, some people
would pay millions for that diagnosis.
- So what the hell's wrong with me?
- My guess is simple gas.
I always say
he's full of hot air.
Pharmacy's down the hall.
They will give you some antacid.
Take care.
Arrogant prick.
Nervous Nellie.
That's what you are.
I'm so sorry.
This asshole Wall Street couple
came back to look
at this loft space.
- (EXHALES)
- MMM.
(GASPING)
- I'm dyin'. My heart!
- Oh my God!
- (ELEVATOR DOOR OPENS)
- (PHIL GRUNTING)
Okay, we're here.
We're here.
It's all right, it's all right.
It's okay. Don't worry about it.
Help! My husband.
- Phil!
- Crash cart!
Can I get a crash cart?
Crash cart!
(POP MUSIC PLAYING)
Heh, I fucked a girl
wearing a Santa hat once.
It was too distracting.
I kept losin' my hard-on.
Hey Ton'.
Did you hear?
Phil Leotardo took a heart attack,
a big one apparently.
Ho! So there is
a Santa Claus.
He's in Intensive Care over in
Brooklyn. Doesn't look too good.
Sweetheart, drinks all around.
And a club soda
for the messenger here.
You're happy about this, T?
Why not? He's a pain
in my balls.
A manageable pain though, eh?
The devil you know...
After the scene
at Little Carmine's?
Corrado, don't you have nothing?
You can make a hand turkey.
For Christmas?
Fuckin' idiot.
Visitor for
Mr. Soprano.
Bobby!
Any of you know
what "bacala" is?
Of course you don't.
Well, it's salted cod.
We taught the world how to eat.
Junior, sit.
Happy holidays, huh?
You smell the piss
in this place?
I ain't gonna stay too long.
Just to say you
should keep this.
- What's that?
- You had Beppe drop it by, remember?
Had a Post-it?
It said "Merry Christmas"?
It's a gift.
It's a little something
for you and Karen and the kids.
It wouldn't be right.
I mean, frankly I shouldn't be here
after what happened with Tony.
He's still up on his cross, huh?
Junior, you shot him.
Yeah, well it's not that simple.
I know a few things you don't.
Like maybe I wasn't
acting alone.
Junior, JFK was 40 years ago.
That's all I'll say about that.
You see that one over there?
An attorney.
I'm mounting my case.
Look, I should take off.
You want a snack?
A soda?
What the fuck?
You just got here.
Happy holidays.
Here.
One hand washes the other.
So the husband says,
"I wasn't talkin' to you."
(LAUGHING)
You know her?
Oh that's right, you and her...
- How'd that all go?
- I had to put her on the shelf.
Yeah, she's a friend of Kaisha,
the black one I was tellin' you about.
She was just now asking
what to get Kaisha for her birthday.
What'd you tell her?
Luther Vandross, a box set.
(SNIFFS)
Mmm.
You know what's interesting?
Hmm?
Us being able to use again,
but integrating it
into our lives.
Yeah.
Work...
socialize...
but still having a mastery.
Not easy.
But interesting as shit.
For one thing,
we don't use needles.
I should probably tell
Tony we're fucking.
What?
We're not anymore.
He's already hinky.
He starts pokin' around,
finds out we met in AA,
he could suspect
I'm usin' again...
Hmm.
...and ruin everything.
(RETCHES)
There he is.
Where the fuck you been?
You hear that Phil
had surgery now?
Turds in the aorta...
a medical first.
Gotta see my chiropodist.
T...
there's something
I should tell you.
- The real estate agent.
- Yeah?
I've been bangin' her.
See, I knew some shit
was goin' on.
Why the fuck did you lie to me?
I wasn't sure
how it ended with you two
till you set me straight.
Stupid, right?
Point is I want
everything above boards
as always between you and me.
I don't give a fuck.
Do what you want with her.
- This is my reward.
- Your reward.
I do not betray my wife.
I go out of my way
not to have an affair with this woman,
this very hot,
very beautiful,
intelligent woman...
'cause of the way Carmela
nursed me and cared for me.
And my fuckin' turkey-neck
of a nephew
winds up with his dick in there.
A guy I gotta see every day.
This is my reward.
Frankly, I'm encouraged.
With the fuckin' riddles again.
I sat here dreading
the end of the story
would involve you erupting
in some act of violence
towards your nephew.
Well, Christmas isn't over yet.
You came out of that shooting
feeling each day
is a "gift."
Well, this is
a corollary to that.
A what?
You don't have to eat
every dish of rigatoni.
You don't have to fuck
every female you meet.
You know what I've
been realizing?
These women...
they're all sort of the same...
dark complexion, smart,
they smell a little
bit of money.
There's you and...
Gloria
and this "Ashkenuzi."
So what's that about?
What do you think it's about?
Well... ahem...
It's probably
the reason I still come here
to hang out with you...
'cause nothing really changes
with the therapy part.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC
PLAYING)
(BREATHING)
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Ton'? That fed's
out front. Harris.
Says he wants you to know
he's here having a sandwich.
What's the matter?
Not enough mayo?
Tony, how you doing?
Good, so how's
the War on Terror?
Christmas is always
potentially our busy season.
So, Phil Leotardo, huh?
Coronary?
I swear to God
I had nothin' to do with that.
Just so you know,
I'm still in touch
with some agents who work O.C.
From what they hear, you're not very
popular in Brooklyn right now.
So what else is new, huh?
That someone close to you
may be in danger.
Really?
Anybody specific?
All they know is it's under serious
discussion at top levels.
- Thanks.
- It's Christmas.
What? You want me
to call a doctor?
Cramping in my legs?
It could be anything.
Well, then what'd
you call me for?
- Just to say hi.
- But you're all right?
Yeah.
I'll see you later.
Bring me home
a quattro formaggi.
I don't care what time it is.
Wake me up.
- All right.
- Mwah.
(SIGHS)
We were talking about recovery
and your organized crime thing.
That I took an oath
that was a sacred oath.
- That's not an urban legend?
- No, you burn a saint.
You draw blood... but technically
I shouldn't even be tellin' you this.
Ooh.
The program...
I could never really get
into the "Higher Power" part.
Well, me neither.
It's hard.
I mostly think of the group
consciousness as a Higher Power.
I said to myself that that oath
would be my Higher Power.
That would be my strength.
That code... that's
a soldier's oath.
- I could see that.
- But the problem is
nobody lives it no more.
Not Tony, not nobody.
They let you down.
Whatever...
here I am.
- Using.
Are you breaking up with me?
No.
Should we go to a meeting?
I don't know.
What do you wanna do?
I know one that starts
in half an hour in Glen Ridge.
Take one car?
I'll follow you.
You should've called first.
How's John?
Some Christmas present, huh?
I'll see you in the morn...
(WEEPS)
I'll see you in the morning.
God loves you.
Finally got you to come
to Brooklyn, cocksucker.
Listen to me.
Now, I never told nobody this,
but while I was in that coma...
somethin' happened to me.
I went someplace...
I think. But I know I never
wanna go back there.
And maybe you know
what I'm talkin' about.
Believe me, nobody ever
laid on their deathbed
wishin' they saved
more no-show jobs.
Now you take your time.
You get better.
And you get out
of this fuckin' place.
But when you do,
you focus on grandkids
and good things.
We can have it all, Phil...
plenty for everybody.
Stop cryin' now.
We should let him sleep.
We gotta stop
meeting like this, huh?
(PHONE RINGING)
(BEEPING)
George, hi.
Carmela Soprano.
Listen, I wanna move ahead with
the roofing... ordering the slate?
(BABY WHINING)
Carm, you got cocktail sauce?
Uh, in the fridge, top shelf.
(BABY CRYING)
Bob Cratchit!
Pass out the punch!
...gift set...
What I said is none of your business!
I'll make it my business!
- Sophia, come help, hon'.
- I don't like disturbances in my place.
Either lay off
politics or get out!
Jesus, that's a lot of presents.
You sure you got enough?
Remember you're
a kid... WABC?
They'd tell you where Santa was,
trackin' him on Air Force radar?
(ICE CLATTERING)
Are you gonna hog all the ice?
- To America.
To America.
Hello.
Everybody, this is Blanca.
Blanca, my mom,
- my dad.
- Hi.
This is Hector.
Say hello, baby.
Hi, Hector.
Oh, look at those eyes.
He's not so shy at home.
Hey, that is quite a bagatelle.
Oh, it's from Anthony.
Really?
Hector, no, papi!
Those ain't your presents.
It's okay.
I got him.
(PHONE RINGING)
Hey, come here, you.
Come here.
(GRUNTS)
Who's coming later, huh?
- Santa!
- Is Santa Claus coming, huh?
- Carmela, it's Meadow!
- Tell her I kept my promise.
I'm wearing
your present from Paris.
Excuse me, my daughter's
calling from California.
(CHRISTMAS MUSIC
PLAYING)
- Ahem...
- She's 10 years older than him
and she's Puerto Rican.
Dominican...
maybe.
Least she's Catholic.
What are you lookin'
at me like that for?
You were overjoyed
when I sent him down there.
Carmela, your daughter says
you're using up
all her cell phone minutes.
Nice piece, that necklace.
Where'd you get it?
- The mall.
- Should've told me.
- I got a guy.
- And I got a job.
(POURING)
My dear mademoiselle,
perhaps you have already observed
that in Casablanca human life is cheap.
Good night, mademoiselle.
Okay, sweetie.
I love you too.
Merry Christmas, baby.
Yeah, we're all here,
same as always.
Bobby Jr.,
get in here and eat!
You want some wine?
Aunt Barb's comin' later.
Uncle Tom had to work.
All right, honey.
I miss you too.
(FIRE CRACKLING)
Merry Christmas.
Love to Finn, huh?
(CHRISTMAS MUSIC
CONTINUES)
You have a gorgeous home.
Thank you.
We do.
(BOBBY JR.
CRUNCHING FOOD)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)