- They obstructed the harbor.
- I know.
- Two ships they sunk.
- I know, I...
- Then why didn't you warn us?
- I did warn you!
We don't have sufficient
numbers to move on Nassau,
but if we could
increase those numbers...
- Increase them how?
- The Underhill plantation.
Captured nine more just
east of the fence line.
I want the trial started
as soon as possible.
What did he do?
Set a course for Nassau to
send a message when we return.
When I informed Sarah of my intent
to formally end our marriage,
her family persuaded my old creditors
to accelerate my
timetables for repayment.
I would default.
Three men know the
resting place of the chest,
and one woman.
He told it to me before we left home.
There will be no pirate king here.
Of that much I am certain.
Long John Silver. Welcome home.
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
What is this?
I said, what's going on here?
What do you want from me?
Blacksmith pays for these.
Jeweler pays for these.
The law pays for you.
500 pieces for Long John Silver.
I'm sorry, I think you're
mistaken. I'm not...
I seen you. Huh?
Before.
Before you was Long.
Now...
they say you're supposed
to be a pirate king.
A strongman.
That true?
Hmm.
That's what I thought.
More lies.
So,
you returned.
You're angry.
Ah.
And you just killed one
of the governor's men.
Now write that.
I killed who?
Killed him.
What?
500 pieces they pay before you did it.
I think more after.
Fuck you.
Write.
I am told it will begin soon.
The executions of the men
captured on the beach yesterday.
It's for the best to have it done.
It could have been you.
I gave you...
both of you,
a place to stand here.
I gave you a life,
and you repaid me
by conspiring with my enemies.
Ma'am, I don't know what
you think you heard, but...
Quiet.
I know you were responsible
for Captain Rackham's escape.
I know you solicited her
to aid you in the effort.
I know you relayed information
to the pirate resistance
throughout the purges here.
I have been monitoring
all of it since it began.
Monitoring?
You intercepted his message.
The warning that was
to alert Captain Flint
of the governor's
obstructing the harbor.
Why aren't we out there?
Why didn't you report
us to Captain Berringer?
Let fall!
The continued pirate threat
makes Captain Berringer
a necessary, if temporary, evil.
But I do not care for
the idea of having him
trampling through my affairs,
encouraged by one scandal
to search for more,
which is why I secured an
agreement from the governor
that my informants would be
held immune from any prosecution
for their prior associations
with the pirates.
This will all pass soon enough...
if we let it.
My grandfather was a
pirate of another sort.
When he was a young
man, he swindled a ship,
hired it to privateers,
and earned a share of their
spoils for his trouble.
But he had an ambition for
something far greater than plunder,
a desire to build
something more permanent.
So, plunder purchased more ships.
Ships generated more profits,
profits became wealth,
which became influence,
which became power.
By the time I was born,
my grandfather was one of the
wealthiest men in the New World.
If I go to him,
if I plead our case
and gain his support,
that might be all we
need, all Nassau needs,
to emerge from this intact.
He could pay my debts?
Several times over, yes.
He could send us ships?
And guns?
And mercenaries?
Yes.
But?
My father was ill-favored by his family,
and that was before he
made their name synonymous
with piracy in the West Indies.
And all I've done
since is make their name
synonymous with scandal in London.
It is far from a foregone conclusion
that they'll be inclined
to offer me their help.
But,
given our state of affairs,
it seems more than worth a try.
And unlike in the past...
I now have something to offer them
that may make the ask more attractive.
What's that?
You.
They can purchase ships
and influence and power,
but they cannot purchase
what they ultimately want.
And that is for the family to
be known within London society
for something more than being
a backwater merchant clan.
Calling you a part of it
certainly wouldn't hurt matters.
What is it?
Steady, now.
She drifted into the
harbor a little while ago.
A message from Teach upon his return.
There he intends to sit.
Denying passage in or out of the bay.
If we cede to his demand, he will leave.
What demand is that?
That we surrender to him the
woman he holds responsible
for the murder of Charles Vane.
He also holds 61 more of my
men prisoner aboard his ship.
If we refuse,
he promises they will meet
the same fate as these men.
He won't turn her over.
Not for 60 men.
Not for 600 men.
No.
I don't expect he will.
Nor do we have the stores to
maintain this blockade for long.
So we need to move quickly.
You'll gather your men.
You will stand ready to
depart upon nightfall.
And whilst the enemy
remains focused on us,
you will make your landing to the west
and move undetected into town.
You will find Eleanor Guthrie
and you will bring her
out of Nassau, back here.
There ain't no good
way in from the west.
I agree. Perhaps an
approach from the lagoon.
Do it.
We depart for the Underhill
plantation on the hour,
arrive just before dark,
approach from the east,
eliminate the overseers,
secure the main house, and in so doing
establish a camp
capable of Billy's plan.
Your plan.
You will be leading our forces.
Does that not make it your plan, too?
What choice do I have?
I must say, it, uh,
caught me by surprise,
your assertion that Mr. Silver
had revealed the whereabouts
of the buried cache.
- Assertion?
- Maybe he told you.
Felt close enough to you
to share it, or maybe...
you saw an opportunity
to counter my leverage with Billy.
And all it took was a lie
that's terribly
inconvenient to disprove.
And what choice did I have?
The moment we arrived,
it was instantly clear to me...
he is the one keeping
this place together.
His men look up to him, rely on him,
trust him.
Many of your men even
trust him, as well.
He is going to be relevant
to what happens next here.
That much is painfully obvious.
And your first instinct
is to dismiss him.
Had I not stepped in,
who knows how destructive
that could have become
for everyone?
Can't sit still and
let him hold us hostage.
Can't fight him directly
or we risk losing what
few soldiers we have left.
And even if I could slip a ship past him
to seek aid from your
family in the colonies,
you'd have to be on that ship.
And you'd never get that
far before he caught you.
I won't risk that.
All right.
Here's what we're gonna do.
I board the sloop...
- No.
- ... and I run.
You just said it's
too far to outrun him.
To Philadelphia it's too far,
but I can make safe
harbor somewhere nearer.
Outrun for a day, pull
him away from here,
then seek shelter in a friendly port
strong enough to prevent his entry.
Meanwhile...
the door will be open for you
to reach your grandfather
and gain his aid.
Why you?
Why not have someone else lead him away?
Because he won't leave that
position to chase someone else.
He'd chase you,
and I believe, given the opportunity,
he might chase me for a chance
at ending this regime once and for all.
From where I stand, it's
the only way out of this.
Insurrection against the
lawfully appointed governor,
high seas piracy, treason.
Does the accused have any words to say
in his own defense?
Fuck... you.
- Oh, get him.
- This is injustice!
Fuck you!
Gentlemen, that's enough!
Get out there. Go on.
Bring in the next man!
It's been like that all day.
We've condemned a
dozen men since morning.
And between them,
I've yet to see an ounce of remorse.
Savages to the bitter end.
When you condemn a dozen
men in as many hours,
perhaps remorse is a bit much to ask.
You object to these trials.
I do not object to trials,
I do not object to hangings.
What I do object to,
however, is spectacle,
certain to increase defiance and anger
rather than sooth it.
We should be moving past this,
not wallowing in it.
That's a very noble perspective.
And I might share it were it
not for the soldier of mine
found with his throat
slit this morning...
with a note attached...
threatening that any
further hanging of pirates
would be met with more reprisals.
A note attributed...
to Long John Silver.
I believe our current
war is far from over.
I believe there are yet
still radicals amongst us
eager to do us harm in the
name of their pirate king.
And I believe there is
more you could be doing
to aid us in ferreting
out those radicals.
If you choose to.
I am very sorry for
the loss of your man,
and I will be vigilant, as I always am,
about any information
that might allow us
to make Nassau safe.
But promises were made
by the governor to me,
by me to my informants.
And if oaths are no longer kept here,
if boundaries are no
longer respected here,
then there is no civilization
left here to defend,
and I do not know what
we are fighting for.
In a matter of hours,
the governor and his wife will set
sail from here aboard separate vessels
to seek aid in our efforts.
He to Port Royal,
she to Philadelphia.
I alone am to be left in
charge of Nassau's security.
And I gave our lord
governor my solemn oath
that I would see it protected...
against any and all enemies.
I look forward very much
to be working with you to that end.
Philadelphia?
What is in Philadelphia worth
leaving things here in this state?
My grandfather spent his winters there
negotiating with his
suppliers for the spring.
I'll find him there and
secure his assistance.
I must strongly advise against it,
against you and the governor
being gone in this moment.
We are so very close to winning this war
and finally bringing
Nassau out of the dark.
But I fear we cannot complete
the victory on our own.
We're going to need help, and this
is the only way I know how to get it.
You and I both know that there
are men on both sides of this war
whose identities are so
enmeshed in this conflict
that they are more afraid of ending
it than they are of losing it.
And I believe you are about
to elevate one of those men
into a position of significant power.
That may very well be,
but Captain Berringer is loyal.
Captain Berringer is strong.
And at this moment, Captain Berringer
is a man before whom
Nassau lives in terror.
Right now, that might be what she needs.
The governor will return
soon and I soon thereafter.
We just need things to hold until then.
And this seems like
our best chance at it.
"More lies."
Who else's lies am I to
be held responsible for?
I heard a story once...
told to me by Captain Flint,
who knows Nassau's history
as well as any other.
A story about a man
consigned to the wrecks.
A man who was quite
specifically disfigured.
A man who sailed with Edward Teach
in his early days.
One of his most trusted men...
and one of the deadliest
men that Nassau ever knew.
I heard that on the day
Governor Thompson fled,
it was actually this
man who wielded the knife
that killed his wife and son.
So, all Teach and
Jennings and the giants
were hailed as the fathers
of the pirate republic.
It was actually another
who cut the cord.
I heard his name was...
Israel Hands.
It's a pleasure to
make your acquaintance.
Though, given the rest of the story,
it is of some curiosity to
me that you're still here.
See, I heard that when Captain Teach
began to see Charles
Vane as his heir apparent,
Israel Hands became
jealous of Teach's affection
and that it led to a
falling out with the captain
that was most humiliating.
A degrading beating before
all the crews on the beach.
A pistol shot just missing his eye,
rendering him a misshapen wretch.
You talk too much.
So, you can understand my confusion,
given that Nassau's first king
embarrassed you so
thoroughly and so publicly,
forbade any other crew from having you.
Why on earth would you have stayed?
I sincerely hope it isn't
because you're still holding out
for some sort of apology from Teach.
Fuck Teach.
Yeah, fuck Teach.
Huh?
We are brothers that
sail beneath the black.
How can a man like
that be the best of us?
Well, they followed Teach,
and where did it lead?
An English governor raising
his flag over Nassau.
Fuck Teach.
He was almost the end of us.
But now I'm here...
and things are about to begin again.
You?
Who are you that I ought
to pay you any mind?
I'm no one.
From nowhere.
Belonging to nothing.
I'm a wretch like you.
And yet...
mountains of gold have changed
hands because I chose it.
Thousands of men in Nassau
are living in fear of my return
because I decreed it.
Hundreds of dead redcoats in
a forest not far from here,
because I made it so.
I'm the reason grown
men lie awake at night.
I am a new beginning for Nassau.
And you'd trade all of that for what?
500 pieces?
You think you're worth more?
To the right people.
Who?
Who would pay so much for you?
Enough.
Is she asleep yet?
Audrey?
Are you asleep yet?
Yes.
Your daughter.
Ruth, fix some more
hot water, would you?
Ruth?
What is it?
We're under attack!
Move! Move!
The main slave quarters.
Take as many extra weapons as you can.
Let's get them armed.
It's only a matter of
time before militia arrive
from other estates that heard the alarm.
Wait!
If you shoot,
I'll have to do the same.
Hello, Ruth.
You knew my father.
I had heard that you might be coming
to set us free.
Yes.
I'm glad that you came.
And now...
I need you to go.
They say your ship is ready to depart.
The launch awaits you at the jetty.
I should be going.
How long do you think to Port Royal?
I'll make it.
I promise you I will make it.
Don't you dare let him
catch you, don't you dare.
I won't.
You wait until morning to depart.
I don't want him lurking in the dark
out there awaiting another departure.
I know.
I hear Philadelphia is lovely.
Try not to dawdle there.
I will see you back here again.
Soon.
He wants to know when you're leaving.
You have no intention
of leaving, do you?
What exactly do you suggest I tell him?
Whatever the fuck you wanna tell him.
Anne.
At a certain point,
there is a good chance
he'll just decide to kill you
than take your no for an answer.
He can try.
"He can try."
I'll pass that one along.
I go looking for Eleanor Guthrie,
you know I'm gonna find her, too.
Max.
Said if I turned over
the cache, you'd be safe.
And it ain't just the lie.
She tried to take you away from me.
When I left that island...
all I could think about was
having a chance to make her pay...
for what she done.
Now that we're here...
it would be so easy.
And I don't wanna do it.
Don't wanna live with it after.
The sight of her hurt in that way.
Just don't want it.
That fucking island.
Makes you do shit you don't wanna do.
How is it we haven't
figured that out by now?
What the hell are we
doing back here, Jack?
It's the governor's banner!
Glass, please. Quickly.
Well, the good news is...
Ben's squad just found a
storehouse filled to the ceiling
of salt pork, corn.
They must have been readying
a shipment back into Nassau.
So, between that and the
ordinance we just scavenged,
we may be better supplied than the
British in Nassau at this moment.
That said,
the strangest thing just happened
out by the slave quarters.
The doors were locked...
from the inside.
How did you know that?
What?
What did she tell you?
When I acquired those weapons
we used to fight the British,
it apparently aroused suspicion
amongst the estate owners,
concerned that the alliance
between your people and mine
might prove dangerous to maintaining
control over their holdings,
so they took precautions...
against any move that
might incite revolt.
Any man who had a woman,
any woman who had a child was separated.
With families distributed amongst
the other plantations on the island,
if any one community revolted...
or by inaction allowed
an estate to be toppled,
their husbands and wives...
and children who are held
on the other plantations
would be punished most severely.
If we complete this conquest,
if we force a situation
which might see these people's
husbands and wives and children
brutalized this way,
many of them would die by their own
hand before they let that happen.
We'll move quickly, take the
other plantations as well.
To seven different estates?
Wait a minute.
- We have no choice.
- You want to withdraw?
If we don't, knowing full well the cost,
it will be the end of
whatever trust exists
between us and the slaves on the island,
or anywhere, for that matter.
The end of any alliance
that might be between us.
How is leaving them here any better?
The only way to free them safely
is if it is all at once.
Simultaneous revolts across the island
initiated by one very loud
and very clear signal
that will be heard by all.
- If we take Nassau first...
- Take it first?
... it would demonstrate
to the slave communities
the viability of our enterprise.
Show them that beyond
revolt lies a safe harbor
with allies strong
enough to protect them.
It is the only way to ensure that
the greatest number of them survive.
I lost six men tonight.
The men I have left know this estate
means supplies and full stomachs.
They know they are stronger with it.
And, thus, fewer of them will die in
the weeks ahead than would without it.
- And you want to walk away.
- We didn't come here to take an estate.
We came here to make a statement,
not just to expel England,
but to defeat them.
And to do it together. That
has always been the goal.
And right now, that requires a
painful but necessary tactical retreat.
I'm asking you...
please...
don't do this.
Militia's approaching.
The neighboring estates must've
heard the guns and rallied.
This was never gonna be easy.
It just is what it is.
There's been a change in circumstances.
We need to be gone before
that militia arrives.
Gather all the weapons you can.
- We're gonna be moving back towards...
- We're not going anywhere.
Henry, Davis, restrain the captain.
What are you doing?
I'm through following you down
a path only you seem able to see.
Towards a victory only
you seem able to define.
We will hold our position here
until we can find our way into Nassau
and free the rest of the men.
And we will do it without you.
Do it.
The rest of you form a firing
line to repel that militia.
Are you sure you want to keep
following him down that path?
Stand your men down...
and follow me away from here,
for any man who offers
resistance to that militia
will be held responsible for...
Fire!
Plantation men!
- It's over now!
- We're under attack!
- Fall back! Fall back!
- Fall back!
Fall back to the corn field!
It's been confirmed.
The governor was spotted
boarding the brig.
They're hauling back
their anchor as we speak.
He'll be gone within the hour,
off in search of aid, no doubt,
to secure his possession of Nassau,
win the war for England.
And with him will depart
a number of soldiers,
diminishing the number of bodies
between us and Eleanor Guthrie.
That many fewer obstacles between
us and justice for Charles' murder.
If you still wish Anne to lead
the vanguard to do it, tell me now.
I'll have it done.
Would you like to know what I think?
I think Anne is right.
She said something to me earlier.
She said only a fool would give his life
to earn the admiration of a corpse.
I wanted to strangle her.
But part of me could not
help but note in that moment
she sounded an awful lot
like someone else I once knew,
someone you and I both once knew
who shared...
Anne's mistrust of sentimentality.
And just after he joined my crew...
I spent two weeks careening on
this shit island with no name.
I knew right away he was
different than the others.
He was so like me when
I was a younger man.
And that he and I
somehow were fated to
matter to one another.
I was consumed with the question
of whether our similarities
would be a blessing or a curse.
So, whilst the others were careening,
a number of us were inland
by a spring.
The sun climbs up over
the top of the trees...
in just a way that it
shines off the pool...
lighting up all around us.
In that moment,
a bird lands on the water...
massive, snow-white beast,
big as a boar.
To this day, I've never
seen anything like it.
Between the sun and the size of it,
it just felt...
meaningful.
The answer to a question I
did not yet know how to ask.
I told him...
that there were men in the east...
who would have seen in that
bird the darkest of all omens,
bringer of death.
But then,
there are other men near Clifton...
my... my mother's home...
who would've called it
a sign of great fortune,
an indication from the heavens
that someone up there
favored our endeavor together.
And I asked him what
he thought it meant.
"Dinner."
I don't know what made
me think of that story.
There are moments in the dead
of night when I can't sleep,
and I wonder if I will ever
be able to truly rest again
until I know that Eleanor Guthrie
has paid for what she took from me.
And then there are other moments
when I wonder if it would actually
please him to see her dead,
to know the scales had been evened.
Or if despite all they had been through,
despite the anger and
the blood and the betrayal
and all he'd done to her and she to him,
despite what I or you or what
anybody else might think of it,
if wherever he was,
he still didn't just
a little bit love her.
I wonder if he were here now,
watching us battle with the
choice to kill her in his name
or defeat the governor
and perhaps therein win the
war we all together started,
if he might call us fools.
And then I wonder if maybe we
don't have to work that hard
to imagine what he'd say.
Maybe we've already heard it,
and the only choice is
whether we choose to listen.
Cannon fire from the port!
He's underway, Captain.
Using the fort guns for cover.
Do we pursue?
Slip the cables.
Set a course to overtake her.
Slip the cable!
Set course to pursue!
Ma'am?
Long John Silver.
So big a name for so small a man.
What is it you have to say to me?
You owe me.
Certainly your fortune.
Probably your life.
You might wanna consider that
and then choose a new tone,
especially given that
in the very near future
your life might end up
in my hands yet again.
Is that so?
Is Teach still free?
Is Rackham?
Is Flint?
This war may feel over,
but as long as we're all
free, it's far from it.
And if somehow we prevail in Nassau,
what happens to former friends
who've since aligned themselves
so warmly with the governor?
I've come to offer you a chance
to earn back our friendship.
Or, more specifically, to buy it back.
An amount of money that
proves your desire to come...
No.
No?
I am tired of this.
This thing that perpetuates itself
with anger and bluster and blood.
I do not want to be your friend.
What I want is for all of this to end.
For it to end, you must end.
I imagine I have some obligation
to surrender you to Captain Berringer,
but the spectacle he would
make of your trial and execution
would only fan the flames of
what is burning in Nassau now.
I am tempted to put the sword
to you and your man both,
and bury this story for good,
but what am I...
if I spend my days pleading
for a return to civility
and then do dark things
under the cover of night?
So, you will remain in my custody
until I can find a place
far from here to deposit you.
You will be gone,
but you will live.
And for that, I will consider
whatever debts I may owe you
to be paid in full.
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com