RON: There's never been
an inquiry of this scale
in the annals of police history.
He must speak with a Geordie accent.
Anybody not meeting
these five points, they're gone.
Mr Peter Sutcliffe?
DAVID: I do not think
the man on the tape is the Ripper.
You've made that clear.
I want that on record.
But you're wrong.
This is starting to affect
the public's confidence in
the police as a whole, nationally.
RON: The most wanted man
of the century,
more resources than anyone ever,
and you have failed.
I want to ask everyone
to please help us find the person
who killed my daughter.
He won't be back in a hurry.
MEG: No.
But he'll turn up somewhere.
HE SIGHS
SUTCLIFFE: It's quiet enough here,
isn't it?
WOMAN: Yeah, it's fine.
Come here all the time.
We won't be disturbed.
You got a tenner for me?
Why don't we get in t'back?
CAR APPROACHES
Oh, no.
Erm...
You're my girlfriend.
Is this your car, sir?
Yes.
Can you give me your name
and address?
I am John Williams.
65 Dorchester Road, Rotherham.
And who's she?
My girlfriend.
And what's her name?
I don't know. We've not known
each other that long.
Right.
Just stay there.
OFFICER: Just take the keys
out of your car.
2-5-6 to Control.
RADIO: 'Control speaking.'
Number plate check, please.
'Roger that. Go ahead.'
Yeah, it's foxtrot, echo, hotel,
9-0-7, Juliet.
Over.
'That's coming up
as a Skoda saloon.
'Owner is a Mr Aslam Khan. Over.'
POLICE CAR DOOR
CLOSES
APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS
Right, so, the number plates
on your vehicle
don't match that of the car itself.
So what's gonna happen now is
I'm gonna arrest you both
on suspicion of theft.
And if this turns out
to be soliciting as well...
Well, we'll get into that
back at the station.
OK?
Right, out you get.
We'll leave your car.
You heard him. Let's go.
Come on. Chop-chop.
Come on.
Yeah, stick them in the back.
Where do you think you're going?
I need a piss.
Well, quickly, then.
Do it over there.
You've been in before, Olivia,
haven't you?
For prostitution.
And that's what you were doing
this evening when we picked you up.
The fines get worse the more
you deny it. You know they do.
You've got two kids at home -
it says so on here.
So the more you sit there
not saying owt,
the more the food's coming off
their table.
Doesn't it?
Start by saying your name.
You know my name.
Nice and clearly, so PC Small here
can write it down.
"My name is Olivia Reivers." Go on.
My name is Olivia Reivers.
"I am a prostitute."
I'm a prostitute.
"And I am guilty, yet again guilty,
of picking up a punter,
"this time on the evening
of January 2nd 1981."
Go on, you tell the story.
Got picked up this evening.
For sex. Go on.
For sex.
£10.
Got in his car, parked up.
But that were it.
Then that's when you came along.
Right.
Thank you.
Right, if you just sign here,
I'll let you go.
You'll get a court date through.
It'll likely mean another fine.
More severe this time
because it's repeat offences,
you see.
This is just what happens
when you can't leave it alone.
What about this bloke
who picked you up?
His car number plates
weren't registered in his name.
What's that got to do with me?
Well, you've never met him,
or he's not a regular, or...?
I've no idea who he is.
He's just some...
..just some ordinary guy.
Mm.
You've given your name
as John Williams
of Canklow, Rotherham.
There is no John Williams
So, come on. What's your real name?
Sutcliffe. Peter William Sutcliffe.
From?
Garden Lane, Heaton.
Bradford?
Aye.
Now, is that your real name
and address, or are those more lies?
No, no. You can check that.
So why lie the first time, Peter?
I said a fake name
because I panicked.
I regret that now.
I should never have done it.
Those plates on your car,
they don't belong to you, do they?
You stole them. Why?
Didn't want people seeing you
in red light areas.
It's not against the law
to go in t'red light area.
We're not saying it is.
It's whores who are criminals.
We're not saying otherwise.
We're asking why you'd be
driving about with stolen plates.
So you're admitting
that you stole them, then?
So, you've got that now?
Sorry?
I've admitted that,
so you can charge me and let me go.
Well, what's the big hurry, Peter?
I just wanna get back. That's all.
To Bradford?
Yeah, to Bradford, aye.
A lot of this Ripper business,
that's been up Bradford way,
hasn't it?
Leach.
Was that her name?
The student. She were Bradford.
You ever been questioned
about the Ripper, Peter?
What's so funny about that?
Look at me.
Have you been questioned or not?
Everybody has.
This one, is it?
It's that one there.
Right.
DC Nunn.
Where?
Well, I doubt it.
He's never done Sheffield.
What accent's he got?
At one in t'morning?
You've no chance.
No, there's nobody else here,
and if there were, they'd tell you
the same bloody thing.
Well, bail him, then.
Leeds won't send anyone.
They're saying it's too late.
So they're happy to bail him?
Well, we can't keep him overnight,
Des. Not on stolen plates.
Especially if he's admitted it.
Well, that wouldn't be the reason
we're holding him.
That'd be the excuse.
We should follow their advice.
Bob's right, sir.
If Leeds aren't bothered,
why should we be?
Because we're here,
and we can feel it.
We can feel
that something ain't right.
SCRAPING
I thought you were off home.
Is it just me
or is the car parked wrong?
Punters usually park
pointing away from the road
to stop people seeing in
when they're doing the business.
He were facing out. Do you remember?
Like he wanted a quick getaway.
Maybe.
Or he weren't wanting sex.
So if he weren't wanting sex,
what were he gonna do?
But what with?
Sorry?
Well... if he's t'Ripper,
he'd have had weapons on him,
a hammer and...
But we searched him,
searched his car. He never had owt.
Bob.
PHONE RINGS
Yeah, that's fine.
OK, yep, checking for you now.
Thanks. Bye.
PHONES RINGING
RINGING CONTINUES
Ford Corsair.
Look.
God, Sue.
I'll get the others.
Morning.
CLAMOURING
Sue?
Sue.
What's happening?
Have they... Have they got him?
Think so.
Right, so, they've kept him in,
this fella, overnight.
So, what they're saying is
one of the coppers went back,
had a look down by the side
of these bins, you know,
where they've nicked him,
and that's where they've found it.
Found what?
Hammer and knife. Kitchen knife,
same as he used on Rytka.
Fucking 'ell.
Phone Sheffield.
Tell 'em
I want that scene sterile.
No more coppers tramping about
and toing and froing.
Well, no, look - to be fair,
they did find the weapons.
There's nothing to link the weapons
to him, is there?
not unless there's prints.
Are there prints?
Well, I mean, we've gotta wait.
So where is he now?
Well, they're bringing him
to West Yorkshire
so we can take over.
All right.
And these are his details?
Yeah.
Get me George Oldfield.
Now, come on, what is it?
Hm? This is everything
we've worked towards.
This is him.
PHONE RINGS
Grange Moor.
George. Yeah...
they think they've got him.
'His name's Peter Sutcliffe.
Lorry driver.'
'They're getting him back
to West Yorkshire as we speak.'
We've been here before, Dick.
'Yeah, I know.'
You have to be absolutely sure.
'Agreed, but I'll get on it.'
LINE DISCONNECTS
Mrs Peter Sutcliffe?
Can we have a word?
Mrs Sutcliffe,
your husband is in police custody.
He was brought in last night
in Sheffield,
being transferred as we speak.
TV NEWS PLAYS
OK, listen love.
I've got half the detectives
in the north of England
saying that your Peter
is The Yorkshire Ripper -
minds made up.
So if there's anything you wanna
tell me that might dissuade them
from that opinion, anything at all,
this is the time to say it.
Do you mind if we ask
a few questions?
FAINT: Just some specifics.
Would that be all right, Sonia?
Do you mind if I call you Sonia?
Sonia, I have a list of dates,
so if you can think of any way
to demonstrate...
He would've been at work.
Sorry?
Or he was with me.
But Mrs Sutcliffe,
I haven't asked you the dates yet.
TV PLAYS
30th of the 10th, 1975.
Now, we know that's five years ago.
It's vitally important that we know
the whereabouts of Peter.
FAINT: Sonia, this is really...
John.
There's one missing.
I'll call Millgarth.
His name's in nominal three times,
his car's in vehicle
multiple times,
and he's listed
in triple-area sightings...
We did our bit, you know?
If it's him, then everything were
logged and in the right places.
It's all we could do.
But if we did that,
then they must've been out.
They must've interviewed him
already. They must've done.
They did.... more than once.
MAN: Far too many people
stood around doing nothing
when there's plenty of work
to be done.
So get on with it now!
Have they asked you back in?
No, but they will do.
They won't want me sitting round
here doing bugger all, will they?
Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
I will call you.
CAR HORN BEEPS
CLAMOURING,
SHOUTING
HORN BLARES
Move!
EXHALES DEEPLY
The press are outside already.
I'm speaking to them shortly.
Yeah, I was just saying that
he's coughed up, he's confessed...
about ten minutes ago.
He's admitted everything.
He's admitted McCann,
Jackson, Richardson.
He's even admitted to doing
another one after Barbara Leach.
Now, apparently, he said that
he were hoping to get bail.
He said he were gonna get a cab
to Sheffield, pick up them weapons,
then he'd be in the clear.
He... He said all that? What,
just to two bobbies in Sheffield?
Well, he wants it all off his chest.
He said things about the Hill murder
that only the killer could know.
He said things...
well, that nobody ever should know.
Well, let's have it.
Is he a Geordie?
He's from Bradford.
But his voice, Jim.
Does he sound like a Geordie?
He sounds like he's from Bradford.
Hello.
Afternoon. All right.
George.
We have, this afternoon,
in this very building,
detained a man
on several counts of murder.
We are questioning him
in relation to The Ripper murders.
It is expected that he will appear
before the court tomorrow.
JOURNALIST: Is it fair to say, then,
that the hunt for The Ripper
is over?
'That's right.'
'So, have you got
any information on the man?'
'Not at this stage.'
JOURNALIST: 'Can you tell us
if he's got a Geordie accent?'
'I cannot tell you that
because I've not heard him speak.'
'Can you give us any details
at all?'
I can tell you that we are
absolutely delighted
with developments at this stage.
'Absolutely delighted.'
MAN: 'Now, please, gents.
Smile for the camera.'
'Really delighted.'
'Give us a smile, George!'
THEY LAUGH
And George is delighted, as well.
Are you delighted, George?
Give us a smile, George!
Absolutely delighted.
LAUGHTER
JOURNALIST:
'The time is twenty past six.
'The headlines again.
'Peter Sutcliffe, the man who became
known as The Yorkshire Ripper,
'was today sentenced
at the Old Bailey
'to life imprisonment
for the murder of 13 women.
'A lorry driver from Bradford,
'Sutcliffe was a man
so unremarkable
'that for five years, he was able
to elude the biggest manhunt
'in criminal history.
'During that time, he roamed freely
across the north of England,
'attacking and murdering
women indiscriminately.
'The judge, Mr Justice Boreham,
'described Sutcliffe
as an unusually dangerous...'
DISTANT CHATTER
KNOCK AT DOOR
You've seen it all?
That he admitted to it?
Attacking you.
So, now the trial's finished,
I was thinking we could get started.
We can get that compensation.
They've said it's gonna be
another couple of minutes
before they come live to us
here in the studio.
A make-up woman's coming.
Why would I need make up
for a programme like this?
PRESENTER: 'Let's see this opening.
Erm, "Trial of the century..." '
I'll make us a tea.
"Crime of the century"
or "Trial of the century", Tony?
I think I can say both, don't you?
TONY: Yeah, sure.
Shall we try that?
You happy? Yeah, I think
it might be a bit stronger.
Yeah, trial and crime.
Can you put that on the, erm...
Put that on the autocue,
and I'll see what that sounds like.
MAN: Going live in five.
Great, thank you.
The crime and the trial
of the century is over.
The Yorkshire Ripper
has been given a life sentence,
and a five-year manhunt is finished.
Yep, I think that's...
Yeah, I think that's better.
We'll go for that. It's stronger.
'Er, it's a stronger opening.'
BELL RINGS
Don't be nervous, now.
Just remember to say
the things we spoke about.
We've been through them
a thousand times.
The crime and trial of the century
is over.
The Yorkshire Ripper
has been given a life sentence,
and a five-year manhunt is finished.
But the questions
raised by that manhunt remain.
How efficient was the hunt
for The Yorkshire Ripper?
Ronald Gregory is the chief
constable of West Yorkshire Police.
Irene MacDonald is the mother
of Jayne MacDonald,
murdered by The Ripper in 1977.
And she very bravely has agreed to
join us tonight in our Leeds studio.
Ken Dwyer is a journalist who's been
following the investigation
from the very beginning,
and his book on the case
is now being rushed into print.
Another parent, Mrs Doreen Hill,
is the mother of Jacqueline,
The Ripper's last victim.
She understandably cannot face
the prospect of visiting Leeds
after what has happened,
and so joins us
from one of our London studios.
Chief Constable,
was any wild goose chase
more wild
than that which led the police
to concentrate all its attention
on the voice recording?
And the fact that
you instructed your men
to discount anyone
who didn't have a Geordie accent.
That's not...
Thus allowing The Ripper,
who didn't have a Geordie accent,
to go free for that much longer.
'No, that's not true. You see,
that's a miss-statement immediately.
'We did not reject anyone
who did not have a Geordie accent.
'The decision on the tape was taken
after very careful consideration
'because the senior investigating
officers were in a dilemma.
'Had they chosen
not to reveal the tape,
'they may have faced
much worse criticism.
'So when they did reveal it,
they had to be positive.'
"They."
But at no time was that
the only point of elimination.
But you were eliminating people
who didn't have a Wearside accent.
No, not solely on that.
Mrs Hill,
do you now feel able to say,
"It's over,
I have no more recriminations?"
'There are aspects
that I'm not happy about.
'The handbag was found
on the Monday evening.'
But no-one bothered
to look for its owner.
When the detectives
went to Jacqueline's body,
they knew nothing at all
about that handbag.
Could Mr Gregory clarify that?
'Mr Gregory?'
'I can't remember exactly.
'I know the handbag had been found.
'But I cannot say with any accuracy
'whether the detectives
knew about it at the time.'
'Mrs Hill,
would you welcome an inquiry
'into the way the police
conducted the investigation?'
Yes, I would.
If there's going to be an inquiry,
can I see the report?
Would Mrs Hill be entitled
to see that report?
If Mrs Hill is dissatisfied with
any aspect of the investigation,
if she'd like to come
and see us at any time,
we could explain to her
exactly what happened.
Can I ask a simple question?
No doubt you'll tell me I'm wrong.
But could you not
have done that earlier?
Sent for Mrs Hill
and Mrs MacDonald here
and invited them in
and set their minds at rest?
Well, I don't know what they want
to be reassured about.
'This is the first
I've heard of it.'
'Really, Chief Constable?
'You see no error
'in the five-and-a-half-years
investigation?'
'Oh, there may have been errors.
We are not infallible.
'But you are not informed
of what the police did.'
I am informed
about what you didn't do,
and that's catch Peter Sutcliffe.
Oh, I'm aware of that.
That's pretty obvious.
Though I'm glad that you welcome
a public inquiry.
No, I didn't say that.
I would not resent an inquiry,
but who did the inquiry and how it
was conducted would be important.
'You see, the public
and so many commentators
'have criticised the police
'when they have not been privy
to all that the police have done.
'Until they are, they should
reserve judgement and criticism.'
Well, we are grateful to everyone
who's taken part
in tonight's discussion,
but we're particularly mindful
of the courage it must have taken
for both Mrs MacDonald and Mrs Hill
to speak out in public tonight.
'Our thoughts must be with them
'and with all the other relatives
of the Ripper's victims.
'From Leeds, good night.'
CREW MEMBER:
Everybody stay seated.
Nice and still
while the credits roll.
BELL RINGS
OK, thanks everyone.
We're just waiting to hear
from the gallery
in case there's anything to pick up.
CREW CHATTER
What about the accent?
What about the fact
that our daughter was told
that men in Yorkshire were safe?
And why did they call him
The Ripper?
He said it over and over on TV,
"The Ripper".
Like that's his name.
That's just what they say, love.
No.
That's what people used to say
when they didn't know who he was.
When they didn't know his name.
But now they know his name,
why don't they use it?
Why do they have to say
that wretched word?
I'll get someone
to take that thing off.
"As Police Constable Andrew Laptew
"sat in Sutcliffe's modestly
furnished living room in Bradford,
"he realised that everything
the police knew about The Ripper
"fitted the man he was questioning.
"He became convinced
Sutcliffe was The Ripper.
"He submitted a report
saying as much
"to The Ripper headquarters
in Leeds."
Everything just "fitted", did it?
It's not how it looks.
Did everything just fall into place
for Sherlock fucking Holmes?
How much they pay you?
They didn't.
No? So why go round there?
I didn't.
To cover his arse.
He met Sutcliffe,
and then all he did was hand in some
shitty bit of paper, and that's it.
Three more lasses get butchered,
and he's got to live with that then,
the fact that he never followed up.
And that is why he called 'em.
Not true, sir.
Make it known
that it wasn't his fault.
A journalist knocked on my door.
He'd heard I'd put a report in.
Said he'd got a tip.
A tip-off? From who?
No idea. But I said nothing.
Is someone trying to protect you?
Read the article.
Cos you went round there...
You'll find no quotes...
Sat there and had a cup of tea
with him in his front fucking room.
I weren't the only one.
Sorry?
He'd been interviewed nine times.
Nine?
That's what they're saying.
T'lasses in t'incident room.
So what does it matter
who spoke to what journalist,
when nine times we went round there,
and nine times we failed?
Just like you failed
when I handed you that report
cos you were blinded by that tape,
by that stupid accent. Careful.
It's not me
that's got to live with it,
with them three dead girls,
it's all of us.
But it is you and Oldfield the most.
You watch your fucking mouth.
I want to create
a substantial new role for you.
A role befitting of an
experienced chap like you, George.
Chief of Operational Support.
Running the engine room,
for the whole of West Yorkshire.
To oversee the policing
of all vehicles
and road-based transport
in our portion of the county.
Traffic.
To oversee the safekeeping of
criminal records and documentation.
The library.
And a full oversight of frogmen,
police dogs and police horses.
Animals.
Frogmen aren't animals, George.
They just have an animal
in their name.
Well, I won't do it.
I'm not going from Head of CID
to running the police farmyard.
People'll think I've been fired.
There's shit
coming down the line, George.
And before I retire, I want
to make sure that you are protected.
We attribute it to your health.
Needn't be a reflection
of you and your team.
What about Dick?
I'll find something for Dick.
Oh, well...
..you know, if there's shit
coming down the line,
then you put as many people
in the way of it as you can, eh?
Don't hold back.
Oh, Margaret wanted to know
if those gifts had arrived.
For Grace's birthday.
Oh, I don't know, George.
That's very kind of her.
I shall ask.
Well, she's good like that, my wife.
Considerate.
DOOR OPENS
Mr Byford, Mr Nevill.
Morning.
If you want to follow me,
I can show you upstairs?
Thank you.
Yep.
You are a bit earlier
than we expected,
but, er, we're nearly ready.
This is Mr Byford,
he'll be doing the official inquiry.
Hello.
OFFICER: Sir.
Did you ladies work on the inquiry,
or are you just packing things up?
We did our share, sir.
Mr Byford requested you draw
all accounts from your system
that might relate to Sutcliffe.
Vehicles, Photofits,
anything you might think relevant.
Yes, sir. Follow me.
Statements, sightings,
any other paperwork, we've boxed up
and we've put in this office
cos, well,
it's more private in here.
These Photofits go back from 1972.
These are from the women
who survived.
The women he attacked
or followed or chased.
The ones he left for dead.
These are what they said they saw.
But not all of the women
were believed.
And these two photos, sir,
these are of Sutcliffe himself.
Er, this one from January.
And this one from when
he was arrested in '69.
Arrested in '69?
For going equipped.
He was caught, late at night,
carrying a hammer.
That's when he started.
KNOCK AT DOOR
Richard McCann?
Is this about our Sonia?
What's she done now?
She only left the house
about an hour ago.
Are you the son of Wilma McCann?
I'm Detective Chief Superintendent
Chris Gregg.
I was a young detective
on the Peter Sutcliffe case.
Sorry, but what's this...?
Because I find these things...
Can I come in?
I've been visiting
all the next of kin,
those related to the victims,
as we've had a development.
A few years ago, we arrested a man
for being drunk and disorderly.
As a result of his conviction,
he had to provide us
with a DNA sample
for the National Database.
Because I'm now Chief Super,
and because this case
really matters to me,
I make sure to run DNA tests
every few years, you see.
Tests on what?
On the man who wrote the letters.
There were never any prints,
but recently,
we found DNA
where he licked the envelope.
So two weeks ago, we ran the tests,
and we found a direct match
with the man who we'd arrested
for being drunk and disorderly.
That man...
is the man on the tape.
The man...
The man who sent the tape.
He's owned up to it.
Said that it was him,
that he regrets it,
the damage that he's caused...
Wait. No, no, no. I, er...
I need to hear him.
Hear his voice.
I-I need to...
Is there any way that you...?
Yeah,
that's one of the reasons I'm here.
Do you mind if I use
your DVD player? No.
It's just to show you,
like I'm showing
all the other friends and family.
But only if it'll help.
You don't have to.
His name is John Humble.
He's from Sunderland.
We had him read out the letters
in case he later
withdrew his confession.
'We've got a transcript here.
'Would you read that
for us please, John? Back in...'
'That's if I can see it.
My eyes are a bit dodgy, you know.'
'Take your time.'
' "I'm Jack.
' "I see you are still
having no luck catching me.
' "I have the greatest respect
for you, George, but, Lord!
' "You are no nearer catching me now
than four years ago, when I started.
' "I reckon your boys
are letting you down, George.
' "They can't be much good,
can they?
' "The only time
they came near..." '
RECORDING STOPS
That's him.
The voice.
The man who killed Mum.
No, no.
He's just the man who...
No, no...
Maybe not for you, but for me.
D'you know, when they first caught
Sutcliffe, no-one bothered.
They were busy patting
each other on the back,
but no-one actually came
to tell me and Sonia, so thank you.
Why...
..did he do that?
Why did he send the tape?
You must have asked him.
Yeah.
And...?
Notoriety.
And everything he said on the tape,
every word and every detail
that he put down in those letters,
it was all there
in the papers already.
It was all there for him
to read and write down
and pass off as his own.
And my predecessors,
they never worked that out.
And, erm... you know...
..I only wish they had.
MAN: Hello, mate.
'People often ask me...
'.."how you do you even begin
to get over something like that?" '
And, erm, "What it's like,
being a survivor?"
HE SCOFFS
We're not survivors.
We're surviving.
It's a, er... What do you call it?
A work in progress.
We're managing.
The good days...
..and the bad days.
And, erm...
the best we can hope for
is that very rare thing.
The odd day, when you're working...
I'm a motivational speaker
these days.
But whatever it might be,
when...
..when it doesn't cross your mind.
Or at least you think it doesn't,
and...
till right before bedtime,
when it pops into your head,
and you think...
"Oh, God...
I nearly made it through."
Sorry.
Our mum were never a prostitute.
Yes, she liked a drink,
and-and...
yes, she had boyfriends.
She-She probably
got up to all sorts.
The point is,
the police never bothered to check.
Those men in charge,
they were more fixed
on finding out who he was.
They never even bothered
to find out who Mum was.
And it was the same
for the rest of them.
The police, they showed up,
and they saw a crime scene,
and they saw a victim.
But what very few of them
ever actually saw were the women.
And that's what's important now.
We want to make those women visible.
We want to see 'em in colour.
We want to bring them out of that...
that same long shadow.
Subtitles by accessibility@itv.com