Well, I find if you don't solve a
murder in the first couple of days,
it's an uphill struggle after that,
isn't it?
Or maybe that's just me.
You've never caught a man
like this before.
You haven't caught him either.
Those murders
are still West Yorkshire, Dennis.
You just won't be
in day-to-day charge is all.
And who will?
How long you been on the game,
Marcella?
That's not what I do.
'She were attacked,
hit on t'back of t'head.'
That is it.
That is the only connection.
'If someone puts out
an appeal on a man
'who has absolutely nothing to do
with any of these crimes,
'we'd send everybody off
down the wrong road
'to create space for that bastard
to kill again.'
Well, this man has taken the lives
of three young women.
Three brutal and savage murders
in the space of 18 months.
So, let me say this.
There are 5,000 men
who work in this police force.
And each time this man commits
one of these unspeakable crimes,
the hunger and the desire
of these men only increases.
MY desire only increases.
So...
I would caution
this individual as follows.
You will be caught,
and you will be apprehended.
I have lasses manning every phone
and men on every corner.
Leeds is watching,
and Leeds is waiting.
And Leeds is ready.
Was that all right?
Yep, it was great.
I think I could do one more,
with just a little bit more,
er... intensity.
OK.
All right?
CLEARS THROAT
Yeah, thank you.
Can I just get some water?
MUSIC: 'Tiger Feet'
by Mud
MUSIC PLAYS
ON RADIO
So, it's eight quid
to get down there.
That's your return ticket.
There's a hotel you can stay in
in Bayswater,
if you need it. And then...
it is 30 quid a time.
Thirteen?
Thirty. Three-oh.
That's London, love.
And it can go higher.
Especially if you go with an Arab.
I'm serious, one week down there
is the same
as one entire month up here.
It's true.
Don't put ideas in her head.
Well, why not?
If it's a good idea,
why not put it in her head?
Because it's daft.
Right...
Work.
I'd do well with the Arabs, me.
Got that coat coming.
What coat?
One of them new-style coats.
They'd like that.
Long, down to about there.
Fur all round here
and on there like that.
Like an Afghan coat?
Afghan, that's it.
They're not new.
He says if I keep tipping up
like I have been, I can get one.
They're not new, are they?
Don't know about new,
they aren't Arab.
Business?
How much?
Five for 20 minutes
or as soon as you're finished.
You got the money on you?
Aye.
Through to the back.
DOG BARKING
I-I don't want sex.
I just...
You just want a suck?
UNZIPS FLIES
DOG BARKING
CONTINUES
HE GROANS
ZIPS FLIES
I'm not like that.
Like what?
I don't do this.
Do you not?
I've got three kids.
They're everything to me.
Can you start the car, please?
I hate myself.
ENGINE STARTS
You should stop what you're doing.
You know that, don't you?
I'd never have pulled over
if you hadn't been
showing yourself off like that.
Dirty little bitch.
Right, get out.
Not here. Back where you got me.
Right, then. Thanks for coming (!)
Summer's the best time.
'Ey?
I were just thinking,
summer's the time to buy it
cos the coats'll all be in sale.
Oh.
Listen...
London.
Don't even think about it.
Thirty quid a go.
Forget thirty quid a go.
I'm allowed to ask him.
Get it out your head, yeah?
You're here. Your kid's here.
You're tipping up.
And that is all he cares about.
I can still ask.
You all right?
HOLLAND: Right, it's taking forever,
finding this car.
First, we've gotta check what cars
actually fit
those tyres' make, model,
and then we've gotta go
and inspect them all individually.
So, inspect them all individually.
In the meantime, let's keep
all eyes peeled on Chapeltown.
What were it, 1,300 statements?
Yeah.
One of our lads'll clock him
eventually.
Simple law of averages.
See, what you really want...
No, go on. Go on.
Well, what you really want is
to be with the prossies themselves.
They're out there all night,
they see these punters close up.
Tarts don't talk, Les.
You know that.
Even in times like this.
Well, what I mean is,
it's all very well having lads
sitting around in unmarked cars.
When he sees them, he's off,
isn't he?
He's thought better of it.
It's the women he doesn't hide from.
So what you want
is someone in their shoes.
You gonna volunteer?
I could see you in a skirt, Les.
DR CAPLIN: No other symptoms?
Just the headaches?
And are they getting any better,
or are they as bad as before?
Worse.
Worse in terms of how long they last
or how much they hurt?
Or both?
Mind if I take a look?
Tilt your head towards me.
I wish he killed me.
Now, you mustn't say that.
Come back and kill me.
Marcella.
They're healing well.
You do know there's compensation
you can apply for?
Has anyone ever told you?
Criminal injury compensation,
I think it's called.
I had a lady come in, a girl.
She was assaulted in the street.
I'm not a prostitute.
No.
And nor was she.
I thought I had a form, but I don't.
But I can get one.
You can come back,
and we can fill it in together,
if you like?
And something for those headaches,
yes?
Before we do anything, has anyone
here worked Chapeltown before?
Either on beat or part of vice?
Right, well, you can go.
Thank you, girls.
Jim?
What's your name, love?
Jill.
Jill, this way, please.
'You a local lass?'
Yes, sir, from Armley.
And how old, Jill?
Twenty-six.
Twenty-six is a distant memory
for the likes of me and Les here.
Especially Les.
Just stand up for me.
Stand up, that's right.
And pop your jacket off.
Let's get a proper look at you.
Now, Les were telling me that
you've only been with us six months.
Is that right?
You can sit back down again now.
Do you know the investigation
that we're doing?
These prostitute murders, sir.
That's right. Now...
we're looking for a volunteer
for a special operation
to help stop this man.
So, how does it feel, being selected
for something like that?
Me, personally?
You, love. Out of everybody, you.
But what can I do
that your other detectives can't?
JIM CLEARS HIS THROAT
Which one?
Number 3, sir.
Professor Gee?
David.
Detective Superintendent
John Domaille, Bradford.
It didn't start here.
She's been lifted onto the bed.
He's first attacked her here...
..and then the murder itself
has taken place
with him on top of her on the bed.
You might want to give Leeds a ring,
get Jim Hobson down here.
Oh, I'll be the SIO on this case.
It's just that
there are multiple similarities -
blows to the back of head,
wounds to the body,
and I'm assuming this flat is...
some sort of prostitute's.
KNOCKING ON DOOR
GEORGIE: Is she in?
Can I just talk to her?
Tell me it's not true.
What's not true?
Her name's Tina.
Tina Atkinson.
Her proper name's Patricia.
Yeah. She lives in these flats.
Back over there with everyone else.
We're not going nowhere.
I'll not say it again!
Can you not scream at us, please?
She's got a kid here.
I can see that.
A little boy.
Are you gonna scream at him and all?
Georgie. You need to calm down.
What?
No.
Is that her jacket?
SOBS: It's hers, it's hers.
It's all right, it's all right.
Breathe.
Can you move, please?
It's all right, we don't know...
Can you move!
All right!
HOLLAND:
Right, this is where they stand.
Look, you can see two of them
up there now, out early.
Irene Richardson lived up there.
Cowper Street.
So she'd have come down
and got in the car
right around there.
Did you get the clothes? The boots?
Aye, and you'll need a jacket.
Something big enough
to put a radio in.
And make-up.
Have you not got any make-up?
I do, sir, only...
not always the same colours as,
you know,
you might see lasses
wearing out here.
Right.
Just make sure you keep receipts.
And they'll want roughing up a bit,
the clothes.
Can't come out here looking all new.
Yeah, that's a good point,
that, Les.
A very good point.
Yeah, they'll need to look dirty.
Any questions?
Why do they work in pairs?
It's safer.
Each one keeps an eye
on where the other one's going.
But... I won't be in pairs.
No, you'll be in a trio.
Me and DI Hanley
are at t'other end of the radio.
You'll be fine, Jill. All right?
Right, pay attention,
cos you need to see
how they work the street,
otherwise you'll stick out
like a bloody sore thumb.
Won't she, Les?
She will.
DSI John Domaille
to see Chief Constable Gregory.
Now, the man that we're looking for
drives a car
with two India Autoway tyres,
both well worn,
a Pneumant tyre and an Esso.
Now, the width between those tyres
are 46 and one quarter inch.
Now, the chances of any car
having that precise combination...
..are 159 million to one.
In other words, unique.
How many cars is that?
You say only one car
actually has them tyres,
but how many cars COULD have them?
How many makes?
Less than a hundred.
Hundred?
Less than.
I couldn't name a hundred.
Well, that number will come down,
Dick.
Will it?
Yes. How?
We've got all officers on the beat
in Leeds checking cars
wherever they go.
Car parks, garages and so on.
Hundreds of officers ruling out
hundreds of cars every day.
And two of these tyres
were worn down, you say?
Mm-hmm.
And when did he do Richardson?
Were that top of February?
Hmm.
That's right.
So, what, that's three months
since he left these marks?
He might have replaced them.
That's what you're saying?
Well, no, it's just an observation.
But, you know, if he were worried
that he'd left these marks
in the first place, then...
Then he definitely will.
Well, you'd imagine, wouldn't you?
Sorry, George.
What are you doing here exactly?
He's fresh eyes, Jim.
We're hunting a man
who's lost all sanity.
I want my best men in this room
thrashing this out.
And it's not just Leeds,
is it, John?
You've got him doing
this whore in Bradford.
Atkinson.
Yes, but...
is that linked, though?
Well, is that what David Gee says?
He wants a meeting up at the lab
to talk it all through.
Does he?
Tomorrow morning.
Was anybody planning on telling me
about this meeting?
Well, that's you being told now,
Jim.
So that's four.
And he's spreading.
Outside of Leeds.
And it's more often.
And the papers are all over it.
Might just be
"ladies of the street",
but it's how it looks, in't it?
I mean, come on...
"Hundred makes of car."
You know what's gonna happen,
don't you?
If it happens again,
your phone is going to ring,
and it'll be me saying,
"I'm having it." The whole case.
Not just a city job now,
this affects all of us,
the whole of Yorkshire.
Well, George.
You know the number.
REPORTER: 'This man
is completely out of control.'
'That certainly seems to be
the case.'
'What clues has he left you?'
'Well, I have a list of men
'that I know knew Miss Atkinson
very well indeed.
'Names listed in her diary.'
She didn't have a bloody diary.
'I shall be visiting
'each and every one of those men
named in that diary, personally.
'I would think it might be helpful
'if those people came forward
to see me
'rather than have me make enquiries
about them.'
Does he think the whole world's
gone stupid or what?
If he really had a diary
with a list of punters,
he'd not be standing about on telly
asking 'em all to come forward.
He'd be talking to 'em already.
Course he bloody would.
NEWS REPORT CONTINUES
You all right?
All right.
Thank you.
DOOR SHUTS
SHE EXHALES HEAVILY
I'm going.
Why don't you stay for a bit?
No, I mean I'm "going" going.
To London.
SHOUTING
It's not safe!
Not with this bastard about.
She were our friend.
Our mate.
She'll never forgive us.
Come.
I can't.
Well, I'll get you a ticket.
I've got my boy.
We can take him, too!
To London?
We'll find a way.
There's no way.
Well, why don't he stay
with his dad?
Cos he's buggered off
back to Dublin.
Listen.
If you stay on the beat,
then that bastard on there...
he'll come for you...
and he'll kill you!
He won't.
He won't, cos we know now...
don't we?
We know to be careful.
We can watch out for each other.
Only go with blokes
we've been with before.
I need to go home.
I'll see you tomorrow night, yeah?
Promise we'll chat tomorrow night.
I'll try.
I'll ring you. OK?
See ya.
Here y'are.
No, please.
Not after today.
"One week spent in hospital,
"so unable to claim Social Security
during that time."
That's right, isn't it?
"Ongoing headaches, so unable
to hold down consistent work,"
which I've been able
to corroborate here.
Erm, I've said that that might be
an ongoing problem,
which it might not,
but that'll only help them
take this more seriously.
OK? And if you're happy with that,
you just need to sign the bottom.
And then while you're doing that,
I'll try and find us an envelope.
Thank you, Doctor.
New?
For the shopping.
Very smart.
Anita.
Where do we keep the envelopes?
We were broadly agreed
on the injuries.
Curved lacerations to the head,
puncture wounds to the torso,
especially the abdomen.
But there are some differences, too.
It's not exactly clear
whether it was just one weapon
or two, for example.
The fact it's indoors.
In Bradford.
Well, that's right.
We shouldn't seize upon connections
in some regards and ignore others.
I wasn't convinced that we could
eliminate Atkinson from the series,
I still had my doubts.
And what did it...
was the boot print we found
at the Emily Jackson scene.
Yep, I know it well.
The size seven.
Except that this is NOT
the Jackson print.
This is a print that was taken from
a bed sheet at the Atkinson scene.
Also a Wellington boot.
Also a Dunlop.
Also a seven.
Jackson, Atkinson.
Exact same boot.
Exact same man.
No. No way on God's earth.
I should never have said anything.
You should never have volunteered.
It weren't like that, I were asked.
Asked or told?
It's the same thing.
They're the men in charge -
if they're asking, they're telling.
And it's all properly organised.
I'll have a radio. Oh, great (!)
And there'll be men and all,
in case anything happens.
This is how it works.
They could've asked anyone, Bob,
but they asked me.
So, what, you'll have to...
dress up? So...
INDISTINCT CHATTER
You'll have to dress up.
As a hooker.
Yeah.
So men can what?
Drive by and look at you?
So men can drive by
and I can look at them.
CAR HORN HONKS
LOCKER SLAMS
KNOCK AT DOOR
DOMAILLE: You ready?
Yes.
Right, we'll be in t'car.
FOOTSTEPS RECEDE
Right, we'll park here, on t'corner.
That way, nobody can spot us.
You wanna try your radio again
for me? Testing.
Any cars, punters,
anything you don't like -
you say it quietly,
and we'll write it down.
Anyone starts wanting business -
you're not working,
just waiting for a mate. OK?
Sir.
'Ey. We're here.
We got lads undercover
parked up the road.
No-one can get near you.
She looks good.
DOG BARKING
MAN: You doing business? How much?
No. I'm just...
I'm not.
I'm just waiting for a mate.
Slut.
Oi. My mate stands there.
I said me mate goes there.
When she comes,
you'll have to do one, all right?
Right.
'Where are you?'
You said you were coming out,
so where are you?
W-We did say that, Georgie.
We did. You said you'd be here.
Hillman Hunter, Grey.
Registration
Kilo-Uniform-Golf-seven.
He's been round a few times.
Erm, same goes for an Allegro,
I think that was.
Green.
X-ray-Mike...
..Victor-six.
SHE GASPS
And a man on foot, over.
White, or Greek, maybe.
He appears to be...
Hey.
In fact, I'm just going to... Hey.
Doing business?
Er, no. Sorry.
Yeah, you are.
I'm not, love. I'm off home.
SHE PANTS
Where you going?
Oi!
SHE GASPS
Fuck...
Oi!
Hello?! Can you hear me?
Slag!
PANTING CONTINUES
I'm on the back of Gathorne!
RAPID FOOTSTEPS,
PANTING
SHE BANGS WINDOW
Where were you?!
Why the bloody hell
didn't you say anything?!
Where did you go?
I were shouting,
I were running right up there!
Did you push t'button in properly?
What?
If you don't press it,
can't hear you.
DOG BARKING
MAN: Someone might come out.
That dog's always barking.
No-one takes a blind bit of notice.
Fiver first.
We've done this before, you know.
Last year.
I only stopped cos it were you,
you know that, don't you?
Shit.
I'll have to give you double
next time.
You won't. You'll give it me now
or you're not getting owt.
Come on.
Don't be like that.
Like what?
Said I'd give you double next time.
'Ey, no, where you going? 'Ey!
No, come on, 'ey.
Come 'ere!
SHE CRIES OUT
Get back in 'ere and
shut the fucking door, you stupid...
SHE SCRATCHES
Agh! Fucking hell!
SHE STRUGGLES,
HE GRUNTS
Jesus!
Shut that fucking door.
HE PANTS
Fuck...
SHE GROANS
Stupid...
You bite...
and I'll break your fucking neck!
BELT JANGLES
No...
BARKING CONTINUES
All right, love?
It's Donna, in't it?
What we done this time, Donna?
Can you leave me alone, please?
You won't get a punter
looking like that.
Don't know what you're on about.
Where are you going, Donna?
To mind my own fucking business.
And so should you fucking be.
We were gonna leave you alone.
You are under arrest
on suspicion of soliciting.
You do not have to say anything
unless you wish you do so,
but what you do say
may be written down
and given as evidence. Now get in!
SHE SNIFFS
Is it done?
Yeah.
You all right?
Hey.
What?
Well, d'you think you can bring
this home with you?
No.
I'm gonna get changed.
'I should be in hospital, I should.
Not here.'
You've no right.
We've every right.
Why?
Cos you're under arrest.
Why?!
You know why.
Loitering for the purpose of
being a common prostitute.
I dunno what you're on about.
It's just like you were loitering
for the purpose of being a
common prostitute back in November.
Just like you were loitering
for the purpose of being a
common prostitute back in July '75.
Look. I told you.
I got me purse nicked in t'pub.
I chased him out.
I should never've chased him,
I know that,
but in heat of t'moment...
And then he turned on me
in Oldcastle Street.
Hit me, and I fell, like that.
Only problem with that is...
You want him in here, not me.
Donna... Case he robs someone else.
Is it hot in here, or...
Shut up and listen.
We've had residents complaining
about prostitutes
taking punters by
garages in Oldcastle Street.
That won't be you, then?
No.
Residents describing
one of the prostitutes
as having "dirty blonde hair".
"A dirty slag with dirty blonde
hair, wearing a sky blue coat.
"I know when she's out there cos
our dog always starts barking."
That slag in the sky blue coat...
That won't be you, then?
All right.
But I weren't soliciting,
cos he never gave me any money.
Who didn't?
The bastard what did this.
So you asked for money,
and he just never paid her any.
No. He did this instead.
Then he forced me to suck him off.
Right. So you're admitting it.
What?
Loitering with the PURPOSE of
being a common prostitute.
The only reason you were with him
in t'first place
is cos you wanted money for sex.
And if you hadn't
have been doing that...
breaking t'law...
and you know it's breaking t'law
cos you've been guilty of it
before...
..then this business here...
..well,
this'd never have happened.
So in a way, Donna...
..this is your fault.
TELEPHONE RINGS
Gregory.
I told you, if it happened again,
you'd be hearing from me.
Where?
'Leeds. Young lass.'
16. And she weren't
a prostitute this time.
She were innocent.
Right, this is me making
the decision.
It's yours, George.
The whole investigation.
'Hobson, Domaille in Bradford,
they all work for you.'
Right. Thank you, sir.
Love! I'm out.
Jim's up there.
A couple of kids found her.
Up by t'trees.
Usual circus round here.
They've really gone at her.
She's up there.
Oh, here we go.
Hey, what's going on here?
Gregory wants me
to take overall charge.
I'm off to talk to the parents,
so you stay here
and secure the scene.
Overall charge? Eh? Find out all you
can, and then I'll call you later.
Hey! I'm talking to you.
What, you want to do this now?
Five. Five dead women.
And this one a normal lass
from a good family,
done nothing wrong,
and she is lying there
because you and Dennis, you failed.
So this gets sorted now.
MRS MACDONALD:
'I knew there was something wrong.'
As soon as they knocked, I said it.
I said that straight away.
I know how you feel.
How can you?
How can you come in here
and say that?
You cannot know how we feel!
I lost a daughter, myself.
She were ill.
Taken from us, me and my wife,
when she were little.
She had her
whole life ahead of her.
Just like your Jayne.
They said on t'news. This...
..Ripper...
..he only kills prostitutes.
Aye, he does.
But that weren't Jayne.
No, I know... Mr MacDonald. I know.
See, what's happened is, he's...
..seen your Jayne, and he's, er...
..he's made a terrible mistake.
SHE SOBS
Mr MacDonald.
I'm now in charge of
this investigation,
and I give you my word.
Look at me.
I give you my word
that I will catch this animal.
Cos that's what he is.
And you have that from me,
Mr MacDonald.
All right?
MAN ON RADIO: 'Jayne MacDonald
is now the fifth victim
'of the man the police are calling
the Yorkshire Ripper.
'Jayne, a local girl
from the Scott Hall area,
'was walking home...'
KNOCK ON DOOR
'..Reginald Street, Leeds,
when she was attacked...'
Where is it?
'..in the early hours of
Sunday morning.
'In other news, British...'
Want me to read it?
'..and Sue Barker and Virginia Wade
are through to the quarter-finals.'
"From the Criminal Injuries
Compensation Board.
"Dear Miss Claxton...
"..we regret to inform you..."
Told you.
"..that your application for the
compensation has been unsuccessful.
Told you.
"Following a consultation with
"the West Yorkshire
Metropolitan Police Service,
"it is the judgement of the Board
that...
"..one, on May 9th, 1976,
"the claimant did attempt to mislead
officers investigating the case.
"Two, the claimant was working...
"..as a prostitute...
"at the time of
the alleged incident.
"A fact that the claimant
tried to deny.
"This not only invalidates
any claim,
"but draws further judgement
from this board
"that by choosing to work
as a prostitute...
"..the claimant did invite
the attack upon herself."
"Choosing to work as a prostitute."
As if them girls have a choice.
TELEPHONE RINGS
Hello?
SHE SIGHS
'I'm glad you picked up and not him.
'I'm sorry it's took me so long
to ring.
'Donna?'
How's it been going?
Brilliant.
I've even got my own car.
It's green.
'How 'bout you?'
Yeah, same. Things are brilliant.
'Things are better, then?'
Oh, yeah. Miles.
Are you still...?
No. I've put all that behind me.
Same.
I've given all that up.
It's not something
you want to be doing forever, is it?
'Listen, I were thinking...
'I might come back.
'Drive back one weekend.
Y'know, for me birthday.'
No, yeah, you should. Definitely.
'And listen...
'if something comes up, if I...
'..can't get back
for whatever reason, I'll ring you.
'OK? I promise I'll ring you.
'Ta-ra.'
LINE CUTS
'This is what I wanted to show you.'
I only clocked this yesterday.
Wilma McCann's body
were found there.
And she lived... there.
Jayne MacDonald
just lived over t'road.
That's two victims
in t'very same street.
Now, they put
everything into Leeds,
so he starts killing in Bradford.
They put everything into Bradford,
and he comes back here,
right where he started.
Well, who's to say t'Ripper
doesn't live here an' all?
He could live in one of them houses.
He could be...
He could be watching us right now.
Well, I tell you what.
If he can see us,
he should be panicking.
Cos he's looking at the two men
who are gonna catch him.
Subtitles by accessibility@itv.com