Fuck her. Come on.
- Okay. Let me out.
- Really, Scotty?
It's been 27 minutes.
That's nothing.
Come on! I'm done.
You have, like,
a half an hour of air left.
- You little bitch, you're fine.
- Let him out, dick.
Whoa! He returns unto us,
unmolested by the great darkness.
Give me a break.
Hey, when he suffocates,
do you suffocate?
- Har har!
- No, really.
Scott Frost
with a pathetic 28 minutes.
That's not even near the record,
buddy.
I can break the record.
Uh, excuse me, Garvey.
You need to do the invocation
before you attempt the crossing.
- That's stupid.
- Invo-fucking-cation, Garvey.
"On October 14th, 2011,
Paul Glouski was forced
inside this conveyance
against his will in a childish prank
and was never seen
or heard from again."
"Nor heard from again."
"Nor heard from again.
Now I honor the mystery of his loss
by repeating his suffering
and embracing the great darkness."
Amen.
I'll miss you. Be safe.
See you on the other side, Garvey.
Thanks.
You want to come over?
- Right now?
- Mm-hm.
You sure?
The first four dates,
I was on the fence,
but I'm over it now.
All right.
Let me just check in with Jill.
- So have you told her about us?
- Sure.
"Hey, honey.
About to go have sex with Nora
for the first time.
A little nervous.
Wish me luck."
- And a winky face.
- No, stop.
Send.
Yup.
Shit.
Fuck.
Twenty-one seconds
and you've got the record, Garvey.
Nineteen, 18, 17,
16, 15,
14, 13, 12
11, ten, nine, eight, seven,
six, five, four, three, two, one!
- You got it!
- Woo!
Get me out of here!
Shit.
- Shit.
- My God.
- What happened?
- This thing isn't working.
- It's not working.
- Get me out of here!
My God!
- Let me out!
- We're gonna get you out!
- Just wait up.
- Find something to open it with!
- Fucking shit!
- How long? How long?
I can't breathe!
Garvey, it's okay.
- Is she breathing?
- Somebody fucking call 911!
Get the fuck back!
Don't tell your dad you saw me.
- Who was that?
- My grandpa.
Shit.
Fuck. Fuck. Fucker!
Goddamn it!
Fuck.
Hey.
Wake up. I made you some soup.
There's spiders under water.
Christine, come on.
You need to eat something.
I'm not hungry.
You're burning up.
- The baby, it's--
- Nothing can hurt the baby.
He's the one.
The only one. He's the bridge.
Okay. Okay. You need some rest.
Did Wayne call?
No, Christine.
Wayne hasn't called in two months.
He'll call.
Here.
I'll be right back.
- Help you?
- Yeah.
- Are these safe for pregnant women?
- How far along is she?
Almost eight months.
She should call her O.B.
Okay, thanks. I'll do that.
Hello?
Wayne?
- Who's this?
- It's Tom.
Tom.
Tom!
Of course it is. I know that.
I called you.
Are you okay?
I'm great. I'm just great, Tom.
Is Christine with you right now?
- No, I'm at a pharmacy, so...
- Fine.
- How much is left?
- What?
The money that I gave you.
How much is left?
- About $6,000.
- Fuck. All right, Tom.
What you need to do is,
you need to take that money
and you need to take half of it.
That's three.
You need to put it in an envelope
and take that envelope
and you seal it very securely
under the mailbox
on Harper and 15th.
It's across from the chicken place.
- When do you need me to go?
- Now, Tom. Fucking now.
- And then what?
- Tom.
Don't ask me "then what?"
I'm sorry.
It's just Christine is--
You know, she's pretty sick,
and the baby's coming soon--
"Naked I came from my mother's womb,
and naked I will depart."
Have you fucked her, Tom?
Have you put it in, just a little?
No.
Just do what I told you to do.
Get the fucking money, yeah?
Yeah.
It won't be long now.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Is this because of me?
Is this Patti's fucking idea?
Okay, I'm asking you to leave.
Right now!
This house is off fucking limits.
Want to come inside?
That was fucking fantastic.
Why, thank you.
I usually ignore them.
First time they've been out there
in a couple of months.
Though I'm pretty sure they broke in
and stole some of my family photos.
Ah. Mm...
On the night of the dance.
- On the night I met you.
- Right.
No, they broke
into a whole bunch of houses.
Basically anyone who--
Lost someone?
Right.
I have to question their strategy.
I mean, that's how they
recruit people?
"No! My family photos are gone.
I better stop talking
and start chain-smoking."
Oh, shit.
Your wife, I'm--
- Ah, no.
- I'm sorry.
Come on. It's okay.
I don't...
I don't know how to talk to you yet.
I don't know how to talk to you,
either.
Those fuckers ruined it, huh?
Wanna try again tomorrow night?
Absolutely.
Hey.
I thought you weren't
coming home tonight.
What's up?
Just ask him.
What? What happened?
What did Grandpa do?
Why?
Did he hurt anyone?
- Why are you asking?
- Did he?
Yeah.
And that's why
he's in that hospital?
Yes.
Well, he's not anymore.
What?
Chief, this is the only photo
I could find on such short notice.
- Everybody's waiting.
- All right. Thanks.
Your daughter saw him, huh?
I mean, what are the odds of that?
Pass out the photos, Dennis.
All right, everybody. Listen up.
As most of you are aware,
a couple of years ago,
our former chief started exhibiting
some erratic behavior.
"Erratic"?
He burned down the fucking library.
Following which
he voluntarily remanded himself
to a secure psychiatric facility...
which he has just walked out of.
I want patrols working all
residential neighborhoods all night.
Work a grid.
How do you want us to handle it
if we get eyes on him, chief?
Do not engage.
Just call me immediately.
Is that understood?
Do you have any idea what he wants?
It doesn't matter what he wants.
What if we find him
in a violent situation?
Then you have to stop him.
Dismissed.
Four on this side.
Squawk me if anyone runs
out the back.
Chief.
- Is he in there?
- What?
My father. Is he in there with you?
- They let him out?
- No.
He escaped.
- Did anybody get hurt?
- Not yet.
I'm gonna have to come in there
and take a look around.
Fuck you, Kevin.
I haven't talked to your father
in a month.
What?
I could ignore the crazy.
Even he could ignore it for a while,
but...
he just wouldn't
shut the fuck up.
Will you call me if he comes here?
He's not coming to me, Kevin.
He's coming to you.
Cairo.
Come on, Chief. I got one trapped.
Dad.
Tommy.
Don't want to shoot.
Did you find him?
What?
- Grandpa. Did you find him?
- No. No. Not yet.
Why is there a dog
tied up in our yard?
Your dad brought him home
last night.
I can't believe you didn't wake up.
So, what, it's ours now?
He's gonna rehabilitate it.
How's your hand? Did you put
Neosporin like I told you?
Yeah.
It's....
It's good. Thanks.
Hello?
Is he okay? I'll be right there.
I got to go.
No, I don't know yet, sir.
What happened?
It's okay. Just tell me.
Saw him trying to get in,
so I went over to talk to him.
Why the fuck
did you do that, Dennis?
He always liked me.
Excuse me.
Did you see the man who did this?
No inglés.
Oh. Uh...
- Visto quién hizo éste?
- Sí.
No.
Come on. Jesus!
Will you please?
Get back, motherfucker! Get back!
This is my house.
Get back! Give me--
Hey, honey.
- What are you doing?
- I know, goddamn it.
I'm not at liberty to say.
- You hungry?
- Uh... uh-huh.
What the hell happened
to my cabinetry?
- Deer broke in.
- No shit.
Try not to get trapped in there.
How did you know?
Uh...
I didn't.
I walked out the back door
of my residence.
I just started running.
About ten minutes later,
I come across a bunch of idiots
yelling at a refrigerator.
You expect me to believe that?
Not really.
Your voices,
can you hear them right now?
Yeah.
What are they saying?
They're saying...
...that you look like Snow White.
Could I borrow 200 bucks?
I don't have any cash.
You have any tranquilizers?
- Will those help you?
- They're not for me.
They're for that dog out there
trying to eat my balls.
Jesus.
Why is your dad taking
all this shit?
He's under a lot of pressure,
I guess.
Yeah, I reckon he is.
How's your brother?
I haven't talked to him in a while.
- You know where he is?
- Anywhere that's not here.
Here ain't so bad, sweetheart.
Bingo.
We need some meat. You got meat?
Why are you drugging the dog?
Because he won't--
She's just trying to help.
What the fuck do you think--
- Jill!
- Disarm system now.
Jill! Jill, where are you?
We're up here!
When did you call him?
Before I let you in.
Good girl.
I borrowed your sweatshirt.
I'll take him back.
Okay.
Dennis okay?
He's gonna need stitches.
He's a nice guy. Tell him I'm sorry.
He just got in my way.
- How you sleeping?
- What?
You have a fucking pharmacy
on your nightstand.
- That shit fucks with your head.
- Thanks for the advice.
You used to take my advice.
- You're not gonna ask me, are you?
- Ask you what?
Why I busted out.
Dad, I don't need this shit
right now.
Maybe it's exactly what you need.
- What the fuck does that even mean?
- Stop!
Damn it! What the fuck!
Jesus fucking Christ.
Get the fuck out of my way.
Get out of my way!
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
Get out of my fucking way.
Fuck.
Goddamn it.
- Bitch.
- Never!
Dude, seriously?
What are you using
my credit card for?
Don't worry about it.
I'll pay you back.
It's just that if you go over
the limit, I'm gonna have to tell--
- Come on!
- That's right.
Are you watching these two fuck,
Garvey?
She's ordering something secret
from the Internet.
How long is it gonna take you
to get ready for Dixon's party?
It won't take me long, dip-shit.
I'm not going.
Are you just gonna hang around here
with my dad all night?
He's not gonna be here.
How do you know?
Because whenever you go out,
he goes out.
I suspect with a lady friend.
Okay.
Ow! Goddamn. Damn it!
Yeah?
I'm here to see Wayne.
Who the fuck are you?
Wayne!
I know you're in here, Wayne! Wayne!
Don't fucking move!
- Take it easy.
- You okay, Liane?
How does he know about Wayne?
I'm the one
who dropped off the money.
I just wanted to talk to him.
Why?
Because I have one, too.
One of what?
One of her.
Hey, Mr. Garvey.
- Where's Jill?
- She went out.
- So you brought your dad back, huh?
- Still working on it.
You might want to feed that thing.
Your new dog.
Yeah.
You don't remember, do you?
- What?
- Last night.
Getting the dog.
Of course I remember.
Then what did you say to me
when I bandaged up your hand?
We really like having you here
with us, Aimee.
- Do you like it here?
- Yeah.
Good.
It's okay. It's okay.
All right. Go get it.
- Hello?
- Is Reverend Jamison here?
No. May I help you?
Matt!
- Mr. Matt is not here.
- Matt! Matt!
- Where's your phone?
- Why?
Because if I call from mine,
he's not gonna pick up.
Call him right now!
Hello.
Mr. Matt, there's--
Matt, it's Kevin Garvey.
Is my father with you?
Kevin, I-- No.
What makes you think so?
I think so because he was just in
my fucking backyard
digging up a jar full of cash with
one of your goddamn fliers in it!
- Kevin, I--
- Is he with you or not?
He's almost ready to see you,
but we need to get something first.
No, you're not getting shit,
not until you tell me where you are
right fucking now.
Meet us at Sonny's off Route 17,
90 minutes.
Matt. Matt!
Motherfucker!
Jesus, you were there
the night of the raid.
Yeah, I was there.
Fuck. So many people.
- Sorry I didn't recognize you, man.
- How did you get out?
One of the tunnels.
Wayne met up with us
at this fucking rest stop.
Gave us some cash, a phone,
looked at me, and then said,
- "This girl--"
- "This girl, she's everything, yes?"
Motherfucker. Word for word, man.
- Which one?
- What?
- Which girl? Who are you with?
- Christine.
Is she pregnant?
And the baby is Wayne's?
It's not mine.
How many others
do you think he's got?
Does it matter?
- Did he ever hug you, man?
- No.
Because he did it to me,
and it was so fucking real, man.
He took away all my pain.
There's got to be a reason
he didn't tell us about each other.
- He's got to have a plan.
- There's no fucking plan, dude.
Where is she?
- Where is that whore?
- Jesus Christ!
Fuck!
- My baby!
- Goddamn it!
He said it would be my baby!
He promised me.
He's the one. He's the only one!
He's the bridge!
- Shh...
- He's the one.
They just got here.
Want us to grab them?
- No, let them come in.
- Copy that.
Kevin.
Reverend, could you give us
a few minutes, please?
- I'll be at the counter.
- Thank you.
Picked your favorite place.
Only way I could get you to church
was promise you fries and a shake.
Will you please take these off?
- No.
- Come on.
I saw two units in the parking lot.
I hired that fat-ass
three booths back.
I won't run.
You have my word.
Come on.
What's this?
Son, you need to know,
I wanted to keep you out of this.
I tried to change their minds,
but they wouldn't stop.
They would never stop.
I couldn't find it in the library,
so I had to go to some asshole
in Gabota that sells them.
May, 1972.
They were very specific.
It had to be this one.
What am I supposed to do with this?
I need you to take it.
Why?
Please, Kevin. Just take--
What fucking difference
does it make, huh?
Oh, God.
You need to accept it.
Dad, what does that even mean?
I know you think I'm fucking crazy,
but I'm not.
I'm not, Kevin.
What I hear, what they say...
...it is the goddamn truth.
It's the truth, son.
They don't tell me what they don't--
Jesus Christ.
I'm trying. This isn't easy.
Okay, I'll tell him.
Listen to me. Just listen to me.
The lucky ones.
They're not needed.
They get to stay sane.
But we....
We're in the fucking game now,
you understand?
That whistle blew three years ago,
and you cannot ignore it anymore.
Your services are being requested.
Eyes open, wide awake.
This is your invitation.
This is your purpose.
This is what you fucking accept.
So now I have a purpose?
Context is everything, son.
Where did you go, Dad?
I'm right here.
You left me.
You left me when I needed you.
Now you wanna infect me
with whatever it is you got.
I don't accept your bullshit.
I have responsibilities.
I have commitments.
I'm not gonna leave my family.
You know.
Inside you know this is real,
and that makes you a coward.
A coward?
You don't want it,
you don't want what I have,
then I relieve you of it.
- Sit down.
- I relieve you.
- Dad, calm down.
- Just don't wake up. Stay asleep.
Just go back to sleep.
Don't wake up!
Don't anybody wake up!
Go to sleep!
Go back to fucking sleep!
- You'll come see me on Sunday?
- Of course.
They're not gonna let you off
that easy, son.
What?
"Said the father, my dear son,
relate not thy vision
to thy brothers,
lest they concoct a plot against--"
Fuck you, Matt.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Hey.
Are you okay?
Oh, yeah.
You wanna talk about it?
I think I might be going crazy.
Well, my friend,
you've come to the right place.
Morning.
- Morning.
So, were you working all night?
I was actually with a friend.
- Oh.
- I think you'd like her.
We've got to find time
to get together soon.
- What is this?
- What?
This.
What the fuck is it doing here?
I ordered it for Grandpa.
- He told you to order this?
- No.
He dropped a piece of paper.
What's your problem?
- I don't have a fucking problem.
- What the fuck, Dad?
Tom?
Christine?
Hello!
It's a girl.