Fuck you, you fucking cunts.
Hey. Hey. Please.
Please. Please don't.
Please.
Please. Please. Don't.
Please stop.
Please. Please. Please stop.
Don't! Please stop!
Please. Stop.
Where is everyone going?
Whatever happened, I wanna help.
Out of the way, goddamn it!
Move aside!
Thanks, Brad.
I'm here at the Heaven's Converts
compound in Noma, Florida,
where cult members recently opened
fire on ATFEC agents.
Tensions between the cult
and the agency
have been escalating for days,
starting when ATFEC--
Morning.
Hey, I'm leaving in 10 minutes.
You want a ride to school?
Uh-uh.
Have you seen
a bunch of my white shirts?
No.
- You sure?
- Yes.
Morning, Mr. Garvey.
You want me to make coffee?
Hey!
Did you turn the alarm off
last night?
Nope. It wasn't on.
It was. I set it to "Stay."
- Motion detector deactivated.
- Looks like you mastered it.
Where is she?
Are you surprised?
We want them to remember something
they wanna forget.
They weren't just gonna
leave us alone, right?
It was only a matter of time.
I guess I should be scared,
but I'm not.
Is that weird?
Fuck.
I just hope
she didn't have to suffer too much.
Are you okay?
Hold on.
It's okay. Laurie, it's okay.
Laurie. God.
I think we need some help!
Laurie, it's okay. It's okay.
It's okay.
Just breathe.
It's okay. It's okay.
Help! It's okay.
Somebody, please help!
Hey!
What are you doing? Hey!
- You got the rocks?
- What?
The rocks.
We need the pictures of position
before you can bag them.
Yeah, okay, sorry.
Give me a break, all right?
She lived with you for a year.
You got no emergency contact?
Nobody?
- "No family."
- I guess she just grew on a tree.
You get statements from everyone
in their search party?
Yes, sir.
Mike's at the Biggie,
getting yellow pads in bulk.
I need you off the streets.
I don't have the resources
to protect you.
I know.
Tell me to fuck off. I get it.
Good. Thanks.
Hey, Chief.
One of the witnesses says
he's gonna late for his
ballroom dancing lesson.
Okay if I let him go?
Your boys gonna give me my gun back?
It doesn't shoot rocks.
- What were you doing out here?
- Drinking beers, star-gazing.
Hell, you could have been my alibi
if you didn't keep blowing me off.
- Hey, Dean.
- Burt.
We have an arrangement.
Population control.
Shit!
Hey, careful, goddamn it!
Fucking horrific.
Is that the best you can do?
Sorry to bother you,
but could I speak with my daughter?
No problem.
Jill. Jill. Honey.
Jill, what's wrong?
Jill? Jill?
- Wait.
- Just tell me.
Tell me what happened to her.
What happened to her?
No, no. Your mom's okay.
- Your mom's okay.
- Then why are you here?
Last night a woman was attacked,
in the G.R.
I wanted you to hear from me first
so you wouldn't worry.
Please don't tell your friends.
I want you home before dark.
You and Aimee order a pizza.
I'm gonna work late.
Might not see you
till the morning, okay?
I'll text you.
Okay, yeah.
I shouldn't have cried.
She wouldn't have cried for me.
Ready? Okay.
I understand we had a rough morning.
Sorry. Compound fracture.
Okay. I had a look at your tests.
Everything seems normal.
Let's have a listen.
All right.
May I ask how many cigarettes a day
you're smoking?
Okay, what you experienced
was most likely a panic attack.
If it happens again,
take two of these.
If you need more,
you're gonna need a prescription
from a psychiatrist.
You're free to go.
"Is the victim
a member of an organization
that claims an independent belief
not listed on the AWR?"
Check.
"Is the membership
of the organization--"
- It was not your call...
- ...currently comprised of more than
- ...to make!
- ...than 40 individuals?"
Check. "Has there been a pattern
of violent incidents involving...."
I know what it fucking says
because I signed that fucking thing!
Check!
"If these conditions are met..."
You gonna continue reading?
There's a whole bunch
of fucking big words in there
that you might not even
fucking understand!
"...Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms,
Explosives and Cult,
please contact the Bureau
immediately!"
Immediately!
How about I immediately shove that
fucking thing up your ass?
- Chief Garvey!
- Fat fuck.
What's up, gentlemen?
Det. Vitello took it upon himself
to call the feds
and punt on our homicide.
I was just doing my job
by following the guidelines--
Lou? Shut the fuck up.
Who'd you talk to at ATFEC?
- Agent Sean Kilaney.
- Great.
Please give Agent Kilaney's contact
information to your boss,
so that he can undo your fuck-up.
Thank you.
You need anything from me?
Curfew. Nobody out past dark.
Look, the town feels a response,
and if the G.R. violates,
I can arrest them.
I'll call a council meeting
for tomorrow.
Can you be there to make your case?
- I just made my case.
- It's a formality, Kevin.
I trust you,
but this is a fucking mess.
Lots of eyes on us.
You won't be influenced
by your family situation?
No. I won't.
- MasterCard gets us miles.
- We haven't flown in years.
- Miles are meaningless.
- They're obviously not meaningless.
- Yes, they are.
- Why do you keep saying that?
- Can you pull my wallet?
- I got it, I got it.
- I did, I did, I did.
- You got it?
Amanda.
Amanda, stop staring.
You, too.
Go.
Sean Kilaney at Alcohol, Tobacco
Firearms, Explosives and Cults.
Leave a message
and I'll hit you back.
Agent Kilaney, Chief Kevin Garvey
from Mapleton, New York.
One of our investigators
just spoke to you
about a possible
cult-related incident.
But his assessment was premature,
so we'd like to handle it ourselves.
If you give me a call back,
I'd appreciate it. Thanks.
Hey! Hey!
Sorry.
They're loud, but they're harmless.
Hey! Hey!
Don't worry about it.
Staking out the Moonies, huh?
They made an offer on my house.
Guess they're running out of room.
- Bought a church, too, I heard.
- Yeah.
One of them got killed, huh?
Sorry, I'm not allowed to discuss
ongoing investigations.
Don't investigate too hard.
- Hello?
- Dennis, it's me.
Yeah, Chief?
I want you to go
and pick up Reverend Jamison,
bring him in.
Morning, Mr. Garvey.
Why isn't the alarm on?
You didn't text me.
I didn't want it to go off at night
when you got home.
Well, that defeats the purpose.
Please, just set it, okay?
Mr. Garvey, we heard that the woman
who got killed
got dragged behind a truck
and, like, crucified.
- Is that true?
- He's not gonna tell you.
- No, Aimee, it's not true.
- See?
What a relief.
Is she okay?
She's Jill.
- What does that mean?
- She doesn't really do okay.
Can't win.
Now you're getting it.
You look nice.
Have a seat. Hungry?
They got all-day breakfast here.
What can I get for you, hon?
- Can we have a minute, please?
- Sure.
How long has it been
since you've spoken, Laurie?
About seven months?
Eight. Right.
Well, Laurie, you are overdue
for a day off.
No, no. You can talk.
Just for today.
Say anything you want to.
Hey, I'm doing it, too, right?
Are you ready?
She's gonna have French toast,
scrambled eggs, order of bacon,
large orange juice.
- Coffee? She's gonna have coffee.
- Coffee.
You got it.
This is fucking good.
Sean Kilaney at Alcohol, Tobacco,
Firearms, Explosives and Cults.
Leave a message
and I'll hit you back.
Agent Kilaney,
Kevin Garvey again from Mapleton.
I left you a message last night,
but I haven't heard back.
Please call me. It's important.
Hey, Officer Mustard Stain.
Dropping off or what?
I'm actually picking up.
You got some of my shirts here.
Sure. You have a ticket?
Just check the computer.
It's under Garvey.
- No ticket, no?
- No, no ticket.
- Okay, you pick up last Tuesday.
- No, I know, I know I picked up.
But I'm missing my white shirts.
Can you just check again?
Sorry. No shirts, huh?
- You didn't even look.
- I looked on computer.
- Unless you have ticket.
- I don't have a ticket.
If they turn up, we'll call you.
Okay?
Mr. Extra Starch!
- Dropping off or what?
- Yeah.
Don't give up.
They want you to surrender
and sell them on the black market.
- Stay strong.
- I hope you have a ticket.
I always have a ticket.
Well, you know what they say.
They'll turn up
once you stop looking for them.
You think so?
No, probably not.
All right, see you later, Nora.
- Bye.
- Mr. Four Eyes! Yes.
Where are we?
Statements from the Moonies.
I didn't check the spelling.
Dennis has your priest
in the war room.
Gonna give him your confession?
Hey, Matt.
Thanks for coming in.
So...
...where were you two nights ago?
Why?
Well, according to the hospital,
you had a rock thrown at you
a couple months ago,
one aimed at the G.R.
Then they repaid your generosity
by buying up your church out
from under you
and they painted it white.
You think I had something to do
with what happened to that woman?
No.
Just wanna know where you were
a couple nights ago.
I was at my house
with my study group.
A few of them spent the night.
I appreciate the extra help
with Mary.
- Can you give me their names?
- Of course.
- The woman. Did she have family?
- Why?
Back when I had the church,
I used to see her sometimes.
She'd just stand outside
the way they do.
She never talked to me, of course,
but I don't know.
She became a familiar face.
Do you think I could see her?
What, her body?
Yes.
You do realize
you're a suspect, Matt?
Well, obviously, but once I'm not,
I'd like to pray for her.
Please? It'll just be five minutes.
No. You can't see her.
Hey, Chief, it's 3:00.
They're in Town Hall,
waiting for you.
What? Who?
- The mayor, the curfew thing.
- Oh, shit!
Please, everyone calm down.
I do appreciate your patience.
Just a few more moments,
I promise you.
- What the fuck?
- They showed up. I didn't know.
What, I'm not allowed
to leave my own house?
- How long is this gonna last?
- Please, hold your questions.
Chief Garvey suggested the curfew,
and he's here to explain
exactly how it will go.
- Chief?
- Really?
Um...
Well, Miss Mayor...
I'm sure you're all aware
that a violent hate crime occurred
a couple nights ago
to a member of the Guilty Remnant.
While we conduct our investigation,
I thought it would be
in the best interests of the town
if people remained in their homes
after eight p.m.
I work nights!
I'm sure we can make exceptions
if you have to get to a job.
So we have to change our lives
because of them?
They broke into my house
on Christmas.
People, please,
we're trying to keep everybody safe.
You're not trying to keep us safe.
Excuse me?
It just doesn't seem fair,
us being locked up
inside our houses.
We didn't do anything wrong.
I mean, with all due respect, Chief.
How do we even know these people
didn't do this to themselves?
Because you were with them
when they found the body.
Well, I was with some of them.
What are you?
You don't even live here.
Well, sure I do.
And when I moved here,
hell, it seemed like a nice place.
- Are you fucking serious?
- Okay.
I think everyone's had their say.
This is not a public vote.
It's for the council alone.
And, for the record,
I fully support Chief Garvey.
All in favor of imposing
an emergency town-wide curfew
to start at eight p.m.,
effective this evening?
All opposed?
Where's Patti?
Get all your people together here
in five minutes
from all your fucking houses.
I'll wait.
It's just been made clear to me
that it's officially open season
on you people.
Now, the ideal thing would be
for you all to stay off the streets,
but we all know
that's not gonna happen, is it?
Whistles.
Keep these on you at all times.
Use them.
I got my people on extra patrols,
and they're ready to respond.
This doesn't have to happen again,
but that's on you.
No one understands
whatever it is you believe in.
They don't give a shit.
As long as you leave them alone.
But if you keep
following people around,
buying up their homes,
painting everything white...
...breaking into their houses,
they will retaliate.
Any questions?
I'll take them in writing.
Thank you for your time.
It's Meg, right?
- Do you still talk?
- Yes.
- Where's Laurie?
- I don't know.
- Is she okay?
I'm the only person
that gives a shit about you people,
and you won't even tell me
where my wife is?
She's not your wife anymore.
- Okay. All done, girls?
- We are indeed.
Just the check.
Could I have a doggie bag,
please?
For what?
- Just get me the bag, sweetheart.
- Okay.
I brought her here, too.
Just over a year ago.
Gladys sat right there
where you're sitting right now.
I don't know how,
but she somehow got word
that her son had died.
Did she ever tell you she had a son?
No. It was over in Yemen, I think.
His helicopter just crashed
or some such.
And as you can imagine,
she did not take it very well.
She questioned her commitment,
she became distracted,
and she began to feel again.
And there was a lot of moping
and crying around the house,
and then it started to happen
out in the open.
So I brought her here, I fed her.
And I invited her
to speak her troubles out loud.
I gave her
every opportunity to talk.
She never spoke one word.
Never broke, just like you.
So I'm going to tell you
what I told her.
I understand the pull.
I understand. It's your family.
It's your past.
I understand that going back to them
feels comfortable and easy...
...because the alternative,
what we do, is very, very hard.
But there can't be any doubt,
Laurie.
Because doubt is fire!
And fire is gonna burn you up
until you are but ash!
Okay. Ladies, come see us again.
Yeah.
You remember what you told me to do
in the last session?
Just before everything changed?
Can I be excused, please?
Yeah.
Okay, Reverend.
You want to pray over her? Fine.
What made you
change your mind?
The closest thing
she's gonna get to a funeral.
Shit.
Jesus said to his disciples,
"Compare me to something
and tell me what I am like."
And Thomas said to him,
"Teacher, my mouth is utterly unable
to say what you are like."
And Jesus said,
"I am not your teacher
because you have become intoxicated
from the bubbling spring
I have tended."
And he took Thomas and withdrew
and spoke three sayings to him.
When Thomas came back,
his friends asked him,
"What did Jesus say to you?"
And Thomas responded...
..."If I tell you
what he spoke to me,
you will pick up rocks
and stone me,
and fire will come from the rocks
and devour you."
You wanna tell me what that means?
It means it's easier to stay silent
than it is to speak truth.
Killing these people is pointless.
They don't care
because they're already dead.
You know, what I want
is to bring them back to life.
Oh, sorry about that.
Must be that one.
Uh, Billy?
What happened to the D.B.
in four?
- Female?
- Oh, we shipped her out.
You fucking shipped her? Where?
Sorry. We got an email ordering us
to send her out to Virginia.
It was from Agent Kilaney.
It says you guys called him.
Sean Kilaney at Alcohol, Tobacco,
Firearms, Explosives and Cults.
Leave a message
and I'll hit you back.
Listen, asshole.
You don't call me back
and then you email my morgue
and you pull my fucking body?
If you don't call within the hour,
I will be in my car driving to D.C.,
where I will personally
hit you fucking back!
Understood?
It's Kevin Garvey from Mapleton!
Fuck!
I say fuck, too.
Disarm system now.
- Disarm system now.
- Shit.
Disarm system now.
Fuck!
Fuck.
Shit. Fuck!
System deactivated.
- Hello?
- Hey, Chief Harvey.
Sean Kilaney from ATFEC.
How are you?
Sorry I didn't get back to you
sooner. I was down in Florida.
Fucking mess.
You see it on the news?
- No.
- Count yourself lucky.
So, you got a cult-related homicide?
- Didn't you get my messages?
- Well, just one. You leave more?
You want us
to take jurisdiction, right?
Uh... Uh, no.
Don't worry about it.
Listen, you never should have
gotten that call.
One of my detectives jumped the gun.
Vitello.
- He said he spoke to you.
- Okay. Let me pull it up here.
Got it. Jesus. Right, the stoning.
Fuck. The victim was what,
Tomorrow's Family?
- No, The Guilty Remnant.
- Oh, those nuts.
What's up with the chain-smoking?
Look, you know what?
Sounds like you got your hands full.
They sent the body to you
a couple hours ago, it's not like--
Shit. They did?
- They said you emailed them.
- That's automated.
It gets sent to the local M.E.
as soon as they put a Tier 3
in the system.
Well, then send her back to me.
Send the body back.
Wish I could.
She's en route
to our forensic processing center.
Then how about I come down there,
I pick her up myself?
Sorry. Once she's in the system,
there's nothing I can do.
What about forensics, evidence,
our witness statements?
- You know what?
- You want me to--
You go ahead
and hold on to all of that, okay?
You should be hearing
from one of our field guys soon.
- In how long?
- Uh, four to six weeks.
Fuck.
Or, if you want,
we could eliminate the infestation.
Excuse me?
I can have three vans
full of armed agents there
by the end of the week.
They pay a visit to whatever compound
these fucks call home,
and they get you the results
you're looking for.
Chief, this shit spreads
if you let it.
Don't worry about your victim.
She doesn't give a shit.
Worry about your town.
And The Guilty Remnant.
What would happen to them?
What happens is, they go away.
They're not your problem anymore.
Just say the word,
and everything can go back to normal.
Well, I appreciate that.
Hello? You still there?
- Chief?
- Uh...
But no thanks. We can handle it.
Okay.
Good luck with that, Chief.
Sorry, I can't sell alcohol
to people who are enibritted.
- Who are what?
- Enibritted.
- Inebriated?
- Yeah.
I'm not, so promise
you won't get in any trouble.
All right.
So, you guys catch
who killed that lady yet?
No. We have not.
Hey. Hey!
- Open the door.
- We're closed.
No, no, no.
It's me, Officer Mustard Stain.
- Open the door. Open the door.
- We're closed!
Sorry, sir. We're closed.
I'm a sir now?
Now I'm a sir. Open the door!
Hang up the phone
and open this door right now!
- Please, if you come tomorrow--
- Open the door.
- Sir! You cannot--
- I cannot? I cannot?
Open the motherfucking door
right now!
Okay, okay.
Please, please. What do you want?
I want you to look for my shirts.
And I would appreciate it
if you fucking tried this time.
Yes, yes. Of course.
Please, let me...
- How many shirts?
- Eight.
Eight.
- And what color?
- All white!
Here we are.
All white shirts, huh? Here we are.
I've got them. They're here.
One second.
Yes. See? White shirts.
Here you go.
More white shirts. That's...
- Here. White.
- Yeah.
White shirts.
- Eight shirts.
- Thank you.
No, no. It's okay.
No charge, sir. Our mistake, okay?
Thanks.
Testing, testing. One, two.
Good evening.
Hello.
My name is Matt Jamison.
I didn't know your friend very well.
I don't even know
if you considered her a friend,
but she lived here with all of you.
I tried to give her a blanket once
on a cold winter day,
but she wouldn't take it.
She was committed to her path.
I don't understand your faith,
but I understand commitment
and I respect it.
But we are, all of us,
no matter what we've suffered,
still alive.
We still feel pain and sorrow.
We still feel loss.
We still feel love.
This woman was one of you,
and now she's gone.
I know you cannot speak her name.
I know you cannot say goodbye.
But I ask you at least to let me.
If any of you wants to,
I invite you now
to come out and join us.
"I lift up my eyes to the hills.
Where does my help come from?
It comes from the Lord.
The Maker of Heaven and Earth.
He will not let your foot slip.
He who watches over you
will not slumber.
Indeed, He--"
Disarm system now.
System deactivated.
Hey.
I heard the alarm.
I wanted to make sure it was you.
- Thanks for setting it.
- Yeah.
- Find your shirts?
Your mother and I
are getting a divorce.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
I love you, honey.
I love you, too.