My kid wants to quit soccer.
You think I should let him?
- Is he any good?
- Nobody quits what they're good at.
So, who the fuck is this asshole?
Wayne Henry Gilchrest, Jr.,
also known as "Holy Wayne."
- Messianic?
- Maybe.
He lost a kid on the 14th,
worked the colleges
and malls for a while.
Claims he can hug the pain
out of people.
Magic fucking hugs.
Yeah, the only catch is he needs
to charge his batteries
with teenage girls.
- Asian ones, apparently.
- Apparently.
We had him on eight counts
of statutory in Pennsylvania
but he went underground in April.
FBI got a tip that he set up shop
at a ranch in Nevada.
- FBI?
- Guy's got a pipeline to D.C.,
sells his hugs to senators, I guess.
Well, that would make him a threat
to national security.
If that's your assessment.
- Guns?
- Got a couple dozen guys
at the ranch.
Semi-pro, no explosives.
Civilians?
Followers are mostly
dumb college kids,
usually a couple on the ranch
running errands.
- He looking to get martyred?
- Looking to get laid.
Okay.
Let's get him.
Here we go!
Go, go, go!
We got clear.
Cease fire!
Don't do it! Come out here!
Hands up!
- Where is he?
- Where's Wayne? Look here.
- I don't know!
Where's Wayne?
I got one! Do not move!
Do not run, you fucking cunt!
Stop!
Do not fucking move!
Hands.
Turn around.
Get on your fucking knees.
- Where's Wayne?
- I don't know.
- Where the fuck is he?
- I don't know. Please.
- I'll fucking kill you right now.
- Please. I don't--
- Where is he?
- Don't shoot! I didn't do anything!
- Are ready to die? Where is he?
- I don't know where's Wayne!
Please. Don't!
I'm sorry, but she's important.
Come on.
Come on, let's go, let's go.
This way.
It's okay.
Don't panic. I got you.
Come on. Okay, go ahead.
Go. Okay.
Hey. Mr. Garvey.
Mr. Garvey, wake up.
- Aimee.
- Hey.
Aimee, you--
You can't be in here.
Shh.
It's okay.
I need you to come with me.
Come on.
He wants you to see.
You have to be quiet
or you'll scare them.
Wh... What are you doing?
Shh. She's right over there.
Do you see her?
Hey, Chief, watch your feet.
Put it out, Paul.
Got a little out of control
but it'll go out.
Paul, put it out now!
Shit.
What the fuck, Paul?
- I told him not to do it here.
- Jesus, Ginnie, the heat's out.
- Close the goddamn door.
- Sorry. Give me that.
My brother's stuff.
Can't you just take it down
to the Goodwill?
So I can see some asshole wearing
his clothes at the A&P next week?
- Should I call 9-1-1?
- No. Do not call 9-1-1.
Next time, just put it in the attic.
I don't really want it in the attic.
You owe me a fence.
Fuck.
You burned his fence down.
Who wants French toast?
Has there been
any further contact?
Sorry. What?
Your ex-wife, Lauren.
Sorry. Laurie.
Have you and she
had any further contact?
- We're still married.
- Does she think you're married?
You're gonna have to ask her.
I get it, because she doesn't talk.
What's that for?
I work with a lot of kids.
They use it for aggression.
All right, so, this mystery man
who shot the deer...
No, he didn't shoot the deer.
- I thought--
- No, no, no. No one shot the deer.
The dogs killed the deer.
Uh....
Right, sorry.
So the mystery man--
Wait a minute. Why do you keep
calling him "the mystery man"?
- You didn't tell me his name.
- I don't know his name.
It says here the squad car--
Your colleagues arrived in response
to a report of gunshots
but there's no mention
of anyone there other than you,
and lots of dead dogs.
The guy got into his truck
and left before they got there.
So no one else saw him.
I fucking saw him.
Soup's on.
Get them while you can.
No pancakes in the big house.
Oh, Christ.
Fucking laundry again?
Good morning.
What?
You want me to cut it down?
I thought you were bringing me
out here to kill me or something.
Hey, Moonie.
Fuck you!
I know for a fact that Torres
won't take attendance.
- I can't. I have an exam.
- Chicken shit.
Good morning. Free of charge.
They are not who you think they are.
You're doing really important work.
Someone needs to tell
that dude about the Internet.
Save us a seat.
I'll go order.
- Sorry.
- Oh, no worries.
- Thank you.
- Sorry.
I may have fucked that barista,
so if he spit in your chai,
that's on me.
- What?
- Do you know who that is?
Nope.
Her name is Nora something.
She was at Heroes Day.
Her husband and her kids
all disappeared.
- There's a gun in her purse.
- No shit?
Yeah, like, a big one, too.
Not some bullshit lady gun.
She probably puts in her mouth
every night before bed
and says, "Just one more day."
No, she, like, puts wigs on
and uses it
to hold up liquor stores
so she can feel alive again.
Or maybe
she actually killed her family
and then just said they disappeared
while she secretly ate their bodies.
- That's fucked up.
- Yeah.
What the fuck?
I'm so sorry.
Oh, uh... No worries.
It's totally cool, Mrs. Durst.
- Let me get you another one.
- No, no, it's fine.
- I've got to be somewhere anyway.
- Sorry.
Bye.
What was that?
Shit.
She's gonna pop father nutballs.
- You want to follow her?
- And what?
- Come on, dude.
- What?
Hey! Big bones!
Top of the morning, ladies.
Y'all need a ride to school?
Only if you let me drive
your awesome Prius.
Hop on in, baby.
- You know how to turn it on, right?
- Yeah.
- Go.
- Quick. Close the door.
It's a hybrid.
Hit the power button.
- Do you have a driver's license?
- This is very confusing.
- Brake.
- You got to hit the--
Here we go.
Ow! Fuck.
Ow!
So what,
the tree's supposed to symbolize
my old life or something?
Can I have one?
You know, you guys are running
a pretty shitty cult
if you can't even join.
"Not a cult."
Then what is it?
I'm not doing this anymore.
Because I don't want to.
Why? Why? Because I've been
with you people for weeks
and all I've got is Ron
and pancakes
and fucking tree-chopping!
What the fuck?
I mean,
it's freezing and it's stupid.
It's fucking stupid.
That's why, okay?
Christine, wake up.
This is it.
Just stay in the car, okay?
Is it him?
Maybe this isn't the right place.
He should be here by now.
Are you calling him?
No.
Tom.
No, no, no. Hey, wait, wait.
Hey, it's Tom.
I'm not here. God bless.
Hey, Tommy, it's your daddy calling.
I saw you called, so...
Listen, I'm gonna leave
my phone on,
so call me whenever you can.
I love you.
Shit.
Hard to get him to talk to you,
right?
Maybe try with the texting.
My ten-year-old,
that's all she uses.
- Where are we on the truck?
- Huh?
Pickup truck I asked you
to find two weeks ago. Where are we?
Oh, yeah.
We put out a bolo but no hits.
Maybe if we had
a better description of the driver?
Big, bald asshole
shooting dogs somewhere.
Uh....
Want me to sit down
with a sketch artist?
No, it's just you're the only one
who saw him, so...
Dennis, do you think
I made this guy up?
This is the part where you say, "No,
Chief, that's fucking ridiculous."
Fine. No, Chief.
That's fucking ridiculous.
- Go find the truck.
- Yes, sir.
Patti.
You know the drill.
I have a signed warrant,
applicable in the case
of a missing person or persons
to enter these premises
and conduct a visual survey
and/or question
the occupants therein.
May I come in, please?
Morning, Mr. Jensen.
How are you?
Terrific.
Obligated to inform you
the missing persons investigation
related to you has been closed
and that your family has been
informed of your whereabouts.
You understand?
Yeah. I understand.
- Hi.
Did you hurt yourself?
Just some blisters.
You mind if I ask your name?
Meg.
Megan Abbott.
You here on your own free will,
Ms. Abbott?
Yes.
You need my help?
No.
Do you mind if we take a picture?
- A picture?
- Mm-hm.
- Have I done something wrong?
- No.
Okay.
- Dennis.
- Yeah, Chief?
Could...
Okay.
- We good?
- Yeah, it's a good one.
If you ever wanna talk...
...we have resources available
to you.
You can feel free to call me,
night or day.
Why don't you fucking mail it to me?
- Don't get too close.
- I know what I'm doing.
Uh...
We're missing first period.
Jill is never gonna fuck you
if you keep acting
like such a puss, dude.
Ow! What?
- Did I mix them up?
- Shut up.
Oh, yeah, here we go.
Why are we following her?
Because she's fucking dangerous.
- Mr. Patterson?
- Uh-huh.
We spoke on the phone last week.
I'm Nora Durst.
I'm here to give you and your wife
your departure benefit.
- I... Come in.
- Thank you.
This guy is in the pledge house now.
No idea where he came from.
"Brandon" might be an alias.
Wouldn't give us a last name.
Got her. Megan Abbott.
From here in town.
Fiancé reported a missing
couples weeks ago.
Ask him to come in.
I'll handle it.
Jesus. I never should have told you
to watch the fucking Wire.
Lucy.
Gentlemen, you mind giving
the Chief and I a moment?
Yeah.
Madam mayor.
Kevin, were you inside
a G.R. Residence earlier today?
I was serving
a missing persons warrant.
I do that every couple weeks.
Uh-huh, and would you say
the climate has changed somewhat
since you went over there drunk
and punched one of them in the face?
I think I punched him
in the stomach, actually.
Want a bagel?
Kevin, I'm trying to help you.
By forcing me to get cleared
by some dipshit
because I had a rough night?
"Rough night"?
You are aware that people like dogs?
- I like dogs.
- Then stop fucking shooting them
because that's something crazy
people do.
You wanna get cleared?
Then you tell that dipshit
what he needs to hear.
- What's that?
- It won't happen again.
Well, I can't say that
because I don't mean it.
They're not our dogs.
Not anymore.
What the fuck does that mean?
Kevin, I need you to stop pissing
on the G.R.S' front porch, okay?
Fine.
See if I can hold it.
I'm visiting tonight, so...
Tell him I said, "Hi".
Fuck.
You have to film us?
It's ridiculous, right?
I guess some people
were filling it out wrong.
That's why they're making us
conduct it verbally now.
How many questions is it?
Just over 150.
Too many, I know.
Do we have to answer everything
to get our check?
Just what you can.
Okay.
This is Nora Durst,
ID number 42ECN.
Today I will be conducting
a benefit release questionnaire
for case file 77123,
Charles Patterson, age 34 at T.O.E.
Present are Louis and Marie,
the parents of--
I can refer to him as "Charles,"
as "your son,"
- or as "the departed"?
- Charlie.
All right. Charlie.
I apologize in advance.
The questions can be strange
for some people.
Were you able to look them over?
- There was a link...
- Let's just get it over with.
Okay.
To your knowledge, did Charlie have
any food allergies?
We sent in his medical records.
I know, and I'm sorry.
I'm not given access to those.
No allergies.
Okay.
To your knowledge,
did Charlie ever travel to Brazil?
No.
To your knowledge,
did Charlie enjoy cooking?
No.
To your knowledge, did Charlie speak
more than one language?
My son had Down Syndrome.
I'm sorry.
I am. These questions,
they're f--
I want to sign off on your benefit.
I know this is hard.
Answer what you can
but I have to ask them.
All of them.
No.
He didn't speak
more than one language.
Okay.
To your knowledge, did Charlie have
more than 20 sexual partners?
Do you have any hand cream?
What?
I'm a man.
Why would I have hand cream?
You're a man?
I'll bet she does.
But if you get caught,
you will be shot.
Oh, my God, guys.
Are you serious?
She's a really bad influence on you,
man.
Jesus, lady.
Oh, fuck yes.
Okay.
Jill, don't do it. Jill.
- Stop, stop, stop.
- Jill, stop it.
- Stop.
- Shut up.
- Go. My God.
- You stupid bitch!
Hit the power button.
My God.
Just turn on the car.
Just go. Just go.
She's right there. Just go.
She's right outside.
Chief, the fiancé is here.
Waiting in your office.
Oh, right, yeah. Thanks.
Mr. Finnerty.
Kevin Garvey.
Thank you for coming in.
So sorry you had to wait.
- You can have a seat.
- Jesus.
You people leave me a voice-mail
regarding my fiancé...
...and when I call back,
nobody will tell me
if she's alive or dead.
- Megan's with the Guilty Remnant.
- What?
I'm assuming they've been following
Megan for some time now.
They usually target somebody
and then--
What do they want?
- That depends who you ask.
- I'm asking you.
Well, they say they want
to remind people of what happened.
But what do they want?
They want to recruit.
Look, the good news
is that right now,
Megan's in what we call
the pledge house.
It's like an orientation.
They don't have to wear white yet,
they can still talk.
I spoke to Megan today personally.
I've dealt
with a lot of these people.
I got a feeling that with Megan,
maybe she's still on the fence.
I think you could still convince her
to come home.
Why would I do that?
Sorry?
Because she needs you right now.
She? Needs?
I postponed my wedding
for three years
because of what she needs.
But she snuck off in the middle
of the fucking night
so she could be with them!
And she needs them!
The fucking ghosts!
What the fuck
are you talking about, man?
What the f....
- What, Dennis?
- Chief, I found the truck.
- Where?
- It's... in your driveway.
Hey. Saw it when I was driving by,
called you first thing.
- Keys are on the dash.
- Yeah, I noticed that.
Did you run the vin?
Uh-huh. No registration, no wants.
I looked inside.
It's a dead dog.
I'll just say we found it abandoned
a couple blocks from here.
- Why the fuck would you say that?
- Well, it's just-- I...
It's not my truck, Dennis.
Someone else put it here.
Yeah. Sure. I know.
- Get back to work.
- Yes, sir.
He never would have let me do that
when he was alive.
- You okay?
- Yeah, yeah, I'm fine. You?
Well, Tom, I've had better days.
Yeah.
Um, what happened back there?
They had papers, some bullshit.
They didn't come to arrest me.
They opened fire
before they even got to the house.
Christine told me what you did.
Yeah, you told me to protect her,
right?
Don't just shrug
like you're not sure
what you want for supper, man.
You killed.
For great purpose, yes,
but you killed.
You're a good boy, Tom.
It's okay.
And that's why it feels like
there's poison inside you right now.
And it's gonna burn
until you're hollow.
Let me take it from you, man.
You don't have to feel
like this anymore.
Come on in.
I can't. I can't.
You're the one motherfucker
I can't figure out.
You're all suffering
and no salvation.
But that's why I chose you
to protect our girl.
I'm glad you're back together.
No, no, Tom, she can't come with me.
She's going with you.
Thanks for letting us
hijack your ride, boners.
Anytime.
Hey, get some fucking hand cream.
- Have a good night.
You, too.
So, you think she's really gonna use
that gun?
If I lost my whole family,
I'd need to shoot something.
- At least she's still here.
- What do you mean?
She could have run away someplace
and nobody would have ever known
what happened to her,
but she's still here.
These jellybeans are stale.
They were probably for her kids.
Hi.
Do we have to?
Please, can we just have one night
where I don't have to give you
any of my stuff?
One night?
Do you even remember
what it feels like
to care about anything?
What?
No shit?
The hot cop?
And you're here?
It's my mom's.
I was saving it for last.
I don't want to feel this way
anymore.
She's far too important
to risk traveling with me right now.
Never stay in the same place
for too long,
don't ever tell anyone
your real name
and don't use your IDs.
- Have you got a phone?
- Yeah.
Give it to me.
When it's time for what comes next,
I'll call you on this.
And get yourself a charger, man.
I lost mine.
Wayne, we have to go.
I love you.
I love you, too.
This girl is everything.
Yes?
Yes.
Road trip.
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
Fuck!
It's gonna be okay.
How?
Wayne told me.
Howdy.
Well, you gonna invite me in?
What's your pickup truck doing
in my driveway?
- I heard you were looking for it.
- Heard where?
Around.
What's your name?
Well, you asking me in
an official capacity or as a friend?
- We're not friends.
- Then I'd rather not say.
- Hey, Mr. Garvey.
- Hey.
These for us?
Young lady, why don't you put this
in the fridge for your dad?
Do not drink that.
So I found another pack.
Of what?
Dogs.
Couple dozen, I'd guess.
I saw them slinking around
the elementary school tonight
and they....
I'm pretty sure they're sleeping
in the drainpipe.
We could set up there
and pick them off
when they come out tomorrow night.
You meet my by the school
just before sundown?
Why can't you do it yourself?
Because I'm lonely.
Sundown tomorrow.
We're doing the Lord's work,
believe you me.
Hey!
Take your fucking truck.
No, it's all yours.
I'm done with it.
Who was that?
Nobody.
Hey, Betty.
How you doing?
- Mr. Garvey. Long time no see.
- Yeah.
Okay if I bring that in?
Long as he eats it while you're here
and you bring the jar out.
Deal.
How can he not like this?
It's great.
Prodigal son returns.
- I'll let you two catch up.
- Okay.
Kevin.
Hey, did you steal my bagels
this morning?
- Did I what?
- Never mind. Forget about it.
How you doing, Dad?
Said you got to eat it
while I'm here.
Yeah, yeah.
I know the rules.
Did she tell you
what's going on with me?
We got better things
to talk about than you.
Mmm.
How's my house?
Paul burned down the fence
in the backyard.
Fucking moron.
How's my job?
It's hard.
You know...
...it wouldn't kill you to show
a little vulnerability now and then.
People love that shit.
No one wants to see the Chief
of Police crying in his car.
You're crying in your car?
You know they all went?
Balki, cousin Larry, Jennifer,
Mary Anne,
whole cast poofed on the 14th.
- Bullshit.
- No, look it up.
- Kids okay?
- Yeah.
Jill, she's fine.
Tommy's still out west, I think.
Been a while since we spoke.
Well, just
because he doesn't check in
as often as he should,
doesn't mean he doesn't love you.
How'd it start for you, Dad?
Well, that depends on what you mean
by "it", son.
You know what I'm talking about.
If you're asking me
when I started losing my shit?
Contrary to the professional opinion
of others,
I maintain my shit remains intact.
Now, I'd venture to guess
the reason you're here seeing me
your shit may be getting lost.
No, not an unreasonable assumption,
considering you've been running
around
shooting dogs in the middle
of the fucking night.
- Fucking Lucy.
- No, don't take it out on her.
She's trying to cover for you.
Why don't you tell that shrink
she sent you to...
...that you were drunk...
...and that you were under
a lot of stress,
and you're very, very sorry?
You realize now
that it was wrong to--
Will you please shut up?
No, no, I'm not gonna tell him.
Tell me what, dad?
He's here, isn't he?
That's something.
Why do I always have to--
Fuck you!
Someone came to see you?
What?
They said they sent...
Motherfucker.
They said they sent
or are sending somebody to help you.
Who?
Help me with what?
Ahh, I don't know.
But whatever it is...
...you might wanna keep it
to yourself.
- Hey, Chief, you good?
- Fantastic.