Christine.
Christine!
She's hungry.
He's never coming for us, is he?
Wayne?
I don't know.
I should have known he was a liar
when he said I was special.
Look at me.
Hey.
I'm going to take care of you
just like I promised.
Okay? I'll get a job.
I'll find us a place to stay,
all of us.
We don't need him.
Christine, we don't need Wayne.
I know.
She's wet.
- Do you want me to--
- No, no, I've got her.
Excuse me, young man.
Young man?
- Can I help you?
- What?
Is there anything I can do
to help you?
- No, I'm fine.
- Are you sure?
Yeah.
It's my ride.
God bless you.
Hey. You just go around
asking people if they need help?
Yeah.
Does anyone ever say yes?
All the time.
Christine!
Christine! Christine! Christine!
No, no, no.
Hey, hey, it's okay.
Christine! Christine!
Christine!
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
Christine!
Sorry.
I got lost coming off the highway.
I tried to call you.
The battery on my phone died.
Where is she?
What are you doing?
I'm closing her eyes.
- You can't touch her.
- Why not?
Because she's--
It's a fucking crime scene.
You told me on the phone
she did this to herself.
No one's going to
fucking believe that.
I believe it.
I brought her here.
I beat her.
I tied her up.
And then you tried to let her go
but she wouldn't let that happen.
She wanted you to pay.
She knew if she did this
that it'd hurt you.
Because you're a good man, Kevin.
If you touch her...
...we're in this together.
Then let's be in it.
I have shovels in my trunk.
Wait.
I, uh...
I marked a passage.
Okay.
- What?
- You should read it.
- No. No, thanks.
- Why not?
Because I don't believe it, Matt.
I'm sure she didn't, either.
Did you ask for my help, Kevin?
Yes.
This is me helping.
Just the highlighted part.
It can get wordy.
"If I go to the East,
He is not there.
If I go to the West,
I do not find Him.
When He is at work in the North,
I do not see Him.
When He turns to the South,
I catch no glimpse of Him.
But He knows the way that I take.
When He has tested me,
I will come forth as gold.
My feet have closely followed
His steps.
I have kept to His way
without turning aside.
I have not departed...
Not departed
from the commandment of His lips.
I have treasured the words
of His mouth
more than my daily bread.
But He stands alone
and who can oppose Him?
He does whatever He pleases.
He carries out His decree
against me,
and many such plans
He still has in store.
That is why
I am terrified before Him.
When I think of all this,
I fear Him.
God has made my heart faint.
The Almighty has terrified me.
Yet I am not silenced
by the darkness,
by the thick darkness
that covers my face."
Amen.
I brought you a change of clothes.
Pardon the fashion.
They're donated.
I'd have brought you some
of mine
but we have different physiques.
Better?
Yeah.
Good.
Let's go home.
ATFEC agents
exchanged fire with Gilchrest
before he staged a daring escape.
A tri-state manhunt is underway.
At this point,
no other agencies are involved.
In business news,
at the Chicago Board of Trade,
corn, wheat
and soybean prices...
Hey. What the--
Hey!
Calm down.
I had to.
There was no other choice.
What the fuck did you do?
Fuck!
- Please get the fuck off of me.
- I'm sorry.
Get the fuck off of me.
- Why did you do this?
- So sorry.
Get the fuck off of me!
This is a mistake.
A mistake.
I have a daughter.
Someone needs to call my daughter!
I'm not supposed to be here.
This is a mistake!
Someone call my daughter!
I'm not supposed to be here!
This is a mistake!
I'm not fucking crazy!
Just calm down.
Calm down. Stay calm.
You're okay.
Just calm down.
Stay calm.
You're okay.
Just calm down.
Stay calm. You're okay.
Just calm...
You going to behave yourself?
Yeah.
I had to ask.
Ten minutes.
Do you usually sleep on that side?
Well, why don't I go to that side?
No, no.
I will go to that side of the bed.
Balki, I don't mind sleeping
on that side of the bed.
I'm not arguing about sleeping
Hey, baby boy.
Have a seat.
Dad, I need to get to a phone.
Jill hasn't heard from me.
I got to call--
Shh...
Quiet. At last.
So, you finally
fucking snapped, huh?
- No.
- No?
I'm not fucking crazy.
Neither am I.
But I am a bad man, son,
and the bad men end up here.
Dad, you're--
Look, you're a good man.
I most definitely am not.
My intentions are good
but my heart and my mind
and my balls, son,
the Holy fucking Trinity,
they all knew.
That night three years ago,
we looked at ourselves
in the mirror
and none of us wondered
why we were still fucking here.
We knew.
Of course we knew.
- You know.
- I don't belong here.
- Yeah, you do.
- No, I don't.
- Yes, you--
- I have to leave here!
There is no leaving here.
Now-- Don't you fucking dare!
Do not turn around.
No, no.
Just get the fuck out of here.
Son, I said do not turn around.
Fuck him.
Turn around.
Hello, again.
Now, why'd you go and do that?
He needs to get out
and you weren't helping,
you crazy, dried-up,
fucking turd.
Oh, fuck you,
you fucking tobacco-stink twat.
He needs to stay.
Is that what you need, Kevin?
This isn't happening.
This isn't real.
You're not here.
It's happening.
It's real.
I'm here.
You're dead.
You're fucking dead.
I buried you.
Not deep...
...enough.
Hey, you leave with her...
...you leave with her.
Dad.
Daddy.
Now, Kevin.
Shh...
Looks like we're going to be
traveling companions.
Until then...
...you should wake the fuck up.
What?
Wake the fuck up!
State police
have roadblocks on Interstate 97
and have issued an advisory
to motorists...
- You okay?
- ...to dial 911 immediately
- if they encounter Gilchrest.
- Yeah. Fine.
- Where are we?
- I got hungry.
Want a cheeseburger?
God, that's good.
- So what'd she say?
- Who?
Patti.
What'd she say
before she killed herself?
I don't want to talk about it.
- I can't help if you don't tell me.
- You've helped me enough, Matt.
Not you. Them. The Remnant.
You can't help them.
Yes, I can. I know I can
because I'm supposed to.
But you need to tell me
why she did what she did.
You need to tell me what she said.
She said, "I understand."
- Understood what?
- I don't know.
Sure you do.
Excuse me?
If she wanted to deliver a message
by cutting her own throat,
I'm pretty sure she'd be confident
you received it before she did.
So, what did you understand?
Why we didn't go.
Why...
...we're still here.
Tell me.
Before it happened,
the 14th?
I wanted to leave.
I wanted to be free of...
...my family.
Wanting and doing aren't the same.
I slept with another woman.
Who?
I don't know her name.
She uh...
She disappeared.
You were with her?
At the moment of the Departure?
Yeah.
No shit.
What happened next?
I don't really remember all of it.
I think I was in shock.
Phones were down
and I was wearing my uniform.
And people kept coming up to me
and asking me for help.
And I couldn't or I...
...I didn't know how.
So I got in my car...
...and I went to Jill's school
and I ran inside.
She and Tommy were both there
and...
...they were scared.
I just remember the look
on their faces when they saw me.
They were so...
They...
They were so happy.
They were happy.
And...
...we went back to the house
and Laurie had already got home
so--
And she was different.
I mean, I think we all were.
But I just wanted to be with them.
And I wanted to hold them.
And then I started to lose them.
One by one.
It's not your fault.
Yes, it is.
It is.
Hey, you okay?
Jesus Christ.
Just sitting here.
Too many woes.
- Listen, don't move.
- Please, what's your name?
- Kevin.
- You need help.
- No, Kevin, Kevin,
I'm going to be dead in a minute.
There's no help for me.
So, please, don't leave me alone.
Sure. Yeah, yeah.
- I'm right here.
- Thank you.
Will you do something for me?
A favor.
Stranger to stranger?
Will you make a wish?
A what?
I think I may be a fraud.
But if I'm not...
...I can give you anything you want.
And that will mean I was real.
Let me do this for you before I go.
Make a wish.
You don't have to say it out loud.
Just think it.
Granted.
ATFEC! Get down!
Get the fuck down! Now!
Get on the ground now!
Hurry up! Get down!
Stay the fuck down!
Let's go!
Come on, turn around!
Stay down!
Go!
What did he say to you?
- Uh... Just asked me my name.
- That's it?
Yeah, that's it.
Talk to you about Russia?
No.
- Make any physical contact with you?
- Why?
Did he?
No.
Who was he?
Just another asshole
who thought he was God.
Excuse me.
This man did nothing wrong.
We were just having lunch
and he's a police officer, a chief.
- You're a cop?
- Yeah.
Why didn't you say so?
I'm off-duty.
- Where you from?
- New York, Mapleton.
Okay, we're good here, Chief.
Thanks for your cooperation.
Go on home to Mapleton.
Stop, now! You...
Hey!
Drop the gun!
Whoa, whoa, whoa...
It's okay. Calm down.
Drop the gun.
- What's your name?
- What?
Drop the gun. We can talk about
whatever you want to talk about.
Listen, I'm a cop.
Do you see what they did?
- Stop!
- Go get her.
It's all right. Calm down.
Just drop the gun.
Fuck you!
- Hey!
- I'll kill you, fucker!
Hey!
Kevin!
Jesus Christ.
Can you hear me?
What happened?
What the fuck did you people do?
- She's hurt.
- She wants to be fucking hurt.
What happened?
I'm going to kill you!
Jesus. Lucy. Lucy.
- You all right?
- You were right.
You were right.
Please. Go back to your homes,
for your own safety!
- Dennis!
- Chief!
- They have not--
- Where the fuck is everybody?
I couldn't stop them.
They left.
Give me a fucking gun.
- Where's all the fire trucks?
- I called them.
They want to wait
until the road's clear.
Well, then
you clear the fucking cars
out of the goddamn road
so they can get in.
Chief, nobody wants to help them.
- Get out of my way.
- It's their own fault.
Listen, go back to that fucking--
Stay at this barricade
and do not let anyone through.
Do you understand?
Go.
Step back!
Hold it! Hold this fucking line!
Step the fuck back!
How dare you?
Stop!
Hey, I'll get you somewhere safe.
I'll get you somewhere safe.
- Jill. Jill.
- I'll get you somewhere safe.
Jill!
You okay?
It's all right.
"Dear Kevin, I need to say
goodbye to someone I care about,
someone who's still here,
so I'm saying it to you.
You were good to me, Kevin,
and sometimes when we were together,
I remembered who I used to be
before everything changed.
But I was pretending,
pretending as if
I hadn't lost everything.
I want to believe it can all go back
to the way it was.
I want to believe
that I'm not surrounded
by the abandoned ruin
of a dead civilization.
I want to believe it's still possible
to get close to someone.
But it's easier not to.
It's easier because I'm a coward.
And I couldn't take the pain.
Not again.
I know that's not fair, Kevin.
You've lost so much, too,
and you're strong.
You're still here.
But I can't be, not anymore.
I tried to get better, Kevin.
I didn't want to feel this way,
so I took a shortcut.
But it led me right back home.
And do you know what I found
when I got there?
I found them, Kevin,
right where I left them.
Right where they left me.
It took me three years
to accept the truth
but now I know
there's no going back.
No fixing it.
I'm beyond repair.
Maybe we're all beyond repair.
I can't go on the way I'm living.
But I don't have the power to die.
But I have to move
towards something.
Anything.
I'm not sure where I'm going,
just away.
Away from all this.
I think about a place
where nobody will know
what happened to me.
But then I worry I'll forget them.
I don't ever want to forget them.
I can't.
They were my family.
I think I loved you, Kevin.
Maybe you loved me, too.
I wish I could say this to you
instead of writing it.
I wish I could see you
one last time
to thank you and wish you well
and tell you how much
you mean to me.
But I can't.
Like I said, I'm a coward.
So, wish me luck.
I think I'm going to need it.
Love, Nora."
Hi.
Look what I found.