("RARE" BY SELENA GOMEZ)
♪ Baby, right now it feels like ♪
♪ It feels like you don't care ♪
♪ Oh, why don't you
recognize I'm so rare? ♪
LUKAS: Why you on your own?
You prefer it, your own company?
♪ I don't have it all ♪
Do you want a drink?
I think you do.
Okay, then.
♪ To tell me I'm rare ♪
♪ To make me feel rare ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ Don't make me count up
all the reasons ♪
♪ To stay with you ♪
CONNELL: I'm glad to hear things
are okay over there in Sweden
and that the course is good.
Everything is basically the same here
as before you left.
I looked up your friend,
the photographer
on Facebook, by the way.
He seems interesting.
Is he your boyfriend or are
you not putting labels on it?
I know you like the tall, handsome guys
as you say.
So, why not Lukas, who looks tall
and is also handsome?
Helen has seen his photo
and agrees, but whatever.
I'm not pushing the boyfriend thing.
I just hope you've confirmed that
he is not a psychopath.
You don't always have
a good radar on that.
Helen says hi, by the way.
And let me know when
you're back for Christmas.
It'd be good to see you.
(KNOCKING)
LUKAS: Marianne?
Mm‐hmm?
Oh.
(SCOFFS)
You looks nice.
You okay?
I'm gonna go grab something
to eat. You want to come?
Sure.
Something the matter?
Oh.
Are you breaking up with me?
Maybe.
Maybe, yeah.
Okay, uh, can I do anything
to stop you from breaking up with me?
(MARIANNE SCOFFS)
(LUKAS SIGHS)
Come on.
- Tell me, what is it?
Look.
I just... I don't think a relationship
is what I want.
What do you want?
I really like you.
That.
I don't‐I don't want that.
I don't want you to say that.
Really?
Really.
I want...
if anything...
the opposite.
Of that.
(WAITRESS AND LUKAS SPEAKING SWEDISH)
Yeah.
That would be better.
We're a bunch of, um...
scientists and pragmatists,
you know what I mean?
Yeah. It's nice to have
somebody with a little bit of creativity.
Thanks, Dad.
TOM: No, I didn't‐‐
no, I mean, in a good way.
CONNELL: Yeah, that was nice.
HELEN: Yeah?
They really liked you.
They never really got on with Rory.
Right.
Don't know why.
Maybe he was a bit full of it.
He was probably a gobshite.
(CHUCKLES)
Did your mom like Marianne?
Of course.
Lorraine likes everybody.
I think she felt a bit sorry for her.
Sorry for Marianne?
About what?
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
♪♪
I want to have a shower.
We're not done here.
Don't ask that,
don't ask me for stuff.
Don't move.
I'll tell you when it's over
and you can have a shower.
You're worthless.
You're nothing.
♪♪
MARIANNE: I feel so
not myself at the moment.
Not in a bad way.
I just feel outside
of my own life somehow.
Sometimes, someone will
make eye contact with me
like a bus conductor or
a person looking for change.
And I'll feel shocked that anyone
can actually see me.
And there's something comforting about it.
Something good about feeling sort of numb.
Detached from it all.
Does that make sense?
("99 LUFTBALLONS" BY NENA)
♪♪
Thank you for bringing us to the fucking
most depressing Christmas party ever.
Look at the roof.
Look at that roof.
It's the most, single‐handedly
the most depressing place‐‐.
NIALL: I'm having a great time.
(LAUGHTER)
All right.
Yeah, four lagers, please.
Thanks.
Connell Waldron.
All right, Peggy.
(CHUCKLES)
PEGGY: Jesus Christ,
haven't seen you in such a long time.
How's Marianne getting on?
I heard she's up to some
interesting stuff over in Sweden.
I'm so fuckin' jealous.
Jamie was saying she was
into some weird stuff.
Like, bondage and shit.
Was that you?
Did you like, kick her off
on all that stuff?
Fuck off, Peggy.
I'm just talking about stuff
I've heard here...
Yeah, and I don't want to hear
about it, thanks.
You all right?
What's up?
It's just Peggy.
Saying shit about Marianne.
Oh.
- Saying what?
Oh, just shit.
- What?
She just...
seems to be a person
that people like to talk about.
Right.
And... I don't know that she...
necessarily has a problem with that.
Uh, what do you mean?
I mean, she sort of fucking
invites it, Connell.
Enjoys it.
Why are you so bothered?
Well, I'm gonna go in.
I'm cold.
CONNELL: From your emails,
it doesn't sound like you're completely
happy in Sweden.
Maybe I'm wrong.
I think I know the feeling
of being detached from the world,
although I haven't felt that way lately.
("BERLIN" BY RY X)
Not to put pressure on you at all,
because it's obviously your decision.
But I'm sad to hear you're not
coming home for Christmas.
Thinking it over,
I don't think I've ever gone
a whole year of my life without
seeing you before.
At least not since we were 11 or 12.
Anyway, that's just my way
of saying I miss you.
And I'm looking forward to seeing you,
whenever that will be.
Will you send a message
to let me know how you're getting on?
Or we could even talk
on the phone if you want.
♪ And I'll stop waiting by the phone ♪
CONNELL: I hope things are okay.
MARIANNE:
It just doesn't make any sense
to come back for such
a short amount of time.
Hello?
DENISE (ON PHONE)
I heard you.
I have a lot of work on.
DENISE: It's Christmas. Yeah.
I'm aware.
DENISE: So you'll stay in Sweden
on Christmas Day?
I don't know.
I'll work or something.
DENISE:
And we'll see you when exactly?
I don't know.
DENISE: Right.
Well, I better not keep you.
You sound very busy.
♪ Sorry love, I'm running home ♪
Bye.
(LINE DISCONNECTS)
♪ I'm a child of sun
and the stars I love ♪
(PHONE CLATTERS)
♪♪
MARIANNE: I've been thinking a lot
about the summer.
And about Jamie and Peggy.
I'm trying to figure out
if I ever really thought
that that was friendship.
That it was real.
Or if I just liked the feeling of it.
The pretense of it.
You must be getting ready to go home.
When I think of Christmastime, now,
I think of Carricklea.
I imagine a Christmas tree
in your front room.
Covered in tinsel.
I can't picture my house at all.
I miss you.
♪♪
(HEAVY BREATHING)
I'm gonna take your photo.
What do you mean?
I have an idea.
When?
Tomorrow.
Okay.
Come in the shower.
Come. Come closer to the water.
MARIANNE: What you been up to?
JOANNA (ON VIDEO CHAT)
I am on part seven,
um, of this documentary about
the American civil war.
(CHUCKLES)
Jesus.
I've got lots of knowledge about
American Civil War Generals
that I can't wait to share with you.
So what about you? How's Lukas?
How's it going?
MARIANNE: Yeah, okay.
JOANNA: Do you like him?
MARIANNE:
It's not that sort of thing.
He's fine.
I mean, I don't really feel...
JOANNA: Okay.
♪♪
Hey.
Hi.
Nearly done.
Okay.
I still don't know with the light yet.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
♪♪
Maybe we can do, like...
first one...
like this, and then another one.
And we'll see.
Okay.
(CAMERA BEEPS, SNAPS)
♪♪
Do you want me to...
Sure, just the jumper for now.
♪♪
Untie your hair.
Maybe take this off now.
♪♪
Can we not do this now?
(BELT CRACKS)
(MARIANNE GASPS)
LUKAS: This is what you wanted.
(MARIANNE BREATHING HEAVILY)
♪♪
Good.
CONNELL: It's been a while since
I've heard from you.
Is everything all right?
I wonder if I said something
stupid in my last email.
And I hope not,
but I'm sorry if I did.
I know you told me the reason
you're not coming home at Christmas
has to do with your family,
and maybe
I shouldn't have brushed over that.
Good.
CONNELL:
I'm sorry to bring this up
because I know we both
feel awkward about it,
but I haven't forgotten the things
you told me when we were in Italy,
and I hope you know that
none of those things are your fault,
and there is nothing wrong with you.
LUKAS: Open your eyes.
I'm tired.
Open your fucking eyes.
CONNELL: You are a good person,
and I say that as someone
who really knows you.
I know I reacted very stupidly that night
and to be honest,
I'm lucky that we're still friends because
it was such an idiotic thing to do.
Just because people
treat you badly at times,
and I include myself in that, by the way,
it doesn't mean you deserve
to be treated badly.
A lot of people love you
and care about you.
I hope you know that.
(GRUNTS) No.
LUKAS:
Don't make this hard on yourself.
I don't want to do this.
No.
♪♪
(BIRD CAWING)