(RAIN PATTERING)
(MARIANNE SNIFFLES)
("TOO MUCH" BY CARLY RAE JEPSEN
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
‐ Stay.
‐ I can't.
‐ I don't have class until three.
‐ Yeah, but I've gotta go home
and get some stuff, and...
Niall worries about me.
‐ Hmm. That's nice.
‐ Hmm.
‐ I like Niall.
Even though I haven't met him yet.
Is he your best friend, do you think?
‐ No.
‐ Oh.
‐ You are.
(LAUGHS SOFTLY)
‐ ♪ And did you know ♪
♪ That I'm wild for your skin
and the dance that we're in ♪
♪ So close now ♪
(MARIANNE LAUGHS)
(CONNELL GRUNTS)
♪ It takes me higher, feel the love ♪
♪ I'm not afraid to know
my heart's desire ♪
♪ Ooh ah ♪
♪ When I party then I party too much ♪
(MUSIC ENDS)
(DOOR OPENS)
NIALL: Ah!
‐ Didn't know you were here.
‐ The ghost of Christmas past.
‐ All right?
‐ I heard someone coming in.
Thought we were being robbed.
You still live here, then?
‐ Don't know what you're
complaining about.
You get the room to yourself
and I'm still paying rent.
‐ Complaining? I'm delighted.
- How's Marianne?
‐ Good, yeah.
‐ Is she your girlfriend yet?
‐ No. (ZIPPING)
‐ What are you playing at?
Are you keeping her on her toes?
‐ Course not.
‐ She's too good for ya.
‐ Yes, I'm aware.
‐ Are ya?
‐ Yeah, look, can you
give me grief about this later?
‐ Can't wait.
LORRAINE (OVER PHONE): How's work?
‐ Grand. Yeah. Busy.
‐ I hope you said thank you to Marianne.
‐ What?
‐ For the job.
‐ No, no. That was Sophie.
‐ And who introduced you to Sophie?
‐ Well, like, Marianne, obviously.
‐ Yes. She's been
very good to you, you know.
‐ Right.
‐ I just hope you're a bit more
appreciative of her now.
‐ Yep. (EXHALES)
‐ Well?
‐ Yeah, well, look,
apologies have been made, okay?
And if...
Marianne isn't dwelling on it,
I don't see why you are.
Like, how would you feel
if I kept going at ya
about some stupid teenage
mistake that you made?
‐ Sweetheart, you are the
stupid teenage mistake I made.
‐ (LAUGHS) Right.
Very nice.
‐ Did you hear back from the magazine
about your story?
‐ Not yet.
‐ Well, fingers crossed.
Be great to see your name in print.
Okay, love. I love you.
‐ Love you, too.
(PHONE CLICKS OFF)
JOANNA: It's only two days.
‐ It's only two days.
‐ Can you not see anyone else?
Make an escape?
‐ No pals, remember? Sad case.
‐ Come on.
MARIANNE: It's just a dinner.
It's just a boring dinner,
and a weekend being a dutiful daughter.
And then I'll be back.
JOANNA: Yeah, they can't do
that much damage in 48 hours.
‐ You haven't met my mother.
(PEGGY SCOFFS)
‐ Do you want another drink?
‐ No, thanks.
‐ Are you sure?
‐ Yeah. You're very kind.
(MARIANNE AND CONNELL CHUCKLING)
‐ You guys are fucking, right?
You're together.
‐ Yes.
- Yes, we are.
‐ Yeah.
PEGGY: Okay.
(CHUCKLES)
And for, like, months.
Everyone's speculating,
even though you, like...
never actually touch each other.
‐ It's not a new thing.
We used to hook up in school.
Secretly.
PEGGY: Oh, really?
‐ Hope you don't mind me saying that now.
‐ No. Not at all.
PEGGY: Secretly?
Like some kind of game?
That's actually really fucking hot.
Well, you make a very cute couple.
‐ Thanks.
- MARIANNE: Couple.
‐ Oh, you're not exclusive?
That's cool.
I wanted to try that with mine,
but he was not up for it.
MARIANNE: Men can be possessive.
PEGGY: You'd really think they'd jump
at the idea of multiple partners.
‐ Generally,
and I am generalizing...
CONNELL: Mm.
MARIANNE: Men seem more concerned
with limiting the freedoms of women
than in exercising their own.
‐ If I were a man,
I would have three girlfriends.
At least. ‐ I see the appeal, but
it also sounds deeply stressful.
PEGGY: What about you?
CONNELL: What about me?
‐ Do you not fantasize about
having multiple women at once?
I thought that was a
universal thing for men.
‐ Right. Well, uh, no. Not really.
‐ We could have a threesome, if you want.
CONNELL: Sorry?
‐ The three of us could...
‐ (CHUCKLES) Right. Uh...
Right. Well, um, I haven't...
wouldn't...
wouldn't really be my cup of tea.
‐ I'm much too self‐conscious.
- PEGGY: Really?
‐ Yeah.
MARIANNE: I'd die. Yeah.
PEGGY: About what?
Your looks? But you're so pretty.
‐ Uh, I mean, thanks. That's not, um...
That's not it.
It's more that I, I don't feel...
uh, very appealing.
(LAUGHS)
PEGGY: What do you mean?
‐ Um...
Well, I... uh...
I guess I have a sort of...
unlovable...
I have a coldness about me.
‐ I don't believe that.
Is she cold with you?
‐ No.
‐ You're cool, but I wouldn't say
you were cold, necessarily.
‐ I think, uh, cool implies
a degree of cold.
‐ You just live up here too much.
You need to be more in touch
with your feelings.
Maybe.
(CHUCKLES)
‐ Well.
I won't intrude any longer.
‐ You're not intruding.
PEGGY: I'll see you tomorrow.
No, stay where you are.
Stay where you are.
MARIANNE: No, not at all.
I'll show you out.
‐ Connell.
CONNELL: See you, Peggy.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(CONNELL CHUCKLES)
MARIANNE: Ah, well. (LAUGHS)
Jesus... (LAUGHS)
‐ Jesus Christ. (LAUGHS)
You saved me there.
I literally physically couldn't do that.
Couldn't have sex with you
in front of her.
‐ I'd have done it.
If you wanted to.
I could see you didn't, though.
‐ Yeah, well, then you...
You shouldn't do
what you don't want to do.
‐ No, I didn't mean that.
It's more that...
had you wanted to...
I'd have enjoyed you wanting to.
I like doing things for you.
‐ No‐‐.
You, you can't do things
that you don't want, or, uh...
or things you don't enjoy
just to make me happy.
‐ But I like making you happy.
‐ I...
Yeah.
Mm.
Uh, sorry.
I'm sorry.
‐ Connell, what's wrong?
‐ I don't know. I just felt a bit, uh...
a bit weird. I don't know. Um...
‐ If I've done something to upset you,
I'm really sorry.
‐ No. No, I, uh...
I, I'm sorry.
I don't know what that was. It's...
Just felt a bit, uh...
Uh, I'm fine.
‐ You sure?
‐ Yeah, yeah. Sorry. (CHUCKLES)
(CURTAINS RUSTLING)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(CONNELL SIGHS)
CONNELL: Marianne?
Look, uh...
Last night, I just... I just felt...
Uh...
(KISSING)
You know I really love you, don't you?
(BOTH MOAN)
(CONNELL MOANS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(BOTH MOAN)
(MOANS)
(BOTH MOANING)
(MARIANNE MOANING)
(CONNELL BREATHING HEAVILY)
(BOTH MOANING)
(BOTH PANTING)
(CONNELL GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY)
(EXHALES)
(MARIANNE SIGHS)
‐ (EXHALES) I was...
Think I was starting to have feelings
for you there at one point.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
‐ Ah, no.
Should have to repress
all that stuff, Marianne.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
That's what I do, anyway.
(MARIANNE LAUGHS)
(EXHALES)
‐ What?
‐ Would you, would you ever like,
um... (CLEARS THROAT)
or would you want to...
‐ Want to what?
‐ Like, uh...
send me a photo?
‐ A photo?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Like, a... a photo of the view, or...
‐ Uh, no, not a...
Not a photo of the view. I mean, um...
a photo of you.
Unclothed, preferably.
‐ Sure.
‐ Only if you wanted to.
‐ All right.
‐ Like, I'd delete it.
‐ Why are you deleting it?
What's wrong with my hypothetical picture?
‐ No, it's not that. It's more so, uh...
It's for you. For your... privacy,
or for your reassurance.
‐ Oh.
What about you?
‐ What about me?
‐ Can I have one of you?
‐ Of me?
‐ Of your dick, preferably.
(BOTH CHUCKLING) ‐ Ah, you'd actually
want a picture of my dick, would ya?
‐ Only fair.
You probably shouldn't.
‐ Hmm.
‐ I'd never delete it.
I'd look at it every single day,
and I'd take it to my grave.
(CHUCKLES)
CONNELL: Mm.
(MARIANNE CHUCKLES)
(CONNELL GROANS)
(MARIANNE GIGGLES)
‐ Oh, Connell, you're all wet.
(CONNELL GROANS)
JASON: Connell!
Can you step into the office for a sec?
‐ Yeah. No bother.
JASON:
Yeah, I mean, it's shit timing.
It is for absolutely everybody,
but it just...
Look, it sort of made sense
to bring things forward, you know?
‐ Right.
‐ Yeah.
See, we wanna get the refurb done
by August so we can have this big...
summer opening, you know?
Catch the holiday crowd.
‐ Right.
‐ Which does mean we are closing
for June and July.
But we'll hold all of your shifts
right through May. Yeah.
And we want you back in August, as well.
‐ Oh, okay. Yeah.
‐ Okay?
‐ Like, what the fuck am I
supposed to do now?
Go looking for a job
in the middle of exams?
‐ I can sublet this place for you,
if you'd like.
Still be here for you in September.
‐ Thanks.
Sorry.
‐ Mate, don't worry about it.
‐ Mm. So that's it, then.
- Off to Sligo for a summer.
‐ No.
Just stay with Marianne for a few weeks
until you find a job.
‐ Mm.
‐ You can't be fucking serious.
‐ What?
‐ You stay with her, what,
four nights a week? Five?
‐ That's different. I don't live with her.
‐ You think if you move your toothbrush
into her bathroom
she's gonna get too attached or something?
‐ Fuck off. I don't think that at all.
I just wouldn't want to ask her.
‐ (SCOFFS) Fuck's sake, man.
I give up. Do what you want.
I can't get my head around it.
‐ Sorry.
(FOOTSTEPS DEPARTING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(SILVERWARE CLATTERING)
‐ We've heard you're doing so well
in college, Marianne.
‐ Well, exams don't start till May, so...
fingers crossed.
TRISH:
But your essays have all gone well,
your mother was saying.
MARIANNE: So far, yeah.
‐ Good woman.
‐ Are you enjoying the flat?
GERALD: Mm.
Of course. You girls lived there
when you were at Trinity.
‐ No. Denise did.
I used to visit. Oh, God,
we had such fun in that place.
Got up to all sorts, didn't we?
GRANNY ROSE:
I never liked Dublin.
Too many people.
TRISH:
I think Dublin is a lovely city.
And where your parents met.
‐ It's a nice flat.
TRISH:
Have you been up to visit, Alan?
‐ No.
AUNT CAITLIN:
You're working him too hard.
GERALD: He's well able for it.
‐ You could give him a day off
to visit his sister.
‐ Caitlin didn't visit me
till I was in my second year.
‐ Did I not?
‐ I have to say, Alan's doing very well.
He got a couple of men under him,
climbing that ladder.
‐ Well, that's great, Alan.
‐ (CLEARS THROAT)
Can I give anyone a top up?
TRISH: Thanks.
(SILVERWARE CLATTERING)
‐ Your father would be so proud of you.
Both of you. He really would.
‐ Indeed.
And how is business, Denise?
‐ Fine. Very good.
(SCRUBBING)
‐ That was nice, wasn't it?
(CAP CLATTERS)
Pleasant, I thought.
Very good of you to come home and...
regale us all with stories
of your achievements in the big city.
Banging on about your...
exams and your essays and your...
fuckin' top of the class
over Mam's birthday meal.
‐ I didn't bring that up. They did.
‐ You're joking.
You couldn't shut up about it.
(DISHES CLATTERING)
Do you think you're smarter than me?
- Can you hear me?
‐ I don't know.
I've never thought about
which one of us is smarter.
‐ Bullshit.
‐ Okay.
‐ Okay?
You do think you're smarter than me?
‐ Sure.
Whatever you say.
I'm the smart one
and you're the hopeless fuck‐up.
(SPLASHING)
(SILVERWARE CLATTERS)
(EXHALES)
(HITS)
♪♪
(SNIFFLES)
(CAMERA SHUTTER BEEPS)
(PHONE THUDS)
(SNIFFLES)
DENISE:
Will we see you again before the summer?
‐ Exams are gonna be pretty full‐on.
‐ You can't study here?
‐ No.
‐ You're very different,
you and your brother.
It's difficult for him.
‐ And things are so easy for me?
‐ Honestly, yes.
Yes, they are.
You're about to head back to Dublin
to your degree and your friends
and your life
that exists outside of Sligo.
That isn't the case for your brother.
It is very difficult for him, Marianne.
‐ And that's my fault?
‐ That's not what I'm saying.
‐ You act like it is.
‐ That's not how I feel.
‐ Why are you living your life like that?
With him dictating everything?
‐ Marianne‐‐
‐ Does it make you happy?
‐ None of this makes me happy.
‐ Then why are you allowing it
to be like this?
‐ What do you think I should do?
Kick him out?
How do you think I should
handle this, exactly,
'cause I'd love to have your insight.
Because I'm trying to do the best I can.
‐ I don't want to miss my bus, so...
‐ Fine.
‐ Thanks for the lift.
(CAR ZOOMS OFF)
(EXHALES)
(MUSIC PLAYING ON COMPUTER)
(SOBBING SOFTLY)
‐ You all right?
‐ I'm fine.
‐ The film get ya?
(MARIANNE SNIFFLES)
‐ No, I'm just feeling a bit off
at the moment.
‐ You're not pregnant or anything,
are you?
‐ (LAUGHS SOFTLY) No.
(CONNELL CHUCKLES)
I got my period this morning.
‐ Can I get you anything?
‐ Tea.
‐ Mm?
Tea?
All right.
(CONNELL GRUNTS)
(MARIANNE EXHALES)
(SIGHS)
(WATER STEAMING)
‐ I think it'll just hurt.
Feeling a bit crampy.
♪♪
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
NIALL: So how's Marianne?
Have you asked her about moving in yet?
‐ Uh...
No.
‐ What is it exactly that's stopping you?
JOANNA: That is precisely what I'm saying.
JAMIE: Come off it.
You're just being politically correct
for the sake of it.
JOANNA:
Oh, my God. Why is it always people
that look and sound exactly like you
that say shit like that?
‐ Look, I just think that we all need
to take some responsibility
for what we put into the world,
right, and then... Sorry. Excuse me.
JOANNA: What does that even mean?
JAMIE: And therefore, what comes back‐‐
JOANNA: But it's so much easier for you
as a straight white man
to say stuff like that.
JAMIE: Oh, come‐‐
I can have an opinion‐‐ Just b‐‐.
Just 'cause I'm straight and white and
male doesn't mean I can't have an opinion.
I can have an opinion, regard‐‐
JOANNA: That's what I mean, yeah.
Exactly. Nothing to do with the years...
JAMIE: I am so sorry.
I am so sorry I'm a straight white man.
JOANNA: The years of oppression
that basically every other group
on the planet has faced,
other than that. JAMIE: And I have to
pay for that. And I have to pay for that.
‐ Because you still benefit from it.
JAMIE: Like what?
(DISTANT ARGUING)
MARIANNE: Are you all right?
‐ Why does he always do that?
‐ What?
‐ The lads you hang out with,
they always have their f...
fucking hands all over you.
‐ (SCOFFS) Oh. Right.
You don't want to touch me,
but you get to dictate who else does.
‐ I touch ya.
‐ Yeah.
As long as there's about six closed doors
between us and another person
who might fucking witness you
demonstrating
some level of affection towards me.
‐ Grand.
‐ It's not a big deal.
Jamie's just like that. Forget it.
(CONNELL SCOFFS)
I think I'm gonna go.
(SNIFFS)
‐ Don't.
‐ I'm fine. I'm just a bit tired.
We're fine.
‐ Please don't go.
(CONNELL INHALES, THEN EXHALES)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
‐ You all right?
‐ Mm‐hmm.
Just a bit tired.
‐ Do you want to skip it?
‐ Ah, you can't.
‐ Why?
It's just a birthday party.
Sophie won't mind.
You can't be indebted to someone forever
'cause they get you a job
in a crappy restaurant, Connell.
‐ Who said I was indebted to her?
‐ When you're a famous writer,
you won't be indebted to anyone.
You'll be, uh,
lording it over the rest of us.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
- What?
‐ You ready?
PHILIP: Have you ever been to Barcelona?
JOANNA: Yeah, but not since I was a kid.
PHILIP: Oh, man. You have to go.
I was at a festival there,
like, last summer.
It was just, like,
punk and techno in these big,
massive, like, airport hangars.
Yeah, like, 20 minutes into the city.
It was a‐‐ amazing.
(ALL CHATTERING)
We should all go, like, this summer.
‐ Guys.
- PHILIP: I'd go back.
‐ Enough drinking and talking.
It's game time.
Get back in the pool.
Connell, can you help break the grill out?
‐ Yeah. Sure.
Come on. Marianne.
PHILIP: Yeah, let's do it.
‐ Oh, we can just watch, will we?
‐ Yeah. We'll ref.
‐ That's a nice solid torso
you have there.
‐ Uh, I bagsied him. He's on my team.
CONNELL: Yeah.
PHILIP:
Peggy, baby, let's do it.
‐ Don't worry, Marianne.
I won't steal him.
(MARIANNE CHUCKLES)
(SPLASHING, CHATTERING)
‐ She said my torso is solid.
‐ Ah, did she really, Jamie?
‐ Yeah, she did. Yeah.
(ALL LAUGHING AND CHATTERING)
Here, get it, get it.
(LAUGHS)
(MARIANNE LAUGHS)
(ALL CHATTERING)
(ALL YELLING AND LAUGHING)
JAMIE: Can I ask you something?
‐ Of course.
‐ Do you think you're right for him?
(ALL YELLING AND CHATTERING)
♪♪
(LAUGHTER AND INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(WATER LAPPING)
‐ I'm just gonna go and have a cigarette.
‐ I've been admiring you.
(SPLASHING)
♪♪
‐ Marianne?
‐ Yeah?
‐ Uh...
It's nothing.
‐ Okay.
♪♪
(CONNELL SNIFFLING)
(DOOR SLAMS)
(FOOTSTEPS DEPARTING)
(EXHALES)
(PANTING)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(SOBBING SOFTLY)
(CRYING)
(GRAVEL CRUNCHING)
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
(SOFT INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)