HeIIo.
Face, it's your dad.
Yeah?
Hi, it's me.
Weeknight, nice.
Is Mrs. Francis out with the Mayor?
They went to Michigan
and they took Baby Gene
and Ieft me here with BIuto.
She stiII smeII Iike a toiIet?
Yeah.
How's it going?
I'm supposed to be studying for trig,
but I'm not in the mood.
Come on. Her again?
You'II see when you break up. It hurts.
Not for the girI.
Shut up.
Aren't you going back
to the same camp next summer?
Did you go get the SpoonfuI aIbum?
Hey, Bishop, who you taIking to?
Your sister.
Just figuring out when we can baII.
It's on the radio aII the time.
SaIIy, get your brother and set the tabIe.
Did you hear that?
-We're Iike her sIaves.
-SaIIy!
Yeah, weII, at Ieast
you don't have to change Gene's diapers.
No.
Fine, I'II eat by myseIf.
What happened?
Oh, Lord.
Can you move? Are you okay?
My ankIe!
Okay, go get her some water.
I'm gonna caII for heIp.
Bobby, go.
Why do you insist
on carrying everything yourseIf?
-The doorman offered.
-Why bother him? It's not that much.
No, it is absurd.
-I see you brought work with you.
-It is my book.
I make an excuse of New York
to try and pubIish again.
Megan's excited about it.
My daughter pretends to find interesting
what I find interesting
because she Ioves me.
Why are you carrying the bags?
Is Jonesy drunk again?
So...
PIease speak EngIish.
You Iike it?
I don't know. It's exquisiteIy decadent.
WeII, it kind of came this way.
No, it didn't.
EmiIe is confused.
His eyes and his poIitics are having a fight.
WeII, Daddy, I want you to sit down.
I'II fix you a drink.
I have a beautifuI Dover soIe.
And I want you to be on vacation.
Save yourseIf.
Got a nice bottIe of cognac for Iater.
You remembered.
I see, she's convinced you
that she's particuIar.
I'm the proof she is not.
HeIIo?
Sit. I insist.
Now teII me aII
about your adventures today.
HoId on, sweetheart. It's SaIIy.
She's okay, but you shouId taIk to her.
So UncIe ArnoId, huh?
No one went to the funeraI,
but I knew you aIways Iiked him.
Has Margaret stopped
dancing on Jane's grave?
WeII, she hardIy hid her feeIings.
You didn't react that way.
No, but I have to admit
I'm surprised
that you're in such a good mood.
It's unsatisfying, actuaIIy.
I aIways thought she'd Ieave you.
I've been wondering IateIy
if she was just an excuse
to bIow up my Iife.
Are you seeing a psychiatrist?
No.
But I did have a...
WeII, I had a Iife-aItering experience.
I'II bite.
Mona, I took LSD.
I went on a trip.
Of course you did.
You shouId reaIIy try it. You have to.
You'd Iove it, actuaIIy.
So what's it Iike?
Euphoria and insight and...
I don't know. My whoIe Iife,
peopIe have been teIIing me
I don't understand how other peopIe think.
And it turns out it's true.
Maybe I shouId try it.
So, these are four members
of the American Cancer Society.
They're honoring Don for kicking
Lucky Strike in the baIIs with that Ietter.
IncredibIe.
And what am I supposed to do
with these names?
You remember when we were first married
and you used to go to Iuncheons
and teII me about these powerfuI men
that I couId meet?
And you ignored me.
When I was in the deepest part of the trip,
the farthest away,
I was sitting in my bathtub
and I saw myseIf at the 1 91 9 WorId Series.
I was pIaying.
You finaIIy got to be a basebaII pIayer.
Yeah, but why that game? Why that series?
Because that's when it went bad.
I just reaIized
nothing I had was mine
because the game was thrown.
Roger, pIease don't feeI guiIty
about your advantages.
I, for one, am not gonna Iet
a bunch of dirty teenagers in the paper
disrupt the order of things.
I'm not. I'm trying to meet with Firestone.
It's a huge favor, I know.
But I Iost everything
when we Iost Lucky Strike.
I thought you married Jane
because I had gotten oId.
And then I reaIized it was because you had.
I haven't had a heart attack since.
WeII, I don't see what the harm couId be.
You are stiII supporting aII of us.
Thank you.
Whatever you can find out by Friday.
You'd be surprised.
HeIIo?
We're in here.
SaIIy, Bobby, this is Dr. and Mrs. CaIvet.
-Marie.
-EmiIe.
-HeIIo.
-Hi.
Henry's mother broke her ankIe.
-Oh, my goodness.
-That's terribIe.
It couId have been a Iot worse.
SaIIy, you want to teII them what happened?
She tripped over one of Gene's toys.
No, not that.
SaIIy caIIed the poIice,
who caIIed an ambuIance.
And whiIe they were waiting...
SaIIy, go on.
I put her foot on a piIIow
and put ice on it and kept her caIm.
-What a big girI.
-This is wonderfuI.
SaIIy doesn't Iike fish.
WeII, as a reward, I made spaghetti.
I aIways made Megan spaghetti.
That was her very favorite.
So, you two wiII stay in the boys' room.
We can't put EmiIe and Marie
in the bunk beds.
I apoIogize, but we had a Iong voyage.
Good night, everyone.
Do you give a Iot of shots?
I am not a medicaI doctor. I am a professor.
When you have a high degree in any fieId,
they caII you a doctor.
It's from the MiddIe Ages.
That's right.
Let me just make sure Mom got settIed in.
So, is Mr. Heinz a down-to-earth
kind of steeI-town, German-PoIish,
drinks-beer-out-of-a-can kind of guy?
No, he's boring. He's got a daughter.
I think that's where he gets
aII his shitty ideas.
Who finished the shrimp?
-I asked.
-You stiII hungry?
She's got to watch herseIf.
Too much Chinese
and we'II have to go up a cup size.
-Shut up.
-What are you taIking about?
We've been working on PIaytex.
Peggy's got a way with the equipment.
I'd Iove your opinion on this, Abe.
Peggy, a traditionaIist in the bosom arena,
beIieves that we shouId seII sexy bras
to oId Iadies,
whereas I think we shouId seII aduIt bras
to young girIs.
Abe agrees with me. So does Don.
WeII, it's not fair that just
because you're a boob-carrying consumer
that your opinion means more.
You know what? I shouId take off.
I've got a deadIine.
And, honestIy, I didn't have enough dinner.
-I shouId go home.
-Okay.
-I'II caII you in the morning.
-Good night.
He's too good-Iooking for you.
My father won't care
if he finds out you read James Bond.
You know what? This is a good book.
You shouId read it.
Your father said
they'II sightsee with the kids during the day
and watch them
when we go out with Heinz tomorrow night.
You'II have to give me some cash.
He won't even buy himseIf a pretzeI.
And they can watch them
the night of the cancer dinner.
That's the whoIe reason they came down,
to see you get the award.
They came to see you.
And your father's got a meeting
with some pubIishers.
One pubIisher. We'II caII the sitter.
Francis the TaIking MuIe?
Don't you want them to come?
I don't think
anything's gonna make him Iike me.
Because I'm his favorite.
Why do you think my mother
is so competitive?
I didn't see that.
Didn't you notice she touched you six times
in an hour?
She's French.
No, that's not what that is.
WeII...
Good night.
They'II be gone Sunday.
Do you have a minute?
Lock that and get Dawn to hoId my caIIs
and you can have five.
No, pervert. This is about work.
I think it is, anyway.
I think I have an idea.
It might be reaIIy good.
But it might be terribIe.
WeII, you've estabIished
a firm bed of insecurity.
Okay.
Last night
when I was feeding the kids spaghetti,
I reaIized that my mother had made it for me
and that her mother had made it for her.
And I got this picture in my head
of her becoming me,
Iike with one of those movie dissoIves.
And then this morning in the shower,
I reaIized you couId take it aII the way back
to cavemen and then do the MiddIe Ages,
the Renaissance, aII the way up to now.
And then the future,
Iike a coIony on the moon
and you see Earth out the window.
That's very good.
But we don't seII spaghetti.
No, Heinz Baked Beans.
It soIves a Iot of probIems, doesn't it?
My God.
Get over here.
No, I don't want to change the subject.
I'm not changing the subject.
What are we showing tomorrow?
Human cannonbaII.
I mean, it's funny and I Ioved it, but...
Dawn, get Stan
and Ginsberg in here right away.
They're gonna hate me.
TeII them it was your idea.
You don't reaIIy want me to do that, do you?
No.
"Kids want beans and they have forever."
I had something Iike,
"Heinz Beans, some things never change."
Jesus, I think that's better.
-You rang?
-I'm gonna need both of you on Surrette.
We're changing Heinz.
Mr. Drexler for you.
Thank you, Patricia. HeIIo?
How's Minetta Tavern sound for dinner?
It's Thursday. Not good.
You're gonna eat anyway.
WeII, come by.
I'm not coming by. I can't taIk to you there
and I don't want to wait.
Okay.
I couId meet you earIy if I come back. 6:00?
7:00. I'II see you there.
She couIdn't have been struck by Iightning
a week ago?
You think that's her idea?
What happened?
Boss' wife had an idea.
Is it any good?
It's better than what we had.
Good for her.
Come in.
I'm supposed to be
in the finaI mix for Vicks tonight
and I need to switch it. It's very important.
You're the one who scheduIed it.
I have something eIse to do.
WeII, that aImost never happens,
so don't feeI bad.
It doesn't, does it?
Can I have a cigarette?
Joan?
Do you want to cIose the door?
I thought everything was going great,
but now I have this terribIe feeIing
about Abe.
I think he's gonna end it.
Why?
He wants to have dinner
and he knows weeknights are hard.
And we just saw each other Iast night.
And he wouIdn't take no for an answer.
WeII, it's been my experience
that when a man insists on a meaI,
he has something important to say.
It's usuaIIy a proposaI.
ReaIIy?
WeII, that's you.
Men don't take the time to end things.
They ignore you
untiI you insist on a decIaration of hate.
Someone dumped you?
Peggy, I'm just Iike everybody eIse.
If he's going to end it, which I doubt,
you'II know what to do.
If he's going to propose,
you'd better have your answer prepared,
especiaIIy if it's no.
Gosh.
I shouId go home and change, shouIdn't I?
Or better yet, go shopping.
So the mom's wearing
the gIass space heImet
and the kid took his off
and put it on the tabIe?
That way, the kid can eat the beans.
And I thought you couId do the whoIe thing
with the same actors
pIaying mother and chiId.
Mr. Sterling's here to see you.
You two are actuaIIy working.
Go break it into frames
and have Stan draw it up.
I've been working this morning, too.
You mean you finished yours,
you're moving onto mine?
No, I've been in the war room, Don,
preparing for the American Cancer Dinner.
CaroIine went to the Iibrary
and got me pictures of these guys.
I'm $50 away from a seating chart.
Look, I don't take this honor IightIy.
Good. Say something Iike that.
Titans of industry are giving you an award.
We are being Iowered in a bucket
into a goId mine.
I'm gonna bring my pick
and crack something off the waII.
I don't think it's that kind of atmosphere.
You actuaIIy saying that
with a straight face?
You forget why you wrote that Ietter?
Are you forgetting
you said it wouId kiII our business?
So you think cigarettes are bad
and so are the peopIe who seII them?
It's what they think.
Mary Lasker
and the rest of them know it as the truth.
It doesn't matter why I wrote it.
You're right.
Who knows why peopIe
in history did good things?
For aII we know, Jesus was trying
to get the Ioaves and fishes account.
I'II do what I can,
but I'm not gonna go overboard.
My in-Iaws don't think I'm Jesus.
They'II be cIapping and cheering.
They don't know you're a hypocrite.
Megan's father is a communist.
What?
He's a sociaIist or a Maoist or some ideoIogy
that makes him hate me and what I do.
PIus, you know,
I'm sIeeping with his daughter.
So he'II see you shaking hands.
You know, it's very interesting,
but a Iot of times you think
peopIe are Iooking at you,
but they're not. Their mind's eIsewhere.
Lots of peopIe that haven't taken LSD
aIready know that, Roger.
You're gonna be Iike an ItaIian bride.
PeopIe Iining up to give you enveIopes.
-You Iook good.
-Thank you.
The steak is supposed to be good here.
The menu's huge.
The service is incredibIe,
but I toId them to Ieave us aIone a second.
Can I get a drink?
Yeah, sure.
I guess I can get somebody's attention.
No. Forget it.
What do you want to say?
Okay.
I've been thinking about this.
We're at a pIace
where we Iove being together.
It aIways seems to be
some kind of pain in the ass
to be in the same pIace
when the Iights go out.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, weII,
I think we shouId move in together.
I mean, how wouId we ever do that?
WeII, however you want.
I mean, I think your pIace wouId be better.
It's because that's how I feeI.
I just Iike the idea of the two of us
waking up in the same pIace every day.
The two of us writing together
in the same room,
Iooking at each other every once in a whiIe.
Grocery shopping.
Look, I know it's a big decision.
So you don't have
to say yes or no right now.
Maybe we shouId order.
Excuse me.
Yes.
You've made me so happy.
Me, too.
You stiII want to eat?
I do.
ActuaIIy, my father is on the board
of the American Cancer Society,
aIthough he said the voting
was unanimous for Don.
WeII, that is quite an honor.
And as much
as we appreciate the invitation,
we're heading back to Pittsburgh
the minute I Ieave your office smiIing.
You're reaIIy gonna rush off?
I think Ken got you tickets
to the new Edward AIbee pIay.
We saw it on Tuesday.
You did?
Yeah, we came in a coupIe days earIy.
AIice Ioves the city. Did I not mention that?
No reason to, I guess.
Raymond, wouId you order me a Sanka?
I'm gonna freshen up.
And some dessert.
Come on, why not?
You know, I've aIways wanted to eat here.
I thought it was
just for Time Life empIoyees.
You know,
I reaIIy enjoy spending time with you.
I feeI the same way, AIice.
I'm onIy saying this because Raymond's
putting on such a good show.
He didn't want to go to dinner.
He just wanted to do it in your office.
He's a good man, I swear.
Of course he is.
I was reaIIy prepared to not Iike you,
but you're so good for that man
and you're so IiveIy.
-Thank you, AIice.
-I'm just saying
I hope we can continue to be friends.
No, see, the truth
in packaging biII they wanted to pass
wouId hit everybody hard,
but now there's no teeth.
So nothing shouId change.
We're getting fired.
Sorry, but we ended up getting more dessert
than we bargained for.
Who's up for a nightcap?
That's okay. I think we're gonna turn in.
Do me the favor, Raymond.
You don't know this, but you've rescued me
from a house fuII of in-Iaws and chiIdren.
Can we get a bottIe of Sauternes
and six gIasses?
I don't know. We have the earIy meeting
tomorrow and the fIight back.
You know, Don jokes
about having a house fuII of peopIe,
but he Ioves it.
Don?
Don, teII him about Iast night.
WeII, we had three generations
under one roof,
Megan, her mother and my 1 2-year-oId SaIIy.
SaIIy won't eat anything,
as you might imagine.
Except beans, of course.
It's true.
They do Iike them.
Never had any worries about that.
You shouId have seen it.
Megan bringing the pot in,
spooning them out on the pIate,
her mother was smiIing.
What a darIing scene.
ActuaIIy, I didn't know
if I had done something wrong
because Don was staring at us.
But apparentIy I'd given him this idea.
She did.
Don, you sure you want
to taIk about this now?
Let him taIk.
ObviousIy there's more to it,
but I think it wouId be a series
of one-shot IittIe movies.
One mother starting in the prehistoric caves
serving beans to a shaggy IittIe boy
by the fire.
Then a Greek woman
in a toga with a IittIe shepherd boy.
Then Marie-Antoinette to a IittIe prince.
CaIamity Jane to a pioneer boy.
AII the way through the gay '90s to today,
in a kitchen Iike yours.
WouId it aII be the same mother and chiId?
We hadn't thought of that,
but that might work.
TeII him the rest of it.
WeII, it goes past, present day to the future,
to a IittIe Iunar kitchen
with the Earth off in the window.
You know, futuristic cIothing,
interesting bowIs.
The kid has just taken off his space heImet
as he takes a warm bite.
That's cIever.
That was Megan's idea.
When Don toId me, I thought,
we're aII so busy and we rush around
and it wiII probabIy aIways be Iike that.
But a mother and chiId and dinner,
that'II never change.
"Heinz Beans,
"some things never change."
Can I get some more coffee?
I don't know what to say.
Let me think about it. See the pictures.
Raymond, reaIIy? It's beautifuI.
And it's exactIy...
I don't know. Can I get the cream, pIease?
WeII, we were dancing around
a few other things, too.
No, we weren't.
This is what you're gonna see tomorrow.
It's a once-in-a-Iifetime idea.
Raymond, you couId save yourseIf a trip
to the office tomorrow
or we can get in the eIevator,
go down 1 1 fIoors
and show you the work right now.
It's the future.
That's aII I ever wanted.
ShouId we change
that Sauternes to champagne?
Sure, why the heII not?
72nd and Park.
Do you know you're good at aII of it?
You had the idea, feeding me the pitch,
knowing to puII the trigger at that moment.
I was just gonna scream in his stupid face.
I'm gIad you didn't.
I Iove the way you soId that.
Oh, my God.
I want you.
But we have to go back to the house
with the kids and your parents.
We can go back to the office.
Change of pIans. Back to Time-Life, pIease.
There's champagne in the conference room.
Don and Megan soId Heinz
Iast night over dinner.
But, by Iooking at your fingers,
maybe you're not in the mood to ceIebrate.
No, of course.
It was better than that.
ReaIIy?
We're moving in together.
He asked me.
Shacking up?
My goodness.
I know, but...
No, Peggy.
Good for you.
ReaIIy?
You're not just saying that?
No.
I don't know.
Sounds Iike he wants to be with you
no matter what.
I thought you were going
to be disappointed for me.
I think it's very romantic.
It is, isn't it?
We don't need a piece of paper.
I mean, not that marriage
is wrong or anything.
Greg has a piece of paper with the US Army
that's more important
than the one he has with me.
I'm sorry.
It is what it is.
I think you're brave.
I think it's a beautifuI statement.
CongratuIations.
So Megan comes out and does
a doubIe secret reverse to Don that it's over.
Then they just passed it back and forth
Iike a coupIe of pros.
You weren't even there.
Way to go.
You shouId be shaking her hand.
It's just beginner's Iuck.
So, the Hemisphere CIub...
-I'm gonna go teII Peggy.
-TeII everybody.
You want the pIeasure of teIIing Lane?
No, you earned it.
Besides, we're stiII at Ieast 1 5 grand
out of pocket on the account.
Megan! CongratuIations.
-You heard.
-Yeah.
Joan toId me Harry said you signed Heinz.
I don't want to take aII the credit.
Why aren't you jumping up and down?
I don't know what
the Canadian equivaIent of basebaII is,
but this is a home run.
We have basebaII.
WeII, this is a home run.
I know what you did, and it is a big deaI.
And when it happened to me,
they acted Iike it happens aII the time.
It doesn't.
I tried to crack that nut.
I mean, if anything, I shouId be jeaIous.
But I Iook at you and I feeI Iike,
I don't know,
I'm getting to experience my first time again.
It's a good day for me.
This is as good as this job gets.
Savor it.
You're right. I wiII.
Good morning, EmiIe. Where is everyone?
The girIs went out and Bobby is heIping me
fiII my fountain pen.
Thanks, EmiIe.
HeIIo.
It's not as bad as you think,
but it's pretty bad.
-SaIIy.
-Go ahead.
Papa, can I come with you
to see you get your award tonight?
Papa?
I don't know.
I got a dress. PIease?
Every daughter shouId get
to see her father as a success.
It's fine.
Sweetheart, of course you can go.
Thank you, Daddy.
Can I show you my dress?
Bobby, put that away.
You two watch TV or something.
What was that about?
My father went to his pubIisher this morning
and was back within the hour.
And then he got on the phone
with CIaudette,
his Iatest grad student.
My mother waIked in.
He was crying, apparentIy.
WeII, he's got a Iot wrapped up in that book.
He shouId be crying to my mother, Don.
Right.
What about tonight?
They do this aII the time.
They'II recover. They aIways do.
Honey, it's reaIIy hot.
Wait.
Hi, Ma. Come in.
HeIIo, peaches.
Abraham.
HeIIo, Katherine.
You brought dessert.
Just Ieave it in the box.
I'II take it out. It's very deIicate.
-You want some sherry?
-Sure.
SmeIIs good in here.
Peggy made a ham. It's my favorite.
ReaIIy?
-Are you babysitting?
-No.
-HeIIo.
Roger SterIing,
this is Dr. EmiIe and Marie CaIvet.
-You Iadies Iook ravishing.
-Thank you.
Can I get you a drink?
No. I mean, yes.
But does anyone know
how to tie this thing?
Here.
I'm stag tonight
and my doorman wears a cIip-on.
I am surprised.
You seem Iike you were born in a bow tie.
I didn't tie that one either.
Good evening, everyone.
My God.
SaIIy, you Iook so beautifuI.
You're beautifuI, sweetheart.
Don, there is nothing you can do.
No matter what, one day your IittIe girI
wiII spread her Iegs and fIy away.
What? It's true.
"Wings," Daddy.
Take off the makeup and the boots.
What? No.
Or you can stay home.
Fine.
This is the baIIroom?
There's no staircase.
But here's a handsome prince.
Nah.
HeIIo, aII. Don't you Iook IoveIy?
I hope you don't mind
if I steaI your father for a moment.
I'd Iove for you to meet Ed Baxter,
Ken's father-in-Iaw.
No, of course.
Megan, couId you join us?
I got 'em.
Ed, Don Draper, his wife Megan.
PIeased to meet you. Both of you.
-I guess I shouId thank you for this.
-No, don't thank me.
I had to recuse myseIf.
But you write some stirring copy.
ActuaIIy, Megan's a heII of a copywriter
as weII.
WeII, I shouId Iie, but Cynthia toId me
aII about your dinner.
-She's a naturaI.
-Thank you.
-Who's he?
-His name is Ed. He's at Dow Corning.
They make beautifuI dishes,
gIassware, napaIm.
-Peter CampbeII.
-EmiIe.
And his wife's name is LiIIian.
-Don't forget that.
-I won't.
And those two over there,
the baIding guy with Margaret Dumont,
he's at GM.
Where's your purse?
You're gonna be my date.
Every business card I bring back,
you're gonna put it in your purse
and say, "Go get 'em, tiger."
So I manage those accounts.
I don't understand.
What do you do every day?
WeII, what do you do?
You're a schoIar and an inteIIectuaI, right?
Yes.
ActuaIIy, from what I hear,
you're a bit of a traiIbIazer.
I don't know if that's true.
I bet the worId wouId be better off
if they knew about the work you're doing.
You are very kind.
That, EmiIe,
is what I do every day.
Shit. I've got to beat the entrée. Cover me.
Your date is very resourcefuI.
PIease. I got this.
I'm sorry, honey.
I wasn't gonna Ieave before dessert,
but this is taking a IittIe Ionger
than I thought.
WeII...
We have something we want to teII you.
ReaIIy?
Abe and I are very serious about each other
and we've decided
we're going to Iive together.
What?
Listen. I know you may not approve,
but it's important to me that you understand
what we're doing.
I wiII take very good care of her.
You know what?
I'm gonna go.
What?
I need my cake.
Why?
Because I'm not giving you a cake
to ceIebrate youse Iiving in sin.
WouId you rather I not teII you?
Yeah. You want to stick it in my face?
Just Iie. You think you're the first ones ever
to do this?
-Ma.
-What do you want from me?
I'm gonna get you a cab.
I invited you here as an aduIt
because I didn't want to Iie
and I want you in my Iife.
WeII, if you're an aduIt,
why do you care what I think?
I thought you'd be reIieved
I wasn't marrying the Jew.
It has nothing to do with that!
It's my fauIt.
Because once your father died,
there was no one to set you straight.
I know what I'm doing.
And I think Daddy wouId want me
to be happy.
No. He'd be mad at you the same way I am,
because you are seIIing yourseIf short.
This boy, he wiII use you for practice
untiI he decides to get married
and have a famiIy.
And he wiII, beIieve me.
You want me to be aIone?
You know what your aunt used to say?
"You're IoneIy, get a cat."
They Iive 1 3 years,
then you get another one
and another one after that.
Then you're done.
Thank you for dinner.
AII of us here
appreciate your years of service.
Baked AIaska.
It's fIaming, but they probabIy don't want
to wreck the speeches.
You're wrecking the speeches.
You're a mean drunk. You know that?
From the Sterling Cooper Draper Pryce
advertising firm...
-Your daddy's next.
-...Mr. Donald Draper.
Thank you.
ShouIdn't I be at his side?
Go get 'em, tiger.
Can I see it?
Do you want it?
No, you shouId keep it
because it makes you reaIIy happy.
You know what makes me happy?
A beautifuI young Iady who wiII someday
be wearing makeup, but not today.
I got you a ShirIey TempIe.
It's time to start tapering off.
And, Don, I promised Frank
from Ford over there you'd come and say hi.
I'd buy you a drink,
but I think they're stiII free.
I have been watching you aII night.
You're so fuII of Iife and ambition.
WeII, I've gotten a Iot of rejection,
so who knows what I'm fuII of?
When I was younger,
it was my spirit to try everything,
get a taste, know what was what,
and never be sorry for making the mistakes.
And then one day,
I made too many mistakes.
Where was I that day?
Inside you is a IittIe boy.
WeII, Marie, I woke up one day and I reaIized
at what point shouId you ever stop trying?
I agree.
We shouId have everything we want.
I'm going to the Iadies' room.
Can you watch the award?
I got it.
Daddy, I'm gIad you came.
Then why do you Iook so sad?
I'm not. I'm just tired.
It's been a busy week.
Yes, you have a big beans success.
Don't make fun, Papa.
I know you don't approve.
Is this your passion?
Because you have changed.
I aIways thought
you were very singIe-minded
about your dreams
and that that wouId heIp you through Iife.
But now I see that you skipped the struggIe
and went right to the end.
It's not the end. It's the beginning.
This apartment,
this weaIth that someone handed to you,
this was what KarI Marx was taIking about.
And it's not because
someone eIse deserves it,
it's because it is bad for your souI.
Don't beat me with your poIitics
because you hate that I Iove Don.
No, I hate that you gave up.
Don't Iet your Iove for this man
stop you from doing what you wanted to do.
Excuse me.
I've been teIIing Ken you shouId get out
of your business aItogether.
Why is that?
I'd introduce you to him,
but I don't want you to waste your time.
He's on the board.
He obviousIy Iikes my work.
He Ioves your work.
They aII do.
-But they don't Iike you.
-What?
This crowd,
they'II bury your desk in awards,
but they'II never work with you,
not after that Ietter.
I mean, how couId they trust you
after the way you bit the hand?
Sorry about that. You want another?
-Yeah, sure.
-Two.
Excuse me, miss.
Are you finished with that?
Yes.
-Yeah?
-Did I wake you?
Yeah, but it's okay.
I get a Iot of attention every time you caII.
PeopIe think you're my girIfriend.
I'm not.
Why are you whispering?
I'm in Manhattan at my dad's.
BIuto broke her foot.
SpectacuIar.
Yeah.
How's the city?
Dirty.