Give me my next change.
I think I'm gonna puke.
- Not on this dress.
- I'm serious.
Kate Moss was doing this at 13.
You have two years on her.
Yeah, that's what I like to see.
You got this.
The next show, you're bride.
Did Austin just offer you bride?
It wasn't a real offer, Dad.
He was just being nice.
These shoes are gonna be impossible
to walk in.
You've done this 100 times before.
The runway's
just a little bit longer here.
One of the girls said
Madonna's in the front row.
Sweetie, hey, come on.
Are you gonna be able to do this?
All right, come here.
Here, hold this.
The doctor gave me these
for anxiety, all right?
It'll calm you down.
Here. Come on, it's okay.
Where's Alex?
Alex, you're up!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Knock them out!
Are you okay?
Alex!
How'd you get here?
- By osmosis.
- No helmet?
Didn't seem like riding weather.
The fact that you can barely stand
upright had nothing to do with it?
Infarctions hurt. House.
It's what they do.
Worsening pain could actually be
a good thing.
It means the nerves
might be regenerating.
It could be good, it could be bad.
Thanks for the differential.
Any other options?
Have you ever considered
a career as a motivational speaker?
- Why don't you check out some rehab?
- I did the rehab thing.
One session, and you
didn't even finish that session.
The guy wanted me
to "visualize the healing".
- I could do that at home.
- At least let me get you an MRI.
It's a very simple equation:
More pain, more pills.
Teenage supermodel.
Presented with double vision,
sudden aggressive behavior, cataplexy.
You had me at "teenage supermodel".
You okay? Mmm-hmm.
Wow.
You should be a model.
- Are you really 15?
- Who are you?
I'll be the one saving her life today,
assuming she's dying.
- Who are you?
- He's my father.
Any idea what's wrong with her?
Well, from the looks of it,
not a single thing.
I probably should stop staring
and check out the file.
So what set off the brawl?
She stand in your light?
I didn't even know her.
I didn't know what happened.
Look, I know some models
are notorious for hissy fits,
but Alex... I've never
even seen her get angry.
Even when she was a kid...
I'm sure she was delightful
in her youth.
Then you passed out.
I was passed out, but I wasn't.
I knew what was going on,
but I couldn't move or talk.
Yeah, it sounds like a medical thing.
It's called "cataplexy".
Catfight and cataplexy on the catwalk.
Cool. How much were you drinking?
She only had one sip of champagne.
Forget it.
I'll find out from the tox screen.
All right, look, I gave her a Valium.
- Do you think that's what did this?
- No.
How long have you had the sweats?
- A couple of days.
- Any other complaints?
My stomach's been bothering me
and I've been feeling a little nauseous.
Okay, here's how this works.
My lackeys will be by shortly
to draw some blood,
collect some urine,
any other fluids you got.
I'll do some other doctorly stuff,
and we'll be in touch.
Since when do you voluntarily
go see patients?
- Have you seen her?
- She's 15.
There's something about her,
something in her eyes,
- kind of a maturity.
- Yeah, yeah, she's an old soul.
This is creepy, even for you.
She's a fashion model,
on the cover of magazines.
We hold her up as the sexual ideal.
The law says
we can't touch her for three more years.
How hypocritical is that?
Did the history reveal anything,
oh, I don't know, medically relevant?
History, right.
I knew I was forgetting something.
You should do one of those while you're
running the labs and the tox screen.
The labs show Valium
and heroin in her urine.
A supermodel on smack. Shocker.
Oh, Alex, I expected
so much more from you.
Heroin chic is so five years ago.
Okay, let's start crossing out
withdrawal symptoms.
A positive test means she tried it once.
It doesn't mean she's an addict.
She's only 15.
- There's no age limit on addiction.
- He's right.
She's never menstruated. Sounds like
a symptom of drug addiction to me.
Or bulimia. Or her age. Some girls don't
start till their mid-to-late teens.
Evidence to the contrary,
the rounded hips.
The perfectly-sculpted,
bountiful breasts.
Implants.
I've seen some of her photos.
They've grown dramatically
since last summer.
Symptomatic of turning 14.
Two clinic hours says that those
"love apples" are handcrafted by God.
- I thought you didn't believe in God.
- I do now.
You're on.
Could we talk about her health
instead of her breasts?
It could be relevant.
Come on, Cameron,
there's nothing to be ashamed of.
Many women develop breasts.
No, I'm fine.
Even if she is an addict,
a lot of her symptoms,
the cataplexy, the violence,
it could be neurological.
If we chalk this up to drugs,
we could be
releasing her with juvenile MS
or Parkinson's...
- Detox her.
- Fine.
We'll set her up on a program,
they'll wean her onto the methadone.
And in four weeks,
we'll know you're right.
Or, we'll know that Cameron's right
and the pretty girl
will do Milan next fall in a wheelchair.
Put her in a coma,
pump her full of naltrexone.
Cut the four weeks to one night.
The lab reports show that your daughter
had heroin in her system.
Were you aware of her drug use?
No.
We think she's suffering
from withdrawal symptoms.
Detoxing generally takes several weeks.
The danger is that if the drugs
are masking some other illness,
it could worsen
before we've weaned her off the heroin.
Well, how much worse?
We don't know because
we don't know what's wrong.
There is a rapid detox procedure.
We flush her system
with an opioid antagonist.
It'll end her addiction overnight.
The process is dangerous
because we have to induce a coma.
It also means that if she ever relapses,
there's a good chance she'll overdose
because her body
won't react to the drug.
So either way I'm risking her life.
Do you have to tell her
how dangerous it is?
Is it dangerous?
There are certain risks.
We've gone over them with your father.
And he's not worried?
He's your dad. He's always gonna worry.
But he knows
we're gonna take good care of you.
Everything's starting to hurt.
My legs are...
Heroin withdrawal
is an extremely painful process.
But we're gonna put you to sleep.
You won't feel a thing.
- You promise?
- I promise.
That was a pretty stupid thing
to do, huh?
Getting hooked on drugs?
Yeah, not the best move
you've ever made.
Just, I thought it would be fun.
You don't have to explain to us.
A lot of,
a lot of the other girls were...
When you wake up,
you'll feel a lot better.
Nurse! Nurse!
You son of a bitch! You killed her!
- She's not dead.
- She had a heart attack.
She's stable now. The anesthesia...
Get her out of that coma.
- I don't think so.
- Stop this!
All right, I don't consent anymore.
I want her to do the slow detox.
Did you ever get a paper cut?
A really nasty one, between the fingers?
Multiply that by about a billion
and you'll just barely approach
the kind of suffering she'll experience
if we wake her up now.
We're committed to this.
She's out till morning. Go get a book.
I haven't slept in weeks,
because my teeth hurt.
The dentist couldn't find any cavities.
And I'm getting these headaches.
Oh! Poor you.
I think I'm going crazy.
And my stomach,
I roll out of bed and I wanna puke.
I take it you're married?
- You must be psychic.
- You must be witty.
- When's she due?
- How'd you know she was...
Because I'm doing her.
You've got Couvade Syndrome.
It's just a fancy way
of saying you should stop whining.
Millions of women have got
the same thing. They're not bugging me.
You're suffering
from sympathetic pregnancy.
Gotta go. People dying.
- Whole circle-of-life thing.
- It's all in my head?
No, it's all in your hormones.
The good news is, no one's gonna
lecture you if you smoke and get drunk.
Shouldn't she be awake by now?
It's only been a half an hour
since we stopped the medicine.
Well, you said
that's how long it would take.
I said it would take
about a half an hour.
- Couldn't this mean something more...
- So far, it means nothing.
She had a heart attack.
She could have brain damage.
- She could have something more...
- She's opening her eyes.
Alex, you okay?
Can you hear me?
I got the cute doctor.
Do you feel any pain?
Good. Let us know if anything changes.
If your stomach
doesn't feel right, anything.
Hey.
Are you mad at me, Daddy?
I let you down.
No, no. Not at all, sweetie, I...
I should have been more mature.
I should have handled the pressure.
Stop, stop.
We're gonna get you better, all right?
Nothing else matters.
Excuse me.
I've got you
on what we call a "banana bag".
Plenty of vitamins, nutrients...
I got the cute doctor.
Are you mad at me, Daddy?
- I let you down.
- What's going on?
I should have been more mature.
I should have handled the pressure.
What's wrong with her?
Anterograde amnesia,
short-term memory loss.
Evidence of a hypoxic brain injury.
It might be the result of getting cut
off from the oxygen when she flatlined.
Probably the result of that
rapid detox you told us to push on her.
You gonna put that down?
Are you gonna sulk?
I'm not gonna indulge you.
He treatment for hypoxic brain injuries
consists of...
Cameron, Chase and the Dark One.
Foreman, right?
The patient flatlined
for, like, 30 seconds.
You've got to be oxygen-deprived
for longer than that
to lose brain function.
- We can't be sure how long she was...
- Her brain's fine.
Memory loss. You're saying
that's not a neurological symptom?
No, I'm saying what I'm saying.
Her brain's fine.
She's faking?
She's got posttraumatic stress disorder.
We got models fighting in Iraq now?
Show me a woman on heroin
who looks like that,
and I'll show you a woman
who's been sexually abused.
That's your proof?
That she's good looking.
He manages her career, travels
the world with her, at her side 24/7.
He's either a very good dad
or a very bad dad.
You saw that tokus.
Would the fact that
she's your daughter really stop you?
Her brain is running away from reality
and when the drugs can't do it anymore,
it starts to shut down.
Your theory has the advantages
of being completely unprovable
and completely exculpating you.
When you guys are done talking,
do an MRI and an LP.
When her brain checks out as normal,
then we'll know that Daddy
really, really loves her.
Where's House?
- He was in too much pain to work.
- Who's covering?
He called 15 minutes
after his shift started.
It was too late to find anybody.
Exam Room One.
- Hi. Where's.
- Dr. House?
I wish I knew. What's the problem?
It's personal.
And it's so personal he didn't bother
writing anything in your chart.
- It's getting worse.
- What is?
It's personal.
- Fine. You can wait.
- Doctor!
I tell you what.
I am going to give you
Dr. House's personal pager number.
Why would your mind
go to abuse so fast?
- Because I had a funny uncle.
- You were abused?
What? No. Why'd your mind
go to that so fast?
I just had a funny uncle.
Great stories, always filthy.
I don't know
if it's something with this case
or you got something personal
going on, the whole breakup thing?
- It's personal.
- House.
Your pain is affecting
your decision-making.
You got a problem
with a call I make, question the call.
Don't make it personal.
Are you saying pain
can't affect your mood?
If I'm right about the pain,
you're gonna wanna rush everything,
which is what you're doing.
Don't.
Thank you.
- Are you doing your daughter?
- What?
We should probably talk privately, huh?
Come on, walk with me.
- Come on.
- He's not!
I'm sure he's not.
She is a babe, though.
- We're gonna need you to keep still.
- I am.
What do you think that means?
It's either neurological
or psychological.
The only thing we know for sure is
it's gonna screw up the MRI results,
which is gonna make House
think he's right.
This is a waste of time.
Let's just get the LP.
I should take your head off.
Your glands are fine.
See, now, you're my patient.
You got doctor-patient confidentiality.
No worries.
- So, what did you do to her?
- Why would you possibly think...
Hard to imagine anyone
not wanting to nail her.
- You son of...
- It's a compliment.
That heart-shaped ass, those perfect,
perky, all-natural breasts.
That is my daughter
you're talking about!
No, that's your daughter
you were talking about.
"She just instinctively knows
how to walk."
"Designers just love that heart-shaped
ass, those perfect, perky..."
I'm her manager. I have to promote her.
Oh, that makes sense.
So you compartmentalize.
When you're dealing with the press,
you're her manager.
When you're helping with homework,
you're her dad.
When you're making sweet, sweet love,
you're her manager.
- All right.
- Do you love her?
- I have never touched her.
What are you doing?
Are you trying to trap me into saying...
Do you love her enough
to admit that you slept with her?
Psychological conditions can manifest
themselves in physical problems.
Sometimes these can be
extreme enough to kill.
There are treatments,
but only if there is a diagnosis.
Are you going to admit
that you slept with your daughter
or are you just gonna let her die?
One time.
PTSD.
Get her a psyche referral,
pack her bags. He did her.
- Don't think so.
- Daddy thinks so.
He could be mistaken.
He said he was drunk.
Maybe it was some other daughter.
Elevated proteins in her CSF.
You're wrong about PTSD and I was
wrong about the hypoxic brain injury.
Daddy didn't do this to her.
And neither did we.
We have to call
Child Protective Services.
Doctor-patient confidentiality.
Doesn't apply in abuse cases.
You know that.
We're mandated to report sexual abuse.
Is it okay if I save her life first
or do you want to make sure
that Daddy doesn't get visitation rights
to the gravesite?
Okay, elevated proteins in her CSF
could mean dozens of different things.
- Viral encephalitis, CNSV.
- Creutzfeldt-Jakob disease?
So we're just gonna leave a child
molester in the same room as his victim?
It's got windows.
Fine. Arrest him. Use Cuddy's handcuffs.
If you're too distracted to deal with
this because your leg hurts, then...
Yeah, I'm distracted!
I'm all hung up on this 15-year-old
patient who's cataplectic,
can't remember what she had for lunch
and is rapidly losing control
of her body!
And I want her father here
in case he's got any more secrets
that I need to know about.
Now, if you're not too distracted,
go take out a piece of her brain,
stick it under a microscope.
- Wilson!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Do you really think we need
to jump straight to brain biopsy?
Nope. Let's continue playing.
"Pin the diagnosis on the supermodel"
until she's dead.
- I heard you killed your supermodel.
- Only for a minute.
Just for my own clarity, how many more
patients do you have to kill
before you admit this leg thing
just might be a problem?
Three.
I need your help.
We're gonna do something
called a burr-hole biopsy.
We drill a small opening
in the back of your skull.
Doctor, maybe you and I
should talk about this first.
No.
I just think Alex doesn't need
to be overwhelmed right now.
I think she should have a say
in what happens to her body.
Now, we're gonna remove
a small piece of brain tissue.
Do you have to shave my hair?
Hair grows back.
I guess I won't remember anyways.
There's a good chance
the amnesia is only temporary.
Okay.
Find a way to kick up the contribution.
What did House do now?
House, this is God.
Look, I'm a little busy right now.
I'm not supposed
to talk during these things.
Got time Thursday?
Let me check. Oh, I've got a plague.
What about Friday?
You'll have to check with Cameron.
Oh, damn it!
She always wants to know
why bad things happen.
Like I'm gonna come up
with a new answer this time.
House.
Quick, God, smite the evil witch!
Are you sitting on evidence
that your patient
was sexually abused by her father?
God, why have you forsaken me?
Don't worry.
I've contacted child services for you.
I let you get away
with more than anyone in this hospital.
Shielding a child abuser isn't covered.
Cooperate with this investigation
or I'll fire you.
What do you think House
is gonna do to you?
No idea.
Well, you did the right thing.
If you hadn't gone to Cuddy,
I would have.
If this guy had known
we'd have to report him,
he'd never have told House the truth.
She's a child,
she needs to be protected.
She dropped out of high school
to make millions of dollars.
Why does she need more protection
than some crack whore
shivering in the clinic waiting room?
I think you're just afraid
to piss House off.
There's that, too.
MRI looks exactly the same
as it did two years ago.
The nerves don't seem
to be regenerating.
I figured as much.
Several different researchers
have proven
psychological pain
can manifest as physical pain.
You think I have a conversion disorder?
You want me to see a shrink?
Brilliant idea sending Stacy away.
It's really done wonders for you.
Listen, none of this
has anything to do with Stacy.
Right. Giant coincidence
that you've gone completely
off the rails since she left.
Inducing migraines, worsening leg pains.
Oh, do you miss Stacy, too?
Brain biopsy shows
no white matter disease.
Cameron, you gonna tell Cuddy, or has
she already got you wired for sound?
I had to do what I thought was right.
So, white is out. It just leaves gray.
Neuronal ceroid lipofucinosis,
Heller Syndrome...
Any one of the mitochondrial
encephalopathies.
Am I in trouble?
You had to do
what you thought was right.
They call it "gray area" because
you never really know what's there.
We can't test for any of those things.
So I'm not in trouble?
You can torture yourself all you want.
What if everything
we're seeing is just smoke signals?
- Okay. Who's sending them?
- Tumor.
If she has cancer anywhere in her body,
she could also have
Paraneoplastic Syndrome,
which could be causing antibodies
to attack her brain.
Antibodies are stupid that way.
Paraneoplastic Syndrome's
awfully rare in a 15-year-old.
15-year-olds who look like
that are awfully rare.
It would explain the aggressive
behavior, the cataplexy,
the memory loss, even the twitching.
It's perfect.
What if it's not?
We could waste a week
searching for a tumor
that we don't even know is there.
Then let's make sure it is there.
There's no test
for Paraneoplastic Syndrome.
Sure there is.
The "squeeze the tube" test.
- What did the biopsy tell you?
- It wasn't definitive.
But the twitching should stop
right about now.
Oh, my God.
Could have just been
a coincidence.
Twitching does tend to stop and start.
Let's be sure.
The MG vacuums her blood, neutralizes
the stuff that's making her twitch.
It's actually kind of cool.
- I wonder if I could make you dance.
- Enough.
This is unbelievable.
You did it. You fixed her.
No.
All I did was prove that she has cancer.
I need a favor.
I'm not in a giving mood.
It'll help us both.
I need a shot of morphine in my spine.
If your leg hurts, take your Vicodin.
It's not enough.
Get a syringe.
Morphine is extreme, even for you.
- Yeah. Write that on the insert.
- Get one of your lackeys to do it.
I don't want them knowing...
That you're on the road
to becoming a junkie?
That I'm in this much pain.
I don't want them
questioning my judgment.
I can't ask Wilson, because he figures
it's all in my head.
Well, I agree with him. I'm going home.
- What about this?
- What are you doing?
Is this in my head?
Because I could swear
I remember a thigh muscle being here.
I'll get a syringe.
- It's gotta be cancer.
- It's not cancer.
You seem to be
back to your old miserable self.
So I just randomly predicted
she'd respond to MG?
Her twitches are gone,
her memory's getting better.
What did you take?
The increased pain was psychological.
No drug's gonna help.
If you think it will help, the drugs
will help. The power of the mind.
You're right.
The more I talk to you,
the more the pain floods back.
I knew the twins were real.
Chase owes me.
- Did you check the pancreas?
- Oh, come on.
You're just making up organs now,
aren't you?
We checked the pancreas.
- Obviously, you've taken something.
- Did you check the bones?
- There are a lot of bones, I think.
- And none of them have cancer.
- Ovaries?
- There's no mass.
If anything, they're undersized.
No leukemia, no Hodgkin's,
we checked everything.
Unless they've invented a new organ,
it's not cancer.
- Differential diagnosis.
- It's gotta be cancer.
There's gotta be something we missed.
You've got to learn to let go, Foreman.
Maybe the protein level
was some sort of anomaly.
It might just still be PTSD.
Just PTSD?
Yeah, Daddy's diddling her.
Nothing to worry about.
Okay, let me rephrase.
Maybe the protein level
was some sort of anomaly.
Oh, my God! It might be PTSD!
If it was PTSD, the twitching
wouldn't have magically disappeared
when we started the MG.
Wrong.
What it wouldn't have done
was medically disappear.
Nothing to stop it
from magically disappearing.
She was watching me
start and stop the medicine.
You think she's faking?
Not consciously.
But if her subconscious
is trying to get away from it all,
cancer's gotta be
a lovely vacation spot.
Tell her you've got to give her
a fresh IV.
Don't tell her
you're starting her on saline.
See if the twitching comes back.
How long has the social worker
been in there?
Just went in.
She was in with the dad before.
- You switched the girl's IV?
- About a half an hour ago.
When's she gonna start twitching?
If she's gonna start twitching.
Another few minutes.
We've got to wait for the remaining MG
to clear her system.
That was quick. What's gonna happen?
What'd you think was gonna happen?
- The father had sex...
- Do you have any medical evidence?
- He admitted...
- He denies the conversation took place.
- But she...
- She denies it, too.
I'm sure you meant well.
You have to tell her the truth.
Nothing happened.
You don't have to be afraid of him.
They can protect you.
From what? Things are fine.
You think things are fine. They're not.
- He's my dad.
- He's abusing you.
He's not a bad person.
I seduced him.
You're the child. He's the adult.
- He has the responsibility...
- I got him drunk.
I had to get him drunk.
I wanted to have sex with him.
You're sexually attracted
to your father?
No. But by sleeping with him,
now he lets me do whatever I want.
I also slept with my photographer,
my financial manager and my tutor.
If I hadn't, I'd be getting Cs
and posing for newspaper ads
back in Detroit.
- Come on, we all do it.
- No, we don't.
After your father slept with you,
you were traumatized.
My dad was last.
You've never taken a run
at your boss or professor
or somebody else you needed?
You're 15. You're smart.
- You don't have...
- I am not that smart.
I am that beautiful.
What's wrong with me?
Oh! George, get your butt over here!
- Help me.
- How'd you get my pager number?
Please!
The problem is,
if I give you an epidural,
you won't be able to feel when to push.
- You're not funny.
- I'm pretty sure I am.
You just can't appreciate it
because you're in pain.
George, if you don't get off your ass
and help me...
Oh, shut up!
You've got yourself the perfect man.
A woman.
He's got more estrogen
coursing through his veins than...
- Who did her vaginal exam?
- I did.
- Did she have hair?
- What are you getting at?
Right now I'm getting at whether or not
she had hair down there.
Not much.
She's manipulative,
yet completely docile.
Everybody tells us that outburst
on the catwalk was out of character.
- She's never had a period.
- You're thinking this is hormonal?
I'm thinking she's the ultimate woman.
I need to schedule an MRI.
The twitching stopped.
Because we changed your medicine
back to the real stuff.
Stop talking.
You gave me fake medicine?
That's what I said,
in the vain hope that you wouldn't feel
the need to also say it.
Stop talking.
Wilson already did an ultrasound.
He said her ovaries were undersized.
The ultrasound would be the way to go
if you were looking for ovarian cancer.
What are we looking for?
That.
Oh, my God.
It looks like a tumor, doesn't it?
- But those are...
- Yep.
We found a tumor.
She has cancer?
- Technically, no.
- So it's not cancer?
No, it's cancer, but "he" has cancer
on "his" left testicle.
- I don't have testicles.
- She's not a guy.
His DNA says you're wrong.
Frogs and snails and puppy dog tails.
You've got male
pseudohermaphroditism.
You see, we all start out as girls
and then we're differentiated,
based on our genes.
The ovaries develop
into testes and drop.
But in about one
in every 150,000 pregnancies,
the fetus with an XY chromosome
a boy, develops into something else,
like you.
Your testes never descended,
because you're immune to testosterone.
You're pure estrogen.
Which is why you have heightened
female characteristics,
clear skin, great breasts.
The ultimate woman is a man.
Nature's cruel, huh?
This is obviously a joke.
This is impossible.
No. A joke would be
me calling you a homo.
You see the difference?
I'll schedule him for surgery.
No! You're wrong!
I'm a girl! Look at me!
How could you say I'm not a girl?
You see, they're all looking at me.
I'm beautiful!
That anger.
It's just the cancer talking.
Put your clothes back on.
We're gonna cut your balls off.
Then you'll be fine.
- How's the patient?
- Post-op.
They sent him/her up for a psyche visit.
Calling her a "him/her"
isn't really helping.
The good news is, I don't think Dad's
gonna be sleeping with him/her again.
You see, now it's gross.
I need another shot.
When did the pain start coming back?
A few hours ago.
About an hour after you solved the case?
If I wanted to be psychoanalyzed,
I'd get Wilson to give me the shot.
Same dosage?
If you'd be more comfortable,
I might be able to deal
with a few less CCs of morphine.
It wasn't morphine.
What did you give me?
I told you I wanted...
It was saline.
I gave you a placebo.