Hi, kids.
Mommy, look what I made.
Oh, wow.
It's a farmer and a cow
and some horses.
It's beautiful.
It's for Ted's office.
Oh, he's gonna love it. And it'd
be nice if you called him Dad.
Give me a big hug.
Secret is the Haas avocados. I can
e-mail you the recipe if you want.
It's the third time they've
changed plans since Friday.
These idiots think you can just add a
14th floor and the mayor won't notice.
And I thought turning the garage
into a nursery was complicated.
Any luck on your end yet?
Not for lack of trying.
Ted.
Come on. Come on, Margo!
I have to go tell a client
he's an idiot.
Go kick some ass.
I have to take Stella to karate by 3:00
and a birthday party at Julia's after.
You okay?
Yeah. I'll be back.
Just make sure she's dressed.
Honey! Honey!
He's actually on time.
He's six minutes early.
- Something's happened.
- I'm on it.
Good morning, Jimmy.
Anybody die while I was gone?
Did you iron your shirt?
I thought about shaving.
Couldn't find a razor.
What the hell happened
in Baltimore?
Sorry, chief.
Never kiss and tell.
I think you just did.
There's no such thing
as "just a kiss".
Did you iron your shirt?
Everybody's flash today.
Has she left Mark?
Is she going to?
I think I can hear
cancer kids calling.
Are you planning on asking her
to leave Mark?
Not sure.
Cameron keeps my calendar.
Hey. This is a big deal.
This is an affair.
Have you even talked to Stacy
about what the hell this means?
Didn't have a lot of time for talking,
if you know what I mean.
Great. Breaking up a marriage.
Fertile ground for high comedy.
We need to talk about this.
Gosh, wish I could. How did
the HIV test go? You study up?
I rescheduled for this afternoon.
We have a new patient.
Thirty-four-year-old female,
movement disorder.
Movement disorder? Fascinating.
This isn't just gonna go away.
No. But maybe you will.
Probably suffered head trauma
in the car accident.
Trauma leads to the dyskinesia.
According to her husband,
the flailing started
before she got anywhere near that car.
What does
the flailing look like?
Her arms spasm uncontrollably
and there's a mild facial twitch.
Demonstration?
You wanna know what it looks
like, go see the patient.
Oh, snarky. Was he like this
the whole time I was gone?
The patient's been on a fertility
regimen for the last 13 months.
Excess estrogen
in the system could explain...
Who finished
the animal crackers?
Sudden movement disorder could
be a symptom of Huntington's.
If you finish something, don't just
put back the empty box, throw it out.
Huntington's
takes a day to confirm.
We should put her on tamoxifen in
case it is the fertility meds,
counteract the estrogen.
That's a great idea
if you wanna kill her baby.
Movement disorder can present
in the first trimester.
She's not pregnant.
Peeing on a stick is only 99% accurate.
Get a real pregnancy test.
You know, the one with the blood
and the hormones and the rabbit.
Oh, I'm sorry,
it's still your limo.
What do you say, Miss Daisy?
Whatever you want.
Lame duck's done quacking.
You quack, people shoot at you.
Cuddy just put me here
to make you miserable.
Another two days, you can go back
to making yourself miserable.
Okay, get an MRI. See if it's
in her head or in her uterus.
You're gonna want
to paralyze her.
You run tests on a flailer,
somebody's gonna lose an eye.
Sorry. You think I'm pregnant?
We need to find out for sure.
Would all this go away
once she delivered?
It could also be neurological.
We need to get an MRI.
Can she do that
if she's pregnant?
The risk to the fetus
is extremely low.
But there is a risk.
I don't think we should do it
until we're sure.
Ted, I think
you should take Stella home.
I wanna stay here.
We should be with you.
You should take her
out of the room.
We're gonna temporarily stop
Margo's spasms.
- You can do that?
- Vecuronium.
It's a paralytic. Essentially cuts
off the brain from the muscles.
Don't worry.
Your mom will be just fine.
It'll make
running the tests easier,
and it won't be dangerous for
the baby if you are pregnant.
Let's go, Stella.
I want to go with Mommy.
We'll be just outside, okay? We gotta
let the doctors get her better.
- All right?
- It's okay, sweetie.
- Love you.
Your vitals
will be watched closely.
I'm gonna close your lids
so your eyes don't dry out.
Just try to relax.
What the hell did you do?
Were you just cold and lonely?
Of course he told you.
He's an eight-year-old boy.
Hey, you're the one
who kissed him.
Why are you so worked up
over this?
- Because you're married.
- Not to you.
This is none of your business.
The last time you left, I was the
one stuck picking up the pieces.
Oh, right. He cried himself
to sleep every night.
That so sounds like him.
He's been pining
for five years.
You're being dramatic.
No. Actually, I'm underplaying.
This is me being restrained.
- It was one kiss.
- Are you being intentionally thick?
This was not
just a one-night stand.
You can't toy with him.
I'm not.
He's probably toying with me.
I don't know what I'm doing.
Oh, boy.
Welcome back to the world.
You're off the vecuronium.
Could you wiggle your toes
for me?
The MRI was clear. Whatever
this is, isn't in your brain.
MRI. So I'm not pregnant?
I'm sorry.
So what do we do next?
Well, it could be a variety of things,
some treatable, others more serious.
Open up.
I'm gonna run a genetic test
for Huntington's.
- That one of the more serious ones?
- Yeah.
It's also possible that this is just a
symptom of the fertility treatments.
And now that we know you're not pregnant,
we're gonna start you on tamoxifen
to counteract the estrogen.
Will that undo
all the fertility treatments?
For the time being, yeah.
But it could cure you.
You can start trying again
once we get you healthy.
Damn it!
The spasms are gonna get worse now
that the vecuronium is wearing off.
What are you so scared of?
I'm still your mother.
I'm just a little sick.
Why did you even bring her here?
I told you to leave her at home.
Hypervigilance,
sudden irritability.
Symptomatic
of lunch with Cuddy?
The patient
now defines Huntington's.
Then what do you need me for?
Start her on Huntington's meds.
Before we get
her test results back?
We start her on valproic acid,
it could destroy her liver.
- Could stroke.
- If we wait,
she could progress
to full-blown psychosis,
and then her kid will never get
the chance to say goodbye.
Wanna tell the class
how that feels?
Huntington's patients don't
progress to psychosis in a day.
She went from zero to 60
in world record time.
Indicating it might be something
other than Huntington's.
We got a problem.
Stay away from me!
Where's my daughter?
- What's happening?
- She's having a psychotic break.
No! She is not yours!
What do you want with her?
- Calm down!
- Honey.
Margo,
you're gonna hurt someone.
No.
Push two milligrams of Ativan.
I want my daughter!
She's not yours! I want my daughter!
No more experiments!
No!
How can her Huntington's
test be negative?
All the signs are there.
Movement disorder, psychosis.
It should be Huntington's.
Yeah. It would certainly
make your job easier.
Well, good news for Margo, it's not
Huntington's. Bad news for us,
her psychotic break
eliminates fertility meds.
Which means we have no idea
what's wrong with her.
We give you so much,
and you give us so little.
You know, the patient is prime age to
develop spontaneous schizophrenia.
Almost impossible. No family
history of mental illness.
How about toxins?
None of her family members are sick.
Nobody at her office, her volunteer group,
kid's classes,
and PTA members, all fine.
So she raises a daughter, runs a
business, she does charity work,
she volunteers at school,
attends PTA.
What makes Mommy run?
- You're thinking drugs?
- Cocaine.
Explains the psychosis
and the flailing.
And the uncanny ability to bring
home the bacon, fry it up in a pan,
and never ever let Teddy
forget that he's a man.
- I'll go look for her stash.
- Take Foreman.
There's gotta be a reason
for the stereotype.
I know you're in there.
I can hear you caring.
The door was locked.
It means
I didn't wanna see anyone.
High school reunion?
It's for a patient.
She can't roll.
Hey, I locked that door, too.
Paranoia.
Must be the good stuff.
Times like these,
I wish I had cancer.
So what did she say?
It depends. What did you do,
and who are we talking about?
We both know that as soon as
we talked, you ran to Stacy
so you could gossip and giggle.
I need to know what she said.
I have a crazy idea.
Why don't you go talk to her?
Because my bestest buddy says
that could lead to trouble.
She sounds confused,
but I don't think she is.
I think she's waiting for you to do
something, show her you're serious.
Wow.
It's a big jump from "infidelity
is morally wrong" to "do her".
I didn't say "do her".
I said do something.
What exactly did she say?
She didn't say
it was a mistake.
She's not gonna leave Mark
in the middle of his rehab.
Too much guilt.
She left you.
Harsh toke, dude.
House.
Killjoy.
I could've covered this. You
need to get that test today.
I wish you guys would remember my
birthday instead of my HIV test.
Forgive us for being concerned.
I got a bet with House.
He says you're too scared to get it.
I say you're too anal not to.
I'll cut you in.
That was a colossal waste.
Who would've known?
Searching a high-end
family home for illicit
narcotics was such
an obvious choice.
Working moms practically
live in their cars.
- Little bump on the run.
- You were a car thief, right?
Mama's little helper.
House, Ritalin.
Cocaine with a PG rating.
Prescribed to her daughter.
Mommy does everything for her family
these days, even swallows their pills.
It's possible the kid's meds
are the kid's meds.
Pop enough Ritalin,
it can explain everything.
Well, Ritalin maybe explains
some tics, some involuntary...
No, case reports
have referred to chorea.
She's been cut off from her stash,
so the flailing's tapered off,
the psychosis hasn't returned.
It's perfect.
Tox screen will confirm that.
Half-life's 12 hours. Drugs
will be out of her system.
- We're done. Get rid of her.
- We're not done.
We have to confirm the diagnosis before we
send her home to die of something else.
Oh, yes. The power tastes so sweet.
You just can't resist.
You're like a diabetic
at the ice cream counter.
You wanna say no, but you
need that chocolaty goodness.
Yeah, well,
I'm still signing the charts.
So until tomorrow, you're
not allowed to kill anyone.
Wuss.
We've asked her three times
if she's on any meds.
So we don't ask her.
Candy striper.
So, you like dogs?
That's not a dog.
Smart kid.
Are you always
such a good little girl,
or does Mommy sometimes say you're the
reason she needs a double martini?
Who are you?
Over here, kiddo.
I'm talking to you. Focus.
Must be because
you're off your meds.
Who are you?
- Doctor and candy striper.
- She's not on any medication.
Well, that's strange.
'Cause this bottle has her name on it. And
I think these are medical pills inside.
What's he talking about?
The doctor prescribed Stella...
A few months ago.
I never told you about it,
because I never gave her any.
That's funny, 'cause the
bottle's almost empty.
You missed a couple of days.
Take five.
- Stop.
- Why? Unless they're not hers.
You need some water, sweetie?
I'm not taking Ritalin.
Come on. All the cool moms
are doing it.
And tox screen
says you're cool, too.
You were on drugs
while taking care of Stella?
I'm sorry, Ted.
It's a cafeteria menu.
It should take a couple hours
to process her.
Then you can take her home
and divorce her.
Working late?
Or are you just avoiding Mark?
It was one kiss, Greg.
So far. I'm planning
on keeping a chart.
I'm moving back to Short Hills.
I think it's time.
You're leaving?
It was never meant to be permanent,
and now that Mark's getting better...
Yeah, much better.
Except for the whole
walking thing.
He needs to get back to work.
Right.
Saving the next generation from
making bad choices about acne cream.
You're running away because
the kiss meant something.
I'm not running away.
I'm going home.
With Mark.
I love Mark.
You love me more.
I don't want you to leave.
Are we okay?
I'm sorry.
Let's just get you home.
That's a good idea.
- Mommy!
- Hey!
- Call a code!
- What's wrong, Mommy?
What's going on?
This better be important.
- You've gotta come back in.
- No, I don't.
- Margo's stable, but...
- Oh, my God.
- Well, I'll be right there.
- She had a stroke.
Perfect.
Gotta go back to work.
Right now?
Well...
Patient's stable.
Could maybe wait a half-hour.
He should have been here
20 minutes ago.
Doubt if he makes it at all.
I saw him leave with Stacy.
He was probably
just walking her to her car.
Oh, yeah.
That sounds like House.
He's not an idiot. He's not gonna
hook up with a married woman.
I hope he is getting some.
Maybe he'll mellow out.
- What took you so long? It's midnight.
- Traffic. Cinco de Mayo.
You owe me $100.
You didn't take the test?
Fear trumps anal every time.
It's not a big deal. I had the
viral load and antibody test.
It's 99.9%
that I don't have HIV.
And if you have the test, and it's
negative, you gain a tenth of a point.
But if it's positive you lose
nearly 100, right?
No arrhythmia, so Ritalin
isn't the big problem.
Something else is going on.
Fine, let's play doctors.
I removed the clot
which caused the stroke.
Problem is, we don't
know where it came from.
Did ultrasounds of her heart,
arms and legs. All clear.
Could be
a protein C deficiency.
Wouldn't explain
the movement disorder.
Nothing explains everything.
What if it's a crime syndicate?
Let's say Ritalin and the
fertility meds plotted a caper.
Ritalin takes care of the
psychosis, the flailing.
I still don't think Ritalin...
Fertility meds
are competitive by nature.
They had to do something bigger,
something really unexpected.
Fertility treatments have been
known to cause endometrial cancer.
Which could cause clots, which
could have caused her to stroke.
So ultrasound her uterus
this time.
See if there's something growing in there
that doesn't look adorable in a onesie.
Cameron. I love you.
You'll get your test results
tomorrow.
The prescription
for my heart condition.
A bit on the cheesy side.
I was trying for romantic.
Still fits.
Did you tell Mark?
I told him I had to work late.
You gonna tell him?
How am I gonna tell him?
Still working on that phrasing.
How about,
"You know all the stuff you were worried
about when we first came here, honey?"
"You were right."
Pithy.
Everything's easy when you
don't care if you hurt anyone.
You already
did the hurting part.
- He just doesn't know it yet.
- If I never tell him, it'll never hurt.
I want not to love Mark.
I wanna hate you.
I want all of this to be
simple, but it's not.
You can either
have a life with me,
or you can have
a life with him.
It can't be both.
It's not easy,
but it is simple.
No endometrial thickening.
No masses.
No cancer.
She's on fertility treatments. She
had a blood clot. It's there.
Millions of women are on fertility
treatments and they don't get cancer.
Right. They get babies.
She had a blood clot
and a stroke.
She'll get another one and probably
die, if we don't find that tumor.
Do an endometrial biopsy.
Biopsy's painful and unnecessary.
We just did an ultrasound.
What?
If you have a personal issue
that's interfering with...
What are we waiting for?
Your four weeks just expired.
Your reign of terror is over.
Mine has just begun.
Now go stick a needle up her
hoo-hoo and find that cancer.
"Hoo-hoo"?
He went to Hopkins.
Pergasaurus has got 1,500 horsepower
blown and injected with alcohol.
Yeah, that baby really moves.
Oh, yeah, and the transmission,
two-speed Powerglide. Suspension...
What are you watching?
TV.
What are you doing here?
Ted's with my mom. He asked
the nurse to watch me.
What nurse?
She's not really watching me.
I got that.
Do you still have the balloons?
No.
- Do you wanna play something?
- Nope.
When can Mommy come home?
Don't know.
- What's wrong with your foot?
- War wound.
- Does it hurt?
- Every day.
Is that why you're so sad?
Oh, aren't you adorable?
I'm not sad, I'm complicated.
Chicks dig that.
One day you'll understand.
That's what my parents say when they
don't want me to know something.
They say that a lot?
Only when they're talking
about making babies and stuff.
When you catch them fighting?
- They don't fight.
- Not ever?
People who love each other
don't fight.
Right. Forgot that.
What floor was that nurse on
who was watching you?
Two.
Good talk.
At your age, the type of uterine cancer
that develops is not likely to metastasize.
It's very treatable.
Okay, hold still, Margo.
I'm feeling a little bit dizzy.
Oh, my God.
BP's dropping.
What's going on?
Get him out of here.
Heart rate's 98 and rising.
We've gotta find that bleed.
What'd you do, hit an artery?
With what? I hadn't even
started the procedure.
I need some advice.
- Whatever it is, can it wait?
- Yeah.
What was Greg like
after I left?
An egomaniacal
narcissistic pain in the ass.
Same as before you left.
Do you think he's capable
of having a real relationship?
- What happened in Baltimore?
- Nothing.
- Right.
- Maybe something.
Right.
Technically, most of the something
happened after Baltimore.
Oh, God, Stacy.
I don't know what to do.
Are you seriously thinking
about leaving Mark?
No. I don't know.
I can't.
And you want me
to tell you it's okay?
It wasn't all bad with Greg.
I was with him for a reason.
You left him for a reason.
I could swear
I remember him being fun.
Sorry for the scare.
Just tell me she's okay.
Ultrasound showed the bleed
was coming from her liver.
It's rare, but the blood
got into her fallopian tubes.
In a way, it was lucky. Let us know
we were looking in the wrong place.
The tumor's in her liver.
Is it cancer?
We're running some more tests.
There it is.
It's a liver tumor.
Well, if it's malignant,
at least she's only
gonna leave one child
without a mother.
Do a biopsy.
We can't. It's vascular.
House.
- What?
- I'm here about Stacy.
What about her?
I think I'm losing her.
Your wife, your problem.
She won't talk to me.
So what? You gonna talk to me instead?
Talk to your shrink.
She keeps saying
everything's fine.
Find a bar. Talk to a stranger.
You're the only one
who's been through this.
I'm shutting her out.
I'm saying things and then
hating myself for saying them.
- How did you get past that?
- Didn't.
Can you please be a human being
for one minute and talk to me?
Sorry. Gotta go. People dying.
You're not gonna outrun me.
House!
You're not ready for this.
I've seen the way you and
Stacy talk to each other.
You're an idiot.
You probably just set your
rehab back three months.
Let go. Get off of me!
Liver tumor doesn't make sense.
You saying the CT was wrong?
I'm saying the symptoms don't add up.
A plus B does not equal liver tumor.
We gotta solve for X.
We gotta look at this
differently.
What do we know about her?
The side effects
of the Ritalin caused the...
No. We've examined the file up and down.
Come on, give me that.
Why do you people always
overlook the human element?
What do we know about her?
Margo...
Dalton. The woman.
She's a people-pleaser. She
doesn't like to let people down.
Never fights with her husband.
She turned to drugs instead of
asking for help to manage her life.
So if she can't manage now,
why does she want another kid?
Foreman, I need your help here.
You wanna pull a bank job,
would you go it alone?
If you gonna rob a home, sure,
that's a one or two man crew.
But a bank, you need a
lookout, a getaway driver.
I'm not saying anything until
the metaphor plays itself out.
So here's the caper.
Fertility meds
create a distraction.
Mommy had three refills on
Ritalin in the last three weeks.
That team goes straight
for the top floor.
No trouble taking out communications, but
they need the specialist, a safecracker.
All he does is stroke,
blood clot, liver tumor.
Foreman was right. This
badass even does flailing.
Come on.
There's only one guy I know
who does that kind of work.
Birth control pills?
While the surgeons are cutting
out a chunk of your liver,
should I have them do
a hysterectomy, too?
A hysterectomy?
I'm trying to get pregnant.
You don't have to lie to me.
We're not married.
You're Supermom.
You can do anything.
You work seven days a week, you
volunteer, you raise a kid.
Yet you still somehow find the
time to lie to hubby number two
that you really, really wanna give him a
child with his chin and pretty brown eyes.
What makes you think
that I would...
Because it fits.
Birth control pills caused
a hepatocellular adenoma.
Explains all your symptoms that
aren't explained by your other lies.
That's it?
Also...
I'll have the tuna on rye.
Would you like
to leave my room now?
Your tumor is benign.
Stop taking the pill, and
it will go away on its own.
I'm canceling the surgery.
What are you
gonna tell my husband?
That I'm canceling the surgery.
You can do the explaining.
It's tricky, huh?
It's one thing to say
you can't have a baby.
It's another to say
you don't want one.
Personally, I'd make up
some other lie.
Could...
Could I die on the table?
Could you die
if you tell him the truth?
I need this surgery.
I'm not on the pill.
You can't cancel the surgery.
If she goes off the pill, the
tumor goes away on its own.
You have no proof the birth
control pills caused this.
You have no proof
she's even taking them.
If we do the surgery maybe
we'll kill her on the table.
Then I can prove
I'm right at the autopsy.
Or we can forget the surgery, let
the tumor grow, and kill her.
Why don't you take it up with Stacy,
see which option minimizes your risk?
Here's what I think she's
gonna say, "Oh, I love Greg."
But if you go against the patient's
wishes, you're calling her a liar.
And if something goes wrong,
I end up in court
having to defend the big mean
doctor, albeit with dreamy eyes,
who wouldn't believe
the nice suburban mom.
"And even though his cane makes
me melt, do the damn surgery."
Shocking.
It's benign.
People do
crazy things for love.
No, crazy is hanging out in the
park all day talking to pigeons.
Margo knows what she's doing.
She gave up half her liver
to save her marriage.
No, she surgically removed her
fingerprints to cover her pathetic lie.
It's twisted and manipulative.
I get that. But it's also
romantic.
I'm barely willing to put
the seat down after I pee.
Do we need to talk?
Nope. I'm fine.
So the surgeon got the whole
tumor, and it was benign.
That's good, right?
Yeah, benign is good.
How could a benign tumor
have caused all the symptoms?
We believe all your wife's
symptoms will go away now.
Oh, thank God.
Look, I'm gonna pick up Stella.
I'll call you
after I get the babysitter.
Dr. Foreman,
you can help me.
You could tell my husband that
because of all this,
I can't take
any more fertility treatments.
Confidentiality rules stop me from
telling your husband the truth.
But my obligation to lie
ends there.
Are there...
Is there a birth control method,
something that won't make me sick?
Margo, you're gonna have
risks with everything,
especially if you're not
telling your fertility doctor.
If you keep doing this, it's gonna
kill your marriage and kill you.
You don't know.
In a few years,
we'll give up.
Stop trying to get pregnant.
We'll hug, cry.
Eventually Ted will stop thinking about it,
and he'll appreciate Stella even more.
And we'll live happily together
for the next 50 years.
Something you need to see.
Knowing is always better
than not knowing.
It's a referral request.
Right.
The HIV thing came in earlier.
You're fine.
You won't read your mail,
but you'll open mine?
It said "confidential",
and I wanted to know.
The most important letter of my
life, and you're still an ass.
Comforting, isn't it?
Hey.
Hi.
I'm gonna talk to Mark tonight,
and I'm gonna stay here with you.
Don't do it.
This isn't funny, Greg.
I know.
You
spent all these months
chasing me.
Now I'm here and you start running?
What the hell changed?
Nothing.
Nothing changes.
- I'm not gonna change.
- Who asked you to?
Mark is willing to do
whatever it takes.
I'm not.
Never was.
Now you're introspective? Weren't
so analytical the other night.
You were happy with Mark.
You'll be happy again.
Shut up about Mark. What the
hell is wrong with you?
- I can't make you happy!
- What?
How do you think
this is gonna end?
We'll be happy, for what?
A few weeks? A few months?
And then I'll...
I'll say something insensitive
or I'll
start ignoring you.
And at first it'll be okay.
It's just House being House.
And then,
at some point,
you will need something more.
You'll need someone who can
give you something I can't.
You know I'm right.
I've been there before.
Oh.
It doesn't have to be.
It does.
I don't wanna go there again.
I'm sorry, Stacy.
$50 says they're
divorced in a year.
Six months, tops.
I'll take that bet.
It's the perfect marriage.
There's nothing to fight over if
you never talk about anything.
What did you tell her?
I told her
she's better off without me.
That's probably true.
You're an idiot.
You don't think she'd be
better off without you.
Right.
I sent her off on a whim.
You have no idea
why you sent her off!
- Don't do this.
- This was no great sacrifice!
You sent her away because
you've got to be miserable!
This kind of psycho-crap help get your
patients through the long nights?
Or is it just for you?
Tough love make you feel good?
Helping people feel their pain?
You don't like yourself.
But you do admire yourself.
It's all you've got,
so you cling to it.
You're so afraid if you change,
you'll lose what makes you special.
Being miserable doesn't make you
better than anybody else, House.
It just makes you miserable.