Your weight is 113.9 pounds.
You gonna make me hurt you?
- No.
- I didn't think so.
Are you alright? Did I hurt you?
Bob!
Bob! What's wrong?
What happened? Talk to me.
Oh, my God! OK, honey,
hang on, hang on.
911, what is your emergency?
Yes, we need an ambulance
at 10600 Xavier, unit 4-B.
My husband can't breathe.
Oh, my God, he's turning blue.
You have to send someone now, please!
Hurry!
You blow-dry your hair?
Oh, sorry. Did I wake you up?
Excuse me for actually caring
what I look like.
I think the word you're looking for
is "obsessing."
You've been at it for almost an hour.
If you wanted in,
all you had to do was say so.
I don't want in. I want sleep!
It's about time you got up anyway.
It's almost 9:00.
This isn't gonna work.
- What?
- You staying here.
You're kicking me out? After one night?
Why, you think we should
try counseling first?
Why do you want to sleep
on a couch anyway?
You got money. At least
until the divorce is finalized.
I'll be out of your hair tomorrow.
What's left of it.
It was three days ago.
My throat got really dry
and then my tongue
felt like it was blowing up
like a balloon.
I assume somebody
checked for food allergies.
- The first two doctors both did.
- Next one said it was a panic attack.
The one after that wanted
to take his tonsils out.
The last one had no idea,
just referred us to Dr. House.
It says the attack was preceded
by some sort of
strenuous physical activity.
- Yeah.
- What were you doing?
Awesome.
A sex fiend with a swollen tongue.
Just think of all the places
I can make Foreman search.
He's not a sex fiend.
He's a happily married man.
No such thing.
What are you doing?
Testing a new caffeine delivery system.
He didn't get his beauty sleep.
Wilson's moved in and apparently
has unusually loud toenails.
If they're into rape fantasies,
S&M is on the menu as well.
Neck trauma could cause vocal cord
paroxysms, which could cause choking.
I didn't see any sign of
trauma, and they were remarkably open.
I asked about STDs
and they admitted participating
in a threesome a few months ago.
A hundred bucks says they're
as miserable as the next couple.
Another guy, or girl?
Girl. His wife's college roommate.
If he's not happily married,
I don't know who could be.
They're looking for something. If you're
happy, you've got nothing to look for.
His wife arranged it
for an anniversary present.
If you ask me, if two people
really trust each other,
a threesome once every seven years
might actually help a marriage.
OK, I say we stop the DDX
and discuss that comment.
I'll take the bet.
Maybe the first doctor was right.
Food allergy explains the anaphylaxis.
Could be neurological.
Progressive bulbar paralysis
would explain the symptoms.
No. ALS would affect his facial muscles
before his throat.
What if the problem's not in his throat?
That would be a little odd considering
that's where all his symptoms are.
- Says who?
- The patient.
And since most patients can't tell
their ulna from their anus,
I'm guessing this guy also doesn't know
the difference
between choking and suffocating.
His throat might be fine,
his lungs might be messed up.
Get more blood, a chest CT
and a body plethysmograph.
Unless, of course, you think
we should be asking the patient
where his anus is first.
It feels like I have to urinate
and then when I try to go...
Pull up your pants.
- It's my prostate, isn't it?
- Nope, not your prostate.
- Herpes.
- Herpes?
Herpes. Your turn.
If it makes you feel any better, half
the patients who come into this place
- have some sort of crotch rot.
- No, it doesn't.
Look, this is impossible.
I've been married for 20 years.
Have you had any sex in those 20 years?
- Yes, of course.
- Then that's how you got it.
The only person I've had sex with
is my wife.
Bummer.
Take this once a day.
Tell your wife to do the same.
It's not going to cure it,
but it will lessen the frequency
of the outbreaks.
But there must be some mistake.
You got any kids?
- Yeah.
- Any of them take guitar lessons?
- No.
- Tennis? Art? Acting?
My daughter does karate. Why?
Give this to her sensei.
- Oh, wait. Does your wife play tennis?
- No.
That's what I figured.
Never hurts to make sure.
For Miyagi.
I'm gonna close the shutter now.
I need you to pant, kind of like a dog.
That's good. Keep going.
Can I ask you a personal question?
Uh, I guess.
The threesome and the role-playing.
Is that because things get boring?
No.
We just enjoy our fantasies.
- Are you married?
- No.
You can go back to taking
the deep breaths now.
Marriages don't fail
because couples get bored.
They fail because while they're dating,
people pretend to be the person
they think their partner wants,
and then...
Well, there's only so long
you can keep that up.
Maybe they are that person while
they're dating, but then they change.
People thinking
their partner will change?
That's another reason marriages fail.
People don't change, at least
not in any way that really matters.
I think you've had enough caffeine.
You were right.
It's not his throat, it's his lungs.
The plethysmograph revealed
decreased lung capacity.
And the CT showed lung
scarring.
It's definitely interstitial
pulmonary fibrosis.
What's not definite is the cause.
There's no arthritis, no sarcoidosis.
He's not on any prescription meds.
And he's a wedding photographer.
So I doubt he got exposed to coal dust
or asbestos at work.
- Cause could be idiopathic.
- Can't be idiopathic.
Idiopathic means without a known cause.
What I meant was that...
What you meant was
you don't know what the cause is.
Just say that and we can avoid
this conversation.
No applause?
- What's his current condition?
- Stable.
- Well, then we can wait.
- Wait for what?
For whatever you can't figure out
to cause something else.
You know it's going to.
It's possible the IPF
could just continue to...
- There's something wrong with his skin.
- Do something.
- Stop scratching. Let me look at it.
- I can't. This is driving me crazy.
Stop scratching, so we can...
Make it stop!
- OK...
- Make it stop!
Make it stop!
Now we've got
something to discuss.
What causes both lung scarring
and the itchy, splotchy red blotchies?
It's obviously not a reaction
to medication.
We haven't given him any yet.
Right. But what besides
what it's obviously not,
can cause both lung scarring
and the splotches?
Where are you going?
To complete the second half
of the caffeine delivery system.
Either talk louder, or get in here.
Same color coming out as going in.
Do you think that's a marketing thing?
A lupus could cause lung scarring
and a rash.
Or could still be a food allergy.
- We've already ruled out allergies.
- Did we?
Where's Cameron?
We're in the men's room.
We need an allergy expert in here.
- This can wait two minutes.
- You don't know that.
Chase thinks that food allergy
should still be on the table.
No, it wouldn't explain
the lung scarring.
Some homeopathic studies
have found a connection
between food allergies
and autoimmune reactions,
which could cause lung inflammation.
Yeah. And some homeopathic studies
have also found
that ground-up spiders can cure cancer.
Can I go now?
No.
Lungs, skin, skin, lungs.
Sklungs?
Lungs, skin...
throat.
Heavy metal toxicity.
It explains the lungs, the itching,
the swelling in his tongue and throat.
I thought you didn't believe there was
anything wrong with his throat.
I never said I didn't believe it. I just
said I had good reason to doubt it.
And now?
I have good reason
to doubt those doubts.
The patient's a little old
to be chewing paint off the walls.
Nor does he drink well water,
eat fish every day,
or do anything else that could have
exposed him to heavy metals.
He and his wife worked a wedding
at Cabo San Lucas last month.
A lot of pottery in Mexico
is contaminated with lead-based paint.
Now aren't you glad you joined us?
Search their house, screen his blood
and hair for lead.
Test for mercury and arsenic
while you're at it.
And, Chase, find out
what the resort cooks with,
if they repainted recently
or did any plumbing repairs.
- But I don't speak Spanish.
- Then it'll be challenging.
Good Lord, what is that smell?
Stuffed pepper.
Stuffed with what? Vomit?
I thought you were going to a hotel.
I found an apartment.
I can move in on Monday.
- Is that fast enough for you?
- What's today?
- Where'd you get all that stuff?
- Not from your kitchen.
Don't you ever eat anything
besides canned soup and peanut butter?
that doesn't look like
it's been rolled onto your plate
by a dung beetle?
Try it.
- It's good, isn't it?
- No.
Just better than it looks.
How much beans and rice
do you think you'd have to eat
from a ceramic pot
painted with lead-based paint
to get enough lead into your system
to damage your lungs?
- Are we talking a child, or an adult?
- Adult.
Then I would say a lot.
You'd have to eat beans
every day for months.
Now, why do you have a season pass
to the New Yankee workshop?
It's a complete moron
working with power tools.
How much more suspenseful
can you get?
I'm... I was watching something.
No, you were about to watch something.
I'm watching something.
See the difference?
If the water was contaminated,
wouldn't I be sick, too?
People can metabolize toxins
at different rates.
We'll test it to be sure.
- Have you done any recent renovations?
- No.
Have any problem with bugs or rodents?
Just the occasional ant.
Use bug spray?
No, I hate the smell.
Luckily both of us are pretty anal
about keeping things clean.
Yeah, I can tell.
You think ants are the problem?
Can you stop stuffing your mouth
with pancakes for one second?
These aren't pancakes.
These are macadamia nut pancakes.
Wilson made them and they're amazing.
She says she doesn't use bug spray.
Like little silver dollar
slices of heaven.
- Some ants are poisonous, maybe...
- Forget the 72 virgins.
If I blow myself up
in a crowded restaurant,
I'm going to be asking
for a plate of these babies.
Was the ant big and red
or small and black?
- Medium and brown.
- Halle Berry brown or Beyoncé brown?
Is there a difference?
Army ants could devour, dissolve
and eat a cow in a matter of hours.
Australian Bull ants, on the other hand,
nasty little bastards,
but more of a nuisance than a threat.
- No surprise there.
- Beyoncé.
Well, then that's not it.
How much clay did he eat at the resort?
It's a five-star, $400 a night place.
They don't cook with ceramic pots.
Tox screen?
No evidence of lead, mercury or arsenic.
Run them again. Call the resort, find
some disgruntled employee to talk to.
- Go back to the home...
- It's not heavy metals.
- The symptoms say it is.
- The tests say it's not.
Who you going to believe?
The symptoms or the test?
- It could also be a food allergy.
- Cameron says it's not.
If your test could be wrong,
why can't hers?
His diet hasn't changed since he was
a kid. His favorite food is cornflakes.
Which, I assume, he eats with milk,
one of the most common
adult onset food allergies.
Start treating him for lead poisoning.
It's the most likely heavy metal.
And, yeah, you can test him for
allergies for dairy, wheat and legume.
I am not having an affair
with my daughter's karate instructor
- and I did not give my husband herpes.
- Find out where House is.
If you're convinced it's allergies,
why are you giving him drugs
to treat lead poisoning?
We're not convinced of anything yet.
I think I need something else,
this cream isn't working.
We're doing everything we can.
Sorry.
No, no. It's not my back, it's my feet!
I think I stepped in something
when I went to the bathroom.
Oh, it's on my socks. It's burning.
I don't see anything.
Please, take my socks off!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
- Ow! Stop! Stop! Stop!
- What did you just scratch him with?
If there was an allergic reaction, it
would be on his back, not on his feet.
Oh, it's burning,
please make it stop!
We need some gabapentin in here.
Excruciating pain
in the lower extremities.
- Not a sign of a food allergy.
- Means there's a neurological problem.
More significantly, it's yet another
classic sign of heavy metals.
And I just did yet another
hair and blood test for lead,
and everything else he could
have possibly been exposed to.
They're all negative.
It's gotta be something else.
- Lupus could cause...
- No.
Lupus progresses slower.
There'd be joint pain.
So it's not a typical case.
- We should get an ANA.
- It's not lupus.
The symptoms don't match.
And the tests don't match heavy metals.
It's happening again.
He's not breathing.
Tongue swelling, airway's closing.
He's not getting any air.
- His lungs are clear.
- We're gonna have to intubate.
Try to relax, Bob.
This is gonna help you breathe.
Oh, my God!
He's gonna aspirate! Need suction!
- What's happening?
- Suction.
There's too much vomit. We're never
going to be able to intubate.
- We're gonna have to trach him.
- He's not breathing!
His urine has elevated
proteins and red blood cells.
It's lupus-induced kidney failure.
If we don't start treatment...
Heavy metal toxicity
could cause vomiting.
So would lupus nephritis,
and it also causes tissue swelling.
He's choking on his tongue,
not his feet.
The corticosteroids we gave him
to control the inflammation
can cause facial swelling.
Still not his throat,
but you're getting closer.
I'm doing an ANA and a serum
compliment.
If you're so sure, why waste time
with tests? Just start treatment.
Oh, no wait. We can't do that
because we already have
and it's not working! Ergo...
Corticosteroids aren't the only
treatment for lupus nephritis.
We could also try cyclophosphamide
or immunosuppressants.
Only if we confirm the diagnosis
with an ANA serum compliment,
anti-DNA, IV pyelogram
and kidney biopsy.
- So, now you suddenly believe in tests?
- The symptoms...
The symptoms all point
to heavy metal poisoning.
Yeah, we all get it.
Unless you've got proof,
and can tell me which heavy metal it is,
I'm starting treatment for lupus.
Systemic lupus erythematosus
causes the immune system
to become hyperactive.
Attack normal tissue.
It could be what caused
the lung inflammation,
as well as the swelling in his throat.
And now what appears to be
damage to his kidneys.
The treatment's usually steroids.
But he's already on the steroids.
If the tests confirm
we're on the right track,
there are other medications we can try.
And if those don't work?
Well, lupus, it's a chronic condition,
but it's generally controllable.
What do you mean, "generally"?
In rare cases, it can cause
cardiovascular or renal failure.
Cardiovascular and renal.
That's the heart and the kidneys.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Don't worry, it'll be all right.
Enjoying the salad?
- There's no lettuce.
- I'm aware that there's no lettuce.
But do you know
when I obtained this knowledge?
Actually, I'm in the middle of
something. When I made it. For myself.
Well, how was I supposed to know?
Well, I was hoping
this might tip you off.
That's kind of selfish, don't you think?
I offered to make you some. You said no.
That was before I tasted the pancakes.
It's a compliment.
You should be flattered.
Here.
It's Mrs. Lambert's herpes test results.
Mrs. who?
You've told more than one patient
his wife is sleeping with
his daughter's karate teacher?
You wanna stir the pot,
you have to clean up the mess.
What would you do if you got herpes?
She's coming in at 5:00.
Don't make me come looking for you.
I'd know what you'd do.
But I mean, a normal guy?
And don't be calling in sick,
or saying that your team
needs you for some kind of
emergency consult.
He suspected that maybe his
wife had also been playing pickle games.
He could just keep it on the down low,
just wait till she got infected.
You'd give your own wife herpes,
just to shift the blame?
He'd give his own mother herpes
if it got him out of clinic duty.
Course, maybe it was the wife.
Maybe she was the one who...
Where's Mrs. Nympho?
She's waiting outside, why?
- Go search her.
- What, you mean her medical records?
If I meant that,
good chance I'd have said that.
You think she's poisoning him?
His symptoms should be getting better
the longer he's here.
Instead, they're getting worse.
So, either she's poisoning him,
or it's not heavy metals.
We've done over ten different
heavy metal tox screens.
Because there's no reason
to test for the other 30.
They don't get into the air or food.
They only get in you
if someone puts them in you.
And the only way we're going to find out
what she's sprinkling on his cornflakes
- is to search her.
- I am not going to accuse a woman
of trying to murder her own husband
based simply on some paranoid theory.
It's the only explanation. We've
eliminated every other possibility.
We have not eliminated
every other possibility!
Has he responded to the lupus
treatment?
He's only been on it a few hours.
He hasn't responded
because it's not lupus.
It's not allergies, ALS,
arthritis or sarcoidosis.
She's all that's left.
Do it!
Hi.
I'm Dr. House.
- Mind if I take a look in your purse?
- Why?
Because I'm going to need
to search it and you
for whatever you're using
to poison your husband.
Why would I want to hurt my husband?
Then you won't mind
if I search your things.
Go ahead.
You satisfied?
Absolutely not!
She agreed to let me search
everywhere else,
- but this she says no to.
- Doesn't that tell you something?
Yes, that she doesn't want
some lunatic doctor searching her vagina
- with a flashlight.
- Cameron can do that.
I am not going to...
The woman hasn't left
since they arrived.
Whatever she's using,
she's hiding somewhere.
- She's not poisoning him!
- It's the only explanation!
No, it's the only explanation
your twisted mind can come up with
because you're angry
that you can't find the answer,
and you're taking it out on her.
And you are protecting
a complete stranger
based on some
childishly romantic notion
that people are all so happily married
they don't want to kill each other.
- You're calling me childish?
- Grow up!
Shut up! Both of you.
And stay away from his wife.
Sorry, I'm not giving you permission
to assault someone.
Let's see.
I'm thinking, Colonel Mustard,
in the music room with a candlestick.
There's no music room.
It's the conservatory.
- Same thing.
- No, it isn't.
If we don't find out what she's using
and start treatment immediately,
- he'll be dead in a week.
- If you're right.
If Foreman's right, you'd have basically
raped an innocent woman.
My wife fired the maid.
Apparently she's getting rid of
everything that reminds her of me.
- You did your maid?
- I was nice to our maid,
which annoyed her, God knows why.
- Maybe she was doing her.
- No one was doing her, all right?
But you still feel responsible?
Even though nothing or no one was
done, it's still your fault.
I offered to keep paying her salary
until she found another job.
But she refused to take any money
without doing any work, so...
You want someone to clean
your apartment? It's on me.
You're supposed to be moving out,
not moving more people in.
She's not moving in, she's gonna clean.
Maybe I should move out,
and the two of you could...
Oh, God!
- Oh, God, no!
- Call a code!
Please!
Charging 360. Give him Epi.
Clear!
- Still no pulse.
- Charging! Clear!
I got a pulse.
Pupils are reactive. You still with us?
He was without oxygen for less than
a minute. It can't be hypoxia.
Could be a stroke.
Bob, can you hear me?
- Back up.
- Bob, talk to me. Bob! Honey, please!
Bob, can you hear me?
- He's awake.
- Can you hear me?
Honey?
Honey.
Yes, she is quite the little actress.
So, let's say she's not poisoning him.
There's nothing more to discuss.
We've got lung and kidney failure,
neurological symptoms
and now, cardiac arrest.
A systemic disease with multi-organ
involvement is the definition of lupus.
Auto-immunosuppressants
aren't helping.
We should start him on cyclophosphamide.
See if it makes a difference.
Yeah, and interferon.
Interferon isn't an approved treatment
for lupus.
You're not still thinking...
Interferon isn't an approved treatment
for heavy metal toxicity, either.
True. But it's pretty much the only
thing we can do for a viral infection.
- We didn't consider it because...
- Because it doesn't make sense.
- There's no fever.
- Because he's got no immune system.
Thanks to the immunosuppressants
you prescribed for lupus treatment.
He didn't present with a fever, either.
Because at that point, he was
a post-viral autoimmune reaction,
which again,
thanks to the immunosuppresants
you prescribed for lupus treatment.
His immune system basically rolled out
the red carpet for the dormant virus,
waking it up and turning it
into a present viral infection.
Give him interferon.
But if it is lupus,
interferon could make it worse,
- suppress his bone marrow even further.
- Which is more likely?
Rapidly progressing, acute onset lupus
in a patient already on steroids,
or a team of doctors
missing a post-viral reaction?
We didn't miss anything.
Well, then I'm wrong. And you
shouldn't... give him interferon!
Intravenous interferon has been shown
to be effective
against some viral infections.
But I thought you said it wasn't
an infection. You said it was lupus.
The increasingly rapid progression
of the symptoms
- has caused us to reconsider.
- And what if you're wrong here, too?
- What if it's not a virus?
- There are risks with interferon,
especially in a patient
who's already immunosupressed.
Look, at this point, your lungs,
kidneys and heart are all failing.
We really don't have any choice.
I cheated.
What?
Ninth grade, Earth Science.
Mr. Foley.
I sat behind you,
so I could cheat off of you.
And I let you cheat,
so you'd sit behind me.
I thought we were going
to grow old together.
- In ninth grade?
- No, tenth.
What, you had to make sure
I put out first?
No, I knew you'd put out
in the seventh grade.
I love you.
Yeah, I know.
Say you love me.
No.
Why not?
Because you're not dying.
Say it anyway.
You gonna make me hurt you?
I love you.
It's not working.
Both his lungs and kidneys
are continuing to deteriorate.
- Up the dose.
- We already have.
- Apparently not enough.
- I don't think it's a virus.
We've been running titers for everything
we can think of. They're all negative.
- Increase the interferon.
- House.
You got a better idea other than lupus?
No.
Then up the dose.
Mr. and Mrs. Lambert's appointment
was over an hour ago.
Sorry, I was sick. And my team
needed an emergency consult.
Your wife has herpes.
What?
That's impossible, I don't have any...
You haven't had an outbreak yet.
Don't worry, you will.
- You rutty jackass!
- Me?
I haven't been with anyone in 20 years.
You're the one with the blisters
on his...
Doesn't mean that he got it first.
You don't need to have an outbreak
to spread the virus.
Yeah, and you're the one always talking
about wanting more sex.
From you.
And maybe I'd get more if you weren't
getting it somewhere else.
You two obviously
have a lot to talk about.
Don't even think
of dumping this in my lap.
There's gotta be some way
to prove that it's him.
I'm sorry, there is no test.
Either of you two
ever sit on a public toilet?
- Well?
- Of course.
Herpes can live for short
periods of time outside the body.
Dr. House, you know
you can't get herpes...
Some politically correct doctors
will tell you that it's impossible
to get infected by a toilet seat.
But they'll also tell you
not to use the same bath towels
to dry your crotch and your face during
an outbreak. See the contradiction?
I always use a paper cover.
- Always?
- Yes, of course.
What about you?
No. I never knew.
Oh, please. This is ridiculous.
Damn, I was sure it was Miyagi.
What?
He could believe that you can get herpes
from a toilet seat,
or he could be cheating on you
and just be happy to have an out.
The toilet seat makes sense, doesn't it?
Sure. But she'd only refused to believe
such a well presented lie
if she were innocent.
And since you both can't be innocent,
you rutty jackass!
You!
- Thanks a lot.
- My pleasure.
Honey, wait. Please!
Wow!
Not bad.
She has a family history of arthritis,
doesn't she?
Yeah, she does. What does...
Stop the interferon,
and do another heavy metal screen,
only this time test for gold.
You don't still think that she...
Don't let her go to the bathroom.
Why would you care if she...
Hello?
Oh!
Hi, I'm Lady.
- What did you do to my closet?
- I cleaned it.
Dr. Wilson said that I could go ahead...
It's not Dr. Wilson's closet.
- Where's the wood box?
- Wood box?
Yes, the wood box. It's made of wood,
and it's box shaped.
It's been in the back of this closet
since the day I moved in.
- I didn't see any kind of...
- You may not have seen it,
but you've obviously moved it.
The question is where.
Well, I did not move anything, I just...
It was in this closet.
Then you came,
now it's not in this closet.
OK. What type of box?
Wood! Wood!
A brown wood box.
It's got a metal handle on the top,
looks like a tackle or tool box.
Ah, you mean the chest.
The one that's under the bed?
Do you need to fix something?
Thanks.
Well, fine, then I'll go to one
on another floor.
Actually, they're not working there
either.
Every bathroom in the whole hospital
is out of order?
Well, the water...
I'm going to the bathroom.
- Where is she?
- Had to go to the bathroom.
I told you not to let her.
What was I supposed to do? Tie her up?
Why not? She likes that.
What are you doing?
Your hand is wet.
Sorry, must be nervous.
I've got some bad news.
What?
The damage to your husband's lungs
is permanent.
The kidney damage is reversible,
and with the right therapy,
he should regain full
neurological function.
Other than the fact that he's not going
to be running any marathons,
he should be fine.
But that's good news, isn't it?
Not finished.
When I was a kid,
my dad was stationed
at a Marine base in Egypt.
We were in the middle of nowhere
and there was absolutely nothing
for a kid to do,
except look for a mummy's tomb.
You didn't want me to go to the
bathroom because you wanted to tell me
my husband is going to be fine
and that you used to live in Egypt?
I didn't have a problem
with you going to the bathroom.
I just didn't want you
to wash your hands.
I never actually found a mummy,
but I did learn a fair amount
about the ancient Egyptians.
For example, they discovered
that stannous chloride
is not only great for toughening
ruby glass, but if it's mixed with gold,
it turns bright purple.
Now, either your fingers actually
are worth their weight in gold...
or you've been sprinkling
your husband's cereal
with gold sodium thiomalate.
It's an arthritis remedy.
It's rarely used here in the U.S.,
but it's still popular in Mexico.
Gotta give you props.
Never heard of anyone using gold before.
It's almost poetic.
That's ridiculous.
Heavy metal tox screen for gold
was off the chart.
- Why would I...
- Because you were trying to kill him.
I'd love to know the why
behind that why.
But you're not gonna tell me, are you?
You're wrong.
I love Bob.
I never said you didn't love him.
How could somebody do that?
Sit by someone's bedside day and night
helping them, comforting them
and at the same time killing them?
Maybe he was having an affair.
Maybe she was having an affair.
Or maybe she just gets her kicks out
of slowly sucking the life out of a guy,
- watching him suffer.
- He must have done something to her.
- Yeah, he had it coming.
- I didn't say he deserved it.
The only thing he did wrong
was marry a sociopath.
Or maybe she just got tired
of being married.
Didn't want to admit
to family and friends
that the marriage
everyone thought was perfect, wasn't.
Shouldn't one of us stay with her?
What if she tries to run?
Yeah, Cameron, go back there.
It'd be weird if we were
all in the ladies' room.
We started chelation therapy
with dimercaprol.
Thrilled to hear it.
His kidney function hasn't improved.
It will.
He's gonna need a lung transplant.
He's becoming more attractive
by the minute, isn't he?
You're pleased.
You think you've proved
that every marriage is a mistake.
Do I look pleased?
Ignorance is bliss.
You have one new message.
Hi, this is Blake Hanson
calling for Dr. Wilson.
I got a better offer for the apartment.
I know I offered it to you already,
so if you match the offer
you can still have the place.
Make sure you call me first thing
in the morning and let me know.
Otherwise, well, you've got my number.
Message deleted.