Good morning.
Hey, Alfredo.
- You done already?
- No. Not yet. I finish tomorrow.
- Mexico playing Argentina on TV?
- No, no.
My asthma is very bad today.
Six years, Alfredo.
You can't lie to me.
- I'm throwing a dinner...
- First thing tomorrow...
Party's tonight.
A little rain and I'm gonna have to
put buckets on the dining room table.
- No clouds, no rain.
- I'll tell you what.
You take off, but if it pours
into my guests' wineglasses...
- Okay. Okay, señora. I'll do it.
- Thank you.
Spinal cord seems intact.
Take a deep breath.
- It hurts.
- Try.
Breath sounds bilateral. I don't
think he has a pneumothorax.
- Just asthma.
- That and probably a broken rib.
Tell me when it hurts the most.
Your two little fingers
are darker than the others.
They feel funny. Como needles.
- How long have they been like that?
- Never noticed before.
Is bad?
Judging by how it looks,
he could lose his hand.
How does falling off your roof
do that to a guy's fingers?
He could have tweaked
a vertebra in his neck.
Could impinge the ulnar...
Sorry, trouble concentrating.
That tank top
really absorbs moisture.
Could impinge the ulnar nerve,
cut the blood flow.
Or it could be disseminated
intravascular coagulopathy.
DIC?
Guy falls off a roof,
the first thought is always,
"It's a clotting problem".
Trauma can activate
the clotting enzymes.
- Guy could lose more than his hand.
- Thank you very much.
This guy's been working for me
for a long time, and I...
Do I get bonus points
if I act like I care?
Cervical MRI. Work up for DIC.
And start him on a heparin drip.
- Who?
- You wanna know his name?
I'm sure it's in the file.
Or you could ask her.
She's his oldest, bestest friend.
They were in Cub Scouts together.
I'll get started
on the blood tests.
You haven't been
a real doctor in 10 years.
You'll make a mess all over the sheets.
- I'll do it.
- You have clinic duty.
- I still know how to handle a patient.
- Get me blood.
Lots of blood.
They're better.
They've showered.
You don't need to see him.
One-handed handymen
aren't in big demand.
Talking. That's how
lawsuits are lost.
I know you, Lisa.
You go in, you offer
to pay his medical bills, his wages,
you'll say something stupid
like, "I'm sorry".
You think I'm an idiot.
I think you're not a lawyer.
Don't go in there.
Trust me, House's people
can handle this.
Yeah.
This might sting a little bit.
The medicine will thin the blood
and help it to circulate.
Those are pretty
nasty scars there.
I work construction.
How long
will I be in the hospital?
Depends how long it takes us
to figure out what's going on.
I need to work. I'll get fired.
I'm sure Dr. Cuddy
won't fire you.
I'm a janitor at fast food six nights.
I need to work.
- My mother doesn't make enough.
- I can work. I'm old enough.
You're old enough
when you finish college.
Why? You never went...
I never had a big brother
to tell me to shut up!
I promise we'll let you out of
here as soon as we're able to.
Look, I... I am fine. Okay?
I feel better. I go home now.
No. If this is a clotting problem,
it could be very serious.
- All right?
- Look, you can't make me stay.
- Wait...
- You can't make me stay.
Turn your hand over.
I need to see your hand.
Where's Dr. Cuddy?
We've got a third finger
turning dark.
His PTT is prolonged and the fibrin
split products are off.
He's not clotting properly.
It looks like a mild case of DIC.
Well, obviously not that mild.
This keeps up, his hand is
literally gonna be dead meat.
His hand is connected to his arm,
and his arm is connected to...
I'm not sure,
but I bet it's important.
All this from falling off
my roof!
Yeah. If only he'd fallen
on his head.
Then he wouldn't have any
of these symptoms.
We need something
stronger than heparin.
Human Activated Protein C.
Looks like Cuddy,
same cleavage.
Protein C is indicated
only for severe sepsis.
How many of his limbs have to be
at stake for it to be severe?
But this stuff
is crazy dangerous.
It can cause internal bleeding.
If he bleeds, he could stroke,
he could die.
He could get better.
You know, if I try
to scheme like this,
you get that nasty wrinkly
face and screech like a hyena.
It's very sexy, I admit.
Do it.
Protein C
is borderline irresponsible,
except that the safe stuff
isn't doing squat.
- It's exactly what you would do.
- Obviously.
- It's exactly what he'd do.
- I know.
I think he's trying
to protect me.
Now, that's not
the type of thing he would do.
I overruled him.
He's the best diagnostician in
this hospital, and I overrule him.
You care about this kid.
Your judgment
should be worth more than his.
He also pointed out that I haven't
been a real doctor in years.
Now that sounds like him.
You were
just jerking Cuddy around?
She seriously thought
I wanted to stop her.
- One thing Cuddy is not is clueless.
- No.
First casualty of this case
is her sense of humor.
That's weird. There's nothing
funnier than almost killing a guy.
I'm just having trouble
getting up those steps.
- When did you start noticing?
- Oh, a week ago.
Your blood pressure's
a little high.
I've got something new
that should help you out.
It combines a nitrate
with a blood pressure pill.
It's targeted
to African-Americans.
Targeted?
Yeah. Well, see, we tend to
have nitric oxide deficiencies.
And the studies show this drug
counteracts that problem.
It's the first drug to...
What kind of studies you talking about?
What kind of studies are there?
They get some patients.
They give them some drugs.
I've had white people
lying to me for 60 years.
- You think this is a tan?
- You think they tell you everything?
The trouble with us black folk,
we can't tell the difference
anymore between racism
- and everybody gets screwed.
- Yeah?
Well, how about them cheap meningitis
drugs they're pawning off in Africa?
- Gonna tell me that ain't racism?
- That's just greed.
You really wanna screw whitey?
Be one of the few black men who live
long enough to collect social security.
Take the medicine.
Nurse.
Nurse! Help! Nurse! Help!
- Nurse!
- What's up?
- I can't move my arm!
- Take it easy. Take it easy.
The Protein C side effects we were
worried about, they happened.
- Where was the bleed?
- His brain.
It's causing
right side paralysis.
I've stopped the treatment
and called a neurosurgeon.
I can move it now.
- It's okay now? Can I go home soon?
- The surgery went well.
But all we did was fix the problem
created by the medicine we gave you.
She says you... You look young.
Are you sure...
There's five of us working on the case.
The others are older.
Why doesn't Dr. Cuddy
come to...
That doesn't sound too good.
His fingers are even darker.
His temperature's 102
and spiking.
And the x-ray
now shows lung infiltrates.
Well, the good news is he won't be bitching
about losing his hand if he can't breathe.
The trauma from the fall could have caused
acute respiratory distress syndrome.
Right. I forgot. Your roof.
It would cause lung
infiltrates and maybe fever
and conceivably
the cyanotic fingers.
- The only question is why.
- Why what?
Why her weird psychopathology
requires a diagnosis informed
entirely by personal guilt.
Let's assume
we've been wrong up until now.
Let's assume,
just for one second,
that the earth doesn't revolve
around Cuddy's roof.
What if he was sick before he
had his run-in with gravity?
He just didn't notice anything.
Well, pneumonia can cause DIC
which can cause cyanotic fingers.
- Pneumonia doesn't hit that fast.
- Sure.
Only pavement hits that fast.
It's not pneumonia.
He might have missed
a finger turning dark.
He's not gonna miss
breathing problems.
- What else?
- It's pneumonia.
He wanted to go home.
I thought he was lying.
I told him I had a dinner party.
I made him go up there.
Well, why didn't you just
take out a gun and shoot him?
I thought it was just asthma.
You might've mentioned this
earlier, Doctor.
Maybe we could have sent
some blood cultures to the lab
instead of wasting a day
indulging your self-loathing.
If it's just garden-variety bacterial
pneumonia, he's gonna be fine.
So give him garden-variety Levaquin,
and a garden-variety echocardiogram.
And go check out
the kid's house.
The blood work will show us which
type of pneumonia it is...
If he's huffing nail polish or pulling
the wings off his pet parrot,
this way'll be faster.
And I bet Julio's just dying to
find out what's wrong with him.
- Go with her.
- It's Alfredo.
And I can handle
getting a key and...
Rico and I no longer trust you deciding
what's important and what's not.
You ever think about writing
a book on office politics?
Trust me,
it would be a lot worse if I told her
that you had to break into her house.
What? Wait, wait, wait...
Cuddy's house?
See? It is shocking.
The guy's been working there every
day for the last three weeks.
You think it's impossible he
could've picked something up?
- I'm not breaking into my boss's house.
- I'm your boss.
She's scarier than you are.
She's a woman.
Relax. I'm coming with.
House is having lunch
with his juniors now?
- No. Not a chance.
- Then where do you think they're going?
I have no idea.
Then why don't you think
they're going to lunch?
Because it's not like House.
That was your point, right?
He had that smug look
on his face.
When he's that pleased
about something
he's gotta tell somebody, and the
only somebody he knows is you.
- He's breaking into Cuddy's home.
- What?
Why?
Medical reasons?
Why is he so curious
about Cuddy?
Why are you so curious
about his curiosity?
about me...
Because you dumped him
and you're married
and they are neither
of those things.
I'm just curious.
- Nothing wrong with that.
- No. Nothing wrong with that.
What do you think? Red thongs?
I think red thongs.
Okay, 20 bucks says I can get
through this door in 20 seconds.
- You're on.
- Count me in.
No furniture polish, no paint thinner,
nor anything else worth sniffing.
Nothing in here, either,
except a few cockroaches.
Nice. Someone
should fix Alfredo's roof.
So, why haven't you
fired House?
It's just, you guys are always
screaming at each other,
- and I figure you hate him, so...
- I don't hate him.
Why not?
He's a great doctor,
but any other hospital administrator
would have fired him years ago.
Four of them did.
The question is,
why did I hire him?
So, how'd you know
about her key?
You been doing a little handyman
work for Cuddy yourself?
Someone as obsessive and insecure as
Cuddy probably has three extra keys
hidden away
within 10 feet of the door.
And you consider obsession
a negative quality.
Insecticide is organic.
Soap is hypoallergenic.
I got the bedroom.
This is where it all happens.
You both went to Michigan. Did you
know him while you were there?
I was still an undergrad,
but, yeah, I knew him.
He was already a legend.
- So you just knew him as a legend?
- My God, you're subtle.
Anything on your mind?
- More cockroaches?
- Worse.
Beautiful.
There's no way you just
deduced where that key was.
Does this count as red?
You gave yourself 20 seconds
and put money on it.
Oh, my God.
She's got pictures
of you in here.
Just you. It's like some kind
of weird shrine.
- You're kidding.
- Yeah.
She uses super tampons.
What does that mean?
You two are just too nasty to each
other not to have been nasty.
I can be a jerk to people
I haven't slept with.
I am that good.
There's nothing here.
You ready to go, or you got some
more stuff you wanna sniff?
Whoa! Check this out.
It's fuzzy. It's black.
It's alive.
Patient's lung function's
declining rapidly.
Levaquin's not working.
He obviously doesn't have
garden-variety pneumonia.
I'm glad you learned to take
his impending death in stride.
- Guess what he does have.
- Rats.
- Scars on his hand.
- Rat bites.
But he says
they're from construction work
so he won't have to admit
he's got rats at home.
Catholics are right.
Pride will kill you.
He has streptobacillus.
Rat-bite fever.
- Boogie oogie oogie.
- Fits the symptoms perfectly.
That's certainly
one possibility.
But what about the aspergillus
fungus we found under the sink?
- What sink?
- You should clean your bathroom better.
You broke into my house?
No. No. You're wrong.
I had a key.
You had no right
to invade my privacy.
There was no medical reason
for that whatsoever,
and there was certainly
no moral reason for it.
Oh, damn.
You're right.
The focal consolidation makes
fungal pneumonia far more likely.
You're right I'm right.
On the bright side, it has the advantage
of keeping you totally responsible.
The treatment for aspergillus
is amphotericin.
- That's hugely dangerous.
- Yeah? Your point being?
Going the dangerous and aggressive
route didn't work the last time.
It's bound to work this time.
Start him on the amphoterrible.
Dr. Cuddy?
I'm Manny, Alfredo's brother.
How's he doing?
He's worried about money.
I wanna work for you.
How old are you, Manny?
- Fifteen.
- Twelve?
I can paint. I mow lawns. I rake leaves.
I can start today.
Alfredo wants you
to finish school.
Like you care.
Manny, I've known
your brother...
He falls off your roof, and
you don't come see him once?
Bitch.
With a patient.
Not according to the log.
- It's 3:15.
- Is it a commercial?
How's Cuddy doing?
She's not acting like Cuddy.
It's a pleasure.
You know her.
She has trouble with these situations,
feels personally responsible.
The technical term
is narcissism.
You can't believe
that everything is your fault
unless you also believe
you're all-powerful.
Wow, does she sound messed up.
I don't believe
I can fix everything.
And I don't lie awake at
night, tormented by that fact.
No. You lie awake
tormented by how...
I thought we were talking
about Cuddy here.
She cares.
She enjoys feeling guilty.
Lisa cares. It's why she drives you nuts.
'Cause it's not just a puzzle to her.
The patients are actually real,
their feelings
actually relevant.
And I'm telling her
she can't even talk to him.
My God, it's contagious.
You're feeling guilty, too.
I'm just saying, take it easy on her.
You owe her that.
From the moment
I saw you at the EI...
- Commercial's over.
- So glad we talked.
Snap, crackle, pop.
You got some
Rice Krispies in there?
That bad, huh?
You were here yesterday.
I see from the chart that Dr. Foreman
prescribed medicine, not a miracle.
Got to give this stuff
more than a day.
I didn't fill
that Oreo's prescription.
On the theory that you didn't
trust him because he's black.
Well, I'm gonna prescribe the same
medicine and see if you fill it this time.
I'm not buying
into no racist drug, okay?
It's racist because it helps black
people more than white people?
On behalf of my peeps, let me just say
thanks for dying on principle for us.
Look, my heart's red.
Your heart's red.
And it don't make no sense
to give us different drugs.
You know,
I have found a difference.
Admittedly,
it's a limited sample,
but based on my experience
of the last 90 seconds,
all black people are morons.
- Sorry, African-Americans.
- I'll see another doctor.
Fine. Fine.
I'll give you the same
medicine we give Republicans.
I think the medicine
is working.
They're lighter, right?
They don't look lighter to me, Alfredo.
How's the tingling?
- Does not bother me.
- Tell her the other thing.
He hasn't peed since yesterday.
- Since last night?
- Afternoon.
It's not a problem.
I don't drink much.
I think we'll give you a little
rest from the meds here.
She says, "That's the medicine
that's supposed to cure me".
Just making a little adjustment.
Excuse me.
He's not making any urine.
I think we just destroyed the kid's
kidney with the amphotericin.
I think he's dying.
Dying?
Cheese it, the cops.
I guess she understands
a little English.
His kidneys are shutting down
due to the direct toxicity to
the proximal tubule epithelium.
Proof that my brilliant idea of giving
him amphotericin is killing him.
That wasn't a complete
waste of time.
His reaction shows that you don't
need to clean under your sink.
It wasn't aspergillus.
And blood cultures show he was
negative for rat-bite fever.
There's still plenty of other
cool pneumonias.
Tested negative for Moraxella,
Nocardia, cryptococcus.
He has a low titer for
chlamydia antibodies. Maybe...
No, no. His chest x-ray's all
wrong for chlamydial pneumonia.
But the titer points to...
- He had an STD last year.
- That explains the titer.
He has low sodium.
Maybe it's Legionella.
No. His antigen is negative.
Well, that all sucks.
Maybe we were right
to begin with.
His problems are all caused by DIC
precipitated by falling off my roof.
DIC wouldn't cause
a fever this high.
See? My lap dog agrees with me.
How high?
Two hours ago
it was 103 with acetaminophen.
What about on St. Alban's Day?
Only temperature I'm interested in right
now is his temperature right now.
Open up.
Okay. Let me clarify.
Open up and keep it open.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Under your tongue.
You're using your left hand.
- Right one hurt?
- No, I feel better.
What, it really doesn't hurt,
or you just figure
if you say no,
you'll get out
of the hospital sooner?
It doesn't hurt. I feel good.
You don't smell too hot.
Your hand is starting to rot.
Why are we here?
We are talking about
cutting off a kid's hand.
Yes, we're talking
about cutting it off,
not subdividing it
and putting in condos.
- It's not a legal issue.
- Are you being intentionally dense?
I think it's premature.
- I've heard enough.
- What?
She says one word
and you take her side.
You should at least wait until she
actually gives a medical reason.
- Otherwise I might take it personally.
- Shut up.
If I were to somehow find out
that you two were in disagreement
over the proper
medical course of action,
it could make it awkward
for my client in court.
My client being the two of you.
So, guys, I'm a little busy here.
Why don't we pick this conversation
up in half an hour? Okay?
All of his symptoms are caused
by his underlying problem
and the medicine we gave him.
What underlying problem?
You have no idea what the
underlying problem is.
- You're the diagnostician.
- Fine. It's all my fault.
Does that make you feel better?
His hand still has
an arterial pulse.
His hand is a cesspool.
And the crap is spreading.
You are being pretty aggressive about
destroying a man's livelihood.
I don't give a damn
about his livelihood.
He loses that hand, he loses
his job, all of his jobs.
- He's not like us...
- Can't work as a cripple?
He loses his home.
- His kid brother drops out.
- An American dream destroyed.
Very sad, very emotional,
not one medical fact
in the whole pathetic tale.
You have lost perspective,
Cuddy.
You've stopped looking
at this as a doctor.
You're acting like someone who
shoved somebody off their roof.
You wanna make things right?
Too bad, nothing's ever right.
I am happy to report
that we're now so in sync
we're actually wearing
each other's underwear.
Chop-chop time.
- Is this true?
- No. I'm lying.
It's stupid to do it with her
in the room, I guess.
- This is a big decision.
- We made it.
We should convene a meeting
of the ethics committee.
No!
Look, she is making a medical decision
based on never wanting to feel regret.
You're making a legal decision
based on wanting me to be wrong.
Greg, you have
a history of aggressive...
You wanted
superficial agreement.
You wanted everybody's asses covered.
You got it.
Now can I do the surgery?
Pretty, pretty please.
Lisa,
are you sure
you're okay with this?
I should be the one
to tell the family.
Your hand is dying.
The bacteria are eating it.
When they run out of food
there, they go somewhere else.
If you cut off my hand,
I'll be cured?
Unfortunately, no.
We still have to find the disease
that's making you sick to begin with.
But you won't die of gangrene
while we're looking.
I quit school
when I am 12 to get a job,
to help my family.
I know I never get a good job,
never save money
or own my own house like you.
But, Manny, he's smart.
He's the best in his class.
Well, maybe Manny doesn't
have to quit school.
Maybe you can...
Are you sure I need to do this?
Yes.
Okay.
I gave one of my clinic
patients a follow-up call.
Your name came up.
I'm guessing an old black guy
who thinks the CIA invented rap music to
make your people want to kill each other.
He said you gave him
the white folks' stuff.
This is exactly why black
people don't live as long...
This isn't about race,
unless annoying is a race.
- Is he not getting better?
- He's fine so far.
I'm calling him back in. I'm
getting him on the right stuff.
Relax, Foreman, he already is.
I told him it was the white stuff.
I gave him the black stuff.
He was right.
You did exactly
what white people do.
You figure we don't need to know
the truth or can't understand it,
so you just lie to us.
- Just a white lie.
- Good one, massa.
Right, and I'm a racist.
Too bad that idiot will never know
for the rest of his long, long life.
Every slave master thought they
were doing the black man a favor.
Negro can't take care of himself,
so we'll put him to work.
We'll give him four walls,
a bed.
We'll civilize the heathen.
I'll tell you what.
Stop doing us favors.
If you're right, and we end up
back in the jungle
with lousy
blood pressure medicine,
it won't be on your head.
You okay?
You wondering
if you made the right call?
I've wanted to be a doctor
from the time I was 12.
I wanted to be a lawyer
from the time I was six
until my second week
of law school.
Sorry. Your story.
I graduated medical school at 25, pissed
off that I was second in my class.
Chief of medicine at 32, second
youngest ever, first woman...
Sad story.
If I had been
Alfredo's doctor...
You are his doctor.
I insisted on giving him Protein C.
We had to cut his skull open.
I insisted on amphotericin,
killed his kidneys.
I missed the pneumonia
completely.
I would have searched his home
and ignored mine.
I would have watched him die
trying to save his hand.
If I didn't have House
looking over my shoulder...
Are you saying you're not as
good a doctor as House is?
I'm saying House is right.
I was so anxious to get ahead.
I haven't been a doctor
in years.
His little finger is dusky.
Yeah, that's why
we're doing this.
No. I mean the other hand, the
one we haven't chopped off yet.
His O2 sats are down to 88.
His lungs are giving out.
He needs a ventilator.
And dialysis.
You're getting distracted by
the multisystem organ failure.
Pinkies are supposed
to be pink, right?
I mean,
they're not called "gray-ies".
But the organ failure
is gonna kill him.
But the pinky is weirder.
What does it tell us?
The same thing the right hand
told us before we cut it off.
- It's the same symptom.
- But at a different time.
His blood work
indicates mild DIC.
What if it's mild in the way that
when you get out of the ocean,
the water clinging to your
body makes the sea level drop?
It's technically true, but
it's completely irrelevant.
A lack of DIC
would explain everything
if there were also
a lack of anything to explain.
Endocarditis.
His heart's infected.
Little bacteria cauliflowers,
clinging to his valves.
Except sometimes they can't hold on.
They go swimming in his bloodstream.
Thursday, one breaks off,
goes to his right hand,
black fingers, gangrene.
Friday's child
heads for the kidneys.
And we all know
what Saturdays are all about.
Party with the left hand.
Also explains the fever.
It's perfect
except for the little fact
that we already tested
for endocarditis,
and he was negative.
Which means he either
is negative or...
What infection can cause pneumonia
and culture-negative endocarditis?
Prize value goes down
with every clue.
You're thinking psittacosis?
Alfredo doesn't have
any pet parrots.
Quit your squawking.
Give him doxycycline.
No! That'll just make
his clotting problem worse.
I liked you better when you were coming
up with wacky drugs for us to try.
We give him the doxy now, damn
it, maybe we can save his pinky.
He can teach his brother
to count all the way to five.
If you're wrong, he'll end up
with no hands and no feet.
Technically, if I'm wrong, he'll end
up dead, but I take your point.
- What's his night job?
- He cleans up at some fast food joint.
What, you think he got it
from a chicken nugget?
Since when do fast food joints
allow 12-year-olds to mop floors?
- Alfredo is 20.
- Really? Looks younger.
Where were you going
to work tonight?
What job do you do
on Saturday nights?
- What are you doing?
- Wake him up.
We just cut off his hand.
- Yeah. We need to talk about it.
- It's not happening.
Honest, I've got no idea
what I just said.
Why didn't you say
you spoke Spanish?
Well, because
she'd wanna talk to me.
Or something like that.
She says he doesn't work
Saturday nights.
Give me the talking juice.
The fact it doesn't fit your
theory doesn't make it a lie.
When she was out of the room,
the kid brother insisted he was gonna
cover for Alfredo at work tonight.
Saturday nights
he goes dancing.
Either it's a lie
or he's dancing with birds.
Give her the talking juice.
She doesn't know
what you're talking about.
Odds are it's gonna be
close to his house.
It's probably an abandoned
warehouse or factory.
Take the Scooby gang
and spread out.
What the hell
are we looking for?
Find somebody
who looks like crap.
Tell him you want
to place a bet.
It's Cuddy.
I already put him
on the psittacosis meds.
As soon as you left.
You're welcome.
What do you think the record
for one-handed juggling is?
You can yo-yo one-handed.
Good point.
I always wash my hands.
If a bird is infected, you can get
psittacosis just from breathing his dust.
But then, why do I get sick
and nobody else?
Your asthma
made you vulnerable.
- You're gonna be all right now.
- Yes.
For saving my life.
He thanked me.
- He should have.
- We cut off his hand.
If we'd figured it out
earlier...
If you'd figured it out later,
he'd be dead.
I never figured it out at all.
- Hello.
- What do you want, House?
If you're wallowing in self-loathing,
I've got something that might help.
We're getting sued.
- You saved his life. He admitted that.
- We'll settle.
He's got a stub where his hand
used to be. We have insurance.
Case seems pretty solid to me.
The new American dream.
Happy ending.
Kid's gonna be just fine.
Cuddy,
your guilt.
It's perverse and it makes you
a crappy doctor.
It also makes you
okay at what you do.
You figure a perverted sense
of guilt makes me a good boss.
Now, would the world be a better
place if people never felt guilty?
Makes sex better.
You should have seen her in the
last months of our relationship.
A lot of guilt.
A lot of screaming.
I know this wasn't just
because it was your roof.
Cuddy,
you see the world as it is, and
you see the world as it could be.
And what you don't see
is what everybody else sees,
the giant gaping chasm
in between.
House, I'm not naive.
I realize...
If you did,
you never would have hired me.
You're not happy
unless things are just right,
which means two things.
That you're a good boss,
and you'll never be happy.
By the way, why does everybody
think you and I had sex?
You think there could be
something to it?
Cuddy feels guilty about not
diagnosing psittacosis any earlier?
I think so.
There's no way she could have.
No.
No way she could have.
It's raining.