Okay, here's another one.
TechCrunch says, "Laurie Bream
spotted lunching at the Rosewood
"with yet another rising tech star,
Sam Herron.
"Could this finally be
the new CEO of Pied Piper?"
Maybe she's just fucking them all.
It's been 10 days.
You know what would be nice?
If I found out what Laurie wanted to do
with my company from her
instead of the fucking Internet.
Richard, the accountants
finally agreed to release our books.
Okay.
Hey, Richard.
ls there anything we should be doing?
I don't know. Why are you asking me?
I'm not the CEO.
There is no CEO.
Because, apparently,
Jack's empty fucking chair
is a better choice than I am.
So, maybe ask the chair, see what it thinks.
Say what you will about the chair,
but at least it never told me
to build a fucking box.
True.
Compared to Richard, it's a lot sturdier.
And it has a lot less of
Barker's ass rubbed all over it.
Are you serious?
On top of Jack's
ridiculous severance package,
we spent $1,000
on each one of your fucking monitors?
We did? Huh. That's very pricey.
So what? Raviga funded us for $5 million.
There's no way we burned through all that.
Do you have any idea how these deals work?
That money's tranched.
- What's that?
- Well, from the Old French for "slice."
Yeah, try to keep up, Dinesh.
We get our money in stages.
Right? We get $2 million upfront
to get us going,
to design and build the product,
but we don't get the next three million
until we take a product to market.
And Jack was
okay with hemorrhaging money,
because he thought
we were launching the box
and then getting the next three million
in the next few weeks.
But the platform will take
way longer to launch than that.
Yes. So we are effectively
a $250 million company
who just took $5 million in funding,
and now we're dead-ass broke.
Our burn rate is astronomical,
and every day we sit in limbo like this...
What if we don't?
What if we don't sit in limbo?
Like, fuck limbo, right?
I mean, right now,
let's fire all these fucking sales assholes,
and break the lease on this place
and get the fuck out of here.
Can we do that?
There's no CEO here to approve any of that.
Yeah. There's also no CEO here
to tell me not to do it, right?
That's right. You're the CTO.
Technically, you're the ranking officer.
Fucking A.
Look, when, or if,
a new CEO comes to take over the company,
we will do what they say
to the best of our abilities.
But there is a very real possibility
that there won't be a company
for them to take over
if we don't do something about it now.
- So, no more surprise waffles.
- What?
- No more Chef Amy.
- No.
And no more of these stupid offices, okay?
We're going to move back to the hostel.
- Fuck.
- Dinesh, we need to cut every corner,
save every penny, and plow it
into engineers to build the platform. Okay?
Then we will be back on track.
So Gilfoyle, Dinesh,
pack up those gold-plated monitors
because we are selling them.
Jared, come on. Let's do this.
Hmm. Well, that sucks.
Jesus.
Okay, guys.
Can I have your attention, please?
Yeah, next goal wins.
No. Now. Sorry, it's got to be now.
And so, bring it in, Dang,
Chef Amy, Jan the Man,
Keith, Northeast Regional.
And do you still have your shadow?
- Yo.
- Hey, there he is.
Okay, uh, circle up.
All right, I have some news for you.
Is this about the new CEO?
Recode is saying
that it could be Reid Hoffman.
No. I don't know anything about that.
No, no. There's no new CEO.
There's no new employees of any kind.
There's actually... It's more about
you guys becoming former employees.
So, look,
we're heading in a different direction.
And what that means is,
if I haven't taken you aside
and spoken to you privately about staying on,
that does mean that you are
terminated immediately.
So, Dang, Chef Amy, Jan the Man, all of Sales,
I am really sorry about all this.
Are you sure that you can fire us,
like, legally?
Yeah. Yes, absolutely.
I'm CTO. I'm the highest ranking officer,
so yes, answer.
You're still CTO? Laurie hasn't fired you yet?
No, she has... Why would she fire me?
Well, Code/Rag said
that your tech is mediocre
and that's why no one will take the CEO job.
- What?
- Yeah.
That's why I assumed that you'd been fired.
Uh, maybe she's waiting till Friday to fire him.
- Oh, that makes sense.
- No, it doesn't make sense.
That's not what's happening, okay?
I'm not getting fired. That's crazy.
I haven't read this article.
Okay, maybe I'm too busy
making the tech awesome,
because it's not mediocre.
It's actually...
Turns out, it's fucking revolutionary.
So, I guess that's the truth.
And also, I'm not fired,
these guys aren't fired, you all are fired.
Everyone from this wall is fired.
So, enjoy being fired.
Jesus. This is a good apple.
- Where did you get this?
- Oh, I have a fruit guy.
Fantastic.
Read me back what we have so far.
Uh, "Bachman and Bighetti
shall each include in this venture
"any and all portfolio companies.
"The exception shall be for Pied Piper."
Hey, how come Pied Piper is not a part of it?
'Cause, you know, I actually used to
work there, so maybe it should be?
Big Head, Pied Piper
is no longer an incubating entity.
It would be unfair to you,
and to me, and to them
for me to relinquish
any of my shares in their company.
And besides, like you,
I'm giving up everything else I have of value,
shares, options, cash, liquid assets.
Wait. So all my assets?
That seems like kind of a lot.
It is a lot, Big Head.
We're both giving up a lot.
We're both gaining a lot also.
And that's what
every successful partnership is about.
Committing fully, blindly,
and without concern of the consequences,
-like marriage.
- Right.
Oh, here. Get this down.
In the event of a tie vote,
any disagreement shall be settled
with a toss of a coin
of Mr. Bachman's choosing.
What the fuck are you doing in here?
Can't you see we're having a meeting?
Go ahead, Big Head, read that back to me.
Oh, um, "In the event of a tie..."
The fucking juicer's broken.
This is the second one in two days!
C.J. Cantwell of Code/Rag writes, and I quote,
"Having met this many candidates
without closing one,
"one can't help wonder
why Pied Piper can't land a man.
"Could the vaunted tech
of founder Richard Hendricks,
"whom I once called
the next Mark Zuckerberg,
"be turning Pied Piper from
a unicorn into a donkey wearing a party hat?"
- And?
- And she's slandering my tech.
It's the one thing that's working around here.
Look, I think if I just talk to her,
I can get her to change it.
No. I do not want you to engage
with a muckraker like C.J. Cantwell
simply to salve your male ego.
My male ego
has nothing to do with this, Laurie.
Look, good coders won't want to work
for a company they think has shitty tech.
I need to get ahead of this now.
And if I don't, we're done.
Richard, whether you appreciate this or not,
I do actually have a plan here.
You can meet with everyone
in Palo Alto to replace me as CEO.
I'm not going to tell you how to do your job.
Okay, but I need to do
something about this, now.
She's calling us the next Clinkle.
Clinkle, Laurie. Clinkle.
You do know
what happened to Clinkle, right?
- Do you want us to be Clinkle?
- Please, just stop saying "Clinkle."
It jars the ear.
Fine. I will have my office set up an interview.
But I want you
to present yourself well, Richard.
Be showered, groomed, well-dressed.
And you will need to sit down with our head
of PR beforehand to go over talking points.
Why?
Because you are in an emotional state,
and when you are emotional,
you become highly inarticulate.
Well, I don't say that's true.
Okay. Yes. Fine. Sure.
Um...
And thank you, Laurie.
Before you ask, the answer is yes,
I did blow all these hard drives clean.
- So...
- You really are a moron.
The only way to really blow
the hard drives clean
is to take a drill and punch a hole through it.
All right, calm down, Snowden.
I zeroed them all out, we're fine.
Welcome, welcome.
Uh, we have lost our lease,
so everything must go.
The chairs are arranged
in ascending order of lumbar support.
So, have a gander.
Oh, uh, word to the wise,
the Haworths are like a spa day
for the buttocks.
Yeah, and I have a fragile posterior.
My aunt used to call me "glasshole."
So, you can take it from me.
Look at these fucking maggots.
Crawling all over our garbage,
leaving their slime of mediocrity.
Ah, I thought you'd feel right at home
in a marketplace,
haggling, selling your monkey paws,
looking for Indiana Jones in a wicker basket.
Okay. Marion was in the wicker basket,
Indiana Jones was tipping them over,
you fucking idiot.
Hi.
Let me know if you have any questions.
Well, how about that? I made my first sale.
I've organized a lot of estate sales,
so this is kind of my wheelhouse.
- What?
- I have a lot of elderly friends.
Oh, that is a fun item.
That's a hardware fan.
You've got the yellow hoodie on today.
Oh, yeah.
Wait a second.
None of these are signed.
Oh, yeah. Urn, it's just my business manager
had some questions
about the way some of this stuff
was being arranged.
Like, he said something about
how it's not a corporation.
It's just a general partnership or something.
I mean, he told me I didn't understand,
which is true,
so he wanted to maybe talk to you about it.
So you want to lawyer up?
Is that what we're doing?
I don't think he has a law degree.
Big Head, I would hope that a handshake deal
would be good enough for you.
Because we're headed down a long road,
and that road must be paved with trust.
Blind trust.
And you bringing in these so-called "experts"
really gives me pause,
and it insults my honor.
Huh. Uh, sorry, hold on. I got to take this.
I'll be right back.
Sorry. Hello?
Hey. Uh, how do I look?
If I'm being honest,
like a ventriloquist dummy.
Uh, okay.
Well, you know, that's actually kind of fitting,
because I'm on my way to Raviga right now
to meet with a PR person
to tell me exactly what to say
to a reporter and how to say it.
Well, that does make sense.
You do tend to babble on
when you're under pressure.
Why does this thing people say?
Why indeed?
That was weird.
I just got a call
from Laurie Bream's office at Raviga,
asking if I'd want to interview
for the job of CEO at Pied Piper.
What? Are you fucking kidding me?
That's exactly what I said.
Then I said no, and then we both hung up.
I mean, I assume they hung up.
I had already hung up, so...
Wow. Wow.
Okay. Okay. Yeah, great. Big Head.
Big Head? Fucking kidding me?
What the fuck is going on?
Big Head, you can insult me all you want
by involving your self-described shylocks,
but to insult Richard and humiliate him,
that's like kicking a child
who's done nothing to deserve it.
I may not be able to finish my ramen.
I told them no.
Hi there. Richard Hendricks
here to see Dawn Simon, PR.
Sure, she'll be meeting you
in the small conference room.
- Um, do you need me...
- No, no. I, uh, I know where it is.
It turns out, I actually know something.
I'm not a fucking idiot.
- Richard Hendricks. Hi.
- Before we get any further,
I just want you to know
that I'm not going to be yelling at you,
but I probably am going to yell.
- Okay.
- Okay. Uh...
Because this is bullshit.
Honestly, I mean, I get it.
This is your job. You're in PR.
Your job is to pretty much tell me
what I can't say.
I mean, when I talk to this reporter,
I probably can't say
how fucked up it is that Laurie Bream fired me
and then replaced me with Action Jack Barker.
I probably can't say
how the only action he took
was to essentially pick the wrong product
and then bleed the company dry.
And I probably can't say
how fucking pissed off I am
that Laurie Bream is out there
gallivanting around the Valley,
interviewing every dickhole on Earth
for my job, including Big Head,
a man that I fired, by the way.
And no offense, I like him. I do actually.
He's a close friend of mine,
been that way for years.
But he is a bit of a simpleton,
and his name's fucking Big Head.
But, okay, look.
I want to be CEO of Pied Piper, okay?
It is my company. I worked my ass off
to build this company, okay?
That's my job. I deserve it.
And it fucking kills me that Laurie is out there
trying to give it to someone else,
anyone but me.
But I probably can't say that, can I?
You can say anything you want to say to me.
All right.
Thank you for meeting me, Monica.
You are from...
Baltimore.
H.L. Mencken hails from Baltimore.
Who?
Widely perceived as a racist,
but his work on the English language
is comprehensive,
and his perspicacious skewering
of evangelicals is laudable.
Monica, my mission here
is not merely to have fun.
That's okay.
When I voted against you
at the board meeting, I just want...
Monica, this is not about you, for once.
I brought you here to say
- I am sorry.
- For...
Ah, yes, of course.
You are going to make me say it.
Why am I not surprised?
I made a mistake with Richard Hendricks.
And out I went, right on my ass.
And then Laurie put that jackhole Barker
in to bankrupt the company.
But does she cop to that? No, no, no.
Because the Laurie-tron 6,000
isn't programmed to admit
when she's made a mistake.
I made an error.
Wow, um, that's really big of you to admit.
I should not have removed him as CEO,
and installing Jack Barker in his place
only compounded that error.
But if that's true, then why are you meeting
with so many other CEO candidates?
I am meeting publically
with a number of high-value candidates
I know to be unavailable,
as well as with a number
of less-qualified candidates
with whom Richard compares favorably.
That's why you called Big Head.
Yes. You see, Richard must not be perceived
as being the most expedient candidate.
He must be seen as the correct candidate.
This is very exciting for Richard.
I have been impressed by his conduct
in a tough situation.
- He's shown mettle.
- Mmm-hmm. Definitely.
Therefore, I will call for a vote
at the next board meeting
to offer him the job.
That is, of course, assuming he continues
to demonstrate an air of professionalism.
Hi, Dawn. Are you waiting for someone?
Yes. I'm supposed to be meeting
with Richard Hendricks
before he sits down with a Code/Rag reporter.
Oh, that's weird. I saw him earlier.
And that is why...
I'm just being honest here.
I think that Peter Gregory
is better off where he is.
Just saying, because if he knew
what Laurie was doing to his company,
he probably would want to take a gun
and blow his brains out.
Uh, okay.
We should probably start talking about
the things that I can say.
Um...
Richard. Richard Hendricks?
Yes. Who are you?
Dawn Simon, Raviga's publicity director.
So that would make you...
C.J. Cantwell, Code/Rag.
Thank you, I think I have everything I need.
Please tell me that went well.
Yep. No, yeah.
It, uh... It was gone great.
Yep. It had gone.
It was great.
Uh, she's a great guy.
Really. Girl. She's cool.
She's a cool one.
Cool. I can just... I can get out here?
- Just 'cause I got another thing.
- Yeah.
Slow down. Listen to me.
Look, in my defense,
I said those were all the things
I can't say, okay?
So it's kind of like I didn't even say them.
But you did say them,
at a meeting you scheduled with a reporter.
Reporter? Come on, you're a tech blogger.
Oh, really. Hard to see
why Laurie insisted on a PR rep for you.
Look, uh, just...
Tell me what I can do to kill this?
- You want me to spike the story?
- Yes, please.
Give me something better. I don't know,
go on a drunken racist Twitter rant,
or get in your car, run over Elon Musk,
and give me an exclusive from jail. Yeah.
Otherwise, I'm posting this
at noon tomorrow, so...
No, no, no, no. Look. Look.
If you want to leave,
you're going to have to run me over!
These offices were nice.
Now everything looks so bare.
Yeah. There is a certain sad vulnerability to it.
Have you ever seen a naked dead person?
No. No. No.
Hmm.
Well, the good news is, we cleared
almost $70,000 from selling all this stuff.
That's not enough
to afford all the coders we need.
We need at least a dozen.
Where would we even put them now?
Shall we?
Wait. Where's my hard drive?
What did it look like?
It just looked like
a normal standard hard drive.
- You sure it was in your bag?
- Yeah, it was in my bag.
Could it maybe have slid out
and was next to your bag,
which was next to
all the hard drives we got rid of?
Did you sell my personal hard drive?
You didn't happen to
wipe that one clean, too, did you?
- My personal hard drive?
- Yeah.
No! Fuck!
So it had our confidential IP on it?
Yes. All the work we did on the platform,
the box, everything.
Okay, well, what's gone
is not necessarily lost.
Okay, we just need to find it.
I found my retainer in the school dumpster.
I found my biological father
in a militia up in the Ozarks.
This should be no problem.
Don't worry, Dinesh, we'll find it.
Uh...
Does he not know we're moving out?
Should We tell him?
No. Jack paid him in full up front,
and he seems so at peace.
- All right.
I am such an idiot.
You've got no choice, Richard.
You need to go in to Laurie
and just tell her what happened.
What? It's bad enough she's going to find out
what I said after this piece posts online.
You want me to go in
and tell her right to her face?
No fucking way.
You could spin it. Tell her you're sorry.
I had it.
I had my old CEO job back, and I fucked it up.
I'll get it.
Ah. The Super Angel Premium Deluxe.
In the flesh.
Yeah, I had to drive to San Mateo
to get one that has auto-reverse.
Why didn't you send your assistant?
She was on the phone, so...
Well, Big Head,
it takes a brave man to admit his mistakes,
and with this token of apology,
you've officially righted your wrong.
Consider the matter resolved.
Cool.
Traditionally, the offender
shakes the offendee's hand,
so you would come to me.
That's an honest Thomas.
Gentlemen, Monica,
from the ashes of whatever happens here
will rise the phoenix
that shall be known as Bachmanity.
That's what you're gonna call your company?
Yeah, well, before it was gonna be
Bachman Capital.
Because I provide the Bachman,
and he provides the capital.
Yeah, but then, we compromised,
and made it Bachmanity,
'cause it's Bachman from him
and then the "etti" from me.
So it's two syllables each.
Very much into keeping score, this one.
Have a seat.
I'll go fetch the documents and my Montblanc.
Psst!
So, slight hiccup. I tracked down
the woman who bought the drive,
but she wasn't interested in selling it back.
Apparently, she's already given it
to her elderly father
and booked the Geek Squad
to set it up for him this afternoon.
What about my drive?
All our stuff is on there.
I think we're fine.
She said he mostly uses the computer
to download photos of old ships.
I don't think he'll be able to find our files
even if he wanted to.
Well, I mean, hopefully. But still...
Dinesh is right, this is sloppy.
Where does this guy live?
Shit, Richard, I'm sorry, man.
Initial here and here.
No. It's okay. I deserve it. It's my own fault.
And you're gonna wanna sign here.
Still, man, that just really sucks.
You know, I bet you wish
you could just scrub the whole Internet,
like Gavin Belson does, right?
Whoa, weird.
Every single one of my signatures
looks totally different.
- Wait. What?
- Yeah, look.
This one's in cursive,
this one's just printed, and then I...
One I just wrote "Big Head,"
but that's not going to hold up.
No, no, no. Did you just say
Gavin Belson scrubbed the Internet?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, and then they told me to my face,
that after Nucleus was shut down,
Gavin had one of his execs
order them to scrub
all negative mentions of Nucleus
off of Hooli Search.
Wow. Okay, when exactly did this happen?
No, no. Actually...
You told me that you would spike my story
if I give you something better.
This is better, right?
Yeah. Light-years better, actually.
Your story's spiked. Great, okay.
As long as we're trading apples
for comparable apples,
I've got a fresh and juicy
that's ripe for the picking.
Ms. Cantwell, what say you to an exclusive
on the launch of a future financial behemoth?
How about we just stick with Gavin?
Gavin for Richard? Deal?
Done.
Monica, do you really need to be here?
- Geek Squad.
- The computer's right here.
You're not wearing the shirt.
I spilled coffee on it.
I'm a nerd.
All right. We're all set here.
Yes.
Can I have my hard drive?
Oh, no. You fucking dick.
Shit.
You're gonna be replacing it.
You're back. How did the board meeting go?
Well, um...
You're looking at the past, present,
and possibly future CEO of Pied Piper.
Oh, that is...
Oh, congratulations!
- Jared...
- My captain.
"O Captain! my Captain!
Rise up and hear the bells
"Rise up-for you the flag is flung
for you the bugle trills."
All right. Dismissed.
Well, uh, just to remind you,
Pied Piper is still a sinking ship, so...
Enough with the maritime metaphors.
This is honestly, like, the best birthday gift
that I ever could've asked for.
-It's your birthday?
- Uh, I don't know.
The CPS worker
couldn't find my birth certificate,
but maybe now it is.
And in other good news, we've managed
to fill out our engineering team.
Did you tell them that my Fage's off-limits?
Oh, that won't be a worry.
Come meet them.
All right, guys, who wants to start work
on the fragment uploader?
Uh, Gleb, why don't you and Sanjay take it?
Richard, say hi.
Yes. Hello, lam, um, Richard Hendricks,
the CEO of Pied Piper.
- Welcome aboard.
- Hi.
What the fuck is going on here?
We got a little creative.
Um, I read that the woman who started Pegg'd
built her entire app using a team of coders
from India she never met in person.
And it only cost $15,000.
Yeah, so we figured why limit ourselves
to a few expensive people in the Valley,
when we could afford a full complement
if we outsourced?
Um, Richard, I know we said
that we sold everything in the offices
to pay for these guys,
but that was not exactly true.
Um, we kept one thing.
Okay.
Oh, wow. It's the CEO chair.
Ah.
Have a seat.
Okay.
Okay, uh...
Well, why don't we
go around the room, or screens, or whatever,
and introduce ourselves?
Hello, my name is Gleb. I am in Bulgaria.
Hello, I am Sanjay. I am here in Mumbai, India.
- You having trouble?
- No.
Hello. I am Elisabet.
I am speaking to you from Estonia.
Uh, thank you for the...
Whoa!
It's fine. It's fine. It's fine. It's fine.
-It's fine. I got it. I got it.
- Dude.
- I got it. I got it.
- You're making a great first impression.
Sorry. Can we go to the...
Do the names one more time?
http://hiqve.com/