I'm going to send you
to a series of checkpoints.
You won't know the final destination
until you arrive.
Mark isn't a part of this.
I need to know that he's walking away.
Do as I say,
he gets to go home
and watch 7he One Show.
And Alice?
Sorry.
You know how it is.
I still need to know
he's all right, I need proof.
You have my word.
I said I need proof.
Stay by your phone.
Oh...
Oh, yeah.
Yes, yes I did.
-Organic, yes.
-Excuse me.
And the kitchen rope.
No, no, I got Braeburns instead.
-Sorry, excuse me.
-About 10 minutes.
Yeah. Love you. Yes. Yeah. Love you.
- Sorry, excuse me?
- Bye.
I'm so sorry.
Er, I'm afraid you dropped this.
That's so kind, thank you.
No worries. Happy to help.
# Love is like a sin, my love
# For the ones
that feel it the most
# Look at her
with her eyes like a flame
# She will love you like a fly
# Will never love you again #
Stay away from the door, he said.
He's not here, is he?
He's out there.
Preparing to kill John.
And then you. And then me.
If that's what he wants,
why hasn't he done it already?
John wouldn't come here
without proof of life.
Well, your life anyway.
Mine, not so much.
You make a good bag lady.
Thank you. Listen, we need every scrap
of insulation we can find
or we'll have frozen to death
by the time he gets here.
Don't you give me the runaround.
Guv, where are you?
So it turns out Jeremy Lake was keeping,
I don't know...
Er, I don't know what to call it
-a scrapbook?
-Look, Catherine, I need some help.
What sort of help?
I just need you to find someone
for me, all right?
His name's, er,
Ronald Massey.
He works for a man I need to find.
Erm, Guy, I can't just...
I mean, who is he?
Look, Catherine,
I'll be there as soon as I can.
I'll bring in Jeremy Lake but I need you
to do this first, okay?
Can you just do it?
- Boss, I...
- Catherine,
do it.
Massey. Let's see.
Ronald Massey.
The mask's
of Lake's own face,
which is new behaviour,
as far as we know.
But it is consistent with some
of the images in the diary.
His condition disinhibiting him?
Yeah, or maybe he knows
we're breathing down his neck
and he's decided to go
all carpe diem on us.
Do we have the faintest notion
where DCI Luther is?
Sorry, boss.
Catherine, do you know anything
I don't know?
Sorry, boss, no.
Vivien Lake knows her husband's mind.
She's the only one who can help us
get ahead on this.
Let's bring her in.
Well, she's being treated
at the hospital.
I don't care.
Wheel her in in a gurney if needs be.
Hey, Guv, I don't know what your
other thing is but the big boss
he's on his last nerve and I...
I don't feel comfortable lying for you.
And things are really kicking off here.
We need you.
Hello, I'm inquiring about
the availability of Illeana.
This evening.
Overnight, for preference.
Ah, good. Thank you.
Yes, hello, King of Plumbers,
I have a dreadful smell
coming from my drains.
Thank you.
Dr Lake,
would you follow me, please?
That's right, quickly now.
Boss,
we should probably go.
Nah, sod it. It's just a drill.
Well, they usually say
when it's a drill.
We'll go when the hair on your bollocks
starts to sizzle.
I just... Let me go and check.
Yeah, yeah.
Call him off.
We're on schedule.
Luther should be here soon.
Er, yeah, I actually need you
to hold off on that for a bit.
Why?
Because that's what I want.
We entered into a contract.
Er, you... You'll get your money,
just, erm, tell me where they are
and then, er,
take the rest of the day off.
-Go to the pictures or something.
-Come on. Come on.
It's not that easy.
A police officer is dead.
I can't have that coming back on me.
Ah, it... It won't come back on you.
Just text me the address and then
pack your sandwiches and go home.
I'll make sure everything's
tied off.
He says a copper's dead.
Yeah.
-That would be your mate.
-Yes.
Well, for what it's worth,
I didn't ask for that.
Didn't you?
Your mate chucked it in for free,
didn't he?
So where does that leave us?
I came to off you for Benny.
I'm going to end this.
All this eye for an eye bullshit,
it's all just a game, isn't it, George?
You don't want this.
You don't want any of it.
Do you?
You lost your discipline, George.
You robbed Alice, she robbed you back,
now Alice is dead.
That's not her fault, that's your fault.
Benny's dead.
That's not your fault, that's my fault.
I couldn't shoot you in the head
because I made a mistake.
But if you can shoot me
then go ahead and do it.
It doesn't change anything,
does it, George?
What I lost was my son.
George.
Take it.
Eye for an eye.
You think I won't do this
and piss on your body after?
Go on, George.
Just do it.
Go on.
Stop there.
Do you have a gun?
Oh, er...
So, where is Luther?
He's in the boot.
Dead?
As a dodo's granddad.
How did you find him?
He came to me, as it happens.
And how did he find you?
I'm not entirely sure, to be frank.
But there you are.
He was a clever old sausage,
but not bulletproof, as it turns out.
- Open the boot.
- Oh, come on.
Now. If you would...
Open the boot.
All right, all right.
As you speak, so shall it be.
Oi!
I don't get it.
Peace In Our Time.
I'm Adolf, he's Neville,
you're the Sudetenland.
You're going to go down.
You're going to go to prison
for killing my friend.
Do you understand that?
And if I don't agree?
I shoot you dead right now
and tell a story to my boss.
No!
What did I tell you?
You're going to jail.
And you're going to hate...
Sorry, old bean.
Couldn't take the risk.
Here we are.
You, smoking gun,
damning evidence and whatnot.
All in the cloud.
Whatever that actually is.
Hand over the gun.
I think it's one of mine, anyway.
You're a clever one, ain't you, George?
You would have been a good copper.
No.
Too honest to have been a copper.
Schenk came to me, John.
He knows something's
not right between me and you.
I'll settle this with Schenk.
He trusts me.
Yeah, so do I.
But only because I got this.
Alice?
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Oh, shit.
Shit.
Is your friend in there?
- Yeah.
- Aren't you gonna call someone?
I'll find him.
Well, we can't just leave him here.
We have to.
For God's sake, he's your friend!
Got himself killed trying to protect us.
Do you think I want
to be doing this, Mark?
Do you think I want to be doing this?
Benny's dead.
The man who killed him is dead.
What I'm trying to do is handle it
so that your name is clear.
What time does your wife get back?
Half-seven, quarter past?
I think we need to get back
and clean the scene.
What's happened to you, John?
What about
the George Cornelius problem?
Have you dealt with it?
Yeah.
-Let's not be coy. Is he dead, John?
-Yeah.
Because it's the only way.
He'll kill us both. You do know that?
Alice, it's done.
You wouldn't lie to me, would you, John?
Not about something this important.
No.
Because you're the only person
I ever knew
who always told me the truth.
Come what may.
You never lie to me.
It's done.
That'll be your fancy lady
calling you in for tea.
Oh, why don't you just give it a rest.
I've got to deal with this thing.
Deal with it, then.
Just go home and we'll talk later.
Good luck with your whatnot.
Hello?
Hello, who is this?
Hello...
I hope you're not too uncomfortable.
A young woman just stabbed me,
of course I'm uncomfortable.
I'm afraid that a number of doctors
have certified you fit to be questioned.
And if there's one thing we can all
agree on is, well,
you can always trust a doctor.
Right?
We know your husband
is gravely ill, Vivien.
Jeremy doesn't have long.
One more Christmas, perhaps.
But he'll never see another summer.
Now, if we can find and detain him,
his case will never get to court.
He'll never go to prison.
The worst he can expect is
a few months in a secure hospital.
But he will stop.
This will stop.
This
will stop.
And this.
It will stop.
I have no idea
about Jeremy's activities.
I'm as horrified as you.
Oh, I doubt if you have the capacity.
And to be fair, we did catch you
in a plastic-lined room
getting ready to disarticulate
Penny Leyton with surgical tools.
I'm afraid you've misinterpreted
that situation.
Actually, I was there to rescue her.
Get her out of there. Poor thing.
But you were wearing surgical scrubs
and were attacking her with a hammer.
I was defending myself
from a very confused
and frightened young woman.
Who understandably, given her
state of delirium, misread the situation
and believed, incorrectly...
...that I was there to do her ill.
I have to make a call.
We've had some urgent news.
Let's hope it's the news we all want,
eh?
DS Halliday,
if you would hold the fort, please?
Where have you been?
I got called away, erm,
to something that didn't pan out, boss.
Any news from Benny?
No. No, he called in sick.
I've been called away.
I want you in there with Vivien Lake.
On my way.
What do I need to know?
Sir, we were investigating
reported gunshots.
You might wanna get
somewhere private.
7 am somewhere private.
Go ahead.
We found a disposable phone
in the glovebox.
Call reports?
Most likely any calls were made
to another burner.
Fine.
So I will need you to determine
where that phone was last used.
See if you can find any CCTV footage
corresponding with the time and place
of that usage.
Absolutely.
You have all the resources you need,
but none of the time. I want this now.
End this.
Stays schtum.
Are we clear?
Nobody says a word.
Okay.
Sorry, I'm late.
I had a very busy day.
So,
where did you meet,
you and Jeremy?
Is that relevant?
I don't know.
We struck up a conversation at
a dinner party talking about Tony Blair
over baked Brie and raspberry jam.
That's not true.
You met at a play party,
basically a fetish club.
You really are
a bourgeois little prince, aren't you?
Thought police.
Sex police.
Erecting an edifice of speculation,
a foundation
for puritanical distaste.
No, that's not what I'm doing.
I'm basically trying to establish
whether you would lie
to protect your privacy,
and the answer turns out to be "yes",
which I find very interesting.
Did you know that Jeremy
kept a diary?
Bit of a leap to conclude
that's a diary, isn't it?
It looks more like a sketchbook to me.
Okay, what about these?
These are actual drawings
of murder scenes
which makes me think about
these other sketches too,
which are, well, I don't know, I mean,
are these real too?
Clearly not.
It's an explication
of Jeremy's fantasy life. An outlet.
A masturbatory aid, nothing more.
Yeah, possibly, it could be.
But it's not just the drawings, is it?
I mean it's the... The text.
Well, that'll be, erm,
cipher text of Jeremy's
own construction.
Well, God knows what it says.
Do you think you could
decipher it for us?
Well, I'd love to.
But I very much doubt I'd be able.
You have to get rid
of this stuff properly.
No throwing it away in your own bin.
Oh, thank heavens I'm here with
a criminal mastermind.
Otherwise whatever would I have done.
I have to go, Mark.
I promise you won't see me again.
Well, that'll be a shame.
Some valedictory advice.
Don't let John Luther
back through your door.
Not under any circumstance
or for any reason.
He's not what you think he is.
Alice,
you have to stop.
Oh, God knows you are what you are,
but you're not a psychopath!
You're... You're not
without conscience.
You cannot live like this!
I know.
Do you need help?
Is there something I...
Hello?
I had a boss, once.
Her name was Rose Teller.
Really good cop.
She used to say, erm,
an assumption is something
you don't know you're making.
Do you know the assumption
you're making, Vivien?
Oh, I might be able to help answer that.
You're assuming that Jeremy doesn't want
people to read what he's written.
Then why employ a cipher text
in the first place?
Because he doesn't want you
to know what he's written.
He doesn't want you to know
that he's written it all down.
Everything that you've done, together.
Dates. Times.
Places.
Because that's the difference
between you and him, isn't it?
I mean, you are very private,
don't want anyone to know the truth
about you, not ever.
And he is very proud of what he's done.
He's done with being anonymous.
He's done with someone else
taking the credit.
This isn't a diary, it's a confession,
isn't it?
And where does that leave you?
-I don't know...
-Yes, you do!
You do, Vivien, don't you?
You know exactly
where that leaves you
if Jeremy has implicated you
as an accessory to murder.
You know exactly what that means.
Well, obviously he wouldn't do that.
Are you willing to bet
the rest of your life on that?
No, of course you're not.
Because he has
been letting you down recently,
hasn't he?
Come on, Vivien.
Help us and we can help you.
You are going to prison, Vivien,
but for how long is really up to you.
Can I have a glass of water, please?
No, you may not.
Jeremy's most outré fantasy,
and I have to stress,
to the best of my knowledge,
it was just a fantasy,
was to play a game of what he called
"Happy Families".
To sit in a house
and summon people to him.
Have them turn up at the door.
Lambs to the slaughter.
Sir.
The phone was used here.
He arrives alone.
George Cornelius.
All right, George,
you wanted it old school.
Thanks for coming so quickly.
Yeah, no worries.
Erm, so what are we looking at?
Oh, through there.
So, Jeremy Lake's
gone to ground.
He's holed up somewhere
getting people to come to him.
How are we supposed to find him?
There are like,
60,000 streets in London.
And previous murders,
they don't tell us anything.
There... There's no pattern.
They're random.
But they're not disorganised, are they?
I mean, everything he's doing,
he's doing to tell himself
how clever he is.
Oh, the audacity of that. I mean,
he can take care of whoever he wants
whenever he wants.
He can have the police
run around in circles.
He can make the police
blame the wrong man
and then he's come to an end.
Which means he's gone somewhere
of significance, with meaning.
-To who?
-To us.
To him.
And if you were him, right,
where's the most
audacious place you could go?
If I were him, I would go home.
No. Too big a police presence.
Where's the next best equivalent?
Well, if I couldn't go to where
the police are,
I'd go to where they just left.
Left. Right, yes. Ballarat Street.
The schoolteacher. Yeah.
Should we tell someone?
No.
Not until we've checked it out.
-Are you sure?
-I am sure. Come on.
Illeana?
Wow, you look lovely.
Please.
# I'll be seeing you
# In all the old familiar places...
# In that small cafe
# The park across the way
# The children's carousel...
Move to the counter!
Do not move!
# In everything... #
Martin, I think it's time
maybe we discussed
getting me some legal protection?
I can't pull it together, George.
I've tried,
but I can't work out what happened.
I need a show of goodwill.
An upfront payment.
Right now.
Now, I told you, Martin,
your lads a wrong'un.
- Hey, Boss.
- Yes, Halliday.
Are you with DCI Luther?
Yeah, I am.
Now, I need you to listen
to me, very carefully.
Without alerting DCI Luther
to this order, I need you
to bring him back
to the station as soon as possible.
Okay, yeah.
If you alert him to this,
there is
every chance that he will run,
do you understand me?
Yep, got it.
Good.
Now, get him back to the station.
Tell him
I have some interesting news.
And I want to give him
it face to face.
Schenk has asked you to bring me
back in, hasn't he?
Er, yeah.
Yeah, he said that he's got some news,
something he wants to tell you.
Fair dues.
I'm not going anywhere until this
is dealt with.
You think he's in there?
-I know he is.
-How?
Plumber's van. Pest control.
Food delivery.
All people that would come to you.
We can get back up in nine, ten minutes.
We've got no evidence.
If we call it in, we'll have to go
through due process.
Get a warrant.
It would go on and on and on
and what does that mean
for anyone that's alive in there now?
If you found out tomorrow
that if we went in there today
you could have saved someone's life,
-would you be okay with that?
-Boss, that's not fair.
All right, do what you have to do.
Pizza delivery.
Catherine.
Get rid of him.
But what about you?
Pizza.
Catherine!
Stop, boss.
Boss...
What did you think? Do you like it?
Are you okay?
Yeah, yeah.
You should know, Schenk's on his way.
You called it in, didn't you?
You...
You know they're coming for me, right?
Yeah.
What did you do?
Nothing I can't fix.
I just need time.
Are you... Are you asking me to...
To let you go?
Catherine, I have to go, okay?
It's a mess.
But it's not what it looks like,
I promise you that.
Can I stop you from leaving?
No.
Then I won't try.
John?
Did you use me as bait in there?
Send me downstairs to lure him out?
No.
I think you did.
I think you dragged me here
and threw me in front of him
so that you could be
the man to stop him.
That is not what happened.
So what did happen?
Why are you making such a fuss?
I mean, this is what happens, isn't it,
to those of us who are no longer useful.
Who's next, hmm?
Could it be me, I wonder?
Well, no.
I won't let that happen, John. I can't
allow it.
She did nothing
to you, Alice!
Neither did my parents, really,
or Henry Madsen.
Or Ian Reed. It never seemed to...
You never seemed to mind, really,
though, did you?
Well, what are you going
to do this time, DCI Luther?
Arrest me? Well yes, you should!
But you won't, will you?
You'll let me go.
Because think of the tales I could tell.
But how?
How are you going to cover
this up, I wonder?
What lies can you tell?
Quick, John, think of a lie.
-Come on, come on, think of a lie!
-Put it down.
Make me, liar. Liar!
Liar!
Next one's in your mouth.
Put it down, Alice.
-In a minute, liar. In a minute.
-Stop...
Oh, oops!
How many more bullets, Alice?
Come and see, John.
Honestly, I'm embarrassed.
I can't believe it took me so long
to see that Zoe was right about you.
You don't care about anyone, John.
Not unless they can feed
your compulsions.
Friends,
enemies, it's all the same to you.
It doesn't matter.
Even Zoe, you loved her so much more
-when she was dead.
-You need to stop.
It gave you an excuse to behave
exactly how you wanted.
You need help.
It's just words, isn't it, Alice?
Just words!
Trying to justify what you
really came here to do.
-And what's that? Please do tell me.
-Well, free yourself!
From this.
From me and you.
You keep coming back,
and coming back, and coming back,
but you're never going to get
what you want, Alice. Never.
- Because what I want doesn't exist.
- No.
So how many more bullets, Alice?
Yeah, well, I've got enough. Enough.
How many more?
Come on!
What now, John?
Alice Morgan,
I'm arresting you for the...
The murder of...
For the murder
of Sergeant Catherine Halliday.
Of course, you are.
You have the right to remain...
The thing is, John,
you don't understand love.
You can mimic it,
you can recognise it in others,
but you can never understand it.
Is this it?
Is this it? Love?
Yes.
Guess what? I lied, too.
There's one bullet left.
I just needed us to be really close.
Good night, John.
Don't.
Alice.
You need to help me.
No, Alice.
No.
Show me your hands!
Not like that.
# Baby you understand me now
# If sometimes you see that I'm mad
# Don't you know no one alive
can always be an angel?
# Sometimes I find myself
alone regretting
# Some little foolish thing
# Some simple thing that I've done
# Because I'm just a soul
whose intentions are good
# Oh, Lord, please don't let me be
# Misunderstood
# Don't let me be misunderstood
# I try so hard so please
don't let me be misunderstood #
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::