BETH: Previously on Good Girls...
Stop, stop.
You can't do that.
Why not?
Because we're roommates.
You remember Angela.
You look great.
(KISSES)
Why did they throw out your case?
Well, if I knew that,
I wouldn't be going home.
Hey, Shel.
I need something from evidence.
So what can I do for you?
Heard you're the ticket guy.
Sorry, what was your precinct?
Fourteen.
Hmm.
Get your coat.
Why?
Because you'll be cold.
Gonna wonder where I am.
Yeah, that's kind of the point.
(FREEZER DOOR CLOSES)
I want my sister back!
Finish the job, then.
See you at school.
Your bag's a fake.
What's this?
Our offer.
This is way less than I paid.
Plumbing, electrical.
It's all gotta go.
We're back in the club.
Whose name is it in?
I need career advice.
You gonna sell out your own wife?
It's not like she ever had my back.
She's not the only one in this.
I will protect Ruby.
What if that's not up to you?
That's why I have to make sure
it all sticks to Beth.
What do you think, man?
I think I got something on her.
(SIREN WAILING DISTANTLY)
Here's the rest of It.
Weird, right?
What's that?
Being reduced to a box.
Where's his daughter?
With the ex.
How is she doin'?
Never been better.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
Random robbery, dad gets slaughtered.
She can't wait for Christmas.
None of it's right.
Any leads?
(CHUCKLES DRYLY)
Just every dirtbag with a prior.
(HORN HONKING DISTANTLY)
HENRY: What are you gonna do?
I have, like, a month of banked vacay.
Aren't you suspended for, like, three?
So I'll get a Peloton after.
Do that before the vacation.
Don't let this die, okay?
Nothing can survive here.
I grabbed your mail, too.
Why didn't I leave Detroit
when you did? (SIGHS)
'Cause you're not smart enough
to know it's all pointless.
Hey, did Dave say anything
about our last night there?
He, like, made this noise
I have actually never heard a man make.
It was, like, high-pitched.
I think we're gonna go on a vacation.
Like, Playa del Carmen.
They like gays in Puerto Rico.
I think he'll like that.
How could his wife not know?
She knows?
What's that gonna do?
We'd be protected.
You mean, you'll be protected.
RUBY: I think the question is,
how does you being
on city council protect us?
Because I'd finally have
some real leverage.
You kinda already do.
How?
I mean, he's not going to
mess with somebody he wants to, uh...
Don't.
Fingerpaint.
That's gross.
Pick your lock?
Somehow worse.
Give you the double gopher?
I think you see
where we're going with this.
I mean, some real leverage.
Like, if he wants
to throw you in a freezer again,
I would have the city on my side.
(SIGHS)
What happened to Nevada?
Nothing.
'Cause we don't have to
worry about the freezer in Nevada, right?
Yeah, but I'd like to
get us there in one piece.
That's a pretty big detour.
You don't really
stop in Miami on your way to Vegas.
Okay, chill!
Gosh, it wasn't even my idea.
Whose idea was it?
Brother-cousin.
Hmm.
(RUBY SNICKERS)
What?
(CHUCKLES) Okay.
That is not why he suggested it.
I mean, isn't it?
He said he could use me.
Oh, I bet he could.
A mom like me.
And I'm guessing he also has fingers?
Hmm.
All right. Forget it.
I'll tell him to ask someone else.
Sheesh.
There's no one else.
No, we don't have to
fill the seat right away,
so, why don't you just
take a minute, and, you know,
realize why I'm right?
(CHUCKLES) Okay,
take longer than a minute.
Yeah, but I'm not gonna give in easy.
(CHUCKLES) All right.
All right.
Talk to you later. Bye.
Maybe she's just not that into you, bro.
Mm. She'll come around.
Bitch like that don't need to be romanced.
Oh, yeah?
What does she need?
Someone to yank her by that ponytail.
That's not my style, brother.
You want her in that seat, right?
(INHALES) What would you do?
I'd give her what she needs.
I Know what you need.
What's that?
You need to stop eating this burger.
Yo!
Gotta make weight.
Always want what I already have, huh?
Always get it, too. Mm.
(DOORKNOB RATTLING)
(DOORKNOB RATTLING VIGOROUSLY)
(UTENSILS CLATTERING)
(LOUD CRASH)
(ANNIE EXCLAIMS)
(ANNIE GRUNTS)
KEVIN: Stop, stop. Annie!
(YELLING)
What are you doing?
I thought you were breaking in.
My key didn't work.
Yeah, well... Yeah,
because the lock is broken.
(SIGHS)
Is that why your entire kitchen's
on the floor?
It's my alarm system.
(PANTING)
It worked.
Where have you been?
Angela's.
Well, you missed all the action.
I did all right.
I meant here.
Where are you...
Where are you going now?
I gotta get back.
Angela could stay here.
I wouldn't wanna break your rules.
I'll make an exception.
(SIGHS)
We might order food.
I could also order food.
We could all three watch a movie, or...
She asked me to move in with her.
Already?
This my avocado knife?
It's not.
Can I have it?
(GRUNTS)
Don't you just...
think it might be a little soon?
It is better than couch-surfing.
Okay, well, then...
You can sleep in my bed.
I mean, I'll stay in Ben's room.
Why would you do that?
'Cause we had a deal.
Just tell the school I still live here.
Wait.
Please, I...
I don't want to be alone.
Neither do I.
(UTENSILS CLATTERING)
What's all this?
Need to get 'em out of here.
What about our money?
Well, you should've thought about that
before you and your bestie
told Eli's mom that she bought a fake.
It just came out.
Yeah, well...
It's all over the parent chain.
Oh, no.
Oh, yeah.
They threatened to call the cops.
What did you say?
It was a mistake.
That's good.
And I refunded all her money.
Not good.
Well, what else was I supposed to do?
This was our way out.
It was.
And not just for us.
Do you feel that?
What?
The deja vu.
This isn't Beth's fault.
Yeah, you go out
with your girl for one night,
and then you come back
with problems that last you forever.
So we'll find another way out.
She'll screw that up, too.
Goodwill will be here in the morning.
Stan?
This one was mine.
ANNIE: It's just, like,
what is he even doing in there?
BETH: Well, he's probably
built up more filth
'cause he's been homeless for so long.
ANNIE: Ugh! He might as well
be showering in Cristal
for what it's costing me.
What if he took baths?
He moved out.
Problem solved.
Still can't pay the water bill.
We need another purse party.
Mm.
Okay.
Check with the girls, would you?
Totally.
Get something on the books.
It might not be right away.
How come?
Just... you know, some issues.
What kind of issues?
Inventory.
Floor seats for the Knicks
Couple models gon' kiss
They don't even want a pic
Wanna lick up on the Yeah, yeah
I done made a couple hits
Goin' hammer with the Bic
God handed me the gift...
So, a dealership?
Never really my thing.
Spas. What are those even for?
But this? (SIGHS)
This is how we make dreams come true.
Not "we."
Public record, darling.
This is ours.
A little Lysol, lot of love.
This is just where we print.
Clean this place right up.
Not a place to wash.
It is now.
We know nothing about
running a strip club.
Didn't know much about cars
or hot tubs either.
How much?
How much what?
Our cut.
Why would I do that?
You know how this goes?
How clean do you want your money?
Oh, I want it to sparkle.
Then you get what you pay for.
What are you doing?
Maybe we could work something out.
Don't be mad.
I'm not mad.
She's mad.
We were out.
Not exactly.
We were more out than in.
You know how you protect us?
By doing exactly what he says.
At least now we're getting paid.
That's what the purses are for.
The purses are gone.
Can't we just make more?
Not without getting Harry
kicked out of school.
(SIGHS) Oh, no.
What happened?
I said a thing.
She said a thing.
Oh, no.
So without this, it is bye-bye Nevada.
(SIGHS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
KRYSTAL: Hey, bitches.
ALL: Hey.
I'm starving.
Yo, hey. Let me get
a Reuben sandwich, okay?
Extra Russian dressing.
What kind of fries you got?
Stick, skinny, Curly.
Okay.
Which one?
All three.
Okay, so we have two parties coming up
and we can stick these guys
with at least 10 purses.
RUBY:
Change of plans.
Okay?
Need you back at the club.
What do you mean?
It's opening back up.
(SCOFFS)
That's not gonna happen.
Well, why not?
The girls have moved on.
Can't we get 'em back?
Oh, no.
Gene treated us like garbage.
Oh, well, there's new management.
Who?
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
(INAUDIBLE)
(MOUTHING) What?
(MOUTHING) Come on.
(MOUTHING) Come on!
All of us.
We'll treat it like a partnership.
We'll split the costs and the profits.
So instead of just dancing
on the table...
You'll finally have a seat at it.
So, what do you guys think?
Oh, yeah.
JULIE: Babe, the geraniums
don't go with the snapdragons.
I'm just planting everything
that's in the flats, babe.
Now we've got purple on top of lavender.
So?
They clash, babe.
It's the exact same color.
(CHUCKLES)
You are such a dude.
Cowboy.
Sorry, the gate was open.
Babe, this is Agent Donnegan.
She was with me in Detroit.
Thanks for keeping him in line.
He's a pretty straight shooter.
Well, my trainer's on her way.
Babe, just make it look pretty.
I tried to sway the director.
It's not your fault.
Yeah, but it was under my watch.
I'm the one who lost the money.
(SIGHS)
You didn't lose it.
You just got played.
I'll be okay.
Wish there was something more I could do.
There is.
Can you, um, help me water here?
Come with me.
Where are you going?
Detroit.
You're off the clock.
It's my vacation.
They'll never authorize this.
They will for you.
We lost, kid.
It's 'cause we didn't connect the dots.
This is for someone else.
It's not just about money.
It's not even our jurisdiction.
He's got the entire city in his pocket,
and you're just gonna plant petunias?
Geraniums.
Well, they're beautiful.
Thank you.
With a garden like that, who cares
if he slaughtered a cop,
card store girl and a team
of federal agents, hmm?
You need a real vacation.
And you need to separate
the purple ones, babe.
I found this in my underwear a while ago.
VANCE: Wow.
Look at the quality.
So, I didn't touch it,
so those are all her prints.
Sweet.
Yeah.
(CLEARS THROAT)
I got this from, uh, my wife's cell.
They're just talking about
going to a book club.
No. It's code.
Yeah. Nobody was doing any reading.
So we made a whole list,
right, with timestamps.
You'll see it correlates with
when she left
in the middle of the night.
Making her drops.
DEAN: Maybe we can use
the towers, you know,
however they do that.
They use the towers.
Maybe that's how you track the money.
I mean, is that enough?
It's up to the DA.
Wait...
What's gonna happen to her?
Everything that never should have
happened to you.
It's the right thing, Dean.
It's easy for you to Say.
It's not your wife.
She brought it on herself.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Listen to this guy.
He knows what's up.
I mean, I'm just trying to
help out a friend.
You're gonna fit in great with the team.
How's that?
You got your territory all set.
Yeah, you can work under Dean
till you get the program down.
I'm... I'm not really
looking for a career change.
Oh, no.
That's the wrong way to think about it.
Yeah.
No disrespect.
The night renewal cream
is really flying off the shelves.
Let's not talk shop in front of tourists.
No disrespect.
It's all good.
(SIGHS)
(FEEBLE CHATTER ON TV)
(DOORKNOB RATTLING)
(UTENSILS CLATTERING)
When are you gonna get that lock fixed?
Why are you home?
I live here?
Uh, but you have the tournament.
Yeah.
Oh.
(UTENSILS CLATTERING)
So, uh...
You guys need, like, a chaperone, or...
Uh, Dad's doing it.
Oh.
What about a water girl?
What's going on?
Huh? Nothing.
(SIGHS)
You ever get the feeling
you're gonna be kidnapped and murdered?
I'm gonna skip the tournament.
No, no, no.
It's one game.
It's the semi-finals.
Why don't you stay with Aunt Beth?
Ugh! 'Cause those kids
wake up at, like, 8:00.
Rather get murdered.
Where did Kevin go?
His girlfriend.
Where's Martha gonna go?
Who?
His friend with the green shopping cart.
How do you know her?
Martha and Tom come over to do laundry
when you're at work.
(SIGHS)
Of course they do.
Rollerblade Roy just chills
and watches Maddow sometimes.
The rest of them crash behind
the food court at the mall.
They throw out everything there.
Panda Express.
Steak Escape.
Wetzel's Pretzels.
Hot Dog on a Stick.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
I think I finally figured out
this bedtime thing.
Only took four kids.
Promise 'em anything they want,
and they'll go to sleep
with a smile on their face.
What happens when they wake up?
They've forgotten everything.
So you're lying.
I'm open to suggestions.
Maybe try holding a pillow
over their cute little faces
till they pass out.
Wow. Let me know how that goes.
I'm on mornings, so...
Well... (SIGHS)
I might be working
more nights from now on.
Why?
He's just throwing a lot at us these days.
All right.
You gotta do what you gotta do.
Thanks.
Don't miss too many bedtimes.
You never know how many you got left.
They don't grow up that fast.
Reservation?
Angela, right?
Sorry. Annie.
I'm Kevin's old roommate.
Oh, my God! Hi.
Hey.
I'm sorry to bother you at work.
I just couldn't get a hold of him.
Oh, he's probably at my place.
Oh, yeah. Of course.
Makes sense.
It's just, you know,
with his phone number always changing,
'cause of the prepaid phones
and all that.
He uses those?
Yeah, that or the payphone
at the bus station,
which he swears still works.
(CHUCKLES) Gross.
Yeah.
Oh, speaking of...
Here.
Yeah, he left this behind.
What is that?
His bathroom.
He poops in there?
Oh, yeah. Poops, showers,
shaves, the works.
He can use my bathroom.
You know Kev.
Creature of habit.
(CHUCKLES)
Uh...
Oh.
He also forgot to take these.
Condiments?
I have all this stuff.
In my experience, you're gonna wanna
double up.
Why?
Well, you know, he doesn't believe
in silverware,
so you combine that with the bucket,
it just gets a little dicey.
Why are you doing this?
Just...
to help you prepare.
Or maybe you're jealous.
Uh, what?
Or lonely, or just, like, psycho.
Okay.
I'm cool with Kevin.
That's great.
I like that he's different.
Hey, he's all yours.
Thanks.
ATM.
Check.
Liquor vendors?
RUBY: Check.
Dry cleaning.
Gene put in coin-op machines.
We'll set up an account.
BETH: Trash removal?
RUBY: Underway.
How are you on diapers?
This one just had a major blowout.
Okay, I'll make sure you're stocked.
Health insurance forms.
Yeah, make sure all the girls get
one of those.
Some ladies outside
wanna talk to the managers.
Can we help you?
We're here about the dancing.
Oh. Auditions are on Tuesday.
Fully nude?
Um, we leave that up to the performer.
Do you know how many kids
ride their bikes past here
every single day?
Oh, we're fully zoned and licensed.
Mm, not anymore.
There's enough there
to keep you from opening.
It's your turn in the freezer.
(FEEBLE CHATTER ON TV)
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
Don't need a turndown.
Thanks.
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
I haven't left my bed
since the last turndown.
DAVE: Not housekeeping.
(DOOR OPENS)
Took me three flights to get here.
Why?
I use miles.
We're both on vacation.
You better give me money for that.
It's mine, too?
How?
We're roommates.
(CHUCKLES) Department chief
can't spring for his own room?
Kind of in the middle of something.
My funds are limited.
My wife left me.
This is all you got, huh?
What happened?
We're still gonna have to track a motive.
No, why did she leave?
I told her... that I like
a more diverse garden.
So what now?
We get him.
(SIGHS)
(EXHALES)
I fart in my sleep.
I watch an unhealthy amount of porn.
We're gonna be just fine.
What is Family First Alliance?
Not a group you want on your bad side.
Women have been naked
in that dump for over a decade.
Yeah, well, when ownership transfers...
Yeah, but it's the same place.
Community has a Say, Beth.
(SIGHS)
I don't even wanna do this.
Then don't!
Oh, sure, so your brother can come
for the rest of my family.
Not my brother.
(SNIFFS)
What is he exactly?
Blood.
Well, you are my elected official.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY) So?
So you're supposed to be helpful.
You want this problem to go away?
Yes, please!
Then run for city council.
I'm just a mom.
I was just a caddie.
Well, what's a plain old mom
supposed to do?
Fight.
How?
WOMAN: Studies show
crimes goes up around a strip club.
Assault, random victimization,
drunk driving,
and public indecency.
This is what we live in fear of
when we take our dog for a walk,
or our kids to a school
that's right around the corner?
What crawled up her butt?
WOMAN: We ask you, tonight,
to restore family values
to our community,
and to finally shut down
this lawless den of sin.
Thank you.
Anyone else like to speak on this matter?
Okay, if there are
no objections, we'll move to...
Just a second.
Someone still has the floor.
Yes. (CLEARS THROAT)
I'd like to read
a statement I've prepared.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Oh, boy.
From the oldest of times,
people danced for a number of reasons.
They danced in prayer,
or so that their crops
would be plentiful.
Or so that their hunt...
Is she doing Footloose?
I couldn't talk her out of it.
Hmm. It worked for Bacon.
They danced to stay physically fit
and show their community spirit.
And they danced...
BETH: Thank you.
Thank you.
(WHISPERS INAUDIBLY)
Um, I would also like to respond to what
the woman from,
uh, Families First said.
Uh, I respect that you're a mother.
!am also a mother.
Um, in fact,
we're all mothers.
Right, Krystal?
I drop my first-grader off at that school
right around the corner
before I go to the club.
My little girl's in third grade there.
My son's in college.
Boy, she looks incredible.
We are all just trying to make a living.
There's a lot of other ways to do that.
Fine, but...
do they all benefit our economy
the way ours does?
Uh, is Mr. Sambroski here?
Right here.
BETH: This is Mr. Sambroski.
He owns the 24-hour donut shop
right next to the club.
My sales between 2:00
and 5:00 a.m.
have gone way down since Sweet P's closed.
That's one business.
Uh, I own a jewelry store.
When Sweet P's was open,
we did so much better.
Husbands are
way more generous
with their wives when they feel guilty.
(ALL CHUCKLING)
WOMAN: The guys always
pregame at my sports bar.
We need to get those girls to
take their clothes off again.
BETH: See?
Whether they're dancing
in a club, or speaking in a boardroom,
or baking in a kitchen,
these women are making a difference
in our community.
And aren't those values
just as important to show our children?
(INDISTINCT MUMBLING)
Well, thank you for listening. (CHUCKLES)
(ANNIE WHOOPING)
RUBY: Ah.
How did I do?
You brought home the Bacon.
(CHUCKLES)
WOMAN: Next up, after the vote,
ordinance 06.82,
the length of retractable dog leashes.
Oh, I gotta hear this.
(HIP-HOP SONG PLAYING)
Open for business!
(ALL CHEERING)
(CHUCKLES) Congrats.
Thanks, baby.
So exciting.
Thank you.
Yes! Whoo!
(CHUCKLING)
Huh, so what should we toast to?
Uh, to our new venture.
Most of which we give to the man
who put you in a freezer.
Why are we even celebrating?
PHOEBE: Hey, guys.
Miss us?
What's all that?
Redemption.
Huh?
We are ice cream social chairs,
running a car wash thing,
holiday boutique, concert committee.
Is that enough to keep the cops away?
Hopefully, it's enough to
keep him in that school.
Car wash is all you.
I Know.
What's all that?
Putting in a spice rack.
Hell no.
Oh, I'm not getting on it.
But who...
Hell to the no.
I think it's fun!
Yeah, for you.
My own private champagne room.
What am I, a piece of meat?
Tonight, no. Tonight...
you're a fireman.
Oh.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Where did you even get this?
Mm, we replaced the old ones.
What's going on, baby?
We're opening the club back up.
Who's "we"?
All of us. Me, the girls,
even the dancers.
Okay, yeah, you can't do that.
Before you get weird,
I'm just as much an owner as Beth is.
(STAN SIGHS)
Ruby...
This is our new way out.
We don't even need the bags.
Is this a done deal?
We're legit.
There might even be
a job in it... for you.
For me?
(KIDS CLAMORING)
VANCE: Who's next?
Nick, Dennis, Tyler.
What do we look for?
We look for weaknesses, right?
(BLOWS WHISTLE)
Let's go.
There you go.
No retreat, no surrender, Tyler.
He's bigger, but you might be better.
Tyler, don't back up.
Get in there.
Dennis, attack!
(DENNIS GRUNTING)
VANCE: Good.
(BLOWS WHISTLE) All right.
Let's take a break.
Dennis, help Tyler up.
Caleb, that's enough crying.
We're not giving out crying patches.
Come on, join the group.
Let's go.
Today. (BLOWS WHISTLE)
This one's trying to get
his fitness patch here.
Yeah, well, this is important.
Make it quick.
So, it turns out that
Beth's not the only one
that's going down.
So?
So, my wife's in it, too.
More the merrier.
You can't give that stuff to the DA.
You're putting me in a tough spot.
I know.
I am Team Dean all the way.
I just need you to drag your feet
a little bit.
Why would I do that?
Come on, man.
No, it'd be a different story
if you were one of us, but...
(TYLER SCREAMING)
Dennis, stop whipping Tyler.
Oh.
If I'm gonna have your back,
I'd want to know that you'd have mine.
I'll do whatever it takes.
Let's talk at the next meeting.
All right.
See you there.
Yeah, you will.
(BLOWS WHISTLE) Let's go.
Line up. (CLAPS)
(DOOR OPENS)
I fixed the lock.
What are you doing?
Hungry?
I mean, yeah, always, but... (SIGHS)
We're having citrus braised lamb shanks.
Uh, what's...
What happened with Angela?
I mean, she's not really
roommate material.
Oh.
What is she, like,
a clean freak, or something?
You ever see that episode of Hoarders
with the woman who kept dead cats?
Of course.
That's Angela?
Yeah, but instead of dead cats,
it was rotisserie chickens.
She would eat off 'em for weeks.
They were all over the place.
You like mint jelly with lamb?
No.
Good.
So, why did you leave?
Isn't that what you wanted?
I mean...
why else would you do
something this crazy?
Are you mad?
I was, at first,
but then I thought about it, and...
No one's ever really needed me before.
No one's ever needed me, either.
Oh, um...
You got any cumin?
Uh...
Does taco seasoning count?
It's close enough.
Also, it's so nice to have my bucket back.
Thank you.
(SIGHS)
NICK: This is older than me.
Well, I figure it's what
fancy politicians drink.
(CHUCKLES)
Thank you.
So, how does it feel
being Tax ID number 49-3451299?
Overwhelming.
(CHUCKLES)
Why is that?
There's a lot more people to answer to.
Based on the other night,
I think you handled it pretty well.
What was the vote?
Four-three.
Close.
There's always someone to convince.
Not if you had my vote.
You serious?
You think a strip club owner has a shot?
(CHUCKLES)
You're of the people.
I'll need lots of advice.
(NICK CHUCKLES)
What changed your mind?
(MOODY POP SONG PLAYING)
You.
Wait, Beth.
Let's crack this open.
Ah, I haven't earned it yet.
You're gonna win.
Share it with someone who already has.
Pour that out.