ANNIE: Previously on Good Girls...
BETH: Dear Dean, I'm gonna tell you
exactly what to do and how fo do It.
RUBY: I know how
we're gonna wash that money.
We're robbing Stan.
ANNIE: It's an armored truck.
Swap fake for real.
Yo, Neil!
I can't stop thinking about you.
RUBY: He wants more than dinner.
HENRY: DL Dave, you know, he and I
were, like, all over.
I mean, like, everywhere.
DAVE: You want it to be her?
PHOEBE: Yes.
DAVE: Get something to convince a DA.
Selling hot tubs in my class?
Kahuna Spas would love
to be part of the ride.
DAVE:
He's walking right into it.
That's 'cause he has no idea
what's going on.
I got the account.
That's great!
I also had to give him the books.
OFFICER: Dean Boland,
you're under arrest.
BETH: Dean, I'll explain everything.
DEAN: What am!
under arrest for?
Can I help you?
Yeah, I'm gonna need a refill.
We don't do that.
You do it for Mountain Dew.
It's not the same.
Haven't I seen you at our games before?
BOY: Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Yeah? Suck it!
(LAUGHTER)
You serious with that?
Hey!
Yeah, you're a cheerleader, right?
Can you do something about your friends?
BOY 1: Hey, ass face!
BOY 2: Ooh.
Hey, you dick!
There you go!
BOY 1: Oh, bull's-eye!
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
Yeah, you better keep running!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
(BELL DINGS)
Pigs.
DEAN: Smarter than dogs, right?
Still gross.
Yeah, well, so are my friends.
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
Oh, no.
What?
Every time I hear this song, just really
weird things happen.
Look, I just, I can't be responsible
for anything I might do, okay?
(CHUCKLES)
(MOUTHING)
I want a girl with extensions in her hair
Bamboo earrings, at least two pair
A Fendi bag...
Okay, stop, I need that back.
No, it's okay, don't worry about it.
I got it, look.
(SINGING)
I need an around the way girl
Around the way girl
She's the only one for me
It was Elizabeth, right?
Beth.
Okay, well, I'm Dean.
I Know.
You do?
You're the quarterback.
Yeah, I know.
And don't worry about this.
I got it, okay?
(DOOR BUZZES, OPENS)
Can you hear me?
How'd you sleep?
I didn't.
This was this morning.
Jane went to school full Elsa.
Kenny's in Kalamazoo at his tournament.
Do they know?
Not yet.
And the accounts are frozen, So...
you might be here a minute.
Tell me one thing.
Was he part of it?
Beth.
The whole time?
I love you.
We're finished here.
I'm gonna fix this, okay?
I promise.
How?
(DOOR BUZZES, OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(DOOR OPENS)
That from the minibar?
Mmm-mmm.
Is he talking?
So it's just a coincidence
that you're eating corn nuts
which are now gone
from the corn nuts slot.
You can take it from my room.
Did you get anything out of him?
Not a word.
Get me in there.
What's the point?
You're already getting a new Office.
I am?
Out of the basement.
With a window?
Pack your bags.
Five minutes.
Take the W and call it a day.
He's protecting her.
Why would he do that?
'Cause he has no idea
what she's gotten into.
They've been married for 20 years.
So have you.
What's that?
Your wife has no idea
who you've gotten into.
But I do.
Because he's a real chatty Cathy.
Are you really doing this?
Just give me five minutes alone.
I didn't know you had it in you.
But I know everything that's--
All right, all right, all right, enough.
You got your five minutes.
Leave the money for the corn nuts
on top of the minibar.
Mmm-hmm.
(INHALES, EXHALES DEEPLY)
BETH: So I'm sure
you all have a lot of questions,
and I'm going to do my very best
to answer each and every one of them.
Where's Dean at?
He is at a hot tub conference.
A very important one.
Are we in trouble?
No, no, no, no.
Just a little misunderstanding...
with our taxes.
Can we FaceTime him?
Ooh.
There's not real good reception in, um...
Uh, North Pole.
Yeah.
He's with Santa?
So if you all just hang tight,
we will have this all cleared up,
and we'll get back to work in a jiffy.
Does this count as vacation days?
Think of it like, uh, a Snow day.
Just enjoy yourself.
Take a little me time.
But you're still paying us, right?
I miss Gayle.
DANNY: When's he coming back?
Uh, as soon as it's over.
When's that?
When he's done.
Who wants another slice?
He really screwed the pooch, huh?
Anything I can do to help my homie,
let me know.
JANE: Where is our mom?
She's, um, helping your dad.
I need a loan.
For what?
Bail.
Yeah, that's not my thing.
I need to get him out.
Nah. You need a fall guy
if you're ever trying
to make money again.
It's not his fault.
I told you to be smart, right?
I was.
Then how'd they get your books?
He didn't know.
Why, he's the perfect fall guy.
He didn't do anything!
That's what makes it beautiful.
Got nothing to say.
Look, they'll cut a deal.
Three years, Club Fed.
What about my kids?
Visitation.
What about me?
Your boy will come back
in better shape than when he went in.
You might even want to hit it again.
There's gotta be a way to get him out!
Do the crime, do the time.
But nothing ever sticks to you.
Yeah, I got luck on my side.
Maybe you do, too.
What's that mean?
Sink that eight ball.
Corner pocket, I'll cover his bail.
I don't play pool.
And I don't do loans.
(SIGHS)
Like that?
Yeah, just like that.
Just hit it straight, okay?
Ha! I did it!
Lucky shot.
No, a deal is a deal.
Yeah, you're right.
Take it out of the cut you owe me.
The place is swarming
with secret service agents.
So?
So I can't wash,
and I definitely can't print.
We're shut down.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
That's why you need a fall guy.
Mom bootcamp.
That's what you get for exercising.
The bitch made me do her nails.
Don't they have to tell you
if they're cops?
Only if you ask.
That's not a real thing,
and she's secret service.
How's Deansie holding up?
He doesn't have his mouth guard
or his sleep apnea machine,
and his cellmate is in
for trying to set a guy on fire.
That good, huh?
Ugh, pink flavor.
He can't be my fall guy.
Well, it can't be you.
It should.
You have four kids.
So does he.
Ugh, orange flavor.
Stop biting into all of them.
What kinda psycho
gets somebody fruit chocolates?
A hitman.
The man is sending you chocolate now?
I mean, kinda.
He wants me to go on a job with him.
Where?
Fiji.
(SCOFFS) Maybe if these were caramels.
I wish he'd just put a bullet in me.
At this point, I think you're looking
at a little pickle tickle.
What am I gonna do?
Over the pants, real fast.
About Dean.
We'll figure something out.
It's either him or me.
Is it?
Isn't it?
On First 48, people call in all the time
to confess to crimes they didn't commit.
Why would anyone do that?
I don't Know, weirdo loners
with nothing to lose.
Maybe being convicted
gives them some purpose.
Huh.
Swimming, tennis,
art classes.
What kinda resort is this?
Not a resort exactly.
(LOUD BANG)
EVAN: Damn it!
Can you take that upstairs?
I mixed the trapezoid up
with the rectangle again.
I'm conducting business.
Your aunt's just gonna
send me right back down.
She's napping.
You're allowed in the parlor till 4:30.
(SIGHS)
It's my room too.
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
So what's the dillio?
Well, think of it as a fresh start.
We would pay off all your credit card debt
and throw in 100 grand for your trouble.
Paid in installments.
Why would you do that for me?
Well, you'd actually be doing it for me.
It's a jail?
With benefits!
Except for the part where you can't leave.
But I hear the library is exquisite.
I Know this is a huge ask,
but you're the one who said
you wanted to help out your homie.
You wanna pay me more money
than I've ever made in my entire life
to have my own room,
unlimited TV privileges,
and vegan-friendly meals
on an all-male campus?
What's the shower situation?
Um, probably group.
Well, how do we get this party started?
Um... just confess I guess, right?
(CHUCKLES)
Well, I...
I think he might actually need
to do more than that.
ANNIE: Wait.
What do you mean?
Well, they have Dean's name
on all the accounts,
so he may need to
get caught with something way worse,
you know, just to make Sure.
(OBJECT CLATTERING)
EVAN: Damn it!
Chillax, man!
You're gonna wake my aunt!
Remember when calculators
used to take double A?
Remember when our calculators
were our brain?
Ugh.
This is Supposed to be
the smart school, right?
Maybe they're doing bigger math.
Yeah, but who just has
a lithium ion 2032
just laying around?
A physicist? Cyborg?
Can I ask you something?
Yeah.
I need to borrow some money.
(SIGHS) Okay.
It's more than you got on you.
What's going on?
And I'm gonna need it in ones.
I'm not stealing from the club.
It's for Dean.
Why do you need all ones?
To get him out of it.
Beth put you up to this.
I offered.
Why?
Because when you were in jail,
she did the same for you.
(SIGHS)
Think there's one of those
batteries in my watch.
Stan, toss me the aloe.
Okay.
Oh, I think Mindy used it all.
I got pole burn bad.
How about some ice?
(MUSIC PLAYING IN THE DISTANCE)
That's my song.
Eesh, take it easy out there.
Thanks, Stanimal.
(SONG PLAYING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
(DIGITAL BEEPS)
(BEEPS)
GENE: Hey, buddy.
Yo, Gene.
Got a sec?
Uh, yeah, man, I was just about
to head back out to the floor.
George'll cover you.
Have a seat.
All right, I can always make
time for the boss.
So what that wife of yours
make you for lunch today, huh?
(CHUCKLES)
Uh, what was it today? Uh...
Penne pasta with those
little green balls.
Peas?
No, not those.
The other ones, uh...
Capers?
Yep, there it is, those things.
She treats you pretty good, huh?
Yeah, man.
She's the best.
We treat you okay?
Uh, yeah.
You happy here?
Hey, man, listen.
I'm glad to have the job, you know?
Good to hear, buddy.
Yeah.
So there's no reason
you'd be upset with me.
What?
You'd tell me if you were
having any problems.
For sure.
I got your back.
Hundred percent.
You got mine?
'Cause something's not adding up here,
you know?
A few weeks ago,
that thing with the bank truck burning up.
Oh, yeah, that was crazy.
Yeah, crazy.
Crazy how much it cost me.
But, uh, doesn't insurance
cover that stuff for--
I have to keep them in the champagne room
a little longer.
(LAUGHING)
Yeah, that's why you the king, man.
Can't have it happen again, though.
Not on my watch.
I hear you loud and clear.
All right.
Oh, and whenever's good for you,
I would love to hear
about them private parties
you've been running
behind my back with my girls.
Now's good.
This is Currency.
Like, top dollar.
You could trade it for anything...
supplies, TV time,
protection.
Who are you?
I Know your wife.
(SCOFFS) I want a lawyer here.
Chill, I just gave you a bunch of ramen.
I had this friend in high school.
Super cool.
Captain of the cheerleading squad.
Hmm.
Always had the newest jeans.
The most expensive makeup.
Everyone wanted to be her,
including me.
She threw the best parties,
and I would bring the wine coolers.
I was, like, in.
We'd go to the movies, the mall.
We were besties before people
used the word "besties."
And then my parents took away my fake ID,
and she stopped calling me back.
What's your point?
Women like your wife,
they use people,
and when they're done,
they throw them in the trash.
So you don't know my wife.
I Know the wrong person
is sitting across from me right now.
So what?
I just need something on her.
Without it, you're gonna need
a lot more of these.
So what's it gonna be, Mr. Boland?
(VIDEO GAME BEEPING)
DEAN: Hey.
Is your sister home?
Doesn't wanna see you.
Did you give her any of my messages?
Hates your guts.
She said that?
Thinks you're a total loser,
regrets ever looking at your ugly face,
and wishes you'd just die.
Hm.
Brutal.
Yeah, so can I just go talk to her?
What's it worth to you?
Wow.
Okay.
All right, fine.
Four bucks?
That's all I got.
You can owe me.
Deansie's here!
No one calls me that.
Annie.
Mom needs you.
What are you doing here?
I called you, like, five times.
I've been busy.
You haven't been at any of the games.
I got a lot going on.
I thought we were cool.
We are.
'Cause if I'm way off, it's totally okay.
It's not that.
I don't wanna look like a dick, you know?
I can't find her meds.
Be right there.
(SIGHS)
It's not you.
Gotcha. So it's definitely me then.
It's not either of us.
It's okay.
Don't worry about it.
I was gonna ask you to prom,
but it's all good.
You were?
I don't wanna put any pressure on you.
I'd love to go.
Uh, okay.
Cool.
Yeah.
(IMITATES BARFING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Mrs. Boland?
He doesn't wanna see you.
Turns out if you make a fart noise
with every math problem
he gets right, he can focus.
Got your bills.
How'd it go?
Piece of cake.
I'm gonna pay you back.
It's just gonna take a second.
No rush.
Really?
You good?
Just thirsty.
At a certain point,
you don't really need the glass, do you?
Had a day.
ANNIE: He'll get over it.
What if he doesn't?
You've done way worse.
I'm a monster.
I mean, he stuck around
after you bone surfed
the guy who shot him.
The kind that climbs skyscrapers
and destroys cities.
Yeah, well, at least your kids
are still talking to you.
Because they don't know.
Ben won't even look at me.
Maybe they've all just had enough of us.
(SIGHS)
God, we are monsters.
(DOOR OPENS)
RUBY: Incoming.
Last dance, ladies.
Let's make it a good one.
Not too good.
(MOODY POP MUSIC PLAYING)
ERIC: You sure about this?
It'll work.
Looks legit.
It's not.
Our worst batch yet.
Your one way ticket to Shangri-La.
(SIGHS)
All right.
See you hotties on the other side.
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
ERIC: I'd like to open a new account.
WOMAN: Certainly, sir.
I'm just gonna need you
to fill out a few forms
and a valid ID.
Thank you.
Um, just to let you know,
we do require a minimum balance of $50.
Oh, that won't be a problem.
(GRUNTS)
Uh, what are you doing?
Giving you 100,000 smackaroos to babysit.
Um, anything over ten grand
we have to report to the IRS.
Ooh. That'll be a problem.
Thought it might be.
(CHUCKLES)
So how about we do ten grand
in ten different accounts?
Um, we don't do that here, sir.
Okay, okay.
Nine grand in nine different accounts,
and, uh...
you keep this for yourself.
Is there a problem here?
Uh, yes, there is.
I'm being profiled.
Excuse me?
She won't take my hard-earned money.
How is that profiling?
Mustache.
That's not a thing.
Sir, we're a family-owned bank.
Then take my money, it's good.
We really don't want any trouble.
Go ahead.
Test it yourself.
Why would we need to do that?
Been in there a while.
Can we please just go?
No, I wanna watch.
Well, I don't.
I feel bad enough as it is.
Shh. Listen.
(SIREN WAILING IN THE DISTANCE)
Here we go.
(TIRES SCREECH)
Okay, show 'em the money.
Ooh, oon.
It is on.
RUBY: Oh, boy, he is getting worked.
Was that really necessary?
ANNIE: Fell for the honeypot.
Okay, what are they doing now?
All right.
ERIC: What?
Uh-oh.
ERIC: I go in the back.
Hey, I go in the back.
Hey. Guys.
What the hell?
What happened?
I think I got robbed.
RUBY: By cops?
(SIGHS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
NURSE: She's stable now.
We had to sedate her to pump her stomach.
She'll be out for a while.
Any other family I should notify?
It's just me and my sister.
Your mom's gonna be okay.
I went to pick you up.
(GASPS)
Oh, God.
What'd she say?
That you didn't wanna go.
At least not with me, 'cause...
I'm the dumbest, ugliest
tool that's ever lived.
I'm gonna kill her.
But 40 bucks later, and here I am.
You didn't have to come.
Got you something.
You look great, by the way.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
So do you.
(SCOFFS) Yeah, I know.
(LAUGHS)
(SIGHS)
Um, do you want anything
from the vending machine?
No.
Okay, good, 'cause...
your little sister took all my money.
(LAUGHS)
Here's a thought.
Oh, boy.
I go right back in there,
grab that guard's gun,
shoot up the place.
Why?
Get their attention.
So then they put you
in jail with Dean and not instead of.
Oh.
Plan C...
Please, no.
Try a different bank.
And deposit what?
Those crooked cops
took everything we made.
Hey, maybe they'll realize it's fake,
and they'll come back and nab him.
No, they didn't even look at my ID.
ANNIE: Okay.
What's plan C?
Track those guys down.
The cops?
We pull in front of their
cruiser, jam on the brakes.
(IMITATES BRAKES SCREECHING)
And they slam into us.
Bam! Airbags go off.
Pssh!
We hop out, shatter their window.
(IMITATES GLASS SHATTERING)
Get the keys to the trunk.
Make it stop.
How can it possibly be
this difficult to get you arrested?
'Cause I'm invisible.
What do you mean?
I've been that way my whole life.
Smack in the middle of nine kids,
you get used to being left in a hot car.
That's terrible.
It all Kinda changed for me
when the D-Man got hired.
Brought me to lunch
with the rest of the crew.
Called me Eric.
What'd everybody else call you?
Scott.
I see that.
He's got a Scott vibe.
Mmm-hmm.
Anyway, lunch becomes work drinks,
and next thing you know,
I'm finally a real person.
Oh, they don't make them
like Dean Boland anymore.
But I don't need to tell you that.
I Know.
Plan D...
No more plans, Eric.
RUBY: Thank Jesus.
What do you want me to do?
Nothing.
(DOOR OPENS)
Hey. I made breakfast for dinner.
I'm not hungry.
What are you doing?
You are gonna eat this.
Can I go to the bathroom?
You love breakfast for dinner.
I ate at Mark's house!
Oh, a lacrosse buddy?
What do you want?
I want you to talk me
like a normal person.
You're not a normal person.
Then talk to me like you want me to be
your mom again, like--
I don't even know what that means.
Like, you don't hate me so much.
(SIGHS)
'Cause, you know,
if you...
if you're unhappy here...
you could always stay at your dad's more.
You think I hate you?
You haven't talked to me
in, like, three days.
It doesn't mean I hate you.
Okay.
I love breakfast for dinner.
Me, too.
Makes sense though.
Hmm.
Just for, like, practice
and school and stuff.
What?
Staying with Dad more.
Oh, yeah?
Nancy would never go for it though.
She's, like, so OCD with Dakota.
I could talk to her.
Really?
Why not?
I can just come back
for some of the weekends.
If that's what you want, yeah.
Not that I want it.
It would just save a lot
of time going back and forth.
Cool.
I still gotta pee.
Yes.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(CHILDREN CHATTERING)
No classes today?
I don't really teach boot camp.
I don't really sell hot tubs.
Yeah, I know.
Mommy!
Look how high I'm going!
Wow!
Like an astronaut!
It all started about a year ago.
I robbed a grocery store.
It was supposed to be one and done.
Don't you want to record this
or something?
It doesn't matter.
Why?
Your husband pled guilty today.
Mommy!
Mommy, watch me!
Jesus!
Your elderly neighbor was getting curious
the longer I stood at your door.
Why does everyone think
they can just let themselves
in to my house?
These things are extremely easy to find
once you know what you're looking for.
I'd offer you a drink, but...
All set.
I can't go to Fiji with you.
Why not?
Huts over the water,
looking at the fish
while you sip your cocktail,
nothing but privacy.
I'm in a little bit of trouble right now.
Perfect time for an escape.
And I have kids.
Happy to make arrangements
for them as well.
I hear your husband's gonna
be tied up for a while.
Put down your tea.
Pardon me?
Get naked, come on.
What?
Let's go!
Now?
Why, you need a pill?
'Cause I've gotta pick up my kids soon.
I think there's been a misunderstanding.
Really?
Because you have made it very clear
that this is exactly what I need to do.
Not like this.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Was I supposed to enjoy it?
Maybe fall in love with you?
End up on some remote island
So you can live out
your twisted midlife crisis?
I thought you wanted...
more.
From you?
From your life.
Oh, and I need a man to do that?
What do you want?
To be nothing like you.
A little late for that.
Why?
You hired me, remember?
Then why don't you pull up
your pants like a big boy
and do your job?
Well.
Seems I read this all wrong.
I'll fulfill our contract
when I get back.
Thank you.
Hide this under a real rock.
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(CELL PHONE BUZZES)
'Sup, Hill?
Hey, can you grab me
some of that lemon pepper
on your way home?
Mmm, might be a little late tonight, baby.
Aren't you lunch shift today?
Yeah, boss got me doing some extra.
Okay. Should I do Cajun?
That sounds good.
All right, I'll throw
your plate in the oven.
Hug those animals for me.
Everything okay?
Yeah, just in the middle of something.
All right, boo.
Okay, see you later, baby.
What's for dinner?
(SIGHS) Chicken.
Nice.
(DOG BARKING DISTANTLY)
GENE: This won't take long.
So what's this cat look like, man?
He's a little bitch.
He alone?
Nah, he lives with his brother.
And what's he look like?
Big bitch.
STAN: What if they don't
give me the money?
GENE: Don't come out till they do.
(SIGHS)
I got a family, man.
Should've thought about that
before you messed with mine.
Car on or off?
Put on my Yacht Rock playlist.
(TURNS ON STEREO)
(MELLOW ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
I miss Daddy.
Me, too.
Does he miss us?
Always.
Why won't he call us back?
Daddy's not at a conference.
Where is he?
Hil Hi!
I love your pigtails!
Did you do them yourself?
No, Mommy did them.
Is there a fence, and if you
touch it, will it zap you?
What's it like in there?
EMMA: Are they nice?
I've made some pretty good friends.
I get my own room.
Do you get ice cream when you're done?
DEAN: As much ice cream
as you could ever possibly eat.
Girl, girl, you're so hard on me
Girl, girl, when you talk to me
You tell me lies and you set me free
Take me by the hand
Then try to understand
You can't make it alone
No, no
Oh, oh, oh
Come to the dark with your fate
All at once, you're in another place
You can't make it alone
No, no