BETH: Previously on Good Girls...
You ever heard of "The System"?
That's like a pyramid thing, right?
A multi-level opportunity.
I want to pull Ben out of St. Anne's.
ANNIE: I am asking you for a favor here.
I don't want to be your favor anymore.
What am I being arrested for?
Trafficking a class one
controlled substance.
WOMAN: How'd you guys get
the wholesale hook-up?
He would be upset if I told you.
How'd we do?
You mean how did I do?
Well, it looks
like you did just fine on your own.
STAN: Beth can't be a part of this.
She does whatever she wants
whenever she wants.
We're gonna give them the broken toy.
So, what you're saying is we're
framing someone?
Who the hell's that?
D.C. is not gonna keep
the tab going much longer.
Remember when I asked you to get a juice?
You want to get a juice,
let's go get a damn juice.
Just pick a side.
BETH: You need us, you need
all of us.
Not all of you.
(GUNSHOTS)
Ringside seats, huh?
How'd you get these?
Called in a favor.
You don't find it coincidental?
What's that?
That both the bullets
in Lucy's head match the ones
in the other bodies.
I don't know any Lucy.
BETH: We got him.
DAVE: Where is he?
GUARD: He walked.
RIO: So what do we do about her?
That's why you got me, brother.
(COSMIC WHEELS PLAYING)
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
Another bad dream?
Banana or blueberry?
Just plain.
Boring.
Which one was it?
Want juice?
Zombies?
Tornados?
I made coffee, too.
Kidnappers?
(TOAST POPS UP)
They came in through the basement.
I lock the door every night.
They kicked it in.
I'd wake up.
But you don't when that's out.
(SIGHS)
Nothing's gonna happen to you, okay?
How do you know?
'Cause I'm your dad.
Can we get an alarm?
Don't need to.
Jenny got one.
Her dad's an accountant.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Hey.
Don't burn my pancakes.
Councilman.
Got a minute?
Always, please.
CHEF: Order up.
(GRUNTS)
Could we get some more
of these wasabi things?
There's a charge for refills.
Oh. No, no, no.
There's still some dust left.
Is everyone a criminal in this city?
Maybe you should slow down.
You can't get drunk off these things.
We're not on vacation.
Not anymore.
Mm. Don't look.
Why did you look?
To see what I wasn't Supposed to look at.
What happened to our meeting?
Would you like one?
Uncle Sam is treating.
I want to know what's going on.
D.C. pulled the plug.
Why?
Clearly, he's got someone on the inside.
I can still get him.
First night I get here,
I'm about to hit the hay, right?
I see a spider
in the bed.
Damn thing runs away
under the sheets before I can get him.
I get my phone out,
I rip the place apart. Nothing.
But that little bastard,
he's under there,
somewhere, hiding, waiting.
You think I'm ever gonna get back
into that bed again?
Where have you been sleeping?
Bathtub.
It's just not safe.
What about my deal?
Drink.
What about my husband?
RUBY: What about our money?
Drink.
There goes Ben's school.
Stan's out of work.
Since when?
Since we put away his boss.
Well, what happened to the girls?
Heaven and Cinnamon went back to Arby's.
Oy.
Dean's gonna go to jail.
They can't do that.
Can't they?
We have to get to Nevada.
How?
They bailed on us.
Well, then we have to get there ourselves.
Are we talking about
"Nevada" Nevada?
It's a metaphor.
ANNIE: Just because I'm not remembering
Nevada's
exact extradition laws,
but if this is about Deansie...
Mexico, Thailand, wherever.
Who's gonna foot those moving costs?
You still have those bags?
STAN: What you doing?
I'm getting these babies
ready for market.
Why?
What do you mean why?
We don't owe Gene anymore.
We still got bills.
Oh,
some of the girls were
talking about doing private parties.
Can't make a living
being a freelance heavy.
Hmm.
Yeah, all right, I hear you.
I guess we can move a few of these.
Gotta move more than a few.
It's only two of us.
Not necessarily.
No.
We need help.
She helped you.
No.
Luck didn't lock Gene up.
We owe her, Stanley.
Hey.
How was the game?
Do we have any razor blades?
That bad, huh?
DIY screen repair.
Step two, scrape off excess.
Did you score?
I didn't play.
What? Who did they put in? Brad?
Don't know.
Ugh.
The coach is, like, so in love with him.
I'm gonna quit.
What?
I want to sell all my gear.
Why?
To pay for karate.
What are you talking about?
I Know I have to go back to my old school.
(SIGHS)
I'm so sorry, Bubba.
It's okay.
Promise?
I still follow some friends from there.
Okay.
And it's closer.
I can bike.
Yeah, that's true.
Classes are way easier, too.
You'll, like, totally be valedictorian.
But...
don't sell all your gear just yet, okay?
They don't have Lacrosse.
I Know but we could find you a club team.
I'm gonna need the karate anyway.
Why?
Last time I was there,
I wasn't Ben.
DEAN: So Vance says
it's all about your base.
I build up enough contacts here,
we'll have a little wiggle room
to grow my business once we get to Nevada.
That sounds like a plan.
Yeah, sol had Carlene send me
all our old contacts
from Boland Motors and Bubbles.
That's smart.
Yeah.
What?
Well,
I don't want to jinx it.
Oh, come on.
I just feel like this time...
we got a real chance.
EMMA: Mom.
Mom, I gotta poop.
(CHUCKLES)
Il run her home.
Oh, wait.
Are you sure you didn't want to
hot bag it in the bushes?
Yes, I'm positive.
Come on, kid.
Not a great time.
I'll make it quick then.
Can we do this some place else?
Oh, you haven't told him our good news?
I don't think he'll take it that way.
(CHUCKLES)
I need you to run a little errand for me.
They are never little.
Get me my funny money back.
How am I supposed to do that?
Ask nicely.
The cops?
(SCOFFS) Not them.
They're your crew.
They're leaving.
Never a good time, is it?
I was just thinking, before you leave,
we could, um,
finally get that green juice.
I can even bring it to
the hotel if that's easier.
I don't Know if you got
my text, but, um...
call me. Okay, bye.
How do you even know the money's there?
I don't.
So, wait, you're just gonna get her
hopped up on green juice?
Could always roofie her.
Just to loosen her up, get her talking.
You know what a little errand is?
Picking up the dry cleaning,
dropping off a dog
at the groomer, getting milk.
Breaking into a hotel room
to steal federal evidence
is a kamikaze mission.
It's suicide.
That is what kamikaze Is.
That's exactly why we have to
get out of this town.
STAN: Y'all ready?
Squad up, bitches.
It's just something we say.
STAN: Mm-hmm.
Oh. Go ahead.
Oh, no.
You take it.
It's your house.
It's my bags.
Oh, boy.
(BETH SIGHS)
So, last time...
I was thinking...
(SIGHS)
Last time we hit the third grade,
now we do fourth.
This way, we don't repeat parents.
Also, let's use a different house,
because we got new prospects.
Oh.
What about Irish twins?
What about 'em?
Same parent could have
a kid in third grade
and in fourth grade.
Not an issue.
Making sure.
So I figured that we'd...
break this down into shifts,
maybe over a few days.
And would that be
the most bang for our buck?
Um, I guess we could
double up in one day.
I mean the whole school thing.
(CHUCKLES) I mean, if it ain't broke...
Okay.
I mean, if you see a problem...
No, no, no.
This should work.
She sees a problem.
No, not necessarily.
Phew. Real big one.
Just a little snag.
Hey, I'm all ears.
It's kind of risky.
Here we go.
Why?
Well, who's on your mom chain right now?
Bunch of people.
And how many fourth grade moms
are on there?
Um...
not a lot.
What's your point?
Moms talk, a lot.
Mm-hmm.
And it only takes one
to smell a knock-off.
Or it's safer.
How's that?
If someone finds out,
then we can get ahead of it
because we're on that mom chain.
Or...
they start another mom chain,
so they can talk about you
behind your back.
How many mom chains are you on, babe?
Not a lot.
And then Harry gets kicked out of school.
Come on now.
And we're all in cuffs.
That's never gonna happen.
Why take the chance?
You know what?
I'm just gonna shut up.
(CHUCKLES)
Stan.
You got a better idea?
It's whatever you want to do.
She's got a better idea.
(MUSIC STOPS)
MAN: What? Hey.
What the... Come on.
(BETH CLEARS THROAT)
MAN: What...
what the hell?
Who are you?
We are your halftime show.
Jesus.
Yeah, uh,
I think we'll stick with the main event.
If you want to see their goods,
you're gonna have to buy ours.
We got all the brands right here.
So bust out that tip money, gentlemen.
We already paid for this party.
Yeah.
No, you paid to get this party started.
You can't do this.
Oh, but we are.
(MAN SCOFFS) Come on.
What are we gonna do with
a bunch of purses?
Give them to your wives.
Or your mistresses, or your girlfriends.
We really don't care.
All right, how much?
Start at 2 grand.
What?
Who carries that kind of cash?
Well, you guys always manage to find it
for the champagne room, don't you?
We accept all major credit cards,
including Venmo and Apple Pay.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold up. No.
Come on over.
Grab them while they're hot.
No, no. What are you doing?
I need to see those goods.
Guys, put your money away.
Girls, put your clothes on.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, it's pay to play, man.
The only thing we're paying for
is some high-class ass.
(SIGHS)
Um...
Sorry.
Okay, thanks.
Maybe next time there won't be a cop.
(SIGHS)
Fourth grade moms
would have been way riskier.
Are you kidding me?
Yeah, come on, man.
It's not that great.
Seriously, how many cars
do you sell in a month?
Three hundred?
Three hundred.
(CHUCKLES)
That's more than we'd sell in a quarter.
Well, I learned from the best.
Aww. You always had the "It" factor.
Nobody would have ever noticed
if you hadn't
pulled me up to the big leagues.
Best porter we ever had.
(CHUCKLES)
Okay, you ready?
Hydrator, toner, tightener.
This stuff right here.
It's great for the circles,
the dark circles under your eyes.
I'll take one of each, man.
Wait. You don't want
me to do the rest of my spiel?
Nah, no need to.
Yeah, I mean, you'll see, I mean, it's...
it's really...
it's really solid stuff.
If you Say so, I am in.
And,
when you respond the way I Know you will,
we can even talk about
other opportunities.
I'm pretty busy right now.
No, I know, I Know.
I'm just saying, like,
ina slow month, it's an easy way
to put a little extra cash in your pocket.
Pyramid schemes aren't really my thing.
It's more of a...
you know, community of men
supporting each other.
You ever think
about coming back on the lot?
Uh...
Nah, it's not...
it's not my bag anymore.
Friend of mine over at, um,
Southfield Volvo
said they're losing
one of their best sales guys.
Southfield, huh?
Mm-hmm.
I can put in a word.
I'm my own boss now.
Just get lunch with the guy,
feel it out.
(BEEPING)
You know what?
Um, actually,
I can just do all this
for you. You don't...
you don't need...
(BEEPING)
That your phone?
Yeah, I think it's...
I think it's, uh...
Out of batteries.
I should really get going.
(BEEPING)
Also need a copy of the arrest file.
MAN: Should be there.
It's not.
Hang on.
Don't see it.
Well, maybe they threw it out
when they threw out my case.
No, no, here we go.
Hmm.
Sign the release.
That it?
Why'd they throw out your case?
Well, if I knew that,
I wouldn't be going home.
Pays to have friends in high places, huh?
Hey, Shel.
I'm not sharing this.
I need something from evidence.
She was someone's daughter.
Rather give you half my sandwich.
You're the best.
CHEF: Order up.
This is a little embarrassing.
Hit me.
You got kids?
Mm-mmm. Married to the city.
An.
My daughter, she's nine.
She's a big MMA fan.
Mm. Who's her favorite?
(SCOFFS)
Anyone who kicks ass.
The whole girl power thing.
Right. Right, right, right.
Yeah.
So what can I do for you?
WAITRESS:
There you go.
Mm.
Heard you're the ticket guy.
How's that?
Word is you got the hook-up for
all the best fights.
(CHUCKLES) Says who?
(CHUCKLES)
Can't be humble on Instagram.
Office seats.
Hook a guy up?
Those are usually reserved for donors,
Make-A-Wish kids, you know.
What about murderers?
I don't know anything about this.
How'd they end up with a gang banger
tied to a homicide?
I guess, maybe they scalped them.
One of the cancer kids?
Mm.
Sorry, what was your precinct?
Fourteen.
Mm.
Let me see what I can do
for your daughter.
Appreciate that.
Yeah.
Have a good day, Officer.
You too.
And I've been using
the same shampoo bottle
for, like, a year.
Just add water and shake.
And I've never bought ketchup
or soy sauce,
I have a whole drawer
dedicated to freebies.
And I always order off the kid's menu.
No doubt about it.
You're poor.
Yes.
Maybe the poorest I've ever seen.
Thank you.
But we can't grant you
financial aid.
Have you gotten to the part yet
where we lived off a deer
for an entire winter?
The problem is your drug charge.
(SIGHS)
I can explain.
That was because a man tried to rape me,
and when I wouldn't let him rape me...
It's just school policy.
The thing is,
Ben loves this school.
We love Ben.
Ben loves this school
so much that he's, like,
one of those kids
that you see on a brochure,
that you're sure has to be an actor
because they're so happy.
But actually, Ben is so happy at school.
What about Ben's father?
Isn't there any other way?
Do you have a boyfriend?
Domestic partner?
Okay, well, now you're just
rubbing it in.
(SIGHS)
Is there anyone you
get naked with regularly?
That counts?
If they share your address.
Ooh.
(SIGHS) Jesus.
I brought bagels.
Man, DWP was jackhammering all night.
You want everything or poppy?
I gave you a house key?
Oh, I used the spare.
(SIGHS)
It's been a while.
Yeah, I got...
Sorry, So busy...
Could have called.
I lost my phone.
Still liked my TikToks.
Hey, question.
You don't have any kind of like...
like a record
or anything like that, right?
Huh?
You know, like,
drug charges or felonies...
(SIGHS)
What do you want?
Nothing.
You only come over
when you need something.
Excuse me
for trying to have a nice breakfast moment
with my...
boyfriend.
Wow.
All right, seriously, why are you here?
Just... Here.
Fill these out, and for the address,
just use mine.
(MUTTERING)
Well, if I do this,
you gotta do something for me.
Yeah, I'm not really ready for
the tattoo thing.
Never come here again.
Okay.
And leave the bagels.
WOMAN: It's like my uniform, you know?
I don't even work out.
Neither do I.
But I still put them
on every morning like it's my job.
That's why I focus on my accessories.
Because I may not feel great in my jeans,
but my bags...
They always look hot.
I! wish I could afford it.
Convince your husband that you need one.
He just sent me on a girls trip
to Chicago.
Ooh, fun.
MAN: Let's go, go, go, come on.
Get your snack.
Move it.
Stop running.
We're not gonna be late, all right?
Hey, hon.
This is Beth.
Her oldest did Ladybug with Olivia.
I feel so bad I didn't remember that.
BETH: Please, it was forever ago.
She's selling these cute bags.
Kim just bought one.
How do you know Kim?
Friend of a friend.
BOY: Mom, where are the nuggets?
In the freezer, where they always are.
BOY: No, they're not.
Excuse me.
What is this?
Never use your real info
when booking strippers.
Do you want to get arrested?
I want you and your friends
to all buy your wives a bag.
Or maybe you're just dumb.
No, dumb would be thinking that
I didn't record everything
the other night.
Hey, babe, we're out of nuggets.
Oh, I wanted to show you one more thing
because I forgot to bring the snakeskin.
Oh, that might be a bit much for me.
Come on, you just
have to channel your inner stripper.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
BETH: Here it is.
So this is from a trunk show
that we did the other night.
Let's just get it.
Babe, these are expensive.
Call it an early birthday present, huh?
Wow.
Someone won the husband lottery, huh?
I so did.
Uh, maybe the other guys' wives
would dig them, huh?
Are you kidding?
They would love them.
I would really appreciate the referrals.
What are all these emojis?
That's everybody paying everybody.
That's confusing.
Okay, click there.
So that's everyone paying you.
See? One emoji.
Is that a middle finger?
You did blackmail him.
(BOTH LAUGH)
Happy hour?
Very happy.
She got the money.
Well, not all of it.
A few guys want to pay in cash
'cause they don't want it on record.
Cool.
(MOUTHING)
Ignore him.
Can somebody read my Bio report?
What's it on?
Cellular organelles.
Yeah, that's all you.
Okay.
You know, I was the queen of
cellular organelles,
back in the day.
Is your account
@themHills?
Yep.
And...
that is your cut.
Must feel good proving me wrong.
Feels better to get the money.
Like that's why you did it.
What's your problem?
You.
Okay, I'm sorry that I...
You could have waited for the next party.
I saved our asses.
No, you went back over there
because your ego couldn't take the hit.
Okay, let's not talk about ego.
Got ignored for so long
in your own home...
Mr. My Bags.
Now all you want to do is matter.
Excuse me?
You use whoever you can
to get whatever you want.
I got you your money.
You got my wife shot.
And that's the least of it.
If you think that I would ever do anything
to hurt her...
I think that you don't think
about anyone but yourself, Beth.
RUBY: Ready to go?
Yeah, let me grab my jacket.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
What are you doing here?
Do you want to have that green juice?
I'm kind of over it.
Good. 'Cause that's why I brought this.
I got work to do.
Is that your version of
"gotta pick up the kids"?
Only mine's real.
I'm not a total bitch.
I only do shots.
Here you go.
All right.
Let me ask you something.
You got a glass?
Uh... your choice.
Mug or sippy cup?
Never mind.
Okay.
What do you know about cars?
I Know what I like.
No, like, how they work,
like, why is a Cadillac good for one guy,
but a BMW is great for someone else?
I was really good at that.
You're a natural.
At cars.
Think I see where this is going.
You guys have been so incredible to me...
When you were little,
what did you want to be?
Easy, astronaut.
Stuntman.
Okay, so?
You didn't know anything about cars.
I didn't know anything about
men's skincare.
I got a better chance
at being an astronaut...
But you have something down here
that you wouldn't have in outer space.
What's that?
This guy.
It's just not for me.
And look, I really hope
that I can still bike
with you and the guys.
Dude, you're my ride or die.
Come on.
Thank you.
'Cause you're mine, so...
You just write me
a check for the product, we're good.
Oh, okay. Um...
so I knew this was coming,
so I boxed it up.
These are just the samples.
That's all you gave me.
When you sign up, you commit to product
for the year.
How much product?
I got a whole garage full for you.
(SCOFFS)
Maybe I'll give it another shot.
You just gotta get your groove.
(CHUCKLES)
What's the deal with local news
these days, anyways?
It's like, what's the point?
Unless you don't have a phone,
because I'm pretty sure
by the time you get home
and it's 11:00 p.m., you've been reading
all about everything
that's been happening all day.
It's kind of like, uh,
when parents send you a meme
after six months,
and you're like,
"Um, that's not funny anymore, guys."
(CHUCKLES)
She was smoking in homeroom.
I Know, but why did you care so much?
It's the principle of the thing.
That's why you're so good at your job.
Secondhand smoke causes lung cancer.
You've always been a professional narc.
Mm. And then she told the whole school
that I got genital warts from my dad.
I told her that in confidence.
Last part was a joke.
Oh.
Oh, come on, you would have done
the same thing to somebody like me.
I honestly probably wouldn't have
even known you.
Mm. Well, definitely wasn't
homecoming queen.
Me either.
Oron prom committee.
Or cheer squad.
Okay, I was cheer squad.
A-ha!
But I was kicked out.
Partying?
Um...
manic depressive mom.
Sucks.
If it makes you feel any better,
I didn't make it to
any of the dances either.
Oh, I went to prom with my dad.
And do not even get me started
on how useless the weather people are.
My husband hates my best friend.
So what I'm learning here is,
you're basically a better person than me.
I'm not so sure about that.
(RAP SONG PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
Don't forget the hook.
Ooh! Oh.
There it is.
What's up?
Now you're the coach?
Used to beat your ass.
(LAUGHS)
When was that?
When we were in diapers?
Well, what's up?
Come teach me something.
It could get ugly.
Good.
Let's see what you got, man.
You good?
Yeah.
Hands like this, right?
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Oh.
Damn.
You pick up some moves
at that Ochoa fight?
Kid kept dropping his hands.
That could get you into trouble.
Or draws 'em in.
(GRUNTS)
What was that knockout like?
Boy got whooped.
Nothing like ringside seats, huh?
Yeah, I could hear his whole nose explode.
How's that?
Come on. Come on. Whoo!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
The kid got cracked.
(GRUNTS)
Yeah. Thing is,
you weren't at that fight, right?
Too busy putting a bullet
in that girl's face.
Sometimes I work weekends, bro.
(RAP SONG CONTINUES)
So...
you were just gonna...
what, keep it to yourself?
It don't concern you, dude.
No, no.
It does.
When a cop ruins my breakfast over it.
I'll buy you some eggs, come on.
Did you do it for her?
Huh?
Don't worry about it.
Oh.
Gangster Rio had to whip it out.
I got it covered.
Show the soccer mom how big it is.
She knows.
(CHUCKLES) Right.
Aww, what's up?
Wore you out already?
No, cousin.
Round two.
All right, come on. Yo?
What's that for?
Doctor.
That was quick.
So there was this electrical line.
Uh-huh.
For the street lights.
Cool.
And it fell.
Can I have that back?
On my house.
On your car.
I was fine because of the whole
rubber tire thing,
but long story short,
it ignited the gas tank.
And you're telling me this because...
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON TV)
(DOOR OPENS)
Hey.
You want the good news or the bad news?
Good.
You can stay at St. Anne's.
How?
Well...
Yo, you're out of Q-tips.
That's my toothbrush.
I'll get you back.
Roomie.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
In case it wasn't clear,
that's the bad news.
So how'd you get it?
Just being myself.
Sometimes it's worth it.
What are you gonna buy?
Something special for you.
How'd you get that?
(CHUCKLES)
Just being myself.
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
(SIGHS)
Monkey?
I thought Mom was picking you up.
You awake?
Mm-hmm.
Never did it for her.
Okay.
I did it for me.
What smells so good?
(SIGHS)
Chef Boyardee.
That Washington?
The Queen.
ANNIE: Ugh.
I hate Canadians.