ANNIE: Previously on Good Girls...
So we wanted to talk to you
about doing some custom work for us.
Casino night.
LUCY: /f it got into the wrong hands,
it's kind of like counterfeit.
So you mean, like, if someone wanted
something special printed
you would draw it?
What's up, ladies?
You cannot finish that plate.
He said he'd let me go...
He won't.
Wait. You need us.
You need all of us.
Not all of you.
(GUNSHOTS)
Hers.
Ugh, ugh.
Take it out, Elizabeth.
That's what we used
to take care of your friend, by the way.
Why?
Incentive.
Why did I touch it?
Why did you touch it?
ANNIE: What if we pay someone
to blow his brains out?
A professional.
So how's a lady like you
get involved with a guy like that?
I was just bored.
HENRY: Third one this month
out of Detroit.
Car paint?
Or nail polish.
It's a woman.
You Know, this bitch is hiding
Ina cave somewhere.
We just got to root her out.
Have you guys seen my phone?
HENRY: Is that hers?
PHOEBE: They got nothing
in their bank accounts.
HENRY: So?
They're making some of the best
fake money I've ever seen.
You don't live a little?
To hitmen.
Good luck and Godspeed.
PHOEBE: No way!
You did my nails.
Oh. Hey.
So, what are you guys celebrating?
You had pizza with your therapist?
He's helping me.
It's like a study buddy.
Before we get started,
I wanted to introduce you to Lila.
LILA: I'll see you at home.
I proposed to Lila a couple nights ago.
We would like to buy your place, Gayle.
Where do you think
we can get that kind of money?
I don't know.
I just don't want him involved again.
Okay.
Hot tubs.
He gets to feel like a man,
and we have a new way to wash our cut.
DEAN:
Welcome to Boland Bubbles.
BETH: When does it get to be mine?
When does what get to be yours?
I made all this happen.
Next time empty the clip.
Pressure pushing down on me
Pressing down on you, no man ask for
Under pressure that burns a building down
Splits a family in two
Puts people on streets
Mm-ba-ba-beh
Dee-day-da, ee-day-da
That's okay
It's the terror of knowing
what the world is about
Watching some good friends screaming...
(SCREAMING)
(DOG BARKING)
TEACHER: I'm gonna color in the first part
of the fraction
and you guys can do the rest.
(FARTS)
(KIDS GIGGLING)
Does someone need to use the restroom?
(FARTS)
(KIDS LAUGHING)
Okay, who's the comedian?
(FARTS)
(KIDS LAUGHING)
Hand it over.
RUBY: Is that silly putty?
TEACHER: Squeeze it.
(PUTTY FARTS)
It's not silly putty.
He hid under my desk last week.
He and his sister
play hide-and-seek at home.
I had the whole school looking for him.
(PUTTY FARTS)
I'm sorry.
We were drawing the SpaceX rocket.
Oh, well, he loves art.
He added testicles.
So...
Don't worry.
We're all over this.
Mmm-hmm. Like the wind.
I'm afraid there's
something deeper at play.
What do you mean?
Have you ever heard of ADHD?
Uh, okay, hold on a minute.
Fart putty is a disorder now?
Yeah, I mean...
(PUTTY FARTS)
Stuff's addictive.
TEACHER:
He treats my classroom
like it's his own YouTube channel.
Yeah, okay, but he's not deficient.
There are 20 other students
that are here to learn.
He loves it.
Okay.
If you're not gonna handle this,
then we might have to take
a different course of action.
Huh?
Like what?
Kick him out of school?
Just have him tested.
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
What about a magician?
BEN: 'Cause I'm turning eight?
Oh, what about the bingo hall?
'Cause I'm turning 80?
Fine, well, you tell me.
What do you want to do?
Nothing.
Nothing?
We're not gonna not
celebrate your birthday.
Birthdays are lame.
Well, I'm trying to un-lame them.
What about just a dance party?
In our living room?
Yeah, we do it all the time.
And, you know, Janet down the hall,
she could DJ.
I mean, we always listen to her music
through the walls anyway.
She plays the organ.
Just... Just send me
your friends' Instas,
and I will slide into their DMs
and I'll plan the whole thing.
All you have to do is show up,
get turnt up
while we celebrate you growing up.
Nancy has a stupid dinner planned.
Oh.
Birthdays just kind of
aren't my thing anymore.
I'm gonna dip.
Later.
(DOOR OPENS, CLOSES)
(SIGHS)
He has no friends.
Um, have you talked to him?
(SCOFFS) Uh, yeah.
About what?
You know, him.
Mmm, of course.
Me?
Of course.
It's a lot of me.
Aha.
It's mostly me.
Mmm.
It's 100% me.
And how is that an issue?
Don't tell me.
This is the part where you want me
to realize out loud
that I'm some kind of narcissist
and I've been ignoring my son.
The out loud part is optional, but...
Perhaps we could talk
about something else.
Your time.
Okay.
What happened to your face?
I shaved.
For her?
For me.
You picked a date for the wedding?
No.
Venue?
Guest list?
Not yet.
Am I invited?
Nope.
Ouch.
Would you want to come?
Nope.
Ouch.
Um...
Is there anything else
you'd like to cover?
What day is it today?
Um...
Tuesday.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
What was yesterday?
Monday.
Tomorrow?
Come on.
Wednesday.
Mmm. (CHUCKLES)
So you do understand the concept of time.
Where my cut at?
I said we were almost open.
Mmm-hmm.
Kind of like being almost pregnant, right?
We have been killing ourselves,
printing money for you seven days a week.
Don't touch that.
It's still wet.
Just a bunch of pretty paper.
You know, you can't just start
selling hot tubs willy-nilly.
The city has rules.
And that's not your problem.
Well, then what is my problem?
It's the school carnival.
Uh, okay.
I'll make cookies.
Oh, um...
So we were thinking more, like,
mini kKnanom chan.
What's that?
The traditional Thai dessert.
"Chan" means "layer."
Why?
To go with the fundraising theme.
"One Night in Bangkok."
It's so cute with the song playing
while the kids ride rickshaws.
(WOMAN GASPS)
WOMAN: Ooh, we should all
wear chut Thais.
Oh, but we'd have to make 'em, though.
You love to sew, right?
(EXHALES)
You didn't forget
about our little incentive program, right?
No, I did not.
Good.
Just trying to keep you motivated.
(WOMEN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Didn't she work with you?
Who?
LAUREN: The girl who
disappeared a few weeks ago.
They just found her body.
What?
They think some gang killed her.
LAUREN: I don't get it.
Who dumps bodies in a graveyard?
WOMAN 1: To hide them on top
of other dead people is super smart.
WOMAN 2: I would be so livid
if there was a dead person...
(CONVERSATION FADES)
WOMAN 1: Beth.
Beth, what's wrong?
I can't see.
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
WOMAN 2: Oh my God, Beth.
DOCTOR: Been under a lot of stress lately?
BETH: Tiny bit.
Her blood pressure's up.
Liver enzymes are elevated,
cortisol levels high.
Your body's telling you to slow down.
Message received.
Join a gym.
(GASPS) It's that bad?
Cut back on coffee, booze...
In the meantime,
try to avoid what's causing
you so much anxiety.
We're on it, Doc.
DOCTOR: Someone will
be in to discharge you.
I got to get my hands on that gun.
ANNIE: Jesus.
My fingerprints are all over it,
and now there's a bullet.
What did the lady just say?
Yeah, I'll go to that mom boot camp
in the park or whatever.
The one that weirdo was talking about?
Well, I'm not giving up the booze.
Where is our hitman?
His appointment girl called me.
He's on a job in South America.
Well, how about
we let that freaky bitch know
that we're gonna put a hit on her hitman
if he doesn't hit our man?
Yeah, why don't you get right on that?
Okay, I'm sorry.
What else makes that gun go away?
If I give him something he really needs.
You're gonna hit baloney town again?
I mean, way to take one for the team.
Not that.
How quickly can we open?
We still need inspections, codes,
new signage.
You're overthinking this.
The health department has to give us
the all-clear on Legionnaires.
The money has run out.
What does that mean?
It means we have
to sell some hot tubs, Dean.
I know. Spas.
What if that can't happen?
Well, then I have to go to him.
Are you serious?
We're running with the shadows
of the night
So baby take my hand It'll be all right
Surrender all your dreams to me tonight
They'll come true in the end
You said Oh, girl, it's a cold world
When you keep it all to yourself
I said, You can't hide on the inside
All the pain you've ever felt
Ransom my heart But baby don't look back
'Cause we got nobody else
We're running with the shadows
of the night
So baby take my hand It'll be all right
Surrender all your dreams to me tonight
They'll come true in the end
Sometimes it feels like
It's all moving way too fast
Use every alibi and word to deny
That love ain't meant to last
You can cry tough baby
It's all right
You can let me down easy But not tonight
We're running with the shadows
of the night
So baby take my hand It'll be all right
Surrender all your dreams to me tonight
They'll come true in the end
(PANTING)
PHOEBE: Feel the burn?
(PANTING) Everywhere.
You're kicking my ass.
That's my job.
STAN: Mmm.
He out?
One song, two books,
and a dissertation on velociraptors.
You think he talks too much?
Um, have you met the boy?
I mean, like, in general.
Kid's a damn chatterbox.
He doesn't lose stuff, does he?
Well, he lost that blue jacket.
But then he found it.
Yeah, but then he lost the hat.
You think he does that occasionally,
often, or very often?
What are you doing?
There's a prelim form to fill out.
Mmm, he doesn't need a test, Ruby.
You heard what she said.
You know what I heard?
That his white teacher
can't tell the difference
between an energetic kid
and a misbehaving Black boy.
What if it's not just that?
And what else would it be?
Us.
What, like, we gave him ADHD?
We dropped the ball.
I thought that was with Sara.
Could be both of them.
Mmm-mmm.
Ain't nothing wrong with him.
And I don't need some tests to tell me
how I'm doing as a father.
Look installation's free.
I'm gonna send my guys over
to your backyard.
They're gonna turn it into paradise.
You're never gonna want to leave.
Welcome to Boland Bubbles,
where we tropic like it's hot.
Hi.
If you have any questions,
I'd be happy to help.
Y'all under new management?
Family-owned and operated.
Looks different.
(CHUCKLES)
Out with the old, in with the new, right?
New paint.
Yeah. And lots of new inventory.
I'm Beth, by the way.
Terry.
Tell me about this bad boy.
Oh, you've got a good eye.
(CHUCKLES)
Um, this is our Insignia X5.
Thirty-five jets, individual seating.
Comes in bronze, walnut and sandstone.
Hmm.
What kind of voltage does she pull?
Uh, standard outlet?
Just plug and play.
Where's the little girl's room?
Got to tinkle.
Uh, just there on the left.
Great turnout, right?
It's crazy.
I'm trying to close an X5.
Nice.
Ooh. Heads up, that was fast.
Well, Terry, you seem
to know your way around a Spa.
So I would love to introduce you
to my husband
and have him walk you through
some of the technical features
and see what you think.
I think you're shut down.
I'm sorry.
I'm a building inspector
with Wayne County.
You folks got yourself
a load of violations.
Painted over your sprinkler heads.
Gonna have to dock you on that.
Got a residential power strip
juicing all your units.
Gotta dock ya.
Centerline of the toilet in your tinkler
is less than 15 inches from this wall.
That's a two-fer, plumbing and ADA.
So what do I gotta do, Dean?
Dock me?
Mmm-hmm.
So that's sprinklers, wiring,
construction, plumbing.
This could take months.
If you're lucky.
Can I get another one
of these for my niece?
Yeah, at the front.
All right, folks,
that's a wrap on Boland Bubbles.
Don't have to go home,
but you can't stay here.
PHOEBE: All right, ladies.
Now pick up those buns.
No slacking. Let's go.
It's like a friends and family discount.
I didn't know y'all were open.
Oh, we're not.
But, you know,
you guys are, like, tastemakers.
I'm telling you,
once you step foot
in a hot and steamy Boland,
we will not be able to keep it a secret.
We just put in a new deck.
Well, you know what goes with a new deck.
Lily just started private school.
We can't afford it.
I'm not even supposed to be selling them.
PHOEBE: Let's keep it going.
I'll work with you.
Less mouth, more ass.
(WHISPERS)
I have brochures.
PHOEBE: You got to breathe!
You want to stop peeing when you sneeze?
BETH: You can just pick 'em up
and pass 'em out at drop-off.
PHOEBE: Tuck your butts.
I'll hook anybody up.
Selling hot tubs in my class?
Sorry.
Do I count as friend and family?
Uh... Yeah, sure.
How low can you go?
I mean pricing.
Oh.
Um...
Lower than my pelvic floor
after four kids.
You take Venmo?
I'll take anything.
Hey.
Where's Ben?
Cleaning the house.
Alone?
Why?
We need to talk about him.
(SIGHS)
It's not cool, right?
He told you?
What do we do?
I don't know.
Nancy thinks we should
make him switch schools.
I mean, maybe she's right.
Over one party?
Huh?
Didn't the cops call you?
What are you talking about?
Ben threw a rager at our house.
Well, where the hell were you?
We were just at Nancy's parents' cabin.
What did you think we were talking about?
That he has no friends.
He had, like, 100 people at our house.
Who?
Sam, Eddie, Janice,
the whole lacrosse team.
I don't know, the usual suspects.
I don't know any of those suspects.
Okay, well, they all
had their shoes on in our house,
and Nancy is losing her mind.
He plays lacrosse?
Yeah. How do you not know that?
How did you know that?
'Cause I bought him the gear.
(SIGHS)
Sorry. Look, you've been really busy.
That's not why.
We just know all the parents
around the neighborhood and stuff.
And lacrosse.
Don't go there.
Already there.
He just knows
you wouldn't really be into it.
What? His whole new secret fancy life?
Well, he's got a game
next weekend if you want to come.
You could meet all the usual suspects.
Can I borrow something
from Nancy to wear?
No, your boobs are too big.
(CHUCKLES)
We would love for you
to take another look at our facility.
You couldn't have possibly
fixed everything that fast.
Well, we came up
with some creative solutions.
Well, I've been doing this for 19 years.
And believe me, I've seen it all.
Have you seen this?
TERRY: Looks the same.
Are you trying to waste my time?
Um, we are trying to make it
worth your while.
DEAN: (CLEARS THROAT)
Yes, uh...
We Know how, uh, how tricky wiring can be.
So please just let us know
if there's anything you'd like us to do.
And, obviously, we can't knock down
the whole tinkler,
so we got a new toilet.
DEAN: We haven't installed it yet.
What do you, uh...
What do you think?
Did we pass?
(SIGHS)
Buy you a drink?
I own the place.
Why don't you buy me one then?
Why would I do that?
Boland Bubbles is in business.
That's what he's calling it?
Yeah, I think it's cute.
Yeah. Real panty-dropper.
Yeah, well, it's fully operational.
Your money is being cleaned,
laundered, folded and pressed as we speak.
Um, a tequila for the chief.
Top shelf.
And, um...
Do you have anything
without alcohol or caffeine?
Just bourbon, neat.
Could be more excited.
Ain't always about you, is it?
It's what you wanted.
You know what?
I got other stuff on my mind.
I need that gun.
I'm sorry, what?
We're up and running.
I'm making you bank.
Doesn't make sense
to hold it over me anymore.
You know what?
You're right.
I am?
Yeah.
I'm not gonna hold it over you anymore.
Thanks.
Cops might, though.
You see, the lawyer says,
I got to go in about
that friend of yours.
Apparently, they think
I had something to do with it,
which is just crazy.
(CHUCKLES)
And what are you gonna tell him?
I'm not sure I've got to say anything.
If you give it to them,
I'm not the only thing that goes away.
Mmm-hmm.
Priorities, huh?
I'll take another one.
There's a one-way to St. Petersburg.
Leaves at midnight.
Florida?
Russia.
Why Russia?
Because they'll give you asylum.
How do you even know
he's gonna turn over the gun?
How do I know he's not?
Exactly.
It's why we got to get your ass
on this plane
to Sheremetyevo Airport, now.
She's gonna live in Russia now?
Yeah. I mean, Snowden lived
in the terminal.
Her kids?
We'll sneak 'em out one by one.
So it's gonna be one big happy family
living in a terminal.
Snowden did.
Eating Sbarro's.
'Cause they have Sbarro's in Russia?
Since 1997.
The point is,
you can't be extradited for murder.
You just need a lawyer.
I was the last person she was seen with.
Okay, a good one.
And I lied to the police.
A real good one.
And I stole her bird.
Technically, I stole her bird.
Okay, where's her power-walking boyfriend?
He'll back you up.
ANNIE: He's probably still in diapers
since the last time he saw gang friend.
You didn't pull the trigger.
I may as well have.
What are you looking for?
She's making me mental.
BETH: Dear Dean,
I spent the last two years
cooking and cleaning.
I've learned I'm excellent at both.
And you will be, too,
because I'm going to tell you
exactly what to do, and how to do it.
My friends will make the money.
You're gonna buy hot tubs with it.
A lot of them.
From as many wholesalers
as you can, just in case.
Spread it around.
This is where you shine, Dean.
Price doesn't matter.
It's all profit.
Now you're gonna Sell 'em.
And this is how you hide it.
Inflate the sales price
or the number of the units sold,
ideally both.
It's pretty simple.
I know you can do this.
You can still live the dream.
Nobody needs to know how you got there.
Love, Beth.
In my nite life I don't think twice
Everything is so nice
Loving in the luxury of the nite life
Everything is all right
Blinded by the headlights
Driving past midnight
Looks like a still life
Give me something cheap
Not enough sleep
Which one do ! keep?
You are my nite life
DEAN: Remember when those raccoons
tracked the mud all over the downspout?
I need to tell you something.
Look at this.
I have to repaint the entire door.
And it's all over,
everywhere that inspector woman touched.
I have to redo the bathroom,
the front area over there.
It's, like, what?
Did she change the oil on her car
before she came here?
And Eric, I mean, he's already
returned the stuff,
and we're never gonna match the color.
I mean, it's Swiss coffee
and pale avocado.
(CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
Hey.
What do you want to tell me?
Nothing.
Stopped by the school today.
RUBY: What for?
Tell little man's principal
that if Ms. Jackson
can't take an honest fart joke,
then maybe our son's not the problem.
How'd that go over?
He starts in Ms. V's class on Monday.
Bad people, not bad parents.
What happens when he does
the same thing in her class?
Well, she sees kids as kids.
What's this?
Science homework.
He didn't do it.
Oh, he did it.
Why did he draw a picture of a cactus?
It's not a cactus.
Meerkat?
Nope.
Prairie dog?
Penis.
Math.
I'm guessing it's not a number.
And history.
I'm gonna get ahead of this one
and let you know right now,
it's not the Washington Monument.
I was really hoping it was.
Me too.
Uh-uh-uh.
I'll call about the test tomorrow.
MAN ON TV:
...who work as well together as meerkats.
These squirrel-sized members...
ANNIE: Hey.
Hi.
How was Dad's?
Boring.
How was the dinner?
Plant-based.
Um, I got homework, so...
Hey, I thought maybe next weekend
we could, like, go to the movies?
You know, buy one ticket
and then sneak into five?
I think I might go to Dad's again.
You were just there.
I know, but I have a school thing.
Oh. Sick.
Can I come?
It's sort of not for parents.
Yeah, no, that's...
That's totally cool.
But I'm still totally down
for the movie thing.
Hey, Ben.
Happy birthday.
Thanks.
(SLURPING)
Sure you don't want a fork?
Mmm-mmm.
Just thought it might be a little more
efficient for your, uh,
situation.
What do you want?
Do you have kids?
I got a little girl in Cincinnati.
You get to see her at all?
I try to get there for her birthdays.
That sucks.
She's got a good mom.
It's better this way.
I need a favor.
You sound like your sister.
She's a really good mom too.
So?
So it really shouldn't be
her prints on that gun.
Dumpling?
When are you going in?
Soon.
I've been thinking a lot about it.
I'll bet you have.
It's hard to wrap your
brain around, actually,
that each of our fingerprints is totally
and completely unique.
Snowflakes too.
And tiger stripes.
Like, why?
Don't know, but it really
works out in my favor.
Does it?
Forgot one.
What's this?
You can keep it.
I've got the original somewhere safe.
Just crazy
that there's a way to get everyone,
even tigers.
Let me know what the cops say.
Is that booze?
This boy has worked a penis
into almost every one of these.
What did the specialist say?
You're probably gonna want some of this.
It's that bad?
It's pretty bad.
Like special-school bad?
Mmm-hmm.
The real expensive kind.
This says he should be in eighth grade.
Yep.
But he's in second grade.
Yeah.
No.
Boy's a damn genius.
What are we gonna do?
How are we gonna afford that school?
BETH: And I went ahead
and made some khao tom mud
banana leaf sticky rice thing,
It's delish.
Oh, but the dye still needs
to dry in the chut Thais,
so that'll take a minute.
Yes, I am feeling much better.
I just needed to take control
of the situation.
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
Wait, can... I'm sorry,
can I call you back?
You called.
May I?
Uh... yeah.
Let me just grab you a plate.
I lived off these on Koh Samui.
Where's your furniture?
It was stolen.
By whom?
Your target.
Remember?
Although, by this point,
he's gonna die of old age first.
I have other clients.
I am paying you a lot of money.
For you.
From Chile.
I don't support how they're made,
but their little hands are SO precise.
Move me up on your schedule.
Try them on.
You've done the legwork.
It's harder than I thought.
He is not hard to find.
He's not the problem.
Well, who is?
You.
Stunning. All of it.
What?
You're distracting.
How?
I can't stop thinking about you.
Mmm.
(SPEAKING THAI)
And if I'm honest...
That's why I've been dragging my feet.
Well, what am I supposed to do here?
Have dinner with me.
When did they get in?
This morning.
DL Dave, too?
The whole posse.
Is he pissed?
You charged a hot tub
to the United States Government.
How do I look?
Like you're gonna cry.
Well, I'm not.
Don't.
I won't.
You haven't cried in three days.
So?
You're due.
I promise, okay?
(CRYING) They bought the place in cash,
and they're selling 'em,
like, way below cost.
And the only way that works is if the plan
to go out of business.
So before you send me home, just, like,
please put forensic
accounting on it, because I swear to God,
if I am wrong about this, I will resign.
This will be the best gift
I've ever given you.
Just trust me.
What do you think, Dave?
No one is shipping you.
(SNIFFING) Thank you.
DAVE: Let's get the team on it.
Yes.
There's a pattern here.
His car dealership got busted too.
Wait, sorry. What?
Put a tail on this guy.
Guy? Wait, wait.
Why? Why is it the guy?
And, fellas, let's tighten the net.
Last time he got off on a technicality.
MAN: Let's get out of here.
Just to see you there cryin' boy
Brings to mind
All the things I've told you one time
I'll sit there and cry boy
The way that I did one time
And wish you could die boy
To get that woman off of your mind
Go on and fall all to pieces, son
The way that she made me do
I know what you're goin' through
And I feel...