RUBY: Previously on Good Girls...
I figured out who we should help.
I got their daughter's kidney.
How about a car?
Pardon?
(FLATULENCE)
(ALL LAUGHING)
RUBY: What did the specialist say?
STAN: Boy's a damn genius.
No.
Chris.
Kevin.
So we'll go to your place.
We already did that.
You live in your car.
Where's Ben?
He plays lacrosse?
He just knows
you wouldn't really be into it.
His whole new secret, fancy life?
So the last time you were cash-heavy,
things got tricky.
You need a system.
BETH: Hot tubs, any idiot can sell them.
I just don't want him involved.
Okay.
There's a pattern here.
His car dealership got busted too.
Put a tail on this guy.
PHOEBE: Why is it the guy?
ANNIE: What if we pay someone
to blow his brains out?
BETH: Move me up on your schedule.
For you.
Have dinner with me.
Hi there. Welcome to the Paper Porcupine.
If someone wanted
something special printed,
you would draw it?
He said he'd let me go.
He won't.
Wait. You need all of us.
Not all of you.
(GUNSHOTS)
She just laid there...
right on the ground,
fight just drained from her,
twitching and drooling
like some kind of animal
that got hit by a car or something.
(SIGHS)
The whole thing went down
right in front of me.
Ringside seats, huh?
Saw the whole thing.
Can anyone verify that?
(ITEM THUDS)
You can check the Kiss Cam thing
if you want.
You sure you don't want a lawyer here?
Nah.
You don't find it coincidental?
What's that?
That both the bullets in Lucy's head
matched the ones in the other bodies?
I don't know any Lucy.
And that the other bodies
were identified as Six Mile gang members.
Yeah, I got no beef with them.
Yeah, not anymore.
(CHAIR SCRAPES)
Hey, one more thing.
How'd you get these?
Called in a favor.
Might wanna call in a few more.
Yeah.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(DOOR SLAMS)
Now, that's what you call
a statement piece.
And I think we all know what it says.
What does it say?
He wants more than dinner.
Ew.
It's the thought that counts.
Ew!
What did you say?
I said I'd check my schedule.
That's not a no.
We need him to do this job.
Or maybe we get lucky
and they figure out
that it was gang friend who popped Lucy.
If we pop him, all of this goes away.
Maybe it's just dinner.
Sure.
If they're serving vagina.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
DEAN: What's for dinner?
Uh, I thought we'd grill.
DEAN: Sounds good.
Hey, can I talk to you real quick?
Big Kahuna, they wanna meet with us.
That's a good thing?
(SCOFFS) Yeah.
Kahuna Brand spas.
They pretty much invented hydrotherapy.
I mean, they are in all the fancy resorts.
So why us?
They heard our sales
were through the roof.
Well, that's all you.
No.
I wouldn't be able to sell 'em
if you didn't get them
so cheap from the wholesalers.
Or you're an animal.
(LAUGHS)
We make a good team.
(CHUCKLES)
STAN: They make you pay for books?
That's like going to Outback
and bringing your own steak.
They said I need a laptop too.
No fair.
And an iPad.
What?
All right, if he gets one, I get one.
(DOORBELL CHIMES)
So what exactly does this school do
to provide for all the money
that we've been dishing out?
Oh, you mean the money we don't have?
Yeah, all that money.
The building.
Okay, great.
So what does a little boy
need an iPad for, anyway?
Coding.
STAN: It's been a minute.
Come on in.
Uh, company.
Hey! (LAUGHS)
There she is.
Oh, my goodness.
Excuse me.
JENNY: Look at you.
Hey.
What a surprise.
CARL: Yeah.
We should've called first.
Well, we tried,
but, uh, we ran out of minutes.
(LAUGHS DRYLY)
Could have texted.
Yeah, we gotta get that, uh, feature
on the next one.
So, uh, what brings you guys to town?
We got home from our, uh, last visit
and found a note
from the landlord...
Very sweet man.
Yeah, gave us a whole week
to clear out our belongings.
JENNY: Yeah.
He didn't need to do that.
CARL: Yes.
But what is that saying?
Every sunset is an opportunity
to reset.
Love that.
(STAN CLEARS THROAT)
We're staying with our friend's daughter,
who works at the Denny's.
Mm, yeah.
Uh, set up a couple cots in the garage,
a little, un, kerosene heater.
We are snug as a bug in a rug!
But, uh, why Detroit?
(INHALES SHARPLY) Uh...
We don't have any family, uh,
to speak of in Madison.
Oh. So who do you have here?
You all.
(CARL LAUGHS AWKWARDLY)
Uh, home is where the heart is.
STAN: Hmm.
What's new with you, little guy?
I'm getting an iPad.
CARL: Ooh.
Oh, so what about dinner?
How about some dinner?
Oh, we couldn't possibly.
No. We already ate, uh, yesterday.
I got your fave mashed potatoes.
Well, if you're gonna twist my arm.
(LAUGHTER)
JENNY: Aww.
CARL: Sure.
JENNY: May I sit right here next to you?
CARL: Just as delicious as always.
(DOOR LATCH CLICKS)
Hey.
Hi.
School still suck?
Always.
Maybe I'll, um, come see for myself.
Huh?
What happens at these things anyway?
Stupid rich parents
bid on stupid rich stuff for the school.
Can't wait.
You're not rich.
But I'm stupid.
So come.
Sweet!
You'll hate it, though.
Well, I wanna meet the other parents.
You'll hate them even more.
Well, how's the food?
Super tiny 'cause none of the moms eat.
They'll have some pizza after.
Really selling it hard here.
It's just a bunch of people
we totally make fun of,
like, who do Pilates
and would've played lacrosse.
What's so wrong with lacrosse?
Nothing, if you're lame.
Are we out of salsa?
(SIGHS)
Maybe, uh...
Maybe I'll skip it, then.
Up to you.
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
Why are you even doing this?
I can't arrest someone ona hunch.
It's her.
Why, 'cause she's good at crafting?
Or 'cause she'd never
be friends with you in high school.
She works at a paper store.
His name is all over it.
Come to think of it,
I think the boots are a little too much.
You want it to be her?
Yes.
Then get me something to convince a DA.
(SCOFFS)
Save the boots for later.
(GROANS)
DEAN: You'll notice
that we are all about the flow
here at Boland Bubbles.
Feng shui.
Yeah, the, uh, accessories...
your filters,
chemicals, your pool toys,
are all in the back.
Like the milk in the grocery store.
She had to move to the whole place
to get the small stuff.
So when it's time
to upgrade to the big stuff...
Say, a Kahuna spa.
The seed is already planted.
(POP MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
Well, Kahuna Spas
would love to be a part of the ride.
Y'all do this for everybody?
I gotta tell you, uh,
we have been so nervous.
We're just huge fans of your brand.
Oh, well, let's take a look
at those books
and see if we can work out
an arrangement.
Books?
Well, we don't really
have a presence here in Michigan.
You'd be the first.
So we just want to make sure
you can handle the kind of volume
we'd expect.
We can get you the books.
No problem. Right?
Yeah, not here right now.
But we can get 'em.
Yeah. It'll take a sec.
But then they're all yours.
You do shots?
Like, right now?
You seem like someone
who knows how to have a good time.
(LAUGHS) Tell your liver
I apologize in advance.
Hmm.
Is that a good "hmm"
or a bad "hmm"?
Good "hmm."
Oh. Good.
Too good.
What do you mean,
"too good"?
You bitches got too much cash flow.
How is that not a good thing?
Accounts don't match up with your sales.
Profits are more than your revenue.
So I'll make it look like
we're selling more.
That's impossible.
Why?
'Cause it already says
you're selling five times
the national average.
(WHISTLES) Go, Deansie.
BOTH: It's not Deansie.
So how do I make it look more legit?
You came to the right place.
Let you in on some of my, uh,
mad money magic.
Kind of like a, uh,
black magic, if you will,
like a dark art--
All right.
All right, uh...
Kick things off
with something called smurfing.
While this Kahuna
is checking out your business,
you put your bread
in someone else's account.
Like whose?
Friend, family, colleagues,
anyone who wants to make a buck.
And before you get any ideas,
I am none of the above.
We're the only other sketchy people
we know.
No sweat.
Then there's layering.
Open up a bunch of offshore accounts
but mini ones.
Only put in enough so you don't trigger
the taxman.
Then there's something
called smurf layering.
We don't have time for any of this.
You girls like to shop?
You're gonna get yourselves
a corporate debit card.
We'll balance your books
by increasing your expenses.
And how many rooms are we doing?
All of them.
JT: Furniture, electronics...
What can I set you up with today?
I think I'mma be setting you up, Todd.
JT: Even charitable donations.
Buy right, they won't look twice.
What kind of event is it?
Like Cinderella,
only the bitch sisters
are private school parents,
and the ball is a fundraiser.
STAN: Hey.
Look who dropped by.
Hey.
Again.
Oh.
Do some damage at the Apple Store?
Yeah.
It's just some school supplies.
Where does he go to school, NASA?
(LAUGHS BOISTEROUSLY)
(CHUCKLES SARCASTICALLY)
(CLEARS THROAT) Oh.
Doesn't do email, but, uh...
Jenny and I wanted
to give y'all something.
STAN: Huh.
A pocket plum.
No, did you ever
hear the one about the fig tree?
It was Heather's favorite.
Well, I guess we gotta
get up on our fig tree stories.
(LAUGHTER)
Farmer had a tree full of figs
till everyone walking by
helps themselves,
thinking, you know,
"What can it hurt?
It's just one."
Where are y'all from again?
You see where this is going.
Okay. (CLEARS THROAT)
Pretty soon,
tree is plucked dry.
Now nobody has figs.
The farmer can't believe it
'cause all they had to do
was take their fig,
plant the seeds,
and they have their own tree.
But instead, they just took,
and they took,
and they took...
And they took.
We're supposed to plant a fig now?
What the hell did you buy?
This is Detroit, not Mesopotamia.
Coming up in here like Steve Jobs.
You could've given me a heads-up.
Like I was gonna pull out
my next-generation iPhone
in front of him.
And then you invite him to dinner. Again!
He asked.
You know what that means?
We're the tree.
They're gonna shake us dry.
What's their last name again?
Haskins.
Why?
I'm gonna put Mike on these fools,
get a background check.
(LINE RINGING)
Yeah, man.
No, no, it's all good.
Listen, got something quick for you.
Oh.
Uh... yeah, she's here.
Okay. Bye.
(SIGHS) He wants me to FaceTime him.
He just got some plugs
and wants you to take a look.
(FACETIME RINGING)
Are you serious?
Yes. Just say they look good.
We need him to do this quick.
(SIGHS)
MAN: Public street, bro.
It's me.
What's up, girl?
(POP MUSIC PLAYING OVER RADIO)
Can I get you a drink?
Uh, got a beer?
Yeah, not while the keys
are in the ignition.
Right.
Red Bull?
I'm okay.
So listen, uh,
there's this thing at my kid's school,
and basically I don't want to show up
and look like some pathetic old
divorced single parent with no life.
So I--
You want me to be your date?
I was thinking more like a wingman.
An.
Already asked the guy you're into?
No.
Cool.
He got engaged.
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(GROANS)
(MUSIC STOPS)
Yeah, you know I would, but...
I'm... I'm busy.
Excuse me?
Doing what?
I got the guy across the street's Hulu.
Gonna binge the new season
of The Bachelor.
Are you being serious?
Uh, yeah.
Hannah B.'s back.
He picks Hannah Ann.
Okay?
I am asking you for a favor here.
Well, see, that's the problem.
I don't want to be your favor anymore.
Oh.
(PAPER RUSTLING)
Will you accept this rose?
Always.
You know, I was gonna use this
for toilet paper.
You're gonna need to wear
something clean.
That's... that's not a problem.
Got, uh...
Mmm, I think...
yeah, there's a nice shirt under you.
What do you think?
DEAN: Very Tommy Bahama.
Yeah, well, I thought
eventually we would do,
like, an island lounge
kind of thing at the store,
so we could feel it out first.
Hmm.
How did you pay for it?
It's a tax write-off.
Yeah, but how?
What do you mean how?
It's just... I mean, it's a lot of stuff.
Yeah, but then
if we use it for the business,
we get a break on our taxes.
I Know how a write-off works.
Okay.
How are those books coming?
Kahuna keeps asking.
Yeah, there's a lot to account for.
I just don't want it to look like
we're trying to hide stuff, you know?
Are we?
Of course not.
You know, I could...
I could help you.
I just have a whole system.
You could teach me.
I know, but it's complicated.
You know, I have been doing this
a little longer than you.
How could I forget?
We almost lost our home.
I just wanna get 'em right.
Yeah. Okay.
You wanna see the hammocks
in the boys' room?
Sure.
What are you doing?
RIO: Just thinking.
Do you have to do it here?
You'd rather I do it inside?
No.
How's Dean?
What do you want?
I need you to hold something for me.
No, thank you.
Yeah, I wasn't asking.
Well, the last time I did that,
I got tied to a murder, so...
What's your routing number?
For what?
For business.
Why?
(SIGHS) I need to move some funds around.
Now?
Still drawing some heat
over that little coworker of yours.
Are you smurfing me?
(LAUGHS)
Where'd you hear that?
Oh, I Know all about it.
(LAUGHS)
And I'd love to help you smurf me,
but I can't afford to be
smurfed right now
because I am also drawing some heat.
Oh, yeah?
From who?
From this hot tub guy!
(LAUGHS)
Routing number.
No.
Number?
Not a chance.
(DOOR CLICKS SHUT)
(FOOTSTEPS TAPPING)
Ready whenever you are.
(DOOR SLAMS)
(LINE RINGING)
How's Thursday for dinner?
ANNOUNCER: All right, parents,
next we have a top-of-the line
robot vacuum
that retails for $875.
How did you two meet again?
Mmm, mmm.
We were both on the freeway, right?
By the freeway...
We ran into each other.
At synagogue.
Uh, what?
No, weren't we on the side?
No.
Wait, you're Jewish?
Yes.
She's not.
I am.
Mazel tov.
ANNOUNCER:
$200 in the back.
Do I hear $250?
Think about that new tennis court, people.
WOMAN: Right here.
$250.
Oh. Mmm.
ANNOUNCER: Do I hear $300?
$300, anyone?
Mmm. Mmm-hmm.
Mmm.
You can go back as many times as you want.
I'm gonna cruise through on the way out.
Mmm.
Stock up on some shrimps.
Excuse me.
Um, are you a dog walker?
I used to be.
Could be again.
What kind of hound you got?
You tell me.
Sorry?
Honey, I found the guy who stole Oatmeal.
Oh, yeah. The, uh...
the chihuahua.
Stole?
Misplaced.
Who is this loser?
Okay, okay.
Come on, man.
Let's just take a walk.
Your dick dog bit me.
Do not call his dog a dick.
Well, maybe I let him go
so he wouldn't
have to live with a dick like you.
That's better.
ANNOUNCER: $400?
Do I hear $400?
I've got $400 from St. Anne's very own
Sister Mary Margaret.
Do I hear...
One thousand dollars.
Oh. (CHUCKLES)
We're only on, uh...
One... thousand... dollars.
(APPLAUSE)
(CHUCKLING)
Wow. $1,000 to...
Ben's mom.
(GAVEL BANGS)
(APPLAUSE CONTINUES)
And we're okay.
Oh!
Oh, my gosh.
(COUGHS)
You do not mess around.
Work hard.
Play harder.
So is your wife cool
with you being gone so much?
What about you?
It must be hard
having to answer to your lady all day.
(CHUCKLES)
I don't answer to my lady.
She just kind of helps out.
Oh, it seems like she does a little
more than that.
Oh, yeah. I mean...
Yeah, she makes me look good.
Yeah, I think the customers like to Know
it's a family-owned business,
but I mean, I call all the shots.
Shots. Speaking of.
Oh, yeah.
Let's fire that up.
I Knew you wore the pants, man.
Yeah. I mean,
I make all the decisions.
Nice.
Which is why you can trust
that Big Kahuna brand
is in the right hands.
Thank you.
So how come it's taking so long
to get those books?
(CHUCKLES)
ANNOUNCER:
Do I hear $750 for a prime
St. Anne's parking spot?
Never circle the neighborhood
again at pickup.
$750.
Do I hear $775?
$775?
$1000.
Sold to Ben's mom. $1000.
(APPLAUSE)
Hey.
What are you doing?
Supporting St. Anne's.
You know you're not winning
the stuff, Annie.
You have to pay for it.
Really?
Gee, thanks.
Yeah. With money.
Ooh, portable projector.
There's no layaway plan.
Got it.
And I'm not covering it.
(INAUDIBLE)
What is your problem?
Is it the homeless guy?
What?
Is he, like, making you sell drugs
or something?
No, he's not like that.
He's actually really...
He stole a dog, Annie.
Misplaced.
All right, well,
you're throwing around money
like a Saudi princess.
Something's up.
I'm just trying to have fun
like every other parent here.
ANNOUNCER:
Six days, five nights,
all expenses paid
at Bermuda's Horseshoe Bay.
You'd tell me
if you were in trouble, right?
How are my finances any of your business?
Because you have no finances.
I have $6,000.
Do I hear $6,500?
WOMAN: $6,500.
$6,500.
ANNOUNCER: Do I hear $7,000?
$10,000.
Wow. (CHUCKLES)
(APPLAUSE)
Ben's mom.
Again!
What?
Daddy's dead.
(DEAN GROANS)
Oh, my God.
DEAN: Ugh.
Oh.
Spinning won't stop.
(SIGHS)
Oh.
How late did you stay out?
DEAN: I'm pretty sure
I'm gonna puke again.
(GROANS)
Why would you get so drunk?
DEAN: Oh!
It's... it's not all I got.
Here, drink.
Ugh.
Drink.
Dave wanted to go back to the store
and wet test the competition.
Where's the aspirin?
I got the account.
(DRAWER SLIDES, THUDS SHUT)
How?
Boland charm
and 45 car bombs.
(CHUCKLES)
That's great!
I mean,
I also had to give him the books.
What?
Don't worry.
It's... I mean, he said they look great.
We're in the Kahuna family.
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
How's that quad jet treating you?
What do you want?
I need you to get something back for me.
Nah, I'm not interested.
This one's on all of us.
You have to pay down your tab first.
Someone took the books.
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
I'll need an address.
Southfield Inn.
And to be clear...
I just need the books.
I won't kill him.
It'll just feel like I did.
(VACUUM WHIRRING)
What's that?
Mmm. That is Larry, our new cleaning lad.
Huh?
Come here, Larry.
Come here.
What are you doing?
I'm feeding it.
Good job!
Look at that.
Good boy.
Huh?
We'll never touch a broom again.
We don't own a broom.
Oh. And check this out.
Check this out.
Okay.
"Hydronic heated towel warmer.
"Wrap yourself in terrycloth heaven."
Can it make our water not run brown?
And for a bonus,
Annie, why don't
you tell him what he's won?
Benjamin Marks,
you are going on a six-day,
five-night trip
to beautiful Bermuda!
Do you even know where this is?
Somewhere sunny.
We could rent a cabana.
We could charter a boat,
swim with sharks.
Okay, or we could just, you know,
grab a pic for the 'Gram
and then jump back on the boat.
How'd you pay for all of this?
How are you not more excited?
I'd be excited about a car
that doesn't have a hole in the floor.
Right.
A microwave that doesn't
set food on fire.
Well, sure.
Yeah, but--
Oh, I know. A house.
Hey, I did all of this for you.
BEN: Yeah, right.
Well, what is that supposed to mean?
You did it to show off!
That's not true!
Stop trying to be them.
Okay, okay.
Sorry, Mr. Lacrosse Midfielder.
I didn't want to tell you.
'Cause you didn't want your cool,
fancy new friends
to know about your broke-ass mom, right?
No. Because when I mentioned
joining the team once,
you called them
douchebags and date rapers.
I meant college lacrosse.
And, what, you want me
to have friends over
when there's birds in the bathroom
and homeless boyfriends on the curb?
I've been working on all of that.
Yeah, by going to a therapist
that you want to bone.
That's not fair.
It's true.
You make fun of everyone,
but no one's life's
a bigger joke than yours.
Hey, where are you going?
Dad's!
(DOOR OPENS, SLAMS)
(VACUUM THUDDING)
Not now, Larry.
No, thank you.
Why not?
Because I don't like them.
I don't know.
I... They're too bitter.
Now try.
Hmm?
Salt pulls out the essence.
Pink Himalayan's best.
Adds a subtle mineral flavor.
And the butter, always European.
It's higher fat,
so it's richer, creamier,
cuts the bitterness.
Without all the elements
working together,
it's just a radish.
But when it's prepared thoughtfully...
a symphony.
I just need the job done.
What's the hurry?
He's making my life hell.
What'll it be when he's gone?
Normal.
(CHUCKLES)
The, uh, black truffle pan-seared salmon.
Thank you.
WAITER: And the beef carpaccio
with braised endive.
Enjoy.
My son plays bantam hockey.
Mine does travel.
He used to get in fights on the ice.
If he started it, I would punish him.
I would take away
his video games, whatever.
After I got into my current line of work,
I just stopped.
Why should he play by some arbitrary rule
when the world doesn't?
Because there's still right and wrong.
Then why do you do what you do?
Because I have to.
Because you want to.
You don't know my situation.
I Know what it feels like to cross a line
you never thought you'd cross.
And so you move that line.
Soon enough,
you don't know where it's Supposed to be.
What's your point?
You wouldn't know normal
if it sat on your face.
Now, what's wrong with your salmon?
It's just a little rare.
You asked for it
cooked through, didn't you?
It's all right.
Excuse me a minute.
You really didn't have to do this.
It is amazing what this woman can do
with a few cans of soup, right?
Topped it off with some bread crumbs.
Carl likes it crunchy.
Mmm. Who doesn't?
(CHUCKLES)
Doesn't quite live up to your meal.
(SILVERWARE CLANKS)
Uh, so we are obviously
in a unique situation here.
Uh...
You can say that again.
And instead of beating around the bush,
figured we'd set up
some kind of financial arrangement.
Okay, here it comes.
JENNY: It is never easy
to talk about money.
Oh, ain't that the truth?
So how about we don't?
Uh, I'm afraid that
that is the whole reason we are here.
JENNY: When you gave us that car...
CARL: Like it was no problem.
(JENNY LAUGHS)
It kind of got me and Carl thinking--
I'm sorry.
I gotta stop you right here.
Something bad happened to your family.
But guess what?
Bad things happen.
You don't get a fair shake
just because you're a good person.
Some people get lucky
and some people just keep drawing
that same damn short straw,
so let me be clear.
Your life is not our fault.
We don't owe you a thing.
Believe me, every day,
we look in the mirror
and hate ourselves for a bunch of reasons.
But our daughter living and breathing
isn't one of them.
And what's this?
$87.
For what?
Carl didn't feel right accepting the car.
I wanted to set up a monthly plan.
Wish it could be more,
but, uh, people aren't as
into buying oranges
off the exit ramp as they used to be.
So what kind of
bread crumbs you say these were?
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey, what's going on?
He's making you a new salmon.
It's really not...
necessary.
It's my pleasure.
How rare was the salmon?
(DISHES CLATTER)
I mean, it wasn't to my liking,
but it doesn't mean
he should have his face bashed in.
Did he actually order radishes?
I don't know.
They just showed up.
That is some serial killer behavior.
Hey, hey.
We need those books back.
We need our souls back.
(SCOFFS) That's rich.
But you're perfectly
willing to smoke gang friend?
The hot tub guy has nothing to do
with it.
So, what, we're just gonna
let the feds come
and kick down our door?
He doesn't deserve this!
Where are we supposed to draw the line?
I don't know.
That's the problem.
(LINE RINGS)
MICK ON PHONE: Yeah.
BETH: Hey.
Do you have a sec?
What up?
Have you done that thing yet?
STAN: Just got their background check.
Oh, God.
Clean as a whistle.
Really?
No priors, felonies,
misdemeanors, warrants, complaints.
Okay.
Not even a damn parking ticket.
So why the face?
One traffic accident.
The daughter?
Happened the day
after baby girl got her kidney.
What?
Not them.
Never was.
How?
Uh, maybe Sara...
(SIGHS)
Screwed up the dates
in that organ donor group.
(SIGHS)
Hmm.
So... you want to make the call?
Haven't they lost enough?
Hmm.
Eh.
They were looking forward
to Sara's recital next week.
I can make the potatoes again.
Carl loves those.
(CHUCKLES)
That man loves anything free.
(LAUGHS)
DAVE: What's this?
Dryer lint.
Gross.
Forensics found a crazy percentage
of starch, linen, and cotton.
So?
She literally launders her money
at home, in her dryer.
This is just this week's.
How do you know it's not him?
Do you know how to clean
the lint trap on your dryer?
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
DEAN: I can't believe
we hooked the Kahuna.
(BETH SIGHS)
You did it, Dean.
It's all gonna happen for us now.
Mmm.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
And from that moment on
I've had a pair of my own
Good evening, gentlemen.
OFFICER:
Good evening, folks.
I'm sorry.
DEAN: What do you mean you're sorry?
Wait, what's going on?
OFFICER:
Dean Boland?
Yeah?
Mr. Boland, you're under arrest.
Dean, I'll explain everything.
DEAN: What...
What am I under arrest for?
BETH: You've got the wrong person.
Sucks.
DA is dry-clean only.
Strolled around a block or two
I will walk the streets of glory
I will tell my Lucy story
And walk with her in red shoes