RUBY:
Previously on Good Girls...
You can stay at St. Anne's.
How?
Well...
Yo, you're out of Q-tips.
That's my toothbrush.
Roomie.
You ever heard of The System?
That's like a pyramid thing, right?
A multi-level opportunity.
I just feel like this time,
we got a real chance.
Or you haven't told him our good news?
I don't think he'll take it that way.
I want to know what's going on.
D.C. pulled the plug.
Why?
Clearly he's got someone on the inside.
I wore you out already?
No, cousin.
Dean's gonna go to jail.
They can't do that.
Can't they?
We have to get to Nevada?
Who's gonna foot those moving costs?
You still have those bags?
I guess we could move a few of these.
We need help.
No.
She helped you.
No!
You use whoever you can
to get whatever you want.
I got you your money.
You got my wife shot.
What time is it?
Time to sleep in.
Are the kids up?
I got it.
You're the best.
Breakfast time!
(MIMICKING GUNSHOTS)
(KIDS SCREAMING)
Wake up, maggots!
I'm up.
'Kay, man.
If you're not up in five,
I'm coming back with
the fire extinguisher again.
(TV PLAYING)
And music camp was so great to have,
and learning to play
the guitar and song-writing...
Oh, hey, look at what I got.
Mint, I got Maple Cream,
I got Birthday Cake
and I've got Double Stuf.
Trade amongst yourselves, mix and match.
But do not tell your mother.
Wait, where is she, by the way?
Work.
Work. We're... we're Supposed
to load up the minivan, right?
I don't know.
When is she coming home?
But she said no snacks.
RIO: Ink, chemicals, paper.
The hologram's polymer.
One stop shop.
Everything you need.
And why are you making it so easy?
Because you bitches made it so messy.
And what happens when I gotta wash it?
Don't worry about it.
Where am I Supposed to do it?
Duty-free?
Tim Horton's downtown?
They take Canadian?
You don't have to.
What about my cut?
What about it?
Does it come in loonies?
Elizabeth...
(EXHALES)
all you have to do is print and drop.
Your husband's here.
Just need to...
trade cars.
Now?
Thought we'd hit the road
early for, you know...
Oh, Kenny's game. Yeah.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
You're not supposed to be here.
Yeah, neither are you.
(LAUGHS)
No, man, I mean, it's not
going to be good for anybody
when the cops come.
I'm within range.
It's low battery.
(ELECTRONIC BEEP)
Please just go.
(BEEPS)
STAN: How you feel about baby blue.
Eh.
STAN: Okay. How about ostrich?
Better.
Okay, okay.
What if...
we combine the two?
That the new one?
Yep.
She said we could swap whatever we want.
Awesome.
Yeah. It lowers our cost, like, 8%
Good for you.
This is good for sales.
Next party is going to be
pure profit, baby.
Oh, I'm not going.
Hey, what now?
I can't.
I didn't even tell you when it is.
Doesn't matter.
Wait.
Baby, you're the one
who wanted to keep this train running.
Not if you two are gonna
keep clapping at each other.
(SIGHS)
Oh, my God. Ruby,
no one is clapping at anyone.
No, it's worse.
Last party, you didn't even speak to her.
What? I got nothing to say.
I had to be the damn go-between
for my husband and my best friend.
Then don't be.
You don't have to love her.
I don't?
Don't even have to like her.
Oh, I don't.
Just take the high road.
What for?
Me.
(SIGHS)
You say all this to her?
She could take the high road.
KEVIN: Our first family meeting.
(CHOMPING)
Just meeting.
One sec.
Okay, first up,
let's go over the bathroom rules.
I know, I know.
Off-limits.
No, we're cool if you use it.
But I got the bucket.
Yeah, we'd... We'd
actually like you to get rid of that.
Number two, do not wash your underwear
in the kitchen sink.
Hmm. Let me guess.
Bathroom.
Washer.
It's in the basement.
And it's free.
What?
Okay, um...
Where do you guys stand on parties?
Anti. We're also anti
your music and the shopping cart
that's parked in the
hallway with all of the cans in it.
My bank account?
Gotta go.
Which I believe brings
us to the timeline.
How long are we talking here?
For what?
For the length of stay.
I don't understand the question.
When will you be leaving?
When's graduation?
Uh...
(DOOR CLOSES)
Is his name Chris or Kevin?
It is way too late to ask.
Car is packed.
They hit the ice at 7:00.
Okay.
DEAN: Next year, he'll be bantamweight,
so you won't have to get up
at the crack of dawn.
Dean...
I mean, I really wish I could take him.
No one knew this would happen.
Could you FaceTime me when he plays?
Not me.
Not the Secret Service.
Don't.
I'm trying to explain what you saw.
I didn't see anything.
All right.
Just FaceTime me, please.
Yeah.
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
How are you doing, dear?
(MACHINE TURNS OFF)
Good.
I'll have them to you in an hour.
What happened with the Klein bat mitzvah?
Oh, the one with the pop up Torahs?
They were a week late.
Yeah, but she loved them.
She didn't really have a choice, did she?
Is everything okay?
We need to talk about Megan.
Oh, God.
That wasn't on her.
I'm going to make some changes.
No, no, no. I was just
going through some personal stuff.
That was totally my fault.
She's getting promoted.
Oh, to what?
Shift manager.
Isn't that my job?
You're a wonderful mother.
Spend more time at home.
They grow up so fast.
My husband's out of work.
I really need this job.
I need someone I can rely on.
Megan's in 11th grade.
(CHUCKLES) Sweetie, it's just a job.
No, Dorothy.
It is so much more than that.
(SIGHS)
I'm going to need
you to clean out your craft cubby.
I still don't get it.
What's there to get?
Well, how are they supposed to know
who they want to marry
if they can't see each other?
RUBY: It's literally the point.
ANNIE: But they're blind.
For four episodes,
she thought this show
was about blind people dating?
It's not?
Thank you.
What's wrong with y'all?
We have bigger issues right now than
Amber and Barnett.
Yeah. Jessica won't hump Mark.
You know, I don't see why.
She can't see anything. Excuse me.
We don't have anywhere to print, guys.
Can't we just sneak in?
Yeah, middle of the night,
do one big run?
Because it's never one.
He always wants more.
So we'll go back.
Then she'll change the alarm.
Why don't we just steal the whole thing?
Hey, Now you're talking.
Okay. And then what do we do with
a two-ton printing press?
I don't know. We put it in your garage.
So Mrs. Karpinski can
just drop in and borrow the leaf blower?
What's she gonna do?
Call a Mountie?
Or my kids walk in
and mom is printing cash.
Yeah, I can see that that could
be a problem.
I got a place.
Let's just get another storage unit,
you know?
Electricity, drainage, ventilation.
Calm down.
Guys.
Not to mention space, privacy.
It's called a brainstorming sesh.
I Know where we can do it.
Where?
Strip club.
Still shut down.
Can Stan get us in?
Er...
What we have to do to convince him?
Not we.
What?
WAITRESS: We have a Philly
cheesesteak special.
That'll come on an onion roll,
choice of side, fries or coleslaw.
I think we need a couple minutes.
Set you up with some waters.
Want to share something?
The answer's no.
Or just get your own.
I'm not putting my neck out
on the line for you.
It's not just for me.
I don't want my wife
in anything else you got going.
Well, it's a little late for that.
Ready to order?
She's on her own.
A couple more minutes.
This guy doesn't care
about what you want.
Find some place else, okay?
There is nowhere else.
Beth, the less you and I got
to deal with each other, the better.
You think he's just
gonna let us off the hook
'Cause you're pissed at me?
I think you've got to worry
about your family, and I've
got to worry about mine.
I'm sorry.
(SIGHS)
Is that what you want to hear?
What for?
What you sorry for?
I am sorry...
that you feel that I have...
somehow put your family in a...
not ideal situation.
Okay. All right.
Let me try this one on.
So you're sorry that
I feel you should be sorry.
What else do you want?
I want you to mean it.
Okay.
I am sorry.
Better.
I'm sorry that what I got
your wife into makes her happy.
That's how you're gonna play this?
Not to mention, pays your bills.
You know what I want?
Please.
I want you out of her life.
Okay.
Okay?
You get us in that club
and she'll never see me again.
Maid of honor.
Oh, I know.
And you...
You're gonna just give all that up?
Dean's facing 20 to 30.
We can't stick around for a trial.
What looks good, folks?
We'll share the chili fries.
And sea kelp moisturizer is up 50%.
All right.
Nice.
Guys, we gotta push the spot
fading serums though, right?
Maybe they'd sell if they didn't smell
like ass.
(MEN LAUGHING)
Active ingredients.
Smell means what?
It's working.
Right.
It's a joke.
I like jokes.
You know what else is a joke?
Your numbers.
It's just one month.
Until it's two and three and four.
Then you're flat on your face.
I'm on it.
What happens if he isn't on it, fellas?
ALL: We pick him up.
What's holding you back?
Uh...
Thing with Jules'
mom again.
How long does she want to stay this time?
She bought a one-way ticket.
Oh, boy.
What's he gotta do, fellas?
ALL: Stand up.
VANCE: Evolution has given us
the ability to stand up.
We stand up for our families,
stand up for our community.
Stand up when we pee.
(SOFTLY)
It's not that easy.
Then let's do it together.
(ALL APPLAUDING)
Good boy, Cory.
Now, you go home
and you stand up to Jules.
Yeah.
Strong sales.
ALL: Strong hearts.
There we go.
Dean. You put up some solid numbers
this week.
Thanks.
Let's keep it that way.
What's going on with you?
I'm fine.
You don't get slapped
with an ankle bracelet by being fine.
Look, I love selling
the products. They're great.
It's just...
You know, all of this,
it's just not really my thing.
All right, let's wrap it up, fellas.
Strong sales.
ALL: Strong hearts!
Hey, Dean?
No pressure.
Cool.
Do you really want to make it here?
I mean, yeah.
You're gonna need
all the help you can get.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON TV)
Hi.
Excuse me,
Any idea where, uh, your friend is?
You mean Kevin?
Kevin. Thank you.
Oh, hey, uh, you're all out of shampoo.
That was a brand new bottle.
Yeah, you know, we were all pretty gnarly.
Can I speak with you
outside for a moment?
Yeah.
I thought I said no parties.
I Know.
Well, then, what the hell is that?
It's laundry club.
That is not a thing.
Well, not for the homed.
Okay, you know what?
This is not going to work.
It's only once a month.
No, no.
This, this.
You here with us.
Well, I have no place else to go.
Can't you...
bunk with that old man?
Oh, no. Murphy's super private.
(SIGHS WITH FRUSTRATION)
It's just...
It's too weird.
Just give it a chance.
It's too weird for my son.
Well, I'm his guardian.
On paper.
(SIGHS)
Yeah, all right. Fine.
I'll, uh...
Yeah, I'll go get my stuff.
Thank you.
And yeah, I'll let the school know.
Whoa...
let the school know what?
I'm no longer your domestic partner.
You can't do that.
Well, I can't lie.
I mean, you can.
But I'm not gonna.
It's for my kid.
Sorry.
It's just too weird.
ANNIE: That woman could only
own a paper store.
RUBY: Mm, I don't know.
Name literally anything else.
Christmas tree farm.
Same diff.
Or like a jam store in Vermont.
I mean something that wouldn't be
in a Lifetime movie.
Okay, then I don't know.
(EXHALES)
Okay, let's go.
ANNIE: We kind of have
a weird thing going on
with the neighbors.
Yes, well, the quicker the better.
And quieter.
We'd do it during business
hours, but the new model
arrives in the morning.
And we've really
got to hit the ground running, right?
Yes. Mother's Day, graduation.
I mean, they're all
right around the corner.
Father's Day.
Can't leave out the dads.
Gonna stop you right there.
We have cash.
We're not doing this.
A lot of cash.
It's not the money.
Okay, you know what?
I'm just going to be real with you.
We are straight-up stealing this thing.
You don't need to
know the why, but just know that our life
kind of depends on it.
And you can waste time with morality,
that's fine.
But just know that you are looking
at three mostly good
moms who really need your help.
We don't have a problem with any of that.
Thing just won't fit.
It's too big. It won't go
through the door.
But if you've got
anything smaller you want to steal,
we're cool with that.
RUBY: How did it get in here?
ANNIE: Maybe they built
the building around it.
This ancient machine
from Germany was just sitting here?
Maybe.
In a field.
Until Dorothy stumbles upon it
and decides, card shop.
Maybe.
Someone must have
put it together piece by piece.
Well, can't we find that guy?
How?
Well, who services it?
Repair guy.
Okay, so we find that guy and...
Who knows Dorothy!
Then can we just
get somebody who's like, handy?
At this hour?
There are apps.
RUBY: What? TaskRabbit?
There are others.
What's it like inside there?
Guys...
Earth's still round?
Is the sky even blue?
Dean.
You think he could do it?
He took apart our dishwasher last week.
I guess this is kind of like
an appliance.
Would he?
So how do we convince him?
Not we.
Honey, wake up.
Come on.
What's going on?
I need your help.
Now?
Yeah. It can't wait.
I'm sorry.
Is it the kids?
No.
Is it my mom?
(SOFTLY)
No. I need your tool box.
Oh, it's the toilet again.
No.
Well, what is it?
Dean...
No.
Listen.
This is the only way
we're gonna turn this around.
How does helping him help me?
Because if I keep him
in business, he won't notice
what I'm doing on the side.
What are you doing on the side now?
I am saving up.
For my lawyer?
To run.
VVhere?
I don't care,
as long as they can't find us.
I'd rather have a lawyer.
You would need the entire
bar association to save you now.
I'll get my tools.
(1960s SONG PLAYING)
What?
Um...
Can you guys give us a minute.
ANNIE: But my pulp's gonna dry.
Let's check out the pole.
How's it going?
Almost there.
Thank you.
I never realized
what went into all of this.
Yeah.
I mean, it took a second
for us to find our groove.
It's impressive.
Yeah?
And terrifying.
Why?
When we get to where we're going,
how do I know he won't be there?
I'm not going to forward our mail.
DEAN: Like...
(STUTTERS) How do I know
he's not gonna be in your head?
Because...
he never belonged there
in the first place.
And what about all of this?
What about it?
What's gonna replace it?
You and the kids.
(SCOFFS)
Where are you going?
We've never made you smile like all
this just did.
You have to finish.
Why?
Because I told you
this is what gets us out.
No, that's what gets you off.
This whole time,
I thought he was the problem.
He's just the excuse.
What does it look like?
Even if we find it,
how are we gonna put it together?
We can figure out five pieces.
It's not like it's 50.
Okay, does it look like this?
BETH: Kind of.
Okay, or more like this?
Kind of.
Just get both.
(GRUNTS)
It's in Germany.
You've got to talk to him.
What's there to say anymore?
What did you say to Stan?
I just told him what he wanted to hear.
Then do the same.
Hmm.
Really, really sucks to be you this week.
Hey, hey, hey.
What are you doing?
Yo, this is super fly.
That is not yours.
Like the Tesla of lacrosse sticks.
Give it back.
(KEVIN EXCLAIMS)
Score!
Stop. Okay, that is enough.
That's enough.
I can't take it anymore.
Okay?
I'm relocating you.
Huh?
Yeah. I'm gonna lease you a house.
(TYPING)
For real?
Yep.
On wheels.
See? It's got a shower and a fold-out bed
and it gets 14 miles
to the gallon and there's a stove.
How can you afford that?
I can't.
But I also can't afford to have my son be
kicked out of his school.
Wow, you want me out that bad?
I never wanted you in.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Well, uh...
Yeah, if we're being honest...
Please. (SIGHS)
I kind of just assumed
he was a little dick.
My son?
You know, he...
he goes to some fancy ass school.
He has a bathroom.
But, uh, and now that
I've hung with him, he's like,
a regular dude.
Thanks, I think.
Yeah, that school could probably use
someone dope like him.
That's why I got to do whatever it takes.
You...
You Know what, just, uh...
Yeah, that you can forget about the home
on wheels.
What are you going to want instead?
Oh, just keep him in lacrosse.
And don't let him become
some theater kid.
Where are you going to live?
With Murphy.
I thought he was too private.
I snagged him a refrigerator box
from Best Buy
so he owes me.
Gotcha.
Uh...
Can I put on Maddow while I pack?
Sure.
(MAN SPEAKING ON TV)
It's real, people...
The stain-fighting power of OxiClean.
WOMAN: It's how I did the towels.
Looks like the stain is coming out.
When the OxiClean started to...
Corporate has given us
an extra 3% margin on all of these.
Cha-ching.
VANCE: Yeah, so let's get them
out there as fast as possible, huh?
Rosehips.
Pair it with a restorative
night cream. Great add-on.
Yeah, but do we use it
before or after the face wash?
I don't know, Cory,
you're gonna wash off $90 face cream
right after you put it on?
I robbed a greeting card store.
What's that, Dean?
Stole a printing press.
Is that how you got the bracelet?
That's...
because my wife was laundering
a gang's money through my business.
Yeah, but what'd you need the press for?
She uses it to make counterfeit.
What happened to her?
Not a damn thing.
And you're the one in the bracelet.
I owed her.
That's a big-time debt.
I messed up big-time.
Girl at work?
More than just one of them.
Still going on?
God, no. It was forever ago.
What's manslaughter get you, 2?
Good behavior, few years, tops.
I didn't murder anyone.
Exactly.
You just put your penis in some strange.
Human nature, bro.
People make mistakes.
She doesn't feel that way.
Then you've got to let it go.
I don't know that I can.
Johnny, give me the key.
(MEN APPLAUDING)
MAN: Whoo. All right.
Come on.
Come with me.
You've got to get up, buddy. Come on.
Come on.
Right over here.
Right here.
Stay right here.
Come on, Dean.
Don't let her keep you behind those bars.
MAN: Nope. Come on, buddy.
There you go.
Come on.
That's right.
It's okay.
MAN 1: Whoo!
MAN 2: Yeah!
You're free.
Free.
Dad.
DEAN: I'm in here, bud.
I got one goal and one assist.
What? Nice!
That's amazing.
Come on. Go get in the bath.
Tried to FaceTime you.
I was busy.
I can't promise you
that I won't get bored.
Or...
think it might be fun
to hit a grocery store again.
But at least we'll have a shot.
Because if we stay here,
nothing's gonna change.
You can print.
I finished it.
Why?
I just let it go.
DEAN: D-man!
Give me the recap.
Braid emergency.
So you're just going to take my job?
You weren't home.
I got 'em.
Work emergency trumps braid emergency.
All right.
Let me see.
It's not bad, right?
I don't think Alicia Keys will
be calling you, but...
Snoop might, though.
Oh, so now you do locks?
Oh, well, you want to give ita go?
I'm all good.
(LAUGHS)
How did it go?
Couple of speed bumps, but pulled it off.
Okay. How long is it going to take?
Till we find somewhere else, I guess.
All right now, the city
is going to put that
place up for auction soon.
What's soon?
I don't know.
You'll know when
the sticker's on the door.
(SIGHS)
Thanks for making that work.
I just gave you a key.
I meant with her.
Mm...
Well, she's your girl.
What'd she say to you?
Everything I wanted to hear.
(CHUCKLES)
What? What's funny?
She said the exact same thing to me.
Mm...
(DOOR OPENS)
Hey, where is he?
He's in the shower.
Oh, God.
Got us all new peanut butter,
mayo, mustard and soy sauce.
Where's he gonna go?
To a lovely DIY duplex.
I used his move today.
What do you mean?
Rusty gate.
Ew.
It's this really tough check.
Because if you
do it wrong, you get a penalty.
Wait. Hang on.
He taught you a lacrosse move?
He was All-American.
What?
He played for Maryland.
(DOOR OPENS)
Okay. just need five
more minutes and I'm out.
Oh, and hey, if you ever
want to work on more defense stuff,
just come by the dumpster
behind the Kroger.
You still coming to the game?
Dude, I wouldn't miss it.
Unless I can't find
someone to watch my cart.
Check. Ooh...
Benjamin.
Nice reflexes.
KEVIN: All right.
BETH: So he's back in?
What do you want from me? I caved.
What about that bucket?
He held strong.
Dude!
ANNIE: Yeah.
What's up, ladies?
Just business.
You know, you still got it.
It wasn't easy.
That maple leaf
is like four different colors.
Cool.
When do you want the rest of it?
I don't.
Why?
My guys can't clean the Queen here.
You said all we had to do was print it.
Yeah. And then drop it.
I assumed that you meant in our country.
Jesus. Not again.
Why can't it ever be Mexico?
When?
When I'm ready.
Avoided it for so long.
Don't.
But I think we all
knew this day would come.
It's like you want it to happen.
I'm just saying.
You stay in the game long enough,
something's bound to wind up in your ass.