BETH:
Previously on Good Girls...
'Cause you didn't want
your cool, fancy new friends
to know about your broke-ass mom, right?
You called them douchebags
and date rapers.
You make fun of everyone,
but no one's life is
a bigger joke than yours.
Where are you going?
Dad's.
Something's not adding up here.
A few weeks ago, that thing
with the bank truck
burning up?
Crazy how much it cost me.
So you steal from me?
It wasn't really from you.
It's still my ass on the line.
I got a family, man.
Should have thought about that
before you messed with mine.
What if they don't give me the money?
Don't come out till they do.
Big Kahuna.
They want to meet with us.
Kahuna Spas would love
to be part of the ride.
DEAN: I got the account.
That's great!
I also had to give them the books.
OFFICER: Dean Boland,
you are under arrest.
Your husband pled guilty today.
He's protecting her.
Tell me one thing.
Was he part of it?
There's got to be a way to get him out.
He's the perfect fall guy.
Is Dean okay?
That depends on you.
He'll kill me.
We'll protect you.
What could I even get on him?
Looks like plenty.
Looks legit.
Who made it?
We both know how hard it is
to find a good artist,
so I'm not gonna tell you.
Fair enough.
SO you approve?
Yeah.
Louie, Louie
Ooh
Me voy, me voy
Ay-ay-ay-ay-ay-ay
Louie Louie
Ooh, me voy
PHOEBE: All you have to do
is make the exchange.
DAVE: Unique New York, unique New York...
What if he figures it out?
We'll protect you.
Red leather, yellow leather.
His gun's the size of my arm.
We're Secret Service.
So?
Ever seen In the Line of Fire?
You'll take a bullet for me?
He will.
Betty Botter bought a bit
of bitter butter,
but the bit of butter was
too bitter for the batter.
(SONG CONTINUES IN SPANISH)
And what if he goes crazy or something,
like kidnaps me?
Already tagged his car.
You just do what you've always done.
(MICROPHONE FEEDBACK)
It's not gonna do that, is it?
Oh. Let's hope not.
He knows.
He doesn't.
Yeah, he does!
DAVE: He might.
Seriously?
Tracker just went dead.
I want a cop outside my house.
That'll just draw attention.
So will my dead body
in the Detroit River.
DAVE: Let's not lose our heads here.
I at least want my husband out.
Not till we know where the money goes.
I did everything you said!
Except the only part that matters.
That's not on me!
It kind of is.
Trackers sometimes glitch.
Wait, what is
"a pet emergency"?
Because this is an actual emergency.
Nanny flaked.
Where's Dad?
SADIE: Chicago.
Some zit cream convention.
Yes! Samples.
Why do none of these freaking things work?
Well, how does tomorrow
help me when the meeting is today?
Okay, okay, okay. Um...
Why don't you just let me know
about Gizmo's MRI?
Okay? Bye.
Why don't you just get
somebody to cover for you?
Because It's not like your mini-mart.
I own the company.
So reschedule the meeting.
It's a whole thing with the bank.
I could take him.
Really?
You have school.
Well, can't he skip?
It's one day.
You always did, right?
Not happening, my friend.
Mom, what is she supposed to do?
Uh, I don't know.
Find literally anyone else.
There's no one else.
Well...
(SIGHS)
What about the retired guy
who sleeps on his front porch?
He's not allowed around kids.
Your pool guy's like family.
Smokes weed all day in his truck.
Come on.
Alex'll bring me my homework.
I'll do it.
But Alex will be at school.
No, no, I...
I mean I will watch Dakota.
(DAKOTA COOING)
Sorry.
Why can't I do it?
You can't even take care of the turtle.
How was I supposed to know
that that green stuff was mold?
You can't even change a light bulb.
Those are all duds.
Obviously, I...
tried that.
Look, I raised you.
Barely.
Excusez-moi?
Auntie Beth took me every day.
Yeah, because I was finishing 11th grade.
You know, it's fine.
I'm just gonna figure it out.
Drop the kid.
It's very sweet of you to offer...
Do you remember when
they found that toddler
wandering alone in the woods?
He made it for three days on his own.
I'm only one day.
If anything happens...
Nothing's gonna happen.
Something's gonna happen.
Come on.
Put him down.
Okay.
Yeah.
All right. The wipes
are under the diapers.
Check.
The butt rash stuff
is in the side pocket.
Check.
The binky is in a Ziploc with the snacks.
Checkity-check-check.
And Mommy will always, always love you.
(CRIES) So, so much.
I think that's enough.
Go, go. Go.
Okay. "
(DOOR CLOSES)
Guess I got school.
(DAKOTA CRYING)
(PHONE VIBRATING)
Hey, baby.
I forgot the sauce.
What are you talking about?
The chimichurri for your lunch.
Ooh.
Doesn't need it.
Meatloaf, and no chimichurri?
(CHUCKLES)
Don't worry about it.
I'll just drop it off.
Nah.
I'm in the neighborhood.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's crazy here.
You know how it is on Wing Wednesday.
I'm not getting on the pole, Stan.
I'll just put it in the fridge.
I already ate it.
You did?
Well, I'm eating now.
Not too dry?
Mmm-mmm.
Mmm, it's just as good sans sauce.
Mmm. Yep.
I find that hard to believe.
You want me to lie to you?
Just want to make sure
you're taken care of.
Always, baby.
Cool.
Later, Hill.
Psst.
I'll take that sauce, if you offering.
Dean hides junk food.
Where were you last night?
What are you doing?
You better watch your back.
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
BETH:
Maybe he doesn't know.
Ata minimum, he suspects.
I read about this lady
who turned on her drug dealer in Florida.
Stop reading those.
Wired up.
Surveillance helicopter tracked her.
The whole shebang.
That doesn't mean it's gonna be us.
They found her stuffed in a suitcase.
I can't.
She was shot
with the gun that
the cops sent her to buy.
I cannot.
At the airport.
How is this helping?
She was his carry-on.
(DAKOTA CRYING)
Oh. It's like...
I give him the bottle 'cause
he acts like he wants it,
but then he doesn't want it.
And then, when I take it away,
he wants it again.
Like, what?
Why'd you bring him here?
(PANTS)
I've tried everything.
(CRYING CONTINUES)
Excuse me?
I mean, there's heavy machinery.
I mean, I've gone all
Harvey Karp on his ass at this point.
I mean, with the shushing
and the swaddling and the shaking.
Shaking's not one of 'em.
This is exactly why I need you.
Oh... Oh, now you want it.
We have bigger problems here.
Will you just give it to him, please?
No way, this is a sick,
twisted little game
he's playing, and I'm not gonna give in.
Give me that.
What?
(CRYING STOPS)
What's up your butt?
I'll tell you what isn't.
Oh... huh.
What?
I don't know.
It's just not what I imagined.
What did you imagine?
I don't know.
Something sleeker.
This is kind of giving me,
like, '90s pager vibes.
She's not wrong.
I mean, not something to track a Car.
(DAKOTA CRYING)
God.
MICK: Kid's hungry.
You got a bottle?
ANNIE: Uh... I... It's...
Seconds count.
(SHUSHES)
Got a lovey?
What is... what's a...
Oh, that.
(SHUSHES)
You're not gonna need those.
He doesn't want the drop?
It's not drop day.
(SHUSHES)
What day is it?
Hey, just go get in the car.
Um, she... she can't.
I can't.
And why is that?
The baby.
What about it?
I can't be left alone with him.
MICK: And what about you?
My kids are grown.
MICK: Then this won't be fun.
"Seafare Pool and Patio."
Hmm. Sounds nice.
Back on the horse.
Do what you love,
you don't work a day in your life.
Too bad my boss is such a D-I-C-K.
You can swear in here.
She's the worst.
(SCOFFS) She can't be worse than Gayle.
Are you kidding me?
Who else would hire me?
(SCOFFS)
Bet she loves that I'm in here.
Mmm.
Well, made any friends?
It's not a frat.
At least you get to work out.
Mmm.
You have to be in the Blood Lords
to use the equipment.
Well, what about classes,
you know, like art?
You know, pass the time?
We can't use paintbrushes anymore.
Why?
This lifer.
He plucked the guard's eyeball
out with one.
Ooh... that's raw, dawg.
I gotta get out of here, man.
Well, how's Beth doing with the bail?
(SCOFFS) I think she wants me in here.
King me.
Why would she want that?
So she can hump the tats
off her boyfriend. (SCOFFS)
Hmm.
I'm gonna get you out.
How are you gonna score a 100 grand?
Let me worry about that.
You live in a basement...
You're my best friend.
...with a roommate.
Your move.
Are you letting me win?
Don't get too comfy in here.
(DOOR BUZZES)
(DOOR OPENS, CLOSES)
Oh, no, no.
No, I'm good, man.
Come on. Join me.
Ah, you know, it's the middle of the day.
That's why I don't wear a watch.
Come on.
(SIGHS)
Yeah.
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
You're a good guy, Stan.
Yeah. Thanks.
You're funny.
You know how to talk to people.
Not too bad on the eyes, either.
What's that?
You work out?
Uh, yeah. You know,
I hit the gym when I can.
Bet those girls at the club can't keep
their hands off you, huh?
Stanimal! Huh?
Hey, man, there's no touching
in the champagne room.
Don't gotta worry about me.
Who I gotta worry about?
Jane?
Someone I want to be in business with.
Why me?
I can't seem to close her.
I have a wife.
Oh.
Oh, the bitch who stole my money.
Come on now.
I'd be happy to put her to work,
if you're not up to it.
(SIGHS)
She's in room 216.
What's the deal?
(DAKOTA CRYING SOFTLY)
It's easier if you put it on the side.
What, are you on crack?
She is not.
The middle's the safest spot
in the vehicle.
Whatever works.
Let's roll.
Y'all realize we're using
a baby as a human shield.
(DAKOTA CONTINUES CRYING)
You're gonna need this...
and this.
Why can't he do it?
Boss is laying low.
And why can't you do it?
You're the banker.
(SIGHS)
Maybe it'll be okay.
How so?
You can't kill the banker.
Unless...
whoever's waiting behind that
door is gonna take you out.
Not every thought
in that head has to come out.
Oh, plus he took the tracker,
so they have no idea where we are.
There's another one.
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
Hello?
Is anybody here?
Nobody move!
Give me the '52 Mantle rookie.
(DOOR OPENS)
Can I help you?
Uh...
I'm the banker.
(VIDEO GAME PLAYING)
(PHONE CHIMES)
Is she alive?
No.
What?
No, it's Nancy.
She wants proof of life.
Oi... okay.
(CAMERA CLICKS)
(PHONE CHIMES)
Could have used one of those from Stan.
Why? Where's he at?
Not anywhere he says he is.
I thought he, like, lived at work.
That's what he says.
MICK: Where's the man work?
Um, Sweet P's.
(CHUCKLES) The place with the shaved ham?
Oh, whoa!
We prefer
"gentleman's club."
Why?
I mean, you gonna Say it oram I?
Come on.
Say what?
He's a bouncer.
And I bet those chicks
know how to show their appreciation.
Okay, you know what?
This is a family matter, so...
Um, you don't know my husband.
(CHUCKLES) You're right.
Man's got lady gardens
in his face all day.
I bet he can't wait to get home.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
He is always tired.
'Cause he's always working.
In lady gardens.
(BABY CRYING)
I'm the banker.
Excuse me.
Yeah. Give me a minute.
I'm the banker.
I'll be right back.
I don't wanna be here
I'm the banker.
Why'd you bring me here?
Giving me bad dreams
Can't scream, bad dream
How did I wake up surrounded by walls?
How did I break all my bones?
Keep banging the concrete
to blow up these halls
I'm the banker.
I'm covered in plastic
Heard of me?
Yeah. The banker.
Mommy, wake up, I can't sleep
I need some comfort from my dreams
I swear I saw you dancing
With some specters
I'm the banker, bitch.
What did you just call me?
I'm sorry.
I'm the banker.
The what?
Who's the owner here?
My mom.
Is she available?
She's, uh... she's sick.
Well, did she happen
to leave any cash around?
Let me see here.
I got gold bars.
Bunch of diamonds.
Nope.
No cash.
Okay.
Your mother pays my employer monthly.
For what?
Well, I guess you could say
for protection.
From who?
From him.
Get out of here.
I'm sorry if this is a hard time...
What do you want me to do?
Maybe shoot her a quick call?
Sure.
Yeah, I'll just have the nurse
hold up the phone
to her dialysis machine,
and you can shake it down.
Okay. I feel terrible...
It'll just magically turn into an ATM.
Is there anyone else here
I could talk to?
What is wrong with you?
I just need my money.
Or what?
Text you back yet?
You know, the nipples, the G-strings.
It's just what he does.
It's not who he is.
Are you gonna finish that?
Oh, my God.
Will you turn the heat down?
It's like Arizona in here.
Little guy sleeps better when it's warm.
He hasn't woken up yet.
(PHONE RINGING)
No! My God.
Just get it already.
She's trying to FaceTime me.
I'll get it.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Because the complete stranger with the...
This whole message is really
gonna calm her down.
(SIGHS)
(PHONE CHIMING)
Oh, Jesus.
She finished early.
We...
You got it?
Yep, all there.
You sure?
Positive.
'Cause if not, you'll have a situation.
Do you want to count it?
It won't be on me.
Let me guess.
He trusts you.
I hate to make this about me,
but, uh, any chance we could
get this show on the road?
(ENGINE STARTS)
JANE: Mommy.
Can I play a game on your phone?
Yeah.
Just be careful with it.
Y'all open?
Told you to get out.
What about with one of these in your face?
It's just your basic Glock, right?
Front and rear sights.
Polymer grip.
Extractor. Slide.
Slide release.
Blah-blah-blah.
What am I supposed to do with it?
Pick it up.
No, I don't want it.
Yeah. And my daughter
doesn't want to wear a helmet
when she rides her scooter,
but you know what?
Bad things happen.
I'm Sure your mom would agree.
I'm gonna call the cops.
Go ahead.
He'll just send someone else.
It's not fair.
That's what the gun's for.
All right.
Oh!
I almost forgot.
Better watch your back.
"Sleep tight, goose.
Sleep tight, moose.
Sleep tight, bear
with the fuzzy, fuzzy hair."
(DOOR OPENS)
NANCY: I meant to be here sooner.
There were, like,
a million documents to sign.
It's fine.
We just got out of the bath.
Oh, how's my little man?
Hello.
Still breathing.
(DAKOTA COOING)
When did you last change him?
Oh, just now.
Mm-mm.
You're okay.
(DAKOTA CRYING)
Okay.
(GASPS)
What is that?
His ding-a-lingy.
It's a rash.
Did you use the cream?
Yeah, of course.
Which one?
The one that said
"diaper cream."
There are two.
I told you to use the one
in the side pocket.
What's the difference?
One works, and one does not.
Then why do you have the other one?
In case of emergency.
That makes no sense.
Well, now he's got a rug burn
on his crotch.
Well, he didn't tell me that he was...
Because he can't speak.
No, I mean he didn't indicate
that he was uncomfortable.
You know what?
Just get me a new diaper, please.
Okay. Okay.
(CRYING CONTINUES)
Yes, we're gonna get it fixed.
I'm sorry. I...
No, no, you know what?
It's my fault.
Why?
Because I left a child with a child.
Okay. Almost.
All right.
What do I owe you?
Nothing.
Fine.
Okay.
I, um...
really, really, really wanted
to get this one right.
Why?
I don't know.
I guess just to know I could.
Sorry.
Tell it to his little sack.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(GRUNTS)
Jesus!
Rough day?
Uh, not what I planned.
You got something you want to tell me?
'Cause I'd really love
to hear it from you.
Straight from the banker's mouth.
I'm sorry. What?
Books didn't balance.
Oh, um...
One of your customers needed
a little bit more persuading.
That's this month and next.
Well, good.
I'm glad it didn't have to get messy.
Glad it's done.
What's that?
Oh, darling, no, no, no.
We're just getting started.
Why?
'Cause I gotta sit tight.
Why me?
You're my girl.
Unless... you're not.
It just, you know, feels a little risky.
How's that?
Shaking down all these people
when maybe someone is still watching.
Yeah, but all they'll see is you.
So...
(TV PLAYING)
Whoa.
Hmm?
You still going, huh?
Is that a problem?
Can you take Harry to quiz bowl tomorrow?
Let me check.
You like mama's new purse?
Yeah.
You think I'm worth it?
Of course you are.
Who is she?
(TURNS OFF TV)
Who are you?
It's So obvious.
I can't even believe it.
You're going through my car now?
What's next, my email?
Oh, I already did that.
Oh, so what, you think
I'm some kind of player?
Exhausted all the time.
Coming home all late...
He had me making a business deal.
Body glitter?
I mean, listen.
Don't get me wrong.
She would've...
Smelling like all kinds of wrong.
Excuse me.
That's part of the job.
What about the lying
straight to my damn face?
I am not sleeping around.
Is that part of the job, too?
It is when you put me in this.
What does that mean?
Who you think's paying off your debt?
You said insurance covered it.
It's not about money.
What's it about then?
(SIGHS)
You can't just take from a guy like him.
Jesus.
Yeah.
What's he got you into?
Whatever Gene needs.
For how long?
How long you into it with your guy?
(SIGHS)
Nah, keep it.
It looks real, right?
Perfect.
I mean, close.
Mmm-hmm.
There's 300 more coming right behind it.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Why?
I just never knew you had a floor.
It's wood.
Who knew?
Oh, hey, by the way,
the kitch is fully stocked.
You got your sour gummy candies,
your sweet gummy candies,
and then a bunch
of the really sour-sweet ones.
Is this 'cause of the baby thing?
What baby thing?
What Nancy said about Dakota.
What'd she say?
That he loved you,
and you did really awesome.
Cool.
(SIGHS IN RELIEF)
Mom?
Yeah?
Why'd you take the turtle out?
I didn't.
(DOOR BUZZES)
How'd you do it?
I'm not some big, dirty thug.
I can't keep doing this.
You don't have much of a choice.
Well, can't we just sit tight?
Like I said, don't have much of a choice.
Why?
'Cause I also have people
that I answer to.
Oh, and, uh, they're gonna
want to meet you.
He's got a boss.