ANNIE: Previously on Good Girls...
Is all that from one night?
I would love to hear
about them private parties
you've been running behind my back.
Ben threw a rager at our house.
You didn't want your cool,
fancy new friends
to know about your broke-ass mom, right?
You called them douchebags
and date rapers.
If you're unhappy here,
you can always stay at your dad's.
Big Kahuna, they want to meet with us.
Kahuna Spas would love
to be part of the ride.
DEAN: I got the account.
That's great!
I also had to give them the books.
OFFICER: Dean Boland?
(HANDCUFFS CLICKING)
Tell me one thing.
Was he part of it?
There's gotta be a way to get him out.
Why? He's the perfect fall guy.
BETH: /t all started about a year ago.
Doesn't matter.
Your husband pled guilty today.
We pop gang friend, all of this goes away.
You're gonna need a sniper.
I Know a guy.
What do you want?
Pull up your pants like a big boy
and do your job.
Dear Dean, I'm gonna tell you
exactly what to do and how to do it.
What's it gonna be?
Pop-Tarts.
We don't have Pop-Tarts.
Yes, we do.
Dad hides them at the top.
Wash them down with some OJ.
Dad lets us have soda.
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
Hi. We haven't actually met.
Aren't you the Big Kahuna?
Just Dave.
Is Dean okay?
That depends on you.
I only see whole milk.
He'll kill me.
You have any almond or soy?
We'll protect you.
He has people everywhere.
DAVE: No one will know you're with us.
Except for your entire department.
It'll just be me.
And me.
This boat, airtight.
No holes.
What could I even get on him?
Looks like plenty.
We need to Know what
he does with the money.
Okay. Well, I'll just
text him and ask, then.
Seriously?
I can't do this.
Okay.
Okay...
Just might wanna give the
rest of your posse a heads-up.
Why?
Because now, we have
to round up everyone.
Okay, I'm a mom.
Who's gonna believe that I wrote that?
That's the gamble. Right?
Oh...
I used to do hearts over the I's.
(SIGHS)
Hi. Fuel up.
Ooh, early bird over here.
Yeah. Gotta drink.
(SIGHS WEARILY)
I gotta go to bed.
Got Harry's assembly this morning.
Well, why can't you go?
I am. They want us both.
(SIGHS IN EXASPERATION)
Do private school parents
have jobs? I mean...
None that start before noon, apparently.
(SIGHS) Babe, I'm supposed to be
on the clock in an hour.
Another double?
Gene needs me.
What's this man got you doing?
You know, just taking care of business.
Excuse me.
What?
Your hand.
What the hell is happening
in the champagne room?
You should see the other guy.
I hope he's paying you overtime.
I'm just trying to keep on his good side.
Please shower.
(BLOWS LANDING)
(GRUNTS, GROANS)
Key's taped to the side.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Thank you.
Mmm-hmm.
I made a frittata.
Gutsy.
Yeah.
I don't have to wake up
at the crack anymore.
You know why?
Why?
No child to get off to school.
Yeah, I got all the time in the world.
Sounds like you're adjusting well.
Mmm-hmm.
It's almost as if I never gave birth.
What's in a frittata?
You know, eggs.
Well, how's it different from an omelet?
I wanted to make
a frigging frittata, okay?
I actually did.
But we don't get
cell reception in my apartment,
and the Internet was down,
and only Ben knows how to reset the box.
And I have this ringing in my ear,
so I wanted to look that up,
but I couldn't because the Internet
and the resetting.
Tinnitus.
Sure. Whatever.
The point is is that if Ben was here,
I! wouldn't have even had to look it up
because he's so much smarter
than me and better than me,
and everything in my life
is just a lot better
whenever he's with me.
You don't have tinnitus.
So, I, uh, purchased
some concert tickets.
When I was a young chap...
I need him to come back.
Dad and I used to collect butterflies.
And I know you're gonna say
that I'm bribing him,
but I'm telling you, it works.
I would run around the field, scooping up
as many as I could,
and the net would snap
their little wings.
(SIGHS)
Jesus. No wonder you became a therapist.
Dad would just stand
perfectly still, so they'd land on him.
And then what, you'd take them home
and let them fly around
your house like a weird pet?
Mount them in decorative shadow boxes.
The point is, you can't use
a net to get what you want.
That's really an elaborate metaphor.
You can't make someone like you.
You know, I think Dahmer
was a collector, too.
See you next week, Annie.
BETH: I know.
Do you?
I do.
Because he's gonna...
I know.
Like, for real.
BETH: I Know.
We're dead.
Okay, let's focus on the positive.
They'll never find our bodies.
We get to start over,
which is a good thing.
Assuming we can even deliver gang friend.
And then they'll move us
anywhere in the country.
Do Alaska and Hawaii count?
BETH: Probably.
To do what?
Whatever we want.
What about Puerto Rico?
I mean, if it's under
their jurisdiction, I don't see why not.
They'll fully set us up.
House, car, job.
American Samoa?
Do you want to live in American Samoa?
I wanna know that I could.
It'll be like we never existed.
Like we never put on those masks.
ANNIE: Ooh, one thing.
Not a big deal.
Real minor.
All the territories count, Annie.
Even Guam.
Okay.
The hitman.
I mean, wouldn't this whole
deal go away if your boy gets whacked?
One other thing.
RUBY: Where the hell they go?
Son of a bitch.
He changed his number,
he pulled his child out of school.
I mean, this man
has completely disappeared.
Yeah. That's what we do before we, uh,
get to work, so to speak.
But we don't want him to get to work.
I can't just call off your hit.
BETH: Why not?
There's a code.
Like in Assassin's Creed?
(WHISPERS) I vouched
for you guys, all right?
We'll still pay him.
It just makes me look bad.
Well, what if we pay you, too?
Yeah.
Like a restocking fee.
I don't need your money.
Why don't you just give us a phone number?
Email.
Insta.
Come on.
We'll do anything.
Anything?
Yes.
There's something
I haven't been able to do
for myself lately.
Uh-huh.
I got needs.
Oh, no.
Seems like something
you girls would be good at.
Hmm?
Yeah, I mean, sure, all of you.
Sweet Jesus.
Okay. Let me just stop you right there.
You. Bathroom.
Five minutes.
Seriously?
Yeah. Your car. Whatever.
I don't care.
I'm married.
Oh.
Well, why don't you just
tell us what it is?
I'll text you.
(SIGHS)
(OVER MIC)
Where are the kids?
They're with your mom.
Wait. Wait. Wait. Just wait.
The kids showed me
where you've been hiding the Pop-Tarts.
And they're actually fortified.
Who knew?
Maybe you did.
DEAN: What is this?
Henderson, Nevada.
Second safest city in America.
Okay.
16.1 miles from The Strip.
And it has this wonderful
big cat sanctuary
called the Lion Habitat Ranch.
What's going on?
You said you wanted to move to Las Vegas.
Have fun.
I mean all of us.
I'm sure Jane will love the lions.
Dean.
I'll see you in 30 years.
It might not take that long.
And then what?
I just pretend like this never happened?
Just don't give up on me, okay?
(DOOR BUZZES)
STAN: What's going on?
Taking measurements.
We getting a new one?
That one's never been
big enough for Thanksgiving.
And people want to grill these days.
But these people's
just fine with a griddle.
What's wrong with the fridge?
It's janky.
Janky?
It's not janky.
It still gets cold.
RUBY: People like all those gadgets
in the doors.
Who are all these people?
I don't know.
Potential buyers.
You selling the house now?
Someday.
Your mama's house.
Why not?
The one you made me promise
to bury you in.
Would getting out of here
be the worst thing?
(LAUGHS)
Oh, you're serious.
You hate your job.
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
What would you do?
I don't know.
Something with nails.
And what would I do?
Anything else.
Take the kids?
Probably.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
(SIGHS)
Can we lay away the layaway?
Why?
That's the only way
we'd be able to upgrade all of this.
Mmm. Well...
Doesn't hurt to dream.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Grab two boxes of those mothballs.
One, two, five, six.
I don't think Go-Gurt's on his list.
Well, it's on my list, okay?
Why does he want us
to go shopping for him, anyway?
How's that guy gonna pick up
a 24-pack of Charmin?
There are people to help him.
I'm just glad we're on
the outside of his pants.
What's next?
Uh, duct tape.
Excuse me.
God forbid I get my Go-Gurt,
but you can have Pop-Tarts?
My kids are really missing Dean.
You're just as fun.
He burps their names goodnight.
I mean,
(SCOFFS) that's easy.
Anybody could do that.
It's harder than you'd think.
Is it?
(GULPS)
(BURPS) Goodnight,
Kenny...
(CAN RATTLES)
Oh...
Is that everything?
Uh, let's see.
We've got the garden hose.
The roofing nails, hydrogen peroxide,
Sun Chips, moth balls, duct tape.
Yeah.
And five bags of fertilizer.
What?
(SIGHS)
These aren't groceries.
I Know.
It's a mix of Sundries.
(MOUTHING) It's a bomb.
What?
(MOUTHING) A bomb.
Jesus, just say it.
There are people here.
Can you fill me in?
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Remember when we did karaoke
and you sang Lovely Day?
Yeah.
How did you do?
I crushed it.
Not that time.
The time at my birthday.
I blew the roof off the place.
Not that birthday.
The other birthday.
When you had a little cold coming on.
Oh, God.
How'd you do?
I bomb...
Yeah. Hmm.
BETH: What's it say?
That we have enough here
to blow up a church choir.
Oh God.
Then again, I don't understand
metric proportions,
so could be more like a jury?
Oh my God.
Maybe a bus.
What are the nails for?
Shredding flesh.
We can't give this to him.
Well, I don't see how we don't.
You want to be responsible for a bus
full of choir jurors?
'Cause I'll never sleep again.
You know where you're really
never gonna sleep again?
Curled up with Deansie in his cell.
All right.
Yeah. 'Cause that's where we're all going
if gang friend gets whacked.
It's not coed, Annie.
Well, newsflash, sis.
The women's ones are worse.
She's right.
I saw this thing on MSNBC.
Okay.
The guard's make them,
you know, do sex stuff to each other.
No.
While they watch.
Thank you. Got it.
So, I mean, if we're on the same block,
it's just a matter of time
before we'd have to...
Can I have a juice box?
Of course, honey.
I want Daddy.
RUBY: There was one where
the warden got in on it, too.
Taped it and everything.
Let's do this.
Ow.
Oh, you know what?
On second thought,
mind putting them up top?
Did you find him?
TROY: Yeah.
So it's taken care of?
Kinda.
What's "kinda"?
Either he's murdering aman or he's not.
He wants to talk to her.
Well, can you patch me through?
(GRUNTS) You know,
we're not doing any more errands for you.
All right, everyone, chill.
He'll call you.
And for your information,
the store has a delivery service.
Not to mention there's an entire industry.
I'm ona million watchlists, butt cheeks.
Yeah, well, whoever it's for,
I really hope they deserve it.
Believe me.
Mom has it coming.
Mom?
Yeah. And at 75,
I gotta do it while she's still around.
Jesus.
I'm just glad the chemo
didn't take her out
before I got the chance.
Okay, you know what?
That's it. We're done here.
Okay? We good?
She'll really appreciate this.
Getting blown to bits?
Her garden.
Huh?
This is a prize for beating cancer. Twice.
You bitches are sick.
Yeah, well...
How about some tunes?
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
(SIGHS)
GENE: Don't have all day, man.
Let's go.
I can't.
You can't?
You, uh, put it in drive, and you...
You press the pedal.
I can't do another one.
We'll go to my restaurant,
put some food in you.
No, man. I'm done.
Okay.
Then drop me at the club.
We'll get an early start in the morning.
I gotta be paid up by now.
Fair enough.
Really?
Yeah.
I need us all on the same page.
So can I have my old job back?
You get some rest.
Come by tomorrow.
I'll see what I can do.
(SIGHS IN RELIEF)
Appreciate that.
Hello?
JAMES: In the kitchen.
So, what's a better closer?
Turkey pinwheels or pigs in a blanket?
Both classics.
So is this place, right?
You want one?
What am I doing here?
Either you are in the market
for a three-bedroom fixer-upper,
or you want out of the contract.
You have your money.
This is why I don't do jilted lovers.
Why do you care?
Unless I go through with it,
you're a liability.
I'm not gonna tell anyone.
Cross your heart?
Yes. Whatever.
I'd feel a lot better
if you were an accomplice.
You don't have to do it.
Just can't live without him, huh?
Believe me, that has nothing
to do with this.
You're not his only side dish, you know.
I just need him alive, okay?
You cut a deal.
It's complicated.
Where are they putting you?
I don't know.
Usually it's Indiana or lowa.
I haven't put a lot of thought into it.
Nevada.
Why does it matter?
You could have had Fiji.
You traded in for a cul-de-sac.
I have a family.
I thought you were special.
I'm a mom.
Just what the world needs.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Excuse me.
Is this the open house?
Let me give you the tour.
What are you gonna do?
My job.
Why don't we begin upstairs?
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
Thanks, bro.
You know what I used to do
before I met you?
Heroin and hookers.
So obvious.
Mmm-hmm.
Carpools sucked.
Class parent is excruciating,
and don't even get me started
on the cookies.
Minute in the sack,
never take it back, huh?
They want you.
Feds?
Secret Service.
Mmm. (CHUCKLES)
Yeah, I figured one of 'em was coming.
Yeah.
They're taking care of you?
Full package.
Good.
I'm worth it.
Quite a situation we got.
Always.
Well, what's it gonna be?
If I have to make
one more cookie, I will die.
He runs the whole thing.
Don't look it.
Trust me.
He's the Big Kahuna.
Who else knows about this?
It's off the books.
What's his name?
Dave.
You sure about this?
Only way it goes away.
Give her the bottle.
(DOOR OPENS, CLOSES)
(CLUB MUSIC PLAYING IN THE DISTANCE)
Hey.
What's up?
Who are you?
Security.
Is that my lasagne?
I don't know.
That's my Tupperware.
How would I know that?
Is your name Stan Hill?
What's your problem, man?
OFFICER: Hey, can I ask you
some questions?
What?
Uh, yeah. Sure.
Is everything okay?
We gota tip about a guy
robbing a dry cleaner over at Hazel Park.
Oh, yeah, I wouldn't know
anything about that.
You fit the description.
What, a brother with a tight fade
with some gray in his beard?
Come on, now. (CHUCKLES)
Oh, good, you found each other.
Gene, help me out here, man.
I'm being profiled over here.
Can I see your hands, please, sir?
Now why is that?
Well, they said the guy went
all aggro on the register.
You know anything about this, Stan?
No.
It's some kind of tip.
Well, show him.
Why are you doing this?
OFFICER:
Can I see your hands, please, sir?
When did you say this was?
Two nights ago.
GENE:
Was that, uh, Thursday?
OFFICER: Yeah.
Hey, you know what?
You got the wrong guy.
We had a bachelor party
that night. Right?
Yeah. Yeah.
I was working the back room.
You got video of it?
GENE: I'm sure I could dig something up.
OFFICER:
I'd sure like to see it.
My guy'll send it over.
We good?
I appreciate your assistance.
In the car in 10.
We got a long night.
Mom? Mom.
I can see you.
Hey. What are you doing here?
It's my school.
Mmm.
Did you see the game?
Dude, you were so good.
You scored like 20 goals.
Three.
Yeah, but last time you only scored two.
One.
Well, penalty shot should have counted.
How many games have you been to?
You know, like, one or two,
or a couple, a bunch.
All of them.
You could have told me.
I just love high school
sporting events, you know?
I didn't even realize
it was your team, frankly.
Mom.
I just... I didn't want you to feel like
you had to acknowledge
your number one fan, you know?
Yo, Marks.
BOTH: Yeah?
He means me.
Tight.
We're going for ice cream.
All right, well, does Dad know?
Cool. Have fun.
Do you want to come?
Some of the other parents will be there.
You know, I'd love to, but I...
I have a...
It's like a thing.
Next time?
For sure.
Later, loser.
So long, sucker.
(SIGHS)
(ENGINE STARTS)
Ew.
(TV PLAYING)
Okay, dinner.
Dad lets us eat here.
BETH: We eat at the table.
We don't have a table.
We've got a counter.
(SWITCHES OFF TV)
(SWITCHES ON TV)
Jane, put that down.
Come eat.
Don't you dare.
(INAUDIBLE)
(CONTINUES INAUDIBLY)
How you wanna do this?
(CHUCKLES) Y'all don't mess around, huh?
Just business.
Mmm-hmm.
May I?
I didn't think she had it in her.
Gotta be careful with a woman like her.
You never know what they're thinking.
Don't.
Don't do that.
Later, Dave.
Dave?
(GUNSHOT)
When's Daddy coming home?
Soon.
And, funny enough, he actually invited me
this time, but um...
JOSH: Okay. That's good.
But I let him go by himself.
Maybe you'll go next time.
Yeah, maybe.
Um, I actually got you something.
What?
Here.
It's just a little...
Little gift.
Uh...
Is that...
It's a Monarch.
I got him with my wiper.
Lovely.
It's for your collection.
Very thoughtful.
And, uh, kind of a goodbye.
Okay.
Like a toodle-oo.
See you next week.
It's more of a forever toodle-oo.
You're quitting?
I'm cured.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Just like that?
Yeah, well, you're that good.
Annie.
(SIGHS)
You can't make someone like you.
I Know where we can move.
We still dreaming?
Wyoming.
Like, the place
with cowboys and rodeos and stuff?
And a super low tax rate,
hardly any crime.
One of the few places that
can boast unspoiled nature.
Mmm-hmm.
And no black folks.
Not true.
Really?
Kanye.
He's up in Wyoming?
The ranch.
(SCOFFS)
(GROANS WEARILY)
(SIGHS)
What's your problem?
I gotta get up in a few hours.
Can't humor me a little?
You know what?
I'd rather stay here.
For the rest of our lives?
At least I know what I'm up against.
RIO: Looks legit.
SO you approve?
Who made it?
Alexander Hamilton.
You dug up an old white guy?
No, but we both know how hard
it is to find a good artist,
so I'm not gonna tell you.
Fair enough.
And I obviously can't wash it anymore.
Spa business ain't what it used to be?
They seized everything.
All of it?
Yes, even yours.
Bummer.
I'll take a smaller cut.
Nah. We're cool.
Really?
Yeah. You earned it.
Oh, one thing, though.
What's that?
Your Kahuna?
He wasn't looking to put me away.
What do you mean?
He was looking to put me down.
They (STAMMERS)
must have been out of options, or...
Hmm.
I must have been all they had.
Yeah, maybe.