RUBY: Previously on Good Girls...
ANNIE: / was at a GED prep class.
How'd you do?
(SCREAMING)
BEN: Now we both have to pay for college.
RUBY: What's he got you into?
Whatever Gene needs.
There's 300 more coming right behind it.
Maybe you can ask for
some kind of commission or something.
You crushed it.
What I am gonna do is invest it
back into the company.
We'd just rather take our cut.
I care about you guys too much
to let you do that.
Weren't you gonna go on a bike ride?
DEAN: Can't. I have
a radius of three blocks with this thing.
BETH: /'ll ask him to increase the radius.
What are we doing here?
Following the money.
BETH: / can't keep doing this.
Don't have much of a choice.
'Cause I also have people to answer to.
They're gonna wanna meet you.
I'm just his grandmother.
Heard a lot about you, Elizabeth.
Just Beth.
RIO: My cousin.
Brother.
Cousin.
ANNIE: He was going to see your wire.
DAVE: Now we're right back
where we Started.
PHOEBE: Her wire's still hot.
I need a bank.
Can't be you.
This is my friend.
She FBI or Secret Service?
Found the wire.
I didn't have a choice.
Well, you got one now.
So what's it gonna be?
(VIDEO GAME MUSIC PLAYING ON GAMEBOY)
Can't do the eyes.
Dope.
You'll get it, brother.
Cousin.
Oh.
For the love of God.
What's older, me or this oven?
Don't answer that.
Nice and hot.
Here you go.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
What's that face?
Tastes nasty.
(GROANS SOFTLY)
Bad eggs.
Try it.
Hell, no.
Rotten one can ruin the whole bunch.
Just put it in?
Mm-hmm.
If they sink, they're good.
Better to catch it now.
Okay. Now we have to start all over.
Uh, now, where is that baking powder?
Here we go.
Vanilla, brown sugar.
Flour. Who wants to help?
(POP MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
You and me,
we got a real opportunity here.
What am I Supposed to tell them?
Just keep 'em busy.
The people who live in a surveillance van
outside of my house?
Yeah, them.
They don't trust you?
I've given them nothing.
Well, you better give 'em something.
They're gonna see right through it.
Not if you play it smart.
I'll end up in jail.
I'm not asking you.
Well, I'm not doing it.
You know, there's worse
places to end up, right?
I thought you needed me.
I do.
Well, there you go.
But not your family.
You feel me?
Keep your head up, champ.
We're playing the long game here.
(DOOR CLOSES)
You guys.
Say something. Anything.
Who exactly do we work for now?
You mean, who don't we work for?
See, that's the part I'm having
a problem with.
Why does he have us printing?
I don't know.
RUBY: What's it for?
It didn't come up.
How are we supposed to keep it secret
from the Secret Service?
Let's just pack it up.
(SCOFFS) Yeah, right.
Did you figure out where his money goes?
Not Mediterranean Avenue.
Not anywhere.
D.C. is not gonna
keep the tab going much longer.
They'll take our deal away.
You know what he'll take away?
(SCOFFS) Like we
have anything left to lose.
Our kids.
What if she's protecting him?
She can't think we're that stupid.
She's not thinking with her brain.
He is pretty hot.
Stupid hot.
So, we're back to where we started?
The man's like IBS.
Ain't no cure.
Never know when it's gonna strike.
Well, now she thinks another baby
is gonna fix everything.
First three didn't.
I got four.
I told her, I said,
"Honey, the time I spend in the saddle,
"the sack is cashed."
Wait, is that a...
Is that really a thing?
It's a perk.
What was it like?
Oh...
This?
Big house.
Yeah. It was kind of a party.
Come on, man.
No, seriously.
Food wasn't that bad.
I got to work out all the time.
Plus I had my own cell, so...
How'd you swing that?
My first cellie tried to steal my ramen,
so I beat him within an inch of his life.
Over ramen?
Took his nose off.
With my teeth.
(LAUGHING)
Jesus.
I'm just busting your cashed sack, bro.
You want to know what it's really like?
Yes.
It's kind of like, um...
being in an elephant exhibit at the zoo.
Dude.
And all the other elephants
think that you are their wife.
Dude.
And it's your honeymoon.
And they won't stop
until they put a baby in you.
I'm kidding!
Okay, I'm not believing
a word that comes out of
this guy's mouth.
I mean, look, I did sell cars.
Yeah, he could sell bottled water
to fish.
I also sold hot tubs.
Dean, how do you feel
about men's skin care?
Uh... neutral.
Mmm, well,
we're about to change that
for you, buddy.
You ever heard of
"The System"?
That's, like, a pyramid thing, right?
No, more like a multilevel opportunity.
I mean, skin care is not really my jam.
It's not really about that.
And there's a good chance I'm
probably going back
to the elephant exhibit anyway, So...
That's exactly why you need The System.
Right, and you don't just get
a bunch of products.
You get a support network.
Well, that sounds good.
Cool. Just, you know,
let me put a think on it, you know.
Mmm-hmm.
All the time you need.
Hey, we're not
just into you for your skin.
(CELL PHONE DINGS)
Tina's ovulating.
DEAN: Let's get back on the road. Yeah.
It's go-time.
When you get out of bed in the morning
and throw your uniform on,
what do you expect out of your day?
I mean, a living wage, maybe.
A reasonable amount of breaks. Okay.
But what does any of that mean
if you don't have respect?
Like, when the customers get handsy?
Sure. I mean, yeah, that's a part of that.
But we get tipped way more
when we let that happen.
Yeah, I'm thinking
more about how you're valued
as an employee.
You guys got a health plan?
Dental?
No.
What about paid sick leave?
How about daycare?
You know we got none of that.
Okay, well, these are the investments
that an employer should make.
Why?
'Cause you are crucial
to the success of this company. Right?
I mean,
picture a McDonald's without a Ronald.
Imagine green beans
without the Jolly Green Giant.
Charles Schwab
without Mr. Schwab.
Exactly, okay?
You are the face of this business.
No one's looking at our faces.
And what does Gene give you in return?
10% of our tips.
That's not daycare.
Well, we can take home
the extra food from the private parties.
Not paid sick leave.
Not dental.
He's not wrong.
And definitely not respect.
WOMAN: Yeah. Stan's right.
We deserve it.
Yeah.
Screw that guy.
He lies. He cheats.
He takes better care
of these poles than he does any of you.
WOMAN: He's right.
That is So messed up.
We deserve better.
(WOMEN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
So what do you want us to do, Stanimal?
How do you strip without
taking any clothes off?
You don't.
But people come to see the booty.
That's my point.
So they won't come.
Now you're getting it.
Okay, well,
that's one of the dumbest things
I've ever heard.
(LAUGHS)
Okay. Hold up.
Gene doesn't have a club
without the girls, right?
So eventually, he's gonna have to come
to me to negotiate...
Or he just sacks
all of you and starts over.
Then we do a sit-in.
Old school-style, right?
Handcuff ourselves to the stage.
I take it back.
Force his hand.
That's the dumbest thing I've ever heard.
Yeah, that's what the girls said too.
(SIGHS)
(HOT TUB WHIRRING)
EMMA: Hey, that's mine.
DANNY: Let go!
EMMA: I had it first!
DANNY: You can't just go in my room.
EMMA: Mom says you have to share.
DEAN: Hey, hey, hey.
Let Danny have it.
EMMA: He only wants it
'cause I was playing with it.
DEAN: Give it to your sister.
DANNY: You gave it to me for my birthday.
DEAN: Yeah, like, three years ago.
(EMMA GRUNTS) Ow!
A little help here would be nice.
This one's better.
The legs bend.
EMMA: Let me see.
That one's busted.
It'll Keep her busy.
Should we be mad or impressed?
RUBY: How do you always lose your key?
What do you care?
It's never locked.
It's always locked.
It hasn't been like the last ten times
we've come here.
Because I always have my key.
Yo, I thought we finished his run.
This one's not for him.
You Know what time
I have to be at the salon tomorrow?
So, he's the toy they want, right?
You're gonna be late.
But we can't give 'em
the toy that they want.
I should text my boss.
So we're gonna give 'em the broken toy.
The hell are you talking about?
I literally just told you.
Not in English.
Okay.
The broken toy's gonna
keep them busy over here,
while the good toy can go off
and do God knows what.
I'll just call in sick.
I would.
So what you're saying is
we're basically framing someone.
Yes.
But who?
Oh, my God, that is the best part.
Because it's...
(RAP SONG PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
There it is.
Fast hands.
(GRUNTS)
Come on. Jab.
Keep your chin down. Jab.
MAN: Son of a gun.
Oh. That's good.
My buddy might disagree.
Now he won't.
TRAINER: Good, good.
Throw the hook.
Go again. Come on, come on.
(GRUNTS)
One more. All right.
Good work.
MAN: Yo, champ.
Your cousin.
Hurry up.
He doesn't seem happy.
Don't be pissed.
Can't keep covering for you, champ.
MAN: Nick.
This... this is too much.
For making me look good.
(CHUCKLES)
Played a great round, sir.
Thanks to you.
You got your head in the wrong game.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Look familiar?
I wondered where I left that.
Yeah.
I! was gonna keep it, but...
It's not your style.
You look better in it.
Thank you.
Um...
do you have a minute?
BETH: I have this coconut milk.
I had a coupon, so I thought I'd try it.
Or just...
So what's the deal?
Plain cream.
With you and him?
What do you mean?
Well, you're just not his
typical colleague.
Well, maybe we're more friends.
Not his typical friend.
You don't even know me.
I just think that you should be careful.
Hey, anyone who wears a cardigan
shouldn't be doing what he does.
What are you, a priest?
(CHUCKLES)
Just trying to help.
I'm fine.
Uh... look.
Tell your neighbors.
And hold on to that.
You could have just
given it to your brother,
cousin, or whatever.
Why? Do you wish it was him?
No.
Good.
Which is it, by the way?
Brother or cousin?
Family.
And thanks for the coffee.
I kind of like coconut milk.
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SCOFFS) What's this?
An offer.
How tall are you?
Five-two-ish.
With or without heels?
Uh...
You ever compete?
For what?
Well, she looks like a gymnast.
You know Gabby Douglas?
Flying Squirrel?
Yeah.
Does she work here?
No.
Uneven bars.
She won.
Can you touch your toes?
Yeah.
How about the splits?
Okay, we're trying to do some
business here.
I want to pay off Stan's debt.
Mercedes.
Throw this in the microwave, would you?
MERCEDES: How long?
Baked potato, 30 seconds.
Looks like a fair amount.
Twice as much as he owes you.
Must really be worth it.
The best.
The greatest.
I agree.
Great. We have a deal.
No.
You can't replace the greatest.
Fine. What's your number?
It's not possible.
Triple?
Serious flex.
Like your Flying Squirrel.
Quadruple?
Got dolla', dolla' bills.
Where do a bunch of bitches
like you get a bunch of money
like this, though? Huh?
Oh, now you've got a moral code?
I just don't do business
with bitches. That's all.
I'll take it upstairs, baby doll.
Auditions are Sunday.
BETH: That guy's a giant turd.
What?
Nothing.
I just have never
heard you say the word "turd" before.
Well, he is.
Way more than that.
He's a giant piece of...
Do you think he knew the money was fake?
That turd just gets off
on keeping a good man down.
Okay.
So we break into his car
and we load up the trunk.
How's that get it in the club?
Well, he parks it
right outside, in his spot.
Then Rizzoli and Isles know it's a setup,
because of the lojack or whatever.
Ladies.
What if we just mailed a box of fake dough
to the club?
ANNIE: Ladies?
No, because then we're gonna
get busted for mail fraud
on top of everything else.
Ladies!
Occam's razor.
What?
The problem-solving principle that says
that entities should not be multiplied
without necessity?
Come on.
She gets her GED
and now she's Stephen Hawking?
ANNIE: Sometimes,
the simplest way is the right way.
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
(HIP-HOP SONG PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
What is going on here?
Eggs and legs.
Carving station's legit.
You said you wanted to know
where it goes.
Where what goes?
It's not enough to sella DA.
ANNIE: Mmm...
Could we grab another round of mimosas?
Can I have some change?
Thank you.
Yeah.
Is that enough?
Mr. Varna needs help with his clubs.
NICK: You want
to handle it from the trunk.
That way, you don't
disturb this right here.
This is called a root ball.
Tree's got a sack.
Fine, yes, it's a sack,
which is why you should protect it more.
Okay?
What do you use for backfill?
Peat moss.
Hmm.
Hey, we're open to suggestions.
I mean, I like bone meal, personally.
That sounds nasty.
Makes them grow.
Like, human bones?
You should see my tulips.
Damn.
Oh.
You do Know that these
are at-risk kids, right?
Yeah, amazing.
Yeah, but you just
sent him on a murder spree
in the name of gardening, so...
But the city's gonna look great, so...
(CHUCKLES)
Okay.
I... I didn't think you'd come.
I didn't think councilmen actually
did anything.
Oh, we try not to.
No, this is more of a campaign promise.
You know how that goes.
What's your brother think?
Cousin.
Whatever.
I'm not him.
It's just a choice, right?
Not always.
Why are you here, Elizabeth?
I just want to plant a tree.
Now you're stuck here.
BOY: Yo, Councilman!
Coming.
Hi.
Thank you.
Sure.
Ready when you are.
I don't even know why I'm here.
Is it Bring-a-Total-Stranger to-Work Day?
Mmm, next week.
Then you must have broken the law.
That's cute.
PHOEBE: How'd it start?
Huh?
What's this?
It's not money.
Don't know anything about that, my friend.
Oh, really?
'Cause your club's
got more of it than toilet paper.
It's n...
It's not my club.
DAVE: It's his, right?
That's why he should be here and not you.
He's not a bad guy.
What kind of guy is he?
(FOLK SONG PLAYING)
Liquor. Cigarettes.
Whatever the kids would buy.
Then we got into gift cards.
Applebee's, Chili's,
Michael's, Bed Bath & Beyond.
Man, we hit a Triple-B so hard once,
they had to stop giving out
all those coupons.
Then his doctor bills
kept coming in and coming in.
Heart medications.
All these boner pills.
And that's...
that's when we started
knocking off the pharmacies.
You know, xanny bars,
those patches with the fentanyl?
Yeah.
(CRYING)
Nursing homes ain't cheap.
And that man treated me
like his own grandson.
(CRYING, SNIFFLING)
If it wasn't for him,
I'd still be in Philly
selling fireworks out of my damn trunk.
Did I dabble in hillbilly heroin,
and some other things?
Oh, yeah.
Guilty as charged.
You haven't been charged.
Then lock me up.
Actually, for anything you confessed.
That's why this country's great.
People care about people.
Who the hell is that?
Wedding?
Bris.
Mmm, quite a turnout.
It's apparently quite a penis.
Thanks for getting us
that guy, by the way.
Oh, yeah.
Anything good?
Oh my God. Tons.
Really?
Mmm.
Confessed to pretty much every crime.
Wow.
Except for anything
having to do with your gang buddy.
Well, those guys all protect each other.
Mmm, this guy pretty much gave up
everyone he's ever worked with.
Well...
he's lying.
Remember after boot camp,
when I asked you to get a juice?
Mmm-hmm.
And you said you had
to pick up the kids?
Right.
Did you really have to?
You want to get a juice?
Let's go get a damn juice.
They're rounding you all up tomorrow.
It's not over yet.
Dave wants to go home.
What do you want?
Just pick a side.
(CAR APPROACHING)
(RIO CHUCKLES)
Look who got her head in the game.
I didn't do it for you.
Aww. That hurts.
Hmm.
Be for real with me.
Who's more fun?
It's all there.
Me? Or your van people?
What do you think?
(SIRENS APPROACHING)
That's a wrap.
(CHUCKLES) Hey, I'm not gonna make weight.
You got me this new stove.
I gotta try all the burners.
Don't make me regret it.
The old one worked fine.
Yeah, if you didn't need to use the oven.
Taste that.
All right, it's going back.
(GASPS)
(CHUCKLES)
Don't you dare.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER OVER POLICE RADIO)
That's him.
(MUFFLED INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Come on.
VANCE: Ten years.
If this was a bar,
I'd card you.
Stop.
You want to lock it in with R-Cubed.
Uh-huh.
Rejuvenate, refresh, rewind.
Hey, baby.
Buzzkill.
Beth?
You look so young, she probably didn't
recognize you.
Excuse me, boys.
They're leaving soon, I promise.
Ride got a late start
'cause Vance was at some conference.
Is that...
Is that okay?
We got him.
"Him" him?
(SCOFFS)
PHOEBE: I call dibs.
You can't do that.
Just did.
Well, then I call rank.
I got a better angle on him.
Oh, what's that?
These.
(SCOFFS)
Means nothing.
To that guy?
It'll get you about as much as this.
I think he's more into these than that.
Trust me.
You never Know.
Okay. Rock, paper, scissors.
Fine.
Still using these.
Sure. If you can find 'em.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Private meeting.
No one's allowed in.
We are.
'Cause of this.
Under orders.
DAVE: So are we.
Mine are from above.
Ours are above your above.
Uh, you can't...
you can't go in.
You...
Where is he?
He walked.
What?
That's impossible.
D.A. didn't charge him.
Guess there's someone above all of us.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
You owe me.
Add it to the list.
So, what do we do about her?
Well, not what you want to do.
Don't see any other way.
That's where you got me, brother.
Cousin.
(CHUCKLES)
Right.
You hungry?
(ENGINE STARTS)
Wear your seatbelt.
What do you know about mail fraud?
It's bad.
Mmm-hmm.
Get-you-five-years bad.
How about tax evasion?
Real bad.
Ten to twenty.
What about inappropriate behavior
with an exotic animal?
Swear to God, something with a hedgehog.
Why are you asking me this?
'Cause you add all that up,
that's how long Gene is out of our lives.
Ding, dong.
You know what this means?
Yeah. The witch is dead.
That's why I said,
"Ding, dong."
We're free, baby.
How's it feel, boo?
(SIGHS)
I feel like the luckiest
son of a bitch alive.
What?
The hedgehog might have you beat.
Yeah. Not alive anymore.
Left? Or right?
Left.
What?
I'm sorry. Right.
I meant right.
It's the right side.
It has way less lines.
You look great.
(SMACKS LIPS)
It's only 'cause The System works.
And I can do it anywhere.
Like, I could do it in Nevada.
How much does all this cost?
I mean, you...
I think you have to think of it
as an investment,
right? 'Cause we're getting in
at the ground floor,
but who knows where this thing could go.
Only up.
Really?
Yeah. Now that you're a part of it.
Thanks.
Um, all right, I'm gonna go see Vance.
He wants to go over the products
one more time
before I meet corporate.
Okay.
All right.
It's obviously the right side.
Go.
I won't be late.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(GASPS)
Shh. You'll wake the kids.
I didn't have a choice.
Yeah, you did.
No, they were gonna...
You just didn't choose me.
Please don't hurt my kids.
I ain't gonna hurt nobody.
But I turned you in.
(POP MUSIC PLAYING)
Got you something.
New gig?
Promotion.
More like reward.
They're all the same.
Could have had my back.
I did.
How? I'm the one
who ended up doing the six-month stretch,
cousin.
Brother.
Got banned from the gym.
Don't need it.
Trainer dropped me.
You don't need that either.
Oh, yeah?
What do I need?
Stolen clubs.
The liquor from the bar.
Register at the pro shop.
Why?
Now they trust me.
Now they'll believe
anything you tell them.
We can do whatever we want.
They'll never see us coming.
(SONG CONTINUES PLAYING)