Don't y'all know the drill by now?
What if we ordered for him?
He'll be here.
(BELL RINGS)
I'm going to go
get that food, and when I come back,
that seat better be occupied.
(EXHALES)
Anything?
Can't pick up the tab if he doesn't show.
You told him here, right?
He's coming.
Just like your strip club guy
was moving all that funny money?
And the stuff from the councilman's office
was all we would need.
We're trying.
It sounds like
you're trying to go to jail.
(CAR HONKS)
Come here.
Yo.
You hungry?
No, I'm good.
Watching your figure?
Yeah, it's hard looking this beautiful.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Are you meeting someone more important?
What's up, though?
Get in.
Excuse me.
Are you Beth Boland?
Yes, I am.
I just voted for you.
Good luck today.
Thank you for your support.
You guys, just don't leave yet.
(CELL PHONE BUZZING)
(CLICKS TONGUE)
You know,
I think I finally figured it out.
What's that?
Oh, why she's got you by the jewels.
Oh, yeah?
(CHUCKLES) Yeah.
It's always the spicy ones.
My kind of girl.
Yeah, well...
It makes me nervous.
Don't be.
Oh, 'cause when it all goes south,
I need you to be clear-headed.
Nah, she's just some bitch, bro.
What if she's more than that?
Hmm?
Come on.
(CHUCKLES)
You know me.
Do I?
I'll do what I gotta do.
Alright?
Let's see how far we can take her, yeah?
Drag that bitch till she drops.
That's right.
(CHUCKLES)
Forget lunch.
I think you need a boba.
(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
Are you too cool for boba now?
Put your seatbelt on.
Okay. Okay.
We're going.
(CELL PHONE BUZZES)
Hey, was that him?
Nope, nothing. Oh.
What's it say?
I won.
Oh, boy.
She won.
Seriously?
Whiskey for the councilwoman.
Where were you?
Something came up.
(CLEARS THROAT)
I looked like an idiot.
To getting tough on crime.
How am I supposed to do that
if I've got nothing to give them?
Change of plans.
Why?
Too much heat.
Yeah, but the heat's in charge.
Yeah. I don't mean
we have to do it their way.
To keep your hands clean.
What is it?
Your acceptance speech.
Break a leg.
Dinner.
Huh?
We have steak portobello
with a five-cheese mushroom risotto,
Hmm?
Is there a problem, sir?
There's ice in the middle.
Oh. I'll just toss it back on the grill.
I'm also cool just PB on Ritz.
Oh. Well, I just didn't want you
to go into food shock
since... you know.
I'll Survive.
I don't know, you guys were just,
uh, pretty close.
We still are.
What do you mean?
He's been helping out at my practices.
He has?
Yeah. He and my coach found out
they used to play against
each other in college.
Does he ever, you know, like, just...
ask about me? Or is it...
Mom?
Hmm? I
(MICROWAVE OVEN BEEPS)
You'll survive, too.
(SIGHS)
Mushrooms all exploded.
Congratulations.
They didn't have any patriotic options.
Taste the same.
Mm.
So do you want to run your speech?
I'm still working on it.
Well, if you change your mind,
I will be in the garage.
What are you doing in the garage?
Cleaning up.
Hey, ladies. (CHUCKLES)
What do you got, a family meeting or...
lover's quarrel?
What have we got?
(CHUCKLING)
No, man, we just want to talk.
Shoot.
I need you to leave my wife out of this.
Why?
What you mean why?
Well, isn't she the problem?
DEAN: Not yours.
Well, she's the reason
that you two are such losers.
No, no, no, no, no, man.
You're not gonna do that.
Harry Potter mind spelling us.
Look, everyone benefits from it.
She's going to help grow the company.
Yeah, I don't...
I don't think you're hearing me.
All right.
Leave my wife out of this.
No, I got that part.
Yeah.
Then don't be stupid.
Or what?
You don't want me to make you understand?
Do you think a guy my size
hasn't taken a few punches?
You're the one talking about punches.
I've been stuffed into lockers, dumpsters.
At camp, I was lit on fire.
Yeah. You ever see a dog
ragdoll a stuffed animal?
You ever seen that?
(CHUCKLES)
Really think that's funny?
(MUMBLES INDISTINCTLY)
There you go.
Take it.
What for?
Because the only way
you're going to shut me up is to kill me.
BETH: I am honored
to have this opportunity.
Uh, Thank you to my husband, Dean,
for his tireless Support
and thank you to all my supporters
and my volunteers.
I made a promise to this city
to reduce crime in our community,
and I do plan to deliver.
But I can't do it alone.
I'm going to need your help.
We're all going to have to do our part.
And together, we can heal our city
of this disease.
Councilwoman, can you speak
to the corruption in your own backyard?
Uh, I'm sorry.
I don't understand the question.
REPORTER: Can you
comment on the allegations
that Councilman Martin uses city projects
for kickbacks and money laundering?
I have only known the councilman
to be honest and loyal
to the people of Ashfield.
But if there is any impropriety here,
I will exhaust every resource
to maintain the community's trust.
You can turn it off now.
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
Yeah.
MAN (ON PHONE):
Got Detroit News on line one.
Tell them no comment.
Uh, what about Oakland Press,
"Freep," Action News 7, WDIV, and FOX 2?
They're all on hold, too.
Hello?
I'll let the councilman
speak for himself.
(REPORTERS SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
Thank you.
No more questions.
I think there's been
a little misunderstanding.
That's why we're here.
Well, ask away.
I'm an open book.
You sure you don't want a lawyer?
I got nothing to hide.
All right.
Explain to us how we got it all wrong.
Are you guys close to your families?
Only on holidays.
I talk to my mom twice a day.
Forget you.
But you get it.
You grow up with someone,
you've got your blinders on
and you want to believe
they can do no wrong.
So this is all on him?
Look, did I know that he was running
with the wrong crowd?
Sure. Did I know that he was going to use
my position to line his pockets?
Absolutely not.
But his name isn't on any of this.
Hey, you're welcome to take a look.
We know yours isn't either.
Then...
aren't you sitting
in front of the wrong person?
Okay.
Maybe you can help us, then.
Why is all the money in question held up
in companies run by your grandmother?
He, um...
He must have set it up this way.
Then you should really get her a lawyer.
Because this is either on you or Grandma.
DAVE: Your choice.
Good news is she won't serve
that much time.
Why?
What is she like? 100?
She'll croak long before
the sentence is done.
Um...
Why can't it be him?
Because he's got something you don't.
What's that?
ANNIE: Can you talk to my landlord?
About what?
You know.
Lowering my rent?
What do you think?
What about a disabled parking permit?
Are you disabled?
She has one.
I was shot.
Being a ding dong doesn't count.
What's the point of all your new power
If we can't get something out of it?
How about not drawing any more attention
to ourselves before we get out of here?
Where we at?
Okay. Now I've lost my place.
Just ballpark it.
Well, between the club,
the trips to Canada
and what's left from the purses...
It looks, um...
good.
How good?
Good enough.
MAN 1:
Fine. Who's yours?
MAN 2:
Evel Knievel.
MAN 1:
No way, dude.
MAN 2:
Come on, man.
Do the math.
Anybody can hurl themselves
over a bunch of cars
and break every bone in their body.
But they didn't.
'Cause it wasn't a sport.
Until he invented it.
Anyone can box.
(CHUCKLES)
Where is he?
I don't know, but I never Known
this guy to be late.
Know where Vance is?
No, man.
MAN: Whoa!
VANCE: Hey, guys.
Sorry about that,
but something big
just rolled in from corporate.
MAN: Sweet.
We are getting in to hair care.
MAN: Yes!
Huh?
VANCE: Now, we need
someone smart to spearhead this.
I'll do it.
VANCE: Okay, now
we've got a lot of capital
we've got to raise,
but I think the payoffs
will be pretty huge.
Hey, we do...
We can pool our funds.
Actually, I was thinking about
going to Stan and Dean for this one.
You guys up for it?
Why not?
Strong heart, strong sales.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
RUBY: No!
Rest is in the car.
We already have a garage full of it.
That's skin care.
It's like a Sephora out there.
This is grooming.
Stop being his bitch.
How am I supposed to do that?
We run.
Now?
Drop everything.
What about the house?
We sell it later.
Kids.
Put 'em in new schools.
We just vanish?
Like we were never here.
Whose gonna pay for that?
Hello.
Um...
Hi there.
I'm looking for Kevin.
WOMAN: Use the bell.
Oh, my God.
(BELL RINGS)
Kevin?
WOMAN:
Don't know him.
Okay. (SIGHS)
Hey. Hey, is... is he here?
Doesn't want to see you.
Please. I really need to talk to him.
Thank you.
Hey.
You're supposed to ring the bell.
(SCOFFS)
What is up with the bells?
Basic etiquette.
This place is sick.
A friend of mine's on spring break,
Hmm.
Where'd they go?
I don't know.
Just...
hopped the train south.
We should do that.
You want to go on spring break?
Except maybe you don't come back.
You bought it.
Yeah, well, they wouldn't
give me the deposit back.
SO...
How many bedrooms?
Two.
And what about Benjamin?
He gets the other one.
I can't.
I don't wanna go with anyone else.
You don't need a roomie.
No, I don't...
need any guy.
Then why are you here?
I'm choosing to be.
That thing have cable?
I think there's probably a dish
on there somewhere.
All right.
That's why you're coming?
Uh, well, the new season
of The Bachelorette just started,
so yeah.
Mm.
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
That was a quick ride.
MICK:
He hasn't left yet.
The girls already made
the drop this week.
It's not about that.
Hey, Beth?
Bethy?
Beth?
What is this?
DEAN: Beth!
Open the door!
(INSISTENT KNOCKING)
Consequences.
DEAN: Bethy!
(KNOCKING CONTINUES)
My children are upstairs.
DEAN: Beth!
Thanks.
DEAN: Open up.
What do you want?
DEAN: Open the door!
You want a hot tub?
You want a better one?
You want money?
(MUFFLED GUNSHOT)
(KNOCKING CONTINUES)
DEAN: Beth!
(DOOR OPENS)
(PEPPY MUSIC PLAYING)
(WOMEN VOCALIZING)
(VOCALIZING CONTINUES)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
Hey.
We got to move.
Why?
Guy's rig is, like,
right up against our porch.
Okay, well, so ask him to scoot over.
No. He's a total dick.
What happened?
He made fun of my beard.
Oh, honey.
You know what?
I hear there's a nice park in Reno.
We can't go to Reno.
We can go anywhere.
Actually, baby, we can't.
That's the perk
of having a house on wheels.
What about Ben?
He can play lacrosse somewhere else.
This is the only free school in Nevada
with a program.
We're parked in the only
free spot in Nevada.
Jesus.
Suburbia sucks.
Mm.
Well, what time...
What are you...
What are you doing?
I'm wrecking his view.
Uh...
Morning!
Morning.
A little snack for ya.
I might be late.
I have practice.
Oh. When's the first game?
Mm, we haven't gotten a schedule yet.
Why not?
Uh, I guess they start later
out here, so...
Okay.
All right, well, just let me know
because, you know,
I want to brag about you.
With all the other trailer trash moms.
I love you.
Love you, Ma.
Bye.
BEN: What are you doing?
KEVIN: Just catching some rays, BM.
BEN: Oh, my God.
KEVIN: Just catching some rays.
(UPBEAT INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC
PLAYING ON SPEAKERS)
BOTH RAPPING: Them heels
Jump on it, jump on it
Jump on it
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
Mani-pedi
BOTH: Jump on it Jump on it, jump on it
(BOTH CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
RUBY: We got a lot to offer.
Perfect.
Oh! Jump on it Jump on it, jump on it
Whoo! Hey!
Jump on it!
(RUBY LAUGHS)
(STAN HUMS)
BOTH: Open on Sunday.
Get on it! Get on it!
Get on it!
(MUSIC STOPS)
What do you think, baby girl?
Well?
It makes me want to get my nails done.
Boom! That is what I thought it would do.
That's what I'm talking about right there.
(LAUGHS)
What if you guys don't get customers?
We will.
But what if you don't?
Oh. Uh.
Don't you have to go to school?
Hey. What about your breakfast?
Not hungry.
You barely ate dinner.
You need me to drive you?
Uh, someone from the dance team
is picking me up.
She's a Vegas girl now.
They have dancing in their blood.
Oh, damn!
Two-thousand miles away from that club.
You still got to worry about the pole.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Don't throw that away.
(SIGHS)
What if we don't get any customers?
Then we have to take
a little money out of
that boarding school.
(SCOFFS)
You'll have to do more than that.
We're gonna have to put him to work.
He's nine.
He's short.
He can do the feet.
(HUMMING TUNE)
Hey, what is on tap for you today?
Something crazy.
Should I be worried?
Yoga.
(DEAN CHUCKLES)
Seriously?
Yeah, some mom in the neighborhood said
there's an online class
that changed her life.
Hmm. Get over here.
Whoa.
Welcome back.
I never thought you could be you again.
Thank you.
DEAN: Bye, babe.
(AMBIENT MUSIC PLAYS OVER SPEAKERS)
MAN: Everyone on the floor!
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
MAN: Face down!
Get on the floor!
Open the door!
Open it!
Don't bother.
I said floor, bitch!
They always empty out
the drawer in the morning shift change.
(CASH REGISTER THUDS)
Give me your purse.
I'm not gonna do that.
Because the manager
over there has already hit
the panic button.
So when you try to grab this,
I'm obviously going to stall.
The cops will already be here.
Do you want to die?
Kinda.
(SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE)
So how was practice?
It was fine.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Yeah, I was thinking
maybe I could come
to the game on Saturday.
Oh. You got the schedule?
Yeah, it was online.
Well, the coach might not put me in.
Maybe because you never
actually joined the team.
I went by there today.
It's just not the same out here.
Well, why not?
I don't know.
Is it because of the heat?
Because of everything.
But I mean, the sport's
been around for 300 years.
It's not like...
Well, it's not that.
It's not the sport.
It can't be that different.
They won't let me change
in their locker room.
They said that?
They just put my uniform
in the other one.
Best teams are in Reno anyway.
So...
(DOOR OPENS)
(KEVIN GRUNTS)
So get this.
Reggie said there's a way
to hook both of our trailers
together to make one big giant one.
Huh?
So Monique said she didn't show up
because she had some bad tuna.
Maybe she did.
Sara! Dinner.
Yeah, but when I asked
her about it today,
she said she had period cramps.
Well, which one was It?
Neither.
How do you know?
Because you only get one, Stanley.
Either you had some bad tuna
or you got your period.
Sara! No such thing as tuna period.
(LAUGHS)
I mean, I mean, really,
the girl just has to
answer the damn phone.
Hey, young lady.
Enough with the TikTok.
Time to eat.
Sara?
Sara, open up.
Sara!
Hey? Baby?
Sara, open the door.
Sara!
(KNOCKING CONTINUES)
(CELL PHONE BUZZING)
She was fine at home.
So was Ben.
We'll get through it.
She's rejecting the kidney.
Oh, my God.
We'll get through it.
Our insurance hasn't kicked in.
Oh my God.
We'll get through it.
Will you stop saying that?
How?
I've been knitting.
(SIGHS)
ANNIE: All right!
Hands where I can see 'em.
Nobody move.
Just be cool and nobody gets hurt.
Right. You.
Come on. Let's go.
Open it up. Go!
All right, ladies, open it up.
Nice and easy.
ANNIE:
Come on, hurry up.
Nice and easy.
ANNIE:
More, more, more.
Quick!
That's right.
Open those up.
Look down, please.
Do not look at me.
Open up that drawer.
ANNIE: That's right.
Get it in there. Come on.
Time?
ANNIE: All right, where's the manager at?
Three minutes.
Get the video feed.
Look away.
I said,
"Where's the manager at?"
Pretty sure it's this guy right here.
ANNIE: All right.
Come on. Let's go.
RUBY: Let's go.
ANNIE: Let's go to the back, you.
RUBY: Bro, what's going on?
ANNIE: Let's go to the back.
Come on.
RUBY: Bro!
Go!
Guys, what is going on?
(ALL SCREAMING)
Are you okay?
Do something!
Beth, are you all right?
(MUFFLED SPEAKING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER AND SCREAMING)
Beth! Can you hear me?
(CHATTER CONTINUES)
What did you think was gonna happen?
Can't run from who you are, Beth.
How many times have I told you that?
How many?
OFFICER:
How many, Beth?
How many fingers am I holding up?
Two.
Where are the kids?
Neighbors.
They're okay.
Hey. You're gonna be okay.
OFFICER 2:
Can you tell us who shot you?
Go ahead.
(EXHALES)
Beth?
It, um...
happened so fast.
Tell him.
Who did this, ma'am?
I don't know.
(SCOFFS)
ANNIE: What?
Do you not like the flowers?
They were on sale.
I'm not going to Nevada.
We can get you other flowers.
Nothing will be different.
Except you won't be a criminal.
Exactly.
But what about the part
where you don't have
to live in fear for your life?
Because that's pretty enticing.
It just grazed me.
You got shot.
You are extremely lucky that he missed.
What if it wasn't luck?
You guys, he left his gun behind.
Must feel like a boss.
Nah.
No, man.
It just feels right.
You know none of it's going to stick.
Not without me.
You know, the crazy thing is,
I don't blame you.
It don't matter
what you try to put this on.
You're gonna leave her be.
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah.
And don't be using my people
for your dirty work.
He's on my payroll.
Not anymore.
(INHALES AND EXHALES)
Ah, there's nothing more I could
do to her anyway.
Yeah?
You should have finished the job.
I did.
How so?
I... I took your advice.
Hit her where it hurts.
Remember?
What if it's that gun?
Except, why shoot me
with a gun with my prints on it?
OFFICER:
Her prints are all over it.
Sibling rivalry?
Way more than that.
Not the only time it was used.
Jesus.
So, what do we do?
It's not our case.
BEN:
You bought an RV?
Yeah.
Does Dad know?
ANNIE: Not yet.
Benjamin was freaking out about school.
BEN: But then I was like,
"Why don't we go across
country for summer?"
And I could be with Dad for school
and then fly back for Thanksgiving?
KEVIN: Ooh. We should do
a college tour on the way.
I want to see Oberlin.
Fork that, you're going to Maryland.
Guys.
Um...
I may not be able to go.
What?
Why?
Uh, I'm actually
in a little bit of trouble.
STAN: Hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
Check this out.
Three bedrooms, two baths, central air.
Because we're going to need it out there.
Stanley.
(SIGHS)
Let me guess.
I can't leave her like this.
This was your idea.
Maybe we can go once
everything blows over.
(SIGHS)
Maybe you could just join us.
What do you mean?
When you decide.
Decide what?
Which family you want to be with.
Don't do this.
I've already put the application in.
Why can't we just wait?
The longer we wait, the worse it gets.
(EXHALES)
We just can't do it anymore.
I Know.
(SLOW MUSIC PLAYING)
KID: Mommy, I want to do the swing!
Wait your turn, okay?
He'll share.
You know the best part about all this?
What? Not the city salary?
You work for me now.
(CHUCKLES)
You got it, boss.