BETH: Previously on Good Girls...
All you have to do is print and drop.
Your husband's here.
My wife was laundering
a gang's money through my business.
Danny's in the hospital.
Can you go be with him?
Sort of out of the country.
I just woke up.
About time.
I want you out of her life.
You get us in that club
and she'll never see me again.
What'd you say to her, Stanley?
We made a deal.
I'm a building inspector
with Wayne County.
You folks got yourself
a load of violations.
DEAN: We came up
with some creative solutions.
What do you think?
You said all we had to do was print it.
And then drop it.
BETH: I assumed
that you meant in our country.
I don't like this SUV.
ANNIE: Every time we make
a move, he does, too.
Turn! Turn!
Easy!
Grab the money.
What are we doing?
Getting rid of it.
Put it all on two.
Oh, thank God!
RIO: Lady luck ain't
on your side tonight, huh?
You got a guardian angel
I don't know about?
Maybe.
MAN: (ON TV) At the women
in lT awards in 2017,
which fictional character
did the head of MI-6 reveal
is actually female?
Mm. Q.
Mark from Ohio, let's see what you said.
Come on.
MARK: M?
Oi.
(BUZZER SOUNDS ON TV)
You idiot.
It's Q.
MAN: Austin in consumer marketing...
You said...
Q.
Yes.
(CHEERING ON TV)
You the man, Austin.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(SIGHS)
Hey.
You still have my mini blender?
What mini blender?
The one that you borrowed
to make pina coladas
with your wi-fi neighbor.
No, I gave that back to you.
Well, I can't find it.
Maybe you loaned it to someone else.
No one else borrows a blender.
So maybe you lost it.
Where would I lose it, Annie?
I guess if you knew that,
it wouldn't be lost, would it, Beth?
Can you please just look?
Chillax.
I'm looking.
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
Okay, let's see.
Looking, and I'm looking.
Nope. Don't see it.
It's red with a black lid.
Silver button?
Yep.
White cord?
Yeah, I think so.
Dishwasher safe?
Do you have it?
I'll Keep looking.
All right. Well, if you find it,
can you bring it by here tomorrow?
What time?
Early.
I have work.
Before that.
Why do you need it?
It doesn't matter.
It's mine.
Yeah, except that when I borrow
something from you,
I have to bring it back.
But when you borrow something from me,
I still have to bring it back.
I just have a lot going on tomorrow, okay?
I have a job.
So do I.
Since when?
It's called raising four children.
(SIGHS) Okay.
You know wnat?
That's fine.
I just won't take Ben to school,
or have any money to give him for lunch
because I'll have to skip work,
so your husband, who is on house arrest,
can have his nutritious morning smoothie.
I thought you didn't have it.
That's...
If I have it.
Jesus.
(DOOR OPENS, CREAKS)
I thought it was trash day.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Excuse me. I mean, date night with Angela.
RIO: Who's Angela?
Get your coat.
Why?
Because you'll be cold.
Cold 'cause...
I'm dead?
The shoes, too.
My son's gonna be home any minute.
Mm-hmm.
We should probably hustle then, huh?
Gonna wonder where I am.
Yeah, that's kind of the point.
(EXHALES)
No.
Don't do that.
(MAN CONTINUES ON TV)
For Canada's centennial,
what gift did Elizabeth I!
give Ottawa Six pairs of
for the Rideau River?
Swans.
(SNICKERS)
After you.
MAN: (ON TV)
Tom from Boise.
TOM: Swans?
(CROWD CHEERING)
(BELL RINGING)
BETH: Tell me when.
(CHUCKLES) It's gonna be all chocolate.
Okay, when, when.
(CHUCKLES)
How about some OJ?
How about a Coke?
Okay, one Coke.
Can I have one?
Not for breakfast, honey.
That's not fair.
Just be grateful you have
two working wrists.
Okay.
Yes!
Don't break anything.
Dad, look what I got.
Nice.
Hey, have you seen my phone?
Yeah. You...
left it in the bathroom.
Huh.
Hey, where is the mini blender?
Annie has it,
which is why she won't text me back.
Oh, great.
What's on tap for you today?
Carpool.
Is that what they're calling it now?
What does that mean?
Mm.
Are you going to drop off kids or cash?
Kids.
Hmm. Then what?
Some laundry.
Hmm. You gonna wash clothes or cash?
Clothes.
Hmm. Just wondering what to expect today.
Just some errands.
In what country?
What are you doing?
(CHUCKLES)
Daddy's just kidding.
Okay, you guys, go brush your teeth.
But I'm not done.
You can take it with you.
Let's go, vamonos.
Nothing's going on right now, okay?
That's what you said
when you were overseas.
It was just Canada.
While our son was in the ER, alone.
That won't happen again.
Mm-hmm.
(SIGHS)
Hey.
I got nothing.
Did you go through her phone?
Yeah, she deletes them all.
Well, that's not gonna help.
But what about the fact
that she ran a crime ring
through my hot tub store?
That's the problem.
It was yours.
You need something that's hers.
How about all the fake
Canadian money she's printing?
On the press that you built.
I read her emails, I tore through her car.
I even dug around
in her underwear drawers.
Nothing.
She keep a journal?
Can't you find some kind of
a legal loophole?
Not with a case like yours.
I thought you were the best.
He'll keep you out of prison.
Great.
But the day they cut
that thing off your ankle,
who's gonna be celebrating?
Me.
Her.
'Cause she got away with using you like
one of those period cups.
Oh, Jesus.
If you don't put a stop to it now,
she's going to be using you
again and again and again.
This isn't about your case, man.
Then what's it about?
It's about sewing your sack back on.
Right now, you don't even need
that seat on your bike.
He's right.
Here.
Just sit on the post.
Guys.
There you go.
Sit on the post.
Give me my bike seat.
No, you don't need it, Dean.
I hear you, okay?
Then give us something we can use.
Come on, Dean.
(SIGHS)
Mm.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Hey, bud.
Have you seen my mom?
BETH: Did you try homeless guy?
He's at his girlfriend's all the time.
What about the therapist?
She's over him.
I'm gonna call your dad.
He wouldn't know.
They're in Minnesota,
visiting Nancy's parents.
I'm sure she's fine.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hey, Aunt Beth.
She left her phone?
It was just in the kitchen.
Was there anything missing?
There's nothing to take.
Maybe we should call the police.
You know...
I think I might know who she's with.
Don't forget to subtract
the cost of goods.
Um...
What's that?
It's the cost of everything
that goes into selling the bags.
Okay.
(DOOR OPENS, CLOSES)
Hey.
What are y'all doing?
Business.
Teaching baby girl accounting.
Um, so, this is Aunt Beth's pile.
This is Annie's and this is ours.
Mm-hmm.
Had a good week.
You want to do the deliveries?
I'm going to need all of it.
That an expense or a loan?
Just straight-up theft, baby.
What's this?
First installment.
We'll get the rest.
Oh, I know you will.
Give her back.
Okay.
Where should I send the first installment?
What do you want?
(SNIFFLES)
You know how much of my money
you left in that casino?
All of it?
All of it.
Guess we'll call it even.
I don't want to be even.
She ain't worth much more than that.
Not sure how we'll use her.
We'll think of something.
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, Jesus.
I want my sister back!
Do you?
Finish the job, then.
(SIGHS WEARILY)
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
(DOOR OPENS)
(MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
Regular or double stuf?
What?
Which one?
I don't know.
You can try.
Everyone tries.
Double stuf.
You want the Chex mix or Cheetos?
Chex mix.
Uh, grab some Skittles, would you?
I don't like Skittles.
They're not for you.
I'll go grab water.
Sparkling or regular?
Sparkling.
Oh.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey.
See that guy I'm with?
Don't look.
He's kidnapping me.
These are two for one.
I'm good.
Except for the fact
that I'm being kidnapped by him.
So make an excuse.
Go call the cops, please.
Run. Quick.
Hey, bro.
What's up?
How's your moms?
CASHIER: You're always worried.
You should stop by.
Yeah, I definitely will.
Um...
Can we get a couple of those Slurpee cups?
I don't want a Slurpee.
It's not for that.
Huh?
We've got a long ride ahead of us.
(REGISTER BEEPS)
Ma'am. Ma'am, he's not available.
MAN: I want you to look into...
BETH: This is how you
serve your community?
I'm in a meeting here.
By looking the other way?
I didn't think it was
something we could discuss over texts.
"Of the people,"
my ass...
Okay.
Can we have the room, please?
Thank you.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to help me get her back!
Not so easy.
Why not?
I can't be anywhere near that.
Oh, so, now he's not
your brother or whatever?
It's political suicide, Beth.
What he will do to my sister is far worse,
trust me.
(SIGHS)
(DIAL TONE, KEYS BEEP)
(LINE RINGING)
MAN: Detroit Police.
Councilman Martin for the Chief.
One moment.
(LINE BEEPS)
I can't.
Why not?
You know why.
(DISCONNECTS PHONE)
Not so easy, is it?
It's not my job.
That's the problem.
Tell that to your sister.
It's him.
I-I got Chief Gorski on line one.
Tell him false alarm.
See, it's not only for your face,
It's also a whole-body oil.
What's this have to do
with fantasy football?
Well, yeah, but first things first.
Look.
Can we just talk about our picks?
Yeah. As soon as we
talk about your dermis.
Listen, I got my own system.
Are you using Brawn and Beauty?
Brother, this is soap and water.
Oof.
That is a dangerous road, my friend.
Yeah. So are these dudes
that you're in with.
Nah, it's not like that.
No? What's it like?
It's like a brotherhood.
The kind with the Nikes and the Aliens?
They're just...
They're just trying to keep me
out of jail, that's all.
How?
You know, legal advice,
and they know how to work the courts
or whatever.
What's their angle?
Beth.
Wait, you...
You gonna sell out your own wife?
I mean...
It's not like she ever had my back.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Hold on.
What? She just gets to destroy my family?
Why? Because she's the mom?
She's not the only one in this.
I will protect Ruby.
I promise.
What if that's not up to you?
That's why I have to make sure
it all sticks to Beth.
(SIGHS)
That's heavy, man.
That's why I need your help.
Uh, what can I do?
You got eyes and ears.
If something doesn't,
you know, look or sound right,
you just pass it along.
Uh...
Even if I could...
I Know how close you guys are.
It's not that.
Well, you don't do anything,
you're gonna be wearing
one of these things, too.
No, that's not my kinda look.
Good thing is, I've...
got something for the chaffing.
(CHUCKLES)
Can we please pick our teams now?
Yes.
Thank you.
Who's going to do the holograms?
I don't know.
Because I don't do that.
I'll do it.
You do the color.
I can do both.
It'll take twice as long.
We'll figure it out.
I just talked to her last night.
You talk to her every night.
I accused her of stealing my blender,
which she denied.
And so, then I thought she really did it.
And then she got defensive.
So then it turned into this whole
passive-aggressive thing,
which it always does,
that had nothing to do
with the blender in the first place.
You're gonna get your blender back.
Just, maybe not right away.
It went back to the city.
How?
It says
he owes a bunch of property taxes.
Sounds like Gene.
He's going to lose a whole club over like,
9 grand?
STAN: Sounds like Gene.
All you gotta do is pay his back taxes.
What, like, first dibs?
Yeah, city doesn't want
to get stuck with that dump.
Well, we don't have enough anyway.
Family first, right?
(DOOR OPENS, CLOSES)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Hey.
What you doing?
Couldn't sleep.
You want a snack?
I already housed all your chips.
I can get more tomorrow.
Thanks.
Okay.
Good night.
Aunt Beth?
Yeah?
Was she always like this?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON TV)
What do you mean?
Just like, drops everything
to run off to Mackinaw with some rando?
Well, I don't know how rando he is.
I've never met him.
Maybe she didn't want
to bring him around until
it was serious, you know?
I mean, she just does
whatever she wants, whenever she wants.
Well that's...
totally your mom.
(CHUCKLES)
So not cool.
She's very impulsive.
Yeah.
Not the most responsible.
Like, at all.
She's a train wreck.
Yeah.
But, you know, that's what makes her
so great, right?
Huh?
When we were little,
life was kind of a bummer.
But she found a way to make it all...
fun.
Like how?
Like a million different ways.
But...
So we never went anywhere
for spring break, right?
And one year, she decided
that we should spend the night
in the camping section at Target.
Did you get caught?
Yes, we got caught.
(CHUCKLES)
But, she also convinced
the security guard to order us a pizza
and let us watch Fried Green Tomatoes
in the home theater section.
She makes me watch that
every spring break.
She can turn anything into a party.
Literally.
She just doesn't know when to leave.
I wish I was more like her, honestly.
Is this new guy cool?
(CHUCKLES)
He thinks he is.
At least she's having fun.
Yeah.
Get some sleep, bud.
(COUNTRY/REGGAE MUSIC
PLAYING ON CAR RADIO)
Hit me.
I think you've had enough.
One more.
I'm not doing that thing again.
I can't do it.
Try.
It's too dangerous while I'm driving.
It's upsetting.
Don't make me pull over.
(CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS)
How much longer?
Stop asking.
Then tell me.
You'll know when we get there.
You know, you are making a big mistake.
Do you think I want to be here?
It's your job.
It's my day off.
Whatever.
Then your boss is making a huge mistake.
Yeah?
Yeah.
'Cause good luck making money without me.
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(ENGINE STOPS)
What makes you so important?
I basically do everything.
I'm... I'm like the brains
behind the operation.
(CAR HONKS)
He doesn't see it that way.
Well then, he's...
sorely mistaken, because I basically
do ital. I...
I do.
I'm the one who...
I do the blender thing,
and I do the holograph, the shiny part.
That's me as well.
I'm the one who cuts
the sheets into bills.
It doesn't sound hard.
Oh, it doesn't?
Well, it is hard.
Do you think people are
buying sheets of money?
No, because it wouldn't fit
into their wallet!
(DOOR CLOSES)
It has to be cut!
(DOORS LOCK)
(BREATH TREMBLING)
(INAUDIBLE)
You know who the really
important people are?
The ones who don't have
to tell you how important they are.
(ENGINE STARTS)
WOMAN: Sidwell number 09-875-688-4.
Fourteen unit apartment building,
back taxes of $21,800.
Do I have any bids?
Okay.
Moving on.
Sidwell Number 02-467-8895-3.
Banquet hall.
Back taxes of $12,482.
Right here.
Any other bids?
Pick up your title
at the table and pay the cashier.
Oh, my God.
Ruby, hi.
I didn't know you were in real estate.
I'm not.
We're... Yup.
We're paying a tax bill.
What do you guys do?
Hey, great bag.
Oh. She's the one with the hook-up.
Her son's a mathlete with Harry.
Oh.
By the way, how did Barnaby Prep
kill us at semi-finals?
I keep telling Harry
you can't win until you learn how to lose.
Well, they're going to learn real fast
if they keep getting
those quadratic equations.
Sidwell number 82-667-8230-9.
(SIGHS)
Crap.
Adult entertainment center.
Back taxes of $9,172.
Do I have a...
Here.
WOMAN: Any other bids?
$9,200.
I didn't see this one.
$9,300?
Yes.
$9,400.
(WHISPERS)
That's all we have.
WOMAN: Do I hear $9,500?
You already have one!
It's just such a steal.
Yeah.
From us.
But you can't win
until you learn how to lose.
WOMAN: Anyone else?
Anyone?
Pay the cashier.
See you at school.
Your bag's a fake.
WOMAN: Okay.
Moving on, Sidwell number...
(ENGINE STOPS)
Morning, sunshine.
Mm.
What are we doing here?
Paying our respects.
To who?
The cast of Cocoon?
Skittles.
Oh, my God.
He helps old people?
I don't know about that.
But he won't steal from them no more.
Now can I please have my Skittles?
Sit tight.
(LOCK BEEPS)
NICK: Hey.
Where is he?
Out back.
Hey, big-time.
Hard at work, huh?
Love what you do,
never work a day in your life.
You're not making things easy for me.
Nope.
What are you thinking?
I had to do what I had to do.
Huh.
Well, that's playing it smart.
Ball.
See, while y'all
are over there planting trees
or doing whatever the hell you doing,
I'm losing money.
What about the position you put me in?
Oh? You have a lover's spat?
I was making progress.
My money can't wait.
See, that's always been your problem.
You never were a big-picture guy.
Because I don't see it your way, right?
No.
Never did.
It's like they say.
What's that?
Keep your eye on the ball.
You know what else they say?
I feel like you're going to tell me.
Hit 'em where it hurts.
I hope you're right.
Ball.
Later, brother.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
You hear that?
(ENGINE REVVING)
The motorcycle?
No, not that.
I don't hear anything.
Exactly.
Because Annie's not
in the back seat asking us
if we'd rather die
of a thousand bee stings
or be mauled by a bear.
That one's her fave.
Yeah, 'cause she thinks
there's a right answer.
Bees.
The bear.
'Cause eventually, you go numb.
You don't feel it anymore.
The bear's way faster.
Not if it starts at your feet
and works his way up.
What if the bees decide
to sting you one at a time?
Like they're waiting in line at the DMV?
If she was here, she would settle it.
No, she'd tell us we were both wrong.
Just weird not having her around.
It'd be weird
not having you around, either.
He told you?
You should never have had
to make that deal.
Come on.
Seriously.
No boy's gonna break us up.
Say you were allergic to bees.
Fine, bees.
Now let's go get Annie back.
She's here right now?
Yep. Replace the floors, little paint.
This place will be
up and running in 30 days.
I gotta call you back.
How's it all looking?
Better than my knockoff bag.
Mm.
'Cause we don't think this is
the right place for you.
I'm going to need a refund, by the way.
You know how they say
a space chooses you?
This one chose us.
You're not a right fit.
(CHUCKLES)
What's this?
Our offer.
To take it off your hands.
Well, this is way less than I paid.
Yeah, we're trying to get it for a steal.
WOMAN: All set in here.
I can't do this right now.
My inspector's here.
Quite a place you got here.
Right?
(BOTH LAUGH)
I used to get my groove on
back in the day.
Right?
Well, now it's going to be a dog hotel.
Oh, it might be cheaper
to house them at the Four Seasons.
Excuse me?
Plumbing, electrical, ADA,
got to dock you for all of it.
What?
That's ridiculous.
Hey, I'm just getting started.
Fire suppression, asbestos.
And I don't know what you got going on
with that tinkler back there.
It's all got to go.
Excuse me, ma'am.
You dropped this.
Oh, sweet of you, hun.
Mm-hmm.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(TIRES SCREECH)
MAN: My mom found me
this morning in our driveway.
I've never seen this guy in my life.
You bashed my face in.
MICK: I don't know
what he's talking about.
Look at his hand.
Cut it shaving.
Your knuckles?
She knows.
She was in his car.
She saw the whole thing.
Ma'am, do you know this guy?
Yeah.
COP: Were you with him last night?
Did you witness anything?
Yeah.
First degree murder.
Pardon?
Of my vagina.
What's that now?
Kind of like Lizzie Borden
with the hatchet,
except the hatchet is his...
So, he didn't assault this man?
(CHUCKLES)
Trust me, Officer.
He wouldn't have had the energy.
Oh, my God, she's lying.
We haven't even left
our motel room in days.
Are you sure you don't have
the wrong guy?
Who else would look like him?
A lot of people say I look like the guy
from Lord of the Rings.
(CHUCKLES)
Baby, I'm starving.
Let's go get our electrolytes up.
Are we free to go or what?
(CHUCKLING)
How'd she do?
Well, Megan Thee Stallion called,
and she's her new backup dancer.
Um, no, she's going
to be my backup dancer.
Ah. Okay.
Go wash up.
It's taco night.
How'd it go?
We're back in the club.
I knew you'd get it.
I gotta go print.
Make sure Harry
doesn't eat all the taco shells.
(CHUCKLES)
So, uh...
whose name is it in?
Ah, she's not going anywhere, is she?
Nah-uh.
Family first, huh?
Now you're getting it, Hill.
Okay.
Good to see you.
Bye.
Bye, babe.
(SIGHS)
(SCOFFS)
I Knew it.
No, thanks.
For back there.
Oh.
Running would have made more sense.
Well...
Couldn't have you
getting arrested in front
of your grandpa, could we?
He's not my grandpa.
Then who is he?
They call him the janitor.
Oh, no.
Did clean up.
Clean up?
Anything that needed to be dissolved.
Okay.
Then flushed.
Got it.
He was like a grandpa.
That's sweet.
The kind of guy you want
to do things for.
Like that sister of yours.
It's not the same thing.
Mm.
How can one bitch
have such a hold on so many people?
She's not all that.
Then why are we both here?
Let's call the ladies.
He should have taken me.
He never will.
I need career advice.
(ALL LAUGHING)
No, no, no, wait, wait, wait.
What about... what about, uh... lip balm?
Oh, forget lip balm.
No, lip balm sells.
Dude, dude, you've got to have lip balms.
Yeah?
What do you think, man?
I think I got something on her.