ANNIE: Previously on Good Girls...
Electrical companies,
plumbing, construction,
the shell companies
build whatever projects
Gang Fairy Godfather could get approved.
Which is why he needs you in that seat.
So all your projects and whatever,
they're all above board.
Wow. This is, like, kind of amazing.
So is he.
I'm really happy for you.
Oh, uh, it's not like that.
You got another zit?
Beth's not the only one
that's going down.
My wife's in it, too.
More the merrier.
You can't give that stuff to the DA.
Vance, what are you guys waiting for?
Ask your friend.
TINA: I just need you
to answer something.
How do you make it
through your day being such a moron?
(GRUNTS, GUNSHOTS ON TV)
(EARS RINGING)
(GUNSHOTS, EXPLOSIONS ON TV)
All right, turn it off.
No.
(MAN SCREAMS ON TV)
Your guy died.
I'm not going.
What do you mean?
I told him he could skip.
Why?
It's a special day.
Yeah, he has a math test.
It's his half-birthday.
BOY: You got pawned!
I just wish you'd ask me first before
you make any promises.
Can you cut those a little smaller?
You know, no other parents
celebrate half-birthdays.
Do I get a present?
Sure.
No.
I'll text you guys my list.
Just get him half a present.
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
(CELL PHONE CONTINUES CHIMING)
Here.
Who's Vanessa?
Just take it.
I! asked for almond milk.
They were out.
So what is this?
Milk.
I'm lactose intolerant.
Don't be such a woman.
(POP SONG PLAYING ON SPEAKERS)
(SIGHS)
Excuse me?
Can I download my own ringtone?
My grandson plays clarinet, and...
Excuse me, sir?
Vance Madison.
Employee ID number 53802.
Thank you.
Yeah, I need to track a stolen phone.
Boland. Elizabeth.
Mm, it kinda burns.
That's how you know it's working. See?
Ow!
Oops.
All right.
That's enough.
Go get ready for school.
It's supposed to remove age spots.
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
Who got you into this?
(SIGHS)
Hey, Ruby.
Here you go.
What's up, man?
(EXHALES HEAVILY)
I need you to do something for me.
Name it.
Share, brother.
(SIGHS)
I didn't know what else to do.
I mean, you could've told me.
They were gonna take Ruby down, too, Dean.
I've Known you for 30 years.
I'm not the bad guy here, man.
They're all I got.
ANNIE: (SIGHS) Let's do it
in the bathtub next.
KEVIN: Mm, that never works.
Why not?
Unless you have, like,
one of those fancy tubs,
it's like you're on a bobsled.
No, no. We'd be facing each other.
Then we're, like, on a weird rowboat sitch
where everyone's freezing.
Fine. Okay, um...
What about... the closet?
That's kinda limited.
I like a challenge.
(POP SONG PLAYING ON PHONE)
Huh? Sorry.
It must be on shuffle.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no. No!
This is a banger.
(ROMANTIC POP SONG PLAYING LOUDER)
(SIGHS)
It's... Train.
Whatever. I know.
They're easy to hate on.
I love everything about them.
Which closet?
Broom.
(SIGHS)
All right
(ANNIE MOANS)
(CHUCKLES)
You know, I...
(SIGHS)
...never thought that I'd
date someone who loves Train
as much as me.
Are we?
What?
Dating?
Aren't we?
(SIGHS) I mean, uh...
Maybe.
(SIGHS) Um, what do you wanna Call it?
Why do we have to call it anything?
Because we've been doing the other "it"
now for, like,
three days straight,
so I'm just kinda curious.
Mm.
I don't know.
Really?
(SIGHS)
Come on.
Isn't this something that we could settle
in the broom closet?
No. I'm kinda tired.
Hey, come on.
My junk needs to recharge.
The song isn't even done yet.
SCOTT: Your supporters are highly loyal,
with 60% being completely or very certain
of their choice.
Hispanic support with some college
to college grad
is also solid,
with an overwhelming majority
in strong favor
of your "clean up the streets"
message.
Polls also show 83%
of voters want a visionary,
as opposed to a politician.
Uh, is that part good?
Are you a politician?
(CHUCKLES) No.
Then it's not bad.
(CHUCKLES) Okay.
And women like you in red.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Thank you, Scott.
Seriously?
It's a power color.
I hate red.
You gotta play by the rules.
Why?
'Cause then we get to do things our way.
Urban garden, basketball courts,
ice arena,
nature trails all over.
Olympic-sized swimming pool.
Cafe, lounge, amphitheater.
Money laundering, bribery, extortion,
all wrapped up in your friendly
neighborhood rec center.
(SLURPING LOUDLY)
(EXHALES) Okay.
Okay.
That's it?
What more did you want?
Need a warrant.
Great. Get one.
We need someone to sign off on that.
Can you do that?
Mm-mmm.
And you can't do that.
No. Need access to a judge.
Need my old job back.
To even get access.
My hands are tied.
We're on vacation.
(SLURPING LOUDLY)
What are you gonna do?
Not us.
How would we get it?
Isn't that what you guys do?
Uh... Sorry.
Are you asking us to break the law?
Does that make you uncomfortable?
Consider it a favor.
DAVE: But the clock's ticking,
because we used miles
for our room and they're almost gone.
Then we're even.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
Time?
Five minutes, 40 seconds.
I can do better.
I love that she needs
the whole look to get into character.
Okay, what about dinner Thursday?
Won't it be weird?
Stan loves Deansie.
Not the problem.
It'll make you guys better.
Or it'll make us worse.
We'll just talk about their stupid
skincare business.
How's that gonna help?
When was the last time
we all got boozed up
and it didn't end in a hug fest?
When was the last time
we got all boozed up?
Exactly.
(DOOR OPENS)
Time?
It was faster.
You didn't even time me, did you?
How are we gonna
even get into the building?
Why don't we just go during the day?
Because he'll be there.
So, distract him.
How?
You know how.
No, I don't.
Why did Watergate fail?
'Cause they got caught.
'Cause they were men.
She means use your hoo-ha.
Just stop.
Worked with the wire.
You use your hoo-ha.
I'm just saying, take the brousin to lunch
or something.
I thought we agreed on
"Gang Fairy Godfather."
"Brousin" makes more sense.
I'm not doing anything with the brousin.
Why not?
Because then he'll Know it's me.
Okay, you guys, we obviously go at night.
What about the security guard?
(SIGHS) We'll use my hoo-ha.
Can I help you?
May I use your bathroom?
(HUMMING)
(KNOCK AT WINDOW)
Okay.
(STRAINING)
What took you so long?
I actually had to pee.
I'm, like, covered in thorns.
Okay, here we go.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
The penguin is in the igloo.
ANNIE: Huh?
RUBY: The horse is in the barn.
ANNIE: Then where's the security guard?
He's still at his desk.
ANNIE: Can you just say that from now on?
Ten-four.
ANNIE: Bye.
Over and out.
(ANNIE SCOFFS)
I'm just trying to make it fun.
(ANNIE GRUNTING)
Yeah. Give me the L-15.
Wait.
The L-16.
They don't have names on them.
The crocodile teeth ones.
They all have teeth.
Oh, my God.
Crocodile, you amateur.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(WHISPERS) Where is he?
What's his 20?
Huh?
ANNIE: Where is he?
RUBY: Uh, he's eating a KitKat.
ANNIE: UA, but we heard a door.
Yeah, he's got a whole stash
in the closet.
He's just getting a snack.
Okay, well, hurry up.
Come on. Come on.
(EXCLAIMS TRIUMPHANTLY)
Bada bing, bada boom.
What's going on?
It won't open.
It's unlocked.
Oh, my God.
What?
Do you have a tool for one of those?
(ANNIE SIGHS)
That is a whole different set
of YouTube videos.
Okay.
Maybe his assistant has,
like, a Spare or something.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hmm.
He's kinda cute.
Got it.
Sick.
He has a card for everything.
(PHONE VIBRATING)
Talk to me, baby.
BETH: We okay?
He's on the move.
You got this.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
Come on, ladies.
Give me a sign.
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
Well?
(SIGHS) I tore my jeans
on my way back out the window.
No!
Yeah, my favorite pair.
Where we at?
You guys want in on this?
What are we gonna do?
10% off at Chili's?
I could do a marg.
Hill, you up?
Nope.
Guess where I went?
You smell like a cantina.
I only had one.
I didn't ask how many.
Fine, three.
All right, where did you go?
When was the last time you had
Southwestern egg rolls?
(GRUNTS)
I bought some from Kroger's last week.
No, at Chili's.
(EXHALES)
I don't know, Ruby.
Remember that time
someone pulled the fire alarm
and we all had to go outside?
And we sat at the wrong booth
when they let us back in.
You got halfway through that guy's
black bean burger
before you even realized.
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah, we were pretty bombed.
We haven't had fun like that in forever.
Need more like it.
How about Thursday?
They still got that Texas lemonade?
They do.
In.
So are the Bolands.
What do you mean?
We all used to have fun together.
Babe, I'm not going to Chili's
with no damn Bolands.
Fine.
Good.
They can come here.
What is wrong with you?
I don't want a situation.
It's just dinner.
It's gonna be weird.
Don't worry.
I got you covered.
How?
Dean will be there.
(EXHALES)
(YAWNS, SIGHS)
Something smells good.
What you working on over there?
KEVIN: Spanish omelet.
Mm!
Little chorizo.
Red peppers, fried potatoes.
And a pinch of salt.
Mm!
Just like we are in Barcelona.
Mm-hmm.
Mm.
Oh?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, sir.
What?
(CELL PHONE CHIMING)
Well, where's mine?
Everything you need is on the counter.
(CELL PHONE CHIMING)
Well...
It's just that, you know,
you usually make me one.
(CELL PHONE CHIMING)
Well, that's when we were roomies.
Well, what are we now?
You tell me.
(CELL PHONE CHIMING)
Oh, come on.
I mean, we're definitely
not dating, right?
We really can't just move past this?
Oh, I have.
(CELL PHONE CHIMING)
(SIGHS)
What is that?
Hinge.
(CELL PHONE CHIMING)
Wait, no.
This is Tinder.
You're...
back on the apps?
How else am I supposed to
put myself out there?
Why do you need to put yourself anywhere?
(SIGHS) 'Cause you don't want
to do this, right?
I don't... (SIGHS)
I don't want to not do this, okay?
And I definitely don't
want you doing this with anyone else.
So you don't wanna date?
Right.
But you don't wanna not date.
Essentially, you wanna not not date.
I think so.
But...
you wanna not not date anyone else?
No.
(CHUCKLES)
I mean...
Yeah, I'm...
I'm down with that.
Cool.
(CELL PHONE CHIMING)
You want cheese in yours?
Duh!
(CELL PHONE CHIMING)
Uh, you can just turn that off.
Yeah, I think I will.
(CELL PHONE CHIMING)
Jesus.
How did you get so many matches on this?
I'm a catch.
Obviously.
No, you wanna know my secret?
Yes, please.
Uh, I just...
I think about the kinda tale
I wanna land, right?
And then I just sort of
cater my profile to the customer.
Sorry, like, you make stuff up, or...
Uh, I mean, it's more like,
I just sort of tell them
what they wanna hear,
then they come to you.
Have I ever volunteered
at an animal shelter?
I mean, no,
but I don't want them gassed either.
And once you figure it out,
it's like shooting fish in a barrel.
And I'm no, like, coder,
but I don't want some algorithm telling me
who I should be with.
Ooh!
Oaxacan street corn.
Um, Dad hates that cheese.
She is not wrong.
I'll make coleslaw.
Then, after dinner, you and Stan can be
on the same team.
For what?
Scattergories.
Wait, now we're doing a game night?
We just need to be normal
around each other.
We've never played Scattergories.
Twister?
You guys, I can get us into that office.
We've been using my hoo-ha all wrong.
Hey, Sara, how are you?
It's a little late
for you to be up, isn't it?
Well, my bedtime's not
for another two hours.
(WHISPERING)
Go to your room.
What?
(LAUGHS) I can't believe
I finally met a girl who butt chugs.
Well, how else are you gonna
pound a White Claw?
Cheers.
So what did you major in at Michigan?
Oh, um, science.
God, how did you get through organic chem?
I just really love organic stuff.
It's actually pretty easy at Whole Foods.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(BOTH SIGH)
You know, most girls are
turned off by my profile.
You're kidding me. Why?
The get all uptight about
the hating kids stuff.
I! mean, kids suck.
Right?
Yeah.
Oh, hell yeah!
Jell-O shots.
Our fave.
To not remembering anything
tomorrow morning.
I will drink to that.
Mm.
(SHUDDERS) Ooh.
They go down easier the more you do 'em.
Oh, no, uh, I'm just...
I'm cold.
Should've brought a jacket.
Wanted you to, uh, have the full picture.
Appreciate it.
Now that you've had a preview...
Can I borrow yours?
Seriously?
Next round will be on me.
Fine.
(SIGHS) You're sweet.
My mom always says that.
(CHUCKLES)
She is right.
Mm.
Ready when you are.
Uh, ready for what?
That shot.
Right. Yes. Okay.
Let's just get the waitress.
But then you'll see me roofie it.
Will you marry me?
(CHUCKLES)
(SMOOTH JAZZ SONG PLAYING)
You gotta be kidding me.
Please, Clark.
I'm gonna burst.
You should see a doctor.
Showtime.
(EXHALES)
What took you so long?
Oh. (SIGHS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
These are, like, really complicated.
Mm.
Mm. (CHUCKLES) Mm.
Just tastes like tequila.
Really? No.
They, uh... First, they light 'em on fire.
I came in and looked for you.
(SCOFFS)
Well, they...
They wouldn't do it inside.
What's going on?
Okay. Um...
I'm gonna level with you.
That's never a good sign.
I went outside to ask the valet
if I could leave my car here overnight.
Or maybe it's a great sign.
Yeah, maybe.
(CHUCKLES)
KEVIN: Uh, hey.
Beat it, bro.
We don't have any money.
No, no.
It's okay.
I know him.
How?
Uh, he's my...
roommate.
Oh, we're back to that now, huh?
RUBY: Clark is on the prowl. I repeat.
Clark is a-prowlin'.
Who is that guy?
He's just a...
He's a co-worker.
You work at a mini-mart.
Yeah, he's...
He's the boss.
SO now you wearing your boss' jacket?
Uh, no, he...
He was thinking about
adding a jacket to the uniform,
and he wanted feedback,
so, obviously, I'm gonna tell him...
smaller sizes.
Hey, you know what?
I'm sorry.
Kevin, please.
This is my fault.
Can we please just talk about this later
when we get home.
See, I really thought
things would be different now.
I promise you.
It's not what it looks like, okay?
But can't talk about it here, so please.
Is everything cool?
Yeah.
It's fine.
Listen, I don't wanna
get in the way of anything here.
No, that's fine.
I was just leaving.
No.
No, I feel like I should go.
No to me, or no to him?
We literally just met, so...
How'd you meet?
Uh, Bumble, Hinge?
I don't even remember.
She's all yours, man.
Wanna go do another shot?
Yes.
I got phone records, bank accounts,
names, numbers...
VANCE: Quite a haul.
He knows everything.
VANCE: Gotta say...
None of this looks good for a lady
who's tough on crime.
What do you want?
Let me buy you guys a drink.
Why?
Talk strategy.
What's good around here?
There's a Chili's.
Perfect! Can I throw my bike in the back?
(DOOR HANDLE RATTLING)
Can you take the child lock off?
That doctor dude sounds way more messed up
than you.
Therapist.
Textbook.
Mm. Textbook what?
Gay.
He's just British.
Your ex-husband?
Super gay.
Don't tell me. Noah?
Everyone in law enforcement is gay.
And why is it that I am listening to you
about any of this again?
'Cause I'm the only one
who calls it like it is.
But you just have the one call.
(CHUCKLES)
Okay.
You know who couldn't be
more straight and into you?
Lemme guess.
Your hobo friend.
He's experiencing homelessness.
Whatever.
That dude's all-sac.
I just don't think
I should be with anybody right now.
Why is that?
Because I have
(SIGHS) issues.
Everyone does.
Well, mine could be studied.
Well, at least you're not in denial.
Thanks?
I'm serious.
Being aware of it means
you can't be that messed up.
How can a bro like you
be such a good listener?
I'm not really a bro.
Sorry. Bruh.
(CHUCKLES)
I'm gay.
That's funny.
Everything on my profile is made up.
But what about
the picture of you in Jamaica
with the cheetah?
Photoshop.
But you had on a backwards hat.
To convince my dad.
(CHUCKLES)
Hmm. Well, okay then.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Mm.
Mm!
(BOTH MOANING)
You know, this is actually
one of the best dates
I've ever had with a girl.
And you, my friend, make very convincing
human garbage.
Could I get a selfie for my dad?
Why not?
Um, sorry.
Why?
For what I'm about to do.
(FAINT TV CHATTER)
(DEAN LAUGHING)
Hey.
Have you seen this bit,
where the guy, the dude from SNL,
he recaps TV shows?
Nope.
It is genius.
He does this thing where
he tries to guess what the show is
based on the title, but he has no idea.
How could you?
STAN: How are those housewives
in the ATL?
Didn't watch.
What did you guys do?
We went out for drinks.
Twice in one week?
Ran into a friend of yours.
Yeah?
What, were you trying to
show off in front of your bike dads?
No.
You must have felt like a real big shot.
It's not like that.
What's it like then?
You put me in jail.
Not on purpose.
What's the difference?
You would still be in there.
This guy's trying to make sure
I don't go back.
Oh, the grown man in tights.
He's got my back, okay?
You're such an idiot.
Yeah, for trusting you.
He's not your friend!
At least he's trying to help.
To get to me.
What are you talking about?
I have to get the city
to plug his stupid face creams for, like,
conventions or hotels or whatever.
Wait... he said that?
He was never in it for you.
I really did want Nevada.
She could lose everything.
So can we.
She has kids, Stanley.
Who's sleeping down that hall?
Since when do you get to
decide to put a woman away?
It's not just about her.
'Cause I don't remember marrying a judge.
You can't even see it anymore.
I can see we're not in a courtroom.
You could dress it up, talk around it.
At least in court, you get a jury.
But we're just criminals now.
You remember our old Nissan?
Rust bucket?
Mm-hmm.
It started out with a little patch
on the door.
But eventually,
it took over the whole car.
Come on.
When's the last time
we've been to church?
It bought our daughter a kidney.
Or volunteered at the food bank?
It pays for Harry's school.
And the Crazy thing...
is that I don't even feel guilty anymore.
'Cause we deserve it!
Justify it all you want,
but eventually,
it rots out the floorboards.
I guess we should
cancel dinner with the Bolands.
Yeah, probably.
(NICK AND SCOTT LAUGHING)
SCOTT: Oh, dude, dude.
She practically broke my jock.
Sounds like a wild night, buddy.
I was like...
I was like, "Chill.
"I Know you can't get enough,
but Papa's gotta sleep."
(CHUCKLES)
Hey, where's the file key?
Top right.
Yeah, that's where I left it.
Hmm.
You're gonna see her again?
Hell no.
I cannot keep up with your women.
SCOTT: Oh, here.
That's weird.
You must have moved it.
I didn't.
Well, it wasn't me.
Can you grab the night logins
from security?
Yeah.
(DOOR OPENS)
(RIO LAUGHS)
Who is she?
Not your boy's girl.
You think this is funny?
(LAUGHS)
What did she get?
What do you think?
I think you got played, brother.
(LAUGHS)
(GUNSHOTS ON TV)
BOY: Yes! Suck it!
(EAR RINGING)
All right, chief, time for homework.
One more level.
You got a book report, buddy.
BOY: I'll do it later.
It's late.
Mom said I could stay up.
Did you get almond milk?
I got oat milk.
It's better for you.
Where did you get this?
It was on my car in the parking lot.
She's your buddy's wife, right?
I like her.
Why?
TINA: I don't know.
She seems like a leader.
I hope she wins.
You know wnat?
Me too.
(YELLING) Die!
Hey!
Turn it off.
I can't see.
Turn if off.
Mom, tell your husband to move.
Just let him finish, honey.
BOY: Mom!
TINA: Vance!
What the hell are you doing?
Book report. Now!
BETH: Hey, you're here.
I Know you're not allowed to endorse
one way or the other,
but I thought you could wear one
while you work out.
Would you take a seat?
Uh-oh.
Am I falling behind with working women,
ages 18 to 34, who like to eat food?
No. (GRUNTS)
I have something that's gonna help you.
Thought you weren't allowed to do that?
What? I don't mean the election.
What's this?
Everything you were
looking for last night.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Well, you or your sister,
or someone else that you're working for,
swiped in at 9:38
with my assistant's ID.
So, when you're done,
I am gonna need 'em back.
What happens now?
I don't understand.
I wake up with a gun to my face
in the middle of the night?
You have a Campaign to win.
And then, when we're done,
you roll me up in a carpet for trash day?
Relax. Please.
No, that's not my style.
I'm more the guy that
makes things difficult.
I Know people, right?
You got a husband
that's facing a long stretch.
Sister's got a record.
I mean, those two are low-hanging fruit.
And there's no way that
that friend of yours can pay for
her son's private school.
That's just a quick call to state,
get her tax returns.
You know how that goes.
Yeah, can't let you off that easy, Beth.
You have a lot of work to do.
(ACOUSTIC FOLK SONG PLAYING)
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Stop. Right there.
Zug Island Holdings.
DAVE: Where does it go?
Romeo Pipe Fitters
and B and J Construction.
Could make a case from the numbers that
it's padded for kickbacks.
But none of it goes back to him.
Just leave it on the table, man.
Beth wanted to, you know,
make sure you guys still had it, so...
That's a lot of slaw, bruh.
It's the half of what she made.
(CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS)
Listen, man, I'm sorry...
(MUSIC STOPS)
We're in a cult, dude.
Yeah, they got us good.
(SIGHS)
You wanna...
You wanna take the brotherhood down?
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
Now you're knocking?
You said to.
(SCOFFS) When have
you ever listened to me?
Nah, don't be like that.
What do you want?
I'll take an apology.
What did I do now?
You hurt my feelings.
How's that?
If you need something,
darlin', all you gotta do is ask.
He's your brother.
Cousin.
Family.
He's in our way.