RUBY: Previously on Good Girls...
You're not supposed to be here.
Yeah, neither are you.
This is the only way
we're going to turn this around.
How does helping him help me?
I'm saving up to run.
I'd rather have a lawyer.
We've never made
you smile like all this just did.
Because, I told you,
this is what gets us out.
No, that's what gets you off.
This whole time,
I thought he was the problem.
He's just the excuse.
Anyone who wears a Cardigan,
shouldn't be doing what he does.
What are you, a priest?
Just trying to help.
You got my wife shot?
I got you your money.
RUBY: Last party, I had to be
the damn go-between
for my husband and my best friend.
I want you out of her life.
You get us in that club,
and she'll never see me again.
What's going on with you?
My wife was laundering
her gang's money through my business.
What happened to her?
Not a damn thing.
You still coming to the game?
Dude, I wouldn't miss it.
BETH: So, he's back in?
What do you want from me? I caved.
Not Washington?
BETH: The Queen.
I hate Canadians.
You said all we had to do was print it.
And then drop it.
BETH: I assumed
that you meant in our country.
DEALER: Seven's a winner.
(CHEERING)
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Okay, whoa, whoa, wait.
Try it this way.
Okay, ready? Ready.
Ready?
(ALL CHEERING)
Oh, my God.
RUBY: Why do you keep winning?
ANNIE: I'm trying not to.
I swear, I swear to God
I, I'm usually never,
ever, ever this lucky.
Gimme those.
Bets in, ladies.
What do you think?
Hard 10.
How would we train thousands of pigeons?
You only need one.
One pigeon's gonna carry
all that cash across the border?
Well, not all at once.
Thank you, ladies.
RUBY: Y'all killed it tonight.
Ugh. The launch sequence
was all messed up.
What are you talking about?
That was the best part.
And then it felt like
no one got the crawling
on the ground part.
Hello. Obviously, an homage
to Sandy B at the end of Gravity.
Oh, love you guys.
Bye.
(WHISPERS) Hey.
What about drones?
Like the ones they use
in Guadalajara for heroin?
Well, it's easier than training a pigeon.
Yeah, and way less range.
Plus you better
pray for perfect weather.
They have them at Hobby Lobby.
But you know what can fly in a storm.
Let's go tomorrow.
I'm busy.
Okay. And we can look into your bird, too.
No, no, I, I really am busy.
I, I have plans.
Doing what?
Jobbie Nooner, baby.
Aren't you a little old for that?
You'd really put an age
on the Mardi Gras of the Midwest?
That's tomorrow?
Taking a "me" day.
So sue me.
No, no, no, no, no.
You're going to a party,
on a boat...
that is literally on the border of Canada?
Yeah, my buddy Tim just got out
of rehab, and we always go, So.
Where you don't have
to go through customs?
And there's millions of boats.
Filled with tons of drunk people
who aren't paying attention
to what anyone else is doing.
Okay.
Okay. Yes.
I see where you're going with this.
And it could work.
What was your friend in rehab for?
Meth.
They let him keep the boat license.
(DOOR OPENS)
Look, when do we set sail?
Going on a boat?
An.
Yeah, you know, for a girls' trip.
Where?
Detroit River.
Why?
Girl stuff.
Pedicures.
Waxing.
It's like a day spa/sunset cruise.
Sounds shady.
I think it's how they dodge
all those health department codes.
Yes, just one of those
spa days that ends up with
a bullet in her other knee?
(CAN OPENS)
I'm just looking out for my wife.
A little self-care never hurt anybody.
I would never let
anything happen to my maid of honor.
That a promise?
Oh, we have a deal.
Mm-hmm.
Well, I think y'all look great.
Well, tell that to the alpaca
sitting on my crotch.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(DOOR OPENS)
Well, it got him out of here, didn't it?
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING ON SPEAKERS)
Hey.
What, uh...
What's all this?
I thought we could all eat together.
Why?
For a change.
Huh.
Well, Ben's at his dad's.
Well, then it's dinner a deux.
Okay.
It's a pretty fancy setup
for tortillas and soy sauce.
Not what we're having.
That's all I have.
Lemon chicken piccata.
What...
You made this?
Well, it's not Olive Garden,
but it's the best with what I could find.
Jeez, what...
The hell is this?
A white carrot?
Parsnip.
And a few other root veggies.
Mm!
It's So good.
Thanks, man.
No, thank you, man.
No, no.
Thank you for letting me crash.
No. Thank you for picking all this up.
NBD.
(SCOFFS) Later.
Must have been expensive.
Not at all.
I mean, last I checked,
food was not free.
Or maybe you're just not looking
in the right place.
Kevin?
Mm?
I went a little heavy
on the, uh, rosemary.
Where did you get this food?
Kroger.
(CHUCKLES)
Thank Jesus.
Yeah, they throw out the best stuff.
Like, even before it goes bad.
(GAGS)
Ew.
What is wrong with you?
It's fine.
It's trash food.
You never would have Known.
Mm. Except I do.
So, if I paid, would it taste better?
(SCOFFS) I mean, I guess not.
Then what's the difference?
The amount of E. coll.
I washed it.
Where? In the toilet?
(SIGHS)
I thought you were cooler than this.
Oh, why? Because I'm not down
with gourmet dumpster diving?
No, because you think
money makes everything better.
Doesn't it?
Uh, yeah, sure.
If you want to live
for what you don't have.
Oh, boy.
Here we go.
This treadmill you're on...
Excuse me for wanting more.
...won't get you anywhere.
It's called the American Dream, baby.
Okay, well, while you're dreaming,
you're also sleeping through
a pretty choice piece of chicken.
(SCOFFS) At least I won't have
hepatitis A, Bor C.
Whatever.
Ugh! Ugh!
I won't tell you where I got that.
(LAUGHTER, INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Hey, guys. Uh, I thought
we were meeting down at the park.
Oh, the guys can wait.
You're not going
anywhere with that derailer.
Let me see that.
Hey, uh, look, I'm sorry.
I'm doing everything I can
with that night cream.
Oh, I get it.
Guys don't really like
stuff on their face before bed.
Right? Get stuff all over your pillow...
Not why we're here.
Oh.
The other night at the meeting...
Ugh, yeah, I over shared.
It was beautiful, Dean.
You're going through
a lot right now, you know?
You got a lawyer?
Not one that's gonna keep me out of jail.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Well, you do now.
Oh.
Oh, that's so cool.
Never lost a case.
Which is why I definitely
can't afford him.
Don't worry about it.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Dean...
You're family now.
That bitch has done enough to you.
(DOOR OPENS)
Hi, boys.
Pulled 'em out of the freezer,
so they got that big ice cube you like.
Thanks.
Do you guys want a refill?
No, we're fine.
Good.
Don't forget to wear
the reflective stuff.
We'll look out for him.
Oh, uh, Danny's
hockey game got rescheduled.
I got him a ride with the Simpson kid.
You just need to pick him up.
Sure.
(DOOR CREAKS)
(SIGHS)
Saddle up, cowboy.
ANNIE: Take a bunch So you can layer.
All right, here.
We're not here to party.
So you'd rather stick out?
I just want to make a run for the border.
Yeah, well, that's why you got to blend.
BETH: Where is your friend?
He's probably just gassing up the boat.
Sure this is the right place?
It's where we park every year.
What if I have to pee on the water?
Well, get it all out now.
Where?
This is also where we pee every year.
Is that your guy?
Oh, here we go.
(SIREN CHIRRUPS)
Mm-mmm.
Nope.
What are you doing?
It's an open container.
We have a cooler full
of Canadian counterfeit.
Will you please just act chill?
He's coming.
Okay. Music on or off?
On. On.
(LOUD MUSIC PLAYS)
Off, off, off.
(MUSIC STOPS)
(EXHALES)
(RADIO CHATTER)
Mike?
Hey, Ruby.
What's going on?
What's in that?
A whole lot of fun.
Yeah, it's her first Jobbie Nooner's.
So, we went all out.
Open it on up?
You know, if this is about
the parking or something,
we could pull up...
What's in the cooler?
RUBY: You put your boy on me?
You're welcome.
He gave Beth a ticket.
Yeah, lucky that's all she got.
We could've just slipped over.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON TV)
Not on the weekend,
where they triple border patrol.
We were going to bury it
and go back tomorrow.
That's just brilliant.
Drive right through customs
and pick it up.
'Cause nobody's ever thought
of doing that on Gull Island.
Yeah.
Smugglers.
Not a bunch of moms.
Is that her angle?
I need it back.
Oh, what else you got?
I don't know.
Hmm.
Come see me when you do.
Who are you, my dad?
No. You know, I'm just worried
that she's going to come up
with something even dumber.
I'm not some kid
you caught with a case of beer.
This isn't just beer, Ruby.
I need to make that drop.
And I need to keep you out of jail.
MAN: He's ready for you.
MAN: Now, you don't look like
you're here for the sewer
expansion meeting.
I'm not sure I'd have a lot to offer.
(CHUCKLES) Come on.
You know, they're actually
really interesting.
Really?
No.
(LAUGHS)
Not at all.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
So what can I do for you, Elizabeth?
(EXHALES)
It's really stupid.
Oh, I've heard it all.
And it might be crossing a line.
I'm okay with that.
(SIGHS)
It's kind of more of a favor.
Is it a parking ticket?
No.
Okay, because, you know,
people hit me up with that all the time.
It's a trespassing ticket.
(CHUCKLES)
Oh.
Okay.
So, what's next?
Burning Man?
It's a long story.
Try me.
I got time.
It's more of a thing for, you know,
your brother-cousin.
Him.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Which I can't explain to a judge, so...
(PA BEEPS)
MAN: (ON PA) We're waiting for
you in the conference room.
You know what?
You're busy.
Look, it's just, um...
I don't, I don't like...
to get involved with his... things.
I never should have asked.
Just puts me in a bad place, you know.
Go to your meeting.
This never happened.
I'm an idiot.
Wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no. No.
Hold on. Hold on.
(SIGHS)
I'll do it.
You really don't have to.
I really want to.
Come on.
Thank you.
But...
You're going to have
to do something for me.
Yeah. What?
I'mma put you to work.
(ANNIE SIGHS)
Please, no.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Just try it.
I don't want to release
whatever is trapped under there.
Don't you want to add rabies
to your hep A, B and C?
I guess.
(KEYS RATTLING)
(EXHALES)
I'm scared.
What is this?
Yeah, I'm no Shakespeare, but I am sorry.
Let me take you out.
Why?
To make up for the other night.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
Where?
Restaurant.
A real one?
You like French?
Oui.
Ma'am.
(CHUCKLES)
This place is like, legit fancy.
Oh, I know.
Hey, Kev.
KEVIN: Hey, Ange.
You come here often?
All the time.
Do you have, like,
a special table or something?
Sort of.
Right this way, madame.
What is this?
This is dinner.
What are you doing?
(GRUNTS) i.
Are you high?
Little bit.
This three-course meal right here.
No way!
One bite of each.
(CHUCKLES)
No. Never.
Not in hell. No.
I'll cook for you for a month.
No, no.
I don't want to be eating your trash food.
Your food. From whatever
grocery store you waste your money at.
No. Bye.
(GRUNTS)
Ben, too.
Ben is not ever hungry.
Well, he eats at his friend's house
so he doesn't have to at home.
One bite.
(INAUDIBLE) No.
Well, I, uh, started as a prep chef.
Mm-hmm.
Became a line cook and, uh...
And now I just sort of sub in
whenever I need cash.
Wow. Oh!
Forgot to ask, what was the...
It was like a little brown
chewy, sausage-y, garlic-y butter thing
on the, on the toothpick.
Ah, yes, yes, yes, yes.
That, uh, that was escargot.
Oh, escargot to you, monsieur. (CHUCKLES)
Snails.
What?
Yeah. See, even from the garbage,
they're pretty great, right?
Ew! I never would have
eaten those even inside.
That, my friend, is exactly the point.
Ugh! Ugh!
It doesn't matter.
Mm.
Mm-mmm, mm, mm-hmm.
(CHUCKLES)
Stop! Stop! Stop!
What are you doing?
I, I don't know.
You can't, you can't do that.
W-Why not?
Just...
(SIGHS)
Because it's, it's...
Because we're roommates.
So?
So, it's not...
It's just...
Just too easy.
That wasn't in your rules.
(SIGHS)
We just, we can't, okay?
(PHONE VIBRATING)
(EXHALES)
Um...
I... I have to...
I have to go.
I'll walk you.
No, no, no, it's fine.
Just stay and enjoy the, um...
Well, I'll see you at home.
(SONG PLAYING ON STEREO)
We get a P.O. box.
Or whatever they call it up there.
And just overnight it.
Customs.
Let 'em open it.
All they'll see is lots
and lots of Huggies.
Disguising, of course, the cash.
Why would anybody want to overnight
diapers to Canada?
Uh, they use those cloth ones up there.
I'm out.
You didn't want us
involved in the transport.
Next.
This is so low risk.
Yeah, until you're surrounded
by a bunch of Mounties
asking you why your Pampers
are so absorbent.
(MUMBLES) Huggies.
ANNIE: Hear me out.
There's a mini Submarine
called the Dolphin...
I thought we weren't
going to pitch this one.
No, you weren't going to pitch this one.
It's like 20 grand, Annie.
It's a lifelong investment, Ruby.
You wanted one
way before we started all this.
Look, it's just so simple, you know?
We blend in with the marine life,
we pop up, we ditch the cash, we...
This is ridiculous.
Agreed.
Why do we have to answer to you?
Oh, um...
(CLEARS THROAT)
How about my bag business,
my dancers, my club, and, uh, what?
My wife.
He makes some good points.
Are you ever going
to give us our money back?
Well, not with these ideas.
(SIGHS)
Well, let's just sell some bags, then.
Uh, that's not gonna be
necessary this evening.
Why is that?
Because you're gonna need
these guys to help you with your drop.
Hey.
How's it going?
Canadian dudes are the most respectful.
Yeah?
My nipple popped out too early
and they all looked away.
So, we good?
Oh, yeah, they're not going
to ask any questions.
That's it.
Yeah.
(GIGGLES)
Work all of that.
The girls also dance in Windsor.
And?
Fully nude.
Twice the money.
How does that help us?
They're real tight with the border guards.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING ON SPEAKERS)
Ugh.
Canadians.
Hey, how's it going?
IDs, please.
Have we met?
I don't think so.
Oh, wait. No, you're,
you're Krystal's friend, right?
That's it.
Oh, yeah!
Krystal. You know, Krystal.
What's her real name?
She's actually right behind us.
(GASPS)
How do you guys know her?
We met at the gym.
She teaches the most amazing Zumba class.
She's so flexible, you know?
Uh, (CLEARS THROAT)
Yeah, well, I wouldn't...
exactly call us friends.
Totally get it.
Um, where were you guys headed today?
We're going to go see her dance.
Hashtag women supporting women.
(RADIO CHATTER)
You should stop by.
Tell your wife you got
front row tickets to the Windsor Ballet.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, I wish I could.
I, um, I got my kid's
violin concert, so...
Next time, then.
(CLEARS THROAT)
All right.
You guys bring anything in?
Nope.
Just us.
Great. Then just pull over
right over there and pop the trunk.
But it's empty.
Should be quick, then.
Enjoy the show.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(BEEPING)
All right.
Good to go.
It's like, no biggie at all.
Well, we really appreciate it.
Anything to help a friend.
But we're going to need
our expenses covered.
I thought this was a favor.
(CHUCKLES)
And what expenses?
You know, the car is super heavy,
so it uses more gas.
Okay. Can we just do this already?
Okay.
How much?
5%.
Of what?
Um, just, like whatever's in the cooler.
That's not our money.
It's not our problem.
BETH: Ok... Okay.
Okay.
5%.
(SCOFFS)
How are we going to give them 5% of a cut
we don't even have?
How are we going to drop a cooler
that we don't have?
I don't like this SUV.
BETH: Why?
'Cause it's silver?
Because it hasn't moved.
It is a parking lot.
Let's roll, bitches!
DEAN: How bad Is it?
Remember Payne Stewart?
Isn't he a golfer?
Try US Open champion.
Okay.
He's up in his private jet, right?
On top of the world.
Tower loses communication.
So they scramble
some F-16s to check it out.
It turns out, the hull was breached.
Everyone inside was sound asleep
from no oxygen.
So what did they do?
Plane's on autopilot, just cruising.
All they gotta do...
is wake up.
And what happened?
After three and a half hours,
it runs out of fuel.
And they crash into a cornfield
in South Dakota.
Jesus.
That's not going to be you.
I already pled guilty.
I know.
And they want to move the trial date up.
Yeah.
So...
How do I not end up in the cornfield?
VANCE: Her.
It's not an option.
So are you the one printing fake money?
I already know where you're going
with this.
Cooking the books, committing wire fraud?
I'm not going to turn on my wife.
She did it.
I have kids.
So?
They need their mother.
Oh.
Okay.
So, what's Plan B?
Who taught them how to ride their bikes?
I mean, I did.
Who taught your son how to do a slapshot?
Worked on that for months.
Who built the tree house
in your backyard?
I bet they'd say
all that stuff is pretty important, too.
There's no plan B, man.
Come on, you guys.
She didn't leave you a parachute.
Wh... what am I supposed to do here?
Wake up.
GPS VOICE: Prepare to turn left.
This left or next left?
Mm.
Looks like next left.
Oh. Oh, no.
What's "Oh, no"?
That was the other left.
GPS VOICE: Recalculating.
Where do I go now?
I don't know.
It's... it's...
it's recalculating.
Where is this stupid place?
Here, here, here.
Next left.
It's cool.
We got it.
We're not there yet.
You must admit, Stanimal did deliver
on this one.
Yeah, except for the shakedown part.
That wasn't his plan.
Wasn't our plan, either.
Better than taking a jet ski.
Okay, I get that you need to defend him.
I'm not defending him.
But he has not made our life easier.
Aren't we in Canada with the money?
That's defending him.
GPS VOICE: In 400 feet,
take the next left.
I thought you were cool with him.
I am.
'Cause I know he's cool with you.
GPS VOICE: Recalculating.
Would you please tell me where to go?
God, that is so weird.
What?
It's just this guy.
Every time we make a move, he does, too.
Oh, God.
What?
Silver SUV?
Silver-ish.
That's the car from the parking lot.
Okay.
You don't know that.
Same plate.
GPS VOICE: In 100 feet,
please make a U-turn.
take the next left.
What do we do?
Just... just drive.
Where?
Just go, go!
GPS VOICE: Please make the next left.
Just turn that off!
I'm trying.
GPS VOICE:
Please make a left...
God!
She's persistent.
What about the drop?
We can't stop.
GPS VOICE: Recalculating.
The second, we do, we'll be surrounded
by Mounties.
Mounties ride horses.
Not when they're undercover.
We don't know that they're Mounties.
Okay. Border Patrol.
As if that's better.
Maybe Krystal sold us out.
Stan wouldn't let that happen.
Stop defending him.
Just dump it.
It's gang friend's money.
You wanna explain that to the Mounties?
Either way, we can't make the drop.
Well, at least my way.
We don't end up in an Ontario gulag.
Okay, how do we dump it?
Roll down the windows.
GPS VOICE: Recalculating...
So, what? We can just
make it rain all over their windshield.
Here, turn!
(TIRES SCREECH)
Jesus!
We can lose them in here!
(EXHALES)
Pull in somewhere.
Where are they?
Can you see them?
Just do something!
(TIRES SCREECH)
Slow down, slow down!
Stop yelling at me!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(SCREAMING)
(TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
Come on.
Do you think they're gone?
Coast is clear.
(EXHALES)
Where did you learn all that?
YouTube.
And they're back.
Grab the money.
Why?
Come on.
Just do it.
No, no.
Just take it out and divide it up.
What are we doing?
Getting rid of it.
Where?
ANNIE:
Where's the bathroom at?
Now, Annie?
To flush the money, Beth.
There's eyes in the sky.
They see everything.
So, how do we dump it?
We don't.
We can't go back outside with it.
No way.
We'll lose it.
DEALER: Winner!
(CHEERING)
Where are we at?
We're twice what we started.
Jesus!
Why didn't we try craps before crime?
(PHONE VIBRATING)
(CHEERING, INDISTINCT CHATTER)
I gotta take this.
Hang on. What...
What are we supposed to do here?
Just be a loser.
DEAN: I have called you 50 times.
Is everything okay?
Danny's in the hospital.
What?
Some kid chucked him into the board.
He had the puck.
Oh, my God!
He even got the shot off.
What happened?
He got slammed really hard, Beth.
Is he okay?
I don't know.
The coach thinks it's his wrist.
Probably broken.
Can you go be with him?
(SIGHS)
Coach had to go home.
Nurse says he's sitting there alone.
Can you?
Not unless I want to get arrested.
Hello?
(SIGHS)
Yeah, it's going to be a while.
Why?
Because /... (SIGHS)
Because I'm not very close.
Where the hell are you?
I'm...
sort of out of the country.
(SCOFFS) Of course you are.
Next time...
just lie to me.
Wait.
Can't we just keep it?
I mean...
We'll need to sign for it.
So?
You want your name on record here
if they find all our Queens?
Put it all on two.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Are you sure you don't want
to spread it around?
Two.
Oh, my God.
DEALER: No more bets.
(CROWD GASPING)
Oh! Thank God!
ANNIE: Yes!
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, my God.
Phew.
Chips fall where they may.
Yeah, right.
To the unluckiest number.
2-2-2002.
Oh, honey.
Let's go home.
Am I supposed to know what that means?
You were there.
Oh, the dotcom crash.
Her wedding.
Right. Yes, I knew that.
I'm gonna go to the grocery store
and make him French toast in the morning.
He didn't even ask for you.
(SIGHS)
Don't worry.
I paid for It.
Smells amazing.
And it should, for how much it costs.
Is this, uh, an Olive Garden special?
Yes, complete with unlimited breadsticks.
Mm. Mm-hmm.
Uh...
So...
Um...
Last night, uh...
I made things weird.
No, no.
No, seriously, not at all.
It's...
It's fine.
I... It'll never happen again.
Cross my heart, hope to die.
Please.
Let's not go that far.
BEN: Sweet.
Right?
Can I have cheese?
Absolutely, Benjamin.
Mm.
So good.
Yeah.
There you are, sir.
Thank you.
Where's yours?
Oh, uh, I'm eating out tonight.
Why?
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
That's for me.
Hello.
ANGELA: Hey.
Hey.
You look great.
(KISSES)
Thanks.
I love you in this shirt.
I don't think you've ever seen me
in another one.
(LAUGHING)
You remember Angela?
Hi, yes, of course.
Hey.
Just having some dinner with, uh, my son.
You guys should go have some fun.
Not too much fun, but, you know.
I'm just kidding.
I'm kidding.
Better hurry up.
It's trash night.
(CHUCKLING)
Bon appetit.
(DOOR CLOSES)
You should put cheese on it.
SARA: You're looping it the wrong way.
I got these sausage fingers.
Okay, but you're
just making a knot now. That's not...
Friendship knot.
That's not a thing.
That's totally a thing.
No.
It's better.
You...
you can't undo it.
Uh-huh. Okay.
It's tight.
Make me one?
Yeah, sure.
In your room.
All right.
(SIGHS)
How'd it go?
Why are you helping us?
What do you mean?
Why did you let us print at the club?
You needed a space.
Why'd you make Krystal do the drop?
I didn't want you to drown on a jet ski.
Remember our wedding?
Um...
Well, not much.
Before my mom made you do shots.
(CHUCKLES) What, like the ceremony?
The part where we promised to treat
each other's family
like our own.
Yeah.
Why do you think I did the shots?
I'm not talking about my mom.
What'd you say to her, Stanley?
Oh.
(EXHALES)
We made a deal.
Well, we kind of made a deal.
(SOMBER INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(VOICE STARTS TO FADE)
I told her that
I'd give you guys the place,
she stays out of your life...
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(INAUDIBLE CONVERSATION)
Lady luck ain't on your side tonight, huh?
There was a problem.
Always is.
And I had to get rid of it.
Never a solution.
Well, I didn't have a lot of options.
Oh, yeah?
Or did the dice just not roll your way?
We were being followed.
Yeah, by my people.
Well, that would have been
really nice to know.
They don't like to make a scene.
But I don't mind so much.
Well, someone else will.
Hmm.
You got a guardian angel
I don't know about?
Maybe.
NICK: Everyone, meet Beth.
(ALL CLAPPING)
Let's...
Hi.
Yes.
Um, she's gonna be
running things around here.
No, I'm helping.
Just so we don't kill whatever we plant.
Yeah. Uh, they're all yours.
Okay.
Well, I'm the new kid.
SO maybe you guys
can help me out a little bit.
Show me what you've already started.
Z: Are you okay, man?
I'm fine.
You don't look so good.
I just woke up.
About time.
(SCOFFS)