BETH: Previously on Good Girls...
We get to start over,
and then they'll move us
anywhere in the country.
Assuming we can even deliver gang friend.
We need to know
what he does with the money.
BETH: He'll kill me.
You got something you want to tell me?
(MICROPHONE FEEDBACK)
It's not gonna do that, is it?
RUBY: Another double?
What's this man got you doing?
Who do you think's
paying off all your debts?
BEN: You had pizza with your therapist?
And a couple beers.
So what?
She's really into you, okay?
I proposed to Lila.
You're quitting?
You can't make someone like you.
Annie, what are you doing?
Tyler, please, there has to be
something that you want.
(OVER MIC)
I'll see you in 30 years.
It might not take that long.
(DOOR BUZZES)
How did you do it?
BETH: / can't keep doing this.
Don't have much of a choice.
Why?
Because I also have people to answer to.
They're gonna want to meet you.
He's got a boss.
(RELAXING MUSIC)
WOMAN ON PHONE:
Make peace with yourself.
Make peace with the amazing person
that you truly are.
Your mind is your greatest asset.
You are your own best tool.
He said, Baby, what's wrong with you?
Why don't you use your imagination?
Oh, no, oh, no
Standing in the half-light,
you're almost like her
So take it slow like your daddy told ya
Strut, pout, put it out
That's what you want from women
Come on, baby, whatcha takin' me for?
Strut, pout, cut it out
All takin' and no givin'
Watch me baby, while I walk out the door
I am my own best tool.
Be cool.
(ZIPPING)
BEN: Why are you in clothes?
Why are you awake?
I have practice.
Before school?
Can't do it in school.
But it's extracurricular.
Yeah, extra.
Hmm.
What's your excuse?
Work.
You got home like three hours ago.
I forgot to lock up.
The store is open 24 hours.
What's in the backpack?
Mostly tampons.
Can I see?
You know what's So weird?
Guns.
You didn't go to bed a cop...
Drugs?
But you woke up one.
Body parts?
Remind me never to get up early again.
All right.
Be on your way.
I will bring you a Slurpee.
(KISSES)
If only you were going to work.
(SIGHS)
TEACHER: You're not dumb.
(EXHALES)
You just weren't prepared.
So let's try again.
If you can open up your textbooks
to chapter 6, page 89.
Will you take me to Annabelle's?
Can your mom take you?
I want you.
Could she come over here?
She has better dolls.
What about FaceTime?
Not the same.
What if you rode your scooter
over to her house?
I can't cross the street by myself.
(SIGHS) Well, maybe it's time.
BETH: Hey, go get your shoes, sweetie.
But I want Dad.
Go.
How long does that take?
DEAN: When it beeps.
Do you want a pillow or something?
How'd you get it?
What?
The bail.
I mean... (SCOFFS)
We were drowning before
they even took the shop.
Come here, sit up.
What'd he make you do this time?
It's not him.
Who is it?
Does it matter?
(SCOFFS) Yeah, kind of.
Would you rather just go back?
(SIGHS, SCOFFS)
(ANKLE MONITOR BEEPS)
I'll take Jane.
(BEEPING CONTINUES)
(BEEPING STOPS)
(PEOPLE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY IN DISTANCE)
(BICYCLES WHIRRING)
We out of peanut butter?
We are.
We out of bread too?
Do you see any bread?
No.
Then you have your answer.
Can you go to the store?
Sure.
As soon as we stop showering,
stop watching TV,
and stop cooking.
(SIGHS) Got it.
How bad?
As long as you don't need to see the food
that we can't buy or cook,
we can probably keep the TV going.
Well, it's okay, 'cause I got a craving
for saltines and mustard.
You cannot be serious.
I could do Cheerios and barbecue sauce.
Her meds went up again.
They just upped them.
And they upped the up.
How much?
What are we going to do?
I Know this is kind of my fault.
All your fault.
And I don't want to make things
any worse than I already have.
But you just can't help yourself.
What's going on with the bags?
What do you mean?
Maybe you can ask for some kind of
commission or something.
This isn't Herbalife, babe.
But you made the deal.
To stay alive.
Well, are they selling?
I don't know, Ruby.
He's got 'em in some
car washes around town.
Car washes?
Some gas stations too.
They're fake Celines, not Slim Jims.
Looks like it's gonna be
a condiment kind of month.
Got to do better than that.
Well, get it from your guy.
BETH: He just won't wash right now.
And we can't live without our cut.
How is that my problem?
This takes up all of our time.
I can barely work.
And it's not like we're ratting out
some pencil pushers.
There's crime,
undercover crime.
These fools are packing, yo.
None of it pays anymore.
We're not your financial planners.
So could we get, like,
an advance or something?
On what?
On our salary.
What salary?
The one we're gonna get in our new lives.
You don't have new lives yet.
But we can't afford our old ones.
I can't even pay my rent.
Hey, guess where you won't have to.
(SCOFFS)
When do you meet the boss?
Oh, I'm still waiting on my e-vite.
I like your eyes.
Excuse me?
The smoky stuff.
My makeup?
What's it called?
Eye shadow.
Would you say it's, like, slate
or more of, like, a smoky gray?
She'll text you a link.
Mmm.
(DISTORTED) Hey, mama.
I can trust you, right?
Follow the money.
What color lip gloss is that?
Boss will Know where it goes.
My people want to check you out.
You've got this, girl.
We're counting on you.
Don't let me down, all right?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
DEAN: Do you have a USB cable?
This thing is flashing,
and I need to charge it.
Yeah, it's in my purse.
Okay.
(PHONE CHIMES)
RUBY: What happens
when his boss has a boss?
And that boss has a boss?
We work harder and harder.
And get poorer and poorer.
And still end up deader and deader.
And deader.
'Cause there's three of us.
Hello?
Yo, Holly Hobby.
Anything at all to contribute?
What do we do?
Green or orange around the mouth?
DAVE: Hey, will you give me that blue AUX?
Do you feel that?
Hmm.
Oh, the rush.
From the fumes?
Here, you try.
This one goes right there.
Okay.
How awesome is it being in the field?
Mmm.
Food's better than the cafeteria.
How about no d-bag suits to report to?
Sounds nice.
Right?
For you.
Point is, if we deliver on this,
everything changes.
Really?
Yeah, yeah.
Could mean division chief.
For me too?
Yeah, if you play your cards right.
(CHUCKLES)
What'd you do to your face?
Nothing.
Oh. Is that eye shadow?
No.
Oh.
Listen, I... I worked with this Cl once.
Great guy.
Loved Kenny Chesney.
We'd go out.
We'd get sauced.
Fun.
He even taught me how to line dance.
You got to make him trust you.
Problem was, I trusted him.
I'm not going dancing with her.
They're not your friends.
I just had to find my way in.
The only reason she's even talking to you
is because we caught her.
And what happened with your Chesney pal?
He played me like a steel guitar.
They shut down the whole op.
I get it.
It took 15 years to dig out of that hole.
I'm gonna make her my bitch, okay?
Just don't forget what's
pretend and what's real.
Not your color, by the way.
TYLER: Your place is really nice.
Oh. Thanks.
You've been here before, right?
Just to help you move your couch.
What about my Super Bowl party?
I wasn't invited.
To any of them?
There was more than one?
Let's talk a little bit
more about you, Baby T.
What's new?
I rescued a cat.
Aw.
Then he drowned himself.
Oh.
So tell me a little bit more
about this exciting new job of yours.
Well, it's not really that exciting.
What if...
What if it could be?
It's a new place in Grosse Pointe.
It's a lot of eyes.
So, one exit.
And a police station right down the road.
(DOOR OPENS)
DEAN: Hey, ladies!
(DOOR CLOSES)
Hey, have you seen my, um, Allen wrenches?
No.
(OPENS DRAWER)
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
Different key for each case.
It'll take forever.
Suicide mission.
Perfect.
I heard what you said
I heard how you said
You heard what I said
You heard how ! said
I'm not afraid
Just tangled in your wires
It's not heavy enough
Unless you open your eyes
I've been crushing almost every night
But it pains me to see
I'm not even bruised
Skin is damp to the touch
I radiate heat too much
My skin Quick, quick, quick
All right, everybody be cool,
and nobody gets hurt!
RUBY: Time.
One minute.
(STUTTERS) Miss, that one is not locked.
Oh, terrific. Thank you.
Time.
Come on, pick up the pace!
Ten seconds.
RUBY: Where is this fool?
(WHISPERS)
He's coming.
That's time.
Everything's insured.
You can go.
Um, we will...
after you open something else.
You took everything.
Well, don't look at us.
I haven't called the cops yet.
Get on the ground.
Okay.
Go on.
Get down there.
STORE CLERK: Okay.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(WHISPERS) Where is he?
(POP MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
You stay down there.
(KEYS JINGLING)
Be cool.
(MUSIC CONTINUES ON RADIO)
Turn around.
That way.
Donuts?
I thought it was tomorrow.
(SIGHS)
Really?
DAVE: What the hell is going on?
Just trying to make a living.
Armed robbery is five to 10.
For squirt guns?
Doesn't matter, actually.
It does when you pull the trigger.
You think this is funny?
At least here we get three square meals.
And a roof over our head.
Cute jumpers.
Oh, I love orange.
They do blue here.
Oh, even better.
Fine.
You could all rot.
We'll round up your husband too.
But how will we finish the job?
You didn't really give us
anything anyway.
Can you just ask the security guard
for my phone?
I hate when people
don't respond to an e-vite.
Did gang friend actually send a e-vite?
Paperless post.
When's the meeting?
Does it matter?
You know, I think it actually
kind of does
'cause if they bail us out,
which it feels like
they're leaning towards,
then we could hit that credit union
before it closes.
Uh. It's right next to Walmart.
Twofer.
Might want to hang tight
in the parking lot.
We'll probably be back here
before that meeting.
We'll put you on payroll.
Same amount as our cut.
Not happening.
Hmm.
Never knocked over a casino.
Open all night.
Loaded with cash.
And on every corner.
How did we not think of this before?
I just did.
(LAUGHS)
(DOOR OPENS)
(SIGHS)
Come here.
Your guy came through?
You tell me.
Hmm?
Real or fake?
As long as it pays the bills.
Come on.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Real.
Fake?
I can't tell the difference.
That's the point.
What's that got to do with it?
You want a cut or not?
You know it.
Then we gotta show your guy
how valuable you are.
It's missing the engraved logo.
Right here.
In the corner.
Can't sleep on the stitching.
At least 10 stitches per inch.
Got to be symmetrical on all sides.
The real ones...
come with a dust bag.
What's that?
It's like a bag for your bag.
Seems like a waste.
Ladies love it.
Why are you telling me all this, Stan?
'Cause, Gene,
you're selling fake for fake.
So?
Convince women these are real,
you get 10 times the money.
All this time, I thought I hired a badass.
Lucky for me, I got a prissy fashionista.
(CHUCKLES)
I really need to pass.
It's not just for me.
It's for my son.
Look, I Know this might not seem like
the most important thing
in the world to someone else,
but I literally cannot move on
with my life without it so...
If there is anything else
that I can do.
There's one thing you can do.
Name it.
Take your seat.
That's...
How many times?
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
Yeah, same here.
TEACHER: You have seven hours
to complete the test.
First section has a limit of 75 minutes.
I'll notify you when there's
five minutes remaining.
When the time is up,
please place your pencils down.
Are there any questions?
BETH: Get 'em curry.
Curry?
Yeah, Jane's learning cultures.
Okay.
She likes India.
Is the store paying you in cash now?
Remember when you first
went to work for your dad,
and you said, "It's only
gonna be for the summer"?
Yeah, stuck for life.
Me too.
No, just leave it.
I got it.
Leave it.
You okay?
Kenny likes the naan.
It's just flatbread.
BETH: What if he checks me?
Improvise.
What if he finds it?
He'd have to get you naked.
RIO: Hey, now.
Come on.
Do you need to frisk me or something?
Nah, you're good.
Don't sweat it, all right?
This is my boss.
I'm just his grandmother.
(PEOPLE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
(ANNIE GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
(GRUNTS)
Come on, creepy guy in 4A.
Why is your Wi-Fi so weak?
Yes.
No!
(SIGHS IN FRUSTRATION)
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
This is not my house.
What are you doing here?
I just left my stag night.
That doesn't help me.
Your people call it a bachelor party.
That would explain
the boob glitter on your face.
It got really weird.
With the strippers?
With a mini horse.
I don't even know
who to feel sorry for there.
I can't get married tomorrow.
(SIGHS)
You should go home.
I don't want to.
Then go somewhere else.
Can I, uh, just please come in?
Find yourself a good therapist.
Please, I really need...
Josh, you have to trust me.
I think I'm gonna crap myself.
It's around the corner.
Okay.
BETH: Oh, no, that's too much.
Thank you.
Don't worry.
She'll tell you when you've had enough.
(WOMAN CHUCKLING)
How do you know my uncle?
She's just a work friend, bud.
What's she do?
Um, she helps me out.
That right?
We're partners.
That all?
I'm married.
How many children?
Four.
She's married.
Mmm-hmm.
(WOMEN CHUCKLING)
Where's the ring?
Let the girl eat.
Come on.
I'm just playing.
My cousin.
Brother.
Cousin.
Heard a lot about you, Elizabeth.
Just Beth.
Okay, Elizabeth.
(DISTORTED)
Got to watch out for that one.
WOMAN: You've got to watch out
for both of these guys.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Like you're some peach.
(LAUGHS)
Is there a bathroom?
Oh, yeah, inside, sweetie, off the den.
Thank you.
WOMAN: Mmm-hmm.
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
I'd avoid going in there.
How long?
A week to be safe.
(EXHALES)
Feeling better?
Not really.
Well, pre-wedding jitters
are totally normal.
I've never gone number two at Lila's.
Huh?
Never.
But... But what do you do?
There's a café
down the street.
They know me.
The key's waiting when I come in.
Why?
Because her bathroom
is so fresh and girly.
It smells like gardenias.
Yeah, 'cause she's trying
to mask her own dumps.
No, she doesn't do that.
So she also goes to the cafe?
No, she just doesn't do it.
Are you kidding me?
She never has to go.
That's just physically impossible.
She eats so clean,
there's very little waste.
Jesus.
Yeah.
She really is perfect.
Just not for me.
You destroyed my office bathroom
after our first session.
(CHUCKLES)
I thought I sprayed.
Not enough.
Can I ask you something?
Okay.
Do you really want to be with me
or do you just not want to be with her?
Half of my whole life is gone
Let it drift and wash away
It was just a dream I had
RIO: What are you doing?
I don't... I don't Know.
Don't know?
Don't want to say?
I'm just Curious.
Oh, yeah?
You figure it out yet?
What's that?
Grandma loves Grisham.
(CHUCKLES)
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
(CLEARS THROAT)
What is all this?
RIO: Family.
I thought this was business.
RIO: Same thing.
Why do they care about me?
Got to know you're good enough.
For you?
For business.
What if I'm not?
Then you don't get invited back.
That doesn't seem fair.
Hmm.
Mmm-mmm.
Half of my whole life is done
Heather gathers in its place
It was just a dream I had
It was just a dream
The mark where he left me
A clip on my wing
Oh, let it soften
I forgive everything
I once hummed the seasons
Now, I'm whistling
What's going on?
She improvised.
Hey.
They like you.
(GRUNTS)
Morning.
What time is it?
You're good.
But, uh...
it's approaching go time.
Oh, God.
(CLEARS THROAT)
So what are you gonna do?
Not how this works, remember?
Oh, we're back to that now?
You never really needed me.
(EXHALES)
Hi, Ben.
You've got to be kidding me.
Well, good luck.
You too.
Hey, it's not that.
It looks like that.
It's... It's a different kind of that.
That is that.
(SIGHS) It's that without the that.
Why should I believe anything
that comes out of your mouth?
Because I'm not lying.
I called the mini-mart after you left.
What?
Where were you?
Not where you think.
'Cause I think you were
humping your shrink.
(SCOFFS) Jesus.
I was ata GED prep class, okay?
For real?
Yeah.
I just...
I didn't want to tell you.
Why?
In case I failed again.
(SIGHS SOFTLY)
How'd you do?
Come on, creeper in 4A.
Ugh, he has really got to upgrade.
It's loading.
(GASPS) Oh my God.
I can't look.
I got this.
(COMPUTER BEEPS)
Oh, no.
Now we both have to pay for college.
(SCREAMING)
(LAUGHING)
STAN: Hey. (KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Rise and shine.
Are you just getting home?
Mmm-hmm.
Got my cut.
For real?
Did everything you said.
How much?
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Even more than I asked for.
How much?
Depends on how many I sell.
Why you?
He didn't know any women
who could afford a real one.
And we do?
(SIGHS)
We're gonna have to find 'em.
They look legit, though.
You see the hardware?
Mmm-hmm.
(EXHALES)
(ON TV) Sorry about this,
my gaily colored beach ball of rapture.
MAN: Actually, this look
is very popular...
You guys, please turn that down.
You're gonna go deaf.
(ON TV) Earthworm Jim!
Dean?
(TV VOLUME DECREASES).
Earth to Dean.
Oh, sorry.
I was just spaced.
Weren't you gonna go on a bike ride?
Can't.
Didn't you fix the tires?
(SCOFFS) I have a radius
of three blocks with this thing.
Well, why don't you just go up and down
the driveway like Jane?
(TV VOLUME INCREASES)
It was a joke.
You guys, TV!
(TV VOLUME DECREASES)
Might as well just throw me back in.
Because you can't go on a bike ride?
Because you gave 'em
enough evidence to put me away
for as long as they want.
I'll ask them to increase the radius.
There's gonna be a trial.
There's not gonna be a trial.
They're not gonna cut me a deal.
You won't need one.
Well, how do you know that?
Danny, turn the TV up.
(TV VOLUME INCREASES)
MAN ON TV: (SINGING)
Through the soil he did crawl
Earthworm Jim
Come on, even louder.
(TV VOLUME INCREASES)
Jim was just a dirt-eating
Chewing length of worm flesh
But all that came to a crash
(INAUDIBLE)
Earthworm Jim He's such a groovy guy
Earthworm Jim He rockets through the sky
Cruising through the universe
Having lots of fun
Here comes Earthworm Jim
You know that he's a mighty one
Look out!
Earthworm Jim A hero for all time
Earthworm, Earthworm
Earthworm, Earthworm Jim!
Despite his great big muscles
And his really big ray gun
Jim is stillan earthworm
But then he's the only one
With a super suit to make
him really super strong
Jim can be a winner if we only sing along
Earthworm Jim!
We think he's mighty fine
Earthworm Jim
A hero for all time
Earthworm Jim!
The soil he did crawl
Earthworm, Earthworm
Earthworm, Earthworm Jim!
Hooray for Jim!
Groovy!