Annie, are you okay?
Not now, Owen.
[Mantleray] What? What? They're awake?
They're not dead?
They're alive. You woke up!
Were we not supposed to?
- Hello.
- Congratulations.
- So nice of you to come.
- Good to see you. You look wonderful.
- Congratulations.
Hello, hello. So good to see you, yes.
Are you feeling pure, unaffected joy?
Why are they all staring at us?
- [D'Nail] Like we're in a zoo.
- [Raymond] No, like cattle...
in a slaughterhouse.
Fuck the Evens.
I'm a big fan. I have all your books.
Oh, thank you. Thank you so much.
You've just completed
the 73rd iteration...
of the ULP.
It's been a complete success.
Congratulations.
You're healed.
[Yoda] Years of work...
years of research...
hundreds of millions invested.
Idiots.
You can speak to them that way,
but you cannot speak to me that way.
Perhaps you know me from my books,
my radio program.
I'm globally recognized.
My technicians cannot locate
the consciousness you created.
They believe she may have slipped away.
That's not true.
Mmm.
She no longer exists.
Muramoto's family
intends to file a lawsuit.
- I intend to sue as well.
- Good for you.
You stole my mind from me for profit.
The combination of hubris and idiocy
is inconceivable.
I agree.
I advise that you never allow my son
to practice in this industry again.
For his sake, as well as all of humanity.
I assure you, he will not.
Fine.
Do you have anything
to say for yourself?
I believe I've...
said everything that I...
needed to say.
Fine.
- Well, Mother, I...
- Yes.
- I suppose...
You and I could share a very brief...
lunch together sometime.
- I'm leaving the country.
- Oh.
I'm going on a 47-city book tour,
all seven continents.
Oh.
So you and I won't
be seeing each other again...
for...
quite some time.
Until then.
[exhales]
Your idiocy regarding the ULP
may be useful to me...
in a private matter
[speaking Japanese]
Keep it.
I'm sorry I said all that stuff.
There was never a guy with a van.
I would never hurt your daughter.
I hope it was worth it.
Remember your NDA.
[speaking Japanese]
- Thanks.
- Remember your NDA.
[speaking Japanese]
Please remember you signed an NDA.
Remember your NDA.
- [speaking Japanese]
- Remember you signed an NDA.
- Remember your NDA.
Hey. Hey.
I know you're probably
still processing all that.
[sirens wailing]
I just wanted to let you know I'm...
I'm gonna leave you alone.
I won't, like, follow you around
in regular life.
What?
I won't make more of this than it was.
I didn't think you were going to.
I have a problem with that. I...
I get weird.
Okay.
If that's what you think.
Bye, Annie.
Bye, Owen.
[taxi door opens]
[taxi door closes]
I'm sorry about...
everything.
I know it wasn't easy to bring me back.
It was the only choice.
The calculation failed, but I believe
it would have failed in any case.
I was the one who created an...
intolerable situation for Gertie.
The work you did with the GRTA
was remarkable...
Azumi.
Perhaps...
Gertie was the real project.
[elevator dings, door opens]
[man screams in distance]
Room E, phase three?
- Hmm.
- Yeah.
Remarkable work they're doing up there.
[speaks Japanese]
I'm starting to think that your kiss,
not my mother's behavior,
was the catalyst for my...
temporary failure of my visual cortex.
During my hysterical blindness,
I had this...
vision that...
An internally generated vision...
[elevator dings]
It's called a fantasy, James.
Yes.
A fantasy.
You and I were at sea.
You were my first mate...
and nurturing life partner...
and we were on a journey.
To where?
The lost city of Atlantis.
Oh.
What is it?
- It's just I don't like boats.
- Oh.
Can I give you a lift somewhere?
You know how to drive?
[elevator dings]
[doors open]
[Azumi] My therapist told me
it might help.
[Mantleray] Yes.
That sounds...
most excellent.
- [horn honks]
- James, it's this one.
Of course.
[woman] There's no greater tragedy
than the destruction of a family.
You can be the one
to hold them all together.
- [girl] Daddy!
- [woman] Daddy's Home.
Share your joy with others
and make yourself feel whole again.
[car door slams]
[footsteps approaching]
- I thought it was gonna be everyone.
- Just me.
You look nice.
How are you feeling?
- You don't have to be worried.
- I'm not worried.
You're worried I'm gonna ruin Jed's trial,
and I'm not, okay?
It's okay.
I think you're going to tell the truth
and help him.
It makes me proud.
Can't I be proud?
Yeah, you can. Sorry.
By the way, has...
anyone...
approached you and tried to get you
to change your story about Jed?
- What do you mean?
- Uh...
Have you encountered any strangers
trying to manipulate you?
Because I've heard
that sometimes these women
who make false accusations
against the wealthy
will sometimes hire people
to... to intimidate and confuse witnesses.
I think there's even a service.
No strangers, no.
Would you describe your brother
as a good person?
Yes.
[telephone buzzes]
[man] Yes?
Have you ever seen
your brother engage in an act
of consensual or non-consensual urination?
- Absolutely not.
- And have you ever...
- We have a new settlement offer.
- What terms?
Generous.
How many times do I have to tell you guys?
We are not settling.
[Owen] Why not?
Because it's bullshit. That's why.
Then I wouldn't have to lie under oath.
Look, this is a one-time thing.
My oldest son made a mistake.
Any settlement will ruin our family name.
And if this... woman,
if she can't find the generosity
to forgive Jed
for something that she agreed to,
then we as a family
will rip it out of her chest cavity.
That's a confusing metaphor.
That's how the Milgrim family
deal with our enemies.
[door opens]
[footsteps leaving]
[door closes]
[Jed] Don't let this happen, Owen.
I'm a horrible person.
Adelaide's gonna leave me.
I don't know how this happened.
Jed...
[mug smashes]
[Jed sniffles]
These are real fucking tears, Owen.
You're either a part of this family
or you're not.
[Owen] I buzzed him up at 7:05.
I know the time
because he's always five minutes late,
and I asked him to be there at seven.
And I know we were there for four hours
because that's how long
it takes me to beat him at Risk.
[laughter]
So, is it possible for Jed Milgrim
to have been at the office at 8:25?
Not unless someone could be two places
at the same time.
Objection, Your Honor.
There is no real documented time line.
- [judge] Overruled.
- [Frank] No further questions, Your Honor.
Nobody can be two places at once,
but everyone has to be somewhere.
Do you agree, Mr. Milgrim?
I don't understand the question.
You have no data portals
in your micro apartment.
You live in a building with no doorman
and no security monitoring whatsoever.
- That's true.
- Why?
I prefer to be disconnected.
[lawyer] In a sense, you're invisible,
aren't you?
Sure.
Then let's see something visible.
At this point, Your Honor,
we'd like to introduce
the plaintiff's exhibit eight.
Video footage pulled
from the closed-circuit system
of the defendant's place of work.
Do you recognize this place, Mr. Milgrim?
That is the factory floor
of my father's company.
[lawyer] And this?
That's the stairwell
of my father's company.
[lawyer] What do you see happening here?
[Owen] I see a man groping a woman.
[lawyer] This is the man
who used his power in the workplace
to force my client
into a heinous sexual act.
[courtroom murmurs]
[lawyer] The defense's entire case
rests on you not believing
your very own eyes,
and instead believing Owen Milgrim.
Mr. Milgrim, were you diagnosed
with schizophrenia ten years ago?
[Frank] Objection.
Irrelevant and prejudicial, Your Honor.
[judge] Overruled.
Answer the question Mr. Milgrim.
[lawyer] Are you schizophrenic,
Mr. Milgrim?
[clears throat]
Yes.
[lawyer] Are you on any
anti-psychotic medications?
I'm supposed to be,
but I stopped taking them a while ago.
[lawyer] Do you ever get confused
about your brother, Jed?
As in you believe you're seeing him,
when, in fact, you are imagining
someone who just looks like him.
[Owen] Not anymore.
And do you have trouble telling
the difference between what is real
and what's not?
[clears throat]
- Sometimes I do, yes.
- [Frank] Objection, Your Honor,
the witness is clearly having
a panic attack...
I would like to submit my testimony.
[lawyer] As I said before,
this entire case rests
on what Mr. Milgrim thinks of this image.
Does this man
look like your brother, Jed Milgrim?
It doesn't look like him.
See? I told you.
It is him.
[man] What the fuck did he just say?
It's obviously him.
Motherfucker.
[lawyer] Just to clarify,
- your brother wasn't with you...
- I'm saying I lied, and he's guilty,
and he's a monster,
and I'm sorry for lying.
I'm not a liar.
He's guilty and he did it.
- [lawyer] No further questions.
- [Frank] Your Honor, I move to redirect
and treat Mr. Milgrim
as a hostile witness.
[judge] It's too late, Counsel.
You've already examined him.
Motion denied.
[Frank] No further questions, Your Honor.
You're dead. You're fucking dead.
I'm gonna kill you.
I'm gonna kill you my fucking self.
[yelling] I'm gonna fucking kill you!
[gavel pounds]
[birds chirping]
I need to tell you something.
I need to tell you
that it's not okay for me...
out here...
all by myself.
It was before, but it's not anymore.
Yes, you married a woman...
who was sick.
And she couldn't handle having a family,
and she left us.
And it broke your heart.
And then your daughter died.
And it was the wrong one.
It was the easier one...
who was good at life. Who made you laugh.
Who didn't cause problems,
who always called you.
Who didn't remind you of her mother.
And it's okay that you had to go in there,
but I don't accept it anymore.
I need you out here.
We are the only ones left.
I need you out here with me, Dad.
- I'm lonely.
- I take it your trip to Salt Lake...
opened things up.
What are you doing?
Annie, I don't think that,
what you said about the wrong one.
I don't... I don't think that.
Did you steal all my money?
I can pay you back.
When I saw how much you took,
I figured you weren't coming back.
I just figured, well...
there it is.
The third and final Irish exit.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
How was it?
I didn't go.
Not technically.
[Hank] Your brain is not melted, at least.
It would have been painless, I heard.
According to the, uh...
insane computer.
[grunts]
She was going through a lot.
Well...
You seem good, Annie.
I don't feel good. How is she? How did...
- How'd she seem?
- Who?
Ellie.
Um...
None of that was real.
You get that.
I just... made up a version of her.
Maybe but, you know,
who really knows how this stuff works.
So, how'd she seem?
She seemed like herself.
Good.
Anything come to you
in the last three days?
I don't know. I think so.
But honestly, I feel confused.
I feel like maybe I did it wrong.
Owen listened to all of my stories.
But in the reflections, I kept giving him
all these reasons not to trust me,
but he just... kept trying to help me.
He acted like a friend.
[woman] I want to talk to you
about something
you've been avoiding since you got here.
Okay.
You talked about what happened
at the drug trial,
and you talked about
what you went through with your family,
but I still don't understand why you never
tried to talk to Annie again.
Because there were two options,
and neither could end well.
What are the two options?
Option A, she doesn't really exist.
I look up her name,
figure out where she lives,
and realize there's no one on Earth
with that name.
Next, I go
to Neberdine Pharmaceutical Bio Tech
and find out there's no such thing
as Neberdine Pharmaceutical Bio Tech.
What about option B?
Option B's even worse.
[Annie] Owen, look.
I was so focused on my own shit.
I should have said I care about you,
and that after everything we've been
through, I can't not have you in my life.
Because it's really hard...
to actually just connect with somebody.
And... when you do...
you don't... You can't just run away.
[man] Hey, Annie...
you don't have to explain it.
I know how special our connection is.
It means so much to me that you would
ask me to come with you to San...
to Salt Lake City.
[Annie] Hmm.
Uh, Annie, I love you.
And I'm not gonna let my schizophrenia
get in the way
of these two big, beautiful beating hearts
because we're meant to be together.
Anna, I, uh...
- Um...
- [Annie] What are you doing?
- Annie.
- No, no. You know what? No.
Will you marry me?
[Annie] No.
- What?
- No? No.
- Just stop.
- Oh, I guess I misread the file.
Yeah, it's not like that at all,
and you're doing him wrong.
It needs to feel like pain,
but not an awful kind of pain.
It's like this low-level sadness
that has a lot of...
caring and sweetness underneath it.
Forget it.
That's a lot to remember, but, uh...
Are you firing me?
[man] I can't lose another one, fuck.
This is...
This is real Owen.
Oh, they had me committed?
There's no way this is a coincidence.
This... This is a sign, Friend Proxy Owen.
Maybe the universe isn't total chaos.
That's comforting.
Let's do this.
[engine turns over]
Hey!
Oh, I wasn't going to get in any way.
Cue the music.
There she goes.
- [gear grinds]
- [man] Okay, can't really drive stick.
[man] Stuck in Bushwick.
[exhales] God, I hate my fucking life.
[gear grinds] Hello.
Would you sign in
and check your bag, please?
Oh, sure.
For you, sir.
- Hey, there.
- Hello. Just here to visit my niece.
My husband is already inside, so...
I'm late. I'm in trouble.
- Here you go. Thank you.
- All good?
- Okay, where should I go?
- Right here.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
What are you doing?
- What the fuck are you doing here, Owen?
- Moving benches.
[Annie clears throat]
- My family had me committed.
- I know that, idiot.
I mean, what are you doing in here?
This isn't even a state-run facility.
I'm crazy.
[Owen coughs]
You're not fucking crazy, Owen.
Come on, you're just kind of crazy.
I made some threats to powerful people.
I sent anthrax to the governor.
Your brother did that.
I had a blip...
in college. I should be here. I'm sick.
Okay.
Maybe you're diagnosed,
maybe you need to be medicated,
but this...
This does not work for me, Owen.
I don't think it works for you either.
So you saw some things
that weren't there. So what?
People see aliens, people hear voices,
people see ghosts.
That's different.
My mind, it...
- It doesn't work right.
- No one's does.
I'm gonna go into that bathroom
right there...
and 30 seconds later,
you're gonna go into that bathroom.
You get me?
No.
What is the problem?
I'm afraid.
Of what?
Option B.
Annie, the same thing happens
every time I meet someone
or get close to someone.
I mess it up.
I'm gonna get frustrated...
one day, and yell at you out of nowhere,
over something insignificant
I'm fixated on.
And then you'll stop calling back.
And you'll change your number
and it'll break my heart.
It's just easier if you're not real.
But I am real.
You know me.
You're braver than this, Owen.
And I will never do that to you.
Never.
Thirty seconds.
[Owen clears his throat]
[sniffs]
Thirty seconds.
[clears throat]
Hey.
Come in here.
Come on.
Lock the door.
Our niece is out there.
We were visiting.
She's the one dancing by the wall.
It was a great visit,
but, you know, it's over now.
And you're Bruce.
I'm Linda.
Sorry these are weird. They're my dad's.
Owen, I saw this in a movie. It works.
Here.
Put 'em on.
Owen.
[Owen clears his throat]
Annie, why are you here?
Because I'm your friend.
And that's what friends do.
Okay.
Hey.
Didn't you come in alone?
No, we were together.
You're seeing things.
Uh, I'm pretty sure you came in alone.
I'm pretty sure she came in alone.
Uh...
Let me see the sign in sheet.
- Is that the truck?
- Yes, yes, my dad gave it to me.
Just get in.
Let's go, come on. Go, go, go.
It's open! Get in!
That's Harpo. She's a rescue.
- Dammit.
- What's wrong?
This just happens
when I try to start cars.
Owen, will you go to Salt Lake City with me?
I don't technically have a driver's license.
Yes! You've gotta start the car, though.
Okay. Okay.
- [engine turns over]
- Go!
Okay, okay, okay. All right.
Annie, be careful!
Go, go!
Hey, hey!
Hey, hey, stop!
Annie, be careful!
I got it. We're good.
Shit, I missed the exit.
Hey! Stop!
Let go! We're good.
We're fine. We're fine. Bye!
[man] Stop!
This is it.
[Mantleray] It's a ridiculous theory.
More something my mother
would have cooked up.
- [Azumi] I'd like to hear it.
- [Mantleray] Oh, you would?
- [Azumi] It's a long way to Newfoundland.
- [Mantleray] Okay, yes. Well...
it begins like this.
Two billion years ago, an amoeba...
[Owen] How far away is Salt Lake City?
[Annie] It's far.
And I'm not entirely sure
this truck is gonna be able to get us
the whole way there,
but, you know, we'll get there one day.
[Owen] Do we actually know each other?