http://hiqve.com/
Where are you going?
This isn't yellow fever. This is smallpox.
I know.
And you didn't think this was important
information for me to have?
Yellow fever is common.
Rest of the world would not even notice.
But smallpox,
would you buy beef or coffee beans
from a country with that?
But I could have brought the vaccine.
Medicines.
I'm equipped for the wrong disease.
You will do as you're told.
After all, it was your country that
caused this outbreak in the first place.
Are you American?
Help me. Help me.
John Thackery, Philadelphia.
August Robertson, New York.
I know the name.
What are you doing here?
I'm a doctor.
I was working the Mosquito Coast.
They called me in for this.
This is the last place I expected to
see a man from the society pages.
My shipping company,
they use Nicaragua as a shortcut
to the West Coast and the Orient and back.
Two weeks crossing this country
saves me two months
in navigation around South America.
So why are they keeping you prisoner?
Are you the American that's supposed to have
caused this outbreak?
My shipping company pays them
in trinkets and blankets
and now they're saying
those blankets made them sick.
That's very possible.
- They killed 12 of my men. Mostly Hondurans.
- Hey! Hey!
And they're gonna kill me, I can assure you.
Please, you've got to help me.
You need to let the American go.
He will pay for this disease with his life.
But you can't be sure he's responsible.
He stays.
Well, then I won't cure these people.
Then you will end up
like your American friend.
If this thing spreads,
it's the most contagious thing on the Earth.
You let him go, I will save these people.
Without the vaccine?
I have a way.
These are the survivors.
They can no longer get the disease.
They're immune.
So they can help us
with those who still have it.
Tell them to wrap these
bandages around the skin.
It will help their sores heal.
For those who haven't gotten the disease,
this will keep them safe.
They'll get a mild case of it.
They'll definitely recover
and they'll never get it again.
Even if this does work,
I'm still keeping his cargo.
Girls, you ready?
Good morning, Dr. Gallinger.
Detective, what can I do for you?
I had some more information
regarding Dr. Cotton's death
that you might be interested in hearing
since, as you said, you and your wife
were so fond of him.
Uh, would you follow me?
What is it?
We've confirmed that he was
most definitely poisoned.
And we now know who did it.
You do?
You might want to prepare yourself.
It was his sons who did him in.
They both were studying at Princeton,
were slowly adding arsenic
to their father's meals over time.
You're positive about this?
They confessed it.
They were surprised that he'd died so quickly
since, as they said, they had
only been adding the arsenic a short while.
Must have given him more than they realized.
Not that I blame them.
From what I gather, the old man was a nut.
You know, that crazy man
pulled the teeth out of their head.
His own children's teeth.
Why the hell do you do something like that?
He thought it would keep them sane.
Have the boys been arrested?
They killed themselves before we could.
So I guess Daddy's treatment
didn't work out so great.
Anyway, just thought you'd want to know.
Ah. Thank you.
How's your wife?
Doing well.
Give her my best.
Will you excuse us for a moment, Dudley?
Thank you.
Your mother said you're leaving.
Going to Ohio tonight.
The refinery is nearly ready.
Talking with some men in Cleveland
and up near Detroit
about using our gasoline
for automotive propulsion.
Well, when will you be back?
Do you really care?
Of course.
'Cause I want you to come with me.
It's a part of my father's business
that could be mine.
I can build it. We can make a life there.
Phillip, it's a lot all at once.
I need some time.
No, I don't want words or protestations.
It's not what you say, it's what you do.
I'm leaving tonight.
I don't know when I'll be back.
Now either you're coming
with me, your husband,
to be with me wherever we end up,
or you're not.
And if you're not,
I'll find someone who wants to.
I deserve at least that.
May I come in?
How are you doing?
I'm deeply sorry, John.
What did you want?
Just wanted to give you
a report on the twins.
Some good news for a change.
Dr. Chickering and I
examined them this morning.
Nika's pneumonia has receded.
The amount of albumin
in their urine has decreased.
They're eating full meals and
they took their first steps alone.
Also, the orphanage informs me
that a family from Missouri
has agreed to take the girls.
They arrived in the city yesterday
and are just waiting on
our approval to let them go.
I think they're ready.
Sounds like it.
Congratulations.
So, here's what I'm thinking.
We start at the East Side piers.
Find some sailors coming back
from a long time at sea
looking to get their logs dunked.
Then we head to 29th Street.
They've got enough brothels and dance halls
to keep us selling till Christmas.
Fine.
How long you gonna be sore with me?
As long as I feel like.
I may not be a nun anymore,
but I took my vows,
vows that you know I intend on keeping.
It was one little kiss, all right?
A kiss I didn't even get.
You're a hound,
like all them fellas getting off the boats
looking to get their logs dunked.
I can't trust you now,
just like I shouldn't have all this time.
I got carried away is all.
Because what I said is true.
I do have feelings for you.
Then I'd ask you to please
keep them to yourself.
This box is ready.
Guess those vows
didn't include one of forgiveness.
What?
Nothing, all right? I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to tempt you
into breaking your vows.
Believe me, a gorilla like you,
there wasn't the least bit of temptation.
Mr. Jenkins.
- Herman Barrow.
- Good to meet you, Mr. Barrow.
And you, sir.
- Shall we?
- Yes.
Thank you, Mr. Barrow.
Welcome to the Metropolitan Club.
I don't know what a Vander is,
but I'm sho glad he done built it.
Herman, how are you?
I'm very well, Corky, thank you.
That was a wonderful evening. Please.
Oh.
Well, we very much appreciated
your generous donation.
Dr. Thackery?
Dr. Thackery, it's Nurse Baker.
The twins are leaving.
I thought you'd want to know.
Where is Dr. Thackery?
We want to say goodbye.
I'm sure he wishes he could be here,
but unfortunately he's elsewhere.
Be well, girls.
Finally, a good outcome.
Well, I don't suppose he's rushing over
for one last wave at the twins.
You brought me up on charges?
What?
I've been called to defend myself
in front of the state medical board.
You sterilized idiots?
Dozens.
I had no idea how far outside
the brotherhood of physicians
you were until now.
And I had no idea how far outside you were
until you sabotaged me.
How?
The Carr surgery. I know it was you.
Why? Because there's no chance
you would ever make a mistake?
No, because there is no chance that
you are a better doctor than I am.
Oh, for God's sake. Shut up, both of you.
Everett, you're supposed to be on the ward.
Have I missed the twins?
Just. They asked after you.
Thack! Thack!
Quick, quick, fetch a gurney.
No.
You have been in pain for weeks.
You need to be examined.
You mean opened up? Like hell.
All right, well, maybe there's
another alternative.
Have a look, doctors.
My Lord.
You do realize the patient is conscious,
don't you, Bertie?
I was marveling at the technology.
Zinberg taught you to tell the truth.
I taught you to lie.
Seems like neither of us did a very good job.
It is a marvelous invention.
And what does it tell you?
That a section of your bowel is ischemic.
Agreed.
I suppose we can guess what's caused it.
Well, we don't need to get into that.
No, that's all right.
A man ingests cocaine for long enough,
then his intestinal blood vessels
don't stand a chance.
You'll need a resection.
Is the entire intestine necrotic?
Well, we can only guess
from what little we can see,
but I'll schedule surgery
as soon as possible.
No, I want to find an alternative.
What do you mean?
I don't want to rush into it.
There are other things I want to try.
- Medications.
- You collapsed on the street.
Your bowel looks like the badlands.
What more evidence do you need?
No medication is gonna repair that.
Yet it is not for any of you to decide.
Ladies, I am kindly asking you
to please stay out of my way.
I will go wherever I please.
These nurses are saying
I am barred from the building.
You need to make an appointment
like everyone else.
I am not everyone else.
Thank you, nurses. Everything is fine.
Please close the door.
How's your whore? Is she well?
Junia is very well. Thank you.
And how's your new apartment?
Tiny and awful, I trust?
Actually, that's why I'm here.
I want you to buy me a big,
nice one with a view like yours
for me and the children.
Preferably on the Upper East Side.
In a dream, that might be
something I would do.
By law, I owe you nothing.
What is that?
Apparently,
it's the actual amount of steel
that was delivered to the new Knick
on March 4, 1901.
I'm assuming that somewhere in this building
is a document claiming that the delivery
was much greater,
as was the amount that you required
the hospital to pay for it.
We'll both just suppose
we know where the extra money went.
Where did you get that?
You keep
excellent records, Herman.
And you were very smart to keep them
out of the hospital
where people could find them.
Unfortunately, when I went
to the bank the other day to retrieve jewelry
from my safe-deposit box to sell it,
the banker mistakenly gave me the keys
to the other Barrow box.
Where are they now, the papers?
In a new safe-deposit box.
They're all there, everything you did
and every penny you stole.
What do you want?
I want to live the life
I was accustomed to living.
I want the children back in their schools.
I want the apartment I mentioned.
I want you to suffer.
And I want you to pay me
until the day you die.
How much?
Half. Paid to me every month.
All right. Half my salary.
And half of everything you steal, skim,
and ferret away.
Over that, you can go fuck yourself.
And I'd advise you to find someone else
that wants to fuck you, too,
because I'm only paying for five years.
After that,
you're on your own.
So start casting about
for men with deep pockets,
poor eyesight, and very little need
for proper sexual gratification.
I've sped up the crews
and I believe we'll soon be back on schedule.
Are you sure that's wise?
To rush the crews?
Perhaps we should slow them a bit.
I... I worry about accidents.
As do I,
which is why there won't be any.
He won't cooperate.
He's a by-the-book operator.
He's cutting costs.
Wants to bring the project in under
budget from here on out.
- What kind of fruit does that?
- Exactly.
So, we have our normal arrangement?
Look, Herm, I could bust the guy up,
but what's the point?
- The building's nearly done.
- Let's at least slow it down.
We gotta let it get built sometime.
If we didn't, they wouldn't build the
next one and we couldn't skim off that.
There is no next one. This is it for me.
I have expenses, Jimmy.
You might pull a few more bucks
out of the building,
but short of finding a way
to turn back the clock
and start the whole project over again,
I'd say find another scheme.
I am not giving up.
There are a lot more ways to game this
and I will find them.
I wish you luck, Herm.
And when you do, don't forget our cut.
Yeah.
Do you have a moment? It's rather urgent.
What is it?
It's the new man.
The architect, Mr. Warren.
From what I can tell, he's whipping
us into shape nicely.
Yes. Very efficient.
But I fear there may be some pitfalls
involved in all of that whipping.
Such as?
Such as the cheapening of quality, for one.
He's using fewer joists, thinner materials.
I'm more than happy
to have less of everything.
Everything, including costs.
Yes, but with the demands he is placing
on these crews, the speed he wants,
the dangers are immense.
With all that we have poured into that place,
to have it destroyed
by some terrible calamity...
Warren and his firm have an excellent record.
The Astors' hotel was a triumph.
I appreciate your caution,
but we're backing him.
Of course.
I'm sure you're right.
Mrs. Showalter. Lovely to see you.
And you, Mr. Barrow.
So?
I've tried 100 different ways to find
the holes in this.
I didn't want to believe it either.
It's not in Dad's nature.
I know.
But when I stop looking at him
as just his son,
there is a desperation to him now.
But actual murder?
So what do we do?
I mean, go to the police?
Well, we can't just have
them come to the door
and march him out into some jail.
We need to confront him first.
Allow him to get his affairs in order.
Turn himself in with dignity.
And we need to have him look us in the eye
and admit what he's done.
I suppose it would make it feel
like less of a betrayal that way.
He asked me to meet him at
the construction site at 8:00.
Do you think you can be there, too,
so we can confront him together?
Of course.
What I found in my investigation
of Dr. Gallinger...
By investigation,
you mean breaking into my office
and stealing patient records.
So what you found in your thievery.
What I found is that Dr. Gallinger
has performed dozens of unauthorized
vasectomies on children,
children who had no say in their
permanent alteration
and all in service of some harebrained theory
that has no proven basis in medical science.
Dr. Gallinger, your defense.
I plead guilty, Dr. Phelps.
Guilty to believing what I believe
in doing what I have done.
So you did alter these boys?
Of course. And I stand by it.
Cripples, imbeciles, criminals, defectives...
I spare the world from their line
in order to benefit the greater good.
What gives a man the right to play God?
Deciding who is hereditarily fit
and who unworthy to bear children?
What Dr. Gallinger did was an act of egotism,
of cruelty, and of malpractice.
As his superior at the Knickerbocker,
it is my recommendation that this board
considers a full revocation
of Dr. Gallinger's credentials.
What Edwards has left out
of his mongrelization-loving diatribe
is that full permission was granted
on every single procedure
on every single one of those boys.
Let me introduce Dr. Samuel Reid.
Good afternoon, doctors.
Dr. Reid is the director of the Idiot House
on Randall's Island.
I am indeed.
I have state guardianship
of all the boys in my home
and I did, in fact,
grant Dr. Gallinger full permission
to perform these procedures.
You have papers to substantiate all of this?
Of course.
Dr. Gallinger and I have a similar philosophy
when it comes to these matters.
Oh, so this quackery
is now sanctioned by the state.
Wonderful.
What Edwards and other people
of his kind cannot accept
is there is great validity
in the eugenics movement.
States such as California and Indiana
are already seeing the benefits
of a purified society
and are considering writing
it into their legislation.
This movement is growing faster
than any other in modern medicine.
But men like Edwards
likely also buried their heads
when other revolutions
arose, like germ theory,
vaccinations, things that proved
over time to be miracles.
Now, if the board sees fit to prevent me
from practicing in New York,
there are hundreds of other institutions
and doctors whom I'm sure
would welcome me.
Thank you, Dr. Gallinger.
Dr. Edwards,
how much have you studied
the eugenics movement?
I've read several articles in Lancet
and in other medical journals.
And you believe that's enough
to discredit an entire field of study?
A field which is now being taught
in hundreds of medical
schools and universities?
This isn't about a field of study.
It is about intention.
But Dr. Gallinger's intentions
were, in his words,
"For the greater good."
Yes, but for the greater good of whom?
Himself?
You, Dr. Phelps?
Mankind.
Eugenics is, in my opinion, a very legitimate
and necessary study.
So much so, I've added it to the curriculum
at my own Columbia Medical College.
You broke into his office
and you accused him of doing something
to which he apparently had every right.
Unless my colleagues differ
from me in their opinions,
I see no reason to grant your request.
I see.
Thank you, Doctor.
Thank you.
You really intend on doing this?
You realize you're just proving
my entire thesis?
I just made a logical and scientific argument
and respected, learned men agreed with me
because whether you like it or not,
this field of study is legitimate
and it's not going away.
It is fact.
Of course, instead of being a man of science,
you raise your fists like an animal,
the animal we are proving your people to be.
In the face of intellectual reason,
you can't help but resort to violence.
Well, I won't.
'Cause the fight is already...
Now you just proved it again, stupid nigger.
Dorothy!
- Dorothy!
- Everett?
- What is it?
- I won.
I beat that dusky bastard every which way.
I tamed the goddamn beast.
Did you go for his eye?
Like a hammer to a nail.
He had no idea I knew.
Let's go upstairs.
Take me right here.
It don't matter
if she's a cock-trough whore
or dressed up like a dog's dinner.
You can't tell a thing by
looking at 'em, fellas.
They maybe got it, and maybe they don't.
But these will keep you from getting
the bug no matter what.
You want to lose your nose?
Your ears? Your toes?
'Cause you didn't cover up your bell-end?
You want to be answering
to the name of Daddy?
Coupled off to some mistake with
a face like a bulldog chewing a wasp?
Now I know what you're thinking.
But pulling out of her cave at the last
second and painting her belly won't save you.
All the docs say so.
There's only one way to go here, fellas,
and it's right here in my hand.
Don't slip it in till you slip it on.
It's a dime a fuck. 10 in a pack.
Only cost you a buck for 10 rolls in the sack.
Get your money. What are you doing?
I'm out.
I barely finished my tout.
I didn't have to say a word.
Look what I have.
Only charge you 15 cents for it.
The rest costs extra.
Do you remember Moon Flower?
That old plow mule we had?
I remember how stubborn she was.
We would beat on her and beat on her.
And there came a day finally
when she stopped being stubborn.
She was so old at that point.
Had that lame hind limb.
Eyes always dripping from fly bites.
Levi used to do the
funniest imitation of her.
But she obeyed
and worked all day with no hesitation
and then limped back to the barn at night,
waiting in the dark, not moving
until the beating and the work
started again the next morning.
Did that until she was all used up
and there was nothing
left to do but shoot her.
This world offers too much.
And contrary to what you think,
I'm too smart to let
myself turn out that way.
And if that means sinning to get what I want,
well, then, so be it.
I won't be shamed by the likes of you
or anyone else anymore.
What I've done,
what I will do,
is nowhere near the deceitful life
you've obviously led.
God has turned a deaf ear to you, I'm afraid.
Eternal damnation is the
fate of Pastor Elkins.
But before you go to the flames,
I think it's only fair to confess
the rest of my sins to you.
See, what I confessed in church that night,
that night you beat me like that mule,
isn't the whole story.
The man I mentioned
I had a relationship with,
he's the chief of surgery here.
Dr. Thackery. You met him.
You shook the very fingers
I begged him to slip inside me so many times.
He's older than you.
And he was a terrible cocaine user.
I used to get him his drugs,
and in return he would dip
his erect penis in those drugs
and let me feel just how good it was.
After that, I would do anything for him
as long as he would fuck me.
But that, dear Father,
is not the end of my story.
I sunk lower.
Maybe in all your experience
with the brothels
you've heard of something
called the Golden Lotus.
While he was having sex,
I stuck my foot in the mouth of an Oriental
and let him suck on it as he ejaculated.
And he paid me $100 for the pleasure.
More than once.
I just wanted you to know everything
before you went.
Bye, Daddy.
Enjoy your trip.
Dad?
Are you here?
Hey, there.
I didn't expect to see you here.
Come on up. The view is wonderful.
That's a long walk.
There'll be an elevator soon.
Where's Henry?
He'll be here any moment.
Good. What do you think?
Hmm?
Cold rooms.
Light therapy patio up on the roof.
Gonna be a marvel.
This is it.
This is my legacy.
Long after I'm gone,
this is what people will remember me for.
I'm not certain it's all
you'll be remembered for.
Well, there'll be the shipping
and other endeavors, but this,
this is going to save lives every day.
Then why would you be so greedy and foolish
as to risk and hurt so many people?
What do you mean?
I know about it, Dad.
I know about the inspectors
and the bribes and the ports.
I know about it all.
Cornelia, you're jabbering.
What are you talking...
Inspector Bradley and
the Immigration Office at the docks.
You've been bribing him and his men.
Inspector Brad...
Oh, Neely, there isn't a shipping man
in New York who doesn't go out
and slip those fellas
a 20 every now and again to get
a little happy in a pub.
But that is hardly a crime.
If only that was your crime, but it's not.
I know it and Henry knows it.
You move up the sick and the poor
to second-class,
and the inspectors let them into the country
where they infest the tenements
and the neighborhoods.
People died, Dad. Lots of them.
In San Francisco and Hawaii.
Here in New York.
Speight found out and you killed him, too.
What?
What in the hell are you accusing me of?
Don't make it worse by denying it.
Neely, this is ridiculous.
Don't touch me.
I assure you
I did none of the things that you say.
Look around you. Take a good look around!
If I was so concerned about money
would I be working so hard
to give it away to the Knick?
- I know your business is in trouble.
- What?
- You owe Hobart an enormous amount.
- Neely!
In a way.
But that is just an investment
that he made in me.
I am on the rebound.
Yet you still can't cover
your commitments to the Knick.
I did not do what you think.
We're going to the police, Henry and I.
It's already decided.
Neely, this is preposterous.
Do you smell that?
What?
Oh, my God. We've got to get out of here.
Oh, God.
Look, over there.
It's a 20-foot drop.
Help me with this.
I'm gonna lower this ladder down in the hole.
Oh, wait. You've got to go sideways.
Here, go up. Go up.
I got it.
- All right, here.
- It's not long enough.
It'll carry you most of the way, maybe more.
You can climb down, hang, and drop.
- I'll hold it from up here.
- No.
You have to, Neely. There's no other way.
- And what about you?
- Go find help.
There's a fire brigade two blocks down.
They've probably already seen the smoke.
I'll go up the stairs and
wait it out up there.
- Now, go. You've got to go.
- I won't.
Neely, you're running out of time!
Go! Get on this ladder and go now.
That's it. Climb down as far as you can.
Oh, God.
That's it, Neely. Go.
As far as you can go.
That's it.
Good, now let go.
Now, Neely. Now!
Neely? Neely?
Neely, are you all right?
Go get help.
Go.
Now.
Where?
Dad!
No! No!
Oh, God.
We're almost there.
We should talk
about compensation.
No, I'm not much
interested in money.
You know,
I fund a hospital in New York.
The Knickerbocker.
Isn't that where J.M. Christiansen is?
I hear he's doing some astonishing work.
You two should meet. I'll introduce you.