Good morning, Mr. Draper.
Mr. Sterling's inside.
Do you want ice?
Coffee.
It's one thing to be near the bar.
It's another thing to be under it.
Sunkist sent us a crate.
I've seen blind people juggle, but somehow
it seems to be beyond me.
Just close your eyes.
That's what you did in the meeting.
Whatever I did, it worked. We're in it.
That's good news.
Step one, I send it to research.
Step two, you'll need to get
that little idea factory working.
There's only one angle-
an orange... that's orange on TV.
I thought they were pretty clear
they're too cheap to get out of print.
So talk 'em out of it or into it.
I'd love to, but I think
it demands a media strategy.
Forget research. Put Harry Crane on it.
Look at you.
See?
Not all surprises are bad.
The ants, they look like people.
He should be right out.
Is there anything I can get you?
- I think she would like a cup of tea.
- In a teacup.
I'd be more excited if we didn't have to
go in Ted's plane to present.
- Hello, Mother.
- Hello, Peter.
Manolo, may I speak with you a moment?
Of course, Mr. Campbell.
Your tea is coming.
I'll be fine. I'm not a child.
Peggy, would you mind?
Mrs. Campbell, nice to meet you.
There's no reason for you
to be so formal, dear.
Sit with me.
How are you today?
I can't tell you how much it relieves me
to see you and Peter reunited.
Well, it was really
a by-product of the merger.
I'm glad you both swallowed your pride,
if nothing else...
but for the good of the child
you have together.
Excuse me?
Oh, I've embarrassed you.
Your son and I are not together that way.
Trudy, dear, don't deny him.
Don't reject his caresses.
Mrs. Campbell-
I hope you two can someday find...
what Manolo and I have found.
I waited long enough...
to experience the physical
satisfactions of love.
Did she go to China for that tea?
Thank you for driving her out to Bud's.
I've paid you for the extra day.
I know that you don't drive.
Well, I do, but not to her satisfaction.
Bob Benson was right about you.
You're worth every penny.
Bob is a wonderful salesman.
Still, I want you to have
a little something off the books.
Mr. Campbell, I refuse.
It's important to me that
you treat my mother well...
but also that you treat yourself.
- The pleasure is all mine.
- I know that isn't true.
Sally, get in here.
Hello.
What?
Julie's mother called and told me you
were the only two girls on the trip.
So?
You're not staying in a Midtown hotel
with all those boys.
Miss O'Shea's gonna be there.
She's 25.
What's the point of having a mansion...
if you're gonna spend
all your time in here?
Fine, I won't do the Model UN.
It was his idea.
Fine, you're not going.
- Can't we stay with Daddy?
- You mean with no one.
You hate that Daddy supports my dreams.
He doesn't think
I'm just a pain in the ass.
Your father is a hero.
Like everything else in this country...
Diplomacy Club's just
another excuse to make out.
I thought she should join
the Student Congress. The UN's a joke.
- Oh, you're home.
- Who's this?
This is Mitchell- Sylvia and Arnold's son.
Nice to finally meet you,
Mitchell. I'm Don.
Thanks again, Megan.
What did he want?
Um-
I'm sworn to secrecy,
but he's in a lot of trouble.
What happened?
He's 1-A.
But he's in school.
He sent back his draft card in protest.
They reclassified him.
What did he think was gonna happen?
Stupid kid.
Don, he knows he screwed up.
He wants to run.
You know, to Canada.
I suppose I could call my brother-in-law,
but I can't do that to Sylvia and Arnold.
- Can I?
- Just leave it alone.
- He's so scared.
- He should be.
He can't spend the rest
of his life on the run.
I know how you feel...
but you don't want him to go to Vietnam.
Megan, it's not our problem.
Could you get me another whiskey sour?
Sure.
Maybe I'll switch to whiskey sours.
How about a Shirley Temple then?
I don't think Dramamine
and booze go together.
and cranberry juice go together either.
But I thought we'd be back
on your little plane...
not having a romantic dinner.
- Don't you want to celebrate?
- I want to live, Ted.
What?
He doesn't like flying.
Well, you've seen how simple it is now.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
My father died in a plane crash.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
Was he a pilot?
Ha! No.
A passenger.
Look, you're driving. Can we please,
please have another round?
You still have to get home
from White Plains.
I'll hail a cab.
He's such a New Yorker.
This is the agency I always wanted.
Ambition, brains, and beauty.
Yeah, but what about him?
I'm gonna cut you off too, my dear.
I should call home.
If the check comes,
I'm sending it to Ocean Spray.
Can you imagine what it does to his wife
every time he takes that plane?
I guess so.
You don't want me to talk about his wife.
You don't know what you're talking about.
But I do. I've seen that look.
I know, but-
nothing can happen.
And he's in love with you too.
You're the one who's in love with him.
Well, I could use an account,
and he's been generous.
At least one of us ended up important.
Please tell me you don't pity me.
I don't.
Because you really know me.
I do.
I should tell you...
I had a very strange
conversation with your mother.
There's no other kind.
Well, it doesn't matter.
What did she say?
I think she thought I was your wife...
and Manuel was her husband.
My father never treated her that well.
Maybe that's it.
She thinks she's in love with him.
I could see it. Manolo is very charming.
I don't think you understand.
She thinks she's... making love with him.
Tell me exactly what she said.
Did your father ever
give her spa treatments...
that released a "fire in her loins"?
Oh!
Oh, I think I'm gonna be sick.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have told you.
But I can't get the image
out of my head.
Stop it, please.
I don't even want to think
about her brushing her teeth.
I thought I cut you two off.
Ted, I have never been
less afraid of flying in my life.
What? What does he mean?
Nothing.
Well, I should get the check.
Honey, who's that gonna be?
- Arnold.
- Is it too late?
For what? Come in.
Look, I would have called,
but Sylvia is-
Listen, about this afternoon-
Oh, hello, Arnold.
I'm sorry about my kid dropping in on you.
I didn't know if I should tell you.
Well, he figured you would...
and I don't want you
in the middle of this.
His mother's treating it like he's dying.
She doesn't want anyone to know.
Do you want a drink?
Sit up here drinking while they're down
there slamming the doors?
And you lied to me.
Been meaning to knock on your door anyway.
You know, catch a game or something.
I get baseball tickets. Mostly the Mets.
Well, then I'm glad you didn't.
You know, I didn't
even know he left school.
Sylvia says she didn't know either.
She's doing that a lot lately-
lying about little things.
Could tell something's
been wrong all year.
- Another Manhattan?
- Nah. No.
Should have never let him go to Paris.
He got there right in
the middle of the riots.
His French is excellent.
I think he got a lot of girls
as an expatriate revolutionary.
Could kill him right now.
There has to be a way.
Oh, believe me,
everybody's an expert on it.
Sylvia's father was suddenly
Clarence Darrow.
It's thrilling to see
a plumber interpret international law.
You're one of the top
surgeons in the country.
You must know somebody.
I know a lot of people,
but it doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter
if he goes back to school.
He's 1-A.
His induction could be tomorrow.
He's on a damn list
for the rest of his life.
On some level, you have
to admire his idealism.
You sound like Sylvia.
But she doesn't really buy his bullshit.
You think she's gonna
let her baby rot in jail for a cause?
I don't know what to do.
What would you do?
If it was my kid, or if it was me?
You were in the service, right?
I was.
You see action?
It was very different.
I wanted to go.
And then when I got there, well-
That's the trick.
Kids 18, 19 years old,
they have no sense of their own mortality.
Or anyone else's.
That's why they make good soldiers.
Well, the army paid for med school.
I served in a hospital in Pusan.
We were very lucky.
Lucky enough to live in this country.
And service is part of that bargain-
sacrifice.
We knew that.
The war is wrong.
I'll tell you right now, if anyone was
ever gonna get it, it's gonna be him.
He's soft.
I'm sure he's a good kid.
The best.
Cold pills and capsules
take a while, don't they?
Dristan Mist can unlock sinus blockage.
What you watching?
I don't know.
What's the matter? I called.
I didn't want to get into it
when you're about to fly...
but you were supposed
to have dinner with us.
I made a mistake. We'll do it tomorrow.
You don't have to make
a federal case out of it.
Why don't you get a legal pad
and write down...
a bunch of excuses for the next week?
Because none of them
mean anything to the boys.
What about food, clothing and shelter?
Does that mean anything?
Remember what the minister
said at Frank's funeral?
"God can turn off the lights
at any moment."
You know where you're gonna be?
The office.
This is temporary.
I just have to do this until-
Until what?
Until you... are
back where you were at the old firm?
Because things weren't
so great then either.
So we've moved on from
I'm working too much to something else.
The problem is, even
when you do come home, you're not here.
You're obsessed.
And I can feel how disappointing this all is
compared to your battles at work.
I'm not enjoying that.
How did we get to the point where you
think I don't want you to enjoy things?
I know you like having
a young copywriter in your airplane.
Come on, Pete was there too.
And I know you like facing Don Draper
every morning more than the clients.
How was your day?
I just wish you liked being here more.
Could you get Mr. Campbell?
Do you want to see him
before the status meeting?
- When's that?
- Now.
And I also need to know
if you're attending the Chevrolet dinner.
- When's that?
- Tonight.
- Morning.
- May I speak with you?
Does your friend still work
at the Department of Defense?
No, he left for Union Carbide.
But he probably still has pull over there.
What happened now?
You must know plenty of people
with kids getting deferments.
How are they doing that?
They go to college.
Divinity school. Medical baloney.
No, it's too late for that. I need someone
who can really pull strings.
Well, aren't you having dinner
with General Motors...
one of the largest
defense contractors in the world?
What are the politics of that?
I don't know, Don. I'm not on Chevy.
Shall we?
That's not my fault.
Don't worry. If I had Chevy...
I wouldn't be able to devote
my full attention to Ocean Spray.
- Cranberries?
- Cranberry Cocktail.
And they like us so much,
they might even give us the blends.
- What about Sunkist?
- What about it?
It's orange juice.
Morning, everyone.
- Did you know about Sunkist?
- What about it?
Don told Harry to put together
a media plan right away.
Why didn't you tell us about that?
Isn't this the meeting where I tell you?
Are we having this meeting?
Why didn't you tell us
you were presenting to Ocean Spray?
There's been a series of memos.
Didn't you wonder where everybody was?
- We can't present to both.
- Which one is bigger?
They're about the same. Three million.
We've already spent $5,000 on Ocean Spray.
What about our trip to California?
Was it $5,000?
I have a lot of receipts.
I haven't figured it out yet.
Why don't you join this company
and read a memo once in a while?
Maybe they're not a conflict.
We don't have either yet.
I really didn't know.
I warned you about the memos, Ted.
The more you send, the less they get read.
Imagine if every time
Ginger Rogers jumped in the air...
Fred Astaire punched her in the face.
Why are you taking this to heart?
Because it's directed at me.
Can you not see that?
So what?
You know we'll end up with just one juice.
I don't want his juice. I want my juice.
It's all your juice.
Tell him that.
Michigan's in the Big Ten.
Ron Kutchinski just ran
the fastest half mile in the world.
- He's going to the Olympics.
- You're selling yourself short.
I'm telling you, they would
be lucky to have you.
I got it.
Look at this. Got a couple
of high fashion models.
Aren't you a gentleman?
- Hey.
- Hello.
Youse two don't know each other.
These are my two favorite people.
Mitchell Rosen, 16A...
I'd like you to meet Sally Draper, 17B
and all points north.
I'm Julie. I'm crashing at Sally's.
Cool.
They were supposed to leave a key for me.
I lost mine.
Nobody said nothin' to me,
but that don't mean nothin'.
We were going to go out for dinner tonight.
What's good around here?
His mother's cooking.
Around here, it's just old people.
Are you a musician?
'Cause you look like one.
Who?
I don't see it. I'll let you in.
- Oh, good day to you, Mrs. Rosen.
- Hello.
- Mitchell, did you get a cab?
- I was waiting for you.
You're unbelievable.
I got it, Mrs. Rosen.
Do you know Sally and, um-
I'm Julie.
I'm sorry, girls.
We're in a bit of a rush.
I'll get your cab lickety-split.
Bring them right back.
You're living with Mark Lindsay.
I don't live here.
What are you doing here?
I said I'd meet you at La Grenouille.
Dorothy, you must let me
manage your calendar.
I'm not standing in the hallway.
Come in.
You get ready, Mr. Campbell.
I'll entertain her.
Actually, Manolo,
I'd like my mother to myself this evening.
Very well. Good night, my sweet.
Must he?
He has other plans, Mother.
Yes, Dorothy.
I'll be there when you wake.
- Can I fix you something?
- No.
Manolo doesn't like me to drink.
He likes me sharp.
It's so nice the way he looks after you.
Oh, Peter, he's a gift to me.
I just wanted to make sure
you're aware he's your nurse.
You are prone to moments of confusion.
I suppose there's a way
I could mistake your tone for concern.
Oh, I am concerned that you have-
how do I put this?-
misconstrued Manolo's
attention for affection.
If we're going to have
an adult conversation...
let's have an adult conversation.
Has he taken advantage of you?
Manny has awakened a part of me
that was long dormant.
Don't you think I'm entitled
to the pleasures of love?
Do not be more specific.
Since when is it any of your business
what goes on in my bedroom?
I am afraid that we are going
to have to let him go.
Oh, no. What did he do?
He's a pervert.
You were a sour little boy.
And you're a sour little man.
How could I expect you
to be understanding?
You've always been unlovable.
Now I've lost my appetite.
I'm leaving.
You'll never find your way home.
I have carfare...
and a piece of paper with my address...
written in his elegant handwriting.
Mother.
Cheesecake? Chocolate cake?
- Two of everything.
- And another round.
- Why not?
- Oh, I can never get enough of it.
Growing up in Cleveland,
my dad would take me right on Lake Erie.
But the water's gone bad now.
You should go to Florida.
Saltwater.
Down off the Keys, where the marlin run.
Write your own Hemingway story.
If you don't catch anything,
you have to blow your brains out.
So, Ross, where do you
take your kid fishing?
I just got the two girls, and they could
never keep their mouths shut.
But my grandson's just like me.
Last summer, we went up to Muskoka.
Ontario.
Jesus, now we gotta hear
about this kid again.
Brendan's at Antioch.
Yep, studying the classics.
But I hope he'll come to his senses.
He's got a couple of years
before he has decisions to make.
Well, as long as we're working together,
he's got a job with us.
Friend of mine's kid
just got to that point.
He doesn't have a lot of choices left.
1-A. Can you imagine?
Well, my heart goes out to him...
but that's just one of those problems
that can't be solved.
Yeah.
I've got two sons.
Thank God they're too young.
I don't even like to think about that.
I know.
My friend is just beside himself.
I mean, people are doing things though.
Believe me, we know about that.
Makes me sick.
Well, next year this time,
we'll have won the war.
We'll take Brendan to dinner,
get him plastered...
and have him read the menu in Latin.
Ted, are you an angler?
My hobby is coming up
with names for the XP.
Last one.
Okay.
"Things I like about Mitchell."
- "His ass"?
- Shh.
When did you see that?
I couldn't think of anything else.
What did you put?
"How he smiled at me."
"His shoulders."
"His red shirt."
You girls have a big day tomorrow.
And I can tell you right now, the next
time this door opens, it won't be me.
- Lights out.
- Good night, Mrs. Draper.
Why do you keep calling her that?
'Cause she hates it.
Think about it. He's right down there.
You should sneak down and kiss him.
He talked to you.
God, I wish I lived here.
- Yeah?
- Did I wake you?
- Yeah.
- There's a rat in my apartment.
Told you to get traps.
It's in the trap,
and it's mortally wounded.
I'm pretty sure,
'cause there's a lot of blood.
Did you call an ambulance?
You have to come over.
It went under the couch.
I can't even look.
What if it's still alive?
What if I lift the couch
and it starts flipping around?
I'm not your boyfriend.
Maybe I'll make it worth
your while if you come over.
No, you won't. Now good night.
- You're not interested?
- No.
Then why are you using your sexy voice?
Tuesday morning's great.
For what?
Oh. Why didn't you say so?
You can bring her.
It'll be dead by morning.
Eleanor Roosevelt.
I can't remember anything
'cause I didn't sleep.
Your floor smells like pee.
- No, it doesn't.
- Do I smell like pee?
You smell like Prell.
Sally, you're not ready?
I let the guest shower first.
Well, I have to go to work.
But first I have to put you two in a cab,
so shake a leg.
Oh, take out the trash.
I have to get ready.
I'll do it, Mrs. Draper.
It's Megan.
I would love to visit the studio sometime.
Well, hopefully I'll still have a job.
I have to make a phone call.
- Your agent?
- Yes, actually.
Could you get me some coffee?
What the hell were you up to last night?
Mr. Draper?
I'm fine, Dawn. You want some coffee?
What the hell were you thinking?
You said you weren't
going to be involved in Chevy until 1970.
So stay the hell out of it.
Stop trying to poison my relationship.
Last time I checked,
it's our relationship.
And not everything's about you, Ted.
Then be better at it.
- What are you talking about?
- You know this.
A client shouldn't have a single negative
feeling in your presence.
Not the food, not the wine
and certainly not the war.
I was just taking their temperature.
Why would you do that? It's Chevy, Don.
- You'd do it for your kid.
- But it's not your kid.
Oh, is it your kid?
No, it's my friend's kid.
Well, I bet you don't have
a lot of friends, Don...
so I'm going to assume this is important.
It is.
I just- I don't know what to do.
Do you know how young 19 is?
Did you ever think about talking to me
instead of our most important client?
I don't know. It's GM.
Who else has that kind
of clout in Washington?
Does he wear glasses?
I don't think so, but he could.
The guy who taught me to fly...
is a brigadier general
in the Air National Guard.
They're always looking for exceptional
young men to become pilots.
And you'd be willing to call him?
I'd consider it.
But first, you're
going to have to stop the war.
I can't stop the war, Ted.
Don't be an asshole, Don.
The war you're waging on me.
You have to lower your weapons.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about how we are going
to get Ocean Spray.
So you need to stop chasing Sunkist.
You're not going to compete
with me like that anymore.
We're on the same damn side.
That's it?
Don't act like it's nothing.
It seems to be impossible so far.
You'd really do that?
Thank you.
This is not a handshake of gratitude.
This is a binding contract.
Of course.
Whatever you want.
That's what I want.
Hold on. What's the next step?
Tell the kid to write a letter about
his childhood dream of being a pilot.
And it better be convincing.
You should write it.
And tell him to get a haircut.
Be straight, Ted. What are the chances?
I'm going to call right now.
Thank you.
Can you get Dr. Rosen on the phone?
Rosen residence.
It's me. It's Don.
What do you want?
I'm trying to reach Arnold.
The office said he was home sick.
It's about Mitchell.
What? Tell me.
I know someone who knows someone
in the Air National Guard.
He's getting him a spot.
You told someone?
It's my partner.
He's doing me a favor.
Did you fix it?
He just wants Mitchell to cut his hair
and sign a letter.
And the two of you need to make sure
he follows through.
Oh, he'll follow through.
I bet.
My God, is it possible?
I think so, but we have to act fast.
They went upstate to the VA
to call on an army buddy.
I'll send them up tonight.
Sylvia, sweetheart, it's gonna be okay.
Are you there?
Yes.
Please, stop crying.
Oh. I feel better, but I'll feel better
when I know it's done.
Don.
Yes?
I can't believe you would do this for me.
You know I have children too.
I know that's not why you're doing it.
And I hope-
Well, I hope you know
that I was just frustrated with you.
I do now.
I didn't want you to fall in love.
You didn't feel anything?
No, I just-
I don't want to go through this again.
You were good to me.
Better than I was to you.
Are we going to lunch? Because-
Get in here and close the door.
You have given me a terrible problem,
and now you're going to fix it.
Is this about Sunkist?
Because I did some digging-
I told you we needed a nurse,
and you sent us a rapist.
Manolo?
In fact, I never told you anything.
You were just doing some digging.
Calm down. Sit down.
Bob.
She has the mind of a child.
That man took advantage of her.
I assume she told you this story.
Don't you have
your answer right there?
She says they're in love...
and it's the first time
in months she's seemed sure of anything.
I don't think that Manolo's
interests turn that way.
Great, so he's a degenerate.
That means he's capable of anything.
What exactly did she say?
Please, I'm just trying to forget it.
Drink that.
- You feel better now?
- I do.
Can I ask you something?
Did she seem happy?
Yes. She did.
Is it really
so impossible to imagine?
What?
Couldn't it be that if someone
took care of you-
very good care of you-
if this person would do anything for you...
if your well-being was his only thought...
is it impossible that you might...
begin to feel something for him?
When there's true love,
it doesn't matter who it is.
Tell him I'll give him a month's pay.
And tell him it's disgusting.
Of course.
The capital
of the Philippines is Manila.
Its president is Ferdinand Marcos.
Its national language is Tagalog...
but many of its inhabitants speak Spanish
due to its colonial past.
And their national product is-
I don't know. Manila envelopes?
- You don't know anything.
- So?
How about this? All the boys are going
to think you're dumb.
Don't tell me how to get boys.
You went to second base twice.
That's a lot more than you.
- So if I were you, I'd be scared.
- Of what?
Of what you're going to do
when Mitchell asks you to go all the way.
He doesn't even know I'm alive.
Oh, I took care of that.
What did you do?
- I introduced you.
- I introduced myself.
No, I took the letter,
and I signed your name.
- What?
- And I slid it under the back door.
Ow! That really hurts.
How could you do that?
Now I can never go back.
You know you're going to thank me.
Just because your shift is over...
doesn't mean you can get
undressed in the lobby.
- Incredible.
- What?
He should greet you. How you doing today?
I'm- I got- I left something.
And I don't have my key.
You mean you lost it already?
Can I have the keys, please?
Yeah. Okay.
Go fast.
Oh, what have we got here?
Couple of high fashion models?
Oh, God.
- Sally.
- Oh, God.
Oh, dear God.
Dear God, what have we done?
Sally!
Did Sally just come through here?
Mr. Draper, I didn't know you was home.
She hopped in a cab just now.
I'll go get her.
You okay?
Yes.
Did something happen?
I know she lost her keys.
I gave her the keys. It's my fault.
Mr. Draper?
Don't you ever work through channels?
- Who blew the whistle? Brent?
- Loud and clear.
Governor, I've tried to work with local
intelligence from the beginning.
Brent threw me out. Now, why?
Because it's big. That's why.
We've had big ones before,
but, this time, all I get is smoke.
Why didn't you tell me?
McGarrett, this is an important state.
It's our nation's
extended finger into the Pacific-
the ocean where two-thirds-
two of the three billion persons
on earth meet and touch.
Hello?
Oh, I'm glad you're home.
Let me get you a plate.
Oh, wow.
I had a client-
meeting. Lunch.
- Sit down.
- I'm, uh-
I'm gonna lie down.
You need to get some food in you.
Sit down.
Do you want me to cut you a piece?
No.
I got it.
Hello.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Don, Arnold and Mitchell are here.
- I don't feel well.
- Stop.
Hello, Mitchell.
I'm sorry to interrupt your dinner,
but we just got back...
and Mitchell has something
he wants to say.
Mr. Draper.
Thank you very much.
We'll see if it works.
What?
He didn't tell you?
Don talked to somebody for us.
Really?
Sylvia sends her gratitude.
She is overwhelmed.
Do you want something to eat?
We should celebrate.
One step at a time.
Anyway, Don...
I owe you.
Let's go.
No, you eat. I got it.
You are the sweetest man.
You make me sick!
Sally, come back here!
What happened?
I don't know.
- I'm gonna go talk to her.
- No. I'll talk to her.
She has a crush on Mitchell.
Oh.
Sally.
- Open the door.
- No.
You don't get to talk to me anymore.
Sally?
Sally, open the door.
I need to talk to you.
I know you think you saw something.
I was... comforting Mrs. Rosen.
She was very upset.
It's very...
complicated.
Sally, can you hear me?
Yes.
Did you hear what I said?
Okay.