Are you sure you don't want me
to order in some food?
- Chinese?
- I'm sorry this is taking so long.
It's a common mistake
to not ask questions...
when you want something
because you're afraid of the answers.
So you want something?
I'm interested.
And considering the precedent
for small agencies...
this is how we might take you public.
With one and a half million shares
outstanding before the offering...
we'd sell 400,000 additional shares
to the public at $9 a share.
- Twelve a share.
- It's not an insult.
Our valuation of your company was made
after careful analysis.
Of papers you spent 20 minutes with?
I can't take this
to the rest of my partners...
but I can take it to other underwriters.
I'll need these documents for 24 hours.
These papers are spotless.
My compliments to the chef.
Shall we?
You don't think Cooper
pushed that poor banker too hard, do you?
We don't want to lose him.
Certainly not.
It's a marvel.
Everyone wants you, don't they?
Pete, no.
No, I believe our primary hurdle
has been cleared.
And our secondary one?
Don't worry about Don.
Even at nine a share...
your part of the company alone
will be worth nearly a million dollars.
My goodness.
You're flushed.
I drank too fast.
I don't think Don cares about money.
That may be true, God bless him.
But he's tired of playing
in the bush leagues.
This capitalization will double our size...
and that will turn his head.
You want another?
No. I can hardly walk,
and you know it.
I hope Clara reminded you
tomorrow's Mother's Day.
Thank you. I'm aware.
Ow.
Just wanted to make sure
you were still here.
I am, but not for long.
You don't even know what time it is.
I do.
Because I already got up
and put on my face.
Is that what you do?
- I wondered.
- I have to go.
Daisy, you're a tease.
What more could I give you?
Look, the first-class lounge would be
a darker place without you...
but you're supposed to have
your ear to the ground.
I feel like you only call me
when you want to see me.
Am I going to see you tomorrow?
If there's a flight filled with P&G executives
headed back to Cincinnati.
- How about tonight?
- I have plans.
Some other boyfriend?
The one you give all the leads to?
With my mother.
It's Mother's Day.
- Don't go.
- I have to.
But my mother just died.
What are you doing?
You told me you wanted me here
Sunday morning.
I'm here.
Oh, Peter, don't.
So we'll just maintain
every other aspect of this marriage...
except the one that matters.
You mean Tammy?
Will you stop
holding the ax over my neck?
So you'd rather I divorce you
just so you know where things stand?
You don't care that I want you.
I've taken note of your efforts.
I'm going to get her.
Well...
you're gonna be sorry when this is over.
You've given up on me
at exactly the wrong time.
I have big things coming.
You have no idea.
Well, I'll take note of that too.
Could you get that?
- Arnold. Come in.
- Hi.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Do you have any wrapping paper?
It's an emergency.
Good morning.
Sorry. This is Megan's mother Marie.
We passed in the lobby.
I thought you were Megan.
Dr. Arnold Rosen at your service.
- Enchanté.
- Are you French?
My kid's going to Paris.
Should I keep him home?
I am French, but I live in Montreal.
And, yes, I believe so.
I assume this isn't a medical emergency.
Mitchell- that's my son-
he came home and surprised her
for Mother's Day.
- How long is he staying?
- Who knows?
I know he thinks a morning stroll
in Central Park is a gift...
but Sylvia's gonna expect an actual gift.
Do you want my flowers?
I'm quite done with them.
Thank you, Mother.
You're a lifesaver.
He's a surgeon.
He's working on heart transplants.
Wealthy, talented, handsome-
I would not leave them alone.
I'm more worried about you.
There's poop on the stairs again.
Somebody's dog got in.
No, it's human.
I think it's from the tenant.
- She wouldn't do that.
- She's a junkie. She doesn't care.
I want her out.
We can't do that.
How is your mother?
I got curtains. She wants to come visit.
Ow! Ow.
Jesus.
We have to hire a handyman.
Why? It's a waste of money.
Because you have no idea
what you're doing.
Herb Rennet called.
He's canceling dinner tonight.
That's a relief.
We can still have dinner.
I'd love to discuss some things with you.
Let's enjoy our reprieve.
Of course.
Close the door.
Did he say your dinner with Jaguar is off?
Yes, unless it was
the world's most boring dream.
Well, it's on, but Pete's not invited.
Herb Rennet wants a word alone
to straighten things out.
Why can't you handle it?
This could be fatal. You're going.
And my plan is to pack it with spouses
to limit the explosion.
Megan made plans with her mother.
She thought I had a business dinner.
Marie's in town? Fantastic.
Bring her along. That's perfect.
Tell her I insisted.
In attendance I have Jim Cutler...
Frank Gleason and Ted Chaough.
Sweetheart, this is a creative meeting.
What are you doing?
It's for the purposes of the memorandum.
Well, Ted,
some men love women, some love memos.
I want to go over where we are
on Chevrolet again...
and devote our final days
to overdoing it...
on the artwork for
the top three campaigns.
I cannot look at these again.
I told you, they're very keen on the rocket
ship thing with the astronaut anecdotes.
You told them about the astronauts?
I had to. It was too vague otherwise.
I don't want to draw any more rockets,
and I don't want to stare at this work again.
We should have never resigned Alfa Romeo.
What, is this mystery Chevy
gonna be in The Graduate?
Those things are flying off the lot.
Frank, are you not on board with this?
I love what you're doing.
I'm tired of rockets, that's all.
Could you give us a moment?
We'll continue this later.
What is that, Shalimar?
What's gotten into you?
You're supposed to be calming me down.
Ted, I've got cancer.
What?
In my pancreas.
I told Jim. I thought he told you...
and you didn't want to embarrass me.
No.
Maybe it's more of
a financial issue to him...
but I'm glad he can keep a secret.
Financial?
The minute I cash out, I cash in.
You two have to buy me out.
You have cancer.
See, if we still had Alfa,
I wouldn't have to worry...
about putting you out of business.
First of all...
stop talking about money.
Second, we are going to get Chevy...
because you're going to do your best work.
Third, you're going to build a wing
at Sloan-Kettering...
and beat this thing.
Aye, aye.
Will you tell Jim you told me?
He'll see it on your face.
Everybody loves astronauts.
I've got to go lie down.
Well, hello there.
How are things in Glocca Morra?
Hello. Can you hear me?
I love it when you whisper like that.
What are you wearing?
My uniform.
I have one and his flight's delayed.
Who is he? What's he do?
I'm not sure...
but he doesn't believe
my name's really Daisy.
Use that.
Shit.
Do you mind?
17, please.
I'm sorry to bother you,
but we love your show.
Oh, thank you.
Can we get an autograph?
I know you're not waving to me.
Makes the delay worthwhile, doesn't it?
- Headed to Detroit?
- Eventually.
Should we try LaGuardia?
They already did. Forget it.
This is why I like to drive everywhere.
I'd live in my car if I could.
You know, with her
in the backseat navigating.
- I'm Roger. What's your name?
- Mikey.
Well, Mikey, since we're
gonna be cell mates...
I'm going to ask the screw
for a couple of drinks.
Jim Beam.
I'll make her bring them over.
- Good idea.
- I'm full of'em.
I want a glass of water with an onion
and bring him a double Jim Beam.
And get me on that flight.
This is my day off. We had plans.
Well, you would rather spend the evening
laughing at Roger Sterling's jokes.
I should return home.
I've overstayed my welcome.
Well, I don't know what's happened.
I knew something was wrong.
We have not had a fight.
He's so far away...
that sometimes when we're alone
I feel like I'm making conversation.
Darling, you have confounded
everyone's expectations.
And it is very hard to
stand next to someone...
giving an autograph.
- He doesn't even care.
- Of course he does.
But he may think you belong more
to other people than to him.
I love coming into the city.
It's 25 minutes, half hour, give or take,
from Tenafly, depending on the traffic.
I always think
I'm gonna go to museums and stuff.
And there's some good ones.
You've probably seen them.
But I always end up at Saks.
And I come home...
and Herb always says the same thing.
How much damage did you do, Peaches?
We always do some shopping.
My daughter is very generous.
She even invited me along
to this wonderful evening.
You get ahold of Silver Bells?
No. But that doesn't mean he's not coming.
- I'm pretty much done waiting.
- Perhaps we should go.
What?
No, I think we're gonna order now.
Herb gets very peckish.
I skipped lunch.
Can I help you, Bert?
You've already done all you can do.
Snapped this place into shape...
expanded our business
while keeping it lean.
Pending due diligence, we're done...
at $1 1 a share.
Really?
I believe I would like a drink.
What do you drink?
Do you have any brandy?
No.
Spirits of elderflower?
No. I don't have any laudanum either.
- Surprise me.
- Night, chief!
Bob, could you get Joan?
- And some ice.
- Absolutely.
When do we break the news?
Call the meeting for tomorrow.
So there she was in the garage...
right among the-you know,
there's an oil stain...
that Herb's been meaning to take care of.
There she is, our little puppy
with a full litter.
You're right, Mother.
They must have been adorable.
There's one yellow and one brown
and then three sort of mixed.
Each one at its own nipple.
- I love puppies.
- Not the way she does.
You know what?
Why don't we let the men discuss the business
they're probably here to talk about...
while we powder our noses?
Tall and tan and young and lovely.
So why are we here, Herb?
Oh, it's nothing serious.
I just had an idea.
There's a kid who's been writing fliers
for me at a few of my lots...
and I'm really getting results.
He's got a good turn of phrase.
I think you'd appreciate it.
Is he looking for a job?
No, he's got a job.
I just thought that
it might help you and me...
if he were to take a look
at some of your work...
even at the formative stages...
just to get his take on it.
What's his name?
Fawcett.
Chris Fawcett.
Here you go.
What is this?
It's the name of the guy who's going to be
handling your account from now on.
You never fail to overheat, do you?
You know the somersaults I'm doing
'cause you're so touchy?
Really? A man your size?
You know what?
Your whole company
should be taken to the woodshed.
First Campbell gives me the sass.
Then Sterling, he didn't even show up.
And you-Yeah.
My friend, you're gonna
be working for him.
And he could teach you something...
like knowing where your bread is buttered.
Why don't you get this?
I want you to buy me one last meal.
I'm tired of taking it
out of your account.
Okay.
And if you ever see Sterling again,
tell him you screwed up...
'cause I'm done with all of youse.
Don't sit down. Dinner's over.
Are you okay?
Never felt better in my life.
Nice meeting you. See you soon.
My mother needs an aspirin.
I don't care.
- Hello?
- Marie.
It's Roger. I'm so glad I got you.
If you are calling to apologize,
don't bother.
- It's too late. Good night.
- Hold on. Don't hang up.
- Let me talk to Don.
- Did you call to talk to Don?
Yes, but I was hoping you were there.
You were next, I swear.
You dragged me out and made me sit...
with that disgusting man
with his disgusting wife.
She is the apple that goes
in the pig's mouth.
Marie, I swear
I wouldn't have missed it for the world.
It's just something came up...
something very important
that I need to talk to Don about.
You are speaking slowly
so I will understand?
Forget... my... name.
Excuse me.
Is it possible for me
to pay for my friend?
Yes, but it's too late for that.
What are you bugging him for?
Aren't I enough for you?
This is my friend.
What was your fake name again?
Curious George?
You're a riot.
Hello.
Good night.
Isn't that guy a client?
- Is he gone?
- Yes.
I have a high-level accounts question.
A hypothetical.
So it doesn't involve
anybody in this room?
Let's say you caught your father-in-law
in a compromising position.
It's every Sunday night.
The guy can't hold his liquor.
Last night I was celebrating at that
party house up on Lex...
and I saw my father-in-law
exit the bedroom...
with the biggest, blackest prostitute
you've ever seen.
Was there anyone else from Vicks there?
Not that I saw. But we spoke.
I mean, all I said was hello, but-
Okay, look, when I was in high school...
they had this picture come
to the only movie theater in Cabot.
It was called Making A Baby.
They invited women and men separately...
but it was a delivery system
for some filthy stuff.
So at the matinee, I look over...
and Mr. Miller,
my science teacher, is five seats away.
And he's not, you know,
working the slide rule or anything...
but we see each other for sure.
But we both knew
that neither of us should be there.
It was mutually assured destruction.
So he's not going to say anything?
He can't.
Mr. Cosgrove, I have a phone call.
Give me a second.
It's why I don't worry about the bomb.
It's urgent.
I have Hugh Hibbert
and John Echolls from Jaguar.
Why are they calling you? Pick it up.
This is Ken.
Good morning.
Do you have any idea where Roger has been
for the last 24 hours?
- I don't.
- Draper!
What in the hell have you-
- What?
- You have done it again.
What did you say
to Herb Rennet last night?
Nothing that shouldn't
have been said last Christmas.
As usual, you have acted impulsively
and harmed the company irreparably.
- Pete, calm down.
- We already lost the account.
He was gonna bring in
some kid to write copy.
That's because
you screwed him last time!
You couldn't wait!
Pete, you've gotta understand
when it's over.
Do you know that we had a public offering
under way? And now it's ruined!
- What?
- You don't care about the company.
- You're already rich.
- Not here.
Inside.
- What is going on?
- Why the hell didn't I know about this?
- We're going public?
- Not anymore.
- When did that happen?
- I was going to tell you this morning.
I tried to last night, but you'd rather
have dinner with Herb Rennet.
Well, I have some good news
and some bad news.
- Where the hell have you been?
- Don fired Jaguar.
What?
Then I just have good news.
We're giving a presentation this Friday
on Chevy's top secret new car.
- What?
- Friday?
Come on! You've been thinking
about Chevy your whole life.
- Are you serious?
- And I have this check for $10,000.
Because I close, Pete. I close things.
Did I mention I was in Detroit...
where my friend Mikey O'Brien-
look him up-
said he was looking for
something cutting-edge...
but none of the agencies had it?
So he had a great idea- bring us in.
We're not afraid of a deadline.
Holy crap. Chevy.
You want to go public?
How much better is it when we have Chevy?
Don't act like you had a plan.
You're Tarzan swinging from vine to vine.
Roger, I want to know everything.
Pete, go box up Jaguar.
Make sure they have all their files today.
Joan, get the creatives in my office.
Get them yourself.
Don't you feel 300 pounds lighter?
I don't.
Honestly, Don, if I could deal with him,
you could deal with him.
And what now?
I went through all of that for nothing?
Joan, don't worry. I will win this.
Just once...
I would like to hear you
use the word "we."
Because we're all rooting for you
from the sidelines...
hoping that you'll decide
whatever you think is right for our lives.
In my office, all of you.
Should we go in there?
I don't care.
XP-887.
- So we get to name it?
- Possibly.
For now it's all cloak-and-dagger.
They've got a room full of R&D on this.
But it boils down
to Chevrolet's top brass...
trying to build the perfect car.
- They designed it with a computer.
- So they're scared.
They run another agency in
at the one-yard line.
- They're terrified.
- So who else is in it?
Well, the guest list limping in
is as follows- Campbell-Ewald.
Chevy's right arm.
They got 200 people in Detroit.
Dancer Fitzgerald Sample
and Cutler Gleason and Chaough.
Fantastic!
Two steamships and a rowboat.
You had to write that down?
There's no pictures.
It's a GM car.
It's got four wheels and an engine.
No, it's totally new.
Go to the library and get me everything
you can on Mustang.
- And Chevy.
- No, forget that.
They know there's been nothing
before Mustang and nothing after it...
but they're hoping it's this.
No one and nothing leaves my office.
How about that?
How 'bout it?
Are you okay?
I just wanted to watch Hazel,
but I can't get any reception.
I think you should go home.
I love how you work every account
like it's make or break.
I need some of that right now.
You've been working plenty.
I have a new way to go.
I'd show it to you, but it's top secret,
and it may be terrible.
Maybe Frank's right.
We should have never dumped Alfa.
It's one thing to want something.
It's another to need it.
This is your agency.
You're always going to need something.
Don't let Frank Gleason
make you question it.
Well, it's Frank's agency too, Peggy.
And I've been counting
on his paintbrush and his negativity...
to balance me out for 20 years.
Fine.
But... I've spent a lot of time
working with pessimistic people...
and I like the fact that you're-
Do not say I'm nice.
I hate it when people say I'm nice.
I was going to say strong.
I'm sorry.
I'm just grateful.
No, of course.
Good night, Peggy.
Yes.
Good night.
Hold that.
I got it.
You want to go celebrate?
I just quit my job.
What? Really?
I had a heart and a kid who needed
the heart, and now they're both dead.
I'm not gonna get the opportunity.
I'm tired of fighting.
Well, you're fighting God in a way.
Bullshit.
You don't think God's in Houston?
My hospital chickened out...
and now some asshole down there
is taking my place in history...
while I piss away my life
in New York City.
You can't think that way.
Fate hasn't chosen me.
Look...
I don't cut people open,
but I don't believe in fate.
You make your own opportunities.
You sure you don't want to go for a drink?
I got work.
- How'd it go?
- I don't know.
I was gonna sleep on it...
but now I think
I'm just gonna shower and go back in.
I love you like this.
Desperate and scared?
Fearless.
And I want to do whatever I can...
to make sure you do not fail.
Then you can jump from the balcony...
and fly to work like Superman.
Will there be anything else?
No, thank you, Daisy.
Actually, can you get those lugs
from Dancer bumped off the flight?
Roger, I told you,
I can't hurt the company.
They bought most of the seats.
Jesus, there's like eight of them.
Surprised to see you here.
Taking your kid to look at colleges?
No, taking him to pick out a car.
When did they add
you guys to the mix?
When they saw your work.
I wish you the best of luck.
In fact, maybe we shouldn't even go.
What are the billings for Vicks?
Nine million?
Someone's gonna pick that up.
Any of you have a cough drop?
I know they don't.
Get him on the phone right now,
or I'm coming over there!
I've got it, Clara.
Roger's calling from the airport.
He says something happened
with Vick Chemical.
Tell my father-in-law I am not joking!
Believe me. You do not
want me in your lobby.
Let me talk to Roger.
So it's true?
No, I'm gonna fix it.
- Jesus, they don't need to hear this right now.
- Roger will handle it.
- Well?
- They're screwing with us.
Really?
Daisy's gonna lose their luggage.
Well, apparently you didn't
get any of my calls.
So I came down here to your lair.
Spare me the outrage, Pete.
I'm tired of it.
Tom, what are you doing?
I know we're both
emotional and vulnerable...
but I'm not the enemy here.
I'm an adult, as are you.
And if anything, our relationship
has shown over the last seven years...
that I have a very short memory.
Now, what can I do
to bring you back to reality...
in this obviously impulsive decision?
My daughter is a princess.
She could have had anyone.
I knew there was a reason
you never wanted children.
You have no business being a father.
You just pressed the button, Tom.
You just blew everything up.
Well, it makes me sick
thinking about the man I saw...
being with my daughter
and my granddaughter.
Why don't you look in the mirror?
You can walk out like a man...
or I can have you thrown out
like the lowlife you are.
If I have as low character as you say,
why would you push me like this?
You'll do the right thing.
The paint fumes are making me sick.
I got the windows open.
It'll be dry in a couple of days.
And when am I gonna be able to walk around
my apartment in bare feet?
Soon. We're fixing it up.
In here, yes. But out there?
Those kids are living on our stoop...
lighting firecrackers
and playing their music.
And you keep waving to them.
Look, the neighborhood's changing.
We're a part of that.
I don't like change.
I want everything to stay the way it was.
I don't think you understand, babe.
Everything's getting better.
Johnson's gone. The war is gonna end.
We're gonna have a new president,
no matter what.
Maybe McCarthy. Worst case, Kennedy.
I love Bobby Kennedy.
Fine.
If that's what you want.
I just want you to kiss me.
Damn it.
Hello to you too.
What the hell
are you doing in Detroit?
My doctor recommended an ocean voyage.
Can I get one of those?
I don't believe this.
I spent six weeks on this pipe dream,
and it's gonna be over in two seconds.
Hell, I knew I was good, but I didn't know
all I had to do was show up.
You don't know what this means?
It's not my job to put you at ease...
but just because they brought us in at
the last second doesn't mean you're dead.
Me? We're both dead.
I've had enough
psychological warfare today.
- Why don't you take a table?
- Think about it.
When it's two top 10 agencies and me,
I've got a chance.
Now that there's two little guys,
we're D.O.A.
I'm not worried. I've got great work.
Of course you do.
And mine's even better, I guarantee.
You know how this works.
They're gonna take our creative
and give it to one of the big boys.
Second place, tied with last.
Come on. You know I'm right.
So they want a name brand.
- We had a car.
- So did we.
It's not the same thing.
It's the size of the team.
It's opening an office in Detroit.
This is General Motors.
They fight the war
with bodies on the ground.
I saw Dancer at the airport.
Looked like half my office.
This business is rigged.
Damn it.
That's what I said. Sorry about that.
I'm tired of this crap.
I should just let Chevy buy my brain
and put it in a jar.
Can I get another?
Brain in a jar.
Put it on your tombstone.
"Here lies SCDP,
the little company with the big ideas."
"CGC, giving away creative
one car at a time."
So what did you go with?
What, I show you mine, you show me yours?
What's the difference at this point?
You first.
Okay, but I gotta stand up.
This is a car for the young
and the young at heart.
Because today nobody knows
where they're headed...
but they're not afraid
of what's around the bend.
Power plus design equals adventure.
Throw the map out the window
and hit the road,Jack.
Then I sing the song.
- That's good.
- No kidding.
Just music. People's faces.
All kinds- teenagers, dads, moms.
Different expressions of wonder.
What could this possibly be?
It's so new...
this combination of power,
technology, comfort and price...
that it's impossible to imagine.
But not at Chevy.
The future...
is something you haven't
even thought of yet.
You run that for a week.
Then you finally show the car.
That's interesting.
Hooray.
So should we go home?
"We."
That's interesting.
Why, you want to stay just so
Chevy can put a feather in your cap?
I have a better idea.
No, you don't. I just heard it.
This is why everyone hates you.
Think about it.
Both of us have the creative...
but neither of us have an agency to match.
Why would I do that?
Because we're dead.
Even if I were to consider that,
Chevy calls the shots.
Hey, Lieutenant,
want to get into some trouble?
How would that even work?
Well, one of us, probably me...
will have to figure out
a way to make Chevy...
think it was their idea
to combine our agencies.
And then the other one-
let's say it was you-
will have to figure out
what the hell we're gonna present.
Well, we have partners.
Who aren't sitting in this bar.
Can I get another?
No, we're done.
We've got a long night.
I want to make it clear.
Unless this works, I'm against it.
I was just saying the same thing.
Shall we?
After you.
You're not supposed to be here
till the weekend.
I don't like you surprising me.
Sit down, Trudy.
Did you know your father
pulled his business?
No.
And I don't care, Peter.
You understand that we were going to be
very rich, but he's ruined that.
He's done everything for you.
He's a hypocrite, Trudy.
Don't you dare criticize my father.
I guess it doesn't matter
that I caught him in a midtown whorehouse.
Just stop it right now.
It's true.
With a 200-pound Negro prostitute.
Ask him to his face.
You'll say anything to hurt me, won't you?
He wanted it this way.
He left me no other choice.
You had lots of choices, Peter.
We're done. Get your things.
Mr. Chaough wants to seeyou.
- He's back?
- That's all I know.
So, how'd it go?
We got it. We won Chevy.
What are you doing here?
We went in together.
What?
What are you talking about?
They wanted our ideas and a big agency,
so we gave them both.
Just for Chevy?
No, we merged-
furniture, fixtures, everything.
I'm sorry. I don't understand.
I did this wrong once before...
so let me tell you
how great it's going to be...
and you can decide
if you want to come along.
You are the copy chief at one
of the top 25 ad agencies in the country.
You're not even 30. I'm jealous.
I just bought an apartment.
Congratulations.
Are we moving?
We are, and we'd like you
to write the press release.
For what?
We don't have a name yet...
but make it sound like
the agency you want to work for.
Who do I give it to?
Give it to Ted.
New York City, May 17, 1968.
For immediate release.