So you haven't officially told anyone
you're looking to change your life?
Yes.
But why put Doyle Dane into hysterics
when all I want to do...
is have what NASA calls
an exploratory mission with your agency?
Still, Timmy...
Don has some anxiety about...
well, obviously about Raymond.
Heinz Baked Beans has given us
national recognition...
and Raymond's a friend.
I'm not used to telling people
what my account is worth.
Not just in billings, but in the prestige
that comes with ketchup.
Don knows that, or he wouldn't be here.
He's not that polite.
Just relax.
If you do the work and I like it...
I guarantee that Raymond will fall in line.
I have that power.
- And if you don't like our work?
- Raymond never has to know.
I don't know if that solves my problem.
Look, I understand your risk.
Or we could have met in your office again.
In fact, we can have
the presentation here too.
No, we'll get a hotel.
I, uh, am supposed to be meeting someone
in about 20 minutes...
and she likes me to wait for her.
Well, take your time.
And remember...
I don't need much of an excuse
to come to Manhattan.
When I say a small team, I mean Stan.
Just the three of us.
We bill it under Project K.
Nice place.
Well, it's available to you.
You know, if you ever have
to spend the night in the city.
I live here, Pete.
It's been 7:00 for 20 minutes.
I'm starving.
I'm sorry I'm late, but I have a job.
You know what, Dawn?
You have another job-
which is being my maid of honor.
Well, I can't lose that one, can I?
Well, I have some bad news.
Al called me...
and he said both the caterer
and your date fell through.
William? What happened?
Al doesn't think he's
ready to settle down.
And he didn't want you
to spend the night defending yourself.
You tell Al to keep looking...
because I'm never gonna
meet someone at that office.
- Al and I met at church.
- Church is impossible.
You can't stand out
in that crowd of harlots.
You stand out.
You must run into somebody downtown.
I get on the train, and it's just us...
and then it gets thinner
and thinner until about 72nd.
Sometimes it's just me
and this old shoeshine.
And he won't even look at me.
Bea Carter says
her son Anthony ran into you.
But that's what you don't understand.
We were walking through the plaza...
and we passed each other
and we just nodded.
Someone told me he said that,
but he didn't talk to me.
And I didn't talk to him either.
Well, I'll keep looking.
That might be too much blush.
If you look a little rusty,
it's 'cause I'm a little rusty.
I need all the help I can get.
The makeup's not the important part.
Mary Kay always says it's really about
making yourself feel better...
and that starts
with doing something for you.
Well, that'll be a first.
- Kate!
- Shh. I just put the baby down.
- You have not changed.
- Well, you have.
How did you suddenly get younger than me?
Because she's in the beauty business.
What do you think?
- How much did she spend?
- It's free.
This is my old stuff.
I'm a sales director now.
- How are your boys?
- Good.
- Did you see Kevin?
- She looked in.
Why don't we let him sleep
while we eat dinner?
I made a pork roast.
And I made reservations
at Le Cirque for two.
Well, I want to catch up.
And, more importantly...
Kate has a job interview tomorrow,
and I don't want her tying one on.
- Who are you meeting with?
- The competition.
- Can we take a rain check?
- Splendid.
She hasn't changed.
Why are you getting on
an elevator going up?
Because the door opened
and you were standing there.
I pressed down.
Where have you been?
I missed you.
Working all the time. Don't tell anyone.
Like who?
Arnie's on call Thursday or Friday.
I'll leave a penny under the mat
when he's flown the coop.
I have to go.
Can you be more specific?
Nope.
Good night.
Dennis must be doing well.
- That's from the company.
- My goodness.
What do you have to do to get this?
Just have a lot of my recruits
sell a lot of Mary Kay.
How much? Those are diamonds.
- Just has to be the most.
- They know what they're doing.
I know. They do. But there's no way
for me to move up there.
So is that why you're going to Avon?
There's women above me at Mary Kay.
It's just working out of Spokane,
there's only so far I can go.
Well, Joanie's a partner...
and I don't know if anyone would want
all that extra responsibility.
You should visit more often.
Turns out someone's proud of me.
I'm a monster.
Believe it or not...
"My daughter is a partner
at a Madison Avenue advertising firm"...
is something I enjoy saying.
It does sound pretty good.
Well, so much for keeping
my wits about me.
I should be getting back to the Waldorf.
Well, I wish you
the best of luck tomorrow.
But if worse come to worse,
you're appreciated somewhere.
What are the Life magazine
closing dates for Birds Eye?
Ken, it's Monday.
I got a perfect cup of coffee
and a Danish on the way.
You want to start with "Good morning?
How was your weekend?"
I spent it with my in-laws
listening to Ed complain...
about how much the world
hates Dow Chemical.
And I know that every gripe he has
is directed at me and this company.
Is it possible that this
has turned Ken Cosgrove into a neurotic?
If he wants people to stop hating him...
he should stop dropping
napalm on children.
I know you just came here to complain...
but I actually think that I can help you.
God, that's really true.
I just came in here to complain.
How hard would it be to meet with Ed,
just you and me?
If I have a good reason?
I'm sorry, Mr. Cosgrove,
but it's the last one.
- Did you find your keys?
- I did.
Can you get Pierre Cossette on the line?
- I have an idea. Let's see what happens.
- Harry has great ideas.
I saw this thing on a spy show.
It's a clock with a tiny camera in it.
All we have to do is get it in there.
If you can get in, you don't need a clock.
I would guess it's a military account.
And I would guess they picked Stan
because he has no conscience.
So Project K stands for what?
Project Kill Machine!
That's not what it stands for.
So what does it stand for, Bobby?
I don't know what it is.
Are you saying that because
you do know what it is?
No.
- Stan come through?
- Stan who?
I know one thing- he's not in a room
with tinfoil on the windows.
How are things, Don?
There's nothing in here.
- 'Cause you're gonna fill it with work.
- Mm.
- If you don't fall asleep.
I'm telling you, it clears the cobwebs.
I think a hot dog
and a hamburger are too similar.
Plus, a hot dog cries out for mustard.
No, I think a hot dog
cries out for ketchup.
A squiggly line.
Hmm.
I think we should order lunch.
Mmm. My goodness.
Someone's having a party
and didn't invite us.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Is Clara's birthday today?
It's tomorrow, and it's $2.00 a head.
And, actually, I don't know
what I'm going to get.
- Do you want to come?
- I can't.
Mr. Draper always needs me.
Could you punch me out when you leave?
Really?
How long are you going to be gone?
Well, if you punch me out-
Okay.
I heard Mr. Draper's in there.
No.
- Did you get the pages?
- No.
Are you two rehearsing already?
Call me when you see them.
Arlene, are you sad it's not you?
You know Mel is my husband.
I could have him write you
into a hospital bed... or a grave.
I'm sorry.
What's going on?
Well, you're going to have
a love scene with Rod.
And between you, me and soon a national
audience, it's more of a love affair.
Oh, my goodness.
That's so exciting.
- Thank you for telling me.
- Oh, I did more than tell you.
Mel's been on the fence,
but I think he really believes in you.
Now, don't embarrass me.
You've done this before, haven't you?
Um, well, of course.
- Does a high school play count?
- No.
It's gonna be exciting at first,
and then it'll be part of the job.
It's pretty exciting.
The hard part is how James Garner there
will deal with it.
Some people think it's better to wait
till after it's happened...
or not tell them at all,
but I think it's best to be up front.
Well, obviously he's not going to like it.
Would you be upset if he did?
I don't know.
Why don't Mel and I
take you two out to dinner?
You know, to make him comfortable.
And, honestly,
all of us should be better acquainted.
I mean, Mel has big plans for you.
I'm gonna leave you alone with these.
- Did you send Scarlett somewhere?
- No, Meredith.
Well, it's just I can't find her or Mr. Crane,
and there's someone to see him.
I'm dying for you to meet Ken.
How are you?
Busy.
Have Scarlett see me when you find her.
Oh, good. You're home on time.
I am. It's only because
I have a lot of work...
and I don't want to do it
in a windowless room.
So, why don't you have a seat?
I'm gonna get you a drink.
And then I'm gonna
stuff you with coq au vin.
I know you're very busy...
but I want us to have- I don't know-
I want us to be able to talk
about things other than work.
Megan, what happened?
Just once I'd like to be that wife...
that lays a trap and has her husband
walk right into it.
Okay, first of all, Arlene-
You know, she plays Penelope Aldridge.
She basically owns Berkshire Falls.
She's married to Mel, the head writer,
and they want to have dinner with us.
Does it get worse?
Well, my story line
is getting more developed...
and that means I'm gonna have
a series of love scenes.
- With whom?
- With Rod Holly.
He plays Rafe Jackson.
He's Arlene's nephew.
Megan, I don't care.
What's a "love scene" consist of?
It's just kissing and hugging.
It's TV. We can't really do anything.
What am I supposed to say?
That you trust me
and that you know it's part of my job.
And maybe that it was bound to happen
if things went well.
Keep going.
I'm dying to hear what I say next.
Should I have hidden it from you?
I don't know, Megan.
I need to think about it.
Look, I know I wouldn't like it...
but I'd look on the bright side.
Okay, I guess if I wasn't your husband,
I would be happy for you.
It does mean they like you.
Do you like me?
Honey, I can tolerate this,
but I can't encourage it.
You're perfect.
Honestly, Ed, it's not just Ken
who's been losing sleep about this.
I mean, last week when half of Columbia
got into your lobby-
It was 15 people.
Look, you've been in
the news every other day.
A couple of articles placed in business journals
are not gonna make that stop.
They acted like they were
storming the Bastille.
This is their country too.
- What exactly is your point?
- Pierre.
A one-hour prime-time TV special
sponsored by Dow...
starring Joe Namath
and 15 or so of his best friends...
putting on a show drawing from America's
most beloved musicals.
Broadway Joe on Broadway.
Joe Namath sings?
Don't you want to watch it
just to find out?
And who are his friends?
I have access
to the greatest talent available.
There'll be sex appeal.
Joey Heatherton, for example.
Pipes, Julie Andrews and punch.
How about John Wayne
in a sketch version of Camelot?
We're mostly household products.
Women don't like football.
Have you ever asked them about Joe Namath?
Forget demographics.
How would you like Dow to be responsible
for making people smile?
And is there anything that makes people smile
more than Broadway and football?
"Yankee Doodle Dandy"
and the Notre Dame fight song...
playing at the same time.
I'm a Yankee Doodle Dandy
Yankee Doodle, do or die
Okay, okay.
Kenny, did you tell them
I went to Notre Dame?
No, I told them about Joey Heatherton.
So it's tailor-made for us?
- What's our commitment?
- Well, you'd be a corner tenant.
There's six minutes
of commercials in the hour.
You'd get three and then
two 10-second billboards...
at the beginning and end of the show.
"Brought to you by Dow Chemical.
Family products for the American family."
Just imagine Joe Namath in a straw hat.
I'm sorry to bother you, Scarlett...
but is Mr. Crane in?
Okay.
No. He's in a meeting.
Is there something I can help you with?
Well, if he's expecting any special guests,
you should let us know.
Because he had someone come yesterday,
and you weren't here.
I must have been in the ladies' room.
No, and it's strange because
you didn't leave until 6:47.
Oh, Joan, it's Clara's birthday today...
and I tried to go at lunch,
but I got stuck at my desk.
So I left Mr. Crane on his own while I
attended to this company business.
We got her a Givenchy scarf from Gimbels.
I have the card here for you to sign.
But you never came back,
and you had Dawn punch your time card.
No, Dawn and I were working together.
But we were all over the place.
But mostly in Accounting.
Thank you for clearing that up.
Dawn.
Have you spoken to Scarlett this morning?
We're missing the big hole punch, and I
think you were the last one to see her.
The hole punch is in the creative lounge.
Dawn, Scarlett told me everything.
Scarlett, you're fired.
Joan, please. It won't happen again.
Not here it won't. Go get your things.
Dawn, could you get Stan in here
before the partners' meeting?
I'll deal with you later.
Girls do it all the time.
Just go before you really
embarrass yourself.
I hope you realize this means
now you're on Ed's radar.
So will I be invited to Sunday dinner?
Something like that.
I don't know where you're going, but I
want you to bring back champagne.
Oh, Harry, I'm not coming back.
What are you talking about?
Joan, you owe Scarlett an apology.
Harry, please don't
involve yourself in this.
I'm tired of your petty dictatorship.
So whatever capital crime or treason
she committed, she's in my department.
I didn't realize you were
that attached to Scarlett.
- We're not attached.
- We are attached!
I have something more important to do.
I would hope you do too.
Scarlett, do whatever you think is best.
You are to do whatever I think is best.
Let's go. Back to work.
Everything's fine.
I understand the confidentiality,
but I need to know how to bill Project K.
Don't.
Meredith, why don't you step out?
I don't know what she said because
I'm not privy to these conversations...
but I would like the chance
to defend myself.
- Mr. Crane, I haven't-
- No, please.
Let him go on.
Well, it's this simple- Scarlett works for me
and Joan tried to fire her.
She left work early
and had Dawn punch her time card.
It's pay for a minimum of five hours of work
that she didn't do that we are paying for.
Well, it's either me or her.
- Joan?
- Scarlett.
I think you mean, "If she goes, I go."
Broadway Joe on Broadway.
Is there anybody in here
who thought of that?
- I did.
- What the hell is that?
It's $150,000 worth of incremental business
I generated while solving a problem.
For what? So I can stand outside that glass
and watch you all in here?
- What did Dawn do?
- Well, I'm almost positive-
Just keep talking to her
because she's a partner.
You know what?
I'm sorry my accomplishments
happened in broad daylight...
and I can't be given the same rewards.
- What is that supposed to mean?
- You know damn well.
The next time this group is called to order,
I expect to be sitting at this table.
I've actually earned it.
Don't worry, dear.
That's not going to happen.
Joan, I don't want to put myself
in the same camp as Harry...
but I might remind you and everyone...
the Commission on Human Rights
is continuing to investigate our industry...
regarding the employment of Negroes.
She's a good secretary.
Of course.
What about Scarlett?
I think this humiliation will suffice.
Can we continue with the billings?
Yes.
Where were we?
"Meredith, why don't you step out?"
Well?
Oh.
I'm sorry, but I couldn't leave.
I don't care, as long as you brought
those bridal magazines.
What is wrong with you?
I had a day today that pushed
your stupid wedding...
to the bottom of the list.
- Did you get fired?
- No.
I don't think so.
Who can tell at that place?
What happened?
One of the girls asked me to punch out
her time card, and we got caught.
I told you,
those girls aren't your friends.
Yes, they are.
She got in more trouble than me.
Why do you think she asked you?
You can't say no 'cause you're too scared.
All they see is, "Yes, sir."
Everybody's scared there.
Women crying in the ladies' room.
Men crying in the elevator.
It sounds like New Year's Eve
when they empty the garbage...
there are so many bottles.
And I told you about that poor man
hanging himself in his office.
Oh, they got it so bad,
they must all be jealous of you.
What am I gonna do?
Throw a brick through their window?
I want to keep my job,
so I'm gonna keep my head down.
Well, I couldn't do it.
Well, you don't have to.
You're getting married.
And dinner.
I should have brought Dennis.
You're not even listening to me.
I'm sorry. I need a drink,
and this place is a soda fountain.
I feel like I'm in high school,
right down to the clientele.
Hello?
We're sitting here waiting for a phone
to ring. This actually is high school.
- So what do you do to have fun?
- I don't look in a guidebook.
This wasn't in a guidebook, okay?
My friend told me about it.
Is she a nun
or just the right age for this place?
Apparently, there are
quite a few men here...
who go for a certain type.
Oh.
Joanie, don't judge me. I'm in New York.
Good evening, ladies.
If there's anything you need,
I'll be over there.
Catherine's got a lot of tables,
so don't hesitate.
I'm Leo.
I'm Kate. And this is Joan.
Actually, I don't think
our phone is working.
- Can you test it?
- I'll see what I can do.
How many girls come in here and complain
that their phones are broken?
He's cute. Reminds me of Scotty.
Well, don't marry him.
That was the worst six months of my life.
You always did everything first.
But you did everything smart.
Well, tonight we are just
a couple of young secretaries.
Answer it.
Hello?
How did you do that?
I didn't do anything. He likes you.
What?
Oh.
Just a minute. Let me ask my girlfriend.
He wants us to meet him after his shift.
- Well, tell him you know a place.
- But I don't. Do you?
- Should I invite him to my room?
- No.
We're just trying to think of a place.
- Tell him to think of a place.
- Do you know of a place?
Oh, good.
- Hang up.
- Till then.
Okay, now I need a drink.
Do you honestly believe a few jokes
on the Smothers Brothers...
are really upsetting people?
I think it's the sponsors
and the network...
don't want to have
a conversation about the war.
I'd like to have an evening without
Darling, you shouldn't smoke so much.
The weight you lose isn't worth the wrinkles.
See, I think the sponsors are for the war.
They don't want to have any dissent.
Don, you're a writer.
You know this is censorship.
I am a writer and I'm against the war, but-
When you buy a commercial,
you're hoping...
that the consumer is in a good mood
when they hear your message.
So if you agree on
a wholesome variety show...
and all of a sudden it's filled with satire-
the most threatening humor there is-
you're worried about people
hating what you're selling.
Megan, let's talk about you...
and how you found this man.
I could cast you, you know that.
Yes, I'm sure he's a man
who plays many roles.
Luckily, you don't have to worry
about censorship with the show...
because it's so tame.
Of course it's for daytime entertainment.
It's for housewives.
It has to be a little titillating.
We have our own standards.
Although they've been
very liberal with us.
But, you know...
when we do things on the show,
it's all very tasteful.
Well, it's not real life.
Why don't you let me get the check?
We go back to our pad,
smoke some grass and...
see what happens.
Sounds like fun.
I don't know. It's late.
It's not.
Look, if you don't smoke grass,
that's fine.
It's not everything we had in mind.
I'm not sure if I understand.
We like Megan.
And we like you.
And we'd like to be friends.
Us too.
Well, then, uh-
I guess it's not impossible,
under the right circumstances...
for us to... become better acquainted.
Hey, it may not work.
It's a chemistry experiment.
I have a big day tomorrow.
You both know that.
That's work. This is play.
I have to get up very early.
That's what black coffee's for.
I make it delicious.
Uh-
Maybe another time.
Arlene, we've heard "no" before.
I guess there's no reason to skip dessert.
What? This is the best seat.
St. Mark's
between Second and Third, please.
Have you been to the Electric Circus?
- All the time.
- We're from out of town.
Let's see who kisses better.
I'm not playing this game.
Because she'll lose.
What the hell was that?
What? They like you and they like me,
and they'd like us to be friends.
They were so out in the open.
It was a good strategy.
I kept thinking he was going to ask me
for a job directing commercials.
Maybe he was waiting for tomorrow morning
when we were basking in the afterglow.
- Don't.
- Just a pile of arms and legs.
I don't know whether
to laugh or be sick...
because now I think that's the reason
they gave me the scene.
I'm sure they've tried that with plenty
of people who haven't gotten scenes.
Don, I have to go back to work with them.
It'll be better than ever.
How long have they been married?
Eighteen years.
I'm busy.
Come up for air.
Oh, hey.
Would you mind?
This is my friend.
I'm Johnny.
Joan. Pleased to meet you.
Johnny and Joan.
Bonnie and Clyde.
- Do you want a drink?
- I have one.
Bonnie and Clyde
What'd I say?
Well, what did he say?
He said I'd want you.
Bonnie and Clyde
Well, war or no war...
Nixon doesn't think he's
running against Johnson.
He thinks he's running
against the ghost of Kennedy.
So does Johnson.
I don't know where Helen is.
How are you both this morning?
Frankly, we're a little embarrassed.
Well, if that has anything to do with me,
I apologize. That was not my intention.
How are Jennifer, Bea and the twins?
It's Nathan and Steven, right?
Yes. Uh, they're well, thank you.
That display yesterday of-
well, of initiative
really caught our attention.
This is a check for $23,500.
That's the full commission
on Broadway Joe.
Well, thank you. That's a lot of money.
So, anything else to say?
I'm puzzled.
What do you make a year, Mr. Crane?
Twenty-two. So what about the partnership?
You want some of the spoils.
Well, there you go.
We have to get bigger
before we get bigger.
What a load of crap.
- You know, Joan's not even in yet.
- Leave her out of this.
Bert, you know how important
I am to this company. You were me.
I was different than you, Mr. Crane,
in every way.
- So you don't want the money?
- No, I've earned the money.
But I've also earned a partnership.
I really hope some other firm
doesn't figure that out first.
That was the most
impressive thing he's done.
Should we fire him
before he cashes that check?
... New York Senator Robert F. Kennedy.
- Aren't you gonna be late?
- Aren't you?
I love you.
Wish me luck.
Good luck.
I'm really waking you this time.
Kate.
Honey, wake up.
Now, you two layabouts have to bathe him.
I have an appointment.
Mom, I'm still going to work.
Do you need to throw up?
Mother, can you give us a minute?
Why did I do that?
You had some fun.
I just wanted to try it.
Now you'll go home and you'll find
everything right where it belongs.
I'm really not you, am I?
- Why would you want to be?
- Are you kidding?
Look what you did.
You came out here.
You staked this out on your own.
I always had Dennis to fall back on.
Even when I went to Mary Kay.
You didn't.
And I never will.
How'd that happen?
The whole reason I even talked to Avon...
is because I wanted-
I don't know- what you have.
It's not what you think.
- You're an executive.
- It's a title.
And money.
I've been working there for 15 years,
and they still treat me like a secretary.
What's it have to do with them?
You're there, Joan.
And from where I'm sitting,
it's damn impressive.
I don't care how they make you feel.
It's right in front of you for the taking.
I'll be back in an hour.
There you go.
Oh.
Okay, I'll draw the bath.
It's clean, it's simple...
and it's tantalizingly incomplete.
What's missing?
One thing.
"Pass the Heinz."
You mean the Heinz Ketchup.
It's Heinz. It only means one thing.
It feels like half an ad.
The greatest thing
you have working for you...
is not the photo you take
or the picture you paint.
It's the imagination of the consumer.
They have no budget.
They have no time limit.
And if you can get into that space,
your ad can run all day.
Well, Pete, you said I'd say it.
It's pretty bold work.
I think I still want to see our bottle.
- I thought that at first too, but-
- We will test it both ways.
It's a testament to ketchup
that there can be no confusion.
Let me chew on it, fellas.
You're going to be thinking
of ketchup all day...
and you didn't even see it.
Thank you. We'll be in touch.
Well, hello.
Hello.
Ted, you want to come in?
I hope you left us something.
Hey, how are you?
It's a bake-off? Since when?
- Come on, Don.
- Go wait by the elevator.
Peggy.
So, what's the difference
between ketchup and catsup?
Well, catsup has more tomatoes,
comes in a bigger bottle...
is cheaper, but tastes just like ketchup.
Now, we know that's not true...
but that's what
your competitors are saying.
Over and over.
And they're selling their watered-down,
flavorless sauce...
by pretending that they're you.
Makes you angry, doesn't it?
Me too.
But I always say...
if you don't like what they're saying...
change the conversation.
"Heinz. The only ketchup."
Imagine this 40 feet tall...
in Times Square.
Ketchup versus catsup-
end of conversation.
- Good morning.
- Good afternoon.
Thank you.
Joan, may I have a word?
I'm sorry I was not
more forthright with you.
I think it would only be fair
if you docked my pay...
to cover the hours Scarlett did not work.
Fair to whom? Scarlett?
I don't know. Fair to the company?
This is the key to the supply closet...
and this is the key to the time cards.
You will be responsible
for monitoring both.
What?
Okay.
- Thank you.
- Don't thank me.
You don't understand
that this is a punishment.
I don't care if everybody hates me here,
as long as you don't.
We'll see.
So there's two of us.
We're both the same size agency.
You're not afraid of
a little heads-up baseball.
I only did it because no one else
was supposed to know.
I think everything
should be done in secret.
Lock me in that Project K room,
I'll work on anything, Don.
I miss it already.
Mind if we join the Lonely Hearts Club?
Who says we're not celebrating?
J. Walter Thompson.
They bought it in the room.
Are you kidding me? We paid for that room.
What do you know?
The biggest agency in the world.
Oh, I'm glad you're here.
See, I just got off the phone
with Raymond Geiger...
and he said that you
were at the Roosevelt...
giving a presentation
to the ketchup brand manager.
But I said that was impossible...
because how could that happen
at my firm without me knowing?
Because no one was supposed to know.
Let me get a rye rocks and an Old Spanish.
I'm sorry, Ken. Damn it.
I'll call him. I'll work it out.
Don't bother.
He doesn't even want to give us 90 days.
There's nothing better
than being known for your loyalty.
You hear that, Ted?
Vinegars, sauces and beans is available.
Help yourself. It's a gold mine.
They'd love that.
There's a pie,
and they slice it into pieces...
and they throw the tiniest piece
into the yard...
and let all the small agencies
fight over it.
Speak for yourself.
It was worth the risk.
I think I see a friend.
Please, Rafe, you have a family.
I have a family that ignores me,
that treats me like I've never been there.
But you, you make me feel new again.
I work for you.
And for her.
She's good to me.
Stop fighting. I don't know
how much longer I can take this.
This is your bed you share with her.
I can't.
Rafe, we can't.
Corinne, don't deny this,
what's between us.
Don't deny me when I know you feel it too.
I do.
Rafe.
You like to watch, do you?
Oh, Rafe.
And we're clear.
Everyone to the conservatory set.
- Very nice, everyone.
- You did great.
Thank you.
Megan, your agent's here.
That was steamy.
So I should go change, and we can go.
I'll keep you company.
What are you doing here?
Because you didn't want me to see that?
No, and I don't understand
why you'd do that to yourself.
It's a hell of a lot better
than letting my imagination run wild.
The first time you come to set
is for this?
I've been here for months.
What did you think was going to happen?
- I didn't expect you to enjoy it.
- It's acting, Don.
Were you gonna brush your teeth at least
before you came home?
I'm sick of tiptoeing around you every
time something good happens to me.
This is my job. No, my career.
You kiss people for money.
You know who does that?
You couldn't stop it,
so I guess ruining it was enough for you.
Would you rather have not known?
You never watch the show.
It'd be like it never happened.
Why don't you have dinner
with Arlene and Mel tonight?
They're much more open-minded.
That's been out there all day.
Was it going to be out there all night?
Yes.
- Take that off.
- Why?
It doesn't mean anything to you.
- It does to you.
- It does.
So what do you do when I leave here?
Get on your knees and pray for absolution?
I pray for you.
For me to come back?
No.
For you to find peace.