Sure, let's give up now.
It's no big deal.
It's just Pharmacide,
just their tour kick-off.
I mean, who cares if we miss the
most insane party in the world?
Come on, Phoeb.
Victory or death.
Or possibly cake.
Look, I'm sorry.
Sorry, your caffeine fix
is on its way.
Will you hold on?
Hi, we're the DJ's assistants.
Hold on.
No. I said we both
work for him.
You mean "her."
The DJ is a she-jay.
It's okay, Dave,
she's my plus one.
Make that plus two.
You weren't worried, were you?
Yes.
And there will be punishment
unless you tell us everything.
You've been here all night?
After the party, we went up to the
Presidential Suite with the band.
It was ginormous,
like 10 rooms.
We had a few drinks
and some weed,
and played Drummer God
on this giant plasma TV.
Which she rocked, by the way.
I think I hate you right now.
Colt took me up to the roof, but by
then the gate to the pool was locked.
So no one was up there. So we just
climbed over and jumped down,
and went skinny dipping.
Did you do it?
No. He was so sweet.
Later, he played his guitar
and he wrote a song for me.
Oh, my God.
Jord, what happened
to your foot?
Maybe you twisted your
ankle when you jumped.
Or it could be your allergies.
My aunt was allergic
to some cold medication,
and her hands swelled up
like the Marshmallow Man's.
Jord, are you okay?
Jordan!
Foreman expects me to read an
x-ray on this itty-bitty screen.
He should have e-mailed
me a larger phone.
Why are you packing?
We're leaving this afternoon
for the conference
on pharmacology
and public policy.
We? We discussed this.
It's been on your
calendar for weeks.
So has Ramadan.
Think of it as a vacation.
Nice, healthy Adirondack air.
Or not, I don't care.
You're coming with.
You should come with me. State
Pillow-Fighting Championships.
Dollar beers, wet t-shirts.
In the words of the
philosopher Eddie Money,
"I've got two tickets
to paradise."
House, when you moved in, I promised
your therapist I'd be here for you.
I can't be here if I'm there,
unless you're there, too.
So it's not a discussion.
Fine.
I'll let Foreman know that the 16-year-old
patient with the severe edema can wait.
Relax, I got no idea what's wrong
with her, so odds are not fatal.
Still not going.
She's got rhabdo.
Who wants to come to the
Pillow-Fighting Championships?
Rutgers has got a
great team this year.
So glad their anchor
didn't turn pro.
Sixteen-year-old girl suddenly has
the joints of an 80-year-old.
You think we can discuss
this for a second?
It's rhabdo.
Patient gave you the answer.
She fell down and went boom.
We have to leave in an hour,
so should we eenie meenie?
The fall would explain the lower leg
damage, but not the swollen hands.
Hard landing caused
crushed muscles,
crushed muscles released
toxins into the bloodstream,
toxins caused swelling
in the hands and legs.
Just another way of saying it's rhabdo.
Fifty-nine minutes.
She's a credit-card kid.
Parents are architects. They're
working on a project in Shanghai.
Could you be sitting any further away
from Chase and still be in the same room?
It doesn't have to be rhabdo.
The swelling could also be
caused by deep vein thrombosis.
She has allergies,
could be anaphylaxis,
or some heart condition
that we don't...
It can't really be any of those
things since it's rhabdo.
I know it's rhabdo,
Foreman knows it's rhabdo,
deep in his heart, even
Chase knows it's rhabdo.
Isn't it annoying when everybody in
the room knows something you don't?
I'll test for everything.
He's an ass.
Contrast is ready.
She already thinks
I'm cheating on her.
Maybe this is House's way
of telling you to talk to her.
Sure. "How was your day, honey?
By the way, I killed someone."
If I tell her, that's dumping
a burden on her forever.
Okay.
No sign of
obstructions or clots.
Tell me what you
came here for, House.
I've got a legitimate
medical reason.
You must be so proud.
I've forgotten it.
I guess it's no big deal
since I was only using it
as an excuse to come check
out Patty and Selma.
I feel bad. I haven't
named your testicles.
Word on the street is you set a
new personal best for low-cut.
I don't know why you chose to give
them the names of somebody's aunts.
It's a compliment.
They're always smoking.
I remember. I need you to authorize
the medical discharge of a minor.
That's why I'm holding
this in my hand.
Haven't finished
testing yet, but it's...
Your outbox is three times normal size.
That's not a metaphor.
There's a lot to be done
before the weekend.
You could take papers home with you.
Unless you're not gonna be home.
Unless you were, for example,
going to a medical conference.
I'm driving up with Wilson.
Me, too.
You aren't on the
registration list.
I love that you checked.
But Wilson said...
That I have a case? Yeah.
You're authorizing the discharge right now.
That was a metaphor.
I'm busy right now.
Is he dying? Yeah.
In the next 10 minutes?
Unfortunately, no.
He's in a lot of pain.
I thought about it. You're right,
I should go to the conference.
You found out Cuddy's going.
Oh, God, no.
She'll ruin everything.
We leave in two hours.
Please, morphine.
I'm right here.
I'm right here, Joseph.
Two days away. You think
I should pack Bally?
You can't leave. You lit a fuse,
you need to watch the bomb go off.
The bomb was gonna go off on
its own if you kept quiet.
So now you either have to
come up with a convincing lie
or tell her the truth.
Your choice.
CK levels point to rhabdo.
Of course.
Except for the part where imaging
shows no sign of muscle crush.
Hi. I'm your doctor,
and this is Lars Ulrich, greatest
metal drummer of all time.
You know the song?
Good. Drumstick.
Here's another drumstick.
I want you to rock out to the
music, the way you did last night.
Come on. This is a
classic medical test.
Hippocrates used it. Let's go.
Come on, you gotta keep time.
Crossover on the high-hat.
Let's head-bang.
House, what are you doing?
Chart said her potassium's low.
Rhabdo elevates potassium.
And the monkey drums.
Ergo, her levels must have
been really low last night.
Which causes...
I can't move them.
Temporary muscle paralysis.
Given this rate of muscle fatigue,
there's no way she could have climbed
stairs and then a fence to the pool.
Low potassium means no
jump, means no trauma.
Tests mean, yes, rhabdo.
Ergo, something else caused both
the rhabdo and the low potassium.
This time, start by getting
an accurate history.
Be careful, our patient's
a big, fat liar.
What did you
really do last night?
We need to find the cause
of your low potassium.
You could have a kidney
disorder, leukemia, adenoma.
We need to know about
any drugs or alcohol,
anything that might have
threatened your health.
Come on, Jord.
Okay, we didn't spend the
night with the band.
You can't tell our friends.
Have you heard of
Warrior Queen of Space?
It's a comic book, right?
Thank you, yes... Yeah.
And a freaking amazing
new sci-fi series,
and they're filming
the motion picture now.
It's a prequel.
The other girls
wouldn't get it.
Only Phoebe understands
my passion.
"the bushido of the heel."
So what actually
happened last night?
We were with our friends,
trying to get into the Pharmacide
tour party at the Adams.
And then I found out that Jeffrey
Keener was gonna be there.
I follow his tweets.
It's tragic that
I have to explain this.
He's the creator of Stiletto issue
number one and the TV show.
He's a god.
So did you guys go up to him?
God, no.
We keep a 10-foot rule.
It's not stalking if you don't go
up to the person and bother them.
So we just followed him around.
Discreetly.
He ditched after half an hour and went down
to the hotel restaurant for a late dinner.
And you went with him?
Discreetly.
We played it so cool.
For two hours,
we lived his life.
We did everything he did, ate
the exact same meal he ate.
Cool.
The rest of
their story checks out.
Hotel manager says Mom and Dad
were charged for food and a room,
three pay-per-view
episodes of Stiletto...
You trying to kill yourself? It's
from the same batch the girls ate.
They ate what he ate, and what
100 other healthy people ate.
Dig in, lunch is on the Adams.
What if food is the answer?
Not this food, any food. Jordan
says she ate all of this.
She's 16, all about body image,
and she obviously
worries about fitting in.
Bulimia would account
for her symptoms.
We should do a barium swallow
for Mallory-Weiss tears,
start her on nutritional
supplements, get a psych consult.
Why are you reading
my program guide?
It's not like you plan on attending
any of the presentations.
I like to know how much
boredom I'm missing.
"Patient perceptions of complications
in end-stage chemotherapy."
You didn't tell me
you were giving a paper.
And that was wrong?
The last time you
presented a paper,
you gave me an advance copy
and asked for feedback.
And you're wondering why I wouldn't
want to repeat that experience?
Oh, look, an '80s party.
Just when you think you've left Flock of
Seagulls behind in your rear-view mirror,
suddenly it's up ahead
like an undead hitchhiker.
Cuddy's going.
Did you pack my legwarmers?
If you want her, ask her out.
My God, man.
She's not some floozy in a bar,
she's the floozy I work for.
There's gotta be no radical
steps here, gotta be subtle.
We happen to attend
the same party,
the chat happens
to turn personal.
Like the frog in
gradually boiling water.
Exactly.
She'll be red and delicious
before she knows it.
That's fun.
What could possibly go wrong?
Chase went to the gym
five times this week.
Okay.
One of those times,
I followed him.
What?
I followed him. And, yes, I know
how humiliating that admission is.
Where'd he go?
The gym. That time.
But I know that something's...
I'm stopping you right there.
This is a conversation you should
be having with Chase, not me.
I've tried having this
conversation with Chase.
No sign of tears.
It's not bulimia.
Is he having an affair?
No.
Why should I believe you?
You shouldn't.
You should believe him.
Baby, how are you? Sweetie.
Jordan.
Normal sinus rhythm.
Heart rate's fine.
BP's dropping. What's
happening to her?
No pulse.
Oh, my God. You said her
heart rate was fine.
Cardiac tamponade,
drain the fluid now.
What is going on?
She's bleeding
around her heart.
Blood constricted
her heart muscle.
She's on antiarrhythmics, but we don't
know how long we can keep her stable.
Seemed to be triggered by stress.
Her parents had just...
Did her blood pressure drop
during the barium swallow?
Dropped to 50 systolic
in three minutes.
Rules out chronic conditions.
Acute conditions limit us
to toxins, infections...
Could be anything. A gas leak, arsenic in
the wallpaper, fungus in the shower...
I'll get samples from her
room and the restaurant.
Talk to our little Gossip Girl.
You need to know
exactly where she's been
and what she's done
in the last 24 hours.
Oh, I think...
Welcome to the convention,
Dr. Perlmutter.
It's my 25th consecutive year.
Perlmutter loves the '80s.
Do you need me to leave, too?
You might remember
stuff she doesn't.
We didn't do anything
we haven't told you about.
We hung out at Jordan's all day, and then
we called a limo to go into the city.
We stopped at Bruce
Springsteen's house.
Jord, don't joke around, okay?
You're really sick.
Just tell him the truth.
Bruce let me play the first
electric guitar he ever owned.
My God, why are you lying?
How can you not believe me?
Turn to your right.
Mr. Keener, I really
appreciate you coming.
Oh, it's not that much of a hike.
My room's only six floors up.
Last night, do you remember
two girls, about 16?
That table right there.
They made an impression.
They were hard to miss, with
the giggling and the staring.
I'm sure that happens
to you a lot.
to you a lot more.
She can't control it.
A bleed in her brain is affecting
her thalamus, causing her to lie.
We need to know everything.
You two were never apart?
Except for when
she went to go get ice.
But that couldn't
have taken very long.
You don't know?
It was in the
middle of the night.
I woke up when she came
back into the room.
And she told you
she went to get ice?
House.
1980s.
Are you sure?
They weren't specific.
How much did it
cost you to rent that?
It was in Wilson's bag.
Dr. Perlmutter. I read your
article on neural degeneration.
You didn't really take
that seriously, did you?
I just wrote that
for the money.
Well, hey, there, Jane Fonda,
would you care to dancercise?
Sorry, we were just
about to hit the floor.
Thank you.
Your leg?
I'm okay, as long as you
don't expect rhythm.
You remember the
last time we danced?
Med school. The week we met.
No.
I saw you in Endocrinology,
tracked you down to the hoe-down.
I meant we met before that.
In the bookstore.
Ah.
My third day of school.
I hand my syllabus to the
guy behind the counter.
He barely looks at me,
just skims the sheet
and tells me
I'm overly ambitious,
I have a chip on my shoulder
and I know how to party.
I'd forgotten you
knew how to party.
I said, "You're
making that up."
Then you said, "Your class
schedule is overloaded",
"but none of your classes
are before 11:00,"
"and no one takes Professor Lamb's course
unless they have something to prove."
Because Professor Siegal covered the
same ground and was the easier grader.
I tracked you down.
Endocrinology, the party.
And one thing led to another.
And then it didn't.
I was gonna call you.
No, don't do that.
There was no expectations.
I was just as into it...
I was gonna come see you.
Figure out where things
would go from there.
That was the morning I got
the call from the dean,
and I was expelled from
my first med school.
There didn't seem any point.
I should go to my room and review papers
for the infectious disease panel.
Hello.
Yeah. Thanks for telling me.
It's 7:00 in the morning.
Somebody better be dead.
My patient. Joseph Schultz.
Oh.
Under the circumstances, it was the best
thing that could have happened, right?
Yeah. I just wish
I'd been there.
Didn't hear you
come in last night.
Yes, it was almost 9:30.
Things didn't go
as you planned?
We've moved on to a new phase.
I tell Cuddy that I've
always been interested
in her, and she walks
out of the room.
Well, either she
just wasn't ready for that,
or maybe she was just surprised
and didn't know how to react.
What are you doing?
Interesting reflex
of guilt just now.
Your patient's been
dying for six weeks,
you couldn't have predicted
that he'd go this weekend.
Or could you?
"Euthanasia. Let's tell the truth.
We all do it."
It's a great opening line.
Are you insane?
I didn't want
your notes before,
and I don't want them now.
Well, she didn't get ice.
She got out in the lobby.
She could've gone anywhere.
Let's start with for
how long. Fast forward.
Stop. Rewind. Back.
Wherever she went, she was only
gone for like five minutes.
She's holding something.
That's Keener's journal.
He must have left it in the
restaurant that night.
She went back, claimed
it belonged to her.
She was looking for an
excuse to knock on his door.
I know what you're gonna say.
I'm not insane.
Doctors are rarely indicted.
I was just thinking
of your career.
But, yeah, if you're one of the
doctors occasionally indicted,
I guess it could affect that.
Someone needs to say what life is really
like, now, for people who are dying.
What doctors
have to go through.
The decisions we have to make.
Alone. Without guidance.
Someone should say that, in an
unsigned letter to the Times.
I'd be telling the truth. I'd be
saying what we're all thinking.
Who cares?
The oncology department is
subsidized by drug companies,
they don't want it
run by a murderer.
We're all murderers. We just
don't have the guts to admit...
And once again, who cares?
You won't be hirable. Anywhere.
If there's one thing
I've learned from you,
it's that I should do
what I think is right,
and not worry about
the consequences.
Yeah, it's worked
out great for me.
I don't mean to be rude,
but I'm expecting a notes call from LA.
Can we make this quick?
Did Jordan come to your
room the other night?
Let me put it another way. We know Jordan
came to your room the other night.
Look, I've tried to be helpful.
I don't know why you want to
pretend I'm lying to you,
but this is getting
too weird for me.
We need to search your room.
You don't, because
she was never here.
Allison, calm down.
You would cover your ass at the
expense of someone's life?
We know she brought
up your journal.
That was helpful.
He'd be crazy to risk his marriage for
a one-night stand. With a teenager.
Sensible people only risk their
marriage for something more serious?
I'm not having an affair.
We're talking about Keener.
Fine.
He doesn't care about his
marriage, what about his career?
Statutory rape would ruin it.
It's admitting statutory
rape that could ruin it.
Which is why we'll never
hear the truth out of him.
Roofies OD explains
all her symptoms.
We should start treating
her with flumazenil.
Isn't the MRSA panel going on?
We got kicked out.
She started crying.
Yeah, well, discussions of urinary
catheterization will do that to me, too.
The babysitter
had an emergency.
Oh, how did you
like '80s Night?
House talked with you?
I was being subtle about it.
You left suddenly.
I know House can be
a little much sometimes.
He was sweet. I just know
better than to rely on that.
He's trying.
Yeah. I know.
I'm a mother now. I need a guy I
can count on every single day.
That's never been House.
It's not roofies. She's
bleeding behind her kidneys.
We're transfusing another
two units packed red cells,
but she keeps springing leaks.
It looks like a toxic reaction.
Keener must have
given her something.
The guy's a comic book
writer, not a drug dealer.
There's a lot that wouldn't show
up on a standard tox screen.
But he's never gonna
tell us the truth.
We're not going to get the
truth out of her either.
We will if we drug her.
Amobarbital would
suppress her thalamus.
She's on antiarrhythmics.
Amobarbital could stop her heart.
She's already dying.
You're angry at me.
You're taking it out on this guy 'cause
you think he's lying to you, too,
and you're going to kill our
patient in the process.
We need to know the truth.
We should call House.
Yeah, he'll recommend
we take the cautious approach.
Pretzel?
Those are gonna show up on my
credit card at seven bucks a bag.
There's an all-you-can-
eat buffet downstairs.
Studies show that $10 wine tastes better
if you're told that it costs $90.
I'm sure the same thing
must be true of grape soda.
Have one.
We can toast your
impending unemployment.
Yes, you can sit here
running up my hotel bill,
or you can go get the
woman of your dreams.
I didn't know Angela Merkel
was attending the conference.
I just spoke with Cuddy. She
doesn't think you're reliable.
And you will remain friend-zoned
until that changes.
I can't convince her that I've changed
my entire personality in a weekend.
Yeah, but you could
make the first step.
What does she need?
Today, a babysitter.
What are you thinking about?
Fjords.
You see? Seriously, I know this
is out of your comfort zone,
but don't scheme, don't...
Just do the deed...
You tell me that I gotta
show her I've changed,
and yet you act like
you don't believe I can.
If I can't convince
my best friend...
I'm sorry, and that's... I didn't mean...
I didn't mean...
You drugged me.
She's better off without you.
Words can hurt, you know.
I thought truth serum was only stuff
they gave people in lame spy movies.
We know you're scared, and we
know you want to tell the truth.
We're going to
help you do that.
What happened between you and Keener
the night you went up to his room?
I couldn't believe
he even talked to me.
I told him how much
his work means to me.
I figured I must sound like a
moron, but he was nice about it.
He said I was special.
Heart rate's increasing.
140's acceptable. Let her talk.
Did he give you
anything, a drink, pills?
He said it was Ecstasy.
But it didn't
look like Ecstasy.
And it didn't really make me
feel how Ecstasy usually does.
How did it make you feel?
It just made me really tired.
What did it look like?
A capsule? Tablet?
It was a tablet. Round.
Could be lithium.
He just started touching me.
At first, it seemed
nice, but then...
I didn't want to insult him.
That's enough.
I'm so sorry.
I love you guys
so much and I just...
I feel like I've let you down.
I'm gonna kill him. I'm gonna
kill that son of a bitch.
Before you do that, look here.
Increased periorbital
blood flow throughout.
It means everything she's
been saying has been a lie.
Everything?
So you still don't know
what's wrong with her?
Sorry.
I thought you
were room service.
Is something going on
with your patient?
It's quiet in there.
Is Rachel asleep?
I thought maybe you
could use a babysitter.
Actually, I've got her
in daycare downstairs.
Oh.
Great. Maybe later.
Hey, House.
Hey, Lucas.
This is awkward.
A bit.
That awkwardness would
probably go away if I left.
Hello? It's Foreman.
I'm trying to update House,
but his phone's off.
House!
He's not here.
Patient's losing blood faster
than we can transfuse.
Cameron did an online search, found
out Keener travels with his dog.
We're treating for Rickettsia.
Any idea where he is?
Oh, no! I was supposed to be
giving a paper five minutes ago.
Okay. Okay.
Dr. Wilson has asked me to tender
his apologies for his absence.
You'll be hearing
my paper instead.
Unfortunately, there wasn't time
to correct the program schedule.
Euthanasia.
Let's tell the truth.
We all do it. We just
don't talk about it.
We play the game. We use other words,
or we don't use any words at all.
Hmm.
Nice phrasing.
Hello.
I don't know what department I want.
I need
pants.
Patient S, 55-year-old man
end-stage lung cancer.
His pain was beyond the point where
we could even pretend to treat it.
I showed him how to use
the morphine pump.
I told him too much
morphine would kill him,
but not to worry, the machine
only gives out so much.
To override it, you need
to enter a special code.
I went to the door
and told the nurse,
"The code is 328."
I said it loudly.
When he first
came to my office,
I'd told him I would be with
him every step of the way.
But I left him
alone at the end.
I broke that promise.
To cover my ass, I failed...
I was wrong when I wrote that.
I've never given
any less than my best.
I'm incapable of turning
away from a responsibility.
My friends take advantage
of that fact far too often.
I know that I gave that
man everything I could.
And I know that
he knew that, too.
This is a burden no one
should have to carry alone.
And this is a decision
no one should make alone.
Because, frankly,
I don't trust all of you.
Doctor! Doctor!
Doctor! Question!
Excuse me, Doctor. Not many
people would have your courage.
Thank you, Dr. Perlmutter.
Hey!
Before I start shouting, Foreman
says they're looking at Rickettsia.
Thanks for the
message. Continue.
What the hell?
You think that little shout
out is gonna make me forget
that you drugged me, hid
my pants, stole my speech?
You wanted the paper out there.
It's out there.
And your job is safe.
That was my paper.
You don't ask what I want, you
ignore my wishes, you drug me...
I'm waiting for you to name
something new to our relationship.
You got no good reason
to be angry with me.
Oh, really? I should
be thanking you?
If this was about getting the
story out there, then, yeah.
Of course, if this is actually
about something else,
maybe you feeling impotent
because patients keep dying,
and you think you need to make some
grand, stupid gesture, need to be a hero,
well, then, yeah, sorry,
I did screw it up.
You stepped over the line.
This was not your decision.
My God, there are 10,000
oncologists in this country,
every one of them
loses patients,
but only you would
feel guilty enough...
Of course. We can't even
argue on my schedule.
It's House.
Take down the bags.
It's too soon to tell
if the meds are gonna...
It's not the meds.
It's the blood
that's killing her.
What's everybody doing?
You're stunned, right?
I mean, blood?
She's had internal bleeding,
she needs the blood to...
Is that the mom? I got a good
comeback if it's the mom.
Yes, I'm her mother.
Sure, she needs blood,
if you want to kill her.
Then you'd have nobody left to neglect.
Great plan.
Your daughter has
Vibrio vulnificus,
courtesy of a few scrumptious
oysters on the half shell.
I didn't eat any oysters.
Thus proving that she did.
Boy, that's neat.
A hundred other people
ate those oysters. I ate...
Is that the dad?
I got a good comeback if...
It's Chase.
Oh. Thought the dad might
have been Australian, too.
There was nothing wrong with the oysters.
All oysters have Vibrio.
But almost no one
has hemochromatosis.
It'd give her a unique susceptibility
to Vibrio, cause the swollen joints.
It got attributed to bulimia,
so she got supplements.
With iron.
Which overcooked the liver,
which caused bleeding.
More blood, more iron,
more bleeding, more blood.
Is she going to be okay?
Only if we give her high-dose
ceftazidime for the Vibrio
and chelate for
the hemochromatosis.
Now, Cameron, pick up the phone
and give me a dramatic exit.
So, how did you
two crazy kids hook up?
I suspected someone in
accounting was skimming money,
and I wanted to
investigate quietly.
And since you introduced me to
the only detective I know...
One thing leads to another.
Why keep it a secret? Were you
protecting me in my fragile state?
You think I was
an unhinged loony
who was about to go off the rails
at a badly-timed bit of news?
I just don't advertise
my personal life.
I needed help with the
baby, Lucas drove up.
Yeah, she was worried.
A little worried. As a friend.
I had to hide in our room and be the
dirty little secret. Kind of sucked.
I told her it wasn't necessary.
So you had some hallucination
about having sex with her.
I don't think
we need to talk...
I mean, I imagine having sex with
women all the time. No big deal.
Though I guess if they knew what I
imagined, it could get awkward.
And I guess it's different because
in the fantasy, she was your savior.
But I mean, that was
months ago, right?
All the work that you had
to do to get straight.
You've been institutionalized, you've
had way bigger stuff to deal with.
I should shut up.
Can I buy you a ginger ale?
Ginger ale would
be good. With lemon.
Infection's clearing up nicely.
You should be out of
here in a few days.
That is wonderful.
Jack, how are you?
Sweetie,
your father and I think we should reward
ourselves with a little time off.
That meeting's gonna have
to wait a couple of weeks.
We're staying here.
You should think about
where you'd like to go.
Honey, they're saying the specs
are off for the whole foundation.
Can you at least
come talk to him?
Let me see.
You okay? Yeah.
No. Soil engineering
report was fine.
I'm used to it.
So, about what
happened that night...
I never even got up the
courage to knock on his door.
Well, you'll have to
send me their numbers.
Yay!
You want to go driving?
He looks like a guy
who'd be there every day.
Mini-bar's re-stocked. I say we
grab some pretzels for the road...
When you do what I did,
it's not enough to tell
yourself you did nothing wrong.
You need to hear it
from someone else.
If not God or society, a friend,
otherwise you go crazy.
What you said to me up there...
Thank you.
You're a good friend.
Cuddy should know that.
Yeah, you should let her
know that I drugged you
so you wouldn't confess to murder.
Let's get out of here.
Someone could have
recognized you.
First US conference
I've attended in 15 years.
Perlmutter?
Toronto, all weekend,
airtight alibi.
I'm sorry.
I don't know why I always
suspect the worst.
If you say you're
not having an affair,
you're not having an affair.
Oh, God. You are? I'm not.
Okay. Sorry. Again.
If you don't wanna tell,
okay.
But I could help.
Whatever this is,
it's eating away at you.
We could get past it together.
I love you no matter what.
We lose patients sometimes.
One of those patients,
Dibala,
we didn't actually lose him.
I killed him.