Previously on Dexter...
Judging from the spray, we're looking
at somebody tall. Over six feet.
He moved the arm.
For a reason.
The killer leaves the ash as his signature,
making his vics point at it.
Lundy came to Miami to hunt this guy.
I think he got too close
and I think it got him killed and me shot.
It's been my dad's baby for years.
A few days ago, he hands me the keys.
No, no. Smooth circular motions, son.
- I got it, Dad.
- If you got it, I wouldn't have to remind you.
Small cracks in the perfect family.
I can lose my job.
Not like I'm the only one.
Being a journalist these days is like
a straight ticket to the unemployment line.
Either I get a lead that bleeds
or basically... I'm done.
Are the sweeps connected
to the shootings of Agent Lundy?
I know it's really tough for reporters
right now.
So maybe instead of this one,
I can give you that interview
you've been wanting from me.
Mother shit fuck.
How tall was my shooter?
My height.
- Then it wasn't Trinity?
- Nope.
I was a "dress over the head" party girl.
- You must think I'm...
- Totally charming.
We broke up. Officially.
If I find out this is bullshit, there will
be severe, career-ending consequences.
Fuck it.
No more confessions,
no more good deeds,
and no more fucking remorse.
No, you're mine.
Arthur Mitchell, you just got a reprieve.
This'll do the job.
Cut you into exactly the right size pieces.
You got one more day.
Happy families are all alike.
They never leave you by yourself
on holidays.
I got some interesting Thanksgiving
greetings from your Coach Davis.
If you're not gonna play baseball anymore,
I suppose you aren't gonna need this.
- No, D-Dad...
- All right?
How about this?
Oh, you're full of awards.
Once the turkey's gone...
so is Arthur.
How about this one?
This one's for Most Valuable Player.
Fuck you, Dad.
Family business.
It's my business too.
OK. Healthy way to blow off steam.
What the hell?
Jonah? Hey, it's just me.
- Mr. Butler, what are you doing here?
- I stopped by your house.
I saw you arguing with your father.
No, I don't argue.
- I never argue.
- Still, it looked like a bad one.
Man, you have no idea what he's like.
How he treats my mother and Rebecca.
You don't know what he's capable of.
- Well, actually...
- He hits me.
That's not right.
You know, I'm running out of clichés
to tell the coaches.
You know, "Hey, I fell down some stairs.
I walked into a door."
I know it looks like we have
the perfect fucking family,
but in that house...
when he's there,
it's not a life; it's a tour of duty.
Shit. I...
- He'd kill me if he knew I was telling you.
- I won't say a word.
You should have just let him die.
- Where you going?
- Anywhere away from here.
I can't go back.
Not to him.
Not with the car like this.
So I'll go with you.
I'll be there when you tell him.
- Why?
- You're not the only one with father issues.
Well, you know, maybe...
I mean, I guess if you came
to Thanksgiving tomorrow,
- Dad would be on his best.
- Thanksgiving?
Dinner's at one.
I can stay at Luke's house until then.
Guess I'm having two turkey dinners
this year.
The DNA sweep didn't
give them Trinity.
But it did bring in
a cornucopia of criminals.
That should keep Miami Metro
off the Trinity case through the holiday.
Deb won't be anywhere near as easy.
Sorry, Dex, but I'm spending Thanksgiving
with 90 or so of my newest friends.
Look at these victims.
It looks like a family portrait.
The bathtub women, they're always
young and single. A first girlfriend maybe.
The jumper's always a mother of two.
Maybe that represents his mom or his wife.
But I don't think this guy's married.
The bludgeonee's always a father...
You used to love Thanksgiving
when we were kids.
You wore the little Indian headdresses.
Picked the pearl onions
out of the green beans.
Yeah.
Mom's green beans.
And then she died.
And it was you and me
and Dad and football
and TV dinners in aluminum trays.
- Talk about your lonely.
- Well, you won't be lonely at our house.
You'll never get the chance.
Dexter...
I am lead detective
on the biggest case of my career.
- This is where I belong.
- I thought Batista was lead.
He's the lead on Lundy now.
Once we figured out Trinity didn't shoot me,
- there was no conflict for me...
- What? Wait.
Trinity didn't shoot you?
While you were at
your Rain Man convention,
Masuka and I put it together
form the bullet's trajectory.
- How did I not see that?
- We were too close.
That's what happens
when you make it personal.
So I've heard.
So... who shot you?
Maybe Trinity knows.
I'll ask him when I haul his ass in here.
Deb, you really, really need
to come to Thanksgiving.
Tell the family I said "hi".
Heads up, everybody.
This DNA sweep has been like Christmas.
We got hits on three open rape cases
and one open burglary case,
but best of all,
hits on two homicides.
Merry Thanksgiving, Soderquist.
This one is mine.
Keep up the good work, guys.
- Sarge... any news on any other cases?
- We'll find the fucker who shot you.
You know that.
Focus on what you can control.
- Catching Trinity.
I heard the ACLU's
filing suit on the sweeps.
We've got maybe 72 hours
till we're shut down for good.
- We'll just have to keep pushing harder.
- The holidays may slow us down.
- We'll have a skeleton crew.
- I'll be here.
Never been much
for family holidays anyway.
Particularly when they're all still in Cuba.
Particularly.
Are you with Auri tomorrow?
- She's with her moms this year.
- Hmm.
Plus I have a chance to close
an old case of mine, so...
So I guess we'll both
be working Thanksgiving.
Together.
How unfortunate.
- Put it up higher, Mom.
- No, I want it lower.
Are happy families all alike?
Much better.
- Dexter's home!
- Oh, good. They didn't run out of pies.
Here you go.
OK, bird, confess.
- How big are you?
- 22 pounds.
- That's a lot of bird.
- Better too much than not enough.
I mean, that's what the holiday's about.
That and family.
- About tomorrow...
- Uh-oh.
It's not a big deal,
but the Monroe County PD
needs a spatter interpretation on a bar fight
and their blood guy's in the Bahamas.
Should just take a few hours.
- Does it have to be tomorrow?
- That's when the reconstruction is.
- Mm.
- Plus I'll be making triple overtime.
Sure, that's a plus...
but you'll be missing all the fun.
Yeah.
Poor you. Poor us.
- At least Elliot will be here.
- Yeah, good old Elliot.
So is Deb coming?
She's on the fence.
No, tell her that this is
our first family Thanksgiving
and that we're establishing traditions
that will shape our kids
and that they'll pass on to their kids
and that she's a part of that.
An important part of that.
Rather than me tell her all that...
OK, guys, now look real sad,
I mean, really miserable.
And... action.
Hi, Aunt Deb. We just heard that you
might not come to Thanksgiving dinner,
- and, well...
- We really want you to come.
- Look sad, retard.
- All right, all right. Just...
Take two.
Will you please come over?
Fuck me.
You're here late.
Ah, didn't even notice.
- Big plans tomorrow?
- You're looking at them.
Whatever about tomorrow, right?
It's just another day
where people eat turkey.
I can eat turkey any day of the year.
Dexter's having people over.
Well, me.
He invited me over.
Have a good time.
You know...
- I could use a wingman...
- Yes.
I can't promise it'll be any fun.
Well, I could be your thigh man.
Don't press your luck.
I'll let Rita know.
What time do you want
to eat tomorrow?
Oh, bad news, babe. I got to work.
Oh.
Well, what time do you get off?
Uh...
You do want to spend
the holiday together, don't you?
- It's a holiday.
- Exactly.
Spending it together makes things all...
serious.
Oh, it's just a casual Thanksgiving
with your girlfriend.
Girlfriend?
That sounds... really serious.
Joey...
I don't want to spend it alone.
Plus, uh...
I make the best pecan pie
in the state of Florida.
I guess I could, you know...
come by for dessert.
Oh, so you just want to eat my pie.
Is that it?
- Happy Thanksgiving, Mr. Mitchell.
- Happy Thanksgiving!
I'll be at Arthur's by one, home by four.
A serial killer's Thanksgiving recipe
for success.
- How can none of these be big enough?
- Well, maybe if we, um...
Turn the bird on its side...
Hey, Dex.
Howdy, pilgrim.
Did you hear that the pilgrims
didn't eat turkey on the first Thanksgiving?
- Really?
- They ate corn and eel,
which the Native Americans
taught them to plant and fish.
Then the pilgrims slaughtered them all,
took their food,
and went to church the next day
to thank God for all their good luck.
Mm, it's a phase.
Don't worry about it.
What you said about traditions
shaping our kids...
My not going to work, will that...
misshape them?
Look, I wish it was otherwise,
but you'll be home soon, right?
Right. I just...
I don't want to do any damage.
You're a parent.
Parents do damage.
Hopefully we'll do enough
of the good stuff to balance it out.
Hopefully.
Thanks.
- "Ashes to ashes..."
- Doughnut to doughnut.
- It's all the store had left.
- What are you doing here?
Avoiding Christine.
She can be a little intense.
Tell me about it. She keeps calling
to set that interview with me.
- You said you'd do it.
- Little busy here.
Look at the timing of the Trinity kills.
15 in December,
40 in July and August...
20 or so in the spring.
What's the pattern?
Long-haul truck driver?
Migrant worker?
Some kind of salesman.
Yeah.
Gobble, gobble.
- She's nothing if not persistent.
- Hey, babe. What are you doing here?
I thought I'd bring Thanksgiving to you.
How sweet.
- There's enough for both of you.
- Oh, thanks, but I'm heading out.
- Debra's taking the day off.
- Fuck that. I'll be multitasking.
- Well, I guess you can take the day off too.
- Sure he can.
Yeah, let me just... check with the boss.
We'll go eat.
So, Debra... how are you feeling?
Do you mind if we put off that interview
until after the holiday?
I'm not here as a reporter;
I'm here as Joey's... girlfriend.
My condolences.
You know, he really cares about you.
After you got shot,
you were all he could talk about.
- Really messed him up.
- Well, that makes two of us.
I just... I just wanted to say...
Um...
I'm really sorry...
about what happened to you.
I can't even imagine...
looking into the eyes
of the person you love...
watching as he takes his last breath.
Let's hope you never have to.
You got Lloyd Paulson to confess?
Been waiting ten years to close this one.
I promised the victim's husband
I'd find the man who killed his wife.
Finally lived up to that promise.
You should go tell the husband.
Give him something to be thankful for.
As soon as I process that pendejo.
Do you want to come with?
To a next-of-kin notification?
It is official business.
- Kyle!
- Happy Thanksgiving.
To you too.
Kyle. What a nice surprise.
Apparently Jonah
didn't mention inviting me.
I just wanted to drop by and say hi.
It's my first Thanksgiving
without my family and I...
didn't know what to do with myself.
I suppose you should eat with us.
Full tables, full hearts.
Full bellies. Come on in.
- Aunt Deb's here!
- Happy Thanksgiving, turkeys.
Thanks for the video.
- Hi, Deb.
Hi.
- Who's that?
- Danny and Grace's dad.
Danny, let me help.
Ah. Where's Dexter?
He's at some crime thing
in Monroe County.
- Said he'd be back for dinner.
- He's more like Dad every day.
Come look at our puzzle.
We've already got the corners.
Cody, leave her alone.
- You don't want to help?
- Sorry, little man, but I've got work to do.
Oh.
You are good.
Another three hours to go.
When do you want to put in
the broccoli-cheese casserole?
About an hour before.
The sweet potatoes need an hour and
the corn pudding needs about 30 minutes.
Is it all gonna fit?
No. None of it's gonna fit.
What was I thinking?
You were thinking, "My fabulous neighbor
has not one, but two ovens."
You know, you really are a lifesaver.
You should just wear a red cross
on your forehead.
Oven crisis.
Deb, can you watch the kids?
Harrison's asleep.
Actually, I was gonna try to get some...
Oh!
...work done.
Vince, hi!
Vince, Elliot. Elliot, Vince.
Hi. Uh, bye.
- Uh... bye.
- Bye.
- They're using his oven.
- Oh.
Well... guess I'll be using his oven too.
Chocolate lava cakes.
My specialty.
You have a specialty?
A river of chocolate love
that melts in your mouth.
Wow. You can make
anything sound perverted.
It's a gift.
Arthur seems to be in a decent mood.
Maybe I'll be able to slip out early.
It's almost one.
You want me to set the table?
No, we've got to watch the game first.
- The game?
- Yeah, it's tradition, Kyle.
Ah! Will the kids be joining us?
That too would be tradition,
but apparently Jonah has forgotten.
I'm sure he's on his way.
He knows how important
holidays are to you.
Not such a decent mood after all.
Do you think Rebecca could come out now?
I suppose.
I'll go get her.
- She grounded or something?
- Oh, no.
No, nothing like that.
This is Carl Haas?
He's been in a persistent vegetative state
for several years.
Stepped off a sidewalk,
got hit by a bus.
I didn't know.
It's been a long time.
Would it be possible
to have a moment alone with him?
Have a good Turkey Day.
Tell him.
Like he can hear me.
He'll hear you.
Mr. Haas...
I'm the one who told you about your wife.
I also promised that I'd fi...
This is pointless.
Mr. Haas, Angel knows how much
your wife meant to you...
and he wants you to know...
I want you to know...
that we found the guy who killed her.
I wish...
I wish we would have found him sooner.
Really, I wish he would have
never killed your wife,
but I can't change that.
Can't change anything.
But we got the guy.
We got him.
- Hello, Mr. Butler. How are you?
- Well, I'm fine, Rebecca.
Kyle, you up for
a little pre-game football toss?
I suppose.
I'll go help Mom in the kitchen.
At least I have one perfect child.
Yeah, so it would appear.
Come on.
Normally, Jonah supplies the football.
- How about a baseball?
- No. We throw the baseball in spring.
Thanksgiving, we throw the football.
Traditions matter, Kyle.
Yes, they... shape people.
Yeah, and give children
a sense of history, tradition.
Teaches them who they are
and what's expected of them.
And what is expected of them?
Generosity, common sense, obedience.
It's a father's responsibility
to set the boundaries,
child's duty to honor them.
No, there's nothing down there.
Stop! Kyle, no!
I made that...
when I was still confused.
Well, it's beautiful.
Which is why I haven't torn it apart.
Probably donate it to the needy.
Obviously, I won't be needing it.
No, you'll be buried at sea.
I have a new lease on life.
Thanks to you.
Hey.
Oh. The best laid plans...
It's Jonah's.
What's the point of giving him the better
things in life if he can't take care of them?
What kind of father
keeps a coffin in his garage?
keeps blood slides in his shed?
Hey, we can still get some...
Here we go.
Dad, I don't know what happened. The car
was parked in Luke's driveway all night.
I came out this morning and, you know,
someone had just gone all mental on it.
Dad, I am so sorry.
That's why God
invented car insurance, right?
It'll be OK.
There!
Now it's drivable
till we can get her fixed.
Well...
Game's about to start.
Shall we?
Come on, Danny. Throw it here.
- Oh, good one.
- Hey, you two. No wiffle ball in the house.
I don't know how you do it.
All these kids at home at the same time.
Thanksgiving's only four days.
You should try keeping them entertained
for three months in the summer.
Yeah, plus spring break
and Christmas break.
That's when you're really climbing the walls.
June, July, August...
December.
Oh...
fu-u-udge!
Trinity's in the school system.
Quinn.
Joey, it's Deb.
His kill schedule matches the school year.
Trinity could be a janitor.
He could be a cafeteria worker,
a bus driver, a teacher, a principal.
- We got to get to the station.
- I haven't eaten yet.
Jesus, grab a drumstick to go.
Deb, no one's working today
and we're gonna need a warrant
to access any school databases.
We can find a judge.
Yeah, who's gonna love us
for tearing him away from his family.
Come on, we're not gonna
get anywhere today.
Fu...
Fudge.
- Break in a case?
- We'll see.
Not a horrible Thanksgiving, right?
No, actually it's kinda nice.
You sound surprised.
I am a little.
Hmm.
So having a girlfriend isn't so bad after all?
You with the labels.
Why does it matter?
I just...
I care about you.
I'd kinda like to have it returned.
Come here.
I have a better idea.
Aw!
You are so my girlfriend.
Get... get... get him!
Get him!
Get... get... get... get him!
Ah!
It's OK, they didn't get the first down.
Jonah seems safe for the moment.
I'm not a big football fan.
I think I'll go see if I can help Sally.
Oh, that's very nice of you.
Look at that.
There's three men on him.
Yeah, I know.
This room's kinda young for a teenager.
Are those to keep someone out...
or keep someone in?
My God.
He locks his daughter in here.
You need any help?
I'm completely useless in the kitchen.
Sure. Uh...
something for the centerpiece.
Roses.
Dad always likes these.
Everything for Dad, huh?
Those locks on your door for him too?
- He says they're there to protect me.
- And do they?
He's open. He's open! Go, go!
Touchdown! What a play!
No, no. No, Dad.
Ow!
And that's for my windshield.
Things of beauty need to be honored.
I ran away once.
He caught me and...
- it was bad.
- It's not always gonna be like this.
- Jonah told me that you're helping him.
- Yeah, if you can call it that.
You can help me too.
Get me out of here.
You just need to wait a while.
You're too young to be on your own.
I don't have to be on my own.
I could be with you.
- With me?
- Jonah also says you're nice.
I try to be.
If you're nice to me,
I can be nice to you.
I'll do anything you want.
Whoa... I don't...
Rebecca, you're 15.
I don't want anything from you.
I don't believe you.
- Look, I know what guys like.
- No.
Rebecca?
Go inside.
- Sally, it's not...
- Shh!
I am so sorry about Rebecca's behavior.
Oh.
Just... please...
don't say anything to Arthur.
Kyle, you can't.
- Whatever you did with Rebecca...
- I didn't.
Whatever you're going to do,
I don't care.
Just, please, I'm begging you...
don't tell him.
I wouldn't.
I wouldn't. I-I won't.
Please.
Yeah, I promise.
Thank you.
What the hell is he doing to these people?
- Rita, hi.
- Hey. How far away are you?
Uh... Probably about an hour or so.
All right, well, I don't want you
to be surprised when you get home.
- About what?
- Cody fell into your shed.
- What? Is he OK? What happened?
- Well, he's fine.
He hit a wiffle ball
onto the top of the shed,
climbed up to get it,
the skylight cracked...
and he fell through. Elliot was
gonna push in the air conditioner...
- No, don't!
- Uh, he didn't.
- He took off the door with an axe.
- So my shed has no door?
Dexter, Cody was scared and crying.
I told Elliot to get him out
however he could.
Yeah, of course, of course. I'll...
...thank Elliot when I get home.
Well, I'll see you soon, OK?
No one can get into
the trunk's false bottom.
You didn't think anyone
could get into your shed either.
I gotta get home. Now.
Arthur, I just got a call and I think I have to...
Jonah, what happened?
- I whacked it on the coffee table.
- My son, the klutz.
This team hasn't been the same
since they traded Johnson.
What else will he do to Jonah if I leave?
Turkey wraps, ICEEs...
And Cuervo Silver.
Only the best for you.
You know, I was thinking...
Carl Haas's wife gets mugged.
Boom. She's dead.
Carl gets hit by a bus.
Boom. He's a vegetable.
You never know when you
wake up in the morning
- what the day will bring...
- I love you.
I love you.
Are you saying that because
you're afraid you'll get hit by a bus?
No.
Well... yes, but...
I just want you to know what I know
before I don't know it anymore.
And I love you.
- I love you!
- Shh! I can hear you.
- I love Maria Esperanza del Alma La...
- Shh!
I'm not gonna say it.
You don't love me?
I'm afraid if I say it...
something will happen,
like you'll get hit by a bus.
So watch out for moving buses.
'Cause I love...
Angel Juan Marcos Batista.
- Oh! Ah! Rats! Ow!
- Uh-oh. Come here, come here.
- Ooh!
- There you go. Isn't Thanksgiving fun?
Thank God it's only once a year.
Do you have any ice?
No. Peas are better.
Come on, Rita. Give peas a chance.
- Now, come on. Take a seat.
- Oh.
All right. OK.
There.
Did you say "rats"?
I guess I've been spending
too much time with the kids.
Thanks for this.
I like taking care of you.
I am so sorry.
I don't know what I was thinking.
Yeah, I don't either.
It's just we have this connection,
and it's not just because we're both lonely...
No, I'm not lonely.
I have Dexter.
The guy who's never home?
- Thanksgiving Day parade...
- Hey, uh... Deb, I'm gonna take off.
- Not feeling so hot.
- Oh, no, you don't.
Here.
- You're my wingman.
- This family doesn't need me around.
- I'll see you at the...
- No, no, shh!
You belong here as much as anyone does.
And if you go,
I'll be the one single person here.
I really don't feel like remembering
why that is, you know?
Why Frank's gone.
- Why I'm here.
- Yeah.
Hey...
Yeah. I'll stay.
But I need booze.
You and me both.
Hi!
Are you the one
my mom told me not to talk to?
Awkward.
...and for this bounty before us,
we thank you and look to you, O Lord,
to strengthen our resolve
to strive, to seek, to find,
- and not to yield. Amen.
- Amen.
- Looks marvelous, Sally.
- Thank you, Arthur.
We, uh...
We have a little... family tradition, Kyle,
before we start...
of saying what we're thankful for.
I'll start.
I'm thankful for this family.
Pass your plates. Sally?
I'm... I'm thankful for this lovely home...
and for my son,
who I am so proud of.
- Me too.
- Is that all?
And for my beautiful daughter...
who is growing up... so quickly.
I am so blessed.
I'm thankful that Mrs. Wilder
gave us an extra two days
to finish our report on Aeschylus.
And I'm also thankful
for this nice home.
Is this what it takes to survive with him?
Um, I'm thankful for this house too...
...and for God.
You know what I'm thankful for?
My car.
- I'm thankful for yams.
- Yams?
Comfort food.
Thank you all for the comfort
of your home.
Where no one said
they were thankful for me.
Did you, Jonah?
Did you say you were
thankful for me, Jonah?
- What's that?
- I did not say I was thankful for you.
Because I'm not.
- I am so thankful for you, Arthur.
- Shut up, cunt.
- Whoa, Arthur...
- Kyle, perhaps it's time for you to go.
- I think I should stay.
- Yeah, sure. Stay. Watch the show.
- I'm thankful for you, Daddy.
- Go to your room, Vera.
No! She's not Vera!
And she's not your goddamn prisoner
and she's not eight anymore!
This whole life...
Your life is a lie!
These are lies!
Fucking community hero?
Jonah, this isn't the way.
I know who you really are!
- Oh, who am I?
- You're a killer.
Sucking the fucking life out of all of us!
Mom, Becca, me!
- Fucking little...
- No, Daddy! Don't! Daddy, no!
You're killing us!
- Put her down.
- Fuck you and fuck Vera.
Don't!
Fuck you!
Get the fuck off him!
- Oh, my God! No! No!
- No, Daddy! No!
No, you don't have to kill him!
No! Dad! Dad!
I should have fucking killed you
when I had the chance.
- Oh, my God! Arthur!
- Daddy!
Sally!
I'm thankful to be out of that fucking house!
You showed Trinity the monster in you.
He'll see you coming now.
I don't know.
Seeing them like that...
He's destroyed everyone in that family.
That's what happens to people
who live with a monster.
I am nothing like him!
My family is nothing like that.
What's 18 more years of being with you
gonna do to them?
Arthur's terrorized them
into maintaining his cover.
They're nothing but human shields.
The only reason you started dating Rita
was for cover.
She's much more than that now.
She and the kids. Much more.
My family is nothing like that.
- Hey.
- Dexter's home!
- Who's hungry?
- Me.
- I am.
I am so happy you're home!
- Oh! Me too.
- Mm! Mm!
All right, uh...
Cody, why don't you help
your Aunt Deb set the table?
Astor, I can use your help in the kitchen.
Sorry about your shed, Dexter.
Hey!
Well, as long as you're OK,
that's all that matters.
I'm gonna go check on the shed,
make sure it's safe in there.
Miss us?
You have no idea.
God, I miss my apartment.
They're safe.
So's my trunk.
Is anything really safe here?
The kids, Rita?
- You?
- I'll find an alternative.
Trinity was supposed to be
the alternative.
Uh, spoons go inside or outside the knives?
Um...
Surprise us.
- Ouch.
- Can I see your scars, Aunt Deb?
Sure.
Does it still hurt?
Um...
Sometimes.
Here.
Did you see that guy die?
I did.
- I looked right in his eyes.
- Were his eyes open?
Yeah.
Watched him take his last breath.
- How did she know that?
- How did who know what?
Nobody but me...
How much did you tell Christine
about the Lundy shooting?
- Nothing.
- Maybe you left Lundy's file
- lying around accidentally...
- No.
...and maybe Christine
saw some of the pictures.
She saw how he was lying on his side,
how he fell in front of me,
so that I could see him take his last...
Morgan, I'm telling you,
I learned my lesson.
I never even took the Lundy files
out of the station.
There's no way she could have seen it.
Dinner's ready.
Not all happy families are alike.
They are happy...
aren't they?
Are they normal kids?
How can you tell a loving wife
from a frightened one?
A friendly neighbor...
...co-worker...
...sister...
...son.
Are any of them what they seem?
Or are they little bombs
waiting to explode?
Happy Thanksgiving, son.
Dexter? Everything OK?
Yeah.
It is, isn't it?
Yes, everything is exactly
the way it should be.
Perfect.
Yeah, you're right.
Why don't we go around the table and
everybody say what they're thankful for?
No!
I don't want this yummy food to get cold.
I'm thankful for Dexter.
Let's eat.
- Sure you don't want to stay?
- I'm too tired to spend the night.
You made sure of that.
See you tomorrow?
And the day after that...
and after that.
- I'm here if you change your mind.
- Good night.
Good night.
Joey!
Hi, Dad.