[Boyd] Previously on From...
[screams]
[people scream]
[Marielle]
Nicky, stay with me, okay?
Sheriff Boyd,
I can't take back what I did.
- You killed someone!
- I...
And you left two people
to die in that ambulance!
- I know!
- One of whom
you handcuffed
to a fucking wall!
I am sorry.
[Henry]
Miranda started seeing things.
She said it was like
she'd been chosen
to free the children.
I guess you've
been chosen now, too.
Miranda...
she's the only one who had
a connection to this place
long before she arrived.
[Tabitha] What is this?
Did you see three red stones?
How did you...
When I was a little girl,
I would have the same
nightmare over and over again.
It wasn't just Miranda.
I saw this place, too.
[chittering]
[grunting]
[Randall] If you'd seen
the things I've seen...
What are you talking about?
What do you think
I'm talking about, Boyd?
When me, Julie and Marielle,
wherever we were...
Everybody here just talks about
how afraid they are of dying.
Well, I don't think
that's the worst thing
that can happen to you here.
I feel like something
is watching me.
Is that her?
She looks scary.
[gasps]
Help me, Elgin.
I can save all of you.
Donna, I was told
I can't have kids.
What's happening right now
is medically impossible.
You're gonna have a baby
that you were told
you could never have!
With all you've seen, you can't
wrap your head around a miracle?
[beeping]
I don't see anything.
[Fatima] That's impossible.
You barely looked!
Just keep looking!
You're not pregnant.
And how long have these
cravings been going on for?
Um, about a week maybe?
Guys, what is happening to me?
Um, well, I mean,
if we were anywhere else,
I'd say your body's
exhibiting signs
of a psychosomatic pregnancy.
And what is that?
It's a fairly rare condition
where your body
believes it's pregnant.
It shows all the early
signs and symptoms of...
"Hysterical pregnancy."
Isn't that what
they used to call it?
Hey, no one here thinks
you're being hysterical.
It wasn't so long ago
that Boyd had worms under his
skin that no one else could see.
We're not ruling
anything out here.
And, I mean, you very well
could have been pregnant...
I am pregnant.
It's still there! I can feel it.
Here.
Just take a sip of this.
- I don't fucking want that!
- [glass shatters]
[Kristi] Okay...
Sorry. I'm sorry.
[Kristi]
It's been a long day.
Your body's been
under a lot of stress.
[exhaling deeply]
How about you stay the night?
Ellis can stay, too, and...
- I wanna go home.
- [Kristi] Fatima...
I just wanna go back to my room.
It's raining outside, okay?
I don't want you walking...
You're worried about
the fucking rain?!
Okay.
- Hey.
- Fatima!
Hey, you go. You should go.
Fatima!
- [Fatima] I wanna go home!
- [door opens]
I'm gonna go stay
the night at Colony House.
At least I can
get an IV started.
- Yeah.
- [door closes]
You should've told me about all
of that before the ultrasound.
- It wasn't my place.
- Really, Boyd?
Now you wanna stand on ceremony?
That was information I could
have used before the exam.
I can't help,
if I'm in the dark!
You wanna yell at me?
Fine, but once you're done,
can we maybe figure out
what we're gonna do now?
I don't know
what we're gonna do.
I don't know what's wrong.
Either way, she...
she has something growing inside
of her that we can't see,
or this place has
finally gotten to her head
and made her believe
she's pregnant.
Okay. Then, how do we
figure out which one it is?
I don't know, Boyd.
Then how do we help her?
I have no fucking clue
how to help her.
Okay. Then, do your fucking job
and figure it out!
[heavy rainfall]
["Que Sera, Sera (Whatever Will
Be, Will Be)" plays]
♪ When I was just a little boy ♪
♪ I asked my father ♪
♪ "What will I be?" ♪
♪ "Will I be handsome?" ♪
♪ "Will I be rich?" ♪
♪ Here's what he said to me ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ Whatever will be will be ♪
♪ The future's not ours to see ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ What will be will be ♪
♪ Now I have
children of my own ♪
♪ They ask their father ♪
♪ "What will I be?" ♪
♪ "Will I be pretty?" ♪
♪ "Will I be rich?" ♪
♪ I tell them tenderly ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ Whatever will be will be ♪
♪ The future's not ours to see ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ What will be will be ♪
I'm not scared.
You need to talk.
You... talk!
I know you can talk!
You need to talk to me!
[knock on door]
[murmuring]
[Henry] Uh, Victor?
It's... it's me.
Can I come in?
Victor,
you can't keep doing this.
You were up all night.
You've been in here all morning.
I could hear you yelling
at that thing from downstairs.
Son...
Now, this isn't healthy.
He needs... he needs to talk,
and he needs to tell me...
- Hey...
- ...tell me what he said.
Yeah, but it's...
it's a doll.
Right? I mean you...
You don't understand.
You weren't there.
Look, Victor,
maybe just take a break...
- I can't do this here!
- No. Why don't...
- I can't do this.
- Victor!
Victor!
Hey. Whatcha workin' on?
Oh, it's just a little...
I'm making this for Fatima.
[gasps] Oh!
You know, I thought,
she's been pretty down lately,
and I thought maybe
this might cheer her up.
Well, that's just adorable.
I'm sure she'll love it.
I hope so.
Mm.
[camera shutter clicks, whirs]
[ominous music playing]
♪
You're lucky that
new ambulance came in.
All Kristi had before
was saline in glass bottles.
Yeah, so lucky. [sighs]
Hey.
I know last night was a lot.
- Do you?
- I do.
I also know what it's like to
feel violated by this place.
What happened to me
and Julie and Randall,
there are still times
I can feel those bugs
crawling around inside me.
And what do you do?
I remind myself it isn't real,
that it's just fear,
and fear can only
break me if I let it.
This is different.
You don't know that.
Yes, I do!
[sighs]
Maybe you could just try
eating regular food again,
just small bites.
I'm not eating garbage
because I'm afraid or...
or broken.
It's... it's happening
because it's... it's making me.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, I was just finishing up.
[exhales heavily]
I'll see you tomorrow, okay?
[door closes]
She just cares about you.
Why isn't anybody
listening to me?
It's happening inside of me.
I'm the one experiencing this!
Why is my fucking point of view
the only one everybody
assumes is wrong?
Nobody's assuming
that you're wrong. Okay?
We're... We're just trying
to see this
from every possible angle
we can.
And you? Do you think this
is all in my head?
[scoffs]
Look, ever since that night
at the Sheriff's Station,
when the bus pulled into town,
you... you broke down in my arms.
Do you remember that? You said
you couldn't take it anymore...
This has nothing
to do with that!
Okay, so then tell me
what am I supposed to do?
Believe me!
Look, look, okay.
Just... Ow!
Ugh!
Look!
Just...
I have been measuring every
single day since I found out.
- You just need to stop.
- And my stomach...
And my stomach
is getting bigger!
- Baby, it's not...
- Look! Look at it! Look!
If this is in my head,
how do you...
how do you explain
my body changing?
- I don't know.
- Ellis...
whatever is inside me,
it's getting stronger.
The... the fucking cravings,
they're getting stronger.
Please.
- I'm angry all the time.
- It's okay.
If there's nothing there,
if the baby isn't real,
that means that it's me.
[crying]
I told her it was a miracle.
Yeah, we all, uh...
[clears throat]
We all got a little excited.
[sighs]
You're sure there's no way
Kristi missed anything?
Donna, there was nothing there.
Nothing that showed up
on that machine anyway.
So, the way Kristi sees it,
either there's something there,
like the worms
that were under my skin,
or this place
finally got to her.
Like Abby.
Yeah, like Abby.
Look, if you're thinking about
things you could
have done different...
- No, it's not that.
- Well, it should be.
Look, if it's
some kind of fucked-up
worms-under-the-skin type thing,
then that's a bridge
we're gonna have to cross.
But if it's psychological,
if she's anywhere
near the place Abby was in,
then we need to figure out
a way to bring her back.
Okay, well, let's just...
make sure this stays between us.
And then what?
I'm gonna have a talk
with Kristi later.
Hopefully,
she'll have had time to, uh...
To what?
I don't know. Look.
Look, I...
I'm just telling you
'cause you and I promised not
to keep secrets from each other,
and she's
living under your roof.
Yeah, yeah.
About that...
While we're figuring it out,
I don't think it's a good idea
that they stay at Colony House.
What?!
Look, I am gonna
be there for them,
for you, every step of the way.
But the truth is, there are
two possibilities here,
and each one poses
a different kind of threat
to the people of that house.
I have to think about
everyone here, Boyd,
no matter how much
I wanna help you guys.
Okay, I, uh...
I guess I can, uh...
make some space at
the Sheriff's Station.
- I gotta...
- Oh, Boyd, come on.
No, we're good!
We're good!
I'm not saying
it has to be today.
I'm just saying it's something
we have to consider.
I get it!
You're not wrong! Okay?
You and me, we're okay.
Just... I just...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know. I know.
This one's all right.
Let me help you.
If we get going soon,
we should be able to make
pretty good time back to town.
Whatever was
banging around last night
sure as hell didn't sound like
those things back in town.
Whatever it was,
I'll be glad when
this place is in the rearview.
[Ethan]
Is this what was in your dream?
Yeah.
What the hell?
Tabitha?
Dad!
Hey. What happened?
- Nothing.
- Where's Julie?
Oh, she's... she's fine.
Everything's okay.
What the hell's going on?
[Jade]
Listen, it's okay.
All right? It was my idea.
She needed to come out here.
Why?
Mom saw this place
when she was little,
just like Victor's mom.
What?
Jim!
You coming or staying?
Uh, you guys go on ahead.
We'll... we'll catch up.
Suit yourself.
Come on.
Let's go look around.
Let's go.
Hey.
You moving in?
Yeah, I asked Kristi
if I could spend the night.
- Why?
- [door closes]
My whole family's
at the settlement.
So?
So, it's fucking creepy
in that house by myself.
What's wrong with you?
- Nothing.
- So, we got high on the bus
together and now you're
gonna be all weird towards me?
I'm not being weird.
Where you going?
For a walk.
- Want some company?
- Nope.
'Kay, let me put my bag inside.
[grunts]
[ominous music plays]
♪
[exhaling]
[hinges squeak]
♪
[doors creak]
[knock on door]
[knocking resumes]
♪
[wood scraping, creaking]
[sighs]
Oh, hey. Uh...
Sorry, we're not, uh...
We don't really
serve food here anymore,
if that's what
you're hoping for.
Why is there a diner here?
Sorry?
And why is there
a Sheriff's Station
that looks like a post office?
Or a goddamn, uh,
travel agency sign?
I mean, what kind of psycho
built this place?
You want... you want me to
go over them one at a time
or you want me...
I wanna know why no one's
asking those questions.
[sighs] We did.
And?
Want some tea?
This place is creepy.
Yeah, it certainly is.
Who do you think lived out here?
I don't know.
What do you think
happened to them?
Maybe, uh...
maybe they got out.
You know, maybe they went home.
Just careful where
you're stepping, 'kay?
Why?
Bear traps.
Seriously.
I'm just saying, given
everything that's happened,
there might be a part of you
that wants so badly
for all of this to make sense.
Do you think I'm making this up?
Of course not.
You had a dream,
a terrifying dream,
when you were little.
This wasn't just
a random nightmare, Jim.
This was a dream I had,
over and over again, for months,
and every night,
I would wake up screaming.
So, when I tell you
that the totems here
are the same ones
that I saw in my dream...
what do you want me to do?
Give up? Stop trying?
I don't know.
[exhales]
Look, Tabby, this place,
I thought
I had it all figured out,
and I almost got Donna killed.
Sara? She heard voices,
and she tried
to murder our child.
- But that's different.
- Why?
Those things happened once
we got here, but my dream...
I was a kid!
I know you're scared.
I'm scared, too.
But these things
are happening to me.
I-I can't pretend they're not.
One way or another,
I need to know.
Okay.
So, my mom is convinced
that these creepy children
she keeps seeing need her help.
And my dad's all,
like, freaked out
'cause the last time
he went down a rabbit hole
about this place,
he almost got everyone killed,
including this one
complete idiot
who tied Donna to a tree
in the middle of the woods.
Yeah.
Are you listening?
Yeah, of course. Yeah.
Your mom and the kids,
rabbit stuff...
[chuckles]
What are you looking for?
What? Uh... chaga.
It's a mushroom.
Grows in cold weather.
Marielle and Kristi are on some
holistic foraging trip.
So, where were you going,
on the bus?
Detroit.
Like everyone else.
Why?
To buy a car, so I didn't have
to ride the fucking bus anymore.
- That true?
- No.
I never even got
my learner's permit.
What?
Yeah, you're supposed
to get it when you're 15.
Everything kinda stopped
after Thomas died.
That's your brother?
Yeah. My dad was supposed
to take me to the DMV,
but we never
got back from our trip.
Uh...
All right, uh...
Come with me.
Where are you going?
Can you just come on?
You have to understand,
uh, things are...
things are a little different
when you first get here.
I mean, you show up,
and you think to yourself,
"I'm gonna figure this out.
All these other people,
they may have given up,
they may have accepted it.
But me?
I'm gonna figure this out.
I'm gonna be the one
who gets to go home."
- And what's wrong with that?
- Nothing.
Completely normal. But, uh...
given some time, it'll pass.
Pass. [stammers]
Sorry. No, that's the thing.
The whole idea of just
throwing up your hands
and saying, "Oh, well, I tried"?
That's not how I'm built.
Right. You're not the type to
just accept the world as it is.
What?
I've had this
conversation before,
and I've been
on the other side of it.
The thing you come
to realize is that...
every... [sighs]
question you're asking
has been asked before.
Every theory that you have,
someone else has had
before you, and at some point,
...you either adapt
or you lose your mind.
So, that's what you did?
You adapted?
Well, me,
I didn't really have a choice.
When I first got here,
I was so busy taking care
of my dad that I was just...
Your... dad?
He passed away.
And your mom... she...
she used to run the diner?
Mm-hmm.
You lost both your parents here?
Yeah. [scoffs]
I'm really sorry.
Thanks.
You're... welcome.
Um, what about, uh,
what about you?
You have any... you have
a family back home?
Uh, no, not...
Um... not really.
Right.
Um, the good news is that
we have the talismans,
and they keep us safe at night.
So, you know... I mean,
that wasn't always the case.
What the hell did
people do before?
They just...
tried to hide
as best they could.
Jesus.
Yeah. I wasn't here then.
There aren't
many people left who were.
Where did they come from?
The talismans.
Uh...
Boyd. He, uh...
found 'em out
in the forest one night.
So, that's why he acts like
the God king of the world.
It's, uh, not like that.
You sure?
I mean, no offense,
the guy's kind of a dick.
You, uh, didn't exactly
meet him under the best
of circumstances.
He took my gun.
Can you blame him?
You know, I'm gonna have to
carry the weight of that...
of what I did,
for the rest of my life.
I know that.
But for him to f...
Hey, you know they have
tons of fresh clothes
up at Colony House.
You'd be a lot
more comfortable, if you...
You know, I don't want your
fucking fresh clothes, okay?!
No offense, really!
I don't want your tea.
And I don't want
your adapt-or-die philosophy.
I don't plan on getting
comfortable here, okay?
I'm gonna figure the...
["O-o-h Child" by Five Starships
playing]
Yeah, they uh...
They do that sometimes.
♪
Is that something else
you get comfortable with?
♪ Ooh, ooh, child ♪
♪ Things are
gonna get easier... ♪
Look, thanks for the tea.
Uh, you didn't even...
Excuse me.
♪ Ooh, ooh, child ♪
♪ Things are gonna
Get easier ♪
She's taking it well.
♪ Ooh, ooh, child ♪
Yeah.
Uh, you need something?
♪ Someday... ♪
Yeah. [sighs]
Yeah, actually.
Um, I was hoping
I could talk to you
about reopening the diner.
♪ Yeah, we'll walk in the rays
of a beautiful sun ♪
[metal screeching]
[ominous music playing]
♪
[gasping]
Is this really where it happens?
[pounding on door]
Hi.
Can I go in your basement?
Why?
Because I need him
to tell me a secret.
'Kay, isn't this,
like, for emergencies?
This is an emergency.
Just get in. Come on.
Let's go.
All right.
Ahh. Okay.
- All right. Bingo.
- [keys jangle]
What you wanna do...
You gotta pay attention.
[engine sputters, turns over]
You turn it on,
you press in the clutch, okay?
Make sure this has been shifted,
then you're gonna
ease off the clutch, right?
[engine revving]
Voilà.
[sighing deeply]
Henry.
You need something?
I... could use a drink.
You know what?
So could I.
Let's go.
[clattering]
Who's in there?
Hello?
What the fuck are you doing?
You took my gun.
I want it back.
You... Get out.
Fine. Give me my gun,
and I'll be on my way.
Hey, hey, hey! I don't
have time for this today!
I don't give a shit
what you have time for!
You shot someone!
A girl is dead
because you panicked!
Yeah, I panicked because
I was being chased in the dark
by things that should only
exist in a fucking nightmare!
Well, they exist here,
and they're going to
continue to exist.
So, until you prove
that you can handle that,
there is not a chance in hell
you're getting anywhere
close to a loaded gun!
[chuckles]
I don't have to
prove shit to you.
You see this?
I'm a cop.
A real one,
not just walking around
in some hand-me-down blazer,
playing make-believe.
Right. And when did you
get out of the academy?
Two days? Three?
That's none of your business.
That's where you are wrong.
Everything about you
is my business.
This place is my business.
You know why?
Why?
Because I'm the one who
makes sure people stay safe.
I am the one who
keeps people alive!
Wow. Well, from what I hear,
you've been doing a pretty
shit job of that lately.
Get the fuck out!
Fucking place...
Hey...
Give me... my gun.
You want your gun?
Correct.
You want your gun.
[sighs]
[gun clicking]
[clicking]
There's your gun.
You get your bullets when
I think you deserve them.
[scoffs]
Hey!
The next time you come in here
without my permission,
you and me
are gonna have a problem.
Whatever you say, "Sheriff."
This fucking kid...
I'd ask you what
you were drinking,
but the menu here's
kinda limited.
Everything going
all right with Victor?
Things are going, um...
No, I don't think they are.
[coughs]
You okay?
Yeah.
[breathes deeply]
[exhales sharply]
I stood there today in his room,
and I... [sighs]
...I had a thought I'll never
forgive myself for. [sniffs]
I wished I had never come here,
I wished Tabitha
had never found me,
because it was easier
when I thought he was dead.
It was only for a second.
What kind of father
thinks that about his child?
Here.
Yeah. [sniffles]
- Mm.
- [glass clatters]
Are these the same ones
from your dream?
It's not just the stones;
it's everything. It's...
It's how it feels.
I still remember the fear
when I was running.
I started over there
and came to hide
behind the rocks.
Which one?
This one.
And then what?
Whatever was
making everyone scream
was on the other side
of this rock.
And I would look up and...
What?
I would wake up
every single time.
Okay, let's say you
actually did see this
place before we came here.
Yeah, like...
like Miranda did.
[Jim]
How does that help?
Maybe Aristotle got it wrong.
You know, free will
and determinism, it's...
Miranda said she was chosen.
Right?
If seeing this place,
you know, visions, dreams...
...if that's the proof...
and you saw this place
as a child?
You never really had
a chance, did you?
[Jim] What...
What do you mean?
If fate exists,
if you were destined
to come to this place
since you were a child...
...then, one way or another,
you were always gonna come
to that tree in the road.
How's Fatima doing?
Oh. [clears throat]
She's, uh... She's good.
You know, we're just taking
things one step at a time.
You don't have to pretend.
She told me about the rotten
food, about the cravings.
I realize
you don't know me very well.
But if you need anything,
I'm here.
We did an ultrasound last night.
There was a machine
on the ambulance.
And? Is the baby okay?
There is no baby.
When Kristi examined her,
she looked.
There was nothing there.
So, it's either there's
something inside of her
that isn't human,
that a machine can't see,
or this place
has just broken her mind.
[kettle whistling]
I just...
I can't lose her. I just...
[kettle whistle slows and stops]
You haven't lost her.
She's still here, Ellis.
A good friend once said to me,
"Enjoy every moment,
and don't grieve the living
before they're gone."
And that's what I told my family
when I got my diagnosis.
Are you afraid?
Of dying?
Sure, at first, I was.
And then I got angry.
And one day, I realized
just how small life is,
how it all goes by so fast.
You start to wonder
how it could be anything
but the beginning
of some grand adventure,
or maybe it's the middle,
but I don't think it's the end.
Not anymore.
Once I realized that,
things didn't seem so scary.
None of us get to stay forever.
I don't need forever.
I just...
Whatever I can do,
whatever you need...
well, it may not be much,
but I'm here.
Mm?
I'm sorry, but why?
I mean, you barely know us.
I'm old, and I have cancer.
I like a good love story.
That work for you?
Yeah. Yeah, that...
that works fine.
Hm. Come on.
[coughing]
[gasping in pain]
[breathing heavily]
[whimpering]
[screaming in pain]
[screaming] Help!
Help!
[gasping]
Help. Help.
Help!
[whimpering]
Fatima?
[gasping]
Hey, babe, what's wrong?
What happened?
[breathing rapidly]
What's...
What's happening to me?
[breathing heavily]
Oh, God...
- I can't...
- [Tillie] Ellis?
It's fine.
[whimpering and sobbing]
Hey. It's okay.
Whoo!
Goddamn, this feels good.
So, am I gonna
get a turn or what?
All right.
Okay, okay.
A promise is a promise.
- [chittering]
- Fuck.
What's going on?
Nothing, nothing.
Uh, the, um...
[clears throat]
Son of a bitch.
[chittering]
Yeah, fuck you!
What are you doing?
- You don't see 'em?
- See what?
It's the fucking...
it's the fucking bugs!
- The ones that...
- No.
- [chittering]
- No, no, no, no, no.
[chittering]
- [Julie] Randall!
- Fuck you, man!
Randall, stop!
- [tires screeching]
- [chittering]
Randall!
Get the fuck off me!
Randall, hey!
What are you...
Get the fuck off!
What the fuck?
What just happened?
Just go the fuck home.
- Hey!
- Get off me!
- Randall! Come back!
- Go home, Julie!
[Kristi]
Hey! Put those back! Ellis!
[Ellis] Look! She's in pain,
okay? I need to do something!
- Ellis! Hey!
- Thank you for all your help...
Hey, hey,
what the hell is going on?
Your son decided to come in here
and root the medicine cabinet!
Yeah, that's because that
ambulance has plenty
of emergency medications!
This isn't fucking aspirin
we're talking about!
Things that can make
her stay calm, okay?
These are powerful
anti-psychotics!
You have no idea what kind
of damage that could cause!
Okay, so what then? What? What?
We're just gonna do nothing?
Okay, you're not the one
that's sitting there,
- watching her go to pieces!
- No, I'm the doctor, okay?
And it is my job to use my brain
and not my emotions
- when making decisions.
- All right.
Ellis, those pills in your hands
could make things a lot worse.
Give them back to me.
[Boyd]
Give her the bottle.
Give her the fucking bottle, man.
Ellis! Ellis! Hey!
What?!
Look, I know you're scared, man.
What am I supposed to do?!
Huh?!
Tell me, what the fuck
am I supposed to do?!
- I don't know.
- Okay, I-I saw it!
I saw what happened
with your fucking worms!
And I saw what happened to...
I saw what happened
to Mom when she...
Which fucking nightmare
am I supposed to be afraid of?
Which?
You know,
she's fucking falling apart,
right in front of me,
and I don't know what to do.
I can't do anything to help her.
Dad, I don't know
how to help her.
- It's all right.
- Please...
- [Boyd] Yeah.
- Don't let this happen, Dad.
Okay.
I...
It's just, uh...
Randall?
[breathing heavily]
Randall?!
[ominous music plays]
[Randall] Julie!
What the hell is that?
I don't know.
What happened to you back there?
Why did you just
run off like that?
I'll tell you on the way back.
- Come on.
- Wait.
Do you feel that?
Julie, we should go.
No.
No, I wanna check it out.
Hey, hey, stop.
Stop.
You do. You feel it.
I don't feel shit.
Okay?
It's gonna be dark soon.
We gotta get that van
back to Colony House.
All right, let's just...
let's just go.
Please?
♪
[sighs]
[exhales deeply]
[exhales]
[gasps loudly]
[gasping in pain]
- [whimpers, screams]
- [Tillie] Fatima?
- Ooh, Fatima!
- [groaning loudly]
- Listen to me.
- [gasps in pain]
- You're not alone.
- Please go.
- I'm gonna help you!
- Get off me.
Everything is gonna be okay.
- Just go!
- It's gonna be okay.
- I said go!
- [gasps]
I'm so...
Tillie, Tillie...
No, no. No, no, Tillie, Tillie,
Tillie! I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean it! I...
Help! Help!
You have to run.
[breathing rapidly]
Ellis, what have I done?
What have I done?!
♪