We have to stop them, Lucy.
He needs you on my side.
Okay.
You wake me up.
We stop him.
But when it's done,
when he's gone,
you stay away from me.
I make my own fate
on my own terms.
And we never speak again...
in that life, or any other.
Deal.
Shepherd. On your feet.
You've got another visitor.
There's no one else on my list.
Special dispensation.
You're still alive.
Have we met?
We have.
And we will. It's all relative.
You're not on my list.
You're not supposed to be here.
Yeah.
I get that a lot.
Your watch has stopped.
Couldn't part with it.
Someone once told me it was important.
What do you want from me?
You're going to change
more than you realise.
You played with the chaos,
and the chaos spat me out.
Not alive, exactly, but something adrift.
Unbound.
That's impossible.
My whole life's impossible.
So is yours.
Yet here we are.
Who are you?
What do you want from me?
My name's Isaac Chambers,
and I want to know
why you killed my mother.
Coming up on the show,
we've got Neil Cock coming in
to discuss his new novel, Snowflakes.
And we talk to paranormal podcaster,
Alice Rider
about the UK's most haunted locations,
from a bridge in Kilmarnock
to a go-kart track in St Kenneth.
But first, we're kicking off
your Saturday morning mix
with the Hazy Eights' "Supposed to Be."
I'm gonna un-cuff one hand
so you can eat.
Don't try anything.
Yeah.
- Lucy...
- It's best if we don't talk.
If you let me go,
I'll tell them you helped me.
Whatever he said to you,
whatever he has done, we can get you help.
We're both his victims.
Eat your sandwich.
Please.
I made your favourite.
Eat it.
Good guess, right?
Or Ravi told you.
You know you're mildly allergic
to tomatoes?
It's why you get stomach cramps sometimes.
You usually figure that out in your 40s.
You don't stop eating them,
you just slice them... thinner.
Help me escape.
If you give evidence against him,
then maybe you can walk away.
Look,
- I don't think you're a bad person...
- But I will be.
I will be. If I walk away,
that's exactly what I will be.
Is there no part of you that remembers?
Remembers what?
All those children.
The ones who die today.
The ones who come after.
Just let me go.
I'm begging you.
I have a wife.
I have a child, Lucy.
Eat your sandwich.
We have to
do something about her.
We'll figure it out after.
If you let her go, you'll have to run.
- Lucy.
- It happens this morning.
- We need to focus.
- Where'd you leave your car?
It's outside Dhillon's place.
We'll pick it up on the way.
Park it on Brennan Street.
Gives us more options.
Get that map.
Keep it.
If you need me,
that's where I'll be tonight.
There is no tonight.
I'm giving you today.
That's all.
Whatever happens, this is as far as I go.
'Cause it has to end.
It never ends.
Isaac. Come here, sweetheart.
I have to go out for an hour or two.
I need you to stay here with Grandma.
Rest that leg.
Okay. Have you got your phone?
Keep it on you, yeah?
Come here. Give me a cuddle.
Don't go.
I will be back here before you know it.
Bad things are going to happen.
No.
No, they're not
because I'm going to fix it.
I'm gonna fix it.
The lives we lead
are like tracks in the snow.
And when we live them again
we're walking in the tracks
we left behind.
But if our path changes,
there are no tracks.
It's like wading through a thick powder.
Some people find it hard.
A powerful explosion originated
on the first floor of the building
just after 11:00 a.m.
Not broken.
Not today.
Why did you think
this was broken? Did it look broken?
I'm not cold.
Do you think
it's because we're talking?
Do you think if we go really quiet,
you might be able to hear them?
Shall we try that?
All right, erm, close your eyes for me.
Keep them closed.
I'm gonna put some music on.
Now, you can listen to the music,
or you can listen to the voices.
Come from behind the curtain,
Amelia. Come on.
Let me see your lovely face.
It's not lovely,
it's ugly and horrible.
Well,
that's not a very nice thing
to say about yourself, is it?
One hour to go.
I could get them out.
I could warn them.
No, you couldn't. If we change too much,
we could spook him.
Yeah, well, he won't know it's changed.
No, but he will sense a déjà vu.
Don't engage,
we both need to see his face.
That's the priority.
So what, you see his face,
learn who he is,
and you come back next time
and kill him as a baby?
I've never murdered a baby.
Oh. Well, that's good.
That's good to know.
Thank you for clearing that up.
I don't know what's gonna happen next
but I have an idea.
An omen.
Lucy,
- if we don't survive this...
- We do!
We have to.
What are you doing?
I'm marking the moment.
That is criminal damage.
- It's romantic.
- It's a crime.
You're a criminal. What are you carving?
It's just our initials.
And then every year on our anniversary,
we add another mark.
That is cheesy.
Cheesy vandalism, destruction of property,
anti-social behaviour.
You should get a big cheesy ASBO.
Oh, come on, it's not like I'm drawing
a big willy or something.
I would love that.
Do a big willy, go on.
Then every year we can come back
and add to it.
How exactly would we add to it?
I don't know. Erm, hairs?
You want to mark the years of our marriage
with crudely drawn pubes?
Hello, Lucy.
Where are you right now?
Oh, still holed up
in Leeds's finest hotel.
- Why?
- Turn on the news.
Police have not confirmed
whether the attack was terror-related.
Is that Hackridge?
We're at the scene.
Is it safe?
Er...
What happened?
Okay, yeah. Understood. I'll brief them.
Sorry, I've got to go.
What... Lucy.
We don't yet know
the precise cause of the blast
which occurred just after 11:00 a.m.
Say cheese.
Cheese.
Let me see.
You're slipping.
Where's that watch?
Oh, well, this won't do, will it?
This won't do at all.
Leave it with me.
I'm sure I used to keep
some tape in here.
All right. Here we go.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop!
Hello?
Is somebody there?
Are you here?
Is this now?
Yes.
Please, Evelyn.
It is Evelyn, isn't it?
I don't like it here.
Neither do I.
Can you hear them?
The voices.
The voices?
Yes.
I hear them all the time.
Do you know how to stop them?
No.
You have to listen to them, Evelyn.
Yeah?
You have to give them what they want.
What do they want?
I think they want you to let me go.
There.
That's better isn't it?
It's quiet.
Well, you can still hear them.
But only if you want to.
They still arguing?
Is it them?
No.
What do we do?
Hide.
Stop it. Stop it!
Shh-shh. Shh.
It's going to be okay. All right?
No one's gonna hurt you. I promise.
Just... Just stay there.
Where did they go?
You must be the mother.
Did you see where they put my keys?
Thank God. Thank you,
thank you, thank you, thank you.
Not long now.
Are you still there?
Yeah, sorry.
Just had to get out of earshot.
How many people are up there?
Er, right now I count...
nine.
Think anyone's noticed you?
Not particularly.
Be careful of the staff.
Yeah, I will, I know what I'm...
Lucy.
There's a bag.
- What?
- There's a bag. Someone left a bag.
What sort of bag?
Er, rucksack.
Oh, you must have missed him.
I didn't.
Then where is he?
Look around.
Hang on.
Lucy. Look around, you have to find him.
- Lucy?
- Just wait.
- Oi! What do you think you're doing?
- Er...
- Why you going through my bag?
- Erm... Well, you just left it.
What? I was right there.
I'm really sorry,
I just... I thought it was...
- You thought it was what? Up for grabs?
- Is everything okay?
No, not really.
- It's fine. Just a misunderstanding.
- I leave my bag for a second,
she's going through it.
Look, I'm just, erm... I'm sorry, I...
- Er...
- Well, don't let her leave.
- I'm... I'm sorry.
- Don't let her leave.
Hey!
Oh, my...
- Are you there?
- What happened?
Oh. I made a mistake.
- Did you see his face?
- It wasn't his bag.
I can't go back in there.
You'll have to take over.
Well, er, that is not going to work.
Well, it's our only option.
My face has been
all over the fucking television,
- it's not gonna work.
- It's the only play we have.
Look, I'll come back to the car.
Lucy, don't...
God.
- Isaac? What's going on sweetheart...
- Mum.
- ...are you okay?
- I've been trying to call.
We had to leave.
Who's we? What happened?
Did someone come to the house?
Grandma said we had to leave,
but I said we had to help you,
otherwise, they'll find you
and they'll take you away.
I don't... I don't know what you're saying,
darling, where are you?
We're under the bridge
where you used to play...
Poohsticks.
Why, Isaac? Why did you leave the house?
She escaped.
She'll be back soon.
Grandma says we're not safe here.
Er...
I think I can hear them.
Erm, listen to me.
Listen, you don't let anyone find you.
You stay where you are, okay?
- Will you come?
- Yeah, I'm coming right now.
Just... Just stay on the phone.
Welcome to
the Tidal phone voicemail service.
Leave a message after the tone.
Lucy, where the fuck are you?
Don't do this to me.
We're almost out of time.
You need to come back, do you understand?
You can't fucking do this!
Show me your face.
- Can I have a word?
- Yeah, all right.
Erm, what's your name?
Er, it's Frank.
Frank, I need you to get
everyone out of the building.
- There's been a suspected bomb threat.
- What?
Quick as you can but do it quietly.
Don't cause a panic.
Er, right.
Say there's a carbon monoxide leak,
whatever you want.
Just get everyone
well clear of the building
and don't go upstairs.
I'll send them down to you.
Don't worry.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Right.
Madam. We've got a security issue.
You need to take
your son outside right now.
What?
Right now, please.
Okay.
Guys, these are all free today
but you've got to go downstairs right now.
Says who?
I do. I'm a policeman.
Go on, go. Before I change my mind.
Now come along.
Yep, we're going now.
Why, we haven't even got our toys.
Stay where you are, please.
Turn around.
I said turn...
Dhillon!
Put pressure on it.
Leave it in.
Leave it in or you'll bleed out.
Dhillon. Look at me.
Look at me.
Where did he go?
I'm sorry.
Police, open up!
Open the door.
Isaac?
Mum?
We're down here.
Isaac.
We have to go.
Isaac, Mum, hurry up!
Okay.
Isaac, what are you doing?
We don't need this.
Okay, okay.
Just pick it up quickly, okay?
Lucy.
Lucy?
Lucy? I know you're there.
I've got six armed officers out here.
I'd like to send them home.
But first I need to come in there
and make sure everyone's okay.
Can I do that?
No one else needs to follow me
unless you give them a reason to, okay?
Lucy Chambers, you are under arrest
on suspicion of the murder of Steven Dunn,
kidnap, assaulting a police officer,
and conspiracy to commit
a terrorist offence.
What?
- What, you're wrong, I didn't...
- You don't have to say anything,
but it may harm your defence
- if you do not mention when questioned...
- Sam, what...?
- ...something that you later rely...
- What are you saying because that's not...
...that you later rely on in court.
Anything you do say
may be given in evidence.
Did it go off?
The bomb?
What happened?
We're gonna take you down to the station
to answer some questions there,
but first...
first we need to know
- where we can find Gideon Shepherd.
- No, no, no. He was supposed to stop it.
So just tell me, Sam.
Just tell me what happened.
Hold there. Hold, hold.
Officers were dispatched
to 13 Wenbourne Street
following reports of an explosion there.
An eyewitness spotted Shepherd
in the area moments before.
That's all we know.
Cuff her.
Isaac.
- Isaac, come back here, my love.
- Hey.
Hey, hey. It's okay.
Erm...
Mummy is just gonna help us
answer some questions. That's all.
You want to take her away.
Isaac.
Come on.
Hey, come on.
Hey, it's all right.
You have to let me go, okay?
Look, you just stay with Grandma.
She will look after you
until I get back, yeah?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
You took me with you.
- There's no house because...
- There's no me.
So this is before?
Sometimes.
Sometimes it's before.
Sometimes it's what comes next.
You know what comes next?
Er, this... this isn't right.
You... You shouldn't have brought me here.
I had to. You said I had to.
What?
- You said we had to get away.
- No, I didn't. I didn't, sweetheart.
You will.
It's cold. Why is it so cold here?
It's always cold.
Where are we going?
We have to get away.
Isaac, Isaac. Stop, stop, stop.
This isn't right. I'm not...
I'm not supposed to...
Isaac?
Boyd.
We checked the whole house.
- There's nothing.
- No.
No, there wouldn't be, would there?
Because she disappeared.
She just disappeared.
Ah, trick of the light.
Maybe a hallucination.
You know, I was raised
to believe in miracles, but...
And now I've actually seen one, I can't...
- I can't even...
- But people don't just disappear, Boyd.
It's impossible.
It's not impossible if she did it.
It wasn't her.
It was him.
Isaac?
He's a special boy.
Special how?
Well, that's the question.
He can see the birds.
And they can see him.
He feels like a memory
and a promise,
and a wish.
He says he's not supposed to be here,
but that's not true.
Oh, no.
No, I think...
I think that Isaac
is exactly where he's supposed to be.
He's not coming.
No, don't... Don't scratch.
- It hurts.
- I know. I know.
But you don't have to walk on it anymore.
We're gonna get help, okay?
I just...
I need to make a call.
Okay.
Ma'am?
Found this in the sink.
Okay. I'll call it in.
Thank you for coming.
Did you fill up on the way?
Two miles back, I've got a full tank.
I'll pay you back.
We have to stay off the main roads.
I've worked out a route.
- Lucy.
- Take us as far as Gloucester.
- We'll make our own way from there.
- Where? Where are you going?
It's...
It's better if you don't know.
Better for who?
I know you've been lying to me.
About what happened last year.
About Isaac.
I never lied to you about Isaac.
- I can't help you if you don't talk to me.
- I will.
I will, but not here. In the car.
We cannot stay out here.
There's a road block on the 325.
Someone knows we're here.
What?
We have to move.
What happened at Rigby's?
Did you catch him? Did you see his face?
No. Someone did.
Gideon.
He came out of nowhere.
He could have killed me
but he let me live.
- Why?
- No idea.
But he'll regret it.
We can't use the roads.
Every route will be blocked.
We have to
take the foot path through the farm.
Make for the woods on the other side.
But we... we can't take him with us?
No, we can't.
You have to leave me.
It's the only way to stop him.
Everything is gonna be okay.
I promise.
I will... I will come back for you.
Do you understand?
I'll find you.
Lucy! We have to go right now.
It's okay.
- Lucy!
- What's this?
Okay... It's everything you need to know.
I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
Oh, I'm sorry...
This way.
- What do we do now?
- Shush.
- Gideon!
- Shut up!
They're gonna find us.
I can't let them take us alive.
No.
We have to reset, Lucy.
No, this is your fight, not mine.
I have a son.
I have a life, I can't...
Ravi's dead.
What?
Got them all out
but he couldn't save himself.
He's gone. I'm sorry.
You're lying.
- I wish I was.
- You're fucking lying!
- Armed police! Armed police!
- Drop your gun!
- No, no, no, don't. Lucy, don't.
- Put the weapon on the ground.
Don't shoot me. Please don't shoot.
Don't shoot.
I said drop the gun.
We have to reset while we still can.
No.
It's all right.
I've done this before.
You won't feel it.
You won't even hear the shot.
Drop the gun.
Stay perfectly still.
- Please.
- It has to be clean.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Close your eyes, count to three.
This is your last warning.
Count to three.
- No.
- Drop the weapon.
- One.
- Put the weapon on the ground.
- Two.
- Wait, what about Isa...
♪ Burning papers into ashes ♪
♪ What a season ♪
♪ How they fly high ♪
♪ From the ground up ♪
♪ There is yet another fountain ♪
♪ Flowing over... ♪
Police are still messing about.
Said this was all we could have.
Kept the memory card.
Evidence.
He hasn't said a word since she died.
How do I talk to him?
You don't. You listen.
He's been through a lot.
Do you know what you're taking on?
We know.
All of you?
Yeah.
We'll make him part of the family.
♪ Virgin dress ♪
♪ You could possibly wear ♪
♪ Mess it up ♪
♪ Time is up ♪
Hello, darling.
Mum?