The scripture says that
he who is without love
does not know God,
for God is love.
And we commend to His mercy
all who have loved and died.
That Your will for
them may be fulfilled.
As in baptism, Betty Gore put on
Christ, so in Christ, may Betty Gore
- be clothed in glory.
- Candy?
Clothed in glory.
- Clothed in glory.
Candy.
Are you ready?
Did you hear me?
I'm as ready as I'm gonna get.
Do not hold anything back.
If it even seems like
you're hidin', we lose.
It's time.
Mr. Crowder, are you
ready to proceed?
Yes, Your Honor.
The defense calls
Candace Montgomery.
You heard Allan
Gore's testimony.
Was his description of
the affair accurate?
Yes.
It petered out into
nothingness? It was over-over?
Yes.
There was no burning ember that
made you wanna get back together?
Definitely not.
Calling your attention to
the morning of June 13th,
why'd you go to the Gore house?
We had plans to see "The
Empire Strikes Back."
Alisa wanted to go, and Jenny
very much wanted Alisa to go.
Jenny is your
7-year-old daughter?
- Yes.
- And Alisa?
Alisa Gore, Jenny's best friend.
She had stayed the night.
Betty Gore's daughter?
- Yes.
- And you and Betty were friends?
Yes.
Prior to June 13th of this year,
had you and Mrs. Gore ever
exchanged any hostile words?
- No.
- Had you ever had
- any physical altercation?
- No.
When's the last physical
altercation of any kind
you can remember getting into
with anyone, other than June 13th?
I don't think
there ever was any.
How about a verbal altercation?
I can't think of any.
To the best of your recollection,
you have never fought with anyone,
either physically or
verbally, prior to June 13th?
That's correct.
So you went to the Gore
house that morning?
To get Alisa's bathing suit.
She had a swimming lesson that day, and
if she was gonna stay another night,
I would have to take her.
Did you call Mrs.
Gore prior to going?
- No.
- Candy.
Sorry, Why call when you
can barge right in, right?
How did she seem
when you got there?
She seemed a bit hurried.
Hurried?
She was planning for a big trip,
and she seemed anxious about it.
- Did she invite you in?
- Yes.
And what happened after
she invited you in?
We
Talked about the movie plans.
I asked her if it was
okay for Alisa to go.
We talked about the
swimming lessons,
her upcoming trip.
She introduced me
to the new puppy.
It was a normal,
friendly conversation?
Very.
Until I was gettin'
ready to leave.
And what happened then?
Well, I said that I should
get going as I had
an errand to run
and suddenly, she blurted out.
Are you having an
affair with Allan?
And what did you say?
Yes.
But it was a long time ago.
You wait a minute.
I thought maybe she had
found a card or a letter
that Allan or I had written
and maybe she just
went to go get it.
And when she reappeared?
She had an axe.
Were you in fear for
your life at that moment?
No.
Because I never dreamed
she would use it.
So what happened next?
Well, I said, under
the circumstances,
I should probably bring
Alisa home after Bible class.
- And she said, - No, I
don't wanna see you anymore.
And she put the axe down.
Had you ever seen that
axe before in your life?
No.
Did you even know
the Gores had an axe?
- No.
- What happened next?
I went into the utility room
to grab Alisa's bathing suit.
And that was about the same time
that Betty had returned from
the bathroom with a towel.
And then what happened?
She just looked so hurt.
Ma'am, I'm gonna
need you to speak up.
Betty looked hurt?
I put my hand on her shoulder.
And that's when I said,
I am so sorry.
And she did not like that.
- You can't have him.
- Then suddenly, she had the axe again.
You can't have him.
You can't have him!
I'm gonna have another baby.
- You can't have him.
- Please. I don't want...
- You can't have him!
- I don't want him!
Betty, don't do this.
What are you doing?
Did you think, at that moment,
she was going to kill you?
I still didn't believe
she'd ever do that.
But, at some point,
your belief changed?
- Yes.
- When?
When she swung the axe up
and it hit me in
the side of my head.
Can you describe the
force of that swing?
It seemed with every
ounce of her strength.
Were you now concerned
for your life?
I knew then that she
wanted to kill me.
And then what happened?
I grabbed the axe.
You...
I thought I'd killed her.
And then what happened?
I just went to leave, but...
But what?
Let go of me!
Please, I don't want him.
No, I don't want him!
I don't want him! No!
Do you recall how many times you
hit her when she was upright?
No.
What about when she was down?
I just remember being afraid
that she'd get back up again
so I kept hitting her.
When you got to the Gore house,
did you have it in your
mind to kill Betty Gore?
No.
After she hit you in
the head the first time,
did you have it in your mind
then to kill Betty Gore?
No.
After she hit you the second
time, did you have it in your mind
- to kill Betty Gore?
- No.
When, if ever,
did it enter your mind that
you had to kill Betty Gore
to keep from being killed?
I never thought about it.
It just happened.
After you stopped hitting her,
what did you do?
I walked around.
I stood back and
I looked at myself and I was
covered with blood.
What were your feelings
at that moment?
I just felt so dirty.
I had to get the blood
off. It was making me sick.
I got into the shower.
I just wanted to make it
all go away, but I couldn't.
And I kept thinking,
I have to be normal.
One thing at a time.
Father's Day cards.
Swimming lessons.
Movies.
One thing at a time. Normal.
And when you left the house
and started to drive home,
what thoughts were running
through your mind at that moment?
That it was all a mistake.
Then it never happened.
It just never happened.
But it did happen.
You killed Betty
Gore with this axe.
- Sorry, please don't make me look at that.
- You killed her with this axe!
- Stop. Stop.
- You can look at it. Look at it!
Do you need a break?
No, I'm okay.
I'm okay.
Pass the witness.
When you left the house,
the baby was there.
Alone. With her mother dead.
I wasn't thinking
about the baby.
My mind wasn't thinking at all.
Well, it was thinking
should get in the shower.
It was thinking should
wash the blood off.
When you left the house,
you knew you had killed Betty
Gore with an axe, didn't you?
- I knew.
- And when you arrived back at the church,
you told no one?
I wanted to pretend
it didn't happen.
Wanted to "pretend"
You "pretended" with your friends
and fellow congregants at the church?
- Yes.
- You "pretended" with your close friend
and former pastor,
Jackie Ponder?
- Yes.
- You "pretended" with your husband?
You especially "pretended"
with the police.
I was not truthful at first
but I was lying to myself just
as much as I was lying to them.
But you're not lying today?
No.
You said Betty Gore went
to the utility room,
then appeared with the axe?
- Yes.
- You didn't try to flee?
As I mentioned earlier,
I didn't think my life was
in danger at that time.
But later, you did? Why
didn't you run then?
At that point, I was blocked.
What about the, the
door to the garage?
It was closed.
Your Honor, may I approach?
I'll show you exhibit 13.
You recognize this?
It's a lens to my sunglasses.
- Sunglasses you were wearing that day?
- Yes.
This lens was found
in the garage. Did
you go in the garage?
- No.
- Never?
I have never been
in the Gore garage.
Then how do you explain
the lens to your sunglasses
being in the garage?
Maybe during the struggle, it
somehow got kicked in there.
It got kicked in? While
the door was closed?
No, as I was trying to get out,
I had opened the door slightly
before Betty came back at me.
And so maybe it got
kicked into the garage
while the door was ajar.
That's the only explanation
I can come up with.
I bet you wish you could
come up with another.
- Objection.
- First, you said the door was closed.
Now, you amend it
to "slightly ajar."
Mrs. Montgomery.
Are you pretending
again with us now?
- Objection.
- Overruled.
Do you consider yourself
to be a good liar?
- Objection!
- Overruled, and stop your nonsense.
When you told your
fellow congregants
back at the church that nothing
happened at the Gore house,
did they believe you?
Yes.
When you told Jackie
Ponder, she believed you?
Yes.
When you told your
husband, he believed you?
- Yes.
- All these people believed you.
You must be a very good liar.
- Objection!
- And I would imagine if you could fool
the people that know you best...
- Objection!
- Oh, alright.
He did damage.
I should have done more with
that fuckin' sunglasses lens.
We had a pretty good day.
Nobody's buying
Candy's testimony.
- We don't know that.
- Are you listenin' to what's being said?
The media doesn't get a vote.
I was watching the jury
during Candy's testimony.
They were hanging on every word.
They seem to be with her.
What about Dr. Fason?
I'm not sure Judge Ryan will
find hypnosis admissible.
Yeah, well, we have to try.
Self-defense doesn't
account for 40 whacks.
We need Fason.
Honey.
Mom?
What are you doing here?
Why are you here?
You need to defend
yourself, honey.
Here, take this.
Candy, what's wrong?
Don, it's near midnight.
I tried calling. Why's
the phone off the hook?
We're getting prank calls.
Well, I need to be able
to contact you both.
Put the phone back on the hook.
Why? What's wrong?
Little change of plans.
I'm puttin' you up next.
Me? Why?
This is Texas, Pat.
Folks might be able
to forgive murder.
Adultery, not so much.
I did forgive her. And do.
In fact, I blame myself.
- Why?
- The relationship with Allan
was really more about
having someone to talk to,
and I wasn't
open enough with Candy.
I wasn't sharing myself enough.
Mr. Montgomery,
when you learned what
happened in that utility room,
you continued to
stand by your wife?
Of course.
Yes. She is not violent.
In fact, once the horror
passed, I felt some gratitude.
I thanked God.
You thanked God?
Betty is a much larger woman.
Add to that, she had an axe.
Could have easily
gone the other way.
Candy is loving.
She's not violent.
For this to have happened,
Betty came at her.
Did your wife tell
you what she'd done?
I think she blocked it out.
She lied to you. She
kept it from you.
I don't think she
really remembered.
She forgot about it, you think?
It's not that she
didn't remember.
She knew she had swung the axe but
she suffered a dissociative reaction
which can induce a form of
amnesia to suppress anger
- and, in this case, shame.
- Hold on.
Are you sayin' she suffered
from a mental illness?
I'm saying she could not
reconcile her actions
with who she believes
herself to be,
so she, in a sense,
blocked it out.
Can this explain why after,
when she went back to church,
and then to Target to
buy Father's Day cards,
it was as if this incident
had never happened
in Mrs. Montgomery's mind?
She knew that it had happened
but by forcing herself to
go about her normal day,
it was as if she were trying
to erase the reality of it.
A portion of her personality was
split off from her consciousness.
Dr. Fason, I admit I
am no medical doctor
but when a personality gets portioned
off from somebody's consciousness,
that sure as hell sounds
like mental illness to me.
Approach, Your Honor?
I don't recall you jumping in with
the prosecution's medical experts.
I can pose questions to
witnesses, sua sponte.
You know what sua
sponte is, counsel?
It's Latin for "my courtroom."
We would like the record to
reflect your obstruction.
You don't have to introduce
what I say into the record.
You know why?
'Cause if I said it, it's
already in the record.
I'm representin' a
woman who may go to jail
for the rest of her life, so
I'm going to perfect the record
so that it accurately
reflects your prejudice.
For that remark,
this court holds
you in contempt.
You're already holdin'
me in contempt.
Well, I'm doin' it again.
Another $100
and 72 hours in the
Collin County jail
effective immediately today
once we stand in recess.
Doctor, I'd like you to elaborate on
my client's dissociative reaction,
if you possibly can without
being abruptly interrupted.
Mrs. Montgomery couldn't fathom
that she was capable
of this kind of rage.
In fact, this woman has
an anathema to violence.
Candy Montgomery is also a person
who is excessively concerned
with what other
people think of her.
This is a common personality
pattern with individuals
who struggle with
dissociative reactions.
Doctor, I'm going to
instruct you to refrain
from narrative responses.
Answer only what
Mr. Crowder asks.
Is it common for individuals who
suffer dissociative reactions
to be excessively concerned
with how others perceive them?
Yes.
It's partly why Mrs. Montgomery
emotionally walled herself off
from the events of that day.
It was only when
I hypnotized her
that she was fully able
to access her memory.
How so?
I was able to age-regress her to
the time when she first experienced
a dissociative reaction.
It happened when
she was 4 years old.
She was involved in a race of some sort
with a little boy who was older than her,
and the winner got to pump
some water into a jar.
She was mad because she lost and
she threw the jar into the pump
and it broke.
A piece of glass
from that broken jar
came back and hit her in the forehead
and she was bleeding down her face.
When she was taken
to the hospital,
she was very frightened about
what was going to happen to her.
And she was screaming.
Her mother said...
What will they think of
you in the waiting room?
Stop crying.
She relayed this to you
while under hypnosis?
Correct. She had no
conscious memory of it.
Even under hypnosis,
she was very frightened
of expressing the
feelings that she felt.
It took a very definitive suggestion
that when I counted to three,
she would express
those feelings.
I counted to three. One,
two, three.
Honestly, it was a scream
a sound, that I had
never heard before.
- Triggered by her mother saying "shh"?
- Yes.
Is it any coincidence that
Betty Gore also said...
It is not.
I look at that explosion
of violence with Betty Gore
as being the result of the anger
that had been buried within her
and blocked off all that time
since she was 4 years of age.
- When I told her that, she said...
- Oh, my God.
Do you mean I killed my mother?
Was she killing her
mother in a way?
No. She was defending herself
against an attack by Betty Gore.
But, the depth of rage and violence,
that did in part come from something
that happened with her mother.
Let me ask you one
final question.
Did Candace Montgomery, at any
time during June 13th, 1980,
knowingly, that is
on a conscious level,
intend to kill Betty Gore?
I do not believe so.
Your Honor, we pass the witness.
Defendant hit the victim
41 times with an axe.
She pulverized Betty Gore's
face into a soft mulch.
Your testimony is that she did
so because Betty said "shh,"
reminding the defendant
of her mother?
My testimony is that she
was defending herself
against Mrs. Gore's
attack, and the violence
unleashed a rage that had
been within her for decades.
A rage caused by her mother saying
"shh" when she was 4 years old?
Not necessarily caused
by, but fueled by.
So she's sane enough
to argue self-defense,
but not sane enough
to be responsible
for chopping Betty
Gore into bits?
Again, her initial impulse
was to defend herself,
but during the struggle,
she lost control.
Just so I'm clear.
She knew she was
hitting Betty Gore
- over and over with an axe?
- Yes.
And she was swinging
it out of rage?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
So is it okay for
us to talk now?
Now that my testimony is over?
It's okay.
Why did you make me look
at the axe like that?
I needed emotion.
Our case is you had
an emotional break.
I needed the jury to
see a flicker of it.
So what now?
Betty Gore had it coming.
I need the jury to see
a flicker of that, too.
You're jokin'.
We can't risk her
being too sympathetic.
I wouldn't say she
was mean, Betty,
but she could be ornery.
Snappish is how
I'd describe her.
I'll say she was mean.
Betty Gore could be
quite confrontational.
Can you give us an example?
She would let out dismissive
snorts during my sermons,
right out there in front where
everyone could see and hear
'cause she was in the choir.
And not long after I arrived at Lucas,
she told me to go back where I came from.
- Betty Gore didn't like you?
- She hated me.
Candy didn't like
me much either.
At least, not at first,
but Candy was cordial.
Betty could be vicious.
You eulogized this woman. You
called her a beautiful person.
She was beautiful, as
are all God's creatures.
But she had a streak.
I pass the witness.
As the hour is late,
seems like a good
time to take a break.
For the day.
What made him change his mind?
Robert made an emergency call to
the Court of Criminal Appeals.
Honestly, I wish he hadn't.
If I did time during trial, more
ammo with the appellate court.
Thank you.
What are you doin'?
We knew Betty Gore.
Were friends with her.
For you to just throw
dirt on her like that.
I didn't do that.
Yes, you did.
You called her pastor to
the stand, to say what?
That God was okay with this?
I just established
that Betty could
be antagonistic.
Which is the truth.
This case is gonna
be your legacy, Don.
Oh, balls.
Legacy is you live, you die.
With any luck, it'll have mattered
a nick you did the former.
This whole thing is
gonna eat at you.
It may rot at you.
I got enough on my plate
without this shit, Carol.
Basically, the doctor said
she acted out of self-defense,
and then transformed into an
unconscious killing machine.
Even the victim's pastor
weighed in with a shot,
along with other parishioners.
God loves everybody.
And he loved Betty Gore.
All I said, she
could be a handful.
I have never seen Betty
be unkind to anyone.
She was a wonderful
human being. Excuse me.
It cannot be healthy for
you to be watching all this.
I can't be in the room until
closing arguments, so this is
the only way I know
what's going on.
I put all of this in motion.
Betty's dead
because I cheated on her.
You couldn't have
possibly foreseen.
You won't survive if you continue
to punish yourself this way.
I'm so grateful
for your support.
I just feel so alone.
You're not alone.
You're not.
I'm not about to
presume what you know
but I think I can safely figure
that all of you can figure
Candy Montgomery didn't
wake up on June 13th, 1980,
with a plan to kill Betty Gore.
She didn't cook her kids breakfast,
head off to Bible school,
perform a parable
in the sanctuary,
drive out to Wylie to pick up
Alisa's swimsuit, and then say,
"Hey, while I'm at it, let's
kill Betty Gore with an axe."
That makes zero sense.
Zero.
What happened here is not just
the most plausible scenario.
It's also exactly
what Candy told you.
She got there. Betty
was in a dark place,
agitated that she
might be pregnant,
upset that her
husband had left town.
Then, after some odd
perfunctory conversation,
Betty suddenly confronted
Candy with the weapon.
A struggle occurred.
Candy reacted in self-defense
after being struck with the axe.
And durin' that violent struggle
she snapped.
Dr. Fason confirmed that Candy
was truthful in her account.
He also found that the violence
triggered a childhood trauma,
rendering Candy into a rage that
caused her to go outside herself.
Candy's testimony was not
contradicted, not once, not by anyone.
Nor was Dr. Fason's
medical opinion.
All the police investigators,
the medical examiner,
the pathologist, none of them,
none could rule out self-defense.
So, how can you?
None could exclude that it was Betty Gore
who first came at Candy with that axe.
So, how can you?
What they all did agree on,
a tremendous
struggle took place.
And if this were
a planned thing,
it was maybe the worst
planned crime ever.
Candy told people at the
church that she was headed
to Betty Gore's house.
Nor was there any motive.
As both Allan Gore
and Candy testified,
my client would stand nothing
to gain from killing Betty.
The affair would not
have been resumed.
Neither Candy nor
Allan had any interest.
It was over.
In Candy's mind, when
Betty Gore came at her
and struck her with that axe,
Betty was no longer human.
She had turned into an
animal in search of prey
and what ensued in
that utility room
was a violent death fight.
Betty Gore was a
much larger woman.
Adrenaline had to take over
Candy in order to survive.
Adrenaline did take over,
and human life was lost.
When a person gets killed,
it's natural to wanna
hold someone accountable.
It's natural for you
to wanna fix things.
To make it right.
It may even cause some
of you to wanna believe
the police version of this.
But I remind you,
the police version itself
cannot rule out self-defense.
John Steinbeck
once wrote that,
"There are those among us who
live in rooms of experience
that you and I cannot enter."
If you're worried about
whether or not Mrs. Montgomery
has been punished in this case,
don't.
She lives in that
room of experience.
She lives in it and she's locked in
it and it now constitutes a cell.
A jail cell.
There won't be a day in
the life of Mrs. Montgomery
where she'll ever put out of her
mind that she committed this act
on June 13th, 1980.
There has been an American tragedy
played out in this courtroom.
But a conviction is
not a proper solution
to this particular tragedy.
The state has not
proved its case.
Reasonable doubt exists.
Good luck to you.
Mr. Crowder hits the point
that Mrs. Montgomery's
testimony was not refuted.
The person to refute Candy
Montgomery's testimony isn't here.
She's dead. Chopped to bits.
See, that's the thing, when
two people are in a room,
and one ends up murdered, you only
get a single version of events.
Let's look at
Candy Montgomery's.
I suspect it quite helped
her that all the evidence
was available to her before she
formed her irrefutable testimony.
- Objection.
- Overruled.
Sit down, Mr. Crowder.
He didn't interrupt you.
Mr. Crowder argues none
of this makes sense.
I won't ask you to
make sense of it.
I'll just ask you to
look at what happened.
Candy Montgomery struck Betty
Gore 41 times with an axe.
Murdering her, disfiguring her,
breaking bones,
severing arteries,
obliterating her skull and face.
That is not consistent
with self-defense.
Mr. Crowder had the temerity
to say Betty Gore
stopped being human.
I ask you, who stopped
being human here?
Who was the animal?
He wants you to believe her.
To find her testimony credible.
Seriously?
She's lied at every turn.
To the police, to her
friends, to her own husband.
It was only after she was caught
cold with a thumbprint match
that Candy Montgomery
decided to become truthful.
Self-defense.
That's a lie.
Hitting an unconscious woman over
and over and over with an axe
as she lay there in her blood,
that's not self-defense.
Because Betty said "shh," just
like my mother did when I was 4?
It insults this
court's intelligence.
It insults yours.
Candy Montgomery knew she
couldn't possibly explain
her actions on June 13th,
so she chose to deny them.
She chose to lie.
On June 14th, on the
15th, on June 16th,
the 17th, the 18th, she
stuck to the same story.
With the police, her
friends, her husband.
She left Betty alive
went to Target to get
a Father's Day card.
Then, as the truth
catches up to her,
she pivots. Self-defense.
As for 41 whacks.
You deserve better.
Betty Gore deserves better.
Both lawyers were strong,
both made their points,
and both were not above
playing to the emotion.
This case stirred up such
strong and visceral feelings,
and neither attorney
shied away from them.
Hey, what do you think?
It's closer than
I'd like it to be.
We just have to wait.
Well, whatever happens, I'm
sure it'll all be for the best.
- Sherry's keeping the kids?
- For now.
Till there's a verdict.
You know, my mom always said
that there's no better comfort food
than Salisbury steak and macaroni.
You talk to her recently?
Other than the, the dream?
This mornin'. She
sends her prayers.
And her prayers usually take.
She's not mad at you, you think?
She can't be thrilled.
Especially after she reads that.
No, I just told her to stay
away from the newspapers
or anything like that.
Right.
Well, I just can't wait
for all this to be over
and I can go back to
having a normal life
and go to the market without
people staring at me.
Candy, I think no matter what
happens, this will never be over.
Well, if they find me innocent.
The jury can't
find you innocent.
They can only find
you not guilty.
And there's a difference.
We have no chance at
a normal life here.
We're going to have
to leave McKinney.
Let's just pray we
get that chance.
Well, I thought your
testimony was good.
Thank you.
I don't know if I
deserve you, Pat.
But I'm sure lucky to have you.
We're both lucky.
I think I wanna go back
and wait it out with Don
'cause I just am feeling a
little too anxious sittin' here.
Yeah. Okay.
Don! Don!
They're back.
The jury. They have a verdict.
- Already?
- The judge just called.
I've got the car
ready to take us back.
We'll meet you there.
Gentlemen, comin' through.
All rise!
You may be seated,
ladies and gentlemen.
I have some instructions for
the attorneys, the parties,
the spectators.
When I read the verdict
into the record,
I want no reaction from
anyone in this courtroom.
Whatever that verdict might be, no
vocal reaction, no physical reaction.
And now don't think I'm picking
on y'all. That's standard.
Alright, bring the jury in.
Be seated.
Alright then, Mr. Foreman, has
the jury reached a verdict, sir?
Your Honor, we have.
Will the defendant please rise?
We, the jury,
find the defendant not guilty.
Each member of the jury that
concurs with this verdict,
will you indicate it to me
by raising your right hand?
The court will accept the
verdict and order it filed.
This case is adjourned.
Congratulations, Candy.
How do you feel about
this? Were you shocked?
What about our beds and stuff?
Well, the movers will come for that,
baby. We just take what we need for now.
The movers will bring it
all the way to Georgia?
Yep. That's why we
call them movers.
Why don't you guys go say
goodbye to Miss Sherry?
- I forgot something.
- Hi, hey, bud.
Hey, how you doing?
Good? You're gonna be good,
right? Okay. See you guys.
I promise I'll call as
soon as we get there.
Okay. You better.
Are we all set?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah?
- I won't be long.
- Okay.
I would've called, but I was
afraid you might say don't come.
Anyway.
Pat, me, and the kids
are leavin' McKinney
and we're gonna go
try and start anew
near my folks in Georgia.
So, I just wanted to
come by and say goodbye.
- Okay.
- Also, Allan.
I'm sorry.
For everything that
happened. I never meant...
Me, too. I'm sorry, too.
Betty and I, we
were good friends.
You know, she was a...
She was a good person.
We were a lot alike
in some ways. Just a
good, good person.
Anyway,
I wish you a good life, Allan.
Yeah. I wish you
a good life, too.
Well.
Okay.
Bye-bye.