Mom?
Present.
What?
Like when the teacher
calls roll call,
you say "present." Mom is
ready, so reportin' to duty.
How come you only
have one sock on?
I couldn't find the other one.
You can't go to
school like that.
Mom, can Alisa come over
Friday for a sleepover again?
Yeah, if it's okay
with her mom, sure.
Sweetie, are we not
combing our hair now,
or is this just a new fashion
thing that they got by me?
- I combed it.
- Well,
maybe we have ourselves a
wind tunnel in the house.
Why don't you go back and
comb it again, please?
What kind of mother
will people think I am
if you are a mop-head and
your brother's half sockless?
Alisa said you worry too much
about what other people think.
Excuse me?
Alisa said that? Now
why would she say that?
She's never said that to me.
Well, she must have got it from
somebody, so that leaves Betty.
I've never heard Betty say that.
I know she doesn't like me.
- What are you talking about?
- I get a feelin'.
Betty adores you, Candy.
You think she'd be trusting you
to look after our kids if she...
The feeling you're
getting is just her usual
depression stuff.
Yeah, how is that goin'?
Well, much better, actually.
This Marriage Encounter
was really a miracle.
What exactly do they do there?
Well, mostly get us to talk
about our feelings and...
Well, they're big into writing
everything down in a notebook.
Sounds a little silly.
I know. That's what we thought
at first, too, but it...
It really works.
For the first time in
I don't know how long
we were
unflinchingly honest
with each other.
Exactly how unflinchingly
honest could you be, Allan?
Well, except for that.
And it was an issue for me.
Betty would bring up sex
and my lack of interest.
And I'd go quiet.
I couldn't exactly say I
was less interested in sex
because I was having it
with Candy Montgomery.
We finally opened
up to each other.
Well, that's good.
I'm glad. So...
where does that leave us?
Well, it doesn't necessarily
change the way I feel about you.
But I do feel strongly
that I should be giving my
full resources to my family.
And my relationship
with you is taking away
some of my emotional
availability and
energy and attention that I
could be directing towards
Betty and the kids.
So you don't wanna
see me anymore?
I don't know. Yeah.
They said an awful lot of
things at the Encounter but
they never said you couldn't
see someone else.
Allan, you seem to be leaving it
up to me, so I'm just deciding.
I'm not gonna call. I'm
not gonna try to see you.
I won't bother you anymore.
Okay.
Ok... Wow.
Well, you certainly unleashed
your feelings there.
Well, I'm not sure how
you want me to respond.
Do you remember
what you told me?
That the days you spent
with me at the Como,
that they were the only
hours of your week where
you didn't feel responsible
for other people's emotions.
Meaning Betty. The burden
of making her happy.
The burden of keeping
her from being miserable.
Now,
have you ever
felt any responsibility
for my emotions?
Do you now?
Candy...
Yeah.
Okay.
You realize that every
time you feel a hole,
you paint the kitchen?
That's not true.
Okay, fine. Maybe
it's a little true,
but also, you know,
it is good therapy.
- Well, it looks really good.
- Thank you.
I keep saying that we should
start our own business.
There's a lot of people in Wylie that
are looking to remake their lives,
and some of which would settle
for a spiffier breakfast nook.
You know, it's not even
like I'm gonna miss the sex.
It's the friendship.
Allan's been like
my best friend.
Hello? What about me?
I just wish I could
talk like that with Pat.
Okay, I'm serious.
Why don't we start
our own business?
At a minimum, it'll get us out
into other people's kitchens.
That's where the real life
happens anyway, right? Kitchens?
God, I'm feelin' angry.
I don't necessarily want him but
I don't like feeling rejected.
You're gonna have to put that in
the fridge, honey, for it to keep.
Or the garage.
- The garage is nice and cool.
- Why does it have to stay cool?
The weather this warm,
I'm afraid it'll rot,
and we still have two whole
weeks before Halloween.
I think it's just a
benign fibrous mass.
You can't possibly know
that. Not for sure.
Betty, this is likely harmless.
How dare you be
impatient with me.
It could be cancer.
I don't think it is.
But you can't know that!
I actually can know it.
It's my business to know it.
And the mammogram confirms it.
So it's nothing?
It's a mass, yes.
But it's benign.
You should stop
taking birth control
and also control
your caffeine intake.
It could be from
drinking too much coffee?
Betty, you're fine.
Honey, I'm just saying
that you were Luke
Skywalker last year,
and there are other
characters in "Star Wars."
No, he wears a mask for
the other characters.
He gets claustrophobia.
- You puked in your Batman mask!
- Hey.
- No, I didn't!
- Alright! Okay!
Jenny! Wait your turn!
Okay!
Thank you. Thank you.
- Wait up!
- Ian, stop following me!
- Hello?
- Hey!
Candy?
Sorry. I know I promised
that, that I wouldn't call,
but this is just
for some advice.
I'm sorry. Bad manners.
How are you?
I'm good. Good. How are you?
You don't sound great.
Well, I said good, not great.
What's the matter?
Betty found a lump
in her right breast.
She's fine. At least that's what
the doctors are telling her.
She's already been to two.
I'm sure she's
looking for a third.
They think it's benign,
but she's a wreck.
Well, I should go over
there. Is she home now?
She is, but you don't have to.
No, I should go check
on her. If it were me...
You're a good friend, Candy.
- Betty.
- Hi!
Hi. I just heard
and I know in my heart
that you're fine.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
You have nothin' to worry about.
- I hope you're right.
- Hey, now, you listen to me.
Doctors are so scared
today about bein' sued
that if you go to them
with a growth of any kind,
the last thing they're gonna do
is say, "Go home, it's nothin',"
unless they are pretty
damn sure it's nothin'.
I am sure that you're right.
How did you find out?
Allan told me.
- Allan did?
- Yeah, he was concerned.
You know how worried
husbands can get.
Oh, wait. No, I
got that wrong.
Husbands never worry enough.
That's it.
Well, you didn't have to
drive all the way down here.
But I cannot tell you how much
it means to me that you did.
These doctors, they think I
am the biggest hypochondriac!
They tell me it's nothing,
convince me it's all in my head,
then write me prescriptions
for anxiety and depression,
of which I'm on a gazillion.
- Hi, honey!
- Hi.
Can you believe Candy drove
all the way down here?
She is just the sweetest.
- You feeling better?
- Yes.
Yes. She helped lasso
my runaway brain.
Look at us making
you stand out here.
- Come in, come in.
- Oh, no! No, no, no.
I gotta get back and make
dinner. It's Meatball Tuesday.
This is just one of those hug-and-runs,
now that I see that you're fine.
- And you are.
- Yes.
Walk Candy to her car.
- Sure.
- Would you, sweetheart?
Thank you again.
So much.
And let's get the kids together
for some trick-or-treating.
Sure, yeah. Perfect.
I'll call you!
Okay.
That is not the same person.
You're saying Marriage
Encounter did that?
I'm telling you, she's
like a flower blossoming.
Yeah, and she was actually warm.
Oh, sorry. I didn't mean to...
Yes, you did.
But it's alright.
You're not wrong.
- But now, she's...
- Just like a normal person.
Hey, do you think that Pat and I
should get into Marriage Encounter?
'Cause that's actually
why I called earlier.
- Well, I'm not sure.
- Well, I gotta try somethin'.
He doesn't know
how to communicate.
The thing is Marriage Encounter
is definitely not for couples
who are having serious problems.
From what you told me about
your feelings for Pat...
I do love him.
- Yeah.
But it really...
It worked for you.
So far.
So far, it's really worked.
She insists on doing the
homework every night.
The dialog sessions,
the love letters.
She wants to become a
group leader in the area.
Very committed.
- Well, that's good.
- But thank you for checking on her.
Yeah. It was good to see you.
Good to see you, too. Alright.
My pleasure.
You're all very special people.
Thank you. We're coming back.
Oh, well, in that case,
I'll double our insurance.
- Thanks for everything.
- Yes. Wonderful.
So long.
Well, what's your prediction?
Oh, definite marriage.
Think they'll have children?
Whether they want to or not.
Hey.
I was watching that.
Yes, I can see that
you were watching that.
I bet you'd love to be a
passenger on The Love Boat,
wouldn't you, Pat?
Well, guess what? So would I.
I feel like I'm in trouble.
I don't know why.
I wanna go to
Marriage Encounter.
What?
It's not just the
Garlingtons. Allan and Betty.
Betty, I mean, she's just
like a whole new person.
It's a cult though, Candy.
It's not a cult!
And even if it is...
Why are we here, Pat?
And I don't mean
on the sofa. I mean
on Earth.
- Yeah.
- Why are we here?
That's a huge question, Candy.
And I'd like an
answer. Your answer.
Well, I mean
why is a tree here?
What?
You know how I hate you answering
my questions with questions.
- Yeah, I have...
- Why is a tree here?
- Seriously?
- Look, Candy.
I'm not going to have this
cosmic grasp
that you're looking
for, I think, but
a tree, it grows its roots.
It sprouts fruit.
The fruit spreads its seeds,
and then more trees grow,
and it goes on and on like that.
And I don't think we're
much different, you know?
We grow our roots.
We raise our kids.
I think that's a good
reason to be here.
Or anywhere.
Well, what's your answer?
Why are you here?
I don't know.
You know
you always want more.
You do, Candy.
Whatever you have,
- you always want more.
- Yes, I do.
I do want more.
And I'm not gonna
apologize for it.
I want more from me.
From you. From us.
You want to go to
Marriage Encounter?
Okay. Let's go.
So he has agreed, and we're
gonna just give it a try.
- This is great.
- Well, you know, it's hopeful,
and every day should have a
sprinkle of hope in it, so.
You should put that in one
of your Sunday parables.
"Every day should have
a sprinkle of hope."
That is lovely.
And you know what else?
And this could be
the best part of all.
Just that Pat is willing to try,
I don't find myself
thinking of Allan as much.
And when I do, the first
thing that comes to my mind
is that his eyes are
too close together.
That's what I've been sayin'.
Here's my new mantra.
It's called, "rediscover me."
With my marriage,
with our new business.
And I thought of the
perfect name already.
The Covergirls.
- The Covergirls.
- It's what we do, right?
I paint, you wallpaper.
The Covergirls.
I love it. "We
got you covered."
Yes.
And thank you, Sherry
girl, for covering me.
So that's 10 windows,
and price per.
Plus saving time on
construction, right?
Don Crowder! Church
grounds on a weekday?
My, my, whose wrath
have you doth incurred?
Just my normal pillar and
beacon of the community stuff.
Trying to figure out
some budget challenges.
Yeah, buildings and maintenance.
That's why I'm here.
Let's see.
What's this?
Now, if you're serious about
sprucing up the parsonage,
Sherry Cleckler
and I have started
a new little boutique
home improvement business.
It's mostly paint and polish,
but it's good work at
a price you won't beat.
Thank you.
I'll certainly consider it.
And references upon request.
Well, how would you have
references if you just started?
Why, Ron, I make 'em up.
I'll leave you to your
pillaring and beaconing.
You wanna get in tighter
with the congregation,
straightest line might
be Candy Montgomery.
Folks love her.
Yeah. Meaning they
don't love me.
Ron, a little friendly advice.
Here at Lucas,
people just wanna
raise their kids,
love their family, love God.
Doesn't call for heavy
lifting on your part.
Just don't be a dick.
Okay.
Is that a moose?
Yep.
- Should we go check in?
- Okay.
When you give yourself, and I
mean give all of yourselves,
I'm gonna make it real simple.
When you give,
you beget.
Let's say it all
together, shall we?
When you give, you beget.
Well done.
And look inside. How
does that make you feel?
Pat?
Should I read yours first?
- Okay. Yeah. Yes.
- Okay.
- "When I think of you..."
- Now, I'm a mathematician,
not a writer. So.
Okay.
"When I think of you,
I feel the earth move."
That is so sweet.
"I feel it under my feet."
Pat.
"I feel the sky tumbling down."
Pat, this is a Carole King song.
She's one of your favorites.
Honey, I told you
I'm not a writer.
- Oh, my God!
- They're good words.
No, but they're not your words!
Words are not my thing!
I love you more than
I could ever express.
More than I could ever write
down in some stupid notebook,
at some stupid cult workshop.
I went with Carole King
because you said she always
wrote close to your heart,
and that's where I wanna be.
Close to your heart.
Why couldn't you have put that
down? That was really beautiful.
It was?
Yes.
I wanna be close
to your heart, too.
Why are we here, Candy?
I don't mean on Earth,
I mean at this place,
and
I...
I don't know what
you're looking for.
Do you know what
you're looking for?
The song "Tapestry"
by Carole King.
I've listened to
it a zillion times,
and I still have no idea what it's
about, but it speaks to me just the same.
"My life has been a tapestry
of rich and royal hue.
A wondrous woven magic."
Now, I haven't a clue what
she's talkin' about...
But I want it.
Yeah, I want it. I want
my royal hue.
Oh, honey.
Pat.
I'm not saying that it
wasn't a little goofy
but, you know, we did connect.
That's fantastic.
Yeah. And we've fallen
off with the assignments.
There's the daily
10-and-10 and so forth.
What's the daily 10-and-10?
Well, you pick a topic, and you
write about it for 10 minutes,
and then you spend another
10 minutes talking about it.
We did do that for
about three days.
But overall, you know, our sex
life has definitely improved.
And I hardly ever think about
you-know-who's
perfectly shaped penis.
- Well, this is all very positive.
- Yeah, I think so.
Sorry.
- Hello?
- Candy. Betty Gore.
Betty, hi! How are you?
I'm fine.
And I'm told that you are.
Marriage Encounter went well?
I think it did, yes.
That is so good.
You know I'm the
local Flame leader.
I think I heard that.
Yes, that's fantastic.
Yeah. One of my duties
is I host other couples
who have been Encountered and,
well, I would love to have
you and Pat over on Saturday.
She wants me to come to dinner.
No.
And you said yes?
Well, I felt on the spot.
Well, it's this Saturday?
Yep. What are we gonna do?
I guess it'll be fine.
Will it be a problem for you?
I don't know. It might be.
To see you in that context
might be painful and
I don't know. What if I
start wanting you again?
I'm so sorry, Candy. I feel so guilty
for messing up your life like this.
No, no. You didn't. Maybe...
Maybe this is just the
best way for us to move on.
Because Betty and I,
we should be friends
and maybe this will be
kinda like a good closure.
Yeah. Good. Okay, good. Good.
It'll be great. I
think it'll be fine.
The best part is the
capsule will be reusable.
So, I mean, you think of
all the wasted technology...
- What a waste.
- Such a waste.
- This looks delicious.
- So delicious.
You know, pot roast
is my favorite.
Well, I did know.
Allan let the cat
out of the bag.
It didn't take you
two scientists long
to start talking about
rocket ships and so forth.
No, but actually, we were talking about
something new called the space shuttle.
Which is a capsule which can
be used for repeated travel.
What did you say, Pat?
A couple of years?
1981. Yeah.
Pretty soon, it'll be easier
to go to the moon and Mars
than to get in
and out of Dallas.
So, you two enjoyed, you
enjoyed the Encounter.
Yeah.
You been keeping up
with your 10-and-10?
Well, we're trying.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Yeah.
Well, that's wonderful.
Isn't that wonderful?
It's wonderful. Yeah.
Yeah.
Candy, I heard about
you and Sherry Cleckler
are talking about a
rediscovering yourself. A
kind of a "rediscover you."
- Wait, did I hear that correctly?
- Yes, you did.
And what does that entail?
Well, Sherry and I are
starting a business together.
Home improvement.
And then, I'm still taking
my writers' workshop classes.
I'm actually moving on
to an advanced level.
That's wonderful.
Some kind of wonderful.
You know
sometimes, the best way to
rediscover yourself is to
look inside you.
Deep inside.
That makes sense.
We all have stuff
buried deep within.
Things we never knew were there.
Yep.
Wonderful.
My God, you must have
been dyin' inside!
- A little, but mostly, I was just bored.
- Bored?
At a couples dinner with your
lover, his wife, and your husband?
He is not my lover anymore.
And you know what? The best
part is I was bored with him.
Allan.
I thought that it would be hard to see
him or that old feelings would bubble up,
but nothin'. It's over.
And Betty, love her to death,
but she's a little weird.
You're just now
figurin' that out?
But she's also nice. You know,
she's odd because she's odd,
not because she's mean
or unkind or uncaring.
And I'll tell you
somethin' else.
I think she's way more
interesting than Allan.
Why does she have to go to
some lake to study the Bible?
- She could just study it here.
- Yep.
Yeah, we have a lot of Bibles.
Maybe she's really
going fishing.
Nope.
No, she's definitely studying.
Your mother is taking
some special time
to further her commitment to our
Lord and Savior Jesus Christ.
And I'm very proud of her.
I think you guys should
be proud of her, too.
- Yeah.
Okay.
It's time for us to pray, right?
- Can we talk after?
- Yeah. Yeah, you can talk after.
Now I lay me down to sleep. I
pray the Lord my soul to keep.
And if I die before I wake, I
pray to God my soul to take.
- Hey, Pat.
- Hey.
Can I talk to you for a sec?
It's important.
Sure.
You can just let that dry.
- Hey. Yeah. Sorry.
- Hi. It's okay.
Alright.
So
I found a love letter
from Allan Gore to Candy.
I was looking for a letter she'd
written me just after we married
and found a different letter.
I need to know something.
I know she would tell you.
Is it over?
- Pat...
- Is it over?
It is.
And it won't happen again.
It was just a brief
thing and, honestly,
it was more friendship
than anything.
It was just a stage
that Candy went through.
We were just over at
their house not long ago.
- The Gores, all four of us...
- She told me, and you know what she said?
She said the best part about that night
was that she felt nothin' for Allan.
That it's over-over.
Pat.
She really loves you.
Candy is a good mother,
and she's a good wife,
and she is a good friend to you.
She just made a mistake.
And it was just a brief thing
and it didn't mean anything.
And it's totally over?
It's been over for a long time.
I wanna talk to Candy
about this in my own way.
I don't want you to tell
her that I talked to you.
- Promise me I can talk to her first.
- I promise.
I promise.
- Mommy!
- Hey.
- Hey, baby! Hi!
- Hey, Mom!
Hi! Oh, my gosh, you grew!
I thought we had a deal.
No growing when I'm gone.
- Hey! Hi!
- Hey, Mom.
- Good trip?
- Oh, yeah.
Yeah, we learned so much.
I better not be hearing that
you grew, too, young lady.
Hello?
It's me.
- Don't change your expression.
- What?
Pat found Allan's letter.
What?
He found one of Allan's love letters,
and he came by the salon this morning
to make sure that the
affair's really over.
And he made me promise not
to tell you that he knows.
So, this is me not
telling you that he knows.
Well, I'll call you later, okay?
- Okay. I'm so sorry.
- Okay. Bye.
Everything alright?
Oh, yeah. Yeah,
yeah, it's good.
I think I should
start fixin' dinner.
And since I have been
gone, it is kids' choice.
- Chef Boyardee!
That is my best work.
Straight out of a can.
Raise your hand if you
love Chef Boyardee's.
I do.
Chef Boiardi is the French
version of Chef Boyardee.
Come on! Come on!
Now, Travis, let him tell his
story the way he wants to.
But, Mama, I just seen that
old yeller dog catch this fish!
Arliss is just a little
boy with a big imagination.
Won't hurt him to
let him use it.
We keep that old
yeller dog much longer,
it's gonna make Arliss
the biggest liar in Texas!
I know I failed you.
I tried to write down
how I feel in a letter.
I'm gonna go downstairs
while you read it.
Come down whenever
you feel like it.
- Take it, Tom!
- No.
It just stands right
up. It's American...
I agree, agree! It felt...
You read the book? Right?
Did you read the book?
Yes, I read the book.
Okay, then you read the
Folk Singers' Credo.
I am so ashamed.
I don't ever wanna
hurt you or the kids.
I know.
Maybe we could get away together.
South Padre Island for a bit.
Just you and me.
Could make it like a
second honeymoon.
That would be nice.
I trust you'll agree that the
added expenditure is well worth it.
They really are the most beautiful
rose-colored cushions I've ever seen, Ron.
They really do make a
wonderful statement.
We'll have the best
pews in the county.
Now, if we could just find
some folks to fill 'em.
Maybe we should just
invite Jackie Ponder back
to give a guest sermon.
That would fill the
seats, wouldn't it?
I think you're being a
little sensitive, Ron.
No! I'm not.
He's feeling sensitive
about the attrition.
Maybe if we can get the Gores
back, and the Garlingtons.
Y'all are friends
with the Gores, right?
No, not so much. No. Just
our kids play together.
You and Allan are in
the same line of work.
We don't need the Gores.
Pryor remained in critical
but stable condition today
at the Sherman Oaks Community
Hospital in California.
Pryor continues his
steady improvement.
Surgery to remove scorched dead
skin could begin next Tuesday,
with skin grafting starting
three or four days later.
Honestly, Pat, can
we not have that on?
- He was doing drugs, they say. Cocaine.
- Well, even so,
this is a day of celebration.
We shouldn't be hearin' talk of
comedians lightin' themselves on fire.
Dad, did you take
my elephant puppet?
- Why would I do that?
- He's missing.
And Noah's ark has
to have an elephant.
We'll find him, honey. Now, can
you please just eat your cereal?
And a cleaner shirt will be nice.
Could somebody call the girls?
- Why are you using that voice?
- What voice?
Your stressed voice.
This is my
zillion-things-to-do voice.
We have Bible camp graduation,
I have to do my parable,
we have the puppet show,
and then I have five different errands
to run in five different towns.
Hey! No, you don't.
- Three Trees?
- What?
Your parable. Are you
going with Three Trees?
Well, yeah. Do you
think I shouldn't?
No, well, it's my favorite.
Kids'll love it.
Mom, can Alisa go to the
movies with us tonight?
I don't know, honey.
Alisa's mom didn't like it
when we took her
to see "Grease."
But she loves "Star
Wars." She wouldn't mind.
She would want me to go.
Oh, sweetheart.
Now, that was just the
most adorable little fib,
but if it is okay with your mom,
we would love to have you.
Pat, are you sure you
can't make the puppet show?
'Cause I saw the rehearsal
and it's gonna be great.
- I wish.
- Okay.
Doesn't that serve
you perfectly right?
You can't come back here first?
My flight's at 4:00, honey.
So, with Friday traffic,
I think I probably need
to leave for the airport.
Best to just go straight
from the office.
- Just two days, honey. Two days.
- Yes.
Two days can go more quickly
for some than for others.
Then, I'm home, and
we're packing for Switzerland and
we're going to have the best time.
I'm almost two weeks late.
I can't take care of
another baby. I'll break.
- I don't wanna be pregnant again.
- Honey, there's no reason to start...
No, please don't...
Do not handle me.
I beg you. Just...
be with me.
Honey, I am. I am with you.
If you are,
we'll deal with it.
We can deal with anything.
Right? We can.
We can.
You wanna say bye?
Bye, Dada. Bye, Daddy. Bye.
Bye, Dada.
"Once upon a time, there were
three trees high up on a hill.
"The biggest tree used
to say to the others,
"'When I grow up, I want
to be made into a big boat.
"The finest ocean
liner in the world.'
"But, one day, a
group of wood cutters
"came to the hill
of the three trees.
"And one of them looked at
the biggest tree and said,
"'This tree looks like it would
make a fine fishing boat.'
"And the big tree
cried and cried,
"but the wood cutters
cut it down anyway,
"and it became the very boat
that Peter used as his altar
to spread the good news."
Isn't this a wonderful
time we're having?
- Yeah!
- Yes?
Hey, Barbara. Let me help
you. I can get the Kool-Aid.
It is gonna be a scorcher today.
Oh, my God, I just wanna
drop and put my feet up.
- Do you ever do that, Candy?
- Well, it won't be today.
The kids all wanna see
the new "Star Wars."
And Jenny wants Alisa to
stay over another night,
which is fine, but Alisa
has her swim lesson today,
so that means I have to
drive all the way to Wylie
to pick up her swimsuit.
I suppose if I do leave soon enough,
then I can swing by the Target
- to get a Father's Day card for Pat.
- Oh my... Go.
Go. I can do this.
And you better get a move on
if you're gonna make it back
in time for the puppet show.
And I can't miss that.
- Ian made the elephant.
- Bail.
- Hey. Listen to Miss Barbara, okay?
- Okay. Bye, Mom.
Hi!
Hi.
Candy! I finished with
your cassette recorder.
Okay, well, I'll be right back.
I just need to run over to
Betty Gore's and then to Target.
Gotcha. Bye.
Yeah. See you.
Candy.
Sorry. Why call when you
can barge right in, right?
I hope I didn't disturb.
No. No, no, no. No,
I just put the...
Put the baby down and then
poured myself a cup of coffee,
getting ready to watch
a little "Phil Donahue."
Sounds like heaven.
- Come in. Join me.
- Okay.
Well, I can't stay long.
Noah's ark is leaving
port within the hour.
But the reason I came is we're
seeing "Star Wars" tonight,
and Alisa wants to come,
and Jenny's just
desperate for her to join.
And I said it was okay with
me if it was okay with you.
Which is to mean her
spending another night.
And I'm happy to take her to her
swim lesson to save you the trip.
No, sure. That's fine with me.
Well, I thought it would be,
so I just came from Bible
school to pick up her suit.
- You sure you can't stay for coffee?
- No, no. Thank you.
Remember, she doesn't like to
put her face underwater. Alisa.
So, if she does put
her face underwater,
be sure to give her
peppermints afterwards.
That's the reward that we have.
- Okay!
- Okay.
I'm just so busy getting
ready for our trip.
- Switzerland! I heard!
- Kansas first.
We're gonna drop the kids and
the dogs off at my parents.
- Dogs?
- Yes.
We got another one. A
puppy, six months old.
He's right out there.
- Oh, my God!
- I know.
What is his name?
- Cheeto.
- Cheeto!
Oh, my gosh. Your
name is Cheeto. Hi.
Alisa can't bear
to leave him alone.
Well, I can see why. You're
just the sweetest little boy!
You're a good boy! Yes, you are!
Come, come. Just
sit for a second.
Okay.
- Okay, outside. Outside. Good job.
- Oh, my goodness.
- Nothing?
- No. Thanks.
Well.
Gonna be a scorcher today.
Scorcher.
I almost forgot. Sherry and
I actually incorporated.
We're lining jobs
up for the fall,
so if you need any papering or
painting done, here is our card.
The Covergirls.
- It's cute.
- It's so exciting.
Well, I should
probably get goin'.
I'm hopin' to swing by Target and
get a Father's Day card for Pat,
so should I just go
grab Alisa's suit or...
Candy.
Are you having an
affair with Allan?
No.
No, of course not.
But you did.
Didn't you?
Yes.
But it was a long time ago.
Did Allan tell you?
Can you wait a minute?
Betty?
Betty.