I'm telling you, Will, you
got a real winner here.
She's just gonna love it.
Stacy?
Box her up.
Just the box.
I'm sure it's prettier
than the paper.
One tiny rock.
So many other cool things I
could have bought for myself.
Sam, Stacy, it's been a pleasure
being ripped off by you.
Such a nice boy.
Too bad he's a handicap.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Just calm down.
Kid's a blind diabetic.
He's hyperglycemia
hyperosmolar.
Which is what we thought
until his blood tests showed a
controlled sugar level and no ketones.
Could be caused by drug abuse.
His tox screens were clean.
You lying sack of crap.
I have them right in front me.
Not you. This time.
My former BFF.
He's S.M.l.T.B.A.W.S.
Stabbing me in the back
as we speak,
Where exactly are you'?
If anyone should happen to ask,
I'm at an out-of-state medical
conference till further notice.
Why would any...
And don't really care.
Auditory hallucinations and disorientation
could be signs of schizophrenia.
They did a psych consult.
Mental status is normal.
A seizure?
Noise-induced epilepsy.
The sound of rush hour traffic
could have set it off.
Run an EEG,
and blast his brain
with harmonics to find out.
Also, if anyone should
further happen to ask,
I spent the whole of
last year in Africa
with Doctors
Without Boundaries.
Who are you hiding from?
Evil.
Where's House?
Uh... He's at an out-of-state
medical conference.
In Baltimore, I think.
Nice to meet you. I'm Blythe.
His mother.
Do you want me to pick up the
Braille writer and laptop
from your apartment?
I don't plan on
being here that long.
I didn't eat lunch yesterday.
I probably just fainted.
Or had an epileptic seizure.
Which is only one possibility.
I'm Dr. Chase.
We'd like to discuss your
case with you privately.
I'm his girlfriend. Is it all
right if I stay for this?
Melissa can stay, and I've never
had a seizure before in my life.
They can be mild, like a loss of
concentration or a muscle tremor.
A lot of times a family member
notices before the patient does.
I'm Dr. Park, by the way.
I'm 5'2", Asian,
and I'm totally cool with it
if you want to feel my face.
Blind people only
do that in movies.
But you sound nice,
so if you want me to...
Her point was you may not have
realized you were having a seizure,
but maybe your girlfriend has.
No.
But I haven't seen him
for the last five months.
We were on a break.
Like Rachel and
Ross on Friends.
Never seen the show myself,
but I hear it's good.
That joke usually
kills my blind friends.
Will, this is serious.
No, it's not, since
I don't have epilepsy.
I have to pay attention to every
signal my body sends or receives
or I end up taking a dirt nap.
You don't think I'd know
if I was having seizures?
It was probably
just low blood sugar.
If that's true, then you shouldn't
have a problem passing our test.
How is he, James?
Really.
He's better than I've
seen him in along time.
Is he happy?
It's okay.
He's always been
a complicated child.
Were you in the
hospital recently?
Nothing serious. I just had a
few moles removed yesterday.
I forgot I even had it on.
Look, if Greg happens to get
back early from the conference,
I'm staying at a hotel in
town for the next three days.
I would like him to call me.
I will pass it on.
Thank you.
Do you think that they would mind
if I got a refill for the road?
Not at all.
Good.
Not seeing any seizure activity in
response to low frequency sounds.
I'm starting him
on mid-range.
Have you seen his girlfriend'?
Extremely hot.
Blind people can't have
attractive girlfriends?
Not my point.
He actually convinced her to go for
the whole relationship break thing.
How do you know
it wasn't her idea?
Because she's back with him.
Women suggest a break when
they want to break up.
Men do it because they want to have sex
with other women before they settle down.
They're a little young to get
married, don't you think'?
I was their age when I did.
I see your point.
He's seizing.
The sound frequency's
at 300 hertz.
It's not a seizure.
He's not spiking on his EEG.
And not moving air. I think
he's choking on something.
Blood, but I don't
see any blockage.
Help me move him.
Just relax and breathe.
What are these?
Three teeth detached from his jaw
bone and lodged in his throat.
He almost choked
to death on them.
Environmental? Could be heavy metal
poisoning or radiation exposure.
Then he wouldn't
be the only one.
He's an accountant who works on the
same floor with 50 other people.
Maybe his girlfriend
poisoned him.
House usually thinks
that's a good guess.
And she's gotta be pissed off
and have low self-esteem.
Why else would she give him a
free pass to pork other women?
Because he's handicapped.
Women feel sorry for us.
This cane is tail-bait.
Where are you now?
You expect an actual
answer this time?
Hi, guys. Was wondering
if House's mother left yet.
He won't let me
go to our house...
It's not environmental.
It's periodontitis.
An oral infection
doesn't explain
his disorientation and
auditory hallucinations.
They're laughing 'cause they know
diabetes exacerbates the condition.
It could progress
to a systemic disease.
The bacteria spread
and affect other organs.
Like his brain. Stan him
on broad-spectrum antibiotics
and book him an appointment
with a periodontist.
He has fake children now, too?
You think I'm not good
enough for your mother.
Not in front of
the kids, honey.
Add a couple of flies, toss in a dead
goat or two and we might have a winner.
Is she gone?
Yeah.
We really need to talk.
Okay.
Crayons down. Line up
if you want to get paid.
It's the only time I ever
successfully lied to my mom.
Is with elaborate
preparations and props.
Hey, hey, hey...
I said no Transformers, slick.
Stay here until
the coast is clear.
Fine.
But you sleep on couch tonight.
You're sleeping with her now?
Just in case an INS guy comes
in through the window.
Yeah, she didn't buy it either.
You need to talk
to your mother.
When I'm ready.
I still need to get
a fake passport,
doctored photos,
maybe a case of AIDS.
She's sick, House.
Did she say that?
She was wearing a hospital
admission bracelet
and carrying around a book on
dealing with terminal cancer.
I'm sorry.
She's staying at the Grand
for the next three days.
The antibiotics will stop the
infection from spreading further.
And I'll spare you the lecture you'll
get from the periodontist tomorrow
but you need to practice
better oral hygiene.
So, are you guys saying this is happening
because, what, I didn't floss enough?
Probably didn't help, but diabetics
are prone to this type of infection.
Half the time he doesn't even bother
getting undressed before he goes to bed.
I can only imagine how many times
you've skipped brushing your teeth
since we...
Sorry.
I don't mean to
lecture you, babe.
But I guess you're right. Look, you
haven't eaten anything all day.
Why don't you go grab
a bite'? I'll be fine.
All right. I'll see
you in an hour, okay?
Not if I see you first.
I was wondering if I could
ask you guys for a favor.
I really need my laptop
and Braille writer
and I can't ask Melissa
to get them for me.
Why not?
Because
I want you to put
this someplace safe.
It's beautiful.
People always say
diamonds are beautiful.
But to me they just feel cold
and have really sharp edges.
I guess convincing her to take
a break was a good thing.
The break was her idea.
Melissa's the only
girl I've ever dated.
She wanted me to be sure
before we took the next step.
Wow.
Yeah.
What are you doing?
We're here. We might
as well search the place
in case we're wrong
about periodontitis.
What are you doing?
We're here.
Might as well eat.
You're stealing food
from a blind man?
We're doing him a
favor, he owes me.
Hake it from your
low self-esteem theory,
you have some experience
with relationship breaks.
What happened?
He talked me into it,
then slept with
three of my friends,
then dumped my ass.
College boyfriend.
I thought he was
the love of my life.
Then why agree to a break?
My self-esteem wasn't
as high back then.
No one's is.
Ugh!
Sugar free.
Disgusting.
I'll check the bathroom.
You keep checking the snacks.
Greg?
Sorry I didn't call first. I just
flew back from my conference.
This really isn't...
I need your medical records,
and the name of your
primary physician.
You remember Mr. Bell?
If I didn't, I will now.
You're not dying.
I may have misled James
by letting him see
a book on cancer.
We did however have some expectations
that you might call first.
Yeah.
This isn't how I envisioned
you finding out.
Mr. Bell and I, we're...
Having sex? Got it.
Getting married. Also.
We wanted you to be
the first to know.
I need 10 milligrams
of benzodiazepine.
Help me hold him down.
I'm putting epilepsy
back on the table.
And I'm taking it off because it
doesn't explain losing his teeth.
The kid's diabetic. The periodontitis
could be real but completely unrelated.
A coincidence?
You buying that, House?
Until I hear something
that takes my mind off
the Jurassic schlong that I was
traumatized by this afternoon.
I know what's wrong
with the patient.
Illegal drugs.
Some kind of acid.
His tox screens were clean.
His apartment wasn't.
We didn't find any drugs.
Then why am I completely
tripping balls right now?
I am seriously
freaking out here, guys.
Can't you tell?
You pretty much look
the same you always do.
Take your glasses off.
Pupils dilated.
Pulse elevated.
Hallucinating?
I think so.
Because he's a rabbit.
Oh! I get it.
Because she's his wife.
They flirt a lot.
I've seen things.
And Taub.
Taub is either
a tooth fairy or Rainbow Brite.
And you?
You're just House.
She ate ice cream and gummy bears
at the patient's apartment.
One of them must have
been dosed with it.
Go back and find the drugs.
You two find out
where he bought them
and then MRI his brain check for
infections, masses and plaques.
Am I gonna die?
We'll get back to you on that.
I've been blind since birth.
I thought maybe if I tried
LSD, I might, you know...
Colors, a shape.
I just wanted to see something.
How many times?
Maybe five or six.
We need to know where you bought it
so we can find out what was in it.
My girlfriend gave it to me.
I'll find her.
No. Don't.
It wasn't Melissa.
I met someone else.
When were you planning
on telling her that?
Before or after you
ask her to marry you?
The ring isn't for her.
We were on a break.
She wanted me to see what
else was out there and I did.
I was gonna tell her
the other night,
but I ended up here instead.
We just need to talk to the
one who supplied the drugs.
She's on vacation
with her parents.
This is her cell.
I don't want her to know I'm in the
hospital She'll only freak out.
That's very considerate of you.
You think this is easy for me?
I know I have to tell Melissa.
Then what's stopping you?
She's still one
of my best friends.
And I don't want
to be alone in here.
You seen your mother yet?
She's not dying.
She was having
sex with my father.
Ignore her.
She's on acid.
Your father's dead, House.
Not the dead dad,
the biological dad.
The one I pointed out to you
at the fake father's funeral.
Hun!
Are you sure?
Your only evidence is that birthmark
you saw when you were 12.
Well, now I've seen two.
The good news is, I won't technically
be a bastard much longer.
We're gonna be one
big crappy family.
Well, that's great news.
Your mother won't be alone anymore and
you can finally get to know the guy.
Yes.
That is one option.
Are you saying you're
not even curious?
You want to know what I think?
I think you know the
answer to that question.
You avoid your mother
because she's the one person whose
opinion you actually care about.
If that was true, you'd have
every reason to shut up.
I avoid my mother
because she's boring.
That's why you've been so
open and honest about prison
and marrying
a complete stranger.
Even if I care what she thinks,
why would I care what
some sperm donor does?
You read the guy's book
about three times.
Years ago and it took three times
because it was so badly written.
Om I get it.
The second birthmark
was on his penis, right?
The kid's a dick.
You've been working
for House for months
and just now realized that disabled
people can also be dicks'?
What he's doing now
to that girl isn't fair.
The break was her idea.
And now she thinks
they're back together.
He's a scared, sick blind kid
who doesn't want to be alone.
You really don't get that?
I do. But...
What is it?
Not good news for him.
Or Park.
Where's Park?
Wilson's babysitting her.
Talking about the fact that she
could have permanent brain damage
might bum her trip
out a little bit.
Dark spot doesn't necessarily
equal brain damage.
It could be a congenital malformation
connected with his blindness or a tumor.
A clot.
Exactly. We need to do another
scan, then inject dye...
I said a clot,
not or a clot.
It's a clot. Cerebral
venous sinus thrombosis.
That'd be good news for Park,
but I've never seen one
present this large before.
It fits.
When it was smaller,
it caused his initial
disorientation and hallucinations.
As it grew larger,
the seizures.
If left untreated, it leads
to cerebral edema and death,
but what causes
that and tooth loss?
Any hyper-coagulable state.
Lupus?
I counter your lupus
with Behcet's syndrome.
No. He doesn't have any
of the earlier symptoms,
color blindness, abnormal
visual fields or...
We've been ignoring his
eyes because he's blind.
If he wasn't before,
he would be by now.
Confirm with an eye exam and start
treatment with heparin for the clot.
Interferon and steroids
for the Behcet's.
Give me back my teeth!
Park, listen. Park!
You're a tooth thief!
No, no, no, stop it!
Stop it!
Back on the couch!
What are you doing
to this poor girl?
It's not what it
looks like. She's...
She's tripping on acid.
Good Lord, man. That's no
way to treat a bad trip.
Put the chair down. You'll end
up hurting the poor wee thing.
Hello, darling.
I'm Thomas and this beautiful
creature here is Blythe.
Is there anything
we can do to help you?
That rabbit stole my teeth.
Of course, he did. But I'll
tell you what he's done.
He's put them back again and they're
twice as nice as they used to be.
You can feel them if you like.
See?
Now why don't we sit on
this nice, comfy couch,
have a nice cool drink and talk all about it?
Would you like that?
He's had some experience with
things like this back in the day.
As I recall, both of us'
Ah! Not the time
or the place, dear.
See? There you go.
There's no way that
guy's related to you.
There's fresh scarring and swelling in
both fundi and a bleed on the left.
House was right.
It's Behcet's syndrome.
Give it to me straight, Doc.
Am I ever gonna see again?
That's a little out
of our jurisdiction.
We need to wrap a dressing over
your eyes to keep the light out.
Not really a problem for me.
You might not see it
but your tissue does.
It'll also help
with the swelling.
I'll leave you in
Dr. Adams' capable hands.
You think I'm an ass,
don't you?
I can tell by your breathing.
Either you're angry or fat.
I think it's unfair that
you're leading on a woman
who obviously loves
and cares about you.
I love and care about her, too,
but we just don't work
together as a couple.
You need to tell her that.
I'm going to,
but I just want to
do it the right way.
I don't want her to hate me.
When she finds out you bought an
engagement ring for another woman,
that option is out the window.
It was going to be for her.
What changed?
She told me we were
going on a break.
I didn't even get
a say in the matter.
She wanted you to be sure
about your relationship.
I can see how that
would be annoying.
I think I liked it better when
you were just breathing angrily.
She still sees me as the same sheltered
blind geek she met in college.
Most of the time she acts more
like my mother than my girlfriend.
I asked her to marry me. She tells me
I need to date somebody else first?
I'd rather she just dumped me.
At least that I can understand.
So you were hurt so much you had
to marry the next woman you met?
Julie doesn't see me as I was,
but for who I am now.
She trusts me to make my own
decisions and to help her with hers.
For the first time in my life,
I have somebody who needs me
instead of the other way around.
She finally fell asleep. I think
she'll be fine in a couple of hours.
How do you know about
handling a bad acid trip?
Friends in your gardening club
been experimenting again?
I was young once.
A little scrapbook that
Thomas threw together.
He even has a couple of
pictures of you as a child.
I've known Greg
almost since he was born.
His father and I
were like brothers.
I was a Navy chaplain
in those days.
I left the service
in the late '60s.
I don't think his dad ever forgave
me for protesting the war.
Of course, if he knew
I got Blythe involved...
You protested
the war? When?
You were a child. I didn't share
my entire schedule with you.
We knew if we told you, you'd
tell him and he'd kill us both.
He was a Marine. That was
the ultimate betrayal.
Penultimate.
Sweetheart, I think we need
to get back to the hotel.
Wilson, it's been
a real pleasure.
You're right.
Much too formal.
Come here, lad.
We're practically family now.
We'll see you boys tonight.
8:00 sharp.
Good.
I invited them out to dinner.
Told them it was your idea.
Straw.
I know we agreed that whatever
happened on break would stay on break
and I don't expect you
to talk about yours.
I just want you to know
that there was no one else.
I missed you so much I barely
even saw my own friends.
I'm just so glad it's finally over.
Are you okay?
What's happening to him?
Is he gonna be okay?
I'm gonna need to discuss
that with my colleagues.
We have to talk.
No,
you need to rest.
I have to tell you
about what happened
on the break.
Later, you just
lie back and relax.
Stop it, Melissa.
Just stop telling me
what I need
and listen for once, okay?
How are you feeling?
Embarrassed.
I'm still not sure what was
real or what I hallucinated.
Did you try to kiss me?
What about you?
He's stabilized for the moment.
Coughing up blood? That
doesn't really change anything.
Hemoptysis is a
symptom of Behcet's.
Except our treatment should
make him better not worse.
It could be doing both.
Our treatment breaks down his clot
in his head like it's supposed to,
except a piece broke off and traveled
to one of his arteries in his lungs.
If anything, we need
to increase the heparin
to prevent further
clots from forming.
We do that and he
starts hemorrhaging,
we won't be able
to stop the bleeding.
We don't do that, the next clot
causes a heart attack or a stroke.
Park's way, he at least
has a shot at living.
CT his lungs to confirm
and up the dose.
She's young and hot.
She'll bounce back.
82 pounds.
How much weight I put on when
my break ended the same way.
People were calling
me Park-ing-lot.
Mmm.
Almost 9:00. I think your
boy's gonna stand us up.
No, no.
He'll be here.
He practically
walked in on us having sex.
God, if I saw my mother doing
that, I'd claw my own eyes out.
Of course, she was nowhere
near as attractive as you.
Horribly fat,
as a matter of fact.
Mother.
Guy sleeping with my mother.
This is Dominika.
My wife.
It's so nice to be meeting you.
Gregory tells me that you were
born in Richmond, Virginia,
and your father was a tailor
who stole from his clients.
James has persuaded me of the value of
openness and honesty in relationships.
We see people with
disabilities all the lime.
But seeing and understanding
aren't always the same thing.
Are you talking to me or
writing a Facebook post?
I'm saying we should have picked up on
the degeneration in his eyes sooner.
We ignored them because we assumed they
weren't even part of the equation.
I also realized,
intellectually,
I may understand what it means
to be disabled, but emotionally?
I didn't have a clue.
Apparently, his
girlfriend didn't either.
So you're back on his side?
It's not a side,
it's a perspective.
He just wants to be treated like an adult.
Make his own decisions.
I may not agree
with all of them,
but how the hell
can I judge him?
I'm sure that's exactly
what disabled people want.
To be treated like
completely foreign entities,
incapable of being
judged and understood.
Park was rig ht about the clot.
Hopefully, the anticoagulants
keep it from killing him.
So, she gets the couch
on the odd nights,
and I get the bed on evens.
In exchange for
a federal felony,
she gets a green card
and I get a live-in maid.
Good for you.
The immigration policy in
this country is a travesty.
It forces people to lie just
so nice people can stay here.
Thank you.
Dad.
I'm grateful you approve.
You should also know that I
was not in Africa last year.
You were in jail.
I've been reading the Princeton Police
blotter ever since you moved here.
And I'm afraid I haven't been
truthful with you either.
And I've wanted to tell you
this for a very long time.
Thomas and I.4.
We got married two months after
your father passed away.
Uh-huh.
You understand, we
didn't want you to think
we were disrespecting
the memory of your father.
And is there another secret
that you want to share with me?
There's nothing you think
might be relevant to my life?
Like what?
I don't know. Just off
the top of my head,
something like
I DNA-tested my dad
and found that he was not
my biological father.
You are.
That's impossible.
People lie.
Birthmarks don't.
Oh, my God!
You told me he was a preemie.
This bloody lunatic is my son?
He's not a lunatic.
All those years, you could've
told me, I could've done things.
I could've made a difference
in the boy's life.
I think we should all
just calm down and...
Look at him sitting there!
A pill-popping sociopath.
If you wanted to
screw up his life,
you couldn't
have done it better.
He's got you there, Mom.
He's one of the most well-respected
doctors in the world.
He's saved more lives
than you can count.
Now you apologize to him,
or I swear you will never
see me again, Thomas.
I can't deal with this anymore.
He.s m
Y son, '
I'm gonna have a bloody breath of fresh air.
That's what I'm doing.
So, who's for dessert?
Somebody help me!
Will, it's Dr. Adams and Dr. Chase.
We just need to know where...
My eyes! My eyes!
Feels like ifs on fire!
It's not Behcet's. It doesn't
necrotize tissue like this.
I think it's
streptococcus pyogenes.
Except we've already treated him
with broad-spectrum antibiotics.
It shouldn't be spreading,
it should be dying.
It just means
it's drug resistant.
We need to remove what's left of
his eyes before gangrene sets in.
It's something that looks and acts
like a bacteria, but isn't one.
Could be viral.
No, it couldn't.
No evidence of viral markers
in the necrotized tissue.
Let me see that image you took last
night of the clot in his lung.
That's not a piece of
the clot from his brain.
That's the point of infection.
Mucormycosis.
He breathed in the spores.
Must be growing and
spreading ever since.
A fungal infection
spreading this fast?
Kid's a diabetic. He already has
a compromised immune system.
He's right. This sample from
his eyes is crawling with it.
Treat him with amphotericin B.
We treated him with gentamicin
when we thought it was bacterial.
Which means the dose of amphotericin
B we'll need to cure him
will probably leave him deaf.
Sorry, stopped listening after you said,
"The dose we'll need to cure him."
Blind and deaf?
I'd rather be dead.
You will be.
I can live with that.
You never did get my humor.
There's a chance your hearing
won't be completely gone.
How much of a chance?
A small one, but a chance.
I'm refusing treatment
You don't know how hard
things are already for me.
I can't handle any more.
I can't.
Oh! Hi.
I'm hereto apologize.
I could have handled
the news with more aplomb.
I have a son.
That's great news!
What else did she
tell you to say?
You're not a lunatic,
you're not a mistake.
I never liked your
friend, my father.
He could be a bit
intense at times.
But unlike you,
I did respect him.
Do you respect your mother?
Well, we do have that in common.
And we all love her.
So we don't have
much choice, do we?
Son, see you at dinner.
Will, it's me.
Let me guess.
The doctor who thinks I'm an ass
wants you to convince me to live?
Yes.
It won't work.
I know.
So I won't.
Wow. You're that angry.
I've made enough
decisions for you.
This is your life.
Why did you come back?
Because I love you.
And I want to be with you
for as long as I can.
Melissa, I'm so scared.
Me, too.
I'll always love you.
Even if I was deaf?
Even if anything.
Is it working?
He's still very ill,
but if he keeps responding the way
he has been, he should be fine.
And his hearing?
It's gone.
We don't know yet
if it'll be permanent.
Melissa, is that you?
We've been squeezing his hand
once for yes, twice for no.
Can I ask you something?
I'll completely understand
if you squeeze no.
Will you marry me?
Don't leave me hanging now.
Yes.
Yes! Of course, yes!
I heard that
You said yes, right?
You said yes.
How long are you gonna
wait until you tell me'?
I thought we already
had the Santa Claus talk.
You don't think I saw you steal
Thomas' fork from the restaurant?
Why would I do that?
For his DNA.
That's...
Very observant of you.
See, you are more me
than you pretend.
You had to know for sure.
So you needed proof.
And the fact that you haven't
told me can only mean...
He isn't your father either.
I'm sorry.
You know what that means?
Your mom's a slut?
That.
And she's not as boring
as I thought she was.