How long has your
daughter had trouble breathing?
About a week now.
The best dads wait two or more.
Yeah, no.
It's not like it's serious.
I checked online and it's
asthma or something.
"Or something" is
the number one killer
of teens with
no medical degree.
When was the last time
he took you to see a doctor?
Uh...
Like five months ago.
We went to a clinic in Trenton.
I had strep throat.
Remember the antibiotic they gave you?
Is it neomycin?
Amoxicillin.
So, about the inhaler
for my asthma, I was...
Sorry.
Hospital policy
specifically prohibits me
from giving meds
to unrelated homeless people
pretending to be
father and daughter.
Your pants are
a size too short,
so either you grew
several of inches
or you grabbed the closest
size in the thrift store.
And only you have dimples,
which are adorable,
but they're also an X-linked
dominant genetic trait.
Which actually
doesn't prove anything.
The fact that she didn't
burst into tears tells me
that you never thought
he was your dad.
Let's get out of here.
Since you're the brains of the operation,
you might want to stick around.
What, so I can get
busted by Social Services?
No. So you can stop
bleeding out of your ear.
It's usually a sign
of a skull fracture.
Someone been using your head
as a soccer ball?
No. As much as I'd like
to take your word for it,
I have no interest in
taking your word for it.
No tenderness. No pain.
Right. Looks like you're telling
the truth about something.
The ear canal is fine.
And you don't have a fever.
Pay the man. He's late
for a trashcan fire.
Would you tell me what's going on'?
What's wrong with me'?
I have no idea.
Why did you ask to meet us 30
miles away from the hospital?
Because I can.
Also, Chris Christie's
blog says
the pancakes here are the best.
So, what do we got
on this 18-year-old
with the ear bleed
and the breathing problems?
CT confirms no skull fracture. And
looking at her confirms she's not 18.
Yes, she is.
Says so in the file.
We can't treat an underage
patient without a guardian.
We need to call
Social Services.
I cut a deal with the patient.
We don't call,
she doesn't bolt.
Whatever age, living on the street
makes her vulnerable to malnutrition,
drug use, HIV...
All things which could
explain her symptoms.
No sign of malnutrition, lox screen's
clear, STD panel was negative
and is that Foreman?
Oh, my goodness, it is.
Hi, Dean Foreman!
Are you not gonna introduce us
because we're married?
No, wait, that's her.
She's a pharmaceutical rep, and
this is a working breakfast.
In a restaurant that's nowhere
near your home or the hospital'?
Chris Christie
recommends the pancakes.
Squamous cell middle ear tumor
could've caused the ear bleed,
paraneoplastic reaction caused
the breathing problems.
Middle ear looks
completely normal.
But there is thickening in the lining
of the wall of the third ventricle.
Could be a sign of
cerebral infection.
It would explain
the lack of fever.
Pneumococcus is pretty common
among the homeless population.
We should find out if
she's been vaccinated.
Sure. Ask her and when she
refuses to tell you anything,
start her on ceftriaxone
for pneumococcus.
And if she says she
has been vaccinated?
Then don't believe her and start her
on ceftriaxone for pneumococcus.
How about we don't believe she's gonna
bolt and we call Social Services.
While I'm in
the little boys' room,
you can pretend I'm seriously
considering that idea.
The bathroom's that way.
Pretty sure there's
one in the hospital.
When I was your age,
I ran away.
Lived on my own.
At the time, it seemed...
Let me guess,
life with mom and dad was kind
of a drag so you just ran away,
lived with friends
and partied with guys
that you knew your
parents would hate,
and then when you got tired of
being a rebel, you just went home.
Being homeless isn't
a vacation for me,
and I'm not acting out.
My life at home sucked, so I
got the hell out of there.
There are other options besides
living on the streets.
Right. Like group homes,
where you're packed in
with as many messed-up,
delinquent kids as possible,
foster parents, who only take you
in because you're a meal ticket.
I can think of easier ways
to make 175 bucks a week.
No, you're right.
I really should roll the dice
and hope for a pair that don't ruin
my life the way that my mom...
Get your hands off my stuff!
This stuff might tell us more
about why you're sick.
A history textbook?
You go to school?
I don't plan on being
homeless forever.
Hello, good sir.
My brother the general here gots
the green apple quick step.
One of us is in
the wrong time zone.
And if it's me, I need
to talk to a stockbroker
and anyone from the Kennedy family.
In that order.
He got the runs
and we do need him
up and at 'em for
battle tomorrow.
It's hardly authentic,
coming to a newfangled clinic,
especially with
a Yankee doctor.
Sir, are you questioning
my resolve?
Yes. And your sanity.
I'm multi-tasking.
General, do not light out.
We swore that we would
see the elephant together.
Far be it from me to come between
two nut jobs and their elephant.
I could add some mercury if you
want to make it more authentic.
The Confederacy
thanks you, Doc.
I got House's phone, deleted
all photos of you and Anita.
I owe you.
An affair? Never knew
you were such a tramp.
Neither did I.
Anita, she's fun, smart,
not looking for anything serious.
It's pretty perfect.
Except for the gnawing guilt
about the husband,
the lies she
must be telling him.
But not guilty
enough to stop seeing her.
She's smoking hot. And ifs not
his job to protect her marriage.
Aren't you supposed
to be pointing a finger
at your own life as
a cautionary tale'?
If not for cheating,
I might still have a wife
but I wouldn't have
Sophie and Sophia.
Which means I wouldn't be preparing
for their visit this week
by child-locking all my
cabinets, padding table corners
and getting rid of
every single magazine.
You could probably just hide the
porn in your underwear drawer.
The magazines go away so I
won't ignore my children.
I know I have to
pay attention to them,
I want to pay
attention to them.
But they're just so
boring.
Did you learn anything
at Jane Doe's school?
They did a bunch of
vaccinations, including pneumococcus.
Take her off the ceftriaxone.
So we're back to square none.
Not exactly.
The name she registered
under seems to be fake,
but the address is
a foreclosed house.
We'll let you
know what we find.
Plenty of food, water.
And beer.
She eats well, goes to school,
makes good grades.
She's a homeless girl who's
captain of the volleyball team.
How can you be okay with this?
Your mom sends you
to work with snacks.
I want and need parents.
Jane Doe is flourishing
without them.
Maybe.
But this mold definitely is.
You went to my school?
Now that they know
they'll report me.
I can't go back there.
You may have a fungal infection,
you need that medicine.
Fluconazole, right?
I'll get it at a clinic.
I can't feel my legs!
Is that the infection?
I don't think so.
So, what causes an ear bleed,
breathing problems
and our runaway's
inability to run away?
Fungal infection's
off the table.
What about transverse myelitis?
Not with normal
posterior column function.
I've been waiting to do
this for months. Pull!
Sights seem to be off on this.
We didn't call
Social Services before
because we didn't want
the patient to take off.
Now she can't. There's no
reason for us not to call.
How about the reason that there's no reason.
This is working fine for me.
Pull!
That one clearly
took evasive action.
You want to protect her,
because you think
she's fine on her own,
outside the system...
Does anyone have a position on
our patient's medical condition?
Could be endocarditis
with septic emboli.
Pull!
I'd turn around and shoot you,
but apparently I'd miss.
There's no murmurs,
no Osler nodes.
You've never done
this before, have you?
No, I have not.
But all the time I had my ankle monitor
on' I was furious that I couldn't.
Vasculitis fits.
Start treatment with steroids.
If she's lucky, she'll be
free to flee again.
Not once I call
Social Services.
I'm not giving up.
You wanna bet?
One shot, one birdie.
You hit, you make the call. You
miss, never mention it again.
No. Why would I agree?
Because your only other option
is you call and I fire you.
Pull!
She responding
to corticosteroids?
Looks like it.
And Social Services.
I thought for sure there'd be
some yelling or profanity,
possible bloodletting.
She's tired of living
on the streets after all.
I'll bet House regrets...
Could he know I'm
good with a gun?
I don't know how, but...
Hiring a hooker to pretend
to be a social worker?
She took a bet that
she knew she'd win.
Frankly, I feel violated.
What happened to the
social worker I called?
Apparently someone identifying
themselves as Dr. Pujols called
and said the patient ran off.
Come on, Poo-holes.
I've informed Social
Services of the mistake
and given Jane Doe's
description to the cops.
They'll track down the parents.
Thank you.
I'll leave you
and Dr. Pujols alone.
You should have told me you were
treating an underage clinic patient.
I was giving you
the gift of deniability.
Now I'm giving you the gift
of additional clinic hours.
No, you're not.
You've got nothing on me.
Check your phone.
MY phone?
Right, I guess I did have
some pictures on that
But I also have these.
Here's the two of you
kissing over dinner.
Busting a move at a nightclub.
Is that your hand
near her nether regions?
Thanks again for
taking out the ankle bracelet.
I'm not gonna let you
blackmail me, House.
Of course not. There's no way
your selling out your integrity
would let me compromise
your job in any major way
over some tawdry bit of gossip.
But what about compromising
it in a minor way,
reduced clinic hours, unlimited
Internet porn budget.
That makes much more sense than
the nuclear option of
ruining both our lives.
You can keep these.
I got copies.
God, how I've missed the sweet
smell of sticking it to the man.
Adams is right.
You're protecting this girl.
Oh, no, I was wrong.
That's the stench
of moralizing.
I'm protecting myself from
meddling bureaucrats and parents.
You admire this girl.
She had a horrible home life
so she went out on her own.
She's your road not taken.
I've always dreamed of living in
an abandoned house with mold.
House, all I'm accusing you of is
having a connection with a patient.
This is a good thing.
It's not a good thing,
'cause it's not a thing.
It is a thing, which you'll
prove when her parents show up,
and you start
protecting her from them.
The sound I make is "moo."
And the sound I
make is "quack."
Moo!
The sound is quack.
Quack, quack.
Quack, quack, quack.
I'm an ass.
On the plus side, I can now
program my DVR from my phone.
They are kind of boring.
All kids. Not just yours.
Very helpful.
You need to log more hours.
Eventually you'll pass
boredom, get to bonding.
Like Stockholm syndrome.
I heard the nurses talking. You
called Social Services for real
Because you shouldn't
be living on your own.
Right. Better my mom should
use me as a punching bag.
If your mom abused you,
Social Services
won't let you go home with her.
Have I mentioned I
don't trust the system?
We don't know if you're better yet.
You can't just take off.
Uh...
Can we help you?
I'm Adele Brown from Social
Services, and this...
I'm Ellen Rogers,
Callie's mother.
You haven't been
that for two years.
I promise,
things are different...
Wow, two sentences in and
you're already making promises.
Okay. Maybe we need to take a minute
here and give Callie some space.
No, I don't need a minute. I need
her out of my life.
Is she okay?
I will be once you just...
oh, my God!
We need help in here!
Go!
You bet 100 bucks
on a turtle race?
I paid Mr. Chips 5
bucks to take a dive.
The bleeding
stopped on its own.
She got worse after being on
steroids, so autoimmune is out.
Diagnosis depends on whether
the blood was coming from
the sinuses, lungs or her guts.
Mr. Chips looks
like he wants it.
100 bucks says he'll make
soup out of Franklin.
You're on.
How'd the mom seem to you?
If you're asking if she looks like someone
who beat her kid, you're a moron.
Move your ass, Mr. Chips!
You should have seen her face
when mom walked in.
Callie hates her.
I don't think she's lying.
Because people never lie
about people they hate.
Big sinus bleed could be sinusitis
and a bleeding disorder.
She didn't
complain about a headache.
If the bleeding is in her gut,
could be Zollinger-Ellison.
Acid reflux causes asthma, and the acid
erodes the stomach, causing the bleeding.
Yes!
Franklin rules.
Mr. Chips drools.
Mr. Chips' owner only
feeds him on apples and bananas.
Nowhere near enough
Vitamin A. Pay up.
Do an upper endoscopy to
confirm Zollinger-Ellison.
After mommy dearest has
given her permission.
Ellen shouldn't have consent
if she beat her daughter.
Doesn't matter if
she beat her daughter.
Only matters if Social Services
says she beat her daughter.
Good thing you
made it all official.
Will the endoscopy be painful?
Is that an issue?
It's a medical procedure,
there will be some discomfort.
I never meant to
hurt my daughter.
And yet, you hit her.
She told you that?
And now you're gonna
tell me you didn't.
I'm a drug addict.
And I've been a lousy mom.
Especially since
my husband died.
He was closer to Callie than I
was, and I missed him so much.
And it was too hard,
and taking oxy just
made things easier.
Right up until it
made me lose my daughter.
I hurt Callie a lot.
But one of the only things that I can
feel okay about is that I never hit her.
Didn't peg you as the midday fun kind of guy.
So glad I was wrong.
Mmm...
Unfortunately,
that's not why we're here.
Remember that guy from
the restaurant yesterday?
Mmm-hmm.
He's got pictures of us. He's
threatening to show your husband.
I thought you said that guy
was one of your best doctors.
Yeah. Not one
of my best people.
We've got to stop
seeing each other.
Not necessarily.
I told my husband about you.
What? Why?
He was saying
that things had been
better lately
between him and I,
that I was happier.
I said that I was,
and that you were the reason.
And he was okay with that?
Not initially. It was a
pretty tough conversation.
Neither of us is ready to
give up on the marriage,
and I am not
ready to give up this.
You don't have to feel
so guilty anymore.
You didn't need
to shoot yourself.
I could have
given you a Section 8.
We've hit
the drills pretty hard,
and by the fourth round, my hand went numb.
The gun slipped.
And I only had
blanks in it but...
It's funny how nearly shooting your
toe off cured that speech impediment.
Ha! Yeah. Sorry about that.
Sheldon's a progressive.
Compared to who?
Rupert Murdoch?
Progressives are reenactors who
strive for complete authenticity.
They never drop character
while in uniform.
Whereas you just
dabble in crazy?
Sheldon and I had a big
falling out years ago.
We only really started talking
again because of the reenactments.
They gave me my brother back.
That's a very moving story.
Be a lot more affecting
if you hadn't bonded
over something so
completely idiotic.
Your mom didn't
hit you, did she?
No.
Then why did you lie about it?
Because I wanted
to get out of here.
People understand getting hit
more than what my mom does.
Tell me, maybe I'll understand.
I was the mom.
She couldn't keep a job,
spent all her money on pills.
I had to get a job.
Double shifts just to keep the
power on, keep food in the house.
I couldn't tell you how
many times she nearly OD'd
and I had to clean her
up and put her in bed.
So I decided if I was
gonna be the grown-up,
I'd rather do it
on my own terms.
Your mom knows she messed up.
She's determined
not to do it again.
Yeah.
And she'll feel that way
right up until
things get too tough
and she has to
start using again.
Do you think people can change?
No.
But I don't think that's gonna change
your opinion because people don't change.
Stop.
Is that an ulcer?
Yeah, it is.
But we haven't
reached the stomach yet,
I'm still high
in the esophagus.
Means it's not
Zollinger-Ellison.
Ulcer's bleeding.
We need to lavage before she
drowns in her own blood.
We cauterized the ulcer,
stopped the bleeding.
Compromised immune system
from living on the street
could make her
susceptible to HPV.
HPV was covered on the STD
panel, she's negative.
What if she didn't get this
from being homeless?
What if she got
it from her mom?
I'm assuming you're thinking
something genetic because...
I'm thinking addiction.
Alcohol-induced
esophagitis.
Explains esophageal ulcers
and her other symptoms.
If only it would
explain why we've never
seen her drunk,
drinking or detoxing.
Her blood pressure's been elevated.
Could be the DTs.
It's been mildly elevated.
Mildly elevated BP could put her
at risk for a berry aneurysm.
Weak blood vessel in the brain
gets pounded on by elevated BP,
causes it to
expand and contract,
causes the symptoms
to come and go.
CT didn't show any
signs of an aneurysm.
Did I mention come and go?
As much as your
presence may cause
objects to become
engorged with blood,
sometimes aneurysms
just aren't in the mood.
Alcoholism and berry aneurysm
are both valid theories.
I think we should discuss this
with the patient and her mom.
Why? We've discussed
it right here.
Tell them she needs a cerebral
angiogram to locate the aneurysm,
surgery to repair.
Brain surgery? When?
We've booked the OR
for an hour from now.
And Dr. House is sure
that's what she has?
He's confident
in the diagnosis.
It's consistent with
all of her symptoms.
But you don't buy it.
No.
I think your symptoms are
the result of alcohol abuse.
But I'm not an alcoholic.
You came to the hospital
with beer in your pocket,
we found more
alcohol at your house...
Yeah, I use booze as payment.
I have an occasional
beer with my friends.
That doesn't mean
I have a problem.
I want the surgery.
Actually,
it's your mom's decision.
I'm not an addict
That's what I always said to you,
Callie, but I had a problem.
I'm nothing like you.
Tell them to do the surgery.
I need a few minutes to think.
The patient asked
me what I thought.
I pay you to think
inside this room.
Outside this room,
I pay you to parrot.
It's her choice.
She has the right to know.
It's a medical choice
that you turned into
an extension of
your baggage and hers.
You told the mom something
you want to believe
because you don't
want to believe that
this girl might be
doing fine parent-free.
Which also happens to be what
the mom wants to believe...
You think she wants to feel responsible
for her daughter's illness?
That woman sees everything
to do with her daughter
through
guilt-colored glasses.
It's all her fault.
House,
don't bully her,
she's overwhelmed enough.
It's nothing compared
to how she's gonna feel
when her daughter dies from the
aneurysm she decided not to treat.
You must be Dr. House.
I save my appearances
for when parents are on the brink of
doing something incredibly stupid.
Your daughter has a berry
aneurysm, she needs surgery.
What she does not need is you
making this or any other decision.
I can't just
leave this up to her.
Then leave it up to me.
And just leave.
I'm not gonna
abandon my daughter.
She hates you.
It's actually not
such a big deal.
Plenty of kids
hate their parents.
What makes it a big deal is
that she should hate you.
Playing the biology card doesn't change
anything except where she lives.
Your daughter's
better off without you,
so let her be
better off without you.
I'm gonna do the surgery.
I'll take the fallout
from Social Services.
Dr. House.
My daughter's
care is my choice.
And so is this.
Treat her for alcoholism.
Peek-a-boo!
Why would Anita tell her
husband about our affair'?
Probably just
got sick of lying.
Look at it this way, now the sex
is both commitment and guilt-free.
And men love
commitment-free sex.
Yes, they do.
Oh, yes, they do.
They're gonna
find out eventually.
Peek-a-boo.
How do you keep doing the
same thing over and over
with the same
level of enthusiasm?
First off, be a decent,
empathetic person.
This is what you
said you wanted,
but you're actually more upset
now that the husband knows.
Because I'm hurting him.
You always were.
But he didn't know that Which
means he wasn't really hurt.
Yeah, I know it's
a rationalization,
but it went a long way to making me feel
a little less guilty about seeing her.
Looks like you're gonna need
a bigger rationalization.
Peek-a-boo. Peek-a-boo.
Social Services
report came in on your mom.
Let me guess, she passed
with flying colors.
She always does.
I think she might
make it this time.
House left a bottle of Vicodin
to see if she'd steal it.
She gave it back.
You could at least let
her sleep in the room.
She could have listened
to me about my drinking.
Even if you are right about it,
why take your word over mine'?
I'm her daughter.
Because she's your mom.
And for the first time
she's acting like it.
It's a little late for that.
Good night.
Morning.
I heard you went
head-to-head with the mom.
Not for your reasons.
You're protecting the girl.
I'm protecting my diagnosis.
And you tested her, to see if
you could get her back on drugs
and out of her daughter's life.
That was to show Adams that
mommy dearest hadn't changed.
I'm taking a principled
stand against idealism.
Your patient's stable?
Maybe Adams was right. The
illness is alcohol related.
I hope so considering that's
what we're treating her for.
You hope you're wrong for
the sake of the patient.
I hope that I'm right, but the
aneurysm bursts without killing her.
Call me a softie.
Or the mom agrees to an
autopsy so I can prove it.
Your patients love you
because you're empathetic.
I also have kind eyes.
Why are you here?
But you don't love
all of your patients.
Of course not.
I'll bet some of them bore you.
Dull people get cancer too.
Why are you here?
But you fake an interest in them
because you need to, right?
And if you do it long
enough, it becomes real?
Well, no, because
the interest isn't fake.
Really?
Because you realize
they're not dull,
it was just your
misinterpretation of them.
I just haven't found a way to
make them interesting yet.
It's all about common ground. You
find one thing you both like or hate.
John Woo movies,
romance novels, kale.
Sometimes the best way
to connect with someone
is stop thinking about them
and focus on yourself.
What is this about?
Not everything has an agenda.
See ya.
I told him because
it was the right thing to do.
Right.
This doesn't change
anything between us.
It sort of does for me.
You want to stop
seeing each other?
No.
But I was thinking, maybe you could
tell your husband that we did.
And then go back to sneaking
around behind his back?
Yes.
Why would you want to do that?
I don't know.
This just feels wrong.
I think I'm gonna go.
Oh, God!
We thought it was
the salt pork...
But all the menfolk
been eating it
and we're the only
ones that sick.
Which one of you is
the cheap bastard?
Your uniforms are not wool They're
polyester, cheap polyester.
Which gets processed with a
heavy metal called antimony.
You wear badly
processed polyester
all day and night
for days and nights,
and you get antimony poisoning
which causes your diarrhea
and your numbness in your hands
and your collective vomiting.
Polyester uniforms?
I was being authentic.
With polyester uniforms?
Confederacy gave men $21
every six months for uniforms...
You poisoned us both.
At least I have principles.
Because they don't
cost anything.
Brother against brother.
Now that is authentic.
I know you don't want me here,
but they had banana
muffins downstairs.
Reminded me of
our St. Pete's trip.
Remember?
We used to walk and get some
every morning at that bakery.
I guess.
Were you high on that trip?
Not when we were together.
I used to wait
until you went to bed.
You can stay,
if you want.
Okay.
Mmm.
It's not bad.
What's happening?
Is this from
the alcohol treatment?
I was wrong. The berry
aneurysm must have just burst.
Temporal lobes are clear.
Parietal clear.
Get me a micro-vascular clip
tray as well as the occlusion.
Check the ventricles.
Ventricles are clear, too.
Aneurysm must've
leaked instead of burst.
Inject the dye.
Posterior cerebral clear. Vertebral clear.
Circle of Willis also clear.
She doesn't have
a berry aneurysm.
Her BP is dropping.
Start her on pressors.
Get her BP up before her
organs start shutting down.
Adams. With me.
The pressors will only give us
a couple hours, max.
What causes breathing issues,
bleeding issues, paralysis,
loss of consciousness?
What are we missing?
That's everything bad that's happened.
What about the good stuff'?
You mean, like,
we should be more optimistic?
She got a little better
when we put her on steroids,
which can attack tumor cells.
Maybe she has cancer.
No hypercalcaemia,
no elevated blood proteins.
She and her mom mentioned a trip they
took to Florida a couple of years ago.
What about dengue fever?
Cholera?
Great ideas. If dengue fever or cholera laid
in wail for two years before suddenly...
Did your biological daughter
go swimming in Florida?
In a lake, or a pond,
or an everglade?
Yeah, there's a canal
near my mother's house.
Do you know
what's wrong with her?
Family vacations kill.
Come with me. Don't want
to explain this twice.
You're letting in the flies.
And she needs an LVAD.
No, she doesn't.
Your daughter has ascariasis.
It's a disease caused by a
parasitic worm found in feces.
Animals used
the canal as a potty,
and the eggs from the feces
ended up in Callie's intestine
when she went swimming.
Where they hung out, quietly and
asymptomatically biding their time.
Until somewhere along the way,
they got knocked loose,
maybe a dive in
volleyball practice,
or maybe she slipped on her
way into a soup kitchen.
But once they hatched, the worms
got to work on her lungs,
her ear, and the nerves
in her legs.
The worms got agitated
by the steroids we gave her,
which started them on their
journey to the esophagus.
And, ultimately, to the heart.
A few pills of mebendazole,
and she'll be fine.
She's feeling much better,
walking on her own.
Getting along with her mother?
As long as I keep
bringing her muffins.
Did someone come
take her for a test?
Callie agrees with you.
That people don't change.
She said when her mom slips again,
she didn't want to be there.
She'd rather remember
her like she is now.
Smart girl.
You got the ending you wanted.
Because I was only looking to
solve the case, not their lives.
I don't care if the people who
work for me are screwed up,
in fact I even encourage it,
but absolution,
do that on your own time.
Or not at all.
Cause clearly you suck at it.
This is Aaron Rodgers.
Wow, 127 quarterback rating.
Do you know what
sound he makes?
Okay. Ow!
Um...
This is Terrell Owens.
People call him T.O.
Do you know what
sound he makes?
This is Mark Sanchez.
Do you know what sound
people make about him?
Working late?
Husband have her tonight?
And every night.
She broke it off.
It's for the best.
I'm not really
an affair guy after all.
Sure you are, buddy.
You just lost interest once
it stopped being an affair.
That's why you're relieved.
But don't worry,
it's not gonna end here.
You'll just have to get your
adrenaline fix somewhere else.
When that
doesn't do it anymore,
you'll just
escalate things somehow.
At least that's
what I've been told.
I'm not like you, House.
True. No limp.