It was very still, except for the tree toads
and frogs in the brook, peeping.
And every little while, Mabel could hear
strange rustlings in the leaves.
She tried to remember the way home,
but the woods looked so different now.
She couldn't think which way to go.
She began to be frightened.
What's that?, said Mabel.
Oh, I'm so frightened.
In a minute or two,
she heard the howl again.
A long, wild cry.
She began to run,
but the poor thing had lost her way.
Is she gonna be okay?
- She'll be fine, Jimmy.
- How do you know?
Just listen. You'll see.
It was so dark that she stumbled over
the bushes and the roots...
Okay. I gotta go down.
Kim.
I know.
Does she need to spend the night?
Once this is done, she'll be discharged.
Good.
Lawsuits. Threats. Recriminations.
This is a situation
no firm ever wants to be in.
It's... Well, it's embarrassing.
I know we all want a swift resolution here.
So, what are our options?
Take it to trial. Expensive.
And extremely damaging
for HHM's reputation.
Not my first choice, or yours, I imagine.
The firm could choose to buy me out...
for an amount that is almost certain
to bankrupt it.
I spent decades building this firm.
I don't want to be the agent
of its destruction.
There is a third option.
There's no reason we can't
put all this unpleasantness behind us...
and continue on as we have been.
I'm willing to let bygones be bygones.
And if you agree...
I think we can settle all this right now
with a simple handshake.
Would you all give us the room
for a moment?
Seventeen years.
Eighteen in July, actually.
All those years
we built this place together.
And all that time I've supported you...
looked up to you, deferred to you.
Because I always thought you had
the best interests of the firm in mind.
I have.
You did.
For a long time.
But you've let personal vendettas
turn your focus away...
from what's best for HHM.
You've put your needs first.
- To our detriment.
- I don't think that's accurate.
And the moment that I mildly suggest,
with empathy and concern...
that maybe it's time for you
to consider retirement...
the first instinct you have
is to sue me?
To sue the firm?
Well, I...
I don't even know...
In what world is that anything
but the deepest betrayal...
of everything we worked
so hard to accomplish?
In what world is that anything but
the deepest betrayal of our friendship?
I could argue that you're the one
who betrayed me.
That's bullshit.
And you know it.
This is pointless.
Here. Just take this.
Three million dollars?
The first of three payments,
as per the partnership agreement.
The firm can't afford this. Are you...?
- You're not shutting down, are you?
- I would never endanger the firm.
This is mostly from my personal funds.
And a few loans.
You're paying me
out of your own pocket?
You won.
There's one last thing.
Everybody.
Thank you for gathering.
I have some bittersweet news to share.
I'm sorry to say, but our fearless leader,
Charles McGill...
will be leaving HHM,
effective immediately.
I wanted to take this moment
to thank Chuck...
for everything he's done for HHM.
We started off with six employees...
and Chuck helped grow us into
one of the largest firms in the state.
We will be forever grateful
for his dedication.
Do you have anything
you want to say?
All right then. Let's give him a hand.
Hey.
Morning.
Close.
Gatorade. You need electrolytes.
You hungry?
I'll make you something.
Be right back. Finish that.
Hey.
I said I'd bring it to you.
I needed to stretch my legs.
Sit. Eggs.
- This is twisted.
- Oh, thanks.
This one-handed crap
is gonna get real old, real fast.
Is there coffee?
Sure. But more Gatorade first.
All right, your two options are...
good old ibuprofen, which, yeah,
should take the edge off...
or the proverbial good stuff.
The answer is always the good stuff.
All right, but food first.
You're not feeding me, Jimmy.
There are lines we do not cross.
I was looking into
our lease on the office.
We'd definitely take a haircut
if we broke it.
But we are allowed to sublet.
Might be our best option.
The furniture's mostly rented
month to month...
so that's not an issue.
For you, I think you need a desk,
some file cabinets.
A Westlaw terminal.
And I haven't figured out Francesca yet,
that's another conversation.
All that sound okay?
Are you sure about this?
I mean,
even with the Sandpiper money?
Look...
after everything...
I don't give a shit about the office.
So can I start looking for a tenant?
Yeah. Yeah.
- I could've killed someone, Jimmy.
- Yeah. Yourself.
I worked most of the last week
on maybe six hours of sleep, and then I...
I crossed three lanes of traffic
and I don't remember any of it.
Look, you were just doing
what you thought you had to do.
Because of me.
You didn't make me get in that car.
That was all me.
I'm an adult. I made a choice.
Hey.
All I can say is, I am gonna fix things.
Okay, so we're gonna
do everything around back.
It's mostly commercial around here,
so it's quiet at night.
We pull the trucks up to the doors,
we unload right into the shop.
We can break down the stuff in here.
There's space in the back
for storing scales and supplies...
when the shop's open.
Should be able
to process everything overnight.
- I'll be here to see it gets done right.
- Where's, eh, Papi?
I'll be taking care of all this.
But he's good.
Once we get everything packed,
Arturo will pick up and supervise distro...
make sure everything's clear.
Here's Papi.
Don Hector.
This is my father, Manuel.
Dad, Don Hector Salamanca.
Relax. We're friends.
Better?
Please, get out of my store.
Dad, please.
Don Hector is being very generous.
Don't be disrespectful.
Think about Aunt Rosa and the twins.
Mama's family in Galeana.
Please.
He's old-fashioned. He'll come around.
Don Hector.
I'll talk to him. He'll come around.
I don't trust him.
These are from Kevin and Paige.
Well, I guess they're from everybody
at Mesa Verde.
And there's a card
somewhere in here.
Here.
- You brought the book?
- Sure.
Mr Gatwood.
The card wasn't clear, but I'm pretty sure
you're getting steaks too.
- Really?
- Texas.
He wishes you a speedy recovery.
You are so lucky.
I used to drive that highway
every weekend...
to visit my brother and his kids...
and I saw an accident
almost every single time.
People die on that road all the time.
I already rescheduled
everything you had this week.
But I didn't touch that meeting
with the regulator.
I know that whole Utah timeline
is delicate.
- All right. It's next Wednesday, right?
- Yes.
There's a lot of prep that we pushed...
so you could focus on getting
Mr Gatwood up by the end of the quarter.
Which isn't happening now.
Actually, I talked with Colleen...
and she said everyone's fine
doing that meeting Monday.
So, you know,
that means we could still slide in...
just under the deadline.
Did you bring a breakdown
of the documents I'll need?
- I would have to figure out...
- Yep.
how long that'll take me.
That's a quarter to 6, 7...
Go to 11.
I found it. Here you go.
And Paige's timeline's on the top.
Kim?
You okay? I can always come back.
I'm gonna need you to cancel Gatwood
and push everything else.
- What? Everything?
- Yeah. Everything.
- Okay.
- But first, could you give me a ride?
Absolutely. Where to?
Ms Wexler sends her apologies,
Mr Gatwood.
And she feels terrible about this,
but with her accident and the recovery...
she's just not gonna be able
to finish her work for you in time.
Oh, of course, I'll tell her.
And again, she is very sorry...
and I know she'll be giving you
a call herself soon.
Well, yes.
Ms Wexler did ask me to tell you...
she strongly recommends
Schweikart & Cokely.
They're an exceptional firm.
Okay.
Well, I will send that info over today...
and Ms Wexler
will follow up herself shortly.
- Thanks for the meat.
- And she says thank you for the steaks.
She's so excited to fire up that grill.
Thank you. Bye.
Okay, how many do I have?
Nine.
Good.
It's Jimmy.
I know you don't wanna see me,
but I just want to know you're okay.
Come on, Chuck.
I just want to see your face.
Come on, Chuck. I just need a minute.
I just need to know you're all right.
I'm all right, Jimmy.
Hey. Good.
I'm glad you're all right. I...
Can I come in? Talk for a minute?
As you can see, I'm more than all right.
I'm very well, in fact.
How...?
I always told you I'd get better.
You just never believed me.
Sure I did.
But, Chuck, this is great.
How did you do it?
What was it you wanted?
Beyond proof of life?
Something happened...
and it made me think about
what went down between you and me.
And...
So I wanted to say, in hindsight,
I could've made different choices.
- Is that so?
- Yeah.
I mean, I'm not saying it's all on me.
It's not.
But if I had to do it all over again...
I would maybe do some things
differently.
And I just thought
you should know that.
That you have regrets?
Yeah. I have regrets.
Why?
Well, because you're my brother.
There aren't that many
of us McGills left...
and I think we should stick together.
No. Why have regrets at all?
What's the point?
- What do you mean?
- Well, look at you.
You're in so much pain.
Why are you putting yourself
through all this?
- Because I wanted to tell you...
- That you have regrets.
And I'm telling you don't bother.
What's the point?
- You're just gonna keep hurting people.
- That's not true.
Jimmy, this is what you do.
You hurt people.
Over and over and over.
And then there's this show of remorse.
- It's not a show.
- I know you don't think it's a show.
I don't doubt your emotions are real...
but what's the point of all the sad faces
and the gnashing of teeth?
If you're not going to change
your behaviour, and you won't...
- I can change...
- why not just skip the whole exercise?
In the end,
you're gonna hurt everyone around you.
You can't help it.
So stop apologising and accept it.
Embrace it.
Frankly, I'd have more respect for you
if you did.
What about you, Chuck?
You didn't do anything wrong?
You're just an innocent victim?
Let me put your mind at ease, Jimmy.
You don't have to make up with me.
We don't have to understand
each other.
Things are fine the way they are.
Hey.
I don't want to hurt your feelings...
but the truth is you've never mattered
all that much to me.
Gold comforter. Green chair.
Brown journal.
Jimmy. What a nice surprise.
Irene, as beautiful as ever.
Why don't you come in?
Can I get you some tea?
Oh, I don't want to be a bother.
I just have a couple things to drop off.
What is all this?
Well, when we win, we celebrate.
That's very sweet.
Yes, and I didn't forget
about Oscar and Felix.
I've got some kitty toys and catnip
in there for those two little rascals.
- You shouldn't have, Jimmy.
- Of course I should.
Now, have you given any thought...
to how you wanna spend
that settlement money?
I don't know.
I can tell you what I'd do.
Alaskan cruise.
You can walk on a glacier
under the Aurora Borealis.
And if Alaska's too cold,
maybe a European river cruise.
Float on down the Danube.
You and the ladies
could split a deluxe suite.
Get into all sorts of trouble.
That sounds very nice...
but I don't think they'd really want to.
Why not?
They're still...
upset.
They must be excited
about the settlement though, right?
You can't let one little misunderstanding
destroy years of friendship.
Oh, it's just not the same, Jimmy.
She showed her true colours.
When it came to that settlement, we were
the furthest things from her mind.
It just took her a bit to realise
what was important to you.
She came around.
She just wanted to get back
on our good side.
Okay, how do you trust someone
who bends any way the wind is blowing?
Where is her integrity?
Well, I can't help but blame myself.
- You were just trying to help.
- No.
I stuck my nose in where it didn't belong
and I stirred the pot.
So...
Look, if you wanna blame someone...
you should blame me.
Jimmy, you're a good friend.
She doesn't deserve you.
No, she doesn't.
Yes, I've shut off all the breakers.
Yes, I have checked. Several times.
The power meter is still turning.
There's something in the house
that isn't wired through the breaker box...
and it's drawing power.
Well, I want you to send someone over
to find it and disconnect it.
Wednesday? I can't wait that long.
Are you sure there's nothing sooner?
Wednesday then.
Yes, hello, this is Charles McGill.
I have a 3:00 with Dr Cruz today.
Yes, well, would you tell her
that something's come up...
and I'm not able to come in today?
No, no need to reschedule.
I'll just see her next week.
Thank you. Bye.
Good.
You got my message.
Yeah.
You strapped?
They're coming.
Don Hector.
Don Eladio wanted me
to speak with you face to face...
so there's no misunderstanding.
From now on...
there will be only one route
over the border for our product.
The chicken trucks.
And that is final.
But you must understand
this is for efficiency only.
There's no disrespect to you
or your family.
What's he doing here?
The boss wants you to settle this.
I settle it right now, okay?
You have to work together.
It's what the boss wants.
The boss can suck me.
- I'd watch what I say if I were you.
- Who do you think you are?
You should be kissing my ass right now.
Me and my family?
We built this whole business.
We all did. Together.
No, no! Salamanca did!
Salamanca money!
- Salamanca blood!
- You have to calm down.
That hacienda! I paid for it.
And you treat us like dogs.
Hector, this isn't personal.
It is! It is personal!
Call 911.
Stash the guns.
You should not be here
when they arrive.
Yeah, I need an ambulance.
Outside a garage at the corner
of Aztec and Jordan.
My boss collapsed.
He's having a heart attack.
Come on.
Be advised, we have one adult male...
Does he have a history
of cardiac issues?
Yeah.
And was he taking any medications?
He took these.
Thanks.
We're headed to Lovelace
if you'd like to follow.
- Hey.
How's Relax-O-Thon 2003
coming along?
No complaints. Join me.
Oh, dip it in the sauce.
- It seems like overkill.
- Trust me.
So, what's next?
Monty Python.
Solid choice.
Or we could just watch
To Kill a Mockingbird again.
- Again?
- Yeah, I watched it this morning.
It was my favourite when I was a kid.
I loved Atticus Finch.
All the girls were in love with
Gregory Peck.
No, I wasn't in love with him.
Well, a little, but...
No, I wanted to be him.
Fight the good fight, change the world?
Yeah. Didn't you?
That was more Chuck's thing.
But, I mean, the good news
is you made it.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
I'm changing the world
by helping a mid-size local bank...
become a mid-size regional bank.
Yay me.
So...
No luck with Mrs Landry?
Shit, that bridge is burned.
Ashes.
It's that bad?
No putting that genie
back in the bottle.
And I've tried everything.
I sent muffin baskets to the gals.
- I signed them from her.
- Nice.
They saw right through it.
Oh, Jimmy, you're too nice.
Jimmy, she doesn't deserve you.
The more I try to make them like her...
the more they end up
loving me instead.
Well, sounds like you've exhausted
all your options.
- If muffin baskets don't solve it...
- I don't know what else to do.
I'm not good at building shit,
you know?
I'm excellent at tearing it down.
Oh, rookie move.
What the...?
- It's already cheese.
- It's cheese on cheese.
See?
You know, sometimes you gotta
play to your strengths.
- You should stitch that on a pillow.
- Oh, I will.
All right, screw it.
Mockingbird encore it is.
No.
Oh, shit.
What? What is it?
Mrs Landry.
You figured it out?
Yeah.
But I really, really don't wanna do it.
- Hello. Hi there.
- Jimmy.
Jimmy.
Okey-dokey.
Testing, testing.
- Good morning.
I know many of you were expecting
Sandy for this morning's chair yoga...
but her daughter has a cold.
She'll be fine.
The nice folks in front
said I could sit in.
So you guys ready to get to it?
Yeah.
Okay, let's wake up those spines
with a cat-cow position.
Very good cat.
And then cow.
Sit up straight. Very good, Jasper.
Cat.
And cow.
Long, deep breaths.
Breathe in through the nose
and out through the mouth.
And cow.
And cat...
Mr McGill.
Erin Brill!
You're just in time for chair yoga.
I need to talk to you.
Well, pull up a chair.
There's always room for one more.
Now, Mr McGill.
- What?
- You are unbelievable.
I could not for the life of me figure out
why Mrs Landry...
would suddenly change her mind
about the Sandpiper settlement.
I had to drag the information out.
You filled her and all of her
friends' heads with lies.
I never lied to anyone.
You drastically misrepresented
the reality of the case.
- So?
- So?!
You took advantage of Mrs Landry.
Does she know
how much money you're gonna make?
Nope. And again, I ask, so what?
These people trusted you, Jimmy.
Do you have any idea
how much time I had to put in...
listening to their ramblings
about their sciatica...
or which grandchild
disappoints them?
Damn right they trust me.
- I worked my ass off earning their trust.
- Then you betrayed it.
If the only thing standing between me and
a million bucks is some old lady's tears...
I'd suggest investing in Kleenex.
You ruined her life
because you wanted your money.
Boo and hoo.
Besides, it's not like she's got
that much time left, anyway.
You're disgusting.
And rich.
Hey, everyone. Apologies.
That was probably more like 20 breaths
instead of 10...
I don't see a lot of
forward folding going on.
Come on, girls.
Shame on you.
So?
- Like a charm. Yeah.
- She'll go back on the settlement?
I imagine you'll hear from her
within an hour or so.
- Good.
- Hey.
Well done in there.
I meant every word I said.
I know.
Thank you.
- You got the address?
- Yep.
- Okay, I'll meet you guys there in an hour.
- Sounds good.
Hey. You guys about done?
Yep.
Listen, I...
I'm real sorry that this didn't work out.
It's fine.
I already talked to my old supervisor.
Looks like they can take me back, so...
Oh, that's great.
And, you know,
if we ever get another office up...
you'd be our first call.
Yeah, okay.
Good to know.
- Bye, Kim.
- Oh, bye.
She understands.
So what's left?
Think this is it.
This is all admin stuff...
Appointment book. Your rolodex.
Hey, why'd you do that?
Because no senior's coming
within 20 feet of me ever again.
I'm gonna need
a whole new business model...
when I get my licence back.
Kim, it's pointless.
They're smearing my name
across the tristate area...
sending telegrams
to everyone far and near.
You never know.
It's a good wall.
- You think?
- Yeah.
We'll get another.
A better wall.
Ready?
Let's go home.