Let there be light.
And then there was light.
Jeez, will you look at this.
That's where your mom used to work.
- Right back there doing the books.
- Yeah, whatever.
Hey, remember when
we used to ditch fourth...
come in the back door?
Tell your folks it was a free period?
- O'Dell's Algebra Two.
- Mr O'Dell.
Man, that guy was a butthole.
And your mom,
I think she knew we were skipping...
but she'd always stop what was
doing, give me a pack of Little Debbies.
I think all those Little Debbies
put them out of business.
How'd you get up there
when you were a kid?
A couple of milk crates, you know.
All right.
No, no, no.
Nope.
Boom. Indian head penny.
All right.
That's worth about three bucks.
We polish it up, run the coin game.
Nice. We get 150 bucks easy.
A hundred fifty? We got 110
for a plain vanilla half dollar.
This, this is actually rare.
I mean, you can see it, you know?
Three hundred, easy.
Three hundred. Me likey.
Now you're gonna tell me what your
coin collection was doing up there.
It's a long story...
Let's get out of here.
- All right. Now let's hit it.
- No. There might be another one.
All right. Then give.
What's the deal with the coins?
Well...
I was what, 12 or so.
I was working the register.
A guy comes in...
and buys a box of Ivory Flakes
and a sixer of Old Style.
He pays with
a couple bucks and this.
The second I see it,
I know what it is.
It's a George Washington silver.
I tell my dad, Pop, this quarter is rare.
It's worth four bucks.
I barely get the words out of my mouth,
he hightails it out to give it back.
He can't find the guy, so he tapes it
to the side of the register.
He's hoping that this guy
will come back so he can return it.
He starts talking about giving it to
Father Mahoney for the poor box...
so I make it disappear.
Then after that, every day after school,
I'm checking the till.
Something catches my eye, I stick it
in the box, put it up there for good luck.
So much for good luck.
It's a crying shame they lost this place.
They never should've
bought it in the first place.
My dad didn't have it in him.
What do you mean?
Your folks worked so hard.
Yeah, they worked hard.
They worked a lot of hours for
a lot of years for nothing.
I don't know, Jimmy.
A lot of customers, everybody liked them.
Everybody liked him because
he was a soft touch, you know?
Every deadbeat in the neighbourhood
owed him money.
You come in with a sob story...
you leave with a pat on the back
and a gallon of milk.
He could've made it work.
He could've sold beer and cigarettes
to the kids from Mary-Margaret's...
but, oh, no, not him.
He was never gonna do
what he had to do.
How'd you know there'd be another?
Okay.
Banquet's over.
Those conventioneers...
been talking farm equipment
for 10 hours straight.
Now they want to party.
Gonna be a big night, my friend.
- What do you say? Time to get moving?
- Let's go.
Yeah, tribal police?
Yeah, I was out on
your property this afternoon.
I found a dead body.
Off the old post road.
Out in the scrub. It was past
the Oasis Motel billboard.
I was out with my metal detector
looking for arrowheads.
No, I don't want to give my name.
I was trespassing.
Look, you better send someone out there
to find him before the coyotes do.
Over here, I've recorded
the location of the incident.
That is where I was
physically when it began.
This column gives approximate origin.
And as you can see,
much of the time...
I couldn't be sure,
so I just wrote ambient.
And of course, I've recorded
the times and dosages of the medicine.
- This is very impressive, Charles.
- And look at the trend.
Day one, pain of seven and eight,
even eight point five.
Day three,
nothing higher than five and a quarter.
And now, it's all threes and fours.
Later, I'd like to give you
some exercises and strategies...
that might help even more.
I'm all ears.
How do you see your next steps?
Well, clearly with this kind of
improvement...
it won't be long before I'm back to
work full time with no accommodations.
And then soon after,
I'm gonna get back into court.
I haven't argued a case
in almost three years, so that's next.
And I'm gonna get these lights
turned back on.
I want this house to be full of music.
I wanna have a dinner party.
Or hell, no. A great big celebration.
I want 100 people in here,
spilling out onto the lawn.
I want caterers and a full bar.
I want to be surrounded
by friends and colleagues.
That's stirring.
Those are excellent goals.
Doctor, I wouldn't have believed
I could come so far so quickly.
And I have to give you
the lion's share of the credit.
Well, it's remarkable.
But Rome wasn't built in a day.
I know rushing forward may be tempting,
but it's important to give yourself time.
You've just begun a journey
that could take years.
Well, I suppose...
but surely you'd admit
that every case is different.
- Of course.
- Then perhaps...
my recovery might be speedier...
than your run-of-the-mill patient.
Is that possible?
I'm just cautioning you
not to push yourself too hard.
I know... Appreciate every step forward,
but modulate your expectations.
Yes, absolutely.
Let's talk about the night
you first called me.
- You sounded very distressed.
- I was.
Using a telephone
must've been difficult for you.
I had to walk 10 blocks to a payphone.
That was extremely uncomfortable.
Probably almost a nine.
What made it so important
to talk to me that night?
I'd had an incident.
A very public incident.
Perhaps the worst experience
of my life.
It was proven to me...
in public and beyond the shadow
of a doubt, that there was a battery...
a fully charged battery...
almost next to my skin
for the better part of two hours.
And I felt nothing.
What does that mean to you?
This condition...
To me, it's as real as that chair.
It's as real as this house.
It's as real as you.
But...
what if it's not?
What if it's all in my head?
And if that's true...
if it's not real...
then what have I done?
It's all in the storyboards.
Get set for the master shot. Okay?
Looking good. We about ready?
- Just about.
- I gotta hand it to you. I...
This is the busiest weekday
we've had in the last six months.
And are people
mentioning the commercial?
You know what, they are.
- Excellent.
- I know.
Oh, here's your partner. Hey, get him
into make-up. We can carve this turkey.
Okay, listen.
Excuse me. Not now.
- It's fine.
- Sorry.
I just got off the phone with the station.
- You don't even work for them.
- I never said I worked for the station.
Saul Goodman Productions?
Remember?
You work with us, you don't have to
deal with the bureaucrats at KWBV.
- We take care of everything.
- Okay.
Remind me, how much
is all this gonna cost?
Exactly what we talked about
the other day.
The first one was gratis.
That's my treat.
Now we're moving on
to the elite package.
Seven commercials for
the heavily discounted price of $6500.
Yeah, the station just
quoted me $450 per.
- Four hundred and fifty dollars?
- That's for airtime only.
Call the station.
Ask them how much
they charge for production...
of seven top-flight TV commercials.
Okay, but why do we need
seven new ones in the first place?
Yeah, what's to stop us...
from paying the station to just
keep running the one we have?
That's not what we agreed to.
How about that for starters?
- He did give us the first one for free.
- Yeah, I know.
Okay, how about this?
How about we pay you
450 for the one that already aired...
and then we take it from there.
Guys, I don't wanna
get technical on you.
But that commercial,
it doesn't actually belong to you.
It's the real and intellectual property
of Saul Goodman Productions.
- I don't think so. I mean, it's our faces.
- It's our store.
And it's my commercial, and you can't
run it without my permission.
- Okay.
- Okay. Wanna play it like that? Okay.
Four hundred and fifty dollars
is now off the table.
- Yeah, and that crew of yours...
- Yeah.
Just a bunch of UNM students.
- We can get those.
- We can get students.
- We can get students. We could...
- Yes, we can.
- Reshoot the ad.
- Yes.
- And then run that.
- Guys, guys, come on.
You wouldn't even be thinking
about a commercial if it wasn't for me.
Okay, we are not
gonna pay you $6,500...
for something
we can do ourselves, you got it?
Seriously?
- Seriously.
Excuse us.
Hello there.
Anything we can help you with?
- Put that camera back up. Roll it.
- It's not gonna do a damn thing.
Don't give me any lip, okay? Just roll it.
Make sure it's pointed in my direction.
It's all about output. What you get
out of it is what you put into it.
- If you're gigging a lot...
- Are you gigging a lot?
Hey, sorry to interrupt. I just wanna
make sure there's no wiggle room here.
We are with customers right now.
Please, all right, just go. Thank you.
Okay, well, best of luck
in all your future endeavours.
- Go. Goodbye.
- Go.
- Sorry about that.
Oh, my gosh. Are you okay?
It was a drumstick.
It was laying loose in the aisle.
- Somebody call an ambulance.
- No, you don't need to.
I don't need...
Yes, an ambulance.
That's a good idea.
You guys have
liability insurance, right?
To our Four Corners strategy.
- Cheers to that.
- Cheers.
I'm not saying this to rush you,
I have a 2:45 tee time at Four Hills...
so don't let me get long-winded.
I've heard the water gets tricky
on the back nine there.
You heard right.
I didn't know you played.
Well, growing up where I did,
there was nothing else to do.
We ought to be having
this meeting out on the fairway.
I think Kim has a lot to cover.
Speaking of which,
I'm sorry, but I gotta ask.
I got a friend, Billy Gatwood.
He's a driller,
has a small operation over near Farwell.
Anyway, poor bastard's
tangled up in some kind of...
interstate wrangle between
Texas and New Mexico.
Now, I can't make heads or tails of it,
and neither can he.
His lawyer was a local guy,
completely over his head.
So Billy's fired the guy,
but he doesn't know...
whether to shit or wind his watch,
pardon my French.
Anyhow, I told him about
the job you're doing for us.
I know he'd love to talk to you.
It's got the beauty of Montana, but you
don't have to wait in the lift lines.
Oh, wow,
I can't tell you how flattering that is.
Remember, Kim's got her hands full
with Utah and Colorado.
As far as I'm concerned, she's proven
she can field whatever we throw at her.
Kevin, your faith in me is...
It's...
It means a lot, but when we first
started working together...
I promised you Mesa Verde
would be my sole focus, and I meant it.
- Sure, but I gotta...
- Hey, there.
- I thought I saw some familiar faces.
- Howard.
Kim, sit. I insist.
- Kevin.
- Howard.
Paige. Always wonderful to see you.
- You too, Howard. How have you been?
- Fantastic. Thank you.
All is well with the expansion?
You got that branch approved
on your original timeline after all.
We did, thanks to Ms Wexler here.
Kim's one of the best.
You're lucky to have her.
She sure is, we sure are.
Seems like just yesterday,
she was logging hours in doc review.
Always a pleasure to see
one of our protégés...
spread her wings
and leave the nest.
Well, I'll get out of your hair.
Best of luck to all of you.
You too, Howard.
I appreciate we got you all to ourselves,
Billy just needs a consultation.
I'm so sorry but...
Would you excuse me
for just a moment?
Sure.
I've had the salmon. If you like
sea scallops, they're fantastic.
- Kim, hello again.
- Howard, sit. I insist.
Sorry to interrupt.
I just needed to give Howard something.
Folks, this is Kim Wexler,
a former member of our firm.
Kim, this is the team
from O'Malley Industries.
Oh, of course. I remember Lauren.
Good to see you.
This is Jack Sweet, our new CFO.
- Hello.
- Pleasure.
Nice to see you too. Henry. Nick.
- Marie Austin. Good to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
Good to see all of you.
Have a wonderful lunch, Howard.
- Sorry to hold things up.
- Not at all.
Okay, Kevin, if you want to
give me Mr Gatwood's number...
I'd be happy to speak to him.
That's great.
Once I understand, I'll put him with
a firm that'll take very good care of him.
I leave it in your capable hands.
Great. Okay, Utah.
The good news is
the filing requirements...
are very similar to
what we submitted for Arizona.
Thanks again. I'll let Billy know
you'll be calling. We'll talk tee time soon.
- Sounds good.
- See you soon.
Bye.
Here.
- What the hell is this?
- I think it's pretty self-explanatory.
Look, Howard, you were very generous
when I left HHM.
It never sat right
that you covered my loans.
Seemed to sit right at the time.
I appreciate the gift, but now I'm able
to afford it, I wanna pay you back.
- Well, you appreciate the gift.
- Yes, I do.
You know what I'm doing in there?
Take a guess.
I'm doing damage control.
I'm doing it three meals a day for
the past two weeks with every client.
I am trying to repair
the reputation of the firm...
after you and Jimmy
dragged it through the mud.
I did everything in my power
to defend my client.
- Is that what you're calling it?
- That's the job, Howard.
It was very convenient for you to
ignore Chuck's illness when it suited you.
I take you out of the mailroom,
put you through law school, mentor you.
You leave and stab me in the back,
that's my fault? I'm not cashing this.
Kim, your debt is forgiven.
But anything else, that's on you.
All we did was show
the situation for what it is.
And if you're hiding that
from your clients...
well, Howard, that's on you.
- Nacho.
- Hey, Papa.
You're here early, son.
Yeah, thought
I'd get a jump on the invoices.
Nice to see you taking
an interest in the business.
I'm gonna start on the Continental.
Grab some of the golden doeskin
vinyl and give me a hand.
Yes, Papa, I'll be right there.
Blue shirt.
Yellow wall.
Silver door.
White sign.
Red pepper.
Purple sweater.
Brown wood.
Black mat.
Jason to the front
for carryout assistance.
Yellow bananas.
Green grapes.
Orange oranges.
Excuse me,
where would I find the soy milk?
Over there and to the left,
just past the freezer aisle.
A white ceiling.
Green basket.
Grey floor.
- All set?
- Yeah.
Courier on the way?
- Twenty minutes.
- Great.
They'll need this back
at Gatwood Oil by EOD.
What's...?
Hey.
What's up?
New guitar.
Check it out.
That is something.
I sold the rest of my ads.
That must be a relief.
They loved the response they got.
So impressed,
they threw in this baby.
Signed by the one and only
Ritchie Blackmore.
And lying on the floor helps you
with your fingering?
- I fell.
- What?
It was during productions.
Crazy stuff happens.
Long story. But the big picture...
I'm up one guitar.
When did this happen?
- Yesterday.
- I saw you yesterday. You were fine.
That was Tuesday.
You picked up clean clothes.
Remember?
Did you go to the doctor?
Oh, it's... it's not as bad as it looks.
I just need to rest it.
It'll be fine.
Look on the desk.
There's something for you.
Yeah, that.
Open it.
That's my half.
It's good for the next six weeks.
So at least we can stop
talking about that.
- Jimmy, I wasn't...
- Just take it so we're square, all right?
Okay.
Sorry.
Just, my back hurts like hell and...
People suck.
Jimmy, you...
You don't have to
push yourself like this.
You could rest.
Let your back heal.
Then go to community service
and get it over with.
Take some time.
Plan your next move.
Meaning...?
I'm saying...
I could cover
our expenses for a while.
- You got the cash in your hand.
- I know...
- Why are we talking about this?
- I looked at the numbers. I can carry us.
Not forever, but at least
until you're back to 100 percent.
I appreciate the thought, but no.
I'll do what I have to do
to take care of my half.
You do what you have to do
to take care of yours. End of story.
Okay.
I mean, you believe me, right?
Yes.
Feel better, Jimmy.
Francesca, is it too late
to get ahold of the courier?
I can call. Need to reschedule?
No, cancel it.
And get Billy Gatwood
on the phone for me.
- Will do.
- Thanks.
I've got Billy Gatwood on the line.
Great. Put him through.
Mr Gatwood? Hi, Kim Wexler.
Listen, I've been reviewing
your documents...
and I thought I might've had to
refer you to a colleague...
but I think I may have a solution
to your problem myself.
Do you think you have some time
this week we could sit down and talk?
- Chuck.
- Howard.
- What a nice surprise.
- I knocked, but there was no answer.
Thought you were asleep.
Figured I'd wait, in case...
- Are those groceries?
- They are.
I decided to go for a little walk.
That's great, Chuck.
- Why don't you come on in?
- Thank you.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
I wish it was a social call,
but unfortunately we have an issue...
- we need to discuss.
- What's that?
It concerns your
malpractice insurance.
There's...
Well, we should sit and talk it through.
You're good.
Cool.
See you, Nacho.
Don Hector.
What?
This one looks funny.
Bring it here.
You see? Is it fake?
No, it's fine.
I'm so sorry, Don Hector.
Carlos.
Nacho.
I'm heavy.
Took care of that problem over on Fifth.
- That crew won't bother us no more.
- Do me a favour. Shut up.
You're good.
Okay.
See you next week.
Don Hector, more espresso?
McGill.
Keep it moving.
Sir? Sir?
- What's up?
- Hey...
It's my kid. Her mom just called.
You're not supposed to be
on the phone.
I know, I know, but she's sick.
She caught pneumonia at day care.
She's in the hospital. Please can I go?
Sure. You can go.
But you're not getting credit.
Come on, can't I just go
and come right back?
I have to get my hours done this week.
Judge says so.
Judge told you, huh?
Sounds like that's on you.
Hey, you wanna get out of here?
How much is it worth to you?
What?
To ditch this.
How much?
Leave me alone, yo.
Come on, you want to get
to your deal or what?
Hey, man,
I was trying to see my sick kid.
No, you're trying to sell something
you shouldn't have...
to someone
who shouldn't be buying it.
Hey, no judgements, all right?
Man's gotta make a living.
I'm just saying, the way you make yours
rhymes with mug mealer.
- What are you, a narc?
- I'm the guy...
who's gonna get you out
and keep your hours.
- Yeah. How you gonna do that?
- Yeah.
Let me worry about the how, okay?
Just...
Seven hundred bucks
and you're gone.
I don't have 700 bucks.
Yeah, you got a couple of grand
in your sock.
Seven hundred bucks,
and you can get me out of here?
All right. You can do it,
you got a deal.
Okay.
Go pick up trash. Go on.
What the hell's this?
Resting. I hurt my back.
Get up.
Nope. My back's killing me.
Suit yourself.
You're not getting your hours.
I'm pretty sure
you're gonna give me my hours.
Oh, yeah?
How do you figure that?
Because if you don't,
I'm gonna sue you.
Hate to break it to you, smart guy,
but you signed a waiver.
I signed a waiver with the city.
But I'm not suing the city.
I'm suing you. Personally.
You can't do that.
Buddy...
This is the land of the free
and home of the lawsuit.
I sure as shooting can.
You know what?
I think I'll bring that guy
in with me.
Make it a class action thing.
What's he got to do with it?
You knowingly prevented him
from visiting his child in the hospital.
If that isn't intentional infliction
of emotional distress, what is?
That's crazy.
Crazy hasn't even started.
I can also sue you for failure to approve
community service hours.
That's a direct violation of your duties
as an agent of the state of New Mexico.
I'm only doing my job.
And just for tickles,
maybe I throw in failure to treat...
and mitigate damages
suffered by me...
due to injuries sustained
under your watch.
- Injury?
- My back.
You're full of shit. The waiver clearly...
That waiver's gonna make
Swiss cheese look solid.
And in a personal lawsuit,
it's a fart in the wind.
You're never gonna win that.
Maybe. Maybe not.
In order to find out,
we gotta do some math.
Let's see, a lawyer's gonna cost you
about 90 bucks an hour.
You're looking at eight to 12 months
of litigation, minimum.
- I'll represent myself.
- Great.
Bring it on. You got a car?
You got a house? A pension?
Kiss it all goodbye.
Look, out here you might be
King Douche-nozzle.
But in court you are little people.
The judge and I, we'll gladly spend
the next five years in the courtroom.
But for you, it's expensive.
It's very, very expensive.
It's third mortgage expensive.
So...
I'm offering you a simple choice.
You go to your wife, explain that you're
about to lose your job...
your pension,
whatever pinhole of a reputation...
you've got at the bowling alley
on Glow-ball Sundays. Or...
let my friend here
visit his sick daughter in the hospital...
and you let me rest my back
on this sacred...
now litter-free, New Mexico soil.
Oh, and we keep our hours.
Fine.
Asshole.
Well, go on.
Get out of here.
Hey, man.
That was some
Jedi mind shit right there.
Best 700 I have ever spent.
Here you go. I'm out.
Yeah, yeah.
Yo, I'm on my way. Yeah, yeah.
I've got a problem
I think you can help me with.
I've got cash I can't spend.
About $200,000.
If anything happens to me,
my family will never see it.
Now, it seems to me...
you opened this place
to solve a similar problem.
And you think that solution...
could be applied to you.
As a one-time arrangement.
It would be unwise for us to be
publicly associated, wouldn't you agree?
Because of the Salamancas.
If they were to take notice...
there would be consequences.
For both of us.
I'm thinking a paper transaction.
Even so.
Perhaps there is a way.
One with a degree more difficulty.
But one I may be able to arrange.
Would 20 percent
overcome this difficulty?
I would not take money
from your family.