Nothing from ANPR.
The traffic cams picked it up
twice on New Park Road,
10:38, heading west
towards the high street,
11:07, coming back the other way.
Timing's fit the bombing at the toy shop.
Makes sense he'd use a stolen car.
- Do we know when it was stolen?
- No.
The owner's a Jack Graham,
22, trust fund kid.
Got pissed and jumped off a wall.
Someone nicked the car when
he was having his legs put back together,
sometime over the past eight days.
Well, canvas his neighbourhood.
This can't be a coincidence.
Find the thief, find the bomber.
It's a bit flash for
a getaway car though, isn't it?
You read the profile. He's on autopilot.
Invincible.
Thinks he can do what he likes.
No point sweeping for fibres.
It's all ashes in there.
But we found a footprint.
Size ten, trainer, wide fit.
Great. That narrows it down.
We could appeal for more information.
Blue Subaru, yellow hoodie. Might jog
someone's memory. Someone might know him.
Or he's a recluse. Lives in
the middle of nowhere, cut off.
Faceless.
Yeah, but could be worth a try though.
Worth a try. Thanks, Boyd.
Bye.
Think she'll find anything?
No.
Not in this lifetime.
Fuck!
Fuck, it's alright.
You're just having a bad dream.
We both are.
Just...
Let's go in...
Let's go inside, right?
That's it. Jesus.
Sit there. Don't move.
I'll find you a blanket.
Who... Who is it?
Who...
Who is that?
Just a spill.
An echo.
He's not here.
Are we?
These...
are my memories.
Taken from where they were supposed to be.
Lifted out of their continuity.
Sometimes...
when I'm slipping,
when the chaos pushes back,
they seem to disappear.
The tin seems empty.
But it's not empty.
And neither are you.
I always bury this tin
somewhere no one will ever find it.
It's my fail-safe.
My anchor.
What did you bury out there, Sylvia?
What were you digging for?
Hello?
Hi, Mum.
Nothing yet.
He's coming, soon.
The owner's in hospital. I checked,
two broken ankles, no deviations.
He's on the same path.
Good.
Mum?
You alright? Did you say something?
I found her out in the garden last night.
She'd wandered out.
About half-three.
What was she doing?
Digging.
She buried something out there
a long time ago.
What?
A memory.
A useful one.
It's in the bag.
I sawed off the barrel.
It's easier to conceal.
You said that she wouldn't be a problem.
And she won't. Just lock the door.
Make sure she doesn't leave.
Oh, come on, Gideon.
If she stays here, you have
to do something for me.
Right.
They're offering a reward for my arrest.
And we've got four days
to find the bomber.
If I get my face in front of
the wrong camera, then this is all over.
It means I can't leave here,
not until we're sure.
You want me to play detective?
Pick up where you left off.
Find the thief.
Find the bomber.
Lucy?
Yeah, you're asking me
to spy on a mass murderer.
I'm just...
It might be more than spying.
You'll need to protect yourself.
"Make your choice,
adventurous stranger.
Strike the bell and bide the danger.
Or wonder till it drives you mad.
What would have followed if you had."
Right, I need to make dinner.
Two more pages.
One. But it's your turn to read.
What's this?
Meredith did it for me.
She said it was okay
because it's not forever.
You can have one too.
She showed me how.
Now we have to wait.
How long?
Thirty seconds.
Oh? Is that all?
How many did she give you?
Seven, for when they rub off.
You're happy.
Is that 'cause Meredith's your girlfriend?
- She's not my girlfriend.
- No, I know, I know.
She's... She's your friend.
Maybe a best friend?
You're my best friend.
Hmm.
Strange, but real.
Unexplained phenomena,
paranormal events.
These are the true stories
that never made the headlines.
Too disturbing for the public eye.
Join us tonight as we attempt
to solve The Unsolvables.
- What is this?
- Just keep watching.
Keep an open mind.
Reincarnation.
For centuries, mankind has pondered
the question... Is there life after death?
Perhaps the answer lies in science.
Perhaps it lies in religion,
or perhaps it lies in a family home
on a quiet street in
the market town of Hackridge.
Evelyn Wiseman
began life as a happy baby,
a bright and inquisitive toddler.
But not long after
she began to speak in full sentences,
her parents realised
that something was wrong.
She started talking
about things she remembered.
Things that hadn't happened yet.
We thought, "Well, that's nothing.
That's just kids, isn't it? Imagination."
What are you drawing, Evelyn?
- What's it supposed to be?
- Death.
When she was three, she'd ask
if she could play with the pink house.
We'd say, "What pink house?
There is no pink house."
Then one day the neighbours
were having a clear out
and they brought round
this pink doll's house.
And her face lit up, and she said,
"There it is. There it is."
That was two years later.
We'd moved to a different town.
From an early age,
Evelyn would talk about leaving,
complaining that she wasn't
where she was supposed to be.
That they were all supposed to die in
a car crash on the 5th September, 1977.
That is the date
that Shepherd mentioned on the tapes.
The exact date.
Where did this come from?
I... I was Googling anything
connecting the name Evelyn
with recurrence,
reincarnation, time loops.
Look, maybe we can track down the family,
get some answers.
What I wanna know is,
where did Lucy Chambers
get the name from?
Maybe she went down
the same rabbit hole you did.
Look, I know you want to trust her.
I want to. Doesn't mean I do.
Then bring her in for questioning.
- Not until we've got something more solid.
- But...
I accuse Lucy, she goes on the defensive.
Better to keep things friendly.
How friendly?
Look, I'm sorry, Ravi, but this
is dangerous. She is a suspect.
No, she isn't. She's a person of interest.
Right. Right.
So that's why you're spending
so much time with her, yeah?
Out of interest?
What happens if someone finds out?
They'll only find out if you tell them.
And she's not dangerous.
Hold it tight against your hip.
You don't want to sprain your wrist.
Here.
Once it's loaded, it's going off.
Don't point it at anything
you don't want to die.
I don't want anyone to die.
That's not how it works.
It's him or his victims.
Try again. Tight to the hip.
I'm pregnant.
Are you sure?
It's very unlikely.
And yet, here we are.
- Do you know who?
- Ravi.
Does he know?
Not yet.
I can't go to prison.
I did.
Twenty-five years.
That's how long you kept me waiting.
Waiting for this,
this chance, this reckoning.
It's what you asked for,
it's what I gave you.
That wasn't me. She wasn't me.
She didn't have a mother.
She didn't have a son.
Some nights, I wonder if I'm going insane
and then I think, "No, no."
People who are insane
don't know they're insane,
so I stop wondering and I tell myself
that I'm doing the right thing.
That I'm not crazy.
Which is exactly what crazy people do.
So then...
I wonder if I'm crazy again,
and then it just goes round
and round in circles until I fall asleep,
and I dream about
everyone who's gonna die.
I don't know exactly
what's gonna happen next,
but I know that you're not
going to run away from this.
What makes you say that?
Because that's not who you are.
Got you.
This is a very good poem, Isaac.
Excellent handwriting, perfect spelling.
Did anyone help you with it?
Where did you get the idea from?
I thought of it.
What, you thought of it all on your own?
It wasn't something you saw on the telly,
or something you heard
a grown-up talking about?
Mum knows about it.
"The Devil's Hour".
What is the Devil's Hour, Isaac?
It's late at night.
When we have bad dreams.
When we get scared.
And do you often have bad dreams?
And things... things always
seem scarier at night, don't they?
Sometimes it happens in the day.
What do you mean?
I'm not allowed to talk about it.
You're always allowed to talk to me.
Is it a secret?
It's not a secret
if you tell people it's a secret.
That's what Mum says.
And does Mummy have a lot of secrets?
Isaac,
if Mummy's secrets make you sad or afraid,
then it's better you don't keep them.
Do you understand?
I'm always here if you need me.
Can I go and play now?
'Course.
Sorry. Thanks for coming to speak with me.
You're welcome.
This looks like a good spot
for some pictures, what do you reckon?
Yeah, come on.
Let's find some nice birds.
I don't feel well.
Erm, we'll...
we'll find another park, okay?
Mum?
Yeah.
We should go away.
Somewhere hot and too expensive.
Ravi?
Hmm?
You're talking in your sleep.
I'm sorry.
I was dreaming.
What about?
I don't know.
What time is it?
It's late.
Go back to sleep.
Shit.
Make it quick. Everyone's asleep.
Not everyone. It's started.
Our blue Subaru, stolen half-an-hour ago.
Have you got a face?
I've got something.
He had a key.
Must have lifted it from the owner.
Could be they know each other.
The owner's still in hospital.
He doesn't know his car's missing.
Maybe you should be the one to tell him.
Why... Why would he talk to me?
Because you're DI Lucy Chambers
of the Heart Valley Police,
and you are investigating a crime.
Impersonating a police officer.
I get caught, it's what,
six months in prison?
I have the feeling
you'll be quite convincing.
Go on then, hit me!
Hit me!
Oh...
Bugger.
Ow!
Hang on!
Hello?
Yes, speaking.
Erm, no, Victoria passed away
two years ago.
Oh. Thank you.
Erm...
Yes. Yes, I... No, I remember.
Well, I, erm... Not really, no.
It's Victoria who wanted to do it.
I'll be honest, I wasn't keen on the idea.
The police?
What do you mean? What...
Do... Do they know where she is?
Yes, of course
I'll speak to them, anytime.
Tell them I'll speak to them anytime.
What...
What... What else did they say to you?
But they have a lead?
No, I understand.
Well, I'll... I'll wait to hear from them.
Thank you.
Yes, erm...
Yes, goodbye.
- Excuse me?
- Just a sec, love.
- Erm...
- How can I help?
I'm DI Lucy Chambers. I'd like to speak
with one of your patients, a Jack Graham.
Jack Graham. Let's have a look.
You want the Hollingbrook Ward.
Down the hall, first on your right.
Yeah. Okay.
Oh, my God, the food is shit,
like, soup kitchen shit.
Drugs are killer though.
I've got a magic button.
Clickety-click, yes, please.
Mr Graham?
Yeah.
My name's Lucy Ch...
Detective Inspector Lucy Chambers.
I, erm... Could I have a word?
Yeah. Shit, yes.
Erm... Shit, sorry.
I've... I've got to call you back.
Is this about Dougie?
'Cause that has nothing to do with me.
What was nothing to do with you?
He took a shit in someone's bin.
I told him not to, but he still did it.
No, that's...
that's not why I'm here. Erm...
Mr Graham,
could I confirm that you are the owner
of a blue Subaru Impreza,
registration KIG 1250?
Yeah.
Why?
The car was, erm, stolen last night.
What?
One of your neighbours caught
the whole thing on a dashboard cam.
What did they do? Break a window?
Er, looks like they...
they had a key. Did you lose a set?
Fuck! Urgh!
Oh, I thought I'd lost them at the pub.
Someone's picked your pocket.
They must have got close to you.
Maybe you recognise him?
Oh, fuck!
Fuck no!
- Do you know him?
- That's Steve Dunn.
Fucking had to be him. Didn't it?
- Fucking had to be him.
- Who's Steve Dunn?
Drinks at The Masons, they reckon
he used to run with a gang.
Got into debt, always nicking stuff.
Mad as fuck.
The landlord's too scared to bar him.
What's his ideology?
- His what?
- His view of the world.
I don't know. We're not friends.
This is definitely him?
Okay.
We'll... We'll follow that up
and, er, let you know what we find.
Yeah. Cheers.
Thank you for your time, Mr Graham.
Hey, er...
be careful if you go after him.
He's... proper psycho.
Well, I framed them all.
Victoria didn't want them in the house,
but they're all still here somewhere.
In the chaos.
I'm trying to make this bike roadworthy
again. It's for my granddaughter.
How much of it was true?
The story on TV?
All of it. Erm, every word.
People said we made it up to,
to get attention, get on TV, but...
I didn't even want to do the show.
No, erm...
I... I don't like to talk about it.
Sorry.
No, no. It's...
When was the last time you saw Evelyn?
21st of November 1986.
And she just left?
Uh-huh, yeah.
She, er, she said goodbye and...
That morning she had a part-time job.
We thought things were getting better.
And then just before
she left for her shift,
she turned to us and said,
"I'm not supposed to be here."
Victoria asked her what she meant
and she said she had to
get away from the noise,
the echoes and she just had to leave.
You didn't try to stop her?
We thought it was an empty threat.
I mean, she said things like that before,
but she always came home.
Except this time, she didn't.
What else did she say?
Anything about where she was going?
Er, somewhere quiet.
Far away.
Erm, somewhere just for her.
But we did try to find her.
We just didn't know where to start.
Sorry. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
We're sorry for digging this all up again.
It's never really been buried.
We used to talk about her every day.
She left because we didn't understand her
and we just wanted to understand.
Oh, careful. I...
Sorry, I meant to clean that up.
Did she paint this?
Yeah, yeah.
That's, er... that's part of her...
her black period.
It's not everyone's cup of tea,
but what can you do?
I can't throw them away,
they're part of her.
But this, you see, this is more like it.
She painted this. Porlock Bay.
We used to rent a cottage down there.
It's very beautiful.
Yeah.
Yeah, she loved her painting
more than anything.
She said it helped her
make sense of the world.
What about this?
Yeah. It's, er... That's one of her best.
Victoria hated it.
- Why?
- I think it worried her.
Evelyn said she painted it from memory,
but we'd never been there.
- It's not real.
- Do you mind?
Not at all.
Hm.
It's very detailed.
"Far Away".
She had a vivid imagination.
Sorry. Do you mind?
No, no. You go ahead if it's helpful.
It might be.
"We found her an old house on the moor."
That's what he said.
"Somewhere she'd never be found."
I think we've just found her.
See? Not broken.
Not today.
Why did you think this was broken?
Did it look broken?
Oh, that's just recording our voices,
just while Mummy's not in the room.
If there's anything
I want to share with her.
It's nothing to worry about.
Let's talk about things that change.
You said that this ornament was cracked.
What else?
The flowers? Yeah.
Flowers change every week.
I get fresh ones.
Sometimes they're not real.
What else do you see?
Other children.
Do they talk to you?
They're in another loop.
What does that mean?
It's a secret.
We don't have secrets in here, Isaac.
Can you see them now?
Why not?
I'm not cold.
Do you think it's because we're talking?
Do you think if we go really quiet,
you might hear them?
Shall we try that?
Okay, great.
Alright. Erm, close your eyes for me.
Keep them closed.
I'm gonna put some music on.
Now, you can listen to the music.
Or you can listen to the voices
and you can tell me if you hear...
Isaac?
Hi.
Lucy!
- How's he doing?
- Oh, well...
Hi, sweetheart. How'd you get on?
Good! Right, we've got to go.
Mummy made us late, again.
How was it?
Fine. Yeah, I think...
I think we broke new ground.
Oh, good. Do you mind
if we catch up on the phone?
It's just I promised to
have him somewhere by 5:00.
- Of course.
- Come on, darling.
Come on! Oh, what's this?
Sorry, yes. Thanks, that's mine.
Thank you, Isaac.
Thanks, Ruby.
Right. See you next week!
See you, then.
Don't forget your PJs.
I told Debbie we'd be there by 5:30.
Nearly ready?
Have you got everything you need?
Are you okay?
Ruby knows.
What does Ruby know?
- About me.
- What about you?
She knows what's wrong with me.
There's nothing wrong with you.
Do you understand?
You're perfect.
You're a miracle.
I don't want to be a miracle.
You like staying at Meredith's, don't you?
- I like it here.
- I know you do,
but it's just for tonight, I promise.
I just have something I need to do.
And then I'm yours forever.
Yes, I'm leaving now.
Well, do you hear this?
That's my front door.
Oh, stop pissing your pants.
I'll be there.
I said I'll be there!
Ah, fuck!
- Are you inside?
- Yeah.
Dunn's just left.
What was he wearing?
Nothing yellow.
I'll check the rooms.
You're looking for electrical scrap.
Circuit boards, wiring, soldering kits.
Check for chemicals.
Ammonium nitrate fertilisers,
plastic explosives.
Try the backs of cupboards,
loose floorboards, attic space.
Lucy?
Yeah, I know how to search a property.
Got a laptop.
And lots of boxes.
Do they smell?
Everything smells.
Be careful.
♪ ...of holly
Fa-la-la-la-la, la-la-la-la ♪
♪ 'Tis the season to be jolly
Fa-la-la-la-la-la... ♪
It's... full of trainers.
Knockoffs, I think.
There must be hundreds of them.
Shit.
- What?
- Well, this is petty crime.
It doesn't feel right.
What if it's not him?
No.
No, no. It's him.
Can you open his computer?
It's got a password.
What make is it?
Er, I can't...
I... I can't see a brand name.
Alright. Use Keyring One.
Oh... Hold on.
Er... Remind me?
F12.
Which life did you
spend hacking computers?
None. I bought this off
a 14-year-old boy in an internet cafe.
Oh.
Guess what his password is?
Is it "password"?
Got it in one! Impressive.
Go on then, Isaac, your turn.
I spy with my little eye,
something beginning with...
...D.
- Something beginning with D?
- D. D. D?
Debbie!
- No.
- No?
So self-centred, Debs.
What about drain?
Isaac?
Is it drain?
No.
Oh, hang on.
Hi.
Yes. Speaking.
That's great news.
I'll get the paperwork sent over tomorrow.
Thank you. Yeah. You too.
Bye.
Isaac?
He disappeared.
None of this makes sense.
Maybe
he cleaned up his search history.
Er, his password was "password", so...
Nothing for bomb.
Explosive.
What about Rigby's Toys?
No, there's nothing on here.
Er...
He has been checking
prices for used Subarus.
He sent them to a guy named French.
What?
What is it?
- He's selling the car.
- When?
This Saturday, 11:00 am,
car for cash, Mornes Hill car park.
That's just off the high street.
It's behind Rigby's.
Erm, buyer's from Newcastle.
They've done...
done business before.
It's a coincidence.
You said someone torched the car.
We put out an APW.
They must have known we were
looking for it, wrong place, wrong time.
Gideon, this isn't him.
No, no. It has to be.
It's not!
I've fucked up!
Oh, God.
What is it?
He's back.
- Isaac?
Isaac!
- Isaac!
- Mum!
Oh, my God.
Meredith, go with Daddy.
Come on, pumpkin.
- Is he okay?
- Don't worry.
What happened, Isaac?
What happened?
It bit me.
What bit you?
The dog.
Where'd it go?
She scared it away.
Who did?
Isaac, who scared it away?
Mum.
Look, listen, alright?
That's not the day we agreed.
End of the week, we said end of the week.
Look, I'll get it back to you
with interest.
Just unfuck your ears for a second
and listen, yeah?
Saturday! That's not tomorrow,
but the next day, Saturday.
I'm shifting a motor, 15k, it's all his.
Will you fucking listen, you deaf prick?
He gets paid when I get paid.
15k and then we're square.
And if he thinks about
sending those kids round here,
they'll be leaving in fucking bin bags!
Work!
Oh, fucking work!
Fucking work!
Shit.
Shit!
Who the fuck are you?
How'd you get in here?
You one of Bianca's mates?
Do you think you can
fucking steal from me?
- No, I'm not! I'm not!
- What's that?
Oh, God!
Please let me go! Please!
You ain't going nowhere.
- What you got on?
- No.
Fuck!
Aargh!
Open the door.
Open the fucking door!
I'm gonna fucking kill you!
Aargh!
You are fucking dead!