You got a fuckin' problem?
Elizabeth.
- Juliet, Mr. Proctor here?
- Is he expecting you?
Oh, I imagine some part of him
is always expecting me.
I hear that.
You can head back.
I'll let him know.
Thanks.
Oh. Sorry, I didn't realize
you were in a meeting.
No, it's fine.
Come in, come in.
We were just finishing up anyway.
Weren't we, Mr. Camden?
Deputy Lotus,
this is my associate Isaac Camden.
What the hell
is going on in here?
Mr. Camden had an unfortunate
accident on his way in,
but we sorted it out.
- Right, Isaac?
- That's right.
- Yeah.
- Hey.
- You sure?
- Yes, it's fine.
Burton, why don't you get
Mr. Camden a drink on his way out?
See you next week.
What the hell was that about?
That was just
a small negotiation.
May I pour you one?
No, thanks.
I'm on duty.
So, what can I do for you?
Well, I'm...
I'm just following up
on those two bodies...
we dug up last month.
Yeah, Munson and Randall.
I'm well aware.
Yeah. They,
they work for you?
They worked for me, yeah.
In what capacity?
They hauled meat, mostly.
Right.
Not a job you generally...
associate with getting shot
and buried in the woods.
No, it's not.
And as I told Agent Xavier,
I have no idea what they may have
been up to in their free time.
Yeah, I read the report.
Well, just figured I'd stop by...
and see if maybe you had
anything further to share.
Are you implying I may
not have been truthful...
with the FBI?
Like I said,
I'm just following up.
Yeah.
And now you have.
You can see yourself out.
Well, okay.
Thank you for your time.
You've been a big help,
as always.
Oh, by any chance,
do you remember the
last time you saw...
either one of those men?
I do, actually.
It was the same day
Sheriff Hood came to town.
It's fascinating how the mind...
makes connections like that.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Now we have yet
to fully calculate...
the losses sustained in
the explosion...
No one told me
the council was meeting.
I called an emergency session.
Really?
What's the emergency?
I've been up front
with you, Alex.
We can't sit back while our tribe's
fiscal security is threatened.
I've been chief less
than two months...
and he's already planning
a coup.
And in those two months,
our hotel project
has been destroyed
and now our casino
has been robbed.
Those are not unrelated events.
Look, I'll admit
we've had some setbacks,
but my people and I
are working on it.
We expect to have
the missing money back shortly.
It's not about the money, Alex.
It's about your ability to lead.
I'd have a lot more faith
in his intentions...
if he weren't angling
to be chief himself.
That may be, but his ambitions
don't in any way mitigate the
troubles we've been having.
I'm very aware of the problems
we've been having,
Mr. Thompson.
I just need some time.
You had quite a bit of time
already.
- Mr. DeLoria, I...
- This isn't a witch hunt, Alex.
We're just trying to do
our duty to the tribe.
Now, I loved and
respected your father.
We all did.
But to give fitting honor
to his memory...
Don't get ahead
of yourself, George.
And don't ever tell me
how to honor my father again.
I'll see you all
at the next meeting.
Hey, Squirrel.
Breece.
Jesus Christ.
You look good.
Deputy, huh?
Congratulations.
You can't be here
right now, okay?
I have a restraining
order against you.
I know, I'm sorry.
I just didn't know how else
to get a hold of you.
You're not supposed
to get a hold of me.
That's what
a restraining order means.
I know. Look, I'm not here to cause
you any trouble...
- You need to leave right now.
- Siobhan, please.
Just, just give me two minutes.
That's all I ask.
Okay, two minutes.
Thank you.
- Listen, Squirrel...
- Don't call me that.
Okay.
I know how angry
you must be at me,
and I deserve all of it.
But I want you to know
that I left here three years ago
angry and drunk,
and I'm neither
of those things anymore.
I've been sober now
for two years.
Anyway, the thing is,
I haven't had steady work
in seven months.
As soon as they do
a background check on me,
all the stuff here
comes up and...
Oh, I know you're not
about to blame me
- for your police record.
- No, no... of course not.
It's just my cousin Jesse.
You remember Jesse.
Anyway, he said that
I could come back here...
and work for him
building swimming pools.
It's decent pay, benefits,
but he won't have me on...
while I have that
restraining order on me.
- You're kidding me.
- Look,
I know this is
a lot to ask, Squirr...
Siobhan.
And I know I don't
deserve mercy from you.
But I have been looking
everywhere for work...
and I'm telling you
there's nothing out there.
This is my best shot.
Hey, Emmett.
What the hell are you
doing here, Breece?
It's okay, Emmett.
Move along now
or I'll move you along.
Emmett.
Emmett, I got this.
Sheriff, I need you to sign off
on these reports.
- What do you got?
- Now I can write it all up,
but only you can sign your name.
What's up?
Breece Connors,
Siobhan's ex-husband.
So what was that about?
A job he's after.
He wants me to lift
the restraining order.
Hope you told him to get lost.
You told him no, right?
I told him to take the job
and I'd think about it.
- He needs to work.
- Are you kidding me?
After everything
he put you through...
Emmett, look...
I'm not the same person anymore.
Maybe he's not.
But either way, I'm not gonna
keep him from working.
So the prosecution and defense
have both signed off
on the plea deal.
- Is that correct?
- Yes, Your Honor.
We're good with it, Judge.
Reduced charges
of reckless endangerment,
and discharging
of an illegal firearm.
- Yes, Your Honor.
- Okay, then.
Mrs. Hopewell,
please rise.
I've reviewed
the police reports...
from the night in question...
and considered
the mitigating factors...
as well as the recommendation
of the DA's office,
and the agreement
of the attorneys present.
Based on minimum
sentencing guidelines,
and the recommendation
of the prosecution,
you're hereby sentenced to serve
no less than 30 days
at the Mercer County
Women's State Correctional.
Your Honor, really?
Mercer County is 200 miles away.
That is an undue hardship
on her family...
Overcrowding
in the county system...
compels us to follow
the empty beds.
There's nothing you can
do about it, Jackson.
Prisoner is to be remanded
into custody immediately.
Can you at least stay
the sentence for 72 hours...
so that Mrs. Hopewell,
who is the mother of two children,
can get her affairs
in order, please?
We're good with that,
Your Honor.
Mrs. Hopewell, you are
to surrender yourself...
to the Banshee
Sheriff's Department at 9:00 a.m.
Three days from now.
If you do not appear,
you will forfeit your bond.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
Gordon.
- Sheriff.
- How are the kids?
How the fuck you think they are?
Racine's squeezing her.
He thinks she knows something.
Yeah?
For all I know, he's right.
Is that why you
let her go to jail?
Fuck you.
You don't put that shit on me.
She's in this mess
because of you, not me.
You want to hit me back?
Yeah, go ahead, hit me.
It's what you do, isn't it?
Come on, motherfucker, hit me.
Hit me, motherfucker.
I gave you the first one.
You don't get another.
- Come dance with me.
- No way. I'm good here.
Come on. I want to dance
with my husband.
That's okay, Squirrel.
Just enjoying the view.
Okay, I'm giving you
10 minutes...
and then I'm coming
back for you.
Ten minutes.
- Hey!
- Fuck you, man.
Breece, what are you doing?
Get the fuck out of the way!
Stay the fuck away from my wife.
Breece, Stop it!
This is your fucking fault, too.
You're shaking
your fucking ass...
on his dick
right in front of me?
Hey.
You okay?
Emmett's got a big mouth.
Just leave it alone, okay?
Please?
Okay.
So Carrie's really going inside?
Yeah.
You know, I don't want to seem
insensitive, but I need...
Racine's not interested
in you and Job.
We get off, just like that?
What do you want,
your own hearing?
Oh, no, thank you.
I just think we need
to worry about...
a high-ranking federal agent...
who doesn't seem
to answer to anyone.
Didn't your mother
ever tell you?
A wise man never looked
a gift horse in the mouth.
No, my mother told me
a word to the wise is unnecessary.
It's a damn fool
who needs the advice.
Well, look here.
Ain't we all
just domestic as shit?
Your cut, baby.
Yours, too.
What the fuck you lookin' at?
It's just sometimes
I just forget how...
Never mind.
Came out to about 156,000.
Split four ways,
39 grand apiece.
Definitely not our finest hour.
This one is hers.
I'll let you hang on to it.
So she's really going in?
It's 30 days.
It's...
it's not so bad.
Locked up, is locked up.
Okay, they're coming out.
- What now?
- One way or another,
you're gonna learn
to stay the hell away from my casino.
This is getting boring.
Can't you come up with
something new?
Okay, here's something new.
Alex.
I guess you're not
the only one in this town...
who can get
their hands on C-4.
You stole $156,000
from my truck.
I want it back.
Let's go. Close it down.
Move aside.
- Let's go.
- Let's go. Move 'em in.
Hi, honey.
I was hoping we could talk.
What are you doing here, Breece?
I heard from some of the guys
that you had a fire.
I just figured I'd...
I don't know.
Do you need something
from inside?
No, I just wanted to see you.
I'm going away soon, and...
Yeah, I know.
The whole town knows.
Congratulations.
I'm sorry, I thought I was gonna be
gone before you got back home.
No, you can't come
around here, Breece.
I know.
Well, maybe I'll just
come inside and give Max...
You can't come in.
I'm still his mother,
Deva, and yours.
I don't know. Are you?
How do I know
that wasn't a lie, too?
Look, I know...
- No. No.
- I have a lot to make up for.
- Baby, I had reasons...
- I don't give a shit, Mom.
You know Max is still
sleeping in my bed?
He's too scared to sleep
in his own room...
because you let them take him.
You said you needed to work
and that's all this was, okay?
I've moved on.
I don't wanna hear from you
and I don't want you
coming around my house.
Well, either way.
It's great to see you
doing so well.
Just stay away from us.
Yo, check this shit out, bro.
Hello, beautiful.
Why don't you come
join us for a drink?
No, thanks.
- We're shipping off soon.
- I'll pass. Thanks.
Well, pass a bit slower...
so I can get a good look
at that ass.
Damn, girl!
That's a thing of beauty.
You ever consider modeling?
You ever consider
shutting the fuck up?
Oh, shit!
You got dissed, bro.
Shut the fuck up, man.
- Yeah.
- Oh.
Well, well, look who's back.
Hold on.
Slow down, now.
You weren't very nice
to me back there.
But now you can make up for it.
Seriously?
You were thinking about hitting
a United States Marine?
Get off of me!
You better learn how to throw a
better punch than that, little girl.
Fuckin' bitch.
- I'll teach you to shove...
- Oh, God!
Who the fuck are you?
I'd tell you, but you
wouldn't remember anyway.
Hi.
Thank you.
Don't thank me yet.
- What is that?
- This?
It's chloroform.
This better be good.
What are you doing?
She's important to him.
Besides, he owes us
a lot more money...
than what we'll ask him for.
George Hunter
is gunning for you.
You need a win to keep
this council quiet.
She just brings Proctor
to the table.
Hey!
Can I help you?
Where is she?
- What are you talking about?
- Rebecca...
I'm talking
about Rebecca. Where is she?
Hey, you're gonna want
to back off right now.
I haven't seen her.
Well, she didn't
come home last night.
Have you tried calling her?
Yeah. Earlier.
Hello, Kai.
- Alex.
- Don't worry about Rebecca.
She's perfectly fine,
for the moment.
- I'm still waiting for my money.
- Put her on the phone now.
Uncle Kai?
- You listening now?
- Yes.
Bring me $156,000
by noon today...
- and she walks out of here.
- I didn't rob your fuckin' truck.
Well, then, I guess
we'll consider it
a down payment
on the casino you blew up.
Now listen to me.
At some point
in the very near future,
you will be made to understand...
how badly you misjudged
me today.
And when that time comes,
and you're begging me for mercy,
I want you to remember
this moment
because this is the moment
you've sealed your fate.
Yeah, okay, duly noted.
Just bring my fucking money.
It's Alex Longshadow.
He's taken Rebecca.
I need you to go get her back.
I have no jurisdiction
on the reservation.
Well, neither do I,
but I'll get around that by going
in with an army.
Is that what you want?
Why don't you tell me
what's going on?
A few weeks ago
you told me you owed me one.
I'm sure you recall
that conversation.
Good.
Then go get her.
Go on. It's all right.
Go on.
Easy.
I'm sure your uncle
will be here soon.
I'm sure he will be, too.
I used to see you
at the farmers' market.
Your family sold pies, right?
Now you've left that behind,
moved into another
family business.
Sad, really.
I loved those pies.
Did you help him do it?
Help him do what?
I think you know
exactly what I mean.
You know, my people
have this myth...
about the Thunder Man.
He's reborn once
each generation.
He's got the power of a god,
prodigious lover,
fiercest warrior.
But outwardly, he looks like
a normal man.
So every man
has to ask himself...
whether he might in fact be,
the Thunder Man.
And every woman has to wonder
whether the man
she's with is him.
Some women live to find him.
Others know that he'll destroy them
if they stay with him.
I believe you think
you found your Thunder Man.
I've got all the thunder I need.
Is that so...
Amish girl?
Did your uncle rob my truck?
My uncle sells meat.
Your uncle blew up
my fucking hotel.
If I were you,
I'd be more worried about
what he's going to do to you.
We'll see about that.
Five more seconds.
And we in.
And by "we," I mean you.
You should be
in the kitchen now.
Excuse me, Sheriff,
are you lost?
- Is this the kitchen?
- Yes.
Then no.
Okay, the most isolated room
is the VIP room.
Where is it?
Baby, I'm looking at
two sets of plans here...
the old casino and the new one...
and I got no fucking clue what's real
and what ain't been built yet.
Best guess?
Take a left
at the end of the hall.
I could be hacking Google,
or the Caymans,
but, no, I gotta be
infiltrating Fort Apache.
Hey. BSD.
I need to get in there.
BSD has no jurisdiction
on the rez.
If you're not on the list,
you don't get in.
Yeah...
I could shoot you.
We could shoot each other.
That sounded nasty.
And no dice.
- Puns? Really?
- Sorry.
Okay,
cut across the gaming room,
go upstairs.
Shit!
What?
What the hell's going on?
Job.
Baby, come back.
Baby?
Fuck.
Fuck!
Hey!
Seriously.
Sheriff Hood.
Oh, hi.
Hi yourself.
You think you know someone?
I know, right?
I'm sorry,
am I missing something?
- We've met before.
- I'm just here for the girl.
Oh. So you're one
of Proctor's lackeys, is that it?
No, no.
If your argument's with Proctor,
you gotta take it up with him.
I just get involved when you start
kidnapping young women.
Now cut her loose.
Well, you're in no position
to make demands here.
What, this?
Come on, we both know she's
not gonna shoot me.
I wouldn't be so sure.
Okay, this is Kinaho land.
I have no authority to arrest you;
we all know that.
But my guess is...
she's not gonna
press charges anyway.
So we can chalk
this whole thing up...
to one big misunderstanding.
You let her go now,
this never happened.
- Put the gun down.
- Fuck that.
Nola!
Bye.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Great.
Thanks.
Are you kidding me?
We're not gonna shoot a sheriff.
It was a bad idea to begin with.
I'm done sending messages.
It's time to take
a more direct approach.
You came for me.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
You're bleeding.
It's fine. It's just a scrape.
- Here...
- I said it's fine.
Rebecca.
I know this is
a hard time for you,
but your uncle,
he's not a good man.
You shouldn't be living there.
Well, then,
let me live with you.
I'm not a good man either.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm gonna go get
something to eat.
So how did it go?
Piece of cake.
Well, thank you.
I do appreciate it.
Like you said, I owed you one.
Sheriff...
you never did ask me
if I robbed that truck.
I guess I figured
it wasn't your style.
No, it's not.
This is nice.
- I got you something.
- Alex.
It's stunning.
What do you think?
You look beautiful.
Proctor, what the fuck?
Hello, Alex.
You come here to my home?
Are you crazy?
Yeah, your security personnel
weren't very effective.
You may want to talk to them
when they wake up.
This is very romantic.
Get the fuck out of here.
Don't worry. Just be a minute.
What the fuck is this?
You go near my niece again
and it won't be cow's blood.
It will be the blood
of your family.
Every single one of them
I can get my hands on.
I'll fucking drown you
in their blood.
I'm not even going to ask.
Figured I'll be
seeing you tomorrow.
Yeah, well, there's not much
of a difference...
between my motel room
and a cell,
so I figured I'd get a drink
while I still could.
It's 30 days.
That's not long enough
for the walls...
to start fucking
with your head, okay?
Anyone messes with you...
you don't engage.
You keep to yourself,
do quiet time.
It's not prison
I'm worried about.
That'll all work itself out.
You just have to give them time.
You should get some sleep.
We got a long drive tomorrow.
Yeah.
You okay?
This is all on me.
She's going to jail,
'cause of me.
You did 15 years for her.
It doesn't make it right.
Look, I think
you didn't consider...
what would happen to her
when you set up shop here,
but no one does
a stretch like you did...
without making some mistakes
when they first come out.
- Now you tell me.
- No, I think I told you then.
Listen, you can
sit here and get drunk...
while you dissect everything
you've gone through.
We're ex-cons. It's what we do.
But at some point or another,
there's only one question
really worth asking yourself...
What are you going to do now?
Hey.
You remember what I said.
Quiet time.
I know.
Back it up.
Rehall, let's go.
- Move it, huh?
- Rowe, against the fence.
Bye-bye!
Look at this bitch.
Fuckin' Malibu Barbie
coming to do time.
Backtracking?
You got some attitude, bitch?
Come on, Squirrel.
We're gonna be late.
- I'm doing my hair.
- Do it faster.
Relax, Breece. The restaurant isn't
gonna run out of food.
Don't you fucking
tell me to relax!
Please, Breece...
Hey, Squirrel.
What the hell
are you doing here?
I just thought, you know,
I'd make you dinner,
like I used to.
You can’t just
come into my house.
Remember our
Friday nights like this?
I'd cook and then we'd dance
right in the kitchen.
I thought you weren't drinking.
It's just a beer, baby.
Come on.
One more dance, come on.
- No. No.
- Come on!
Get the fuck out of my house!
Careful, now.
I'm trying to be gracious here,
to make amends.
I said
get the fuck out of my house.
Now!
You're gonna shoot me, Squirrel?
Huh?
Is that it?
Jesus! What the fuck,
Siobhan?!
The next one's
going in your gut.
Big fucking cop now, huh?
Want your fucking hair
all perfect?
Well, there you go.
Well, go on, then.
God!
Shoot me.
Breece... God!
- Breece!
- Shoot me?
Fucking do it, you fucking cunt!
No!
Don't!
- Come on!
- No, no!
No, Breece, please!
Come on!
- Hey, Alma, what's up?
- I'm a little worried about Siobhan.
She was supposed to show up for
the night shift an hour ago.
- You tried her cell?
- I tried her everywhere.
I was getting ready to call one of
the other deputies...
to swing by her place.
No. No, that's fine.
I'll go.
Siobhan.
What's up, boss?
You expecting someone else?
I wasn't expecting anyone.
You want to talk about it?
Not really.
Okay.
Then just tell me
where he's staying.
He's at the Motor Lodge.
It's right near
his cousin's place.
Fuckin' Dream House Barbie.
Oh, that's so good.
Oh, yeah. Oh, harder.
Wow.
You got a fuckin'
problem, Barbie?
No.
Look who came to apologize.
Come on.
Come on!
So...
it turns out
Breece isn't staying...
at the motor lodge after all.
Sorry. My bad.
I already called
for an ambulance.
Yeah, I heard.
You hurt?
I'm good.
I know I'll lose
my badge for this.
I'm on probation,
for fuck's sake.
Go home.
I'll clean this up.
He'll tell 'em it was me.
Yeah, I'll have a talk with him.
He won't stick around.
- Are you sure about this?
- Yeah.
Go home.
You know,
for the last four years,
there wasn't a day
that I didn't imagine...
some version of this playing out.
How does it feel?
Better than I imagined.
Yeah.
Thanks, boss.
Don't mention it.
Thanks.