I didn't think you'd come.
How are you?
I don't know yet.
- What about you?
- I don't know.
I'm gonna need some time, okay?
I'm ready
to tell you everything.
Hi, Mom.
Where's Gordon?
I don't know.
Where's Ana?
Yeah, Mom, where's Ana?
Morning, ladies.
5:00 a.m.
Time to get your fingers
out of your happy hole
and give God the glory.
You know, we've never
been formally introduced.
- Lucas Hood.
- Nola.
Yeah, the chief's prodigal daughter.
I asked around. Small town.
Heard you arrested
Tommy Littlestone.
We questioned him.
He's not a killer.
And you've got
Chayton locked up?
That must have taken some doing.
He a friend of yours?
No.
But he didn't do it either.
Chayton is a killer,
but he's also a purist.
He would never kill a Kinaho girl.
You can't know that.
Call it an expert opinion.
Okay. So in your
expert opinion,
where should I be looking?
Are you seriously
asking me that?
I mean, isn't that
where you'd be the expert?
- He behaving?
- Yeah, so far.
Hey, black man.
You're a disgrace to your race.
They tore your ancestors
from their land,
raped their women,
and enslaved your people
for generations.
And now you wear their uniform.
Where's your dignity?
How do you live with yourself?
By getting scum like you
off the streets.
I live with myself just fine.
You get anything
from the state police?
They searched the woods,
came up empty.
Okay.
We should press the Bowmans.
Okay. They might know
more than they're saying.
- Right.
- Or...
Or what?
We should talk to the kids.
If Solomon is hiding,
one of his buddies might know where.
- Great.
- Yeah, and I should talk to them.
Alone.
Look, Hood,
it's hard enough to get the Amish
adults to talk to us,
but the kids,
kids are off-limits.
And your... style,
well, it won't work with them.
But they'll talk to you?
I've always had good
relations with the elders.
They trust me.
Okay. Let me know
what turns up.
You were looking for me?
You went a little overboard
on this room, don't you think?
Proctor is one man.
You are the head of
the entire Kinaho Nation.
It doesn't matter if you are weak or
you just appear weak.
There's blood in the water.
And men like Proctor
and Hunter can smell it.
I'm the chief of this tribe, Nola.
I don't have the luxury of being able
to take out anyone who challenges me.
Isn't that why
you keep me around?
Get your feet off the table.
You've reached the voice mailbox of
Gordon Hopewell.
Please leave a message.
Gordon.
It's me, again.
I know you don't want
to talk to me
and I understand that.
I do.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
Hey, where you going?
Out.
Last night I dreamt
that we were a family again.
I know it was just a dream,
but I've got to believe
that if I could find
the right words to say to you,
you would find a way
to forgive me.
I can survive this place.
I can't live without you
and the kids.
I won't survive that.
Please tell the kids
that I love them.
That much at least
I hope you know is true.
Oh, dude, I heard
this Indian chick
had, like, the whole
back of her head busted in.
Do you mean like "scalped"?
Oh, my God.
That is so messed up.
Oh, shit, the cops.
- Hey.
- Sleep well?
- Okay, what the fuck?
- Right back at you.
Hey, man, I don't know
what kind of kinky shit you're into...
Get up and brush your hair.
Job's here to take your picture.
I am?
Okay, who the fuck is this
and what the hell am I doing here?
Well, this is where
it gets interesting.
Introduce yourself.
Jason Hood.
- Fuck me.
- Yeah.
We got to make him someone else.
Well, the motherfucking
hits just keep on coming.
- Nice tie.
- Shut up.
And why aren't we killing him?
- Hey, whoa.
- Shut up.
Proctor?
Morning, Chief.
Paul Moon needed six surgeries.
I'm sorry, Paul Moon?
The man whose balls you crushed.
Ah, I never caught his name.
You came to my home,
you violated my privacy...
You kidnapped my niece.
Yeah, we can stand here
and trade accusations all day.
The bottom line is your own people
have lost faith in you.
And you have no one else
to blame but yourself.
Hey, Alex. How are you?
- What can I get you?
- You're a thug, Proctor.
And when you go down,
and you will go down...
no one's gonna miss you.
I'm gonna come back later.
You know what, Alex?
You care too much
about what people think of you.
You'll never achieve
any power like that.
Lie, cheat, extort...
and you call that power?
That's not power,
that's just being a sociopath.
I'm running a business.
You're running a tribe.
The difference is
I've earned my spot.
- You're a criminal.
- That's just semantics.
"Semantics."
You're operating out of fear.
Fear of losing your position.
Fear of the consequences.
I'm not always
the smartest guy in the room,
but I'm fearless.
I'm willing to do
whatever it takes to get what I want.
And because of that,
people fear me.
Now, unless you can do that,
your tribe will smell
the weakness on you
and the stronger ones
will take you down.
That's a great speech.
Thank you.
But I'm not scared of you.
I'm not really getting
through to you, am I?
This is my fault. I may have come on
too strong with you.
And now you feel that anything other
than war is backing down.
You know, we could have been great
partners, you and I, Alex.
With the casino and all.
Sometimes it takes more strength
to make peace than to fight.
Something your father taught me,
God rest his soul.
You were just a tool
to my father.
He thought you were garbage.
Why don't you go back
to the reservation, Alex?
There, at least,
you are something.
In the meantime, I have more
important things to deal with.
Don't worry.
We'll find your nephew.
If anyone from your tribe
touches that boy,
I'll hold you
personally responsible.
Maybe I should talk
to your sister.
Seems to me she's the one
with the balls anyway.
I should slit
your throat right here.
Yeah? Now that
would take some balls.
Mr. Proctor, Alex,
do I need to call the BSD?
I have them on speed dial.
That's okay, Daria.
Sorry, just a small disagreement.
Here, that should cover that.
I'm sorry, Daria.
Here's the rest of
the Kinaho statements.
Thanks.
About last night...
Oh, it's all good, boss.
Hey, Hood, I...
- you got a minute?
- Yeah.
What?
This may be nothing,
but one of the Amish boys
just told me
that Solomon had a friend
named Daniel Moses
who left the fold.
Guess he was a bit
of a problem child.
He ran away a few times.
They kept dragging him back.
But the last time he ran,
he was 18, so they just let him go.
- You know where he lives?
- Yeah.
Kid said he's squatting in
a building over on Delafield.
- Let's go.
- All right.
What the fuck?!
Were you or were you not supposed
to stay in your motherfucking room?
I got hungry.
Get in the fucking car.
I kind of don't want to.
Bitch, I should be shooting your dumb
white ass right now,
but instead I'm offering
you a ride.
So show some fucking gratitude
and get in the fucking car
or I will run you into a wall and say
my foot slipped off the clutch.
Daniel Moses?
Oh, great.
Hey!
- Hey, hey, hey.
- I'm not going back.
I'm not going back.
- I'm not gonna take you back.
I'm 18 years old
and you can't make me go back.
- Hey!
- We're not... Hey!
God damn it!
We're not taking you back.
That's not why we're here.
We're looking for Solomon Bowman.
Solomon?
Why? What's wrong?
- You haven't heard?
- No.
Solomon's missing.
We know he's a friend of yours.
We thought maybe he
was crashing with you.
I haven't seen him in weeks.
Listen to me.
There's other people
looking for him, okay?
- If they find him before we do...
- I'm telling you the truth.
If you don't believe me,
you can come check my place.
Fix the place up yourself?
Yeah.
- You like to read?
- Yeah.
Salinger?
They don't let you read
that at the Amish school?
No, they don't let us
read anything.
Really?
It's just a way to keep
us trapped on the farm.
Ignorant, unable to engage
the outside world.
So whenever I went to town,
I'd buy one or two books
and hide them in the crawlspace
beneath the house.
You ever get caught?
There was this teacher
at our school.
Even though we stopped going
to school after eighth grade,
he was still responsible
for our religious training.
He caught me reading
Lord of the Flies
and he just went off on me.
Punching me, kicking me,
screaming like a maniac
that my mind
was "poisoned by filth."
Patia.
I heard what happened to you.
I am so sorry.
- You sent me into the woods.
- I know.
My mom, she made me
come back home
after what your uncle
did to those Kinaho men.
Well, someone knew
where to find me.
I didn't tell anybody.
I promise.
I wasn't a rebel or anything.
I wasn't having sex
or doing drugs.
I just wanted to read.
So I ran away.
Patia, what were you
going to tell me yesterday?
Is that normal?
Any other teachers hit you?
No, this guy was kind of a...
religious nut.
And that's saying something
considering where I'm from.
Please.
Just tell me what you know.
He'd look for me,
demanding I repent.
Getting rough with me
when I wouldn't.
I told Solomon that if things ever
got too bad, he could come here.
Wait, wait. So this teacher was
picking on Solomon as well?
Yeah,
Solomon has his sister.
The teacher, he's twisted.
- And he hates Solomon.
- Why?
I don't know. Maybe because
he's your brother.
They were worried he was
gonna go the same way.
Like the whole bloodline
was cursed or something.
Superstitious bullshit.
Uncle...
Then Solomon met this Indian girl.
He tried to keep it a secret,
but word always
gets out, you know?
So this teacher,
what's his name?
Jonah Lambrecht?
- Yes.
- Sheriff Lucas Hood.
Can I come in?
Yes. Yes, of course.
It's about the boy,
Solomon, right?
That's right.
Please, have a seat.
I'll cook up some water.
It's terrible about the girl.
How can I be of help?
You live alone?
Yes, I know it's a bit messy.
No, no. It's not that.
I just didn't realize
there was Amish bachelors.
My wife Sara died
a few years
after we were married.
I'm sorry.
You have any kids?
No.
She'd always been a frail woman.
Couldn't have any children.
But I loved her very much.
So you never remarried?
No. When she died,
I just...
I don't know.
I lost interest
in getting married.
Once you've loved
someone a certain way,
you know you'll never
love another like that.
So tell me about Solomon.
He was your student, right?
Yes.
A few years ago.
He's a bright boy.
Maybe a bit rebellious,
but...
a sweet boy.
I don't think for one minute
that he hurt that girl.
What do you mean "rebellious"?
Well, Solomon was curious.
He couldn't always
accept the restrictions of our faith.
It's a big world out there
and boys will be curious.
I know I was.
So, what, it was your job
to bring him back into line?
No, no, no.
That falls to the parents.
I'm simply there to teach them
the precepts of our faith.
And as a part of this teaching,
you ever get physical with them?
I'm sorry?
You ever hit them?
- No.
- No?
Of course not.
We do not believe
in violence of any kind.
Oh.
'Cause that's not what
Daniel Moses told me.
Yes.
That was a mistake.
I think about Daniel a lot.
At the time, I told myself
it was self-defense.
After all, it was he
who attacked me.
But I would do anything
to see that boy again.
To tell him how sorry I am.
To ask him to forgive me, and...
to ask him to come home.
Excuse me.
You hurt your leg?
It's an old injury.
I got kicked by a horse.
So why is it still bleeding?
What happened
to no violence, Jonah?
You're under arrest.
You have the right
to remain silent...
Where's the boy?
Where is he?
He's not going to tell you.
His psychotic belief in his own
righteousness is too strong.
So what do you suggest?
Just leave us alone for a bit.
You know, I'm finding
everybody's reaction
to this kid disturbingly
underreactive.
We should be digging
a motherfucking hole.
Look, he's just a kid
looking for a second chance.
And when did we become
Touched by an Angel?
- It is strange, though.
- What's that?
Well, of all the chairs
he could have chosen,
he chose the same chair
his father chose
the day he got killed.
- So, Job.
- "Job"?
When do you think
my fake ID will be ready?
Fake ID, hmm?
Bitch, what you think this is?
This ain't some phony
Virginia driver's license
you're buying for 50 bucks
in the back of a head shop
so you can host a kegger
in your backyard
and date-rape the motherfucking
prom queen.
I'm giving you a new name,
credit history,
Social Security number and
a motherfucking birth certificate.
I am turning you into a whole new
goddamn human being.
Okay.
Jesus, I'm sorry.
And let me tell you
something else.
Once I have performed
this little miracle,
you are going to disappear
and we are not going to see or hear
from your punk ass again
because if you
show up a second time
looking for a handout
because you fucked up again,
I will personally put a bullet
between your eyes.
And just for that,
I'm gonna name you Marion.
Now, you may not
be aware, Jonah...
but there is a debate currently
raging in civil society
about the efficacy of torture.
Now, I happen to fall
on the side of those
who believe that pain
is a tool...
like any other.
And where pain will work...
it's far and away the most
efficient tool for the job.
Just tap your foot
when you're ready to talk.
There's an unused silo
on the adjacent property.
He's got Solomon locked away.
Oh, it took me a few
extra teeth to get this.
Fuck that. Let's drive.
- You killed him?
- No.
But you should probably
call an ambulance.
Yeah, I probably should.
Solomon?
God damn it. Hey.
Shit.
- I found him.
- Oh, God.
Solomon.
Hey, Solomon.
- Solomon.
- Hey.
Solomon.
It's okay.
I got you.
Okay.
I love you. It's okay.
It's okay.
I love you.
It's okay. It's okay.
Solomon!
When your own grandson was lost,
you cowered and prayed to God,
and the Almighty would have left him
dead beneath your feet.
Well, maybe God
just doesn't love you
as much as you'd like
to believe.
Maybe He finds it
laughably arrogant
for you to think
you even know His will.
God brought him back to us.
Yeah, you go and see what
I did to Jonah Lambrecht.
You'll see that God
had nothing to do with it.
Nothing.
Let's go.
You're gonna be okay.
All right.
Here's the paperwork on him.
It's two hours
to Jefferson County.
Sheriff's Department
will meet you at the county line.
All right. See you later.
Christ, he's a big one.
Stay alert, huh?
We will.
Hey, what the fuck?!
Jesus Christ.
Hey, cut that shit out now.
Hey, you want to fucking
get tased again? Stop.
Stop it right now.
This is Deputy Yawners
with the BSD.
Shit. Stop that.
You want me to shoot you?
It's happy green.
It makes you happy.
Flynn, where did you
get this stuff?
Actually, I can't tell you.
Come on, Deva.
Please, baby, pick up.
Pick up, pick up, pick up.
- It's amazing, right?
- Watch this.
Hey, it's Deva.
Leave a message.
Or don't. Bye.
Hi, Deva. It's Mom.
I don't even know
where to start.
I have so much to say.
I just want you to know
that I love you.
That I always have.
That part was never a lie.
All I ever wanted was
for you and Max to be happy
and to feel safe.
When I come home,
you can ask me anything
and I'll tell you the truth.
Baby, we can find our way back.
Just don't give up on me.
Okay?
I love you.
Tell Max I love him, too.
Thanks.
Is there something
I can help you with?
You look so sad.
You have no idea.
Want some company?
You know,
any other night
I would tell you to get lost.
What the hell happened to him?
He resisted arrest.
Strenuously.
No.
Don't do this, Father.
You did this.
Daddy! Mama!
Don't let them do this to me!
Did you get a confession?
Don't need one.
We got the boy.
How is the boy?
He'll give you everything you need
to pin the murder on him.
Well, you did a number on him.
Congratulations, Sheriff.
Your department needed this win.
Here to serve.
I hope it hurts like hell.
You heard from Emmett
or Siobhan?
No, why?
I can't seem to get them on
their cells or on the radio.
You know what? They still got
another half an hour.
- Keep trying.
- Yeah. Yeah, I will.
Be still.
What is it with
white people and chains?
From the day you got here,
you've been locking people up.
Tell your sheriff
I'll see him soon.
Hit the dirt, cop!
Get down! Now!
Drop it!
Here you go, black man.
I think these are yours.
It's strong, yo.
I'm bumming.
Look at him in that hat.
- Oh, my God.
- It's the cops.
- Oh, shit.
- Fuck.
- It's fine. Just stop.
- How you doing, Officer?
We weren't doing anything, man.
Your parents know you're
out here getting high?
Allegedly high.
- Go home.
- Don't have to tell me twice.
Now.
Deva.
Let's go, dude.
Come on.
You guys are idiots.
You know, you really
shouldn't smoke pot.
Yeah, I know.
Fair enough.
You angry at your mom?
You don't know how I feel.
No, but that's what
you're doing, right?
Trying to hurt her.
It won't work.
Just make more mess.
What makes you the expert?
Do you have any kids?
No.
But I know how to make a mess.
I believe it.
There's your dad.
Thanks for the lemonade.
So I suppose
congratulations are in order.
You're a father.
I have to say, when it was about
the money, I got it.
When it was about true love
gone tragically wrong,
- I even got that.
- Yeah.
But if you think
you're gonna hang around here,
take a couple parenting classes,
make all this evil shit right,
you are sadly mistaken.
Bad shit happens
to people standing too close to you.
If you care for them,
you have to get out
of their lives.
Take the diamonds to New York.
Fence them. Get what you can.
Say amen, somebody.
The man has come to his senses.
Call me when you're done.
I'll come up.
Anywhere but here, baby.
Anywhere on this big,
beautiful planet but here.
Hey.
You okay?
Jesus Christ. Jesus.
- We got to get you checked out.
- I'm fine. I'm fine.
I didn't realize it was this bad
or I would have come.
I know.
For a moment,
after the crash...
I thought I was dead.
Come on.
I'm gonna take you home.
Here to go another round?
No.
I said something to you earlier.
That it takes more
strength to make peace than to fight.
I think I need to learn
that lesson again myself.
I hope you'll consider this
an adequate peace offering.
Those are seven teeth
of the man who murdered the girl.
The rest of him
is in lockup in town.
Why don't you make
a necklace of them?
Go tell your people
you brought peace on the land.
I think you'll be pleased to know
he wasn't one of yours.
"And thine eye shall not pity,
but life shall go for life.
Eye for eye,
tooth for tooth."
This doesn't change
anything, you know.
I don't like Proctor
any more than you do,
but he may be right.
This isn't a time to fight.
Alex, you will not
get into bed with Proctor.
Hunter's working
the council hard.
I can't afford
another embarrassment.
You said it yourself,
there's blood in the water.
Yeah, that's right.
So be the shark.
Be the fucking shark, Alex.
What are you gonna do, Nola?
You gonna hit me?
I think I was wrong
to ask you to stick around.
After everything
that's happened,
everything you went through,
I should have
thought about that.
I'm sorry,
but you don't belong here anymore.
Yeah.
I never did.
No, I guess you didn't.
Where you gonna go?
- Nola.
- Don't.
You're finally being a chief.
Don't ruin it by
second-guessing yourself.
Nice outfit.
Right back at you.
Thank you.
- Where are we going?
- You have a visitor.
This way.
- In there?
- In there.
Go on.
Sit down.
You're surprised to see me?
No.
Not really.
It seems you and me
are both very hard to kill.
It's a family trait.
What are you doing here?
I see your mother
every time I look at you.
It warms me.
And it kills me at the same time.
When I met your mother,
she was with another man.
But I courted her shamelessly.
Relentlessly.
At first
she thought I was insane.
And then later she knew
I was insane.
But there was
no questioning my love.
Love.
Truth.
Insanity.
These are all
more connected than people...
want to believe.
I made...
I made mistakes, Anastasia.
Too many.
And too terrible to forgive.
But I wanted to tell you
before it's too late...
that what you think...
was insanity...
was the greatest love...
I have ever known.
This is the last time...
we will see one another.