(POP SONG PLAYING)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Good morning.
(ALAN GARGLING)
RICHARD: Who puts
the flowers out there?
BARBER:
Can't say for sure. Why?
RICHARD: Could be the sign
of a guilty conscience.
Out here,
we just call it "Being nice."
Or maybe,
whoever's doing it is superstitious.
Yeah? How so?
Well, they figure
if they honor the dead,
maybe their kids
won't end up like them two girls did.
That's just magical thinking.
You ever been out to the creek,
where Ann Nash's body
was found, Detective?
Yeah.
Well, it's just smooth water
rolling over sand, now.
Well, after Ann died,
the townsfolk went out there
and pulled the rocks out.
The same ones
that snagged the clothesline
that was around Ann's neck.
They loaded them into a pickup truck,
took them out to the edge of town,
and smashed 'em.
Nice and smooth.
Like they figured that destroying them
would ward off any future evil.
Well, I guess
they left a rock, or two.
-How does it fit?
-(CHANGING WINDS PLAYING)
I have a navy,
I mean, if you'd rather.
No, I just think my hips
are a little higher than yours.
AMMA: Curvy.
It's fine. I'm fine, fine.
Let me do that.
This funeral is going to be very hard.
I loved those girls.
How did you know those girls, again?
Camille, I'm very involved in
the community. It's our family's duty.
More dead little girls.
As if Marian wasn't enough.
Were you friends with Natalie?
Enough to be sad, too,
which is why I should go.
You're gonna stay here with Gayla,
and have ice cream.
-l want to know where you are.
-ALAN: Mmm-hmm.
Camille, maybe,
you should stay back, too,
-given your state of mind.
-I have to go. It's my job.
I think Camille knows how to behave.
Adora, we don't want to be late.
We're fine. And I don't want you
to talk like that, like it's work.
We're going to the funeral
to support that poor family.
Ladies, can we please go?
Yes.
I love you, love you, love you.
ALAN: Are you gonna ride with us?
CAMILLE: No, no. I'm gonna drive.
I have to grab my purse.
ALAN: I'll wait in the car.
ADORA: All right.
RICHARD: Morning.
Kansas City.
You know, I've been thinking.
Uh-oh.
Why does a killer
change his MO like that?
The first body left at the kill site
in the forest, but Natalie,
she's dumped in the middle of town
like a prop, or a doll.
My daughter had one of them dolls.
Little "O" for a mouth.
Creepy little fucking things.
Getting her there was risky.
Way more chance of getting caught.
Well, some killers want to get caught.
A cry for help.
This one likes making
people scared for their girls.
Can we just save The Silence
of the Lambs routine for another time?
Look, Bill, I get it, okay.
This is your home.
You gotta look out for your people,
but odds are
the killer is gonna show up here.
Soak up the atmosphere.
I read them books, too,
Agent Starling.
Watch out for anyone trying to
insert himself into the action.
Anyone trying too hard
with the family.
The nature of this crime,
it's personal.
This guy wants to rule the town.
Well, he may not rule it,
but he sure as hell got our attention.
-Look good?
-That's fine.
Yeah, I know you're fond of me,
but don't think
this means we're married.
(CHURCH BELL TOLLING)
Come on in, Mrs. Crellin.
This way, please. Sorry, folks.
I'm so sorry.
Come on, Sweetie. I saved you a place.
Get your cute, little butt in here.
Good Lord. I don't think
I've seen you in a month of Sundays.
-You saw me at the search, Jackie.
-I didn't really see you.
See, it was that sweet tea,
and its kick.
Please tell me y'all
aren't waiting on us.
Well, we weren't waiting
for the pastor. That's for sure.
You look great.
I don't know what I expected.
-You look absolutely...
-Jackie, inside voice. It's a funeral.
You look great.
(ALAN PLAYING HYMN ON PIANO)
They can't release the body
because of the investigation.
Can you even imagine?
That's Natalie's mama and daddy.
They're divorced.
They keep to themselves.
PRIEST: We gather here, to celebrate
the life of Natalie Keene.
Her death is a great tragedy,
but we must
turn our hearts to the light.
We begin with some words of comfort
from Natalie's mother, Jeannie Keene.
Jeannie?
JEANNIE: Natalie was a surprise baby,
but we were grateful for her.
Almost six years
after our sweet son, a girl.
I taped a pink ribbon
to her little, bald head.
She snatched it off.
Six weeks old,
and our girl knew what she wanted.
(PEOPLE LAUGH)
She was always like that.
A spitfire, a contrarian,
a tomboy, a goofball.
Smart as a whip,
she didn't suffer fools.
I remember when she was two,
I was making goo-goo eyes at her.
-I swear she rolled her eyes.
-(PEOPLE LAUGH)
In our first home in Philadelphia,
she'd sneak out and explore the city.
In Wind Gap, she roamed the woods,
and would report back to us
on everything she saw.
She talked a lot...
(VOICE BREAKING) She talked a lot
when she had something to say.
And was quiet if she didn't.
-I wish more grown-ups had that gift.
-(JOHN SOBBING)
It is horrible to lose a child.
It is unbearable to lose her this way,
to a murdering fiend.
I know I'm supposed to be forgiving,
but I am furious.
I know what good people say.
"An eye for an eye
makes the whole world blind."
I wish I could be that gentle.
I want revenge.
I want justice
for her daddy,
who will never get to walk her
down the aisle.
For her brother,
who was her best friend.
(CONTINUES SOBBING)
And for me,
who will never, ever
recover from her loss.
We love you, Natalie. (SOBBING)
PRIEST: Heaven does, indeed,
have another angel,
but we must know that Natalie has gone
to a better place, to sit with God.
Camille, please.
For the sake of the family, please.
PRIEST: Now, would you please stand
as we say, together, the words
Our Savior Christ has taught us?
(FABRIC TEARS)
ALL: Our Father, Who art in heaven,
hallowed be Thy name,
Thy kingdom come, Thy will be done,
on Earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread,
and forgive us our trespasses,
as we forgive those
who trespass against us.
And lead us not into temptation,
but deliver us from evil.
-Hi, Sammie.
-Hi.
(GIRLS LAUGHING)
-Hey, sis.
-What are you doing here?
Shouldn't you be home,
eating ice cream?
Any chance I can
bum a few bucks for the Sprite?
-Sprite?
-Yeah.
Sure.
I knew you'd be cool.
You all, isn't my sister the coolest?
-So cool.
-(GIRLS LAUGHING)
Don't try to work me, Amma.
I've been playing
that game for 20 years.
-JODES: Twenty years?
-Yeah.
Then you're old enough to be my mom.
-Do you know my mom?
-Shut up, Jodes.
Amma, Mama wants you home,
and I want you home.
AMMA: Mmm-mmm.
It's dangerous out there for you.
People are killing little girls.
-Not the cool ones.
-(GIRLS LAUGHING)
Yeah, we're going
straight to Kelsey's,
and I'll be home before curfew.
I swear.
-Straight there?
-Mmm-hmm.
And you call me if you need a ride?
-You promise?
-Yeah, I promise.
Thank you.
Make sure you get home before...
-Mama?
-Yeah. Okay.
Amma. Careful with the vodka.
Yeah.
-Thank you, girls.
-Thank you, Sammie.
-Bye, girls.
-GIRLS: Bye!
CAMILLE: Jeannie Keene is having
all the mourners over to her house.
I think that's pretty nice.
When Marian died,
Mama shuttered our house
for a year with us inside.
Listen. I know this is
delicate ground for you.
-It's not.
-Okay, well, good.
Then get as many personal details
as you can,
and, remember, you're not there
-to solve the mystery.
-Yeah.
Well the brother interests me.
He's not your typical Wind Gap fare.
Excellent. We want characters.
Tell us about the Keene house.
Are Natalie's shoes still out?
Are the photos friendly, or familiar?
Piano, books?
Are the paintings
on the wall original,
or from Antiques 'R' Us, like ours?
Well, why don't I go
through the ice box while I'm at it?
Hey, don't be a wise-ass, kiddo.
You know what I mean.
This could be your big break
if you do it right.
-You gotta stop saying that.
-All right.
Don't go gentle.
Get what you need for this story.
-You're right. Yes, sir.
-Okay, kiddo.
-Bye-bye.
-Bye.
(SIGHS)
-If you're about to say...
-"You can't solve all the problems
-"of the entire world?"
-The other one.
-"Hope you know what you're doing?"
-Bingo.
I understand what you're trying to do,
but what she needs now, is time.
(SCOFFS) Don't we all?
Look, she's a great investigator,
could be a great writer,
maybe even have a life,
but she needs to deal with her issues.
And stop thinking
that vodka doesn't stay on her breath.
You can't fix her
like another thing in this house.
Not now. Can't take that on, too.
(SIGHS)
I'l think about it.
(EILEEN SCOFFS)
-No, 1 will.
-Yeah, right.
(A WOMAN'S HANDS PLAYING)
EILEEN: Yeah, right!
(IN THE EVENING PLAYING ON RADIO)
(BLACK SCREEN PLAYING)
MR. KEENE: I don't care
who told you to come!
Get the fuck out of this house!
Get out of this house! Come on!
Don't make me tell you again!
Just beat it! Get out of here!
BOB: Fuck you!
MAN: Mr. Keene, come on, now.
MR. KEENE: Beat it!
Shut it!
Son of a bitch!
(ENGINE STARTING)
(TURNS OFF MUSIC)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
MAN 1: She thought
that was a good idea, too.
WOMAN 1: I agree.
(GUESTS CHATTERING)
MAN 2: Well, well, well.
Camille's here.
ALAN: I'm not sure that's so.
Adora says it's a comfort
having Marian's room.
WOMAN 2: The little bitch
just waltzed right in here.
CHRIS: No, patrol is what we do.
No, I say, we start over
on the beaner side of town.
Think about it.
A man who could slaughter
pigs all day, that's the type of man
that can yank out
a little girl's teeth.
-All that blood.
-MAN 1: Okay, Chris, stop.
MAN 2: You know where you're going?
Stumbling back to your bed is where.
I brought John some food.
You need to eat, John.
Ashley, John will eat
when he wants to eat. Thank you.
ASHLEY: Okay.
Would you look at them?
Just sitting all by themselves
in a group of people.
And then they wonder why
they're not a part of this town.
GIRL: The funeral was nice, at least.
(SCOFFS) Well, that girl
she described is not Natalie.
Believe me. I should know.
Appreciate it.
MAN: (ON PHONE)
Deputy Coroner's office.
Camille! I heard
you were back in town.
Watch the liquor, watch the men.
- (WOMEN LAUGHING)
-I'm kidding.
ANGIE: How are you?
You never come home.
Well, she's in big-shit St. Louis.
I love St. Louis.
Dan and I took the girls there
after Christmas last year.
Jack and I were thinking about that.
Taking the kids for a visit.
I have four, all boys.
-KATIE: Do you have kids, Camille?
-Here.
-I said I'm not hungry.
-Fine.
-Fuck it.
-GRETCHEN: Sorry.
I guess I have five boys.
ANGIE: What about you, Camille?
You must have a boyfriend.
Do you guys know the Keene family?
You know, Angie's due
in September. Look at this.
-Congratulations.
-I know I look big.
I get bigger every time.
What can you do?
So, the brother, John,
he seems to be taking
the death kind of...
He's been crying up a storm.
-I don't mean to be mean...
-Sure, you do.
But it's a bit much.
It's like he's a little boy.
A lot of tears.
Well, did he fit in at school?
Little Ashley Wheeler made sure
he fit in with the right crowd.
She's a cheerleader.
Like us in the day, right?
-Yeah.
-Until you quit us. (CHUCKLES)
But he is an odd damn duck.
He seems sorta gay to me.
I mean, that would make sense.
If he's the one who did it.
Because sometimes, when siblings
have unnatural affections,
that leads to other things.
KATIE: God, you watch too much news.
JACKIE: Camille Preaker!
KATIE: So damn sick
of your damn theories.
You owe me a scoop...
-It was nice catching up.
-...reporter girl.
ANGIE: I hate her dress.
Thank you.
What are you doing
with those nasty vipers? Lord!
Oh, I'm so happy to see you.
I mean, your mother shows me
pictures of you, but...
She does? What pictures?
Well, she paints a picture of you.
-She's so proud.
-I do not believe you, Jackie.
Well, that's ‘cause I lie like a rug.
You turned out so...
Wonderful, smart, beautiful,
successful, and brave.
-You do lie, Jackie.
-No, I mean it.
I mean it. You tackled those demons.
My demons are not remotely tackled.
They're just mildly concussed.
Well, I'd say that's better than
the rest of us, isn't it?
-How's your mama doing?
-She's sad.
Mmm. I wish you knew her
before Marian. She was lovely,
and frivolous, like a kite.
You still lying, Jackie?
I don't think so.
You're the best.
CAMILLE:
I didn't want him to starve.
I'm sorry for your loss.
She stunned ants
and fed them to her spiders.
It was nasty,
but it was good for Natalie,
the outdoors.
Well,
sounds like she was a tomboy.
Was she playing outside
when she went missing?
Overly Park. Broad daylight.
I heard that she was
friends with Ann Nash.
Until they weren't.
Fine by me they fell out.
That dad, he's a strange one.
Have the police talked to you?
They usually question the family,
these kind of cases.
(SIGHS) I was in Philly at the time,
if that's what you're asking.
What about your son?
My son loved Natalie.
He would've died before hurting her.
(RADIO CHATTER)
MAN: (ON RADIO)
Ninety-seven, over.
You can't just go into the room
of a dead little girl.
You of all people should know
how private, how personal that is.
Well, I was just...
(CRYING)
I don't know how this family
will ever get over it.
CAMILLE: We didn't.
Go report somewhere else,
and let these people be.
Marks on the gums
and inside the cheeks
indicate that the teeth
were removed by pliers.
-What kind of pliers?
-Household pliers.
Sharp-edged pliers.
How hard is it to pull a tooth?
It takes some muscle.
Baby teeth come out a little easier.
The killer would have
some adrenaline pumping,
if he did it right away.
CAMILLE: Hi.
What's your name?
You know, you guys are the first kids
I've seen out playing by themselves.
I ain't no pussy.
I was wondering,
you know Natalie Keene?
No.
But you heard what happened.
Yeah, from James Capisi first.
He was here when it happened.
Did he say who took her?
The woman in white.
Woman in white, like the story?
Ask James Capisi.
Lives over on Crestwood.
Yellow house with a tire swing.
Would you show me?
No, me and James
ain't friends no more. He got weird.
After the woman in white?
What'd she look like?
BOY: Come on. Throw it, man!
Oh, dear.
You look wan.
I suppose I haven't
really eaten today.
You can't go giving the girls
advice you don't follow.
You need your strength.
Now, now, go eat, you don't want
to look like a hairless cat.
(ADORA CHUCKLES)
Don't.
It's not right on a day like today.
-Don't.
-That's not so.
The Lord loves the world
and all its contradictions.
I hope so.
(FRENCH MUSIC PLAYING)
(ADORA CRYING)
(FRENCH MUSIC PLAYING ON HEADPHONES)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
Sorry.
Go get the ball, you idiot.
Fucker.
(GRUNTS)
JAMES: We don't need nothin".
Church brung us food.
James?
I was just...
I was talking
with your friend, little guy, mullet.
Dee ain't no friend.
Well, he was just
telling me about the woman in white.
The one who took Natalie.
She did.
Well, did you tell the police that?
Yes, ma'am.
They say I'm seeing ghosts.
It's like the story.
She ain't no ghost. It was real.
-Did Natalie see her?
-We were playing.
Ball went in the woods, so, she went.
I hollered at her,
but she was gone.
You here by yourself?
-Is your mama sick?
-She gets along all right.
But I don't need no taking care of.
Okay, so, I think
I need to talk to your mom, now.
(DOORBELL RINGING)
Hi. Sorry to bother you.
Your son was
just in the window when I came by.
He's playing with a gun.
Why you care?
Just seems a little young
to have a gun.
Are we breaking some law,
or something?
-I don't know.
-Then screw off.
Mrs. Capisi...
"Mrs. Capisi."
(SCOFFS)
I just wanted to talk to you about
what your son saw
when Natalie Keene was taken.
I'd talk for a fifty.
I'm not allowed to pay for...
Then I'm not allowed to talk.
MARIAN: Mama!
-Mamal!
-Yeah.
You need to take your nap.
(AMMA SNORING)
(SIGHS) Thank fucking God.
(ADORA CRYING)
(ENGINE STARTS)
(THERE'S A KEY PLAYING)
CAMILLE: That's nice of you.
Didn't want Mrs. Keene
driving through town,
getting hit with sign after sign.
Yeah. Did you do the same
with the signs for Ann?
I did.
I don't know what to do with these.
Can't bear to throw 'em away.
Probably just put 'em
in my desk drawer next to Ann's.
You have a nice day.
(MUSIC STOPS)
(GRUNTS) God damn it!
Got no comment, Miss Preaker.
(HAMMERS)
I just spoke with James Capisi.
I'm just wondering why the police
are discounting his story.
You got an eyewitness to an abduction.
The eyewitness is eight.
He's the kid
of a factory worker whose mama...
So, that's the problem?
That his mama makes minimum wage
butchering pigs for my mama?
-How is your mama? She holdin' up?
-She's great.
You know.
So, he's not credible?
Is that what you're saying?
He's got a mom with cancer,
and she's a meth addict on top.
-Well, I don't see how that affects...
-That boy...
When he does go to school,
he comes with tall tales
about where he's been.
His mama took him to Disney World.
She wears those hospital gowns,
white gowns.
Now, he sees a woman in white
do bad things? It's a cry for help.
Well, when I was a kid,
we used to scare each other
with stories about a woman in white
killing little children.
Yeah, I, too. Town folklore.
Well, I don't know.
Maybe someone doesn't
believe it's folklore.
Maybe they want to make it real.
Yeah, like I just said,
James Capisi...
There's no woman in white,
Miss Preaker.
Trust me, it's a man did this.
(HAMMERING)
Bobby, what the hell are you doing?
Get over here!
Porch is the limit. Get over here.
Come on! Get on the damn porch!
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong with you, son?
(I'D RATHER GO BLIND PLAYING)
MAN: She, you know.
She may be able to cover that up.
(MEN LAUGHING)
Maker's Mark, please, double.
Camille Preaker.
You beautiful girl, come say hi.
Come on, Big City.
Come tell us about your adventures.
-Yeah. Your exploits.
-Yeah.
CAMILLE: On the job.
-No rest for the wicked?
-Nope.
James Capisi's mom made a call.
Thank you.
Well, I'm surprised she bothered.
She didn't seem to care
that he had a gun.
This fucking town.
Guns, and meth, and pigs, no offense.
None taken.
So, do you believe him? James?
We have not eliminated
nor we have identified
any theories in the Wind Gap case.
Why were you taking soil
off of Bob Nash's tire today?
I get it, Camille. You can't just sit
with me and have a drink. I get it.
So, why don't you do me a favor
and help me with the case, okay?
Educate me about Wind Gap
because I'll be honest with you,
I can't quite get a handle on it.
If somebody says "Bless your heart,"
what they really mean is "fuck you."
So I've been told by a woman
who just said, "Bless your heart."
Let me guess. Jackie O'Neill?
-She's a character.
-She's sweet.
Only woman who was
genuinely nice to me.
Oh, come one.
Don't give me that bullshit.
I heard about you,
princess of Wind Gap.
-Bow down.
-I said "genuinely."
So, how'd you become
a reporter, anyway?
Coming from here?
Well, just because it's a small town,
doesn't mean we're all rubes.
Believe it or not, some of us read.
We even write.
(MEN LAUGHING)
Some of us do.
There you go,
from the admiring and the envious.
RICHARD: That's what they said?
I don't really feel comfortable
saying what they said.
Next up,
four blowjob shots just for Camille.
(LAUGHING)
Assholes.
Hey, where you going? Come on, Kurt.
(SIGHS) Okay, Wind Gap.
Sorry, I got sidetracked.
Not really.
Those gentlemen told you a whole lot.
Yeah, I want more.
I'll talk off-record.
-Fine. That's fine.
-Yeah?
Okay then, intrepid girl reporter.
-Intrepid.
-Do your worst.
Bob Nash, John Keene.
They're suspects. Why?
We always look at male relatives.
Nash said he was
driving home from work.
Keene said he
was just driving, period.
Neither can prove it.
No tolls, no E-pass,
no CCTV down here,
which, I have to add,
is fucking ludicrous.
Vickery says the killer is a man.
Positively a man. Why positively?
The statistics for one thing,
and it takes a lot of strength
to pull teeth.
-Says who?
-Me.
I tried it.
-You fucking with me?
-No, I tried it.
With a giant pig's head.
-You're a sick fuck.
-Bless your heart.
AMMA: Look. Look, now, it's right.
ADORA:
Just don't put too many pillows.
AMMA: This isn't right.
-This isn't right!
-ADORA: We'll make it right, sweet.
ALAN: So senseless.
Breaks your heart.
Jeannie Keene's house was very nice.
-A little faux bucolic.
-ALAN: Marian,
it all just makes me think of...
But that eulogy of hers was very odd.
For her to tell the world she's angry.
Hi.
Where were you?
-Well, first I was at...
-Never mind.
I don't want to know.
-AMMA: This isn't right.
-(ADORA SHUSHING)
This isn't right!
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
-Hello?
-FRANK: What do you got, kiddo?
Well at the church,
the mourners were acting
like the funeral
was the hot ticket in town.
And at the house,
there's a "whatever" sweatshirt
by the door.
John Keene, the brother,
popular because of his girlfriend.
Probably an oddball like his sister,
and extremely close with his sister,
which the town finds odd.
The owner of Precious Guns and Gold...
(LAUGHS) I love that.
Yeah, well, he says
that he's all sold out of guns.
He's okay on gold.
Yeah, and I have a boy who swears
he saw the woman in white
take Natalie,
which is just a bit
of Wind Gap folklore.
Well what else about Natalie?
Basically a profile on her, you know?
Nothing people go crazier for
than a murdered little girl.
Well, I got a look at her room,
decorated by her mother.
You can tell ‘cause it's all flowery
and pink in contrast to Natalie,
which was sneakers and dirty clothes
and a spider that
she kept in a jar by the door.
Oh! Now, that's gold.
We'll have to figure out
how to use the spider.
"A lover of animals, even ones
that can repel and frighten.”
Yeah. That's good stuff.
The folks give you
permission to be in there?
Otherwise, we're screwed.
Not legally, probably...
But ethically.
We're fine. Her mom gave me a tour.
Good work, kiddo.
That's all fantastic detail.
Use it.
"An adventurous spirit
whose independent streak
"and love of nature
may have been her undoing.”
-What do you think?
-It's a bit much.
How many drinks in are you?
(LAUGHS) Hey, kiddo, it's a week day.
I'm on the wagon week days,
you know me.
So, how are you holding up?
Eileen wants to know.
Yeah. Um...
It's a bit weird being home,
but it's good to be working
on something big again.
-Right.
-Yeah.
-Now, you'd tell me if...
-I'm good, Curry.
Let me be good.
-Okay?
-Okay.
You file as quick as you can.
Okay. Well, don't read it till
you've had three more.
-You'll think it's a masterpiece. Bye.
-(CHUCKLING)
Yeah, it's, funny, funny girl.
(AMMA SCREAMING)
-AMMA: It's not right!
-(ADORA SHUSHING)
-It has to be right!
-ALAN: Amma, remember...
-Hey, what's going on?
-(AMMA CRYING)
-Hey, Mama, what's going on?
-No!
-Stop it!
-Is she all right?
She's scared. She's lashing out.
She just saw two
of her friends murdered.
(AMMA SOBBING)
You were drunk at the Keene's house.
I wasn't...
But even if I was, this is Wind Gap.
-Everyone's drunk.
-Camille...
Now, Amma's throwing a fit,
and you're giving me
a lecture about drinking?
-Camille...
-You're amazing.
You will always find a way to, what?
-Camille, Camille...
-What? What?
I just want things to be nice with us,
but maybe I don't know how.
Natalie reminded me of you.
Always running around in the woods.
Coming home wild and filthy.
I thought maybe I could help her.
Since, clearly, I couldn't help you.
It's okay, Mama.
I think Camille could be good.
Can't you, Camille?
-(EXHALES)
(BLACK SCREEN PLAYING)
Fuck it.
(BLACK SCREEN CONTINUES
PLAYING ON HEADPHONES)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(BLACK SCREEN CONTINUES PLAYING)