(DANCE AND ANGELA PLAYING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(PIG SQUEALING)
BOY: (WHOOPS)
Here, little piggy!
-(TEENAGERS LAUGHING)
-Come on! Get back here!
-ALL: Oh!
-Get up, you little...
Hey, John! Gonna bring me some bacon?
(GIRLS LAUGHING)
GIRL: What's the matter, John?
You break your ankle?
AMMA: Snatch it!
Pretend it's a little girl.
ALL: Ooh...
AMMA: Big guns!
(GIRLS LAUGHING)
(SIREN BLARING)
Well, isn't this a shit-ton of stupid?
Go on, now, party's over.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(VEHICLE APPROACHING)
(AMMA GRUNTING)
Oh, shit.
Don't tell Mama.
(AMMA GIGGLING)
-She loves her roses so much.
-(CAMILLE SHUSHING)
Get in, come on.
-Oh, what are we drinkin'?
-No. We are definitely not drinkin'.
(GROANS) Boring.
There is never anything to do here.
No?
So what were you up to?
Hangin' with my friends.
They love me.
They do, you know,
love me.
They'd do anything for me.
I just ask, and...
They're my besties.
Here, take this.
Why are you being sweet to me?
Why shouldn't I be?
'Cause I'm not nice.
I wasn't nice either
when I was your age.
Well, I'm nearly a woman.
That's what Adora says.
Adora doesn't know about you.
But I do.
I can tell.
You hate this place like me,
but you love dead girls.
Couldn't stay away.
I'm here for the paper, that's all.
You weren't curious?
-About Wind Gap?
-About me.
Drink this.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Nope.
Don't you want one?
Sometimes. Depends.
Kids?
Don't you want a little baby?
Babies are so cute.
Well, I wouldn't know
the first thing to do with a baby.
You take care of them.
You can practice on me, if you want.
Oh, you seem to be doing a pretty
good job taking care of yourself.
I've never had a sister.
I just wanna know you.
-(THUNDER RUMBLING)
-Sister.
-My long-lost sister.
-(RAIN PATTERING)
NURSE: We checkin' in?
We are.
Let me see.
Come on.
Press hard.
Sign 'em on the third page
and we'll get that patched up.
-You have insurance?
-(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
Yeah.
(MUSIC PLAYING ON EARPHONES)
Alice.
Time's up.
(PHONE RINGING)
I have an intake.
Well, find somebody.
-Come on, five more minutes.
-No, I can't. Go on.
Am I the only one workin'
in this goddamn place?
Yes!
(QUIETLY) Go.
(NORMAL) Yes, let me talk to him.
You're kidding me.
Alice, Camille. Camille, Alice.
Good night, girls.
(LOCKING DOOR)
Don't talk to me.
-(CELL PHONE RINGING)
-(MUSIC PLAYING ON EARPHONES)
Hello.
FRANK: Did I wake you up?
No, I just got back from spin class.
(LAUGHS) Your piece wasn't bad.
It'll be on the website later,
paper tomorrow.
Good. When can I come home?
You know what I want.
Are parents taking precautions?
Are people letting kids
out of their sight?
And don't be afraid
to get a little personal.
Like, how does it feel to be home?
Easy.
Every day is a gift.
(CLASSIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Last night I threw up three times.
-I don't like it.
-ALAN: It's just chills, dear.
ADORA: Give Dr. Manning a call.
Just in case.
I love you, love you, I love you.
AMMA: Where's Camille, Mama?
SAMMIE: Have a nice day.
Whaddya know, Joe?
(SIGHS)
RICHARD: A mysterious trucker who
murdered two girls ten months apart.
Half the workers over there
are fuckin' Mexicans.
Whole villages move up from...
Wherever.
Bring their families, their habits.
Who knows what else.
Fuckin' bullshit.
RICHARD: So you're looking at
a trucker or a Mexican
or anyone that doesn't actually live
in or about the town of Wind Gap.
-VICKERY: You don't know the people...
-I know this is a crime of passion.
Nobody touched those girls.
Passion doesn't always
have to equal sex.
This type of thing can scratch
a different kind of itch.
Power. Control.
Now you're just makin' shit up.
RICHARD: I was asked down here
because this is what I do.
I went through your incident reports,
and most Saturday nights
you got a few rowdy teens
and the same drunk
stealing the same car
and leaving it in the same cow pasture
as last Saturday night.
His name is Earl.
And it was his car
before he lost it in a bet.
Right, you know these people.
And nine out of 10 murder victims,
they knew their killer.
The teeth, the strangling...
Someone had a particular problem
with those particular girls.
Anyone fit that profile?
Any specific fuckin' Mexican, Bill?
That'd be great for you, wouldn't it?
-Killer with a grudge.
-What does that mean?
A serial? I betcha
that pops a career into high gear
quicker than shit through a goose.
I gotta think of the bottom line.
All the small town
sit-on-your-ass jobs are taken.
(CHUCKLES)
You best remember...
My town, my case.
My ass.
(ROLLER-SKATERS APPROACHING)
(DOOR OPENING)
It was someone they knew.
VICKERY: Or it wasn't.
(CAR APPROACHING)
Hi.
She wouldn't talk to you, huh?
Well, she had a few choice words
for me.
She's not doing so well.
-Self-medicating.
-Mmm.
We learned about that in health class.
You learn about that
just by living here.
(LAUGHS) Well, I'm Ashley.
Wheeler. John's girlfriend.
-Camille Preaker.
-I know.
I know all about you.
My baby sister Jodes,
she's friends with Amma.
And my older sister Danielle,
she was a freshman
when you were a senior.
She said you were it back in the day.
Yeah, well, that was a long time ago.
No! Dani's married now. Three kids.
She got fat.
Well, tell her I said hello.
And to diet and exercise.
I will.
You wanna talk to John, right?
‘Cause I can make that happen.
He listens to me.
Yeah. Yeah, I'd appreciate that. Yeah.
It'd be good for him
to talk to someone.
Everyone thinks he's guilty
just ‘cause he's sensitive.
I hate that.
I'll bet you're sensitive.
Writers are sensitive.
You could help everyone understand.
-Should I just wait here?
-No. Not now.
He's always agitated
after he talks to his mother.
He's not even staying here anymore.
He's been staying with me
ever since Natalie went missin'.
Just come by my house later.
1834 Tillman.
I'll have John ready for you.
ALICE: Fake piece of shit!
Fuck.
Are you trying to eat it?
What...
(CHUCKLES)
I'm not that good.
Well, yeah.
Okay. There you go.
My mama always says
a lipstick makes you look like a lady,
so there you go.
Rub 'em together.
Now you look like a lady.
Thanks.
You're lucky
you can still wear skirts.
It's a pain.
Making sure
they cover enough territory.
But I made a promise to myself.
Three inches above the knee.
Otherwise, well, you know.
I haven't worn a skirt since college.
How old are you?
Older than you.
I always thought
it was something you grow out of.
I've just never been very good
at the adult thing, I guess.
Peter Pan of cutting.
Yeah. I won't grow up, not me.
My mom hates
everything I wear anyway, so...
What about you? Any visitors today?
My mom said she's comin', so...
She like your clothes?
No.
God, no.
What kind of stuff do you listen to?
That's not really my thing, music.
Well, no wonder you're here, girl.
You're here too, girl. FYI.
Yeah, but...
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Want these? I can get the hell
out of here whenever I want.
(THANK YOU PLAYING ON EARPHONES)
(ENGINE STOPS)
(BELLS JINGLING)
-Hi.
(CLEARS THROAT)
You lookin' at him? John Keene?
I got my eyes on everyone.
You talkin' about the case,
or you just talkin' about me?
What, you're not gonna share anything?
-Not with you.
-Come on.
Theories? Suspects?
You can either help me get it right,
orl can...
Or what? You go to Vickery,
give him that big-eyed flirt
you throwin' my way?
What can I say? I love my job.
Well, good luck with that.
He's a hamster on a wheel
chasin' imaginary truckers.
Mexican hog workers.
You don't think he's right?
No comment.
Come on. The teeth, the bodies...
It sure doesn't feel random, does it?
And that dirt that you pulled off
of Bob Nash's tires...
You trying to tell me
he's not a suspect?
-I'm not trying to tell you anything.
-Okay, give me some insight.
I read your sob story.
Wait till the rest of this place
gets a hold of it.
They'll all be juicin' up
their stories,
angling for their 15 minutes.
And that bullshit from Natalie's room?
There's no way
her mom let you in there.
The best thing for both of us...
Stay out of my way.
(THERE'S A KEY PLAYING)
(TURNS OFF RADIO)
You know, if I were paranoid, Chief,
I'd think you were checkin' up on me.
I'm not the one writin' stories
about our town.
You think about it,
it's you checkin' up on us.
You really think that Ann and Natalie
were murdered by some random trucker?
That boy from Kansas City
talks like a woman from Wind Gap.
Doesn't help anything,
you talkin' to people,
riling folks up.
You got two mutilated girls
on your hands.
Someone else is doing the riling.
BOB: Yeah, Ann was a talker,
bossy sometimes, but she's smart.
Different smart from other kids.
She'd ask me things
that were grown-up, you know?
Stuff she thought was dumb,
stuff she thought was funny.
Can't do that with my other kids.
Hell, I can't even do that
with my wife.
She had never wanted kids.
That was all me.
Figured it would be different
once she loves 'em.
(SIGHS)
What kind of person does that?
Hurt a child.
Somebody with no feeling inside,
is that it?
Are you talking about your wife,
or are you talking...
Talkin' about Ann.
The person who did that to Ann.
And the police, they haven't found
a goddamn thing.
You don't think
they're doing a good job?
They're talkin' to me.
Like I'm the one.
Do you think that has anything
to do with your DUIs?
Or the assault?
I did some checkin'.
What, you never had a few too many?
I got into a fight once...
So that means I killed my daughter?
-No, I'm not implying that.
-Yeah, but they are!
That guy from Kansas City?
He's been all over me
and all over my family?
You know what?
(CLEARING THROAT)
Do you still think
that it's a man that killed Ann?
‘Cause there's a little boy who said
that he saw a woman grab Natalie.
What, the Capisi kid?
-Yeah.
-No.
It was a man. I...
I'd put money on it.
The women around here,
they don't kill with their hands.
They talk, and you're dead.
That's true enough.
If I was pretty and that Keene boy
lived on this side of town,
it'd be a whole different story.
He's got no alibi.
John Keene has no motive.
What, and I do?
That kid, he's all quiet,
he keeps to himself
like he's got something to hide?
You know? Maybe urges,
things he can't control?
I seen him sometimes
out by the plant...
-(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
-What?
-(DOOR OPENS)
-Ms. Crellin's here.
I am so sorry, Bob.
I had no idea she would come here
and pressure you.
-No.
-No, we're just in the middle of...
How dare you interrogate him?
You are not the police, Camille.
You are not to harass good people.
Hmm... Your mama, she tutored Ann.
-Ann was so fond of her.
-ADORA: Camille.
I think you should leave.
I'm here on a social visit.
Your presence here is inappropriate.
-We weren't done talkin'...
-Yes.
You are.
(BEEPS)
-(YELLING)
-(THERE'S A KEY PLAYING ON RADIO)
Damn it!
(MAMMA'S GONNA GIVE YOU LOVE
PLAYING ON EARPHONES)
Hey, Charlie.
(THERE'S A KEY PLAYING)
(TURNS OFF RADIO)
(ENGINE STOPS)
(PIGS SNORTING)
(PIGLETS SQUEALING)
(THERE'S A KEY PLAYING ON RADIO)
Thank you.
I appreciate what you did,
and I apologize
for my daughter's behavior.
Which one?
What are you talkin' about?
I caught Amma out after curfew
with her friends.
Ammal
Come on now, there's no need for that.
Gayla?
Gayla.
-Yes, miss?
-Would you fetch Amma for me, please?
And get the Chief his usual.
The usual with coffee, or ice?
Thank you, darlin'.
How did you know Camille was at Bob's?
You're not having him watched,
are you?
We got eyes on him.
He's not the only one.
I refuse to believe
he'd kill his own child.
-Who would do such a thing?
-We're investigating all leads, Adora.
Well, I do hope
you're getting somewhere.
-The detective...
-He's convinced it's one of ours.
But you're not, are you?
I'm not sure.
Might have to start wrapping my head
around the idea.
But you're broadening the search.
What about the slaughterhouse?
That's a little obvious,
don't you think?
Those girls,
I was a part of their lives.
And with Marian, it feels personal.
Hey, we'll get there. It's all right.
We'll get there, we'll get there.
We're checkin' everybody
you got workin' for you,
all the people you let go.
AMMA: You wanted to see me, Mama?
ADORA: Chief Vickery told me
something I find alarming.
-Come here.
-VICKERY: I've gotta get back to work.
I'll have this coffee another time.
ADORA: What are you wearing?
I was just playing
dress-ups with Kelsey and...
You are not to be outside
this house after curfew.
-Never.
-I was safe.
-That is not for you to decide.
-Well, you let Camille do it!
Excuse me?
You think bad things didn't happen
to little girls when she was my age?
I know they did.
And you let Camille...
And look what happened to her.
You need to understand
your sister does not see herself
in a good light.
It's caused her difficulty.
You need to be careful with Camille.
-She's not someone to be admired.
-What difficulty? What difficulty?
No. Look at me. Look at me.
You are not safe around her.
Do you understand me?
Do you understand?
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Come in.
We're in the carriage house,
in the back. Follow me.
(WIND CHIMES TINKLING)
Come onin.
CAMILLE:
So, you've been staying with Ashley?
Yeah.
Yeah, her parents have been very kind.
How does your mother feel about it?
She understands.
It's...
It's just not comfortable for me there
right now.
-Thanks.
-I thought...
-I thought school was out.
-Oh, itis.
Sometimes I just get
to feelin' spirited.
-Can I get you one of those?
-No. No.
Okay, John, do you mind?
-No, we don't mind.
- (RECORDER BEEPS)
So what I would like
to be able to do is just really
describe Natalie to our readers.
ASHLEY: She was such a tomboy.
Always climbin' trees,
and skinnin' her knee.
Well, Bob Nash has been talkin'
to me about Ann and Natalie.
Why is Bob Nash talking about Natalie?
Well, it's not just Mr. Nash.
Other people are saying
that you two had a very
close relationship.
-And what's that supposed to mean?
-Bob Nash is a drunk.
He doesn't even pretend to hide it.
Did you guys spend
a lot of time together?
Yeah, of course, she was my sister.
What did Bob Nash say about me?
Well, I'm more interested
to know what you have to say.
I bet he told you all about
his perfect little Ann, right?
Sometimes I think
if Natalie never met her...
That little girl is dead, too.
He has a lot of sorrow
in his heart for her.
-Did the police speak with you?
-About what?
Your alibi.
Where you were the night
that Natalie went missin'.
I was out drivin' around.
I'm not sure that a grand jury
will appreciate
the romance of an open highway.
I told you.
Yeah, Ashley doesn't
appreciate it, either.
I do.
It's just a...
It's a smaller town than I'm used to.
John is just being noble.
He was with me that night.
Ashley, no.
-No, listen... Look...
-No.
I'm not gonna have people thinkin'
my boyfriend is a fuckin' baby killer,
thank you very much.
Hey.
How long have you lived here, John?
A little over two years.
Since I was a sophomore.
You like it here?
I miss...
I miss that, in the city, you can...
You can walk outside your front door
and there's people all around you.
And they don't know a thing about you.
You could be anyone.
Natalie never cared
what people thought.
Like this one time,
she made up her own language
with the alphabet and everything.
She was so excited she refused
to speak English for a week.
(JOHN CHUCKLES)
I shoulda learned it.
I hate it here.
If we'd never come here,
Natalie'd still be alive.
No, you don't mean that.
If you'd never come,
we wouldn't be together.
No, it's this town.
(SOBS) It's this town. And someone
here killed my little sister.
I'm just gonna go get him.
-We can finish this another time.
-One sec.
John.
(MAMMA'S GONNA GIVE YOU LOVE
PLAYING ON EARPHONES)
Mama?
I suppose you spent your day
chatting it up to anyone
who would talk to you.
"Work."
I'm sorry.
I didn't understand
how well you knew him.
I told you I did.
How dare you question me
in my own home?
How dare you take advantage of Bob?
Did you see him when you left?
That man was practically quivering.
He lost his daughter.
You have no idea what that's like.
-Well, I didn't mean to...
-You never mean to do anything.
And yet you cause so much hurt.
Bob,
Amma...
-Amma?
-She's a little girl, Camille.
She doesn't...
She doesn't understand what you are.
Ahh!
(GROANS)
Look what you've done.
I didn't crash the cart
into the rose bushes, Mama.
Nothing's ever your fault, is it?
ALICE: Camille?
(ALICE SNIFFLING)
Does it get better with your family?
Maybe when I'm older, like you?
No.
Not really.
So what do you do?
You survive.
(CRYING)
Thank you.
Hey.
Let's get out of here.
-(THANK YOU PLAYING ON EARPHONES)
-(BOTH CHUCKLE)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Do you think Amma's safe
with Camille in the house?
Why wouldn't she be?
Coming and going at all hours,
the drinking.
She sets a bad example.
Well, Camille is a grown woman.
Her choices don't reflect on us.
She makes me feel
as if I've done something wrong.
As if I'm a bad mother.
You do everything you can
for your children.
You're good to me, Alan.
Then perhaps I should
stay with you tonight.
Just in case.
I'm sure that won't be necessary.
Good night.
(MUSIC PLAYING ON COMPUTER)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Hey.
Jodes told me you were over
at her place talkin' to John Keene.
Yeah.
Did he confess?
-Do you think he did it?
-I don't know.
You do.
-You think he did it.
-Amma.
He's probably innocent.
I mean, he cries a lot,
but he's okay.
Ashley is such a bitch.
I don't know what he sees in her.
Well, she's very pretty.
At parties and stuff he's always
lookin' over his shoulder at me.
It's me he likes. I can tell.
He's a little old for you,
don't you think?
No.
I'm "almost a woman," remember?
All the same, you should give him
some space. He's going through a lot.
Whatever.
He's not my type. Too pretty.
-I'm goin' out. Wanna come?
-No, you are not.
Amma, you're the same age
as Natalie and Ann.
(SIGHS)
Would you have gone, if you were me?
Yes.
But I was stupid, and you're not.
I'll be sure I'm safe.
Like, you comin' with me...
Come on, we'll party.
-You and me.
-No, I need to stay home.
When I finish my work,
I'm gonna go to sleep.
Just like you need to stay home
and go to sleep.
-'Cause I want you to be safe.
-Whatever.
Amma...
You promise me?
Fine. I promise.
Mama says I need
to be careful around you.
Is that true? Are you dangerous?
Thought you were the wild one.
I hung out in parking lots
and I talked to boys.
Wild was different back then.
Sleep well, sister.
(DOOR CLOSES)
-(GASPS)
(FRAME CLATTERS)
(MUSIC PLAYING ON JUKEBOX)
CAMILLE: Give me two more of those.
BARTENDER: Yeah.
It's a peace offering.
I spoke with John Keene.
He says he feels
like he has a bull's-eye on his back.
What do you think?
Hmm. Little sensitive.
Cries at the drop of a hat. Unlikely.
Besides, even if his family's messed
up, he kills his beloved sister?
-It doesn't make any sense.
-True.
She wasn't molested, though.
So, have you eliminated him
as a suspect,
or is he still active?
-Seriously?
-Seriously.
-I'm a pariah here.
Vickery, he thinks I'm a threat,
the folks around here,
they fuckin' hate me.
I don't know what I don't know.
That's ‘cause you're not from here.
So enlighten me.
And how do you suggest
I do that, Officer?
Show me around Wind Gap.
Give me some history.
Well, we don't have
any toothless corpses in our past,
-if that's your angle.
-That's not what I'm saying.
It could be some old crime
that leads to a hidden motive,
something's been festering.
What do I get out of it?
Other than my charming company?
I'll answer three questions for you.
BARTENDER: All right, boys,
let's get out of here. Let's go.
You done drinkin'?
Back in high school
this was the place.
This was party central. It was like
the Midwest Lord of the Flies,
with bonfires and drinkin'
and heavy petting.
-Yeah.
I can picture you doing that.
Outdrinkin' the boys, leading 'em on.
So let me guess.
You were like a preacher's daughter?
Looks, money, and brains?
Well, looks and money
will get you pretty far in this town.
And brains?
Well, that'll get you
out of this town.
So why'd you leave?
(CHUCKLING) You're funny.
Okay.
-Let's dig deep here.
-Okay.
Favorite color? Favorite ice cream?
Favorite season?
-Can you handle it?
-Yeah, I can handle it. Um...
Black.
Coffee. And winter.
-No one likes winter.
-I like winter.
It gets dark early. I like that.
Why?
Because I like the night, all right?
Leave me alone.
-You leave me alone.
-No. Stop lookin' at me.
Stop hittin' on me.
-You're not my type.
-Oh. Okay.
-I know.
-You're not.
(TEENAGERS WHOOPING)
-Shit.
-(CAR HORN HONKING)
(GIRLS LAUGHING)
(I LOVE MY MOMMA PLAYING ON RADIO)
Dick.
How's it goin', Dickie boy?
-Good. How you doin'?
-I'm good.
(SING-SONG)
Camille and Dickie
Sittin' in a tree
K-I-S-S...
F-U-C-K-I-N-G!
(GIRLS LAUGHING)
That's cute.
Now, just stop. All right?
I thought you were stayin' in?
Well, I guess you can't trust
Adora's girls, now, can you?
When you said you were going to bed,
I didn't know it was with him.
Dick.
When are you...
When are you gonna
take us for a ride, huh?
Well, I'd have to arrest you first.
Oh. Handcuffs and all?
Sexy.
-You girls know about the curfew...
-So...
Are you guys dating now, or what?
‘Cause I heard
Camille's a real hot ticket.
Or she was.
You should hear the stories, Dick.
They're pretty hot.
-Amma.
-Ask her about the boys.
-All the boys.
Amma.
All right, ladies, we gotta get goin'.
As always, it was a real pleasure.
Isn't he a gentleman?
Can't solve a crime, but can help
my sister to his crappy-ass car.
Knock it off.
-Look, that's enough. Okay?
-You gonna hit me?
-Yeah, you want me to?
-(AMMA LAUGHING)
Be dangerous.
Be dangerous like Mama said.
You could kill me right here,
and you know what?
Dickie boy
still couldn't figure it out.
Amma, go home.
-Go.
-All right, go home. Okay?
-Have fun.
-(TIRES SCREECHING)
Have fun, Camille.
Nolan!
NOLAN: Speed-racin' motherfuckers!
Here, let me get that.
Shit. Okay, I've got it. I've got it.
All right? Just...
(GIRLS CHATTERING)
I think I'm gonna walk, all right?
-You sure?
-Yeah.
NOLAN: Hey, pretty ladies!
Come on, don't be so shy.
-Bye, Camille!
-I got a beer with your name on it.
(TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING)
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(INAUDIBLE)
-(SCREAMING) Why?
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(GASPS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(CLASSICAL MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING)