(Crawford) 'Previously on "Hannibal"...'
You think this was a copycat?
(Graham)
I almost feel like he's been mocking her.
Your name is Georgia Madchen.
You're not alone.
- Somebody told him we were coming.
- The man on the phone?
(Graham) Did you recognise his voice?
How much would I get
if you wrote a book about me?
Nicholas Boyle was gutted with
a hunting knife. You knew how to do that.
You think I did this?
You and I are just gonna have to have
a difference of opinion about who Will is.
I'm worried about you, Will.
What if you lose time and hurt yourself?
Or someone else?
(Gunshot)
(Mouths) Hi.
You look better.
Do I look alive?
You look pretty.
Must be all the oxygen.
(Graham chuckles)
They say what's wrong with you?
No. Just the fever.
They're trying to find out what else.
They won't find anything.
They'll keep looking,
keep taking tests,
keep giving false diagnoses,
bad meds,
but they won't find out what's wrong.
They'll just know that you're wrong.
- I hope you have good insurance.
- I do, too.
They're going to give me
shock treatment.
Electroconvulsive therapy
is what it's called.
Shock treatment sounds nicer.
People who have what you have
can recover with shock treatment.
You know how many times I've been told
that I could recover with treatment?
They said I might remember what I did.
But I don't wanna remember.
You know what you did, Georgia.
But I don't remember it.
It feels more like a horrible dream
where I killed my friend.
You dream about killing anybody else?
I dream you killed that doctor.
But I couldn't see your face.
Smells delicious.
Silkie chicken in a broth.
A black-boned bird prized in China
for its medicinal values
since the 7th century.
Wolfberries, ginseng, ginger,
red dates and star anise.
You made me chicken soup.
Yes.
The nurses tell me
you've been wandering, Will.
I was awake...
...and wandering with purpose.
And good intentions.
Visiting that unfortunate young woman
suffering from delusions.
She's my support group.
And I hope you're hers.
Nothing more isolating
than mental illness.
The hallucinations,
the... loss of time, sleepwalking.
Could that have all just
been the fever?
Fevers can be symptoms of dementia.
Dementia can be a symptom of many
things happening in your body or mind
that can no longer be ignored, Will.
Does Jack know?
That this could be more than a fever?
No. I haven't told him.
Shouldn't you?
Not until we know for certain.
What we must do now is continue
to support and monitor your recovery.
This young woman you were visiting,
how's her recovery?
I don't think she wants to recover.
Afraid to remember what she did.
Can't say I blame her.
(Machine beeping)
(Banging)
The hospital speculates that it was
a short circuit that ignited the fire.
Unit looks well maintained.
No exposed wiring.
Horrible way to die.
There was a kid in Italy
who was in one of these things.
A spark of static electricity
from his pyjamas set it off.
Two cubic yards of oxygen
suddenly became two cubic yards of fire.
Is it possible she set the fire herself?
She wasn't wearing her grounding bracelet.
Prevents the build-up of static electricity.
- She took it off.
- Suicide by immolation?
She was facing
two murder charges.
She wasn't suicidal, Jack.
She was... sick.
I was here. I spoke to her.
Why did you speak to her?
Because I know how she felt.
She's a murder suspect.
She tried to kill you.
Your trying to be her friend
impacts the case against her.
Well, the case against her doesn't
really matter any more, does it, Jack?
(Crawford sighs)
We could use the articles I wrote
at the time of each of the murders
as book chapter headings.
The chapters themselves
would be you telling your story,
where you were
and what you were thinking,
when one by one
eight girls, just like you,
all over Minnesota
were disappearing.
What are we gonna call it?
Well, I thought about
"The Last Victim",
but there is already a book about
serial killers called "The Last Victim".
Was it a bestseller?
Absolutely.
Especially after the guy
who wrote it killed himself.
Just as well.
I wasn't really my dad's
last victim anyway, was I?
Who was?
Marissa.
Marissa Schurr was killed by the copycat.
So was Cassie Boyle.
I still blame my dad.
Blame him for Nick Boyle's death?
I blame Nick Boyle
for Nick Boyle's death.
He killed Marissa.
He got what was coming to him.
- Nick Boyle did not kill your friend.
- Then who did?
Better question is, who killed Nick?
Nick Boyle was just a dumb kid
who was really messed up
because his sister was murdered.
He wasn't a killer.
I've interviewed enough killers
to know one when I see one.
What gives them away?
A very specific brand of hostility.
I see it every time I look at Will Graham.
He did kill my dad.
As far as I'm concerned,
he killed Nick Boyle.
He and Jack Crawford told
everyone Nick was the copycat
and then someone murdered him for it.
You really don't think he did it.
Whoever killed Nicholas Boyle
killed an innocent man.
See?
- What are you doing here?
- Checked myself out of the hospital.
- Well, check yourself back in.
- Fever broke.
I don't care.
Georgia Madchen didn't commit suicide
and whatever happened to her
wasn't an accident.
I'll have Z come down here and
if you got a temperature higher than 99...
She was murdered, Jack.
- By who?
- By whoever killed Dr Sutcliffe.
(scoffs)
His blood was all over Georgia Madchen.
Her DNA was all over him.
She told me
there was somebody else there.
She couldn't see his face.
There was somebody else there,
it was Dr Sutcliffe.
She couldn't see his face
because she cut in half!
Will, I understand.
You're looking for an explanation.
An explanation that makes all of this OK.
No! No, no.
That is not what I want.
Listen, something went wrong
and we will never know what that is,
but for all the doctors she saw,
for all of the help she received,
she was fighting that wrong alone.
There was nothing you could do
about that.
All her adult life
this woman was misunderstood.
And what I can do is make sure
that her death isn't misunderstood.
She didn't kill herself.
And this wasn't an accident.
(Muffled voices)
We dismantled the oxygen chamber,
see if anyone tampered with the wiring,
or even like a short circuit but nothing.
- So what sparked the fire?
- Inconclusive, but...
Not conclusively inconclusive.
Found this.
Thought it might have been part
of the bed or monitoring equipment,
but mass spectrometer
said it was celluloid plastic.
- They don't use plastic in those things.
- It generates static electricity.
Her hair was melted right in there.
Preserved like it was in amber.
Could it have been a plastic comb?
Static charge from a plastic comb
in a highly oxygenated environment
would be a powerful accelerant.
(Zeller) Anything combustible in there
would combust.
- You're holding the murder weapon.
- Or whatever she used to kill herself.
- Will!
- Whoa, whoa!
Whoever killed Sutcliffe
wanted to kill him
how Georgia Madchen killed her victim,
but not exactly how. Correct?
Georgia Madchen carved up
her victim's face.
Sutcliffe was nearly decapitated
at the jaw. I mean...
So she went further the second time.
- Serial killers often do that.
- She was copied.
Like whoever killed Marissa Schurr
and Cassie Boyle wanted to copy
how Garret Jacob Hobbs
killed his victims.
- But not exactly how.
- Wait a minute...
Are you saying that Dr Sutcliffe was
killed by Garret Jacob Hobbs' copycat?
So was Georgia Madchen.
Because he thinks she saw his face.
(Crawford) You said Nicholas Boyle
was the copycat.
His blood was on one of the victims.
Nicholas Boyle is dead.
Well, then he isn't the copycat.
Could this be more than a fever?
Will is connecting murders
that previously had no connections.
Beyond his involvement
in the investigations?
That's right.
So you're wondering if the lines
are blurring or if he's on to something.
I'm wondering all sorts of things.
What's Will's relationship
with Abigail Hobbs?
(Clears throat)
You think he's protecting her?
He has been
ever since he shot her father.
I just don't know from what.
I can't imagine he would hide
anything criminal from you.
I've only ever known Will
as a man striving to be his best self.
You haven't known him that long.
We both know him well enough
to know he hasn't been himself.
He needs our support.
Whether or not mental illness is involved.
Mental illness.
(scoffs)
Is it really mental illness
or is it just that his mind works
so differently from most people's
that we don't know what else to call it?
There are days when even Will
doesn't understand his own thinking.
(Knocking at door)
Dr Du Maurier. I'm Special Agent
Jack Crawford with the FBI.
I'd like to talk with you
about a patient of yours.
Do you have a court order?
Well, I'd rather not get one
if I don't have to.
(♪ Switches music off)
- So it's not an official enquiry.
- Not yet.
I'd hate to damage
anyone's reputation unnecessarily.
Whose reputation would that be?
I suspect that Dr Hannibal Lecter
may be withholding pertinent information
involving a murder investigation.
No, thank you.
So he hasn't confided in the FBI.
You are hoping he's confided
in his psychiatrist and I'll tell you.
Yes, ma'am.
It's not that I think Dr Lecter
is dangerous. I don't.
I'm concerned about a relationship he has
with one of his patients. Will Graham.
Without consent or a court order,
I'd be in breach of confidentiality.
That's correct.
So if we can't discuss Dr Lecter,
perhaps we can discuss you.
You were attacked by a patient
not too long ago.
I read the report.
I know that there was a statement
given by Dr Lecter.
The patient who attacked me
was a former patient of Dr Lecter.
And he was referred to you by Dr Lecter?
- Yes.
- And this patient almost killed you.
He swallowed his tongue
while he was attacking me.
That's the only thing
that saved my life.
Well, thank God for small favours.
Yes, thank God.
You should know there was another
attack recently in Dr Lecter's office.
It involved another patient.
Two dead, including the patient.
That's not bad psychology,
Agent Crawford.
Putting me in a position to have
to defend or not to defend Dr Lecter.
He's had some pretty strange
relationships with some of his patients.
Complicated patients are conducive
to complicated relationships.
All right.
How far do you think Dr Lecter would
go in his therapy to treat a patient?
Specifically, Will Graham.
Hannibal refers to Will Graham
more as a friend than as a patient.
How far do you think
he would go to treat a friend?
Well, he doesn't have many of them,
so I imagine he'd be loyal.
I know that he's concerned
about Will Graham
and... I know that he wants to help him.
Well, I consider Will a friend
and I'd like to help him, too.
It seems to me that
Will Graham would do well
to have more friends like Dr Lecter.
Will Graham theorised
that the copycat killer
and Garret Jacob Hobbs
were somehow connected.
That he had insight
into Hobbs' personal life,
that they may have met, known each
other, perhaps even killed together.
See, I would call that less of a theory,
more of a hypothesis.
- Theories require evidence.
- Let's play jeopardy, shall we?
These people were killed by the copycat
who's connected to Garret Jacob Hobbs.
You tell me how.
You mean beyond the application
of supposition and unexplained leaps?
Yes. That's right.
I've been yearning for a return to
the fundamentals of investigation. Right?
- Where is Beverly?
- Jury duty.
She's deposed in court.
Get her out of court.
Then here's what we're gonna do.
I wanna look at train station,
airport, toll road, hotel details.
I wanna track Garret Jacob Hobbs
using license plate capture
from security footage.
I also want to know every phone call
he made and where he made them from.
I'll see if I can get R&I to loan us
clerks to help us cross-match.
Good. I also wanna know every place
that he went that wasn't home.
I wanna know how long he was there,
who he was there with.
I wanna know the travel time
to the nearest missing girl
in the Minnesota Shrike case,
you got it?
Yeah. OK.
You told me that killing someone
was the ugliest thing in the world.
One of them.
I finally get it.
I thought there was
something wrong with me,
because I didn't feel ugly
when I killed Nick Boyle.
I felt good.
That's why it was so easy
to lie about it.
Like you didn't do anything wrong.
Feel like you'd done something wrong
when you killed my dad?
I felt terrified.
And then... I felt powerful.
It felt good.
To get to end it, to stop it all.
I thought I got away from him.
No. I don't think either of us have
gotten away from your father.
I Wish I'd killed him.
For killing my mum.
For killing all those girls.
For making me...
- Making you what, Abigail?
- Part of it.
Part of any of it.
This wasn't supposed to be my life.
It feels like my dad's still out there.
In a way, he is.
You mean the copycat.
I think I can catch him.
But I'm gonna need your help.
An agent from the FBI
came to see me.
He asked me questions about
your relationship with Will Graham.
Jack Crawford was here?
Mm.
He had enough doubt in whatever it is
you told him about your patient
to feel the need to verify.
He believes Abigail Hobbs
was involved in her father's crimes
and he suspects Will is protecting her.
And, evidently, he suspects
you are protecting Will.
Are you?
Are you asking as my psychiatrist?
I'm stepping out of my role
as your psychiatrist
and I'm speaking to you now
as your colleague.
Whatever you're doing
with Will Graham, stop.
Will needs my help.
You've crossed professional lines.
(Scoffs) By making a friend?
You cannot function
as an agent of friendship
for a man who is disconnected
from the concept
as a man who is disconnected
from the concept.
I'm protecting Will from influence.
He has flaws in his intuitive beliefs
about what makes him who he is.
I'm trying to help him understand.
You may not be able to.
I'm not comfortable telling Will that
my very best attempts to help him may fail
and that my loyalty to him and
his treatment could be compromised.
Then tell him something else.
Agent Crawford also asked me
about my attack.
I see.
What did you tell him?
Half-truths.
That a violent patient swallowed
his tongue while he was attacking me.
I didn't tell him how or why
or who was responsible.
You protect your patient from
Jack Crawford, but I can't protect mine?
Not any more.
Even the very best psychiatrists
have an inherent limitation
to their professional abilities.
You may find that difficult to accept.
You're right. It is.
You have to maintain boundaries,
Hannibal.
When the pressures of my personal
and professional relationships with Will
grow too great,
I assure you...
...I'll find a way to relieve them.
I'm much better now.
I feel clearer.
It had to be the fever.
I am finally thinking clearly
about the copycat.
The murders you're attributing
to the copycat have suspects
whose DNA was found on the victims.
So what?
- You're choosing to ignore that?
- Both of those suspects are dead.
I'm choosing to factor that into
my psychological profile of a killer.
Georgia Madchen followed me
to Sutcliffe's office,
she witnessed his murder,
she saw the copycat.
- Why not kill her then and there?
- Maybe didn't have the time.
She was an unreliable witness,
so that bought him time.
So he framed her for the murder.
He wasn't planning on framing her.
- He was planning on framing me.
- You believe this is personal?
If it wasn't before... it is now.
This could be someone at the bureau,
someone in the police department,
someone who knows the crimes
and has access to the investigations.
Someone like you?
(Sighs)
There will be evidence.
I found a pattern and now I'm gonna
reconstruct his thinking.
- How do you intend to do that?
- By taking Abigail back to Minnesota.
Start where the copycat started,
when he called Garret Jacob Hobbs.
Will, this is venturing into the paranoid.
I can't allow you to pull Abigail
into your delusion.
This isn't a delusion.
I'm not hallucinating.
I haven't lost time.
I am awake and this is real.
(Sighs)
We found train tickets
purchased by Garret Jacob Hobbs.
- Tickets?
- Two.
For the same train line
that one of his victims was using.
Elise Nichols?
Found more instances
of Hobbs crossing with victims.
Dinner receipts for two and two
hotel rooms near the same campuses.
- We know he wasn't travelling alone.
- Travelling with his daughter?
They were registered
for the same orientation programme
at St Cloud State on the Mississippi
where the Nichols girl was at school.
Abigail Hobbs attended orientations
at every school
where a girl was abducted
by the Minnesota Shrike
within days of the abduction.
She was with him
when he was choosing these girls.
She was the bait.
She was helping him choose the girls.
The connection between the copycat killer
and Garret Jacob Hobbs might be family.
She kills Cassie Boyle
to impress dad?
She kills Marissa Schurr in memoriam?
Then she kills Nicholas Boyle
to cover her tracks?
Then why kill Dr Sutcliffe?
Or the Madchen girl?
Because she's got a taste for it now.
Or she wants to impress someone new.
Hello, Agent Crawford.
Freddie Lounds.
You look like you came hereto arrest
somebody. Abigail Hobbs or Will Graham?
- Will Graham was here?
- Oh, then it was Abigail Hobbs.
Where is she?
One of the other girls said
Special Agent Graham snuck her out.
I don't know why he would
feel the need to be sneaky.
He is registered as one
of her guardians. The irony.
Give us a minute here.
- How's the book coming?
- There's plot holes.
Tell me how you're filling them in.
- Did Abigail Hobbs kill Nick Boyle?
- Why do you say that?
Abigail is one of those very smart girls
who hasn't quite figured out
that very smart girls grow up
and know all the moves they're making
when they're trying to hide something.
What is Will Graham trying to hide?
Sorry to barge in on you, Doctor.
Couldn't wait.
What the hell is going on between
Will Graham and Abigail Hobbs?
Will has been victim of many unusual
and irrational thoughts.
- Has he acted on these thoughts?
- Not that I'm aware of.
Or he's aware of, for that matter.
But he has experienced
periods of lost time.
Yes, I've seen him confused at
crime scenes. I've seen him disoriented.
He may have been confused
because he was waking up.
Might not have known
where he was or how he got there.
- Waking up?
- From a dissociated personality state.
He would appear perfectly normal
and not remember a thing.
But a fractured part of him would.
- How long have you been aware of this?
- He's recently started to discuss this.
Unless "recently" means
just before I walked into your office,
you failed to mention any of this to me!
Because I was trying to determine
if it was trauma and stress
from the work he's doing for you
or mental illness.
I thought it wise to be sure before making
any claim about Will Graham's sanity.
He's taken Abigail Hobbs. You have
any idea where they might be going?
No.
We have evidence she was involved
in some of her father's crimes.
We just don't know how involved.
Is it possible Will knew what Abigail was
doing? Is that why he's protecting her?
There's something you should hear.
(Lecter) 'How did you feel seeing Marissa
Schurr impaled in his antler room?'
(Graham) 'Guilty.'
(Lecter)
'Because you couldn't save her?'
(Graham)
'Because I felt like I killed her.'
(Switches off recording)
Where was Will the night
that Marissa Schurr was killed?
He was supposed to be
in his hotel room.
I knocked on his door. He didn't answer.
We know he was in Dr Sutcliffe's office
the night that he was killed.
And Will was the last person to visit
Georgia Madchen before she died.
This dissociative personality state
you say he goes into.
Whose personality is it?
He said he got so close
to Garret Jacob Hobbs
and what he had done...
...that he felt he was becoming him.
And now he has Hobbs' daughter.
Who Hobbs intended to kill.
(Sighs)
I'm so sorry, Jack.
(Door closes)
You look pasty. Maybe you shouldn't have
checked yourself out of the hospital.
I feel fine.
It would've been
my mum's birthday next week.
We were gonna climb
Eagle Mountain to celebrate.
Highest point in Minnesota,
but... it's not really that high.
Less than three hours to summit.
You can see Lake Superior from there.
I could take you if... if you wanna go.
I think it would just make me sad.
Some places are stained now.
Some people, too.
I know I am.
(Sighs heavily)
(Crows cawing)
The copycat knew your father
well enough to know about this place.
You felt like you knew my father?
I wanted to understand him.
I felt like I had to understand him.
Do you ever hunt?
I fish.
Well, it's the same thing, isn't it?
One you stalk... the other you lure.
Were you more fisherman or hunter?
- My dad taught me how to hunt.
- No, that's not what I'm asking.
All those girls your dad killed.
Did you fish...
...or did you hunt, Abigail?
I was the lure.
Did Hannibal tell you?
No, he didn't.
He said you'd protect me.
That you'd keep it a secret.
(Gas-ping)
There's something wrong with you.
I think you're still sick.
Jack Crawford was right about you.
Yeah, he knew!
You killed Nick Boyle and you helped
your father kill all of those girls.
- No, I didn't help my dad kill anybody.
- No, you lured them. You killed them.
How many other people
have you killed?
Do you think I'm the copycat?
You think I killed Marissa?
If you didn't kill her, Abigail,
then somebody you know did.
Ever think that somebody
could be you?
You were there. You saw Marissa.
You knew about this place
and there is something wrong with you.
(Groans)
(Attendant)
Sir, you're gonna have to leave.
We're preparing the cabin
for the next passengers.
I'm sorry. Where... where are we?
Dulles International, Virginia.
Was there a young woman
travelling with me?
The other passengers are disembarked.
It's just you, sir.
Abigail.
- What are you doing here?
- I was so worried about you.
Will told me
he was taking you to Minnesota,
and I strongly advised against it.
Where is Will?
I left him at the cabin.
I didn't feel safe with him,
so I left him.
He knows everything.
So does Jack Crawford.
If I run, they'll catch me,
won't they?
You can't protect me any more.
They'll arrest you
when they find you, yes.
And Will.
Did he kill Marissa?
They will believe he did.
They will believe he killed others, too.
Will always said whoever
called the house that morning
was the serial killer.
Why did you really call?
I wanted to warn your father that
Will Graham was coming for him.
Why?
I was curious what would happen.
I was curious what would happen
when I killed Marissa.
I was curious what you would do.
You wanted me to kill Nick Boyle.
I was hoping.
I wanted to see how much
like your father you were.
Oh, my God.
Nicholas Boyle is more important
for you gutting him.
He changed you, Abigail.
That's more important
than the life he clamoured after.
How many people have you killed?
Many more than your father.
Are you going to kill me?
I'm so sorry, Abigail.
I'm sorry I couldn't protect you
in this life.