(Graham) 'Previously on "Hannibal"...'
You entered into a devil's bargain
with Jack Crawford.
You know what looking
at this does.
Am I your psychiatrist or are we
simply having conversations?
I don't want to get
in the middle of you and Jack.
I like you as a buffer.
- Graham likes you.
- Cos I want to be his friend, and I am.
It seems a shame
not to take advantage.
- This is my friend, Tobias.
- Good evening.
I hate being this neurotic.
If you weren't neurotic, Franklyn,
you would be something much worse.
Whatever the Ripper was doing,
it worked.
(Animal whining)
(Distant whining)
(Animal shrieking)
(Shrieking)
(♪ Cello playing
"Minuet in G Major" - Petzold)
These strings are harder to bow
than the regular ones.
You have to learn how to bow
authentic strings,
to better bow
strings how they're made today.
I should learn to play the easier
strings first, then the harder ones.
- No, you shouldn't.
- Are they really made from cat guts?
Not always.
(♪ Continues "Minuet in G Major")
That's better. Good.
If it wasn't a coyote,
the coyotes probably got it.
Probably got it
even if it was a coyote.
You're not expecting to find it alive,
are you?
We'll be lucky to find a paw.
So you invited me over
to help you collect animal parts?
I invited you over on the off chance
we do find it alive.
It's hard for me to wrangle
a wounded animal by myself.
Did you think it was a date?
- Honestly, it never crossed my mind.
- Oh.
Why not?
- You just don't seem like you date.
- Oh? Too broken to date?
You're not broken.
- What's your excuse?
- For not dating?
- Why are you assuming I don't date?
- Do you?
No.
Seems like something
for somebody else.
I'm sure I'll become
that somebody someday,
but right now I think too much.
So what are you gonna do,
try to think less?
- Or just wait till it happens naturally?
- I haven't thought about it.
- Are you seeing anything?
- Uh, no, actually.
I'm not even seeing any tracks.
I mean, except for the ones we made.
Good morning. Please, come in.
(Franklyn) I have a lot of respect for you.
Since we can't be friends,
or... you're not comfortable with that,
I found myself looking
at my friends through your eyes,
imagining what
your diagnosis might be.
- So you become the psychoanalyst?
- I become you.
- Who are you psychoanalysing?
- (Sighs) My friend Tobias.
I googled "psychopaths",
went down the checklist,
and I was a little surprised
to see how many boxes
I had checked.
Why were you so curious
to Google?
He's been saying very dark things,
and then saying, "Just kidding!" a lot.
It started to seem kind of crazy.
Psychopaths are not crazy.
They're fully aware of what they do
and the consequences of those actions.
Would you diagnose someone
like Tobias as a psychopath?
Or are you supposed to diagnose
other people in front of me?
Would you rather just
talk about me?
Not at all.
Are you bored with me?
No. This is your hour, Franklyn.
We will talk about whatever
you would like to talk about.
I'd like to talk about Tobias.
Perhaps you can help me analyse him.
I'm not analysing your friend,
I'm analysing your perception of him.
It may help you know yourself better.
You could be projecting onto him
what you consider to be your flaws.
Does that mean
that I'm a psychopath?
You're not a psychopath,
although you may be attracted to them.
(♪ Strings crescendo)
The victim is Douglas Wilson,
a member of the Baltimore Metropolitan
Orchestra's brass section.
A trombone player.
He was killed shortly
after his last performance.
Blunt force trauma
to the back of the head.
His killer brought him here to...
put on a show.
Will, is it me, or is it becoming
easier for you to look?
I tell myself
it's purely an intellectual exercise.
In the narrow view of forensics,
that's exactly what it is.
It's not any easier, Jack.
I shake it off, keep on looking.
Good.
You shake it off. Get to work.
We'll come back in
when you're ready for us.
I open his throat from the outside
to access the trachea
and expose the vocal chords.
I open his throat from the inside
using the neck of a cello.
Powder on the wound.
Rosin from the bow.
I wanted to play him.
I wanted to create a sound.
My sound.
This... is my design.
(Strings hum)
(Slow clapping)
(Lecter) I worry that I've made
Franklyn feel powerless.
He wants to be my friend.
His obsession with me
is interfering with his progress.
I'm considering referring him
to another doctor.
Referrals can be complicated.
I referred you to another psychiatrist.
You refused.
I'm more tenacious than Franklyn.
Why were you so tenacious?
I feel protective of you.
You support me as a colleague and
psychiatrist, and as a human being.
I want to be supportive of you
after what happened.
I'm not the only psychiatrist
who's ever been attacked by a patient.
I hesitated to even bring up
the subject of an obsessive patient
because of your traumatic experience.
Hannibal...
...I'm your psychiatrist,
you're not mine.
(Price) Played him like a fiddle.
Along with rosin powder,
we found sodium carbonate,
sulphur dioxide, lye
and olive oil in the wounds.
- What is the deal with the olive oil?
- Sure wasn't making salad.
He removed anything non-muscular
or fatty from around the vocal folds.
The chords themselves were treated
with a sulphur dioxide solution.
The sulphur dioxide had the effect
of hardening the vocal chords.
Made them easier to play.
Had to open you up
to get a decent sound out of you.
(Katz) You pick it up and can't play it,
he'll put you down and play you.
(Price) He took the time to whiten
the vocal chords before playing them.
It's not about whitening them,
it was about increasing elasticity.
He treated the vocal chords
the same way you treat catgut string.
Yes, I play the violin.
This takes a steady hand.
A confidence.
He's killed before.
- Like this?
- No, not like this.
This is a skilled musician
trying a new instrument.
Among the first musical
instruments were flutes
carved from human bone.
This murder was a performance.
Every life is a piece of music.
Like music, we are finite events,
unique arrangements,
sometimes harmonious,
sometimes dissonant.
Sometimes not worth hearing again.
- He's a poet and a psychopath.
- And a craftsman.
He was shrinking and tanning
the vocal chords.
Like turning iron wire
into musical steel string.
Was there olive oil?
Yes.
Whatever sound he was trying
to produce, it was an authentic one.
Olive oil hasn't been used in the
production of catgut for over a century.
It was said to increase
the life of the strings
and create a sweeter,
more melodic sound.
No, I hear what he was playing
behind my eyes when I close them.
What do you see behind closed eyes?
I see myself.
You said the killer was performing.
Who was he performing for?
I don't know.
A patron of the arts?
A fellow musician?
Or... another killer?
- It's a serenade.
- No, this isn't how he kills.
Normally, he doesn't kill
for an audience.
And you believe he risked
getting caught for a serenade?
I believe he wants to show
someone how well he plays.
Do you remember when I said Tobias
was saying very dark things?
I made note of it.
Well, he said that he wanted
to cut someone's throat
and play it like a violin.
They found somebody whose throat
was cut and played like a violin.
So you think Tobias killed
that man at the symphony?
I don't know. I-I...
- If I do, do I have to report it?
- Do you have a reason not to?
- What if I'm wrong?
- What if you're right?
I'm always wrong.
I don't know. Why would he say
something like that to me?
Why do you think?
Cos he knows I'd tell you.
(♪ Cello playing solo)
(Playing stops)
You're Franklyn's therapist,
Dr Lecter.
- Nice to see you again.
- Is it Tobias?
- Yes.
- Your strings are all gut.
I also carry steel and polymer strings,
if you prefer.
I prefer gut. Harps strung with gut
still make music after 2,000 years.
- I didn't hear you ring the bell.
- I didn't want you to stop playing.
- Was it an original composition?
- Something I've been writing.
- You compose?
- I discover.
Can't impose traditional composition
on an instrument
that's inherently free form.
- What instrument would that be?
- The Theremin.
It can generate any pitch
throughout its range.
Even those
between conventional notes.
And so can a violin or a trombone.
It seems we are both comfortable
playing between conventional notes.
I hear the symphony's
looking for a new trombonist.
- Altogether horrible what happened.
- Not altogether.
It's an unfortunate way
to leave the symphony, yes,
but I can't help thinking
the orchestra will be better for it.
At least the brass section.
- What brings you here looking for gut?
- My harpsichord needs new strings.
It's making an awful noise.
Perhaps you could help.
(Scratching)
(Scratching and animal noises)
(Scratching continues)
(Chirruping)
- What kind of animal was it?
- It might've been a raccoon.
"Might've been"?
By the time I'd knocked a hole
in the chimney, it climbed out the top.
Well, at least it got out.
What are you doing out?
I thought I'd come over,
make some noise,
shoo away any predators
at your door.
Looks like you're making
plenty of noise all by yourself.
You avoided being in a room alone
with me essentially since I met you.
You were smooth about it.
- Evidently not smooth enough.
- And now you're making house calls?
Just a drive-by on my way home.
Since you're not my patient.
No. I'm not.
I'm confused.
You have to stop thinking so much.
I can stop the thinking
if we're not...
- But if we're...
- Intimate.
The way that I am in relationships...
Not that this is a relationship,
it's just a kiss.
A great kiss. But I...
The way that I am isn't compatible
with the way that...
The way I am.
I wouldn't be good for you.
You wouldn't be good for me.
And I wouldn't be able
to stop analysing,
because I have this professional
curiosity about you and...
I am not your patient.
If I were my patient,
my advice to me...
...would be don't do this.
I have to follow my own advice.
I'm gonna go ahead and go now.
Goodnight, Will.
More wine?
(♪ Cello sonata playing)
A late harvest Vidal from Linden.
Oh, Virginia.
I thought it was French.
The Virginia wine revolution
is upon us.
I apologise for being so blunt, Tobias,
but I have to ask.
Did you kill that trombonist?
- You really have to ask?
- No. Just changing the subject.
Franklyn gave you my message.
The murder is being investigated
by the FBI.
- They're going to find you.
- Let them.
- You want to get caught?
- I want them to try.
They may investigate me
because I own a string shop.
They'll send men to investigate,
and I'll kill them.
Then I'll find Franklyn and kill him.
Then I would disappear.
- Don't kill Franklyn.
- I've been looking forward to it.
Actually...
- ...I was going to kill you.
- Of course you were.
I'm lean. Lean animals yield
the toughest gut.
What stopped you
from wanting to kill me?
Or have you stopped?
I stopped after I followed you
one night out of town.
To a lonely road.
To a bus yard.
You're reckless, Tobias.
I'm not going to tell anyone
what I saw you do and do well.
So my recklessness
doesn't concern you.
It concerns me because you won't be
drawing attention just to yourself.
I could use a friend.
Someone who can understand me.
Who thinks like I do
and can see the world
and the people in it the way I do.
I know exactly how you feel.
But I don't want to be your friend.
Then why did you invite me
here for dinner?
It wasn't just to restring
your harpsichord.
I was going to kill you.
I didn't poison you, Tobias.
I wouldn't do that to the food.
(Doorbell chimes)
Expecting someone?
No.
I kissed Alana Bloom.
Well, come in.
- You have a guest?
- A colleague.
- You just missed him.
- He didn't finish his dinner.
An urgent call of some sort.
He had to leave suddenly.
This benefits you,
because I have dessert for two.
Tell me,
what was Alana's reaction?
She said she wouldn't be good for me
and I wouldn't be good for her.
I don't disagree.
She would feel an obligation
to her field of study to observe you.
- And you would resent her for it.
- I know.
I'm wondering then why
you kissed her and felt compelled
to drive an hour in the snow
to tell me about it.
I wanted to kiss her since I met her.
She's very kissable.
You waited a long time, which suggests
you were kissing her for a reason,
in addition to wanting to.
I heard an animal trapped
in my chimney. Erm...
I broke through the wall
to get it out.
I didn't find anything inside.
Alana showed up,
she looked at me...
Maybe her face changed,
I don't know.
But, um, she knew...
What did she know, Will?
There was no animal
in the chimney.
It was only in my head.
I sleepwalk. I get headaches.
I am hearing things.
I feel unstable.
That's why you kissed her.
A clutch for balance.
You said yourself
what you do is not good for you.
Unfortunately, I am good for it.
Are you still hearing this killer's
serenade behind your eyes?
Well, it's our song.
I hesitate telling you this,
as it borders on a violation
of doctor-patient confidentiality.
A patient told me today
he suspects a friend of his
may be involved with the murder
at the symphony.
Right, erm...
Erm... what did he say
about his friend?
He owns a music store in Baltimore,
specialising in string instruments.
Perhaps you should interview him.
Yeah.
For the first time in a long while,
I see a possibility of friendship.
- Is there someone new in your life?
- I met a man much like myself.
Same hobbies, same worldviews,
but I'm not interested in being
his friend. I'm curious about him.
And that got me curious
about friendship.
Whose friendship
are you considering?
Oddly enough,
a colleague and a patient,
not unlike how I'm a colleague
and a patient of yours.
We've discussed him before.
- Will Graham.
- He's nothing like me.
We see the world in different ways,
yet he can assume my point of view.
By profiling the criminally insane.
As good a demonstration as any.
I find it reassuring.
It's nice when someone sees us,
Hannibal.
Or has the ability to see us.
It requires trust.
Trust is difficult for you.
You've helped me
to better understand
what I want in a friendship
and what I don't.
- Someone worthy of your friendship.
- Yes.
You spend a lot of time
building walls, Hannibal.
It's natural to want to see if someone
is clever enough to climb over them.
- JSB's Suite No 1.
- OK.
Special agent Will Graham
with the FBI.
- Are you the owner?
- Yes. Tobias Budge.
I'm just showing one of my students out.
Can I have a moment?
Sure.
Adagio. For Saturday.
What can I help you with?
We're investigating the death
of Douglas Wilson. He was...
- Trombonist.
- That's right. Did you know him?
I was aware of him.
Baltimore is a small town.
The cultural arts community
is an even smaller one.
Well, that's why we're here, Mr Budge.
I hear someone cut his throat
and tried to play it with a bow.
Why do you say "try"?
The strings have to be treated.
You can't just open somebody up
and draw a bow across their innards
and expect to produce a sound.
The vocal chords were
chemically treated,
similar to how catgut string is treated.
We kept those details
out of the press.
You're looking for someone who knows
how to manufacture gut strings?
Anybody leap to mind?
Mine are imported from Italy.
Best catgut is.
The string section of the Baltimore
Metropolitan Orchestra
refuses to play anything else.
- More authentic?
- A richer, darker sound.
Allows music to say
what words can't.
(Tyres screeching; crash)
(Shrieking)
Something wrong?
Didn't you hear that?
I didn't hear anything.
Excuse me a minute.
(Animal moaning)
(Animal shrieking)
Sorry about that...
Officers?
I need ERT at Chordophone Strings,
downtown Baltimore. Officer down.
(Scratching)
(Scratching continues)
(High-pitched whine)
(Muffled gunshots)
Nine.
Nine times.
I can count on two hands
the number of times
I've been dumped by a psychiatrist.
I'm sorry, Franklyn, but I think
you should see another doctor.
- You're giving me a referral?
- Yes, I am.
- You were a referral!
- I am also a part of the problem.
You focus too much on your therapist,
and not enough on your therapy.
You lost respect for me because
I wouldn't report Tobias, didn't you?
(Tobias) Report Tobias for what?
Tobias?
I came to say goodbye, Franklyn.
What do you mean, goodbye?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, is that your blood?
I just killed two men.
The police came to question me
about the murder.
OK... you have
to give yourself up right now.
This plane is going down.
Let it have a controlled descent.
We can get you back up
in the air again.
There's rehabilitation for everyone.
Franklyn, I want you to leave now.
Stay right where you are, Franklyn.
You've done a horrible thing.
And... I know...
that you wish to God
that you didn't, but you did.
And there's nothing you can do
to change that.
Only thing you can change
is your future.
Right?
Now, you're probably scared.
You probably feel like you're all alone.
- I'm not alone.
- That's right. You're not alone.
Nothing has happened in
our relationship that you and I can't...
I was looking forward to that.
I saved you the trouble.
Ah!
(Bone cracks)
(Tobias screams)
(Gagging)
(♪ JS BACH:
"Goldberg Variations - Aria")
I was worried you were dead.
Tobias Budge killed
two Baltimore police officers,
nearly killed an FBI special agent,
and after all of that,
his first stop is here,
at your office.
He came to kill my patient.
Your patient. Is that who
Budge was serenading?
I don't know.
Franklyn knew more
than he was telling me.
He told Mr Budge that
he didn't have to kill anymore.
And then he broke Franklyn's neck,
and then he attacked me.
You killed him?
Yes.
Could Franklyn have been involved
in whatever Budge was doing?
I thought this was a simple matter
of poor choice of friends.
This doesn't feel simple to me.
I feel like I've dragged you
into my world.
No, I got here on my own.
But I appreciate the company.
I'm going to start seeing patients again.
It's strange, thinking about
going back to daily practice.
Well, it's good you stepped away.
Even if it was only for a few days.
Patients will sit where Franklyn died.
I will sit where I almost died,
and I will offer therapy.
It's easy to understand why
you retired after you were attacked.
Will you ever feel comfortable
returning to psychiatric work?
This is psychiatric work.
One patient isn't a practice.
I can't help feeling responsible
for what happened to Franklyn.
Every person has an intrinsic
responsibility for their own life, Hannibal.
No one else can take on
that responsibility.
Not even you.
Did you take responsibility when
you were attacked by your patient?
Yes.
But I don't take responsibility
for his death.
Nor should you.