(Graham) 'Previously on "Hannibal"...'
Abigail Hobbs killed Nick Boyle.
We can tell no one.
(Lecter) I'm worried about you, Will.
You empathise completely
with the killers
Jack Crawford has your mind
wrapped around
that you lose yourself to them.
- Maybe I should get a brain scan.
- Do you feel unstable?
Is there a problem, Will?
- You lost time.
- There's something wrong with me.
(Lecter) I don't care about the lives
you save. I care about your life.
Your life is separating from reality.
(Car alarm bleeps)
(Banging)
(Whistles)
(Bird chirps)
(Creaking)
(Water dripping)
(She sighs)
(Shivering)
(Sighs)
(Floorboards creak)
(Gasps and screams)
I can feel my nerves
clicking like roller-coaster cogs,
pulling up to the inevitable long plunge.
Quick sounds. Quickly ended.
Abigail Hobbs ended Nicholas Boyle.
Like a burst balloon.
She took a life.
- You've taken a life.
- Yeah... Yeah, so have you.
You're grieving, Will.
Not for the life you have taken,
but for the life that was taken from you.
If Abigail could have started over,
left the horror of her father behind,
so could have you.
You could untangle yourself
from the madness and the murder.
We lied for her.
We both know the unreality
of taking a life.
Of people who die
when we have no other choice.
We know in those moments
they are not flesh.
But light and air and colour.
Isn't that what it is to be alive?
Do you feel alive, Will?
I feel like I'm fading.
Have you experienced any further
loss of time or hallucinations?
Yeah.
I'd like you to draw a clock face.
Numbered.
Small hand indicating the hour,
large hand the minute.
- Why?
- An exercise.
I want you to focus
on the present moment. The now.
Often as you can,
think of where you are. And when.
Think of who you are.
7:16pm.
I'm in Baltimore, Maryland.
And my name is Will Graham.
A simple reminder.
The handle to reality
for you to hold on to.
And know you're alive.
(Birds squawking)
(Gasps)
(Panting)
(Pants)
Will?
- What happened in there?
- I got confused.
I've seen you confused and upset,
but I've never seen you afraid like this.
Well, I'm an old hand at fear.
I can manage this one.
I just got disoriented.
I can go back in.
I saw the look on your face
when you came out of that room.
Now what did you experience in there
that's got you mute all of a sudden?
I can see and hear better afraid.
I-I just can't speak as concisely.
Will, you contaminated the crime scene.
You've never done that before.
I thought I was responsible for it.
You thought that you killed
that woman in there?
Sometimes with what I do...
What you do is you take all of
the evidence available at a crime scene.
You extrapolate.
You reconstruct
the thinking of a killer.
You don't think of yourself
as the killer.
I got lost in the reconstruction.
Just for a second. Just a blink.
You don't like
to be the cause for concern,
but I am officially concerned about you.
- Officially?
- Yes, that's right.
Hmm.
I thought the reason you had me seeing
Dr Lecter and not an FBI psychiatrist
is so my mental wellbeing
stays... unofficial.
I just wanna be careful with you.
We don't wanna break you here.
Is that what's happening?
Have I broken you?
Do you have anyone that does this
better unbroken than I do broken?
Fear makes you rude, Will.
(Camera shutter clicks)
(Zeller) Her name was Beth LeBeau.
She drowned on her own blood.
And what she didn't drown on
is all over the floor and under the bed.
She was trying to hide from him.
He dragged her there.
He was waiting under the bed for her.
Fought to claw her way out.
He knew her. Someone who cared
about her or thought he did.
(Katz) He cared too much.
So we're looking for boyfriends,
ex-boyfriends, co-workers,
the guy who bags her groceries.
I've got a clean set of prints on
the knife handle. I assume they're yours.
- Sorry.
- Mm.
There's other dermal tissue,
presumably from the killer's.
The skin is so diseased or damaged,
it didn't leave any useful prints.
The victim scratched her killer
to pile tissue under the fingernails,
but never drew blood.
Why didn't he bleed?
After he cut up the victim's face, looks
like he was trying to pull her skin back.
Like he was removing a mask?
I still have the coppery smell of blood
on my hands.
I can't remember seeing the crime scene
before I saw myself killing her.
Those memories sank out of sight,
yet you're aware of their absence.
There's a grandiosity
to the violence that I imagined
that feels more real
than what I know is true.
What do you know to be true?
I know I didn't kill her.
I couldn't have,
but I remember cutting into her.
I remember watching her die.
You must overcome these delusions
that are disguising your reality.
What kind of savage delusions
does this killer have?
It wasn't savage. It was lonely.
It was desperate. Sad.
I caught a glimpse of myself
in the mirror
and I looked right through me.
Past me,
as if I was... was just a stranger.
You have to honestly confront
your limitations with what you do.
(Sighs heavily)
And how it affects you.
If by limitations you mean the difference
between sanity and insanity,
I don't accept that.
What do you accept?
I know what kind of crazy I am
and this isn't that kind of crazy.
This could be... seizures.
This could be a tumour.
A...a blood clot.
I can recommend a neurologist.
But if it isn't physiological,
then you have to accept what
you're struggling with is mental illness.
You're in very good hands.
Dr Lecter here is
one of the sanest men I know.
I would agree.
Dr Sutcliffe and I were residents
together at Hopkins.
Another life ago. Back when you weren't
afraid to get your hands a little dirty.
I was always drawn
to how the mind works.
I found it much more dynamic
than how the brain works.
The projected image is more
interesting than the projector,
until, of course,
the projector breaks down.
So, Will... these headaches.
- When did they begin in earnest?
- Two to three months ago.
About the time Will went back
into the field, which is when I met him.
- And the hallucinations?
- I can't really say when they started.
Um... I just slowly became aware
that I might not be dreaming.
(Lecter) It's encephalitis.
- That's your pre-diagnosis?
- Yes.
- Based on?
- I could smell it.
So your sense of smell has gone
from calling out a nurse's perfume
to diagnosing auto-immune disease.
He started sleepwalking
and I noticed a very specific scent.
And what exactly does
encephalitis smell like?
It has heat. A fevered sweetness.
If you suspected,
why didn't you say something?
Had to be sure.
Symptoms began slowly
and gradually worsened.
And yesterday,
I asked him to draw a clock.
This is what he drew.
(Sutcliffe) Oh. Spatial neglect.
Headaches, disorientation,
hallucinations, altered consciousness.
It's all the telltale signs.
It is so rare to be able
to study the psychological effect
of this type of malady
on a person's mind.
It's more rare still to be able
to study the neurological effects.
A doctor has to weigh
the ultimate benefit of scientific study.
Even in these times,
we know so little about the brain.
There are great discoveries to be made.
(Scanner whirrs)
(Woman screams)
The right side of his brain
is completely inflamed.
It's anti-NMDA receptor encephalitis.
The symptoms are only
going to get worse.
I know. It's unfortunate for Will.
What do you smell on me?
Opportunity.
We didn't find anything abnormal.
No vascular malformations,
no tumours, no swelling or bleeding,
no evidence of stroke.
Nothing.
There's nothing wrong with you
neurologically.
So what I'm experiencing
is psychological?
Well, brain scans can't diagnose...
mental disorders.
They can only rule out medical illnesses,
like a tumour,
which can have similar symptoms.
Look, we'll run some more tests.
We'll take some more blood samples,
but I imagine they'll prove
to be just as inconclusive.
You knew from the moment
you walked into his classroom
that you were putting Will
in a potentially destructive environment.
I had eight college girls
dead in Minnesota.
- Will caught their killer for me.
- He also caught that killer's disease.
He can't stop thinking
about what it is to take a life.
I'd rather he go a little mad
than other innocents lose their lives,
and I think he would feel the same way.
Will is an innocent.
(Sighs)
Yes, he is.
I mean, Will is genuine.
He'll survive anything
I could put him through.
He will always fight his way
back to himself.
Not always. So far.
He saw a neurologist today.
They found nothing wrong with him.
He was very upset by that.
You're saying
he wanted something to be wrong?
I think he wanted an answer
that wasn't mental illness.
You think he's mentally ill.
The problem Will has
is too many mirror neurons.
Our heads are filled with them
when we are children.
It's supposed to help us socialise
and then melt away.
But Will held on to his, which makes
knowing who he is a challenge.
When you take him
to a crime scene, Jack,
the very air has screams smeared on it.
In those places, he doesn't just reflect.
He absorbs.
It's 10:36.
I'm in Greenwood, Delaware.
My name is Will Graham.
(Gasps)
It's 1:17am.
W-w-we're in Greenwood, Delaware.
And my name is Will Graham.
And you're alive.
If you can hear me... you're alive!
Why did you call me?
Why not Jack? Why not the police?
I called you
because... I'm not entirely sure
what I saw was real.
Then let's prove it.
I grabbed her arm.
And an entire layer of dead skin
separated from the underlying tissue,
like she was wearing a glove.
- That's why she doesn't bleed.
- There's no circulation.
- Nothing alive in the tissue to bind it.
- What did you do with it?
(Panting)
- I don't know.
- You can't remember?
Could be a staphylococcal infection.
That or leprosy.
Her eyes were discoloured.
She was malnourished. Jaundiced.
Her liver was shutting down.
She was...
...deranged.
So she mutilated a woman's face
because she thought it was a mask.
She can't see faces.
If she did kill Beth LeBeau,
she might not even know she did it.
- Then why did she come back?
- To convince herself she didn't.
Is that why you came back?
If I wasn't clear on that issue,
I know I didn't kill Beth LeBeau.
I just wanna know who did.
Me, too.
Yeah.
You're the subject of a lot
of speculation at the Bureau.
Oh, yeah?
What are they speculating?
That Jack pushed you
right up to the edge
and now you're pushing yourself over.
This killer... can't accept her reality.
I can occasionally identify with that.
That said, I feel... relatively sane.
It's 7:05pm.
I'm in Baltimore, Maryland.
My name is Will Graham.
Thank you for humouring me.
I feel like I'm seeing a ghost.
- Regarding this killer or yourself?
- Both.
Well, she's real. You know she's real.
There's evidence.
When you found her,
your sanity did not leave you.
- Time did.
- You lost time again?
I spoke to Dr Sutcliffe. We briefly
discussed the particulars of your visit.
Would you like to discuss them
with me?
There are no particulars.
He didn't find anything wrong.
Then we keep looking for answers.
Perhaps you would permit me
to run some tests of my own.
You wouldn't publish anything about me,
would you, Dr Lecter?
If there were ever anything that
might be of therapeutic value to others,
I'd abstract it in a form
that would be totally unrecognisable.
Just do me a favour
and publish it posthumously.
- After your death or mine?
- Whichever comes first.
Have you considered
Cotard's syndrome?
It's a rare delusional disorder in which
a person believes he or she is dead.
Are you talking about the killer or me?
- The killer, of course.
- Well, of course.
Um... she couldn't see the victim's face.
Or she was trying to uncover it.
The inability to identify others
is associated with Cotard's.
It's a misfiring in the areas of the brain
which recognise faces
and also in the amygdala, which
adds emotion to those recognitions.
Even those closest to her
would seem like imposters.
So she reached out to someone
she loved, someone she trusted.
She felt betrayed, became violent.
She can't trust anything or anyone
she once knew to be trustworthy.
Her mental illness won't let her.
(Breathes heavily)
(Panting)
(Gas-ping)
(Crawford) We matched tissue
samples from the crime scene
to your daughter's medical records.
I was almost relieved
when I got that phone call.
I thought that you had found her
and she was...
- Would be at peace.
- You thought she might be dead.
(Chuckles) Well, that makes me sound
like a horrible mother.
I tried to be a good mum.
I tried to do everything that I could.
I just don't want her to be in pain.
No one's doubting your dedication
to your daughter, Mrs Madchen.
How well did she know Beth LeBeau?
They were best friends,
they went to school together,
until it was unsafe
for Georgia to go to school.
When did you first recognise
that your daughter
was struggling with mental illness?
When she was nine
and she told me that
she was thinking about killing me
and said that
she was already dead.
What sort of symptoms did she have?
She had seizures, hallucinations,
psychotic depression.
I was grateful
when she was catatonic.
- (Crawford) Was she ever violent?
- Sometimes.
What did her doctor say?
Not much.
She spent months at a time
in the hospital.
Blood tests and brain scans,
and all of them inconclusive.
They could never tell me
what was wrong.
And you still don't know?
They would just say
it was this or it was that.
They would just...
They were just always guessing.
And I did my own research.
I wrote down every word
that the doctors said,
the different terminology.
Learned a lot.
But mostly what I learned is...
...how little is actually known
about mental illness.
All they know,
it's rarely about finding solutions.
It's just more
about managing expectations.
Managing your expectations?
Changing my expectations.
You know, when Miriam Lass died,
I had to come back here
to this office to pack up.
But that got to be too overwhelming.
I thought I should just leave,
seeing as how I had gotten
a trainee killed.
That lack of leadership on my part,
that was my responsibility.
You didn't kill Miriam Lass.
The Chesapeake Ripper did.
It didn't feel that way to me.
I pulled her out of a classroom,
like I pulled you out of a classroom.
Oh... No, she was a student.
I'm a teacher.
I'm still just as responsible for you
as I was for her.
I'll take my own responsibility.
Well, not from me you won't.
We can do it together.
I broke the rules with Miriam.
I encouraged her to break the rules.
I am breaking the rules with you now.
By letting an unstable agent
do field work?
Special agent. You represent the FBI.
You still represent me.
- Have I misrepresented you, Jack?
- No, no. But you have me curious.
Why are you still here
when the both of us know
that this is bad for you?
- Do you want me to quit?
- No.
No, you had an opportunity to quit.
You didn't take it. Why not?
Let me tell you what I think.
I think that the work you do here
has created a sense of stability for you.
Stability is good for you, Will.
Stability requires strong foundations.
My moorings are built on sand.
I'm not sand. I am bedrock.
When you doubt yourself,
you don't have to doubt me, too.
(Lecter) The Jamón Ibérico.
Still love your little rare treats,
don't you, Hannibal?
More expensive and difficult
they are to obtain, the better.
(Lecter) It's a distinction that adds
an expectation of quality.
Not always.
Well, for Ibérico, only a few thousand
are selected each year.
But is the pig,
once fattened and slaughtered
and air-cured,
really superior to any other pig?
Or is it simply a matter
of reputation preceding product?
It's irrelevant.
If the meat-eater thinks it's superior,
then belief determines value.
A case of psychology
overriding neurology.
So we know how Ibérico gets his pigs.
How did you get yours?
Are you referring to Will Graham?
We know you're fond of the rarified.
What makes him so rare?
Will has a remarkably vivid imagination.
Beautiful.
Pure empathy.
Nothing he can't understand
and that terrifies him.
So you set his mind on fire.
Imagination is
an interesting accelerant for a fever.
So... how far does this go?
Do you put out the fire...
...or do you let him burn?
Will is my friend.
We will put out the fire
when it's necessary.
He has asked for more tests.
Now that we have confirmed what it is,
it'll be easier to hide from him.
Put these in.
This'll be over before you know it.
Dr Sutcliffe?
You're clean.
You couldn't have done this
without getting something on you,
and there's nothing on you.
I don't feel clean.
The murder weapon has the same
sort of diseased or damaged tissues
that we found
at Beth LeBeau's house.
What's this guy got to do
with the other victim?
Just me.
What do you remember?
I remember coming here,
going into the MRI, getting out
and finding Dr Sutcliffe's body.
No confusion.
Well, not that I'm aware of.
Was your Dr Sutcliffe in the habit
of seeing patients after hours
when he's the only one in the office?
He was very accommodating.
Georgia Madchen
followed you here...
...and while you're ticking away
in the MRI,
she does this to your doctor.
- Why him?
- (Graham) She can't see faces.
Maybe she thought he was me.
All right, while we're at it, why you?
I don't know.
I have a habit of collecting strays.
I-I told her,
tried to tell her the night I saw her.
I tried to tell her she was alive.
Maybe she heard me.
Maybe that hadn't occurred to her
in a while.
(Dog growling)
(Growling and barking)
(Groans and gasps)
I see you, Georgia.
Think of who you are.
It's midnight.
You're in Wolf Trap, Virginia.
Your name is Georgia Madchen.
You're not alone.
We are here together.
Am I alive?
(Crawford) She'll recover?
(Lecter) Risk of infection is high.
She's lost most of the vital fluids.
Even some bone mass.
She's being treated like a burn victim.
- But she'll recover mentally?
- She has Cotard's syndrome.
Almost all sufferers of this delusion
recover with treatment.
In extreme cases like this one,
electroconvulsive therapy.
I'm more concerned about Will.
I thought you'd be more concerned
about your colleague Dr Sutcliffe.
I am grieving Dr Sutcliffe.
But Will is very much alive.
He's still desperate for an explanation
that can make everything right again.
I'm pretty desperate
for some explanations myself.
I really want to talk to this
young woman when she comes to.
How much do you think
she'll remember?
Well, I sincerely hope, for her sake,
she doesn't remember much.
(Sniffs)