(Crawford) 'Previously on "Hannibal"...'
The reason you kept failing to capture the
Chesapeake Ripper is I already had him.
I see the Ripper,
but I don't feel the Ripper.
Franklyn, the lion is not in the room.
He's eating them.
The real Chesapeake Ripper is gonna
make sure everybody knows it.
I don't think we've ever been alone
in a room together, have we?
My name is Miriam Lass.
I'm actually just a trainee.
A very brave young woman.
'It's Miriam.
I don't want to die like this!'
The Chesapeake Ripper kills
in sounders of three.
He did his first victims
in nine days.
Annapolis, Essex, Baltimore.
He didn't kill again for 18 months.
Then there was another sounder
of three in as many days,
all of them in Baltimore.
I use the term "sounders" because
it refers to a small group of pigs.
That's how he sees his victims,
not as people, not as prey.
Pigs.
Eleven months after the sixth victim,
there was a seventh.
Two days later, the eighth is killed
in his workshop.
Every tool on the pegboard where
they hung was used against him,
and, as with previous murders,
organs were removed.
The removal of organs
and abdominal mutilations means
someone with anatomical
or surgical know-how.
There... is a distinctive brutality.
An FBI trainee named
Miriam Lass
was investigating
private medical records
of all the known victims
when she disappeared.
She's believed to be
the Ripper's ninth,
but no trace of her was found
until recently,
two years later,
when her severed arm was discovered.
Only because he wanted it to be.
True to his established pattern,
the Chesapeake Ripper has
remained consistently theatrical.
(♪ Female singing opera)
It's been too long since you've
properly cooked for us, Hannibal.
Come over
and I will cook for you.
I said "properly",
means dinner and the show.
Have you seen him cook?
It's an entire performance.
He used to throw
such exquisite dinner parties.
You heard me. "Used to".
And I will again,
once inspiration strikes.
I cannot force a feast,
a feast must present itself.
- It's a dinner party not a unicorn.
- But the feast is life.
You put the life in your belly
and you live.
(She chuckles)
I believe this young man is trying
to get your attention.
- Hello.
- Hi. It's so good to see you.
- This is my friend Tobias.
- Good evening.
How do you two know each other?
There should remain some mystery
to my life outside the opera.
- I'm one of his patients.
- Oh.
- Did you enjoy the performance?
- I did. I loved it. Every minute.
His eyes kept wandering.
More interested in you
than what was happening on stage.
Oh, don't say too much. You must leave
something for us to discuss next week.
Franklyn, good to see you.
- You too.
- Tobias.
- Who's hungry?
- (She giggles)
(Phone rings)
(Ringing continues)
(Continues ringing)
(Phone rings)
Hello?
The victim was found
in a hotel room bathtub.
There were abdominal mutilations
and organ removal on the scene.
Sounds more like an urban legend
than the Chesapeake Ripper, no?
I've had the room sealed.
You'll get it fresh.
Fresh? Fresh as a daisy?
Fresh enough for you to tell me
whether or not it's the Ripper.
- Then you can go back to class.
- You don't want me in a classroom.
You want me to wrap my head
so tight around the Ripper
I won't go back to class
until he's caught.
- Your bad luck that you're the best, pal.
- Expecting more bodies after this one?
- If it's the Ripper, yes, I am.
- Don't let the Ripper stir you up.
The reason he left you Miriam Lass's arm
is so he could poke you with it.
Why not the rest of her?
His other victims...
he wanted to humiliate in death,
like a public dissection.
She was different.
He was probably impressed
that she was able to find him.
He may be starting another cycle, Will.
The Ripper contacted you directly.
If he was killing again,
he wouldn't be subtle about it,
he would just pick up the phone.
- Any more phone calls, Jack?
- No.
If this is the Ripper, there'll be
at least two more bodies
and then nothing for months,
maybe a year.
We'll have a window of opportunity
to catch him and that window will close.
The last time the window closed,
I lost the Ripper and I lost Miriam Lass.
I don't intend to do that again.
Has anyone touched the body?
For once, local police behaved
themselves.
It's fairly evident the man's dead
just by looking at him.
I touched the body.
A lot going on with that body.
Surgery was performed
and then un-performed.
Surgery was un-performed
with bare hands, sutures clawed open.
Er... I also... did
a little bit of touching.
Pieces of him were torn off from the bed
to the bathroom like breadcrumbs.
Surgery wasn't performed here.
There would be a lot more blood.
If he's moving his victims,
he could be performing the mutilations
in the same transport.
(Price) Find the car, find the killer.
- He tore open his own sutures.
- It wasn't to get to his kidney.
The Ripper already took it with him.
Or her.
I'd say him.
- What did he take out of the chest?
- Going for the heart.
Probably interrupted. It's intact.
Traumatised, but it's intact.
Everybody out.
Signs of a struggle indicate
he's suffering from a severe,
violent emergence from deep sedation.
Oh!
His heart seizes up.
(Gasps)
I open his chest wall.
I spread the ribs.
I take his heart in my hand.
Internal cardiac massage.
(Gasps)
Jack?
This wasn't brutal.
The killer wasn't killing,
he was trying to save his life.
The Ripper ever do that?
- It's the Chesapeake Ripper.
- (Graham) It's not the Ripper.
- There are too many similarities.
- There aren't enough.
Knife wounds are cuts, not stabs.
Anatomical knowledge,
dissection skills, mutilation,
organs removed,
victim clothed, on display.
We got 22 signature components
all attributable to the same killer.
Twenty two possible
signature components.
It's the Ripper.
- Are you sure?
- More or less.
Tell me why you're sure.
The Ripper left a victim in a church pew
using his tongue as a page marker
in the Bible he was holding.
This isn't that,
this is a medical student,
or a trainee or someone trying
to make an extra buck
in a back-alley surgery,
and it went bad.
Actively bad.
We'll catch the Ripper. Eventually.
Yeah, well, I want to catch him now.
When I do, you won't get a chance
to shoot him, cos I'm gonna do that.
You can't just jack up the law
and get underneath it.
Can't I?
Tell me how you see the Ripper, Will.
I see him
as one of those pitiful things
sometimes born in hospitals.
They feed it, keep it warm,
but they don't put it on the machines.
They let it die.
But he doesn't die.
He looks normal.
And nobody can tell what he is.
Good morning.
Please come in.
Would you like to discuss
our chance encounter?
(Chuckles)
It wasn't altogether by chance.
I kind of... kinda thought
you'd be there...
which isn't why I was there.
I-I... I was there because
I like that sort of thing.
It just occurred to me that...
that you might like it too.
In fact, I do.
- I tried to get your attention.
- I was aware of that.
I knew that you were aware,
even though you were pretending
that you weren't.
It would be unethical
to approach a patient
or acknowledge in any way
our relationship outside this room
until that patient gives consent.
But I really don't know
who you are outside this room.
- I'm your psychiatrist.
- I want you to be my friend.
Of course you do.
I have intimate knowledge of you.
And we like the same things.
I think that we would make good friends.
It makes me sad
that I have to pay to see you.
(Sighs heavily)
I am a source of stability and clarity,
Franklyn. I'm not your friend.
I'm a great friend.
I was listening to, uh,
Michael Jackson last night,
and I burst into tears, and...
My eyes are burning right now
just thinking about it.
You know what I think is
the saddest thing
about him dying is that
I will never get to meet him,
and I feel like if I was his friend
that I... I would have
been able to...
help save him from himself.
In this Michael Jackson fantasy,
how is your friendship returned?
I just get to touch greatness.
Hello. Come on in.
This always goes better
if I'm perfectly honest with you.
What would be the point otherwise?
Well, one of us has to be honest.
I'm honest.
- Not perfectly.
- As honest as anyone.
Not really.
I have conversations
with a version of you
and hope that the actual you
gets what he needs.
A version of me?
Naturally, I respect
its meticulous construction,
but you are wearing
a very well-tailored "person suit".
Do you refer to me as "Person suit"
with your psychiatrist friends?
I don't discuss patients
with my psychiatrist friends,
especially since I only have
one patient
who chooses to ignore
my retirement.
A patient who wears a person suit.
Maybe it's less of a person suit
and more of a human veil.
That must be lonely.
I have friends.
And the opportunities for friends.
You and I are friendly.
You are my patient
and my colleague, not my friend.
At the end of your hour,
I will pour you a glass of wine.
Nevertheless, you will be drinking it
on the other side of the veil.
Why do you bother?
I see enough of you
to see the truth of you.
And I like you.
Red or white?
I think something pink, don't you?
Good evening, Will.
Please come in.
Oh, you've been drinking.
I had a glass of wine
with my last appointment, yes.
Drinking with a patient.
She was drinking with a patient.
I have an unconventional
psychiatrist.
Well, we have that in common.
Am I your psychiatrist, or are we
simply having conversations?
"Yes" I think is the answer to that.
Then having a glass of wine
before seeing a patient,
I assure you, is very conventional.
Especially for evening appointments.
Huh. How long have you been
seeing a psychiatrist?
Since I chose to be a psychiatrist.
Thank you.
I read the Freddy Lounds article.
Chesapeake Ripper has struck again.
No, no, no.
No, it's not the same guy.
Maybe it's never been the same guy.
Oh, what, now he has a friend?
(Chuckles)
Any variations in the murders that might
suggest more than one Ripper?
Some variations.
The victims were all brutalised.
What was the brutalisation hiding?
The careful surgical removal
and preservation of vital organs.
Valuable organs.
Organ harvesters?
Jack's looking for a serial killer
he can't seem to catch.
It's a brilliant diversion.
That's an interesting theory.
I will keep it in mind
if another body drops.
Please do.
(Man) Any other infections?
(Lecter) You seem convinced
I'm diseased.
I was asking a broader question.
A disease is an infection.
- An infection isn't always a disease.
- That is true.
You should tell me now,
because I'm going to find out,
and it will affect your insurance
if you lie.
May I ask for your business card,
please, for my records?
(Metallic knocking)
Aargh!
Do you need a hand?
I think I must've hit a rock or something.
It gouged my gas tank.
Have we met before?
(Zeller) Found him in a school bus,
sitting across the aisle from himself.
Not only did the Ripper
take his kidney...
...but he also took his heart,
which is what he tried to do in the hotel
but was interrupted before
he could paint his picture.
The Ripper wasn't painting a picture
in the hotel. Someone else was.
You still think he was ripping out
a heart to save a life?
Yes, I do.
The Ripper painted this picture,
for sure, in big, broad strokes.
Could both victims' organs
have been harvested for transplant?
Subtle variation on waking up
in a tub of ice missing a kidney?
I love a good urban legend.
You could put the organs on a ventilator
long enough to coordinate the donation.
At the hotel, the victim's abdominal
aorta and inferior vena cava...
that's like the kidney's in-and-out
for blood... were entirely removed.
They're like USB cables. You keep
them intact for an easy reconnect.
Were Mr Caldwell's heart and kidney
disconnected for easy reconnect?
Yeah.
Other Ripper victims...
Organs and USB cables missing?
It's inconclusive due to the degree
of mutilation,
but yes, that is how the Ripper rips.
Two different killers, same agenda?
Is the organ harvester
disguising his work
as the crimes of a serial killer,
or is the serial killer disguising his
crimes as the work of an organ harvester?
The Chesapeake Ripper
wants to perform.
Every brutal choice has elegance...
...grace.
His mutilations hide
the true nature of his crimes.
I've been unspeakably rude,
I haven't offered you a drink.
I appreciate beer more than wine.
It's not what you appreciate,
it's that you appreciate.
A compromise?
Beer brewed in a wine barrel.
Two years. I bottled it myself.
I'm impressed.
A Cabernet Sauvignon wine barrel.
- I love your palate.
- I love your beer.
I taste oak.
What else do I taste in there?
I will only answer that yes or no.
Are you serving this
at your dinner party?
- No. This is your reserve.
- My own private reserve?
Why, thank you.
I'm curious about something.
Are you purposefully avoiding
the subject of Will Graham?
Absolutely.
Not on my account, I hope.
I'm happy to get your perspective.
No, it's on Jack Crawford's account.
I don't want any information about Will
that I shouldn't have as his friend.
Did Jack ask you to profile the Ripper?
Not since I consulted on the case
with Miriam before she disappeared.
- Crawford's trainee?
- Yeah.
Very sad.
You had me examining
PhD candidates that week.
And I'm grateful you were examining
PhD students and not the Ripper.
You realise those candidates thought
we were having an affair.
- Why didn't we?
- You were already having an affair.
- Will does that too, you know.
- What? Have affairs?
Flirtatiously change the subject.
You have that pathology in common.
Or we just have you in common.
I recall even before I met Will,
you never spoke about him.
Probably because I just want
everybody to leave him alone.
It's not even about Will.
Jack's obsessed with the Ripper
and he's grooming Will to catch him.
And I sincerely hope he does.
(♪ Opera music playing)
(Price) They're all missing
different organs.
Before, we were looking
at waiting lists for a heart or a kidney.
Now we're looking at hearts,
kidneys, livers, stomachs,
pancreases, lungs.
This guy,
he's missing a spleen.
A spleen! Who the hell gets
a spleen transplant?
Intestines were the only organ
missing from this body?
Yes, so we're either looking
for someone with short bowels or...
Ripper's making sausage.
He's selling these organs to someone.
We don't even know if he's
transplanting them within the US.
- He could be exporting them to China.
- The Chinese have a cultural taboo
that restricts voluntary donation.
You gotta die with all your parts
or you dishonour mummy and daddy.
(Zeller) You can still kill a guy
for parts, that doesn't break that taboo.
I was agreeing with you.
- Well, I was.
- Your tone was a little...
OK... How many killers?
Two.
You confident one of them
is the Chesapeake Ripper?
At least one of them, yep.
Good morning. Please come in.
I discovered that
we are cheese folk.
I saw you shopping for cheese.
I didn't say hello, because you were
so uncomfortable the last time I did.
- This city is very small.
- Yes. Jose's.
Jose's has the best selection
of artisanal cheeses
in Baltimore, city or county.
(Chuckles)
Cheese is my passion.
You ever heard of tyromancy?
- Divination by cheese.
- It was my gateway to cheeses.
It was like a magic 8-ball
that you can eat.
Tobias, he, erm...
he doesn't eat dairy.
(Sighs heavily)
Do you desire Tobias sexually?
No. God, no. Uh... no.
Not to be defensive.
I just, erm...
Don't get me wrong.
I was in a "fraternity".
I tried things, you know?
Erm... It's just not my brand.
You care deeply about Tobias?
Despite differences,
he's your best friend, but you're not his.
Well, it's sad
when you say it like that.
You often worry about being alone?
I worry about hurting.
Being alone comes with a...
a dull ache.
Doesn't it?
It can.
(♪ Opera music playing)
It's better that it's just the two of us.
(Lecter) 'Will?'
- Dad.
- Yes?
There's someone else here.
(Lecter) Will?
Will?
I have a 24-hour cancellation policy.
- What time is it?
- Nearly nine o'clock.
- Oh, God, I'm sorry.
- No apology necessary.
I must've fallen asleep.
Was I sleepwalking?
Your eyes were open,
but you were not present.
Jeez.
I felt as if I was asleep.
I need to stop sleeping altogether.
Best way to avoid bad dreams.
Well, I can see
why you have bad dreams.
What do you see, Doctor?
Sum up the Ripper
in so many words?
- Choose them wisely.
- Oh, I always do.
Words are living things,
they have personality,
point of view, agenda.
They're pack hunters.
Displaying one's enemy after death
has its appeal in many cultures.
These aren't the Ripper's enemies,
these are pests he's swatted.
Their reward for their cruelty.
Oh, he doesn't have a problem
with cruelty.
Their reward is
for undignified behaviour.
These dissections are
to disgrace them.
It's a public shaming.
Takes their organs away because,
in his mind, they don't deserve them.
In some way.
What's this?
It's Jack Crawford's trainee.
She's not like the other victims.
The Ripper had no reason
to humiliate Miriam Lass.
Seems to me
he was humiliating someone.
Yeah, he was humiliating Jack.
- Did it work?
- I'd say it worked really well.
I've been looking for the kill truck,
a van or SUV.
But it was a whole lot easier than that.
- What am I looking at here?
- One of the hotel security cameras.
- Kill truck?
- It's a private ambulance.
The city works with dozens
of private ambulance companies.
Including this one.
But not as a first responder.
A first responder driving away
from the emergency?
Have a seat.
Ambulance would be a smart place
to perform surgery.
If the cops show up,
blend in and drive away.
Where's Will Graham?
Will. There you are.
And Dr Lecter.
What a surprise. We have a lead.
Would you care to, uh,
help us catch the Ripper?
How could I refuse?
That ambulance isn't in rotation,
hasn't even been out of the shed.
Surveillance footage says
it has been.
Nobody's signed her out.
My road sheet's got her down for repairs.
And who signed her in for repairs?
Devon Silvestri,
one of our part-time drivers.
- Does he want to be a doctor?
- He's taking the MCATs.
What?
- It was there this morning.
- It was there this morning. Well...
- Is Mr Silvestri working today?
- He's not on the schedule.
- Is there GPS on that ambulance?
- Mm-hm.
Encrypted messaging,
or remote tracking?
We can't afford that kind of hardware.
We use consumer grade.
- Digital trunk systems.
- Yeah.
- Jack.
If the ambulance radio is on,
I can use a DF sweep to find it.
Good.
This is very educational.
- Show me your hands.
- I can't.
Show me your hands.
He'll die.
Dr Lecter!
I need you to assess
the situation here, Doctor.
He was removing his kidney. Poorly.
- I can stop the bleeding.
- Do it.
- Have you got it?
- I've got it.
Mr Silvestri, put your hands
behind your head.
Exit the vehicle slowly. Do it.
On the ground. On your knees.
I have a butcher
who carries sow's blood.
Centrifugate, separate the matter
from the water,
creates a transparent liquid.
Serve with tomatoes
in suspension
and everybody will love
the sweet taste.
Sure you can't stay?
Uh, I don't think
I would be good company.
I disagree.
But before you go,
what became
of Mr Silvestri's donor?
You saved his life.
Been a long time since I used
a scalpel on anything but a pencil.
- Why'd you stop being a surgeon?
- I killed someone.
Or more accurately, I couldn't save
someone, but it felt like killing them.
You were an emergency room surgeon,
it has to happen from time to time.
It happened one time too many.
I transferred my passion for anatomy
into the culinary arts.
I fix minds instead of bodies,
and no one's died
as a result of my therapy.
I have to go.
I have a date
with the Chesapeake Ripper.
Or is that rippers?
Devon Silvestri was harvesting organs,
but not with the Ripper.
- There's no connection between them.
- Jack must be devastated.
I imagine he is.
- Enjoy the wine.
- Thank you.
(Applause)
Before we begin,
you must all be warned,
nothing here... is vegetarian.
(Laughter)
Bon appetit.