(Lecter) 'Previously on "Hannibal"...'
Georgia Madchen was murdered
by whoever killed Dr Sutcliffe.
Dad? It's for you.
They know.
He said he got so close to Garret
Jacob Hobbs, he was becoming him.
- My name is Will Graham.
- (Crawford) You think he's mentally ill?
Whoever killed Marissa Schurr
and Cassie Boyle wanted to copy
how Garret Jacob Hobbs
killed his victims.
- And now he has Hobbs' daughter.
- Who Hobbs intended to kill.
Mind if I sit?
- Did Hannibal tell you?
- No, he didn't.
- How many people have you killed?
- Many more than your father.
Are you going to kill me?
(Laboured breathing)
(Dogs whimper and bark)
(Retching)
I went to Minnesota.
I took Abigail.
We went to Minnesota.
She didn't come back with me.
Show me.
I don't remember
going to bed last night.
But I must have.
Maybe I got up
to let the dogs out and then...
When was the last time
you saw Abigail?
- ...and my feet were muddy.
- Will!
When was the last time
you saw Abigail?
Yesterday.
At her father's cabin.
I had... an episode.
She said something was wrong with me.
She was afraid of me.
- And she ran away.
- What happened? Why was she afraid?
I hallucinated that I killed her.
But it wasn't real.
I know it wasn't real.
Will, we have to call Jack.
You can't run from this.
It will only be worse.
Get dressed.
What are we gonna find
in Minnesota, Will?
I don't know.
Go ahead and process him.
(Dog whimpers)
(Muffled voices)
(Price) Right rear pocket.
A leather wallet
containing $17.00 cash.
(Zeller) Right rear pocket.
Leather wallet, $17.00 cash.
(Price) Right front pocket.
- One folding knife.
- (Zeller) Right front pocket. Folding knife.
I can't do the silent treatment.
I can't pretend I don't know you
and I can't pretend we both don't know
what I'm finding under your nails.
You called me once because you didn't
trust yourself to know what was real.
- This blood is real, Will.
- I know.
Do you know how it got there?
Not with any certainty, no.
Certainty comes from the evidence.
I didn't want to find any evidence on you.
I wanted to be certain about who you are.
But you can't even be certain
with yourself.
Not any more.
If you weren't certain with yourself,
you shouldn't have been here.
This is the FBI.
I thought I would get better.
You always said you interpret
the evidence, so do it, Will.
Interpret the evidence.
According to the evidence...
...I killed Abigail Hobbs.
(Crawford) We analysed the tissue.
It matched Abigail Hobbs.
It was her ear,
her blood under Will's fingernails.
Scratches on his arms are all
defensive wounds, like she fought back.
Shut up.
- I...
- Stop talking.
"He won't get too close."
You said you would cover him.
- You could see he was breaking.
- Yes, I could.
And I kept pushing him,
because he was saving lives, Alana.
Not Abigail Hobbs' life.
Look me in the face and tell me
you couldn't see that he was breaking?
Of course I could see it.
I told you not to put him out there!
Every decision I made
concerning Will's mental health
I made under advisement
of a respected psychiatrist,
who you recommended.
Hannibal had to know,
he had to see something was wrong.
Not until it was too late.
Just like everybody else.
Hannibal said that Will was
exhibiting signs of dementia.
Dementia isn't a disease.
It's a symptom of disease!
We have to find out
what's causing it and treat it.
The concern is that
there may not be anything to treat.
Will had a brain scan.
They found nothing.
Well, then they don't know
what they're looking for.
This started with Garret Jacob Hobbs.
Maybe Will just did
what Hobbs couldn't.
He killed his daughter.
Abigail's blood is on all of us.
And so is Will's.
(♪ Music over audio)
(Door opens)
Hi.
You're flushed. You been yelling?
- Screaming is more like it.
- I could use a good scream.
I can feel one perched under my chin.
- Let it out.
- I'm afraid that if I started...
...I wouldn't be able to stop.
I'm surprised Jack let you in here,
given my romantic overtures.
Jack doesn't know about
your romantic overtures.
Didn't know.
I guess you dodged a bullet with me.
I don't feel like I dodged a bullet.
I feel wounded.
I've been in touch
with, erm... Animal Services.
I'll go pick up your dogs
in a couple hours.
I'll take them back home with me,
and I'll take care of them until...
...whenever.
Whenever could be
a long time from now.
I'll take care of them until then.
Thank you.
We have to do some tests.
They'll be the standard
psychopathology tests.
I suppose you're gonna ask me
to draw a clock while you're at it.
Did Hannibal ask you to draw a clock?
He said it was an exercise...
...to ground me
in the present moment.
A handle to help me hold onto reality.
- Was the clock normal?
- Would I be here if it wasn't?
Draw me a clock.
(Sighs heavily)
(Graham) You see?
It's just a normal clock.
Telling the time isn't my problem.
It's the least of your problems.
It seems hard to find words today.
Ah...
Despite the overwhelming evidence,
I find myself
searching for ways
that Abigail could still be alive.
Grieving is an individual process
with a universal goal,
the truest examination of the meaning
of life and the meaning of its end.
I know what life means.
We've existed for
a hundred thousand years.
In that time, a hundred billion human
lives have had beginnings and ends.
A hundred billion lives
haven't impacted yours,
but clearly Abigail Hobbs' life has
and you seem surprised by that.
I never considered having a child.
But after meeting Abigail,
I understood the appeal.
The opportunity to guide and support,
and, in many ways, direct a life.
- You were having influence on her?
- I was hoping I was.
Young people are supposed
to be the lenses
through which we see ourselves
living beyond this life.
I think of my earliest memory
and project forward to what
I imagine will be my death.
I never think about living
beyond that span of time.
- Except by reputation.
- Even after this loss?
More so after this loss.
Will Graham is a loss, too.
You might grieve him as a loss.
I haven't given up on Will.
If they do find him guilty
of killing Abigail Hobbs...
When.
Let's be honest.
I don't recommend you participate
in any rehabilitation effort.
I was so confident in my ability
to help him, to solve him.
To save him.
Saving him, I lost Abigail.
It's hard to accept that I could
fail them both so profoundly.
(Crawford) OK, Jimmy,
what have you got?
As you know, Will is a big fly fisherman
and he designs all of his own lures.
Most anglers use feathers,
fur, twine, bits of shell.
They design each lure
to catch a specific fish.
This one caught my eye.
I noticed the hair colour.
Took me a few
to accept what I was seeing.
I ran a chem-set
to confirm the connection.
What connection?
Four of the lures are made from
materials including human remains.
(Price) And we have a DNA match
for all of them.
(Katz) This one is Cassie Boyle.
Bits of bone fragments
and pieces of lung.
Marissa Schurr. Antler velvet,
a fingernail, wound with her hair.
Dr Sutcliffe. Crushed teeth,
soft tissue from inside his mouth,
bound with cartilage from his jaw.
All victims of the copycat?
And this last lure was made with hair
and fibre that matches Georgia Madchen.
- He took trophies of all his victims.
- Trophies?
So now Will Graham's a serial killer
who takes trophies?
Somethings wrong with Will physically,
neurologically. He's not a serial killer.
(Crawford) You're sick, Will.
I wasn't consistent
with taking my antibiotics.
The fever came back.
We're gonna move you
to a secure medical ward,
get to the bottom of whatever it is
that's wrong with you
and make sure that you get
whatever kind of treatment you need.
And then what?
Baltimore State Hospital
for the Criminally Insane?
Have Chilton fumbling
around in my head?
This job doesn't generally
lend itself to optimism, all right?
But I desperately want to be
optimistic about an alternative
to what every fibre of the evidence
is telling me you've done.
I can't confess to something
I don't remember.
The question is, how much more
is there that you don't remember?
We found your fishing lures.
Yeah, I should hope so.
They were on my desk
right by the front door.
We found human remains amongst
the materials that you made them from.
The human remains
of Cassie Boyle, Marissa Schurr,
Donald Sutcliffe, Georgia Madchen.
No.
Yes.
I wasn't...
I wasn't sick when Cassie Boyle
was murdered.
I wasn't sick when Marissa Schurr
That's not an argument you wanna
be making right now. Not with me.
Because then I'd be a psychopath.
My biggest fear is that we'll learn
that you knew what you were doing
the whole time.
You don't have to be afraid of that, Jack.
There is something
you should be afraid of, though.
Yeah? What's that?
Whoever's doing this to me...
- Someone's doing this to you?
- They'll be close to you.
It could be someone here.
Working with you.
So that's it? It's a set-up?
They know the cases.
They know forensics.
They know that I'm unstable.
Can you hear how paranoid
you sound?
Or it could just be you.
Then I'd be really screwed, wouldn't I?
I wanted to be the one to do this.
Will Graham,
you're under arrest for murder.
You have the right to remain silent.
He disarmed his guard.
He threw the guard and the driver
from the vehicle.
We found the ambulance
in an alley in Dumfries.
These are not the actions
of an innocent man.
They're the actions
of a man who's impaired.
I had Will draw a clock
to test for cognitive dysfunction.
(Lecter) That is extreme.
Now this is the clock
he drew for me two weeks ago.
It's normal.
What disease progresses gradually
but plateaus for lengths of time?
Will has periods of clarity.
We've seen him lucid and aware
one moment
and then the next moment he's not.
- Could be some form of encephalitis.
- Auto-immune encephalitis?
It's hard to diagnose.
There are no tumours. No lesions.
It wouldn't even show up on a brain scan
unless you were looking for it.
Look, just tell me if he could kill
five people and not be aware of it.
This doesn't feel like dementia.
This is an intelligent psychopath.
Look, this killer called the Hobbs' house,
he warned Abigail's father.
I was with Will that entire time.
Did he have an opportunity
to make a phone call?
Before we went to interview
Garret Jacob Hobbs,
he was alone in the office while I was
outside loading the car with the files,
but that was only for a few minutes.
Dumb luck and bad bookkeeping.
That's how Will said he caught Hobbs.
Now how would you say he caught him?
We were looking through the files
and it was as if Will plucked
his name out of a hat,
based on little more than
an incomplete address.
Let me play the devil here
for a moment, Doctor.
This clock test...
Could Will fake something like this?
Would he be able to do that?
Yes.
Hello, Will.
How are you feeling?
Self aware.
You frightened Alana Bloom.
She's confused about who I am...
...which I can relate to.
- Are you confused about who I am?
- I'm not confused. I'm sceptical.
Meaning I'm willing to change my mind
should the evidence change.
Do you believe I killed Abigail?
I believe it's entirely possible,
if not nearly indisputable,
based on how you discovered her ear.
If it was just Abigail,
I would've believed.
I would've believed that I got so far
inside Hobbs' head I couldn't get out.
But it wasn't just Abigail.
- I know who I am.
- No.
All sense of who you are
has been distorted by your illness.
You know who you are
in this moment.
That's not always the case, Will.
I didn't kill any of them.
And somebody is making sure
that no one believes me.
If we're to prove
you didn't commit these murders,
perhaps we should consider
how you could have.
And then disprove that.
If you are this killer,
that identity runs through these events
like a thread through pearls.
Cassie Boyle would have been
your first victim.
You said her crime scene
was practically gift-wrapped.
It told me everything I needed to know
to catch Garret Jacob Hobbs.
(Lecter) You had seen one of Hobbs'
victims. You knew how he killed.
You may have been exploring
how he killed
to better understand who he was.
I wasn't in Minnesota
when Cassie Boyle was murdered.
She disappeared on a Saturday.
She was found on a Monday.
You would've had the weekend
to do your work.
I know I didn't kill her.
How do you know?
What did you think
when you first met Marissa Schurr?
How much like Abigail she was?
Same height, same weight,
hair colour, same age.
- How could I resist?
- So much like his daughter.
You may have wondered why Garret
Jacob Hobbs didn't kill her himself.
Dr Sutcliffe wasn't killed
how Garret Jacob Hobbs killed.
He was murdered how you imagined
yourself murdering a woman
only days before.
How Georgia Madchen killed.
She dreamt she saw me killing Sutcliffe.
But she couldn't see my face.
And then she was murdered.
You catch these killers
by getting into their heads,
but you also allow them
into your own.
I'm trying to help you, Will.
Then take me to Minnesota.
I want to see where Abigail died.
Have you had any contact with
Hannibal Lecter in the last 24 hours?
He didn't make his session this morning
and he didn't call in,
which he would consider rude.
- Is something wrong?
- I'm on my way to Minnesota.
I believe that Will Graham has taken
Hannibal to Minnesota.
Will thinks he's being framed
for these murders.
He's slipping in and out of delusion.
He could kill Hannibal
and not even know he's doing it.
If anyone could've helped Mr Graham,
it would've been Hannibal.
In fact, he may still be trying.
(Phone ringing)
Hello?
Just a second. Dad? It's for you.
Caller ID said it was blocked.
Hello?
(Lecter) 'Will?'
Yes.
Will?
We're here.
Are we gonna re-enact the crime?
You be my dad. You be my mum.
And you be the man on the phone.
Are we gonna re-enact the crime?
If that would help you.
It's as if Abigail was supposed
to die in this kitchen.
Her throat was cut.
She lost great gouts of blood.
There's an unmistakable arterial spray.
- They haven't found her body.
- Just the one piece.
If you were in Garret Jacob Hobbs'
frame of mind when you killed her,
they may never find her.
Cos I honoured every part of her?
Perhaps you didn't come here
looking for a killer.
Perhaps you came here
to find yourself.
You killed a man in this very room.
I stared at Hobbs.
And the space opposite me
assumed the shape of a man
filled with dark and swarming flies.
Then I scattered them.
At a time when other men
fear their isolation,
yours has become
understandable to you.
You are alone
because you are unique.
I'm as alone as you are.
If you followed the urges
you kept down for so long,
cultivated them
as the inspirations they are...
...you would have become
someone other than yourself.
I know who I am.
I'm not so sure
I know who you are any more.
But I am certain
one of us killed Abigail.
Whoever that was, killed the others.
Are you a killer, Will?
You. Right now.
This man standing in front of me.
- Is this who you really are?
- I am who I've always been.
The scales have just fallen
from my eyes.
I can see you now.
What do you see?
You called here that morning.
Abigail knew.
And you kept her secrets until...
Until what?
Until she found out some of yours?
You said it felt good
to kill Garret Jacob Hobbs.
- Would it feel good to kill me now?
- Garret Jacob Hobbs was a murderer.
- Are you a murderer, Dr Lecter?
- What reason would I have?
You have no traceable motive...
...which is why
you were so hard to see.
You were just curious
what I would do.
Someone like me.
Someone who thinks how I think.
Wind him up and watch him go.
Apparently, Dr Lecter...
this is how I go.
Will?
Easy.
See?
You see?
((Medical instruments bleeping)
(Lecter) The right hemisphere
of his brain was inflamed.
They've placed him
in an induced sleep
and they are treating him
with antiviral and steroid therapies.
- Is he responding?
- More or less.
He's expected to make
a substantial recovery.
Would you have gone to Minnesota
with him if he didn't have a gun on you?
I would have wanted to.
I believe I've failed to satisfy
my obligation to Will,
more than I care to admit.
Well, he's not your victim, Doctor.
Nor is he yours.
You know, in my time
I've seen people broken by the world.
I've seen them broken in all kinds
of hideous and offhanded ways
but never like this.
Never like this.
No one in this room will be the same.
- Good evening.
- Hello, Hannibal. Please come in.
Tête de Veau en Sauce Verte.
It smells like a bonfire.
I smoked the veal
on a pyre of dry hay.
It imparts a unique smouldering
flavour to the meat and to the room.
This is an unexpected treat.
Thank you for indulging me.
You seemed like you needed to talk.
Since you refuse invitations
to my dinner table,
this is the only way I could cook for you.
What's on your mind, Hannibal?
I'm going to see Will tomorrow.
As a patient or as a friend?
As a farewell. Of sorts.
I thought Mr Graham was finally going
to be the patient who cost you your life.
He didn't cost me my life.
He cost Abigail hers.
- Your veal is getting cold.
- Controversial dish, veal.
Mmm.
Those who denounce veal often cite the
young age at which the animals are killed,
when they're in fact older
than many pigs going to slaughter.
You have to be careful, Hannibal.
They're starting to see your pattern.
What pattern would that be?
You develop relationships with patients
who are prone to violence.
That pattern.
Under scrutiny, Jack Crawford's beliefs
about you might start to unravel.
Tell me, Dr Du Maurier...
...have your beliefs about me
begun to unravel?
Hello, Will.
Hello, Dr Lecter.