(Lecter)
'Previously on "Hannibal"...'
I thought it might be
the Chesapeake Ripper,
but there were
no surgical trophies taken.
- I need you to prepare yourself on this.
- I'm prepared.
Prepare yourself more.
It's soup in there.
Jack gave you his word
he would protect your headspace,
yet he leaves you
to your mental devices.
Are you trying to alienate me
from Jack Crawford?
It's difficult to lie still and fear going
to sleep when it's there to think about.
Do you have a history
of sleepwalking, Mr Graham?
My wife and I need to talk.
May we use your waiting room?
- Lung cancer.
- When were you gonna tell me?
- Do I seem different?
- But you've always been a little different.
It's getting harder and harder
to make myself look.
I won't tell you what you ought to do.
I don't know how much longer
I can be useful to you, Jack.
Really?
The last three we had, you caught.
You can't arrest me for writing an article.
You don't write another word about
Will Graham and I won't have to.
This is your final opportunity
to comply.
On your feet, Dr Gideon,
or we will restrain you.
(Door buzzes)
All right, lace your fingers
behind your head!
Get a gurney!
(Machine flatlines)
Thanks to Freddie Lounds,
there's an unconfirmed story out there
that the Chesapeake Ripper's
already in custody.
Unconfirmed. Am I confirming?
- Fact-checking for Freddie Lounds?
- You're fact-checking for me.
I always feel nervous
going in these places.
- Why's that?
- Afraid they won't let me out.
- Don't worry, I won't leave you here.
- Yeah, not today.
Dr Bloom just called me about you,
Mr Graham...
- Or should I call you Dr Graham?
- I'm not a doctor.
You're not FBI either.
That's a temporary identification.
- Mr Graham teaches at the Academy.
- Ah, a teacher.
Please, gentlemen, take a seat.
Thank you.
Dr Chilton, we need to see
the crime scene
while it's still relatively undisturbed.
I assure you, for something
so disturbing, it is quite undisturbed.
Why was a nurse left alone
with a prisoner
in a high-security psychiatric hospital?
For the two years since he was
brought here, Gideon behaved perfectly
and gave every appearance
of cooperating with attempts at therapy.
As dictated by our present administrator,
security around him was slightly relaxed.
I cannot help feeling responsible
myself for what happened.
He sat directly across from me
and I had no idea what he was hiding.
- And now one of our staff is dead.
- (Crawford) I understand, Doctor.
Mr Graham's going to need
to see the crime scene
with as much privacy
as you can provide.
Oh, yes, that thing you do.
You're quite the topic of conversation
in psychiatric circles, Mr Graham.
- Am I?
- Uh, yes.
A unique cocktail
of personality disorders and neuroses
that make you a highly skilled profiler.
- He's not here to be analysed.
- Perhaps he should be.
We are woefully short of material
on your sort of "thing", Mr Graham.
- Would you speak to some of the staff?
- (Crawford) Doctor.
No, no. Not this trip.
Maybe a special visit.
Thank you, Dr Chilton.
I'd like to see the crime scene now.
So Gideon was restrained?
- Handcuffed.
- Hmm.
He concealed a fork tine in the palm
of his hand and used it to pick the lock.
- Where is he now?
- In his cell.
You'll note the removal of organs
and the abdominal mutilations
are all consistent
with the Chesapeake Ripper.
So is the brutalisation of the corpses,
but the Ripper is still out there.
Jack... what I'm about to show you
suggests otherwise.
(Door buzzes)
Dr Chilton consulted on the case
when we failed to catch the Ripper
after his last series of murders.
The reason you kept failing to capture
The Chesapeake Ripper
was I already had him.
(Machine bleeps)
(Nurse Shell)
Ah!
Shh, shh, shh!
Erm...
Far as we know, it's been over two years
since the Chesapeake Ripper killed?
That's correct.
- When was Gideon admitted?
- Almost two years ago.
(Crawford) Lass, Miriam. Come in.
- Morning, Agent Crawford.
- Sorry to pull you out of class.
There's nothing wrong.
Er... no reason to be nervous.
I'm not nervous. Curious.
Your instructors tell me that
you are in the top ten per cent.
Top five, sir.
You'll have to stop correcting me
if we're gonna get along, Lass.
Take a seat.
You wrote me a letter
when you qualified for the Academy.
I wasn't sure you got it.
You never replied.
Never do. Odds are against any trainee
completing the programme.
But I'm glad to see you're still here.
In your letter, you said
you wanted to work for me
in the violent criminal
apprehension programme.
- Yes, sir.
- There might be an opportunity.
I'm assuming that you're familiar
with the Chesapeake Ripper.
- Yes.
- Ripper's very hot right now.
Killed his last two victims
in six days.
There'll be at least one more body
and then nothing for months.
- They say he's a true sociopath.
- What do you say?
I say they don't know
what else to label him.
He has some of the characteristics
of what they call a sociopath.
No remorse or guilt at all.
He won't have
any of the other marks.
He won't be a drifter.
He'll have no history of trouble
with the law. He'll be hard to catch.
I'm assigning you to
the Chesapeake Ripper task force.
You're gonna work directly under me.
I'm grateful for the opportunity,
Agent Crawford.
But I can't help wondering... why me?
You have a forensics fellowship,
six years of law enforcement,
a degree in psychology,
doctorate in criminology.
And what I don't have
are enough warm bodies.
So, I'm gonna need
your full attention on this.
(Lass) 'Yes, sir.'
(Chilton) The volume of Abel Gideon's
mail is becoming a nuisance.
Sometimes I feel like his secretary
rather than his keeper.
Any specific correspondences
that stood out from the others?
Mostly researchers or PhD candidates
requesting interviews.
A scattered dozen lonely hearts
seeking his hand in marriage.
He butchered his last wife
and her family on Thanksgiving.
There's no accounting for taste.
Or intelligence.
Murdering his wife was impulsive.
The Chesapeake Ripper is...
methodical, meticulous.
- That's why he's so hard to catch.
- Was so hard to catch.
- Will you be conducting a joint interview?
- Separate. Compare and contrast.
I know you're anxious to get on with it.
You have talked to Gideon before,
for some length of time.
I saw him mainly in court.
I wrote an article about him
in the Journal of Criminal Psychology.
He is very familiar with you.
- He has given you a lot of thought.
- You had some sessions with him?
Yes, two. A couple years ago
when he was first institutionalised.
I've read your notes, of course,
they were more or less helpful
as I conducted my own interviews
with Dr Gideon over the years.
- Well, I'm glad I was helpful.
- More or less.
I'll go first.
(Door buzzes)
Why, Dr Bloom.
How wonderful to see you again.
You remembered.
I've met a lot of psychiatrists.
It's hard to forget one so sublime.
Thank you for your time, Dr Gideon,
I won't waste it.
Shall we begin?
Dr Bloom, what is this to be?
I was caught red-handed.
I mean, literally.
There's no mystery
as to whodunit. I did it.
The mystery is whether
you are who you say you are.
Or not.
Never liked being called
the Chesapeake Ripper.
Maybe something
with a little more wit.
Is that why you didn't take credit
for the Ripper murders before now?
Just watching the goose chase
from the box seats.
Two years of goose-chasing.
You must be a very patient man.
Are you just gonna run
the psychopathic checklist?
I have had my personality inventoried
by the Minnesota Multiphasic.
Would you prefer a Rorschach test?
If you're gonna show me
those pictures,
maybe you should put a blood
pressure cuff to my genitals.
I find it gives a much truer
gauge of reaction.
What effect were you hoping to have
by killing the night nurse?
The effect I was hoping to have
was her death.
Mission accomplished.
Brutalisation of the body
was done posthumously.
The Chesapeake Ripper usually does
that sort of thing during, not after.
I do not have to convince you
that I am the Chesapeake Ripper.
Seems that's what you need to do.
It's certainly what somebody needs.
Jack. Come in.
I'm sorry. Um...
I was just, uh...
In the neighbourhood.
Yeah, something like that.
How's Mrs Crawford?
Yeah, that's why
I was in the neighbourhood.
She's fine.
Well, she tells me that she's fine,
and she tells me when she's not.
You expect me to tell you more?
Look, Bella's at a NATO conference.
I can't talk to her. She's working.
I doubt I could talk to her
if she was here.
- About her condition?
- Yeah. About her cancer, her dying.
She doesn't want to talk to me about it.
I am prohibited from talking about it.
Doctor/patient confidentiality.
You talk to me about Will Graham.
Will Graham is not officially my patient.
We have conversations.
What do you consider this?
Desperate coping.
You don't think I have a right to know
what's happening with my wife?
You have every right to know
what's happening, but not from me.
I'm not just gonna stand outside
my marriage and watch this happen.
If that's what she wants, too bad.
She married the wrong guy for that.
I'll offer one insight. She doesn't think
she married the wrong guy.
I can't stop thinking about
when my wife is gonna die.
I look at her side of the bed and I think,
"Is she gonna die there?"
I can't stop thinking about it,
you understand? I can't stop.
You're dreading the loss
of your wife.
Yes.
And I'm thinking
about other losses too.
What other losses are you dreading?
Jack, you can't save her.
She won't let you.
The cancer won't let you.
Who else couldn't you save?
- Where is everyone?
- It's just you and me for the time being.
Take a look around here.
Tell me what you see.
He did it all here.
Did it while he was alive. He struck
the throat so he couldn't call for help.
You think he was unconscious
when the Ripper did the ripping?
No, he'd want him awake.
Organs were removed.
Not all of them. He was choosy.
He took the liver, thymus,
but left the heart.
What's he doing with the organs?
Surgical trophies.
He's a medical doctor, isn't he?
Is that why you call him the Ripper?
Why do you say that?
Psychopaths are attracted
to surgical fields.
They offer power
and require the ability to make
objective clinical decisions without feeling.
White male?
40s? 50s?
I don't know that he's white.
He's exotic somehow...
...which is why
you're gonna catch him.
- I'm gonna catch him?
- We call you the guru.
You have a peculiar cleverness.
- I'll take that as a compliment.
- You should.
You'll probably spot him
before anybody else.
Or you will.
Now I want you
to take a look at this.
There's no detectable consistency
with the Ripper victims.
He doesn't hunt exclusively
within his own ethnic group.
He's killed all creeds, colours,
men and women.
She has the exact same wound pattern
as the last victim of the Ripper. Exact.
We never found a body
for his last known victim.
Then the victim before that.
I see the Ripper,
but I don't... feel the Ripper.
This is plagiarism.
We never made the wound patterns
for any of the Ripper's victims public.
Maybe he is the Ripper, I don't know,
but if he's a plagiarist,
the real Chesapeake Ripper is gonna
make sure everybody knows it.
(Phone rings)
Hello.
(Lass) 'Jack? Jack?'
- Who is this?
- 'Jack, it's Miriam.
'I don't know where I am.
I can't see anything.'
- Miriam?
- 'I was so wrong. I was so wrong.'
Miriam?
'Please, Jack... Please.'
(Bleep)
I'm hooked into every carrier database
and telephone provider in the US.
- Nothing.
- Look again.
I did my agains.
And my again and again and agains.
I can't find any electronic trace of
any call made to your home at 2:46am.
I am telling you that the phone rang.
- Wake your wife up?
- I was alone.
Whoever made that call could've made it
from that box outside your house
or a junction in your neighbourhood.
Either way, there would be
no trace signal to track.
- You're sure it was Miriam Lass?
- It was Miriam.
You haven't heard her voice
in two years, Jack.
You gonna continue to question me, Z?
If so, maybe I should ask you to leave
while it's still safe for you to be here.
The Chesapeake Ripper recorded
Miriam Lass two years ago
as he was killing her.
Last night,
he called my house at 2:46am.
He played that recording for me.
Then we know the Ripper
is not Dr Gideon,
because we know the call wasn't made
from the Baltimore State Hospital.
- That we would've been able to trace.
- Are you certain it was a recording?
Jack, you said yourself,
there's no body.
Miriam Lass is dead!
The Ripper is making it very clear
that someone is plagiarising his work!
(Zeller) It was 2:46
in the morning, Jack.
You're in a deep sleep,
you're roused, you're disoriented.
You might not even know
you're still asleep.
I know when I'm awake.
(Hooves stepping)
(stag snorts)
(stag growls)
Will? You look like
you were dreaming.
I was thinking about something else.
Well, here's something
for you to think about.
We have a direct way of communicating
with the Chesapeake Ripper,
and we'd like to see
if we can push him.
Push him toward what?
We might be able to influence him
to become visible.
If we can enrage him.
To what purpose, Jack?
I don't see what you're asking.
Is there a way to push the Chesapeake
Ripper and focus his attention?
He's already focused on Gideon
as his adversary. Don't fool around.
Gideon is just a tabloid rumour right now.
We need to make him the truth.
You might push the Ripper
to kill again
just to prove he isn't in a hospital
for the criminally insane.
I have to push, Will.
Are you thinking about getting
into bed with Freddie Lounds?
You yourself know it's the best way
to bait the real Chesapeake Ripper.
Morning, Agent Crawford.
Thank you for inviting me.
Miss Lounds.
This is Dr Alana Bloom.
She's one of our psychiatric consultants.
- I believe you know Will Graham.
- Mr Graham. So good to see you.
Miss Lounds, you have all
the qualities of a good reporter.
You have intelligence,
guts, a good eye.
So how is it that you wind up
where you've ended up?
Where I wound up
being criminal justice journalism?
"Criminal justice journalism" being
a euphemism for tabloid reporting.
You ran an unconfirmed story
about the Chesapeake Ripper.
What I want...
is for you to confirm it.
An exclusive story would be a coup.
Mm... yes, it would.
And you would get the satisfaction
of seeing the Los Angeles Times,
the sanctified Washington Post,
and even the holy New York Times
run copyrighted material
under your by-line,
with a picture credit.
What's against you
and by association us
is that your brand of journalism is
obnoxious and therefore disliked.
Yes, that is an obstacle.
I tried to get an interview
with Dr Gideon. I was denied.
Evidently some trouble
with my euphemism.
I'm friendly with the new chief of staff,
I can get you an interview.
Not to snap bubble gum and crack wise,
but what's my angle?
Is he the Chesapeake Ripper? Or you
just want me to tell everybody he is?
He could be, and certain personalities
are attracted to certain professions.
You know what profession psychopaths
disproportionately gravitate to?
CEOs, lawyers, the clergy.
Number five on the list
is surgeons.
- I know the list.
- Then you know what number six is.
Journalists.
Know what number seven is,
Mr Graham?
Law enforcement.
Here we are, a bunch of psychopaths
helping each other out.
Dr Gideon, I'm Freddie Lounds.
May I call you Dr Gideon?
Or do you prefer
the Chesapeake Ripper?
'His name is Dr Abel Gideon,
and strong evidence has surfaced
'that he's far more than
a mild mannered surgeon
'who cruelly murdered his wife.
'Maybe, just maybe,
'Gideon is the most sought after
serial killer at large,
'a killer who's eluded the FBI
for years
'and has baffled
their most gifted profilers.
'That serial killer? None other
than the Chesapeake Ripper.
'This would explain why the Ripper has
been silent for more than two years.'
- So are you enjoying reading my mail?
- No, not particularly.
Looking for something instructional?
Diagrams?
Don't believe I can recreate
one of my own murders from memory?
You wouldn't be recreating them
from your memory, Doctor.
You're not the Chesapeake Ripper.
Ooh, have to agree to disagree.
Then why the surgical trophies?
Agent Crawford, there are just
some things you're not allowed to do
in a state-certified operating room.
You didn't take any trophies
when you murdered your wife
and her family on Thanksgiving.
- You put none on display. Why not?
- Crime of passion.
You know how stressful
the holidays can get.
Anyway, you didn't come here to talk
about my wife or the little nursey.
Oh? What am I here to talk about?
Your trainee.
Miriam... somebody.
You're telling me
you killed Miriam Lass.
Yes.
Didn't mean to kill her.
Now don't get mad at me.
I'm not mad at you.
I know where you are.
I know how you got here. I read your file.
I'm curious, why are you being
so forthcoming all of a sudden?
Well, what have I got to lose?
You know where I am
and you know how I got here.
- Why didn't you put her on display?
- What makes you think I didn't?
(Phone rings)
Excuse me.
The polite thing to do
is to ask them to call back.
Unless it's not an option.
You're home early.
Bella? Something wrong?
'Jack, it's Miriam.
'I don't know where I am,
I can't see anything.
'I was so wrong. I was so wrong.
'Please, Jack,
I don't wanna die like this.'
In my house. In my bedroom.
Where my wife sleeps.
I've dusted the phone.
Got a lot of usable prints.
Nice detail too.
I got three distinct beauties here.
Yours, your wife's, and presumably
The Chesapeake Ripper.
I can't imagine the Chesapeake
Ripper would start leaving prints
at his crime scenes now.
The Ripper put his head
on your wife's pillow.
- Now somebody's sleeping in my bed.
- There he is.
Or there she is.
- Was Miriam Lass a blonde?
- Yes.
I pulled her fingerprints from the Vicap
database, Jack, and I got a match.
She's dead. She wasn't here.
Jack. Did Miriam Lass
know where you live?
If she wanted to know,
she was smart enough to find out.
She could've told the Chesapeake
Ripper before he killed her.
Did you know
you were sending her after him?
I sent her after information.
Whoever made that call thinks
you were close to Miriam Lass
and feel responsible for her death.
Don't you have classes today?
Aren't you still in school?
Yes, sir. I thought this might be
more important
than "Exclusionary Rules
of Search and Seizure".
Is that what you thought?
I left a report here for you last night.
I don't know if you got it.
- I got it.
- Did you read it?
Go back to class.
You feeling frustrated, Lass?
If so,
you should start forming calluses,
some thick ones, cos frustration's
gonna wear you thin.
- You could've at least read the report.
- I read it.
Your assessment? Sir.
My assessment is that instead of being
here, you should be in a lecture hall
boning up on
"good faith warrant exceptions".
What you're proposing in your report
breaks confidentiality laws.
You know that.
You shouldn't be so dismissive
of what you're learning here.
If the Chesapeake Ripper is a surgeon,
we should check medical records
for all the known victims.
I knew we couldn't get a warrant
if we didn't have something substantial.
It's one thing for a trainee
to go poking around
in private medical records
without a warrant.
Very different if the guru did it.
Better for a trainee to ask for forgiveness
than an FBI agent to ask for permission?
In my experience.
Then I hope you forgive me
for skipping class today.
If someone were using
manipulative methods
to subvert your sense of control,
you may not realise it
until those methods
are pointed out to you.
Which may be
a manipulative method in itself.
You were a model patient.
You behaved yourself for two years.
Well, no opportunity to be naughty.
You could have been pushed.
Well, that would be unethical.
I can help you find out.
But I need your trust to do that.
Oh, I trust you, Dr Bloom.
To the Chesapeake Ripper.
Dr Gideon is going to provide us
with a singular opportunity
to analyse a pure sociopath.
It is so rare to find one in captivity.
Ah. Dinner is served.
Inspired by Auguste Escoffier,
we are having
langue d'agneau en papillotte,
served with a sauce of duxelles and
oyster mushrooms, picked myself.
I don't think I've ever had tongue before.
It was a particularly chatty lamb.
(Bloom) It smells delicious.
The Romans used to kill flamingos
just to eat their tongues.
Don't give me ideas.
Your tongue is very feisty.
And as this evening has already proven,
it's nice to have an old friend for dinner.
- I see three possibilities.
- Mm-hm.
Gideon is the Chesapeake Ripper.
Or he just thinks he is.
Or he knows he isn't.
He is, he knows he is, so do I.
Did you discuss the Chesapeake
Ripper's crimes with Dr Gideon
before he murdered the night nurse?
Mm-hm. When I began to suspect
what he was.
Fearing he might be exposed may
have, er... spurred him into action.
Is it possible
you inadvertently planted
the suggestion in Gideon's mind
that he was the Ripper?
You're not suggesting
coercive persuasion?
No, I said inadvertently.
Psychic driving is unethical.
But reasonable
in certain circumstances.
What circumstances?
It may have been useful trying to remind
Gideon he's the Chesapeake Ripper,
if he repressed those memories.
But he seems to have come
to that awareness all by himself.
Dr Bloom, if he has been
unethically manipulated somehow,
I need to know,
and I would love your insight.
Dr Chilton, would you care
to assist me with dessert?
A pleasure.
I love Norton grapes.
Same colour inside as outside.
Peel it...
and the flesh is also purple.
Not like other grapes where flesh is white
and colour comes from the skin.
A grape with nothing to hide.
Were I in your position,
I would have attempted psychic driving.
Perhaps you already have.
I promise...
I am much more forgiving
of the unorthodox than Dr Bloom.
Shall we?
(Phone rings)
'Jack? Jack, it's Miriam.'
The last call was made to Jack's cell
from a disposable phone traced here.
Or within 100 feet of here.
- What was Miriam Lass looking into?
- Medical records.
If the Ripper was a surgeon, she thought
he might've treated one of his victims.
- Have they retraced her steps?
- The ones they could find.
She made a jump somewhere
they couldn't explain.
- You make those jumps.
- The evidence has to be there.
Every surgeon that came into contact
with any of the Ripper victims
has been thoroughly vetted
or currently under observation.
- Including Dr Gideon?
- Dr Gideon wasn't in my bedroom.
The Chesapeake Ripper was.
The last call left something
the others didn't.
A phone number.
(Phone rings)
(Ringing continues)
What would be the benefit of making
you believe your trainee was alive?
Hope.
The Ripper wanted
to cloud my vision with hope.
It can sometimes be brave
to allow yourself hope.
Not the false kind.
Don't give up hope for your wife.
Not yet.
She's lost hope,
which means you can't.
- I don't have any control over that.
- Take control.
I'm sorry about your wife, Jack.
I truly am.
I believe the world is
a better place with her in it.
And I am sorry about your trainee.
Whatever the Ripper was doing,
it worked.
I thought she was alive.
For a moment, anyway.
I actually let myself believe something
that I knew was impossible.
Talk to me about her.
What was her name?
'My name is Miriam Lass.
I'm with the FBI.'
I'd show you my credentials,
but I'm just a trainee.
Never just a trainee.
An agent in training.
Please come in.
I was hoping to talk to you
about a former patient.
Not necessarily one of yours,
but someone you may have
come into contact with
when you were a practising physician.
I haven't practiced medicine
for some time,
but fortunately for you,
I have a very good memory.
Please.
His name was Jeremy Olmstead.
Perhaps not so good a memory after all.
I don't recall a patient with that name,
but it sounds familiar.
He was recently found murdered
in his workshop.
We think he may be a victim
of the Chesapeake Ripper.
That's why he sounds familiar.
It was all over the news.
He had two old scars on his thigh.
Pathology checked
with the local hospital.
He'd fallen out of a tree blind
five years ago while bow hunting,
stuck an arrow through his leg.
The doctor of record
was a resident surgeon,
but you were on duty
in the ER that night.
- I was?
- Your name was on the admissions log.
Let me think.
You'll have to forgive me,
I saw so many people in the ER,
but not so many hunters.
It's been a long time
since the accident,
but I thought you may remember if
anything was fishy with the arrow wound.
If it's the gentleman I'm thinking of,
I remember a fellow hunter bringing him in,
but I recall very little else.
I figured it was a long shot.
I did keep detailed journals
during those days.
If you like, I can get them for you.
Maybe you'll find something helpful.
That would be great.
If you don't mind.
Not at all.
If you'll wait here, I'll be right back.
Thank you.
She was a very brave young woman.