Let me out of here!
Somebody, please!
Let me out!
Your son.
We know you've been in contact with him.
- You have to let me-
- When...
and how did you make contact with him?
- What?
- Hmm?
Six.
What?
Six people have been taken this week.
This... thing that took your son...
we don't really understand it.
But its behavior is predictable.
Like all animals...
it eats.
It will take more sons.
More daughters.
I want to save them.
I want to save your son.
But I can't do that.
Not without your help.
Stop.
I know who you are.
I know what you've done.
You took my boy away from me!
You left him in that place to die!
You faked his death!
We had a funeral.
We buried him.
And now you're asking for my help?
Go to hell.
Okay, now what do you know?
I'm sorry.
Did I stutter?
I told you.
Everything.
What do you know?
I know you do experiments
on kidnapped little kids,
whose parents' brains
you've turned to mush.
And I know you went
a little too far this time
and you messed up in a big way.
I mean, you really messed up,
didn't you? Big time.
That's why you're trying
to cover your tracks.
You killed Benny Hammond,
you faked Will Byers' death.
You made it look like
that little girl just ran away.
See, I told you.
- I know everything.
- All right, who are you working with?
Nobody.
But I did give all this
over to my friend at the Times.
He's gonna blow this thing wide open.
You're just a junkie.
A small town cop
who had a really bad week.
Took one too many pills this time.
You made a mistake coming back here.
No, I didn't.
Here's what's gonna happen.
You're gonna let me and Joyce Byers go...
you're gonna give us anything we need,
and we're gonna find her son.
And then we're gonna forget
that any of this ever happened.
Oh, is that right?
Yeah.
That's right.
Nancy? Jonathan?
- They're gone.
- What?
Nancy and Jonathan.
His car's gone.
They're probably
just sucking face somewhere.
- Gross.
- No. No way!
Did they go with the chief?
I don't know.
No.
What? Did you see them?
Do you know where they went?
- Yes.
- Where? Where did they go?
Demogorgon.
Where's the girl?
You gotta give me your word.
Nobody's ever gonna find out about this.
And those other three kids, those boys,
you're gonna leave them alone.
Then I'll tell you.
Tell you where
your little science experiment is.
I don't understand.
We came to an agreement.
What?
Look, everything that's happened here
and everything that's gonna happen,
we don't talk about.
You want Will back?
This place had nothing to do with it.
That's the deal.
You got it?
What is this?
Protection.
The atmosphere is toxic.
But my son's in there. He...
Put it on.
I'm telling you,
this is a mistake.
It's gone.
Isn't that what you wanted?
And if they find the boy?
That's not gonna happen.
Hey, you all right?
Yeah.
I need you to relax, okay?
I want you to slow down your breathing,
take deep breaths.
In and out.
Deep breath in...
and out.
In and out.
- In and out.
- It's troll's favorite food!
- Princess!
- No, Daddy! No, Daddy!
- Roasted princess with paprika and gravy!
- No! No, Daddy. No, Daddy.
Whoa, hey!
Hey.
You all right?
- What's going on?
- Whoa.
- What happened? What happened?
- I don't know. I don't know.
Hey, you all right?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Relax, relax. Honey, honey.
Honey, just breathe.
Breathe, breathe, breathe.
In and out.
Slow, slow, slow.
In and out with me.
In...
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Remember...
- Straight into Will's room. And-
- Don't step on the trap.
Wait for the yo-yo to move.
Then...
All right.
You ready?
Ready.
On three.
One...
two...
You don't have to do this-
Jonathan, stop talking.
- I'm just saying, you don't have to-
- Three.
Guys, guys! This is crazy.
We can't just wait around.
Mike, in case you forgot,
we're still fugitives.
The bad men are still looking for us.
Yeah, and we don't even know
where your sister is.
El can find them.
Mike, look at her.
I still think we should stick
to the chief's plan.
Exactly. We stay here,
keep El out of sight and keep her safe.
That's the most important thing, remember?
Besides, she's okay.
She's with Jonathan.
Yeah, and she's kind of
a badass now, so...
Well, where are you going?
You just said stick to the plan!
I am. I'm just gonna go get
some chocolate pudding.
I'm telling you,
Lunch Lady Phyllis hoards that shit.
Are you serious?
El needs to be recharged!
Did you hear that?
It's just the wind.
Don't worry.
My mom, she said the lights speak
when it comes.
Speak?
Blink.
Think of them as alarms.
Is that too tight?
No, it's fine.
Thanks.
Nancy?
Yeah?
Jonathan?
Are you there, man?
It's... it's Steve!
Listen, I just want to talk!
- Steve, listen to me.
- Hey. Nancy, what-
- You need to leave.
- I'm not trying to start anything, okay?
I don't care about that.
You need to leave.
No, no, no.
Listen, I messed up, okay?
I messed... I messed up.
Okay?
Really. Please.
I just want to make things right.
Okay? Please. Please...
Hey, what happened to your hand?
Is that blood?
Nothing.
It was an accident.
- Yeah, what's going on?
- Nothing.
- Wait a sec. Did he do this to you?
- No.
- Nancy, let me in!
- No. No! No, Steve!
- What is... What the...
- You need to get out of here.
- Whoa. What is all-
- Listen to me. I'm not asking you,
- I'm telling you, get out of here!
- What is that smell?
- Is that... is that gasoline?
- Steve, get out!
Wait.
What? What is going on?
You have five seconds
to get out of here.
Okay, is this a joke?
Stop. Put the gun down.
- I'm doing this for you.
- Nancy.
- Wait. Is this a... What is this?
- Three. Two.
- No, no, no! No, no!
Nancy! The lights.
- It's here.
- Wait, what's here?
- Where is it?
- Where is what? Whoa!
- Easy with that!
- Where is it?
I don't know.
I don't see it.
Where is what?
Hello? Will someone please explain to me
what the hell is going-
No!
Go! Go! Run! Go!
Get out of here!
Jump!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Jesus! Jesus! What the hell was that?
- What the hell was that?
- Shut up!
What's it doing?
I don't know.
Do you hear anything?
No.
Will!
"I asked Mrs. Spencer what made
them red and she said she didn't know
and for pity's sake
not to ask her any more questions.
She said I must have asked her
a thousand already.
I suppose I had, too,
but how are you gonna find things out
if you don't ask questions?
And what does make roads red?
'Well, I don't know,' said Matthew.
It just makes me feel glad to be alive...
it's such an interesting world. "
Will!
This is crazy. This is crazy.
This is crazy.
This is crazy! This is crazy!
This is crazy!
What are you do-
What are you doing? Are you insane?
It's going to come back!
So you need to leave.
Right now.
Where is it?
Come on.
Come on, you son of a bitch.
- You see it?
- No. Where-
Come on.
Where are you?
Come on!
Jonathan!
Go to hell, you son of a bitch!
Steve!
He's in the trap!
- He's stuck!
- Jonathan, now!
Did you hear that?
Get back!
Where did it go?
No.
It has to be dead.
It has to be.
Come on.
Is that my house?
It was hurt.
Mom.
Is that you?
Jonathan?
Joyce, come on.
Where's it going?
I don't think that's the monster.
Found it!
I knew she was hoarding it.
- I knew it.
- Yeah.
Always lying, saying she's out.
Bald-faced liar.
Mike, I found the chocolate pudding!
Okay!
Are you feeling any better?
What's "putting"?
Pudding, it's...
it's this chocolate goo
you eat with a spoon.
Don't worry,
when all this is over,
you won't have to keep eating junk food
and leftovers like a dog anymore.
My mom,
she's a pretty awesome cook.
She can make you whatever you like.
Eggos?
Well, yeah, Eggos, but real food, too.
See, I was thinking,
once all this is over and Will's back
and you're not a secret anymore,
my parents can get you
an actual bed for the basement.
Or you can take my room if you want,
since I'm down there
all the time anyways.
My point is, they'll take care of you.
They'll be like your new parents,
and Nancy,
she'll be like your new sister.
Will you be like my brother?
What? No, no.
Why "no"?
Because...
'cause it's different.
Why?
I mean, I don't know,
I guess it's not.
It's stupid.
Mike?
Yeah?
Friends don't lie.
Well...
I was thinking...
I don't know...
maybe we can go
to the Snow Ball together.
- "Snow Ball"?
- It's this cheesy school dance,
where you go in the gym
and dance to music and stuff.
I've never been, but I know you're not
supposed to go with your sister.
- No?
- I mean...
you can, but it'd be really weird.
You go to school dances
with someone that, you know...
someone that you like.
- A friend?
- Not a friend.
Uh... uh...
Uh, someone like a...
Nancy.
Hold on, I'll be right back.
Stay here.
Go!
You two, on me.
This will charge your battery right up,
I'm telling you.
- Guys! Guys!
- What is it?
They found us.
We know they're here.
Be advised,
west side of the building is clear.
Sir, we've searched everywhere.
There's no sign of them.
Nothin'.
Keep it locked down.
All right.
Kitchen.
How did they find us?
I don't know,
but they knew we were in the gym.
Lando.
Got 'em!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Come on!
- There they are. Freeze.
- Back! Go back!
Go, go! Go left!
El, are you okay?
El!
- Something's wrong.
- She's just drained.
No, no, no,
she won't wake up. El!
El!
There's more blood.
Oh, my God.
This way.
- She's barely breathing.
- We gotta go.
Leave her.
- Step away from the child.
- No!
You want her,
you have to kill us first.
- That's right!
- Eat shit!
- Oh, no! No, no!
- No! No! Get off me!
- You idiot!
- No!
Get off me!
Ow! Let go!
Eleven?
Eleven, can you hear me?
Papa?
Yes, yes, it's your papa.
Get off of me.
I'm here now.
Let her go!
Let her go, you bastard!
Shh, shh, you're sick.
You're sick,
but I'm going to make you better.
I'm going to take you back home,
where I can make you well again.
Where we can make all of this better,
so no one else gets hurt.
Bad.
Mike. Mike.
Mike.
Blood.
What?
Demogorgon.
Go, go, go, go, go!
Come on, come on.
Go, go!
Oh, my God.
Will! Will!
Will! Oh, my God!
Will! Hopper!
Oh, my God!
You need to help get him out!
Get him out!
Oh, Jesus.
Come on, come on!
Oh, my God!
Sorry. Hold on, we're almost there.
We're almost there.
Come on.
Help, help.
Come on, get her on the table.
Just hold on a little longer,
okay?
He's gone.
The bad man's gone.
We'll be home soon, and my mom...
she'll get you your own bed.
You can eat as many Eggos as you want.
And we can go to the Snow Ball.
Promise?
Promise.
Is... Is it dead?
Go, go, go, go!
Get the wrist rocket!
Get the wrist rocket now!
Go, go, go, go, go!
- Go, go, go.
- Take it out now!
Get the rocks, get the rocks,
get the rocks!
Getting the rocks!
- Give me one.
- Come on!
- Go! Go! Kill it! Kill it!
- Fire! Fire!
- Give me another one.
- Kill it! Bastard!
Kill it! Go, go, go, go!
Kill it now!
Get, get, get...
Come on, kill the bastard!
It's not working!
- Hit him again.
- Kill him!
- Keep going! Come on!
- Get, get, get...
- Come on, kill it!
- Come on! Go, go, go!
Eleven, stop!
Goodbye, Mike.
No more.
El? El?
- El!
- Eleven!
Eleven!
El!
El, where are you?
Eleven!
El?
Oh, God.
He's not breathing,
he's not breathing.
All right, Joyce, Joyce, listen to me,
listen to me, listen to me.
- I need you to tilt his head back...
- Okay.
- ... and lift his chin.
One, two, three, four.
Now when I tell you,
you're gonna pinch his nostrils,
and breathe into his mouth...
- twice.
- Okay.
One second...
then pause.
22, 23.
- Then one second.
- Okay.
24, 25, 26, 27, 28...
29, 30.
Now! Go!
- Oh, come on, come on.
- Come on...
Come on, kid.
- Come on, kid!
- Will!
Will, listen to me.
It's me, it's your mom
and I love you so much.
I love you so much.
I love you more
than anything in the world.
Please...
Blood pressure keeps dropping.
Her pulse ox is falling.
I love you so much. I love you more
than anything in the world.
Please,
please come back to me. Just...
- Come on, kid!
- Please, please wake up.
Please, please.
Breathe, Will, come on!
Flatlining!
Come back to me, breathe.
I need you to wake up now.
I need you to breathe.
Please breathe!
Please!
That's it.
Oh, my God, that's it, that's it.
That's it, baby. Breathe.
Breathe. All right. Come on.
Come on.
Breathe, breathe, come on, come on.
Good, good, good, good.
Just breathe, Will, breathe.
Michael?
Michael!
Oh, my God.
You're okay.
Hey.
- Hi, sweetheart.
- Hey.
Where... where am I?
You're home.
You're home now.
You're safe.
Jonathan.
Yeah, it's me, buddy.
We missed you.
We really missed you.
Are you okay?
What, this?
It's just a cut.
It's nothing.
You're worried about my hand.
Oh, hey, uh...
We, uh...
We brought you some stuff...
so you don't get bored in here.
So...
Uh, I made you a new mix tape.
There's some stuff on there
I think you really might like.
Guys. Guys, he's up.
Will is up. Guys, Will's up.
Guys, come on.
Byers!
Be careful.
Be careful with him.
Move.
Guys, guys.
Go easy on him.
You won't believe what happened
when you were gone, man.
- It was mental.
- You had a funeral.
- Jennifer Hayes was crying.
- And Troy peed himself.
- What?
- In front of the whole school!
Yes!
You okay?
It got me.
The Demogorgon.
We know.
It's okay.
It's dead.
We made a new friend.
She stopped it.
She saved us.
But she's gone now.
- Her name's Eleven.
- Like the number?
Well, we call her "El" for short.
She's basically a wizard.
She has superpowers.
More like a Yoda.
She flipped a van with her mind,
and these agents
were trying to shoot us-
- Yeah, it flipped over us-
- Then she squeezed the brains out...
And blood was pouring out
of their faces.
It was pouring out of their eyes.
Agents just started
grabbing us and stuff...
...shot out of the wall...
Something is coming.
Something angry.
Hungry for your blood.
It is almost here.
- What is it?
- It's the thessalhydra, I'm telling you.
It's not the thessalhydra.
I'm telling you, it's the thessalhydra.
The thessalhydra!
- Damn it.
- It roars in anger!
- Will, your action!
- What should I do? I-
Fireball him!
Fireball the son of a bitch.
Fourteen!
Direct hit. Will the Wise's fireball
hits the thessalhydra.
It makes a painful...
and then... it crumbles to the ground.
Its clawed hand reaches for you
one last time
and, and, and...
and...
Lucas cuts off its seven heads,
and Dustin places them
into his bag of holding.
You carry the heads out of the dungeon,
victorious,
and you present them to King Tristan.
He thanks you
for your bravery and service.
Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
that's not it, is it?
No, there's a medal ceremony-
Oh, a medal ceremony?
What are you talking about?
- And-
- The campaign was way too short.
- Yeah!
- It was ten hours!
But it doesn't make any sense.
- It makes sense.
- Uh, no, what about the lost knight?
And the proud princess?
And those weird flowers in the cave?
I don't know, it's-
Jeez, what's that smell?
Have you guys been playing games all day,
or just farting?
Oh, that's just Dustin.
He farted.
- Dustin farted.
- Okay.
- Very mature, Lucas.
Oh.
- Will.
- Shut up.
Come on.
Dustin farted!
Bye, guys.
Bye, Will.
See you, Will.
- Stop.
- No, you stop.
No, you stop.
Yeah, scream!
You're like a little girl.
- So, you have fun?
- Yeah.
Hey, boys.
- Hey, Mrs. Wheeler.
- Hi.
Hey, wish your mom
a merry Christmas for me, okay?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, thank you. Uh, merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas.
- So, uh, you win?
- Yeah.
- Awesome.
- Hey, Jonathan, wait up.
- Uh...
- Merry Christmas.
Thanks, um...
I... I didn't get you anything.
- I... I feel bad.
- No.
No, it's, uh, it's not really a present.
It's, um... Well, you'll see.
Merry Christmas.
- You ready? Let's go.
- Yeah.
All right. Buckle up.
Can I open it?
Yeah, sure.
Whoa.
Pretty cool.
Yeah.
Yeah, pretty cool.
Did you give it to him?
Yeah.
You leaving already, Chief?
Oh, come on, you think I actually wanted
to come to this thing? I was just hungry.
Oh, yeah, that's the spirit.
Well, your wife doesn't have time
to cook for me, you know what I'm saying?
Merry Christmas, Hop.
Mmm.
What you got there?
That one of yours?
- Yeah.
- Looks pretty big.
Be careful.
You'll break it.
What are you...
What are you doing?
Documenting.
Oh, why?
Because...
- It looks great.
- Oh, this is just so overcooked.
- And look, the potatoes are runny.
- Mom.
- They're so runny.
- Mom, it's gonna be great.
- It's definitely an Atari.
- An a-what-i?
The green present.
It's an Atari.
I felt Dustin's today,
it's the same exact weight.
- Really? Well...
- Yeah.
We'll have to see, won't we?
Hey, no more snooping.
No, I forgot to wash my hands.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
He's washing his hands?
Thanks.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Mmm. Very good, Mom.
Mmm. Hey, Mom.
Did Will tell you about, uh, the game?
- Oh, yeah.
- No. What game?
I threw a fireball at him and...
dead.
Wait, what is...
You mean, this is...
No, it's just Dungeons & Dragons.
- Dungeons & Dragons. Right.
- It's fun.