Hello?
Nancy?
Nancy!
Hello?
Oh, my God...
Nancy!
Hey, what's the matter?
Nothing.
You're so beautiful.
Nancy!
Steve?
- Hey, Steve.
- Mmm.
I'll...
see you tomorrow, okay?
Mmm-hmm.
Oh! Jesus, you scared me.
Oh, I scared you?
I know, I should have called.
Where have you been?
We agreed on 10:00.
After the assembly, some people
wanted to get something to eat.
I didn't think it'd be a big deal.
You didn't think to call and let me know?
With everything that's been going on?
I didn't realize how late it was, okay?
I'm sorry, Mom.
What more do you want?
Hey, wait...
Whose sweatshirt is that?
Steve's.
So is Steve your boyfriend now?
What?
No!
It was just cold,
so I borrowed his sweatshirt.
It's not a big deal.
Nancy?
What?
You can talk to me.
Whatever happened.
Nothing happened.
Nancy.
Can I please go?
Will? Will?
Sweetheart, can you hear me?
Will...
Please...
It's me.
It's me. Just talk to me.
Talk to me.
Just say...
- Mom?
- Jonathan!
- Come here. Come here.
- Mom, what is this?
Come here. Come here.
- What's going on?
- It's Will. It's Will, he's...
he's trying to talk to me.
- He's trying to talk to you?
- Yes, through... through the lights.
- Mom-
- I know.
I know.
Just... just watch.
Will... your brother's here.
Can you show him what you showed me, baby?
Please...
Did you see that?
It's the electricity, Mom.
- It's acting up.
- No.
It's the same thing that fried the phone.
No! It is not the electricity, Jonathan.
Something is going on here!
- Yesterday, the wall-
- What? What about the wall?
- I don't know. I don't know.
- Mom, first the lights, then the wall?
I just know that Will is here.
No, Mom.
- Maybe if I get more lamps-
- No, Mom.
You don't need more lamps.
You need to stop this, okay?
He is just lost.
People are looking for him,
and they're going to find him.
Okay.
- This isn't helping.
- Okay, okay.
Okay, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Can you do me a favor, Mom?
Can you just try and get some sleep?
- Yeah.
- Huh? Can you do that for me?
- I promise. I will.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- I just need to sit here for a minute.
All right, I'll go make breakfast.
- Okay.
- Yeah?
Will?
We just tell our parents
we have AV Club after school.
That'll give us at least a few hours
for Operation Mirkwood.
You seriously think that
the weirdo knows where Will is?
- Just trust me on this, okay?
- Okay.
- Did you get the supplies?
- Yeah.
Binoculars... from 'Nam.
Army knife... also from 'Nam.
Hammer, camouflage bandana...
and the wrist rocket.
You're gonna take out the Demogorgon
with a slingshot?
First of all, it's a wrist rocket.
And second of all,
the Demogorgon's not real.
It's made up.
But if there is something out there,
I'm gonna shoot it in the eye...
- and blind it.
- Dustin, what did you get?
Well, alrighty.
So, we've got...
Nutty Bars, Bazooka, Pez, Smarties,
Pringles, Nilla Wafers, apple,
- banana, and trail mix.
- Seriously?
We need energy for our travels.
For stamina.
And besides, why do we
even need weapons anyway?
- We have her.
- She shut one door!
With her mind!
Are you kidding me?
That's insane!
Imagine all the other cool stuff
she could do.
Like...
I bet... that she could make this fly!
Hey. Hey.
Okay, concentrate.
Okay?
Okay, one more time.
Okay.
Use your powers, okay?
Idiot.
- She's not a dog!
- Boys!
Time for school!
Just stay down here.
Don't make any noise,
and don't leave.
If you get hungry,
eat Dustin's snacks, okay?
- Michael!
- Coming!
You know those power lines?
- Power lines?
- Yeah.
The ones behind my house?
Yes.
Meet us there, after school.
After school?
Yeah, 3:15.
Ah.
When the numbers read three-one-five,
meet us there.
"Three-one-five. "
Three-one-five.
Hey!
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah!
Yeah, totally.
I just...
I feel like everyone's... staring at me.
Oh, I didn't... I didn't tell anyone.
I know.
Of course not.
But what about, like, Tommy,
and Carol and them?
You're being paranoid.
- I'm sorry.
- No. No, it's cute.
Hey...
I had a good time.
Yeah.
Me, too.
Mmm.
Hmm.
Hey, Ally.
Where's Barb?
Um, shouldn't you know?
You haven't seen her anywhere...
at all?
There she is.
Emerald City.
I heard they make
space weapons in there.
Space weapons?
Yeah. You know, like,
Reagan's Star Wars.
I guess we're gonna blow
the Ruskies to smithereens.
Hey, can I help you?
Uh, yeah.
We're here for a tour.
Oh, we don't give tours.
Okay...
A quick look around.
You have to get clearance for that.
You can contact, uh...
Rick Schaeffer
at the Department of Energy.
Maybe you seen it on TV.
We got a local kid that's missing.
We have reason to believe
he might have snuck in here.
Like I said,
you have to speak to Mr. Schaeffer.
- What's your name?
- Patrick.
Patrick, I got a panicked mayor,
and I got reporters breathing down my neck
and I got a very upset mother.
Now, I know the kid's not in there,
but I gotta check off this box.
Patrick, would you do me a favor?
Would you speak to your boss
and see what you can swing for us?
I'd really appreciate it.
I'm talking ten minutes, tops.
...was occupying a large part of Lebanon.
Today, Syria has become a home for-
I have the power!
...gift that will last forever.
From the Harmony Treasures' collection-
♪ On the beach and in the sun ♪
♪ The real thing is so much fun ♪
♪ All the times of your life
And the things that you do ♪
♪ Coke is right there with you ♪
♪ Coke is it! Coke is it! ♪
- Joyce-
- Just ring me up, Donald.
And you think this missing boy
may have crawled through there?
Well, that was the idea.
Yeah, I just don't see
how that'd be possible.
We've got over 100 cameras.
Every square inch covered,
plus all my guys.
No one breaks in here.
Certainly not some kid.
Those cameras, you keep the tapes?
If you don't mind me asking,
what do you guys do in here?
You're asking the wrong guy.
- Staying one step ahead of the Russians?
- I expect. Something like that.
- Who's in charge here?
- That'd be Dr. Brenner.
And he builds the space lasers?
- Space lasers?
- Ignore him.
This is the night of the 6th and 7th
we're seeing here?
That's correct.
Is that it?
Like I said, we would have seen him.
The night of the 7th,
we had a search party out for Will.
You remember anything about that night?
Mmm, not much to remember.
Called it off.
- 'Cause of the storm.
- Yeah, a lot of rain that night.
You see any rain on that tape?
What are you thinking?
I don't know.
But they're lying.
That's why science doesn't
make any damn sense to me.
No, I swear. Look at this.
It's totally frostbite.
Oh, thanks, man.
It's a heated pool.
Well, if it's not frostbite,
then what is it?
Ugh, I don't care what it is,
it's disgusting!
Get it off the table.
We're eating here.
Ew!
Hey, Tommy.
When you left, did you see Barb?
- What?
- Barbara.
She's not here today.
I seriously have no idea
who you're talking about.
Come on, don't be an ass, man.
Did you...
Did you see her leave last night or not?
No, she was gone when we left.
Probably couldn't stand
listening to all that moaning.
Oh, Steve!
- Oh, Steve! Oh, Steve!
- Oh, Steve...
Oh, Steve!
Okay, chill.
Listen... I'm sure she's fine.
She's probably just...
she's probably just, like,
skipping or something.
Yeah.
Yeah, probably.
- How about this one?
- Too big for the sling.
So, do you think Eleven was born
with her powers, like the X-Men,
or do you think she acquired them, like...
like Green Lantern?
She's not a superhero.
She's a weirdo.
Why does that matter?
The X-Men are weirdos.
If you love her so much,
why don't you marry her?
What are you talking about?
- Mike, seriously?
- What?
You look at her all, like...
"Hi, El! El! El! El!
I love you so much!
- Would you marry me?"
- Shut up, Lucas.
Yeah, shut up, Lucas.
What are you losers
doing back here?
Probably looking for their missing friend.
That's not funny.
It's serious. He's in danger.
I hate to break it to you, Toothless,
but he's not in danger.
He's dead.
That's what my dad says.
He said he was probably killed
by some other queer.
Come on.
Just ignore them.
Watch where you're going, Frogface.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Hey.
How about this one?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Yeah, this is it.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, this is the monster killer!
Whoo!
Hey.
Oh, hey.
- Hey!
- Hey, Karen.
Hi...
I brought you a casserole.
Oh! Thank you, uh...
Uh, you wanna... come in?
Hey, Marissa.
How you doin'?
You have a lot of nerve showing up here.
What?
You could have at least called, said,
"Marissa! Hey, it's not gonna work out.
Sorry I wasted your time. I'm a dick. "
Yep.
I'm sorry. Uh...
Maybe we could go out again next week?
Newspapers?
You guys got newspapers around here?
We have the New York Times,
the Post, all the big ones.
Organized by year and topic.
You can find the corresponding microfiche
in the reading room.
Okay, we're looking for anything
on the Hawkins National Laboratory.
Well, shouldn't you be looking
for that missing kid?
Yeah. We are.
Uh, so, why don't you start
with the Times,
and we'll check out the Post.
The librarian?
Will always loved
Christmas, you know.
So I thought if I...
I put the lights up...
I don't know, he...
I'd feel like he was home somehow.
It's silly, I know.
No.
No, it's not silly.
How is Jonathan holding up?
You know,
he's good at taking care of himself.
He always has been, you know?
I...
I mean,
he thinks I'm losing my mind, but...
Is something the matter?
Uh, no.
No, I just...
We're having electrical problems.
Joyce.
I want you to know something.
If you need anything, anything at all...
Ted and I are here for you.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Okay.
How... how's Mike
dealing with this?
Is he, uh, okay?
Mike?
Uh... I don't know.
He skipped school yesterday.
He's never done anything like that before.
Let me throw in that casserole, okay?
Oh, where's Holly?
Hey!
She shouldn't be here.
Oh, I'm sorry.
She's quite the explorer these days.
- Wait, did you see something?
- Yeah.
What did... what did you see?
Tell me.
- What did you see? What-
- Joyce... Joyce!
Listen... Karen,
thank you for the casserole,
but I need you to leave.
Okay?
Come on, come on, come on...
- Hello?
- Hi.
Hi, uh, Ms. Holland, it's Nancy.
Oh, Nancy, how are you?
Good.
I'm good.
Um, I was just wondering, uh,
is Barb there?
Mmm... No, she hasn't come home yet.
But she did come home, right?
After the vigil?
No, she said she was staying
with you last night.
Right, yes.
She did, sorry.
I meant, did she come home this morning?
I think she left some textbooks
and she was gonna go pick them up.
Oh, um, no, I haven't seen her.
Do- Do you know what?
I just remembered... she's at the library.
Nancy, will you please have her call me
as soon as you find her?
Yeah.
Yeah, I will.
Sorry to bother you.
Hey, man.
What's going on?
Nicole here was, uh,
telling us about your work.
We've heard great things.
Yeah, sounds cool.
And we'd just love to take a look.
You know, as... connoisseurs of art.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Oh, no? Oh...
Hey.
Please, give me my bag.
No, just...
Man, he is totally trembling.
He must really have something to hide.
Here we go.
Ah...
- Oh, man.
- Let me see.
Dude.
Yeah, this isn't creepy at all.
- I was looking for my brother.
- No.
No, this is called stalking.
Mmm-hmm.
- What's going on?
- Here's the starring lady.
What?
This creep was spying on us last night.
He was probably gonna
save this one for later.
See, you can tell
that he knows it was wrong, but...
Man, that's the thing about perverts...
It's hardwired into 'em.
You know, they just can't help themselves.
So...
we'll just have to take away his toy.
- Steve...
- No, please, not the camera.
No, no, wait, wait...
Tommy, Tommy.
It's okay.
Here you go, man.
Come on, let's go.
The game's about to start.
Boo.
Bye.
Hey, Nance!
Come on.
Three-one-five.
No! No!
Papa! Papa!
Papa!
No!
Incredible.
El!
You okay?
Hop on.
We only have a few hours.
So, I told Mr. Mundy...
"The solution of ten plus Y equals...
blow me. "
Bull, if you did that,
you'd be in detention right now.
Saturday.
I bet Mr. Mundy's still a virgin.
Oh, he's so a virgin!
Maybe you should blow him, Carol.
Help your grades a bit.
Whoa, Nance, where you going?
I totally forgot.
I told my mom I would, um...
I would do something with her.
Well, what do you mean?
The game's about to start.
I'm sorry.
What the hell's wrong with her?
Maybe she freaked out
when you went all psycho on the psycho.
Oh, give me a break.
What'd you expect,
dating Miss Perfect?
Why did they hurt you?
What?
Oh, that.
Uh...
I just fell at recess.
- Mike...
- Yeah?
Friends tell the truth.
I was tripped by this mouth breather,
Troy, okay?
Mouth breather?
Yeah, you know...
a dumb person.
A knucklehead.
Knucklehead?
I don't know why I just didn't tell you.
Everyone at school knows.
I just didn't want you to think
I was such a wastoid, you know?
- Mike...
- Yeah?
I understand.
Oh.
Okay, cool.
Cool.
Barb?
Barb!
Oh!
Will... are you here?
Okay, good, good, good, good.
Are you...
Um, blink once for yes, twice for no.
Can you do that for me,
sweetie?
Can you do...
Oh, good boy.
Good boy.
Baby, I need to know...
Are you alive?
Are you safe?
I need to know where to find you, honey.
Where... where are you?
Can you...
can you tell me where you are?
Please, baby.
I need to find you. Tell me what to do.
Please just...
Will...
Hey! You're home early!
How was the game?
Nancy?
What's the matter?
It's Barb.
I think...
something happened.
Something terrible.
I don't know, Chief.
What don't you know?
This lady, Terry Ives,
sounds like a real nut to me.
Her kid was taken
for LSD mind control experiments?
She's been discredited.
Claim was thrown out-
Okay, forget about her.
Take a look at this.
- Dr. Martin Brenner.
- Who?
Brenner.
He runs Hawkins Lab.
Okay.
You don't find that interesting?
Not really.
He was involved in some hippie crap
back in the day, so what?
No, this isn't hippie crap.
This is CIA-sanctioned research.
Doesn't mean he had
anything to do with our kid.
Come on. Look at that.
Hospital gowns. All of 'em.
Now, that piece of fabric
that the teacher found by the pipe.
That sure looked
like a hospital gown to me, huh?
- Am I wrong?
- I don't know, Chief.
Come on, man.
Work with me here.
I'm not saying that there's
some grand conspiracy.
I'm just...
I'm saying maybe something happened.
Maybe Will was in the wrong place
at the wrong time
and he saw something
that he shouldn't have.
- It's a reach.
- It's a start.
Hey, Powell,
is the chief with you?
Hopper here.
What do you got?
Here.
Yeah, this is where Will lives.
Hiding.
No, no, this is where he lives.
He's missing from here.
Understand?
- What are we doing here?
- She said he's hiding here.
Um... no!
I swear, if we walked
all the way out here for nothing-
That's exactly what we did.
I told you she didn't know
what the hell she was talking about!
Why did you bring us here?
- Mike, don't waste your time with her.
- What do you want to do then?
Call the cops,
like we should have done yesterday.
- We are not calling the cops!
- Hey, guys?
- What other choice do we have?
- Guys!
Will...
Okay.
Okay, baby, talk to me.
Talk to me.
Where are you?
"R." Good, good, good, good.
That's good.
Come on, come on.
"I...
G...
H... T...
H...
E...
R... E... "
"Right here. "
"Right here"?
I don't know what that means.
I need you to tell me what to do.
What should I do?
How do I get to you? How do I find you?
Oh, Jesus.
Oh, God.
Please tell me it's not the kid.
It's not Will.
It can't be.
It's Will.
It's really Will.
Mike...
"Mike"? "Mike," what?
You were supposed to help us
find him alive.
You said he was alive!
Why did you lie to us?
What's wrong with you?
What is wrong with you?
- Mike...
- What?
Mike, come on.
Don't do this, man.
Mike...
Mike, where are you going?
Mike!
Mom?
Mom, what happened?
It's okay.
Hey.
Michael?
What's wrong?