Something is coming.
Something hungry for blood.
A shadow grows on the wall behind you,
swallowing you in darkness.
- It is almost here.
- What is it?
What if it's the Demogorgon?
Oh, Jesus, we're so screwed
if it's the Demogorgon.
It's not the Demogorgon.
An army of troglodytes
charge into the chamber!
- Troglodytes?
- Told ya.
Wait a minute.
Did you hear that?
That... that sound?
Boom... boom...
- Boom!
That didn't come from the troglodytes.
No, that...
That came from something else.
- The Demogorgon!
- We're in deep shit.
- Will, your action!
- I don't know!
- Fireball him!
I'd have to roll a 13 or higher!
Too risky.
Cast a protection spell.
- Don't be a pussy. Fireball him!
- Cast Protection.
The Demogorgon is tired
of your silly human bickering!
It stomps towards you.
- Boom!
- Fireball him!
- Another stomp, boom!
- Cast Protection.
- He roars in anger!
- Fireball!
- Oh, shit!
- Where'd it go?
Where is it?
I don't know!
- Is it a 13?
- I don't know!
Where is it?
Oh, my God!
Mike!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Can you find it yet?
No, I can't find it!
- Mike!
- Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Mom, we're in the middle of a campaign!
You mean the end?
Fifteen after.
Oh, my God! Freaking idiot!
Why do we have to go?
- Mom, wait, just 20 more minutes!
- It's a school night, Michael.
I just put Holly to bed.
You can finish next weekend.
- But that'll ruin the flow!
- Michael-
I'm serious, Mom.
The campaign took two weeks to plan.
How was I supposed to know
it was gonna take ten hours?
You've been playing for ten hours?
- Dad, don't you think that 20 more-
- I think you should listen to your mother.
- Dang dumb piece of junk.
Oh, I got it!
- Does the seven count?
- It was a seven?
Did Mike see it?
Then it doesn't count.
Yo, hey, guys.
- Does anyone want this?
- No.
Yeah.
No, I don't think...
Yeah, he's cute.
Barb, no, I don't think so.
- Barb, you're not-
- Hey, Nancy.
There's a slice left if you want it.
- Sausage and pepperoni!
- Hold on.
- There's something wrong with your sister.
- What are you talking about?
- She's got a stick up her butt.
- Yeah.
It's because she's been dating
that douchebag, Steve Harrington.
Yeah,
she's turning into a real jerk.
She's always been a real jerk.
Nuh-uh, she used to be cool.
Like that time she dressed up as an elf
for our Elder tree campaign.
Four years ago!
Just saying.
Later.
- It was a seven.
- Huh?
The roll, it was a seven.
The Demogorgon, it got me.
See you tomorrow.
Good night, ladies.
Kiss your mom 'night for me.
Race you back to my place?
Winner gets a comic.
- Any comic?
- Yeah.
Hey! Hey!
I didn't say "go"!
Get back here!
I'm gonna kill you!
I'll take your X-Men 134!
Son of a bitch.
Mom?
- Jonathan? Mom?
- Hello? Hello?
And that's it
for News Center this morning.
Thanks for joining us.
Let's hand off now to Liz
at the news desk.
All right, thank you, Donna.
Turning now to local news,
we're getting reports of surges
and power outages all across the county.
Last night, hundreds of homes
in East Hawkins were affected,
leaving many residents in the dark.
The cause of the outage is still unknown.
We reached out to Roane County
Water and Electric,
and a spokesperson says
that they are confident
power will be restored
to all remaining homes
within the next several hours.
Mmm.
In other news,
you might wanna stay home tonight
or at least pack an umbrella.
We turn to everybody's favorite
morning weather guy, Charles.
Where the hell are they?
- Jonathan?
- Check the couch!
Ugh, I did.
Oh... Got them.
Okay, sweetie, I will see you tonight.
- Yeah, see you later.
- Where's Will?
Oh, I didn't get him up yet.
- He's probably still sleeping.
- Jonathan, you have to make sure he's up!
- Mom, I'm making breakfast.
I told you this a thousand times.
Will! Come on, honey.
It's time to get up.
- He came home last night, right?
- He's not in his room?
- Did he come home or not?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
- No.
I got home late.
I was working.
You were working?
Eric asked if I could cover.
I said yeah.
I just thought we could use
the extra cash.
- Jonathan, we've talked about this.
- I know, I know.
You can't take shifts when I'm working.
Mom, it's not a big deal.
Look, he was at the Wheelers' all day.
- I'm sure he just stayed over.
- I can't believe you.
I can't believe you sometimes.
- That's disgusting.
- You're disgusting!
- Hello?
Hi, Karen.
It's Joyce.
- Oh, Joyce, hi.
- What the hell, Mike?
- Hey!
- Quiet!
- Language.
- Are you kidding?
Was that Will I heard back there?
Will?
No, no, no, it's just Mike.
Will didn't spend the night?
No, he left here
a little bit after 8:00.
Why? He's not home?
Um, you know what? I think
he just left early for... for school.
- Thank you so much. Bye.
- Okay. Bye.
That's weird.
I don't see him.
I'm telling you, his mom's right.
He probably just
went to class early again.
Yeah, he's always paranoid
Gursky's gonna give him another pop quiz.
Step right up, ladies and gentlemen.
Step right up and get your tickets
for the freak show.
Who do you think would make more money
in a freak show?
Midnight, Frogface, or Toothless?
I'd go with Toothless.
I told you a million times,
my teeth are coming in.
It's called cleidocranial dysplasia.
"I told you a million times. "
- Do the arm thing.
Do it, freak!
God, it gets me every time.
- Assholes.
- I think it's kinda cool.
It's like you have superpowers
or something.
Like Mr. Fantastic.
Yeah,
except I can't fight evil with it.
So, did he call?
Keep your voice down.
Did he?
I told you, it's not like that.
Okay, I mean, yes, he likes me,
but not like that.
We just...
made out a couple times.
"We just... made out a couple times. "
Nance, seriously,
you're gonna be so cool now,
it's ridiculous.
No, I'm not.
You better still hang out with me,
that's all I'm saying.
If you become friends with Tommy H.
or Carol-
Oh, that's gross!
Okay,
I'm telling you, it was a one-time...
- Two-time thing.
You were saying?
- Steve...
- Mmm-hmm?
- I have to go.
- In a minute.
Steve.
I really, like...
Seriously, I have to go.
Wait, wait, wait.
Let's...
Come on, let's do something tonight, yeah?
Uh... No, I can't.
I have to study for Kaminsky's test.
Oh, come on.
What's your GPA again? 3.999...
Kaminsky's tests are impossible.
- Well, then, just let me help.
- You failed chem.
- C-minus.
- Well, in that case...
So I'll be over around, say, like, 8:00?
- Are you crazy? My mom would not-
- I'll climb through your window.
She won't even know I'm there.
I'm stealthy, like a ninja.
You are crazy.
Wait, wait, wait. Just...
Okay, forget about that.
We can just...
We can just, like, chill in my car.
We can find
a nice quiet place to park, and...
Steve... I have to study.
I'm not kidding.
Well, why do you think
I want it to be nice and quiet?
You're an idiot, Steve Harrington.
Meet me at Dearborn and Maple at 8:00.
To study.
Good of you to show.
Oh, hey, morning, Flo.
Morning, everybody.
- Hey, Chief.
- Damn! You look like hell, Chief.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
Well, I looked better than your wife
when I left her this morning.
While you were drinking or sleeping,
or whatever it is you deemed
so necessary on Monday morning,
Phil Larson called.
Said some kids are stealing
the gnomes out of his garden again.
Oh, those garden gnomes again.
Well, I'll tell you what,
I'm gonna get right on that.
On a more pressing matter,
Joyce Byers can't find her son
this morning.
Mmm.
Okay, I'm gonna get on that.
- Just give me a minute.
- Joyce is very upset.
Well, Flo, Flo, we've discussed this.
Mornings are for coffee and contemplation.
- Chief, she's already in your-
- Coffee and contemplation, Flo!
I have been waiting here
over an hour, Hopper.
And I apologize again.
I'm going out of my mind!
Look, boy his age,
he's probably just playing hookie, okay?
No, not my Will.
He's not like that.
- He wouldn't do that.
- Well, you never know.
I mean, my mom thought
I was on the debate team,
when really I was just screwing
Chrissy Carpenter
in the back of my dad's Oldsmobile, so...
Look, he's not like you, Hopper.
He's not like me.
He's not like... most.
He has a couple of friends,
but, you know, the kids, they're mean.
They make fun of him.
They call him names.
- They laugh at him, his clothes-
- His clothes?
- What's wrong with his clothes?
- I don't know.
- Does that matter?
- Maybe.
Look, he's...
He's a sensitive kid.
Lonnie...
Lonnie used to say he was queer.
Called him a fag.
- Is he?
- He's missing is what he is.
When was the last time
you heard from Lonnie?
Uh, last I heard, he was in Indianapolis.
That was about a year ago.
- But he has nothing to do with this.
- Why don't you give me his number?
You know, Hopper,
he has nothing to do with this. Trust me.
Joyce, 99 out of 100 times,
kid goes missing,
the kid is with a parent or relative.
What about the other time?
- What?
- You said, "99 out of 100."
- What about the other time, the one?
- Joyce.
The one!
- Joyce, this is Hawkins, okay?
You wanna know the worst thing
that's ever happened here
in the four years I've been working here?
Do you wanna know the worst thing?
It was when an owl attacked
Eleanor Gillespie's head
because it thought
that her hair was a nest.
Okay, fine.
I will call Lonnie.
He will talk to me before he talks to-
- What, a pig?
- A cop!
Just find my son, Hop.
Find him!
Dr. Brenner.
This way, gentlemen.
The entire east wing
will be evacuated within the hour.
We've sealed off this area
following quarantine protocol.
This is where it came from?
Yes.
And the girl?
She can't have gone far.
All right, and one more.
Hey, Ben.
What do you think about that, uh...
Hey, I don't know.
I don't know.
I don't know,
37 points per game average-
Thirty-seven now, but...
Mr. Basket.
Hey!
Come here!
Hey, come here!
You think you can steal from me, boy?
What in the hell?
- Remember, finish chapter 12
and answer 12.3 on the difference
between an experiment
and other forms of science investigation.
This will be on the test,
which will cover chapters 10 through 12.
It will be multiple choice
with an essay section.
So, did it come?
Sorry, boys.
I hate to be the bearer of bad news,
but...
it came.
Yes!
The Heathkit ham shack.
Whoa.
Ain't she a beaut?
I bet you can talk to New York
on this thing.
Think bigger.
- California?
- Bigger.
Australia?
- Oh, man!
When Will sees this,
he's totally gonna blow his shit.
Lucas!
- Sorry.
Hello, this is Mike Wheeler,
president of Hawkins Middle AV Club.
What are you doing?
Hello, this is Dustin,
and this is the secretary and treasurer
of Hawkins Middle AV Club.
Do you eat kangaroos for breakfast?
Sorry to interrupt, but, uh, may I borrow
Michael, Lucas and Dustin?
Okay, okay, okay.
One at a time, all right?
You.
- You said he takes what?
- Mirkwood.
- Mirkwood?
- Yeah.
- Have you ever heard of Mirkwood?
- I have not. That sounds made up to me.
No, it's from Lord of the Rings.
- Well, The Hobbit.
- It doesn't matter.
- He asked!
- "He asked!"
- Shut up, guys!
- Hey, hey, hey!
- What'd I just say?
- Shut up.
One at a damn time.
You.
Mirkwood, it's a real road.
It's just the name that's made up.
It's where Cornwallis and Kerley meet.
- Yeah, all right, I think I know that-
- We can show you, if you want.
I said that I know it!
- We can help look.
- Yeah.
- No.
No.
After school, you are all to go home.
Immediately.
That means no biking around looking
for your friend, no investigating,
no nonsense.
This isn't some Lord of the Rings book.
- The Hobbit.
- Shut up!
- Hey!
- Stop it!
Do I make myself clear?
Do I make myself... clear?
Yes, sir.
Yeah.
Ring-a-ding-ding!
Anybody home?
Password?
Uh, Rada...
Radaga- Radagast?
Yeah. You may enter.
Thank you, sir.
So, guess what?
I got off early and...
Ta-da!
Poltergeist.
I... I thought I wasn't allowed to see it.
I changed my mind.
As long as you don't have nightmares
for a week.
No, I won't.
I don't get scared like that anymore.
Oh, yeah?
Not even of clowns?
No.
What about my witch?
- No. Mom...
- Ooh...
- I'm not five anymore.
- But Will Byers...
- I'm going to cook you up in my-
- Stop. That's so stupid. Mom!
Will?
- Will?
- Will!
Will!
Where are you?
Geez.
Your parents forget to feed you?
Is that why you ran away?
They, uh...
They hurt you?
You went to the hospital, you got scared,
you ran off, you wound up here,
is that it?
All right.
I'll give this back, all right?
And you can have as much as you want.
All right?
Maybe even some ice cream.
But you gotta answer
a few of my questions first, all right?
We got a deal?
All right, let's start
with the easy stuff. All right?
My name's Benny.
Benny Hammond.
See? Like this. Here.
I got you.
Don't worry. It's okay.
Nice to meet you, yeah.
And you are?
Eleven?
What's that mean?
What's it mean?
- No.
- Well, I'll be damned.
She speaks.
"No"? No, what?
All right.
I guess no more food, then.
Eleven.
Yeah.
What's it mean?
Eleven.
All right, then.
Here you go.
Take it easy, take it easy.
Yeah, look, all I know
is that she's scared to death.
Yeah, I think
maybe she's been abused or...
kidnapped or something.
Yeah, it'd be great
if someone would come by.
Yeah, we're at 4819 Randolph Lane.
Yeah, Randolph.
Will Byers?
Will!
Come on, kid!
Will?
- Hey! I got something.
- That his bike?
- Yeah, he must have crashed.
You think
he got hurt in the fall?
Not so hurt he couldn't walk away.
Bike like this is like
a Cadillac to these kids.
He would've walked it home.
...get off work if I win.
Oh, Friday I'm supposed to...
...but we will cover
whatever the damages are to your property.
- It's just, um...
- That's for sure.
Is Lonnie there?
Lonnie isn't here right now.
Can you please-
- I told you, Lonnie's not here.
- Who is this?
- His girlfriend, Cynthia.
- Cynthia.
- Who the hell is this?
- Cynthia, this is Joyce.
- Who?
- Lonnie's ex-wife.
- I really need to speak to him-
- Lonnie's not here.
- Can you please put- No!
- Why don't you call back later?
No, not later. Now!
- Can-
- Bitch!
- Mom.
- What?
- You have to stay calm.
Hey, you've reached Lonnie.
Leave a message
and I'll holler right back at ya.
Lonnie, some teenager just hung up on me.
Will is... is missing.
I don't know where he is.
I need...
I just need you to call me back,
please, just-
- Damn it! Damn it!
- Mom?
What?
Cops.
- It was just lying there?
- Yeah. Cal?
- Did it have any blood on it, or-
- No, no, no, no, no...
Phil?
If you found the bike out there,
why are you here?
- Well, he had a key to the house, right?
- Yeah.
So...
maybe he came home.
You think I didn't check
my own house?
I'm not saying that.
- Has this always been here?
- What? I don't know.
Probably. I mean, I have two boys.
Look at this place.
You're not sure?
Hey.
Hey, what's up with this guy, huh?
Nothing, he's probably just hungry.
Come on.
- Hey!
- Jesus!
What are you, deaf?
I've been calling you.
- What's going on?
Hello?
- Are you sure you're okay, Chief?
- Listen, I want you to call Flo.
I want to get
a search party together, all right?
All the volunteers she can muster.
Bring flashlights, too.
Hey, you think
we got a problem here?
We should be out there right now.
We should be helping look for him.
We've been over this, Mike.
The chief says-
- I don't care what the chief said.
- Michael!
We have to do something.
Will can be in danger.
More reason to stay put.
- Mom!
- End of discussion.
So... me and Barbara are gonna
study at her house tonight.
- That's cool, right?
- No, not cool.
What? Why not?
Why do you think?
Am I speaking Chinese in this house?
Until we know Will is okay, no one leaves.
- This is such bullshit.
- Language.
So we're under house arrest?
Just because Mike's friend got lost
on the way home from...
- Wait, this is Will's fault?
- Nancy, take that back.
- No!
- You're just pissed off
'cause you wanna hang out with Steve.
- Steve?
- Who is Steve?
- Her new boyfriend.
- You are such a douchebag, Mike!
- Language!
Nancy, come back.
Come back!
It's okay. It's okay, Holly.
Here, have some juice, okay?
You see, Michael?
- You see what happens?
- What happens when what?
I'm the only one acting normal here!
I'm the only one that cares about Will!
That is really unfair, son.
We care.
- Mike!
- Let him go.
I hope you're enjoying your chicken, Ted.
What did I do?
Hey! What'd I do?
Will!
Will Byers!
Will, we're here for you, bud!
He's a good student.
- What?
- Will. He's a good student.
Great one, actually.
I don't think we've met.
Scott Clarke.
Teacher, Hawkins Middle.
Earth and biology.
I always had
a distaste for science.
Well, maybe you had
a bad teacher.
Yeah, Ms. Ratliff
was a piece of work.
Ratliff?
You bet.
She's still kicking around,
believe it or not.
Oh, I believe it.
Mummies never die, so they tell me.
Sarah, my daughter...
Galaxies, the universe, whatnot...
She always understood all that stuff.
I always figured there was enough
going on down here,
I never needed to look elsewhere.
Your daughter,
what grade is she?
- Maybe I'll get her in my class.
- No, she, uh...
She lives with her mom in the city.
Thanks for coming out, Teach.
We really appreciate it.
- She died a few years back.
- Sorry?
His kid.
Lucas, do you copy?
It's Mike.
- Lucas?
- Hey, it's Lucas.
I know it's you.
And say "over" when you're done talking
so I know when you're done. Over.
I'm done. Over.
I'm worried about Will. Over.
Yeah.
This is crazy. Over.
I was thinking...
Will could've cast Protection last night,
but he didn't.
He cast Fireball.
- Over.
- What's your point? Over.
My point is... he could've played it safe,
but he didn't.
He put himself in danger
to help the party.
Over.
Meet me in ten.
Over and out.
What are you doing here?
I told you on the phone,
I'm under house arrest now.
- I figured we'd just study here.
- No. No way.
Oh, come on.
I can't have you failing this test.
So just... bear with me.
What'd I tell you?
Ninja.
You like that ice cream, huh?
Smile looks good on you.
You know, smile?
All right.
You just sit tight.
Whoever it is, I'll tell 'em to go away
real quick, all right?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah...
- Hey, can I help you?
- Hi, you must be Benny Hammond.
I'm afraid I am. I'm afraid
we're closed for the evening, too.
- So try back tomorrow morning.
- Connie Frazier. Social Services.
Ah, Social Services. My apologies.
I didn't expect you so soon.
- That's a heck of a drive.
- Not too bad this time of night.
Hey, listen, I...
I haven't told her that you're coming yet.
I didn't want her running off again.
She's a tad skittish.
- Children I work with usually are.
- Right, right.
- So, where is she?
- Right. She's in the kitchen.
- Come on up. I'll introduce you.
- Thank you.
Sorry again for trying
to turn you away there.
- It's fine.
- You know, it's funny.
- Your, uh, voice sounds different on the-
Ah, man.
This is it.
Hey, guys.
You feel that?
- I think maybe we should go back.
- No.
We're not going back.
Just stay close.
Come on.
Just stay on channel six.
Don't do anything stupid.
Hey, guys, wait up.
Wait up!
"Which polymers occur naturally?"
Starch and cellulose.
Mmm.
"In a molecule of CH4,
the hydrogen atoms are spatially oriented
- towards the centers of-"
- Tetrahedrons.
Wow.
Jesus, how many of these did you make?
You said you wanted to help.
How about this? How about...
How about every time
that you get something right,
I have to take off
an item of clothing.
But every time
that you get something wrong-
- Uh, pass.
- Oh, come on.
- Come on.
- No.
- Come on. It'll be fun.
"During fractional distillation,
hydrocarbons are separated
according to their-"
Melting point.
Ooh, it's boiling points.
That's what I meant.
Yeah, that's not what you said.
- No.
- No?
Oh, do you need...
Do you need help, or...
No.
Steve.
Steve, come on.
What?
Are you crazy?
My parents are here.
That's weird, I... don't see them.
Was this your plan all along?
To... to get in my room and then...
- get another notch on your belt.
- No. Nancy, no.
I'm not Laurie, or Amy, or Becky.
You mean, you're not a slut.
That's not what I'm saying.
You know, you're so cute when you lie.
Shut up.
Bad Steve.
Bad.
Don't do that to Miss Nancy...
You're an idiot, Steve Harrington.
You are beautiful, Nancy Wheeler.
"Compared to the rate
of inorganic reactions,
the rate of organic reactions
is generally... "
Jonathan, wow.
You took these?
These are great.
Wow, they really are.
I know I haven't been there for you.
I've been...
working so hard and I...
I just feel bad.
I don't even...
barely know what's going on with you.
All right?
I am sorry about that.
Hey, what is it?
What is it, honey?
- Nothing.
- Tell me. Tell me.
- Come on. You can...
- No.
It's just...
I should've been there for him.
No. Oh, no.
You can't do that to yourself.
This was not your fault.
Do you hear me?
He is... close.
I know it. I...
I feel it in my heart.
You just have to...
You have to trust me on this, okay?
- Yeah.
- Oh, look at this.
Look at this one.
- I mean, that's it, right?
- Yeah.
That's it.
That's the one.
- Hello?
Lonnie?
- Dad?
- Hopper?
- Who is this?
Will?
- Will?
- It's Will?
- Mom, it's Will?
- Who is this?
- What have you done to my boy?
- What? What?
Give me back my son!
- Hello?
Hello, who is this?
- Hello? Who is this?
- Mom, who was it? Who was it, Mom?
- It was him.
- Look at me, Mom. Was it Will?
- Yes.
- What did he say?
He just breathed.
- And was someone else there?
- I...
- Mom, who was there? Who was it?
- It was him.
I know it was his breathing.
- Will!
- Byers!
I've got your X-Men 134!
Guys, I really think
we should turn back.
Seriously, Dustin?
You wanna be a baby,
then go home already!
I'm just being realistic, Lucas!
No, you're just being a big sissy!
Did you ever think Will went
missing because he ran into something bad?
And we're going to the exact same spot
where he was last seen?
- And we have no weapons or anything?
- Dustin, shut up.
I'm just saying,
does that seem smart to you?
- Shut up. Shut up.
Did you guys hear that?