I gave up.
After the four miscarriages, we tried IVF.
40 grand for three eggs.
We joked about
how we were gonna end up with triplets
and whether we should
make their names rhyme.
But none of them stuck.
Not the names, the eggs.
And that was that.
I gave up. No baby for me.
And then five years went by and we finally
stopped bullshitting about adoption,
and then it just...
Happened.
I was pregnant.
And he was...
Perfect.
His name is Sam.
Six months later,
I walk into the laundromat
and I strap him into his car seat.
And he was crying, so I didn't kiss him.
I knew that once the car was moving,
he'd calm down.
And then he was gone.
So, I sit in the parking lot
and wait all day,
because he could come back, right?
They could all come back.
And if they did, it'd be on the exact spot
where they disappeared from.
So, my son, who doesn't even know
how to crawl, I mean...
He didn't. It's been two years.
Maybe he's older now?
But he could just reappear
in a fucking parking lot.
And if I'm not there, if I'm not there
when he comes back, what happens?
Do you think he even remembers me?
I should stop.
That's what my husband said.
I need to give up, right?
Right?
Are you gonna say something?
You know there are two of those bitches
in white standing out front right now,
smoking their fucking cigarettes?
They probably think your patients
are easy pickings.
If I asked them to tell me what to do,
they'd at least write it down for me.
Is that what I should do?
Tell me what to fucking do.
I don't know.
Tell me what to do.
Hey, Pop.
Hey, Lorelei.
What you got there?
Shoes.
That's one hell of a shiner.
You should see the other guy.
I take it your husband told you
we were here.
Which husband?
I heard you were with
the good Reverend Jamison.
He coming, too?
No.
He gave me something for you, though.
He says he's sorry
he didn't put you in his fucking book.
Who torched it?
Your son.
Is he here?
He was.
Right now,
he's off having himself a think.
A think about what?
We asked him to die.
Again.
Whatever is happening here,
I wanna be a part of it.
- What happened?
- Dog bit me.
Yeah, I'm fine. Just a little rabies.
-Is it them?
-You tell me.
Oh !
Dr. Bekker and Dr. Eden.
Yeah, that's them.
-Told you it was the right house.
-They don't look like physicists to me.
What are physicists supposed to look like?
I don't know. Shouldn't they be wearing
lab coats or something?
So now what?
Now? Now we wait.
So, I wake up, and my leg is killing me.
I got a tube in my arm,
another one up my dick,
Christopher Sunday is dead,
and I don't know where I am
or how the fuck I got there.
And by there, I mean here.
So, I am discom-fucking-bobulated.
I'm lost. I'm in fucking agony.
I am in so much pain,
I can't fucking see straight.
So I got my hands
on some of the dog's pain pills.
I popped them and soon realized
they were a bit more powerful
than the human variety.
So, I passed out hard,
and when I wake up, I go outside,
and that is the first time
I lay eyes upon this young lady.
And she was drowning the police officer?
Mm-hmm.
Whose name is Kevin.
Correct.
It was a horrible mistake,
and I will be taking responsibility
for what I've done.
I'm not sure she understands.
I understand.
You want to drown Kevin
so that he can go to this place
where the dead people are.
And while he's there, he's going to learn
a song from one of the dead people
and he's gonna bring that song back to you
so you can sing it and stop the biblical
flood that's gonna happen tomorrow.
That about covers it.
And you've...
You've told all this to Kevin
and he's actually considering it.
Yeah.
He got one of Grace's horses, headed out,
said he'd be back by sundown.
And you think that Evie...
That she's in this place, too?
Why wouldn't she be?
Well, so everybody wants something.
A brain, a heart, courage.
Kevin's in the Emerald City.
He's the one that's gonna give it to you.
All right, Dorothy, let's have it.
Tell us we're lunatics.
Yeah, it sounds crazy, but...
These are crazy times, huh?
So, when Kevin comes back,
you're not gonna jam us up?
No.
I'm not gonna jam you up.
You don't think he's coming back.
Well, it's a lot to put on someone,
asking for all that help.
I mean, if it were me,
I would just keep riding.
Get as far from this as possible.
But Kevin, he'll come back.
He always does.
G'day. Miss Playford?
No, sir.
And who might you be?
My name is Maria Carmen Rodriguez.
Date of birth, 8-30-80.
This is a copy of
this morning's Las Noticias.
This was my choice and mine alone.
I indemnify all others.
I'm of sound mind and body,
and give consent to go...
To go wherever they went.
Amen.
So, the two women in that house,
they recorded this?
One would assume.
And we're also assuming
they're just gonna lead us right to this
device they told you about?
You don't have to stay, Laurie.
You can go help Kevin.
Kevin's still at the airport.
Last I checked,
all the flights were grounded.
Well, Michael and John will call me
if they need me.
I'm happy to keep helping here.
You already helped
by finding me the address.
Oh, come on.
You're not gonna let me see this
suicide machine for myself?
-It's not a suicide machine.
-It's not?
'Cause it sure seems like an incredibly
elegant way to kill yourself.
If I was gonna kill myself,
I'd just go scuba diving.
What?
There are lots of ways to die when
you're scuba diving.
Your oxygen tank can break.
You can get a bubble in your blood
that gives you a stroke.
I know. I'm certified.
And Laurie Murphy was certified.
She'd logged hundreds of hours
underwater, but accidents happen.
What a senseless tragedy.
And then Jill and Tom and John
are standing there at the funeral,
and they're protected.
They'll never know that you twisted
the knob the wrong direction
because you wanted to.
And just like that, you were gone.
Clean, quiet certainty.
Fully explained.
Now, that's fucking elegant.
Can I have a napkin, please?
Or if you're going for inelegant,
you could just do it like Matt here.
Know your cancer's back, tell no one,
get no treatment,
pray for divine fucking intervention.
- That's not fair.
- Yes, it is.
-I deserve that.
-You...
You don't wanna kill yourself.
I know suicidal when I see it.
You know suicidal when you see it?
Is that one of your psychic powers?
- I don't have psychic powers.
- Mm !
Oh, that's right. It's John who's psychic.
Come on. You know how it works.
I don't, actually,
'cause I never got a reading.
Why don't you do me?
What?
If I came to your house
and John took my handprint
and I sat down across from him
at the table
and I told him
that I wanted to talk to my kids,
what would you tell him to say to me
in his little earpiece?
- We don't do departures.
- Uh...
Do our parents. They're dead.
Okay.
Um...
Well, I'd start on the Internet.
Look at social media, pictures,
um, personal details.
Like, your parents, how did they die?
In a fire when we were kids.
I didn't know that.
No, fuck my parents.
I wanna talk to my kids.
I just told you, Nora.
We don't do departures.
You did departures when you and your pals
had life-size replicas
made of my family and then sat them down
at my kitchen table.
Come on.
Let me have it.
I can't, Nora. I'm sorry.
Why not?
Because we tried it and it doesn't work.
We had to stop after the third time
John was attacked.
Yeah.
Look, death is easy.
People just want finality,
an end to their grief.
But with departures, there is no end.
And if we indicated otherwise
by just saying we were able to communicate
with those individuals,
it made their loved ones very, very angry.
Because they didn't want closure.
I want fucking closure.
I know.
That's why we're here.
-He's gonna find that body.
-Well, let's hope he doesn't.
It's gonna be okay, sweetie.
Matt gave this to you? Is he okay?
Yeah, he's fine. He's still with Nora.
And where is Nora?
Uh, sorry. I can't disclose that.
You can't disclose it?
Look, when we all found Nora in the hotel,
you said you were going to the airport
to be with Kevin.
And he wasn't there.
So I called him
and he actually answered his phone.
He said he was here
and that we should come.
-So why didn't you tell me?
-Because you don't believe in this.
-Hey, just calm down.
-No.
She just shows up.
She won't even tell us
how she even knew we were here.
You wanna disclose
how you got that black eye?
I got it from Nora.
She hit you?
Thought you were supposed to
be helping her.
-I did help her.
-And now she's helping us, right?
That's right. That's right.
Hey!
You wanna give us a hand?
What are those?
Steroids.
You got any painkillers?
-Headache?
-Nah. My uterus hurts.
Before you got to the hotel, I went to
a clinic and got my IUD taken out.
And they said it might be a little sore.
Told me to take a couple ibuprofen.
Jesus.
So you're trying again.
What?
Nothing. I just thought you would...
Might be done after you gave Lily back
to her mother.
I am done.
Still smoking, huh?
No, I quit.
I haven't had a cigarette
since John and I got together.
You stopped for him?
No. I stopped for myself.
It's an incredibly self-destructive habit.
That's what makes it so cool.
My lighter?
Can I have it back, please?
You said you quit.
-I did.
-Then you don't need it.
Please give it back.
Like I did with Lily?
Give me the lighter, Nora.
Come on, Nora.
-She said she doesn't need it.
-Give it to me!
Hey! Get off! Shit!
- Get off!
Shit.
Oh, God. Shit. Are you okay?
-They're leaving.
-What?
They're leaving !
Fuck.
Go down.
What the fuck?
You steal this thing?
Said the man who just assaulted
an officer of the law.
Eh, he'll be fine. I had no choice.
His chief's in a tarp
under the goddamn church.
He was heading right for it.
Where are you gonna take him?
Far enough away from civilization
to give us time.
You're just gonna leave him?
Well, here's the good news.
If this thing with Kevin doesn't work,
who gives a shit?
Officer Koala Fart here is gonna drown
in the flood tomorrow
along with all the rest of us.
But if it does work, sweet Lorelei,
I will be honored to spend
my remaining days
locked away from the world I just saved.
It's getting late.
I should be getting dinner ready.
I'll be back before it's on the table.
Storm's coming.
What you drinking?
Just some coffee.
Want some?
Oh, Jesus, that's good.
Remember when we went to coffee
for the first time, just you and me?
Of course I do.
I was hurting.
You reached across the table,
took my hands, and looked at me,
and I felt like
I could've told you anything.
But what I couldn't tell you...
I thought my daughter
might still be alive.
Erika never doubted it.
She took it in and moved on.
But me, I just...
I just couldn't believe it.
I should've told you.
Well, if you had, I wouldn't have talked
you into helping people
talk to their dead relatives.
I thought I was helping you.
Should've taken the hint
when you shredded the money.
No, I shredded the money
because what we were doing wasn't real.
And this is.
Is it?
Do you want Kevin to ask Evie
why she left her family?
No.
I asked him to give her a message.
I want her to know that she was loved.
That's beautiful, John.
One of Grace's kids
was fostered out of a local tribe.
He loved boats.
When his family found out he died,
some of his cousins came down here
to leave a mark.
Grace told them to strip the church.
Took the wood from the church
to make a tombstone for the little boy.
A memorial.
Then that crazy old man got here
and became convinced
it was a part of his flood story.
I still believe him.
Because if I throw out his story,
that means I got to throw out mine, too.
Go ahead. Tell me I'm crazy.
Tell me we've gone too far.
Tell me, and we can go home right now
and forget all this.
Because I can still shred it.
I think you gotta see it through, John.
You're so close.
You're getting too close!
They're gonna see you !
Calm down. I know what I'm doing.
Is your eye okay?
Yeah, it's fine.
I wasn't trying to hit you.
C'est la vie.
Did you hear about the guy
on the French submarine?
- What?
- The one who fired the nuke.
Apparently, he thought
there was some big egg
in a volcano in the middle of the Pacific,
and he was convinced
that this giant seven-headed sea monster
was gonna hatch on the 14th
and eat us all.
He said he got the idea from Revelations.
That's ridiculous.
Revelations is not supposed to
be taken literally.
The seven-headed monster, it's a metaphor.
Oh... So it's only literal
when it's not ridiculous?
- That's right.
You would know.
So, let's say this guy comes
and sits on your couch
and he says, "Hey, Doc, I have access
to nuclear weapons
"and I need to destroy Godzilla."
What do you even say to someone like that?
"Don't miss."
Hello?
Laurie, hey. It's Michael.
Hi. Are you at the airport?
No. We're at...
It's a ranch outside of Melbourne.
You're at a ranch? What--
Kevin wasn't at the airport.
He was at this ranch. He's here right now.
His dad found him.
He's with his dad? Okay.
-Um... What--
-You've got to come now, Laurie.
- 5 Pigeon Run Road.
- Okay.
Outside Makarra.
5 Pigeon Run Road.
Is your dad there?
Just get here as soon as you can.
- Are you okay?
Hello?
What happened?
Kevin's at a ranch with his father.
That's good. Tomorrow's a big day.
We should all be with family.
There's not a friend like the lowly Jesus
No, not one
No one else could heal
Is this enough carrots?
That's plenty, love.
My husband, he used to do all the cooking.
I spent years trying to get the stew
to taste exactly like his.
I even got it right once.
Then I forgot what I did.
Well, it smells delicious.
Was he a good husband?
Kevin.
He was a great husband.
He saved me.
But you divorced him.
Yeah. Well, I joined a cult.
You know, it was just one of those things
they made you do.
Hmm.
I'm so sorry about your children.
Their shoes were missing.
Sorry?
When they found their bodies,
it was clear that they'd been walking
for quite some time,
but their shoes were missing.
They weren't here at the house,
they weren't with the kids.
I've covered the ground
in between a hundred times.
Looked through every pair donated
to charity inside 100 kilometers.
When Kevin talks to them,
he's gonna ask them
where they put their shoes.
I need to go set the table.
Mind giving it a stir?
Sure.
Not much of a last supper.
Well, you certainly
cleaned your plate for not liking it.
No, the food is scrumptious.
I'm just saying, not much of a last supper
without our Jesus.
I think I'm gonna go to lie down
for a bit.
Wake me when he comes back.
Truth is,
along with our missing fucking savior,
we also appear to be short some apostles.
Our friend Matthew, conspicuously absent.
Fortunately, I will play
the part of Peter.
You are already John.
What about you, kid?
You wanna be Simon, Bartholomew?
- Pass.
- Oh...
We all have to be somebody.
Somebody who was there
at Christ's last huzzah.
So that would make me Mary Magdalene.
Hmm.
That would be Nora.
Also conspicuously absent.
You, Dr. Garvey, are one apostle
and one apostle only.
Thomas.
Doubting Thomas.
Mmm.
When I first started hearing voices
back in Mapleton,
everyone around me told me
I was fucking nuts. Everyone.
Except you.
You were the one person who believed me.
You said those voices were really there.
The next thing I knew,
I was locked up
in a fucking mental institution.
So you're wrong, Pop.
I'm not Thomas.
I'm Judas.
Doubting is easy
because doubting costs you nothing.
But Judas,
he was surrounded by people going on
and on about how special Jesus was.
But he betrayed him anyway.
Because he was sure.
He believed in something.
And he acted on it.
And then he killed himself.
What, sweetie?
Judas collected his 30 pieces of silvers
and he hung himself.
You all right?
If he was so sure, why'd he kill himself?
Well, Michael, I was not aware
of that part of the story.
I have no idea why he killed himself.
Did he leave a note?
Hey.
Hey, are you...
Are you all right?
When?
He's fine.
He's just sleeping.
I'm sorry.
It's true...
I borrowed your pills.
Looks real.
Indeed, it does.
So, is this the part where you call
the DSD and shut this operation down?
Do you remember when we were kids,
after Mom and Dad died,
when everyone at the church
wouldn't take their eyes off us?
And they'd take us to the movies
and bowling and putt-putt
just to keep us busy?
Of course I do.
And this one time,
they brought us to a baseball game,
and I was too young
to get the rules, so I...
I watched these people in another section
hitting a beach ball.
And the whole stadium was getting into it.
And when the ball came over to our seats,
you stood up and you just whacked it.
It was the first time
I'd seen you smile in forever.
But then the ball went into the aisle
and this usher ran down and grabbed it
and he picked it up,
and he just squeezed the air out of it.
And then everyone started
booing.
Not just the people in our section,
but the whole stadium. Booing.
He just ruined it for all of them.
They just wanted to hit the ball.
Why would he wanna do that job?
Why would anyone?
Because if he doesn't,
that ball is gonna go onto the field,
and it'll be fucking chaos.
You can take the van.
I don't need it anymore.
You wanna drive or should I?
Actually, I think I'm gonna stay here
for a while.
People should be
with their families, right?
Okay.
Can you, uh, give this to Senior
and tell him I'm sorry
I didn't put him in my fucking book?
And tell Kevin I'm sorry I did.
Thank you.
Do you have to tell them I did this?
Give me a dollar.
- I only have 100s.
Give me, um...
Give me your cigarettes.
Congratulations, Nora Durst.
You are now officially my patient.
Same time next week?
You're on.
Hi.
Hey.
John called you?
Michael did.
They said you were with Nora.
I was.
You help her find
what she was looking for?
I think so.
Where's everybody?
Inside, sleeping.
I drugged their food.
Jesus, Laurie.
Well, I wanted to talk to you.
Just the two of us.
I didn't think they would let that happen.
You know what they want me to do?
You came here to talk me out of it?
No. I'm here to say goodbye.
Want a cigarette?
Yeah.
"Don't forget me."
Is this the lighter Jill gave you?
I threw it in a sewer grate
and then went back for it.
- Don't tell Jill that.
That's nothing.
I killed her hamster.
-You what?
-Yeah.
When you guys went down
to that mock UN thing,
didn't fucking feed it.
I went up there about an hour before
you got home and it was dead.
Took it to the neighbor's trash
and threw it in there.
Told you guys it ran away.
Well, rest in peace, Mr. Fuzzy.
Mr. Funny.
It was Mr. Funny.
That's right. It was Mr. fucking Funny.
Remember that psychosomatic medical
conference thing I went to in Phoenix?
I lasted two hours.
And then I went to a spa
that cost $2,000 a night.
I hated our house.
-Really?
-Mm-hmm.
I mean, I didn't say anything
because it was your money that bought it.
Well, you should've said something.
It was our house.
You loved it.
I wanted you to be happy.
I was pregnant.
What?
Sixteen weeks.
I don't, uh...
When?
Seven years ago tomorrow.
I was lying in the doctor's office,
staring at the ultrasound.
Looking right at it.
Then it was gone.
Why didn't you tell me?
I mean, we raised two beautiful kids.
It's the best thing we ever did.
The last best thing.
Did you want another baby?
No.
Me neither.
I didn't tell you
because I didn't want to. And then...
Then I didn't have to.
Are you scared?
Scared of what?
Scared of them strapping you to a seesaw
and holding you under the water
until you drown.
The last time it happened,
where I went, that was so...
It was real.
Maybe I was dead,
but I had never felt so alive.
But no, I'm not scared.
Then I'm not scared either.
And it could work, so I could come back.
I really hope you do.
Will you stay?
I can't.
Wait, wait, wait.
Forgot your lighter.
Uh, you can keep it. I quit.
Thanks.
Is Nora gone?
We're all gone.
Goodbye, Laurie.
Goodbye, Kevin.
Far out as I can take you
with that storm rolling in.
If you're gonna go, you best go now.
Okay.
Hi, honey.
Mom, thank God you answered.
I have a very important question.
- She doesn't know!
- Shut up! She's gonna remember.
Mom, do you remember that one time
when I was, like, five
and you found this videotape at a garage
sale and I was obsessed with it?
Tell her she's making this up, Mom!
It doesn't exist.
It does exist! I remember it.
It had a mannequin that had this hat
that made it come to life
and there was a goose on a rainbow
and this creepy guy puppet
that, like, worked at a department store.
Today's Special.
Today's Special ! Yes! Oh, my God.
Fucking Today's Special.
Eat it, you fucker. Fuck, yes.
- Yeah, yeah, okay.
- I knew you'd remember.
You know how many times
I had to listen to that theme song?
I'm really sorry I put you through that.
It was just a phase. I forgive you.
So, hey, Tommy said
Dad and Nora went to Australia?
I tried calling them. What's up with that?
Who knows?
What are you doing right now?
Where are you?
Oh...
I'm just hanging out.
By yourself? On the anniversary?
Yeah.
It's, uh, kind of nice, actually.
Okay.
Well, enjoy your solitude.
I love you, Mom.
I love you, honey.
Tell Tommy I love him.
Mom loves you, you fucking idiot.
I love you too, Mommy!
Bye, kids.
Bye. Love you.
Miss?
Now or never.
English-SDH