Final boarding call for flight 87...
You two together?
Yes, we are.
Australia, huh? Long trip.
Yes, it is. I have Global Entry.
Where's the pre-check line?
It is right over there, ma'am.
Leave your shoes on.
-No need to take your laptop out.
-Oh.
Is it all right if I go with her? Uh...
-I'm a cop, so--
-Do you have Global Entry?
-No.
-Then you can't go with her.
I'll just see you on the other side, okay?
-Sir?
-Yeah...
This way, please. Single file.
Arms up, please.
-Your watch.
-Oh, shit. Sorry.
Just walk on around. Come back through.
-Enjoy your flight.
-Thank you.
Come on. Hey, give it back.
You can't take it, no.
- Look, no, no. No, you can't take it.
- Sir.
- No, it's my suit.
- Is there a problem here, sir?
No, look,
it's not on the list of restricted items.
Okay, look, there's gonna be
a nuclear event,
and I'm entitled
to protect myself from fallout.
Okay? I'm missing my flight.
I need to get to Antarctica.
I need to get to Antarctica!
Another one bites the dust.
Hey.
Hi.
Everything go okay?
Yeah, absolutely.
-You?
-Great.
What are you smuggling?
Sorry?
You either didn't wanna wait
in line with me
for an extra five minutes,
or you're smuggling something.
So, what is it?
Heroin?
I have $20,000 in cash
strapped to my body.
-Lock the door.
-What are you doing?
I borrowed your duct tape.
They would've seen it
if I walked through the scanner. Sorry.
Why?
It's illegal to travel out of the country
with more than 10 grand.
Why didn't you just give me half?
Huh. Help me get the tape off?
Ooh.
You hiding anything else
you wanna tell me about?
Maybe.
- How many?
- A hundred and nineteen.
Jesus.
They made these testimonials.
They're standing there,
holding a newspaper
like a hostage video.
They, they gave their names,
so I looked them up
just to see if any of them
were still around
after they supposedly got into this thing.
The thing that zaps them
with the radiation?
Yes, honey, the thing
that zaps them with the radiation.
And were they?
-Still there?
-No.
Every single one of them
is unaccounted for.
-Where'd they go?
-Nowhere.
Well, I mean, they have to go somewhere.
- Not if they're being cremated.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the seat belt sign is now turned off,
and you are free to move about the cabin.
So it's a sting operation.
You give them the money.
They show you the thing.
You see that it torches people.
Then you bust them.
Right.
But you don't have any jurisdiction
in Australia.
That is technically true.
The DSD didn't send you.
So you've gone rogue?
The DSD has their hands full
with the coming apocalypse.
These assholes invited me personally,
so I can take them down myself.
They didn't know
you were a fraud investigator?
No, they knew.
They knew
pretty much everything, actually.
Well, then they know about me.
I'm sure they do.
And they still think
you're gonna get into this thing?
And what if they ask
why I came down here with you?
I'll say
that you've come to see me off
because we're
in a toxic codependent relationship,
and we've both come to realize
that we're better off
apart than together.
You gonna look your dad up?
-Look him up?
-Yeah.
I thought that's why you wanted
to come down here.
No, I came down here to be with you.
Yeah, but if he's close by--
Honey, I don't know where he is.
And if he wanted me to know,
he would've fucking told me.
Gotcha.
You brought your book.
It's not my book. It's Matt's.
-But it's about you.
-Uh-huh.
Are you finally gonna read it?
-I already did.
-Really? When?
On the plane when you were asleep.
The whole thing?
- The whole thing.
"And so He left the bridge
and the hangman behind.
"And when He went into the woods,
He lifted the girl to His shoulder,
"and she slept.
She pressed to Him and He to her..."
He capitalizes your H's.
"Now the sun rose,
and they had come to a well,
"and He placed the girl
down upon its edge and..."
What?
If you read the whole thing,
what happens next?
He pushed her in.
Jesus.
Where does Matt come up with this stuff?
--Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit!
Fuck. That's them.
- Yes?
- Is this Nora?
Yes, it is. Who's this?
There's a bus stop across the street
from the hotel.
The 570 will arrive in about 15 minutes.
Take it to the last stop. Don't miss it.
- We won't wait. Goodbye, Ms. Durst.
- What? I don't--
-That was them. I have to go.
-Where?
I don't know.
They want me to get on a bus.
-You want me to go with you?
-I'll be fine.
Are you gonna follow me, Kevin?
- Yeah.
Look, I have to do this alone, okay?
Okay.
Just take your nap. I'll be safe.
Dinner later?
Yeah, sure.
I'll be back soon.
God, motherfucker.
G'day, Melbourne!
It's a beautiful Tuesday,
and I'm Pam Jolly.
And I'm Bruce Quartermain.
Today is October 9th,
and I have to say I'm a bit groggy.
- Ooh, how was your night, Bruce?
- Oh, I had a big night last night.
Did you go to the party?
Well, I went to Melbourne's
Spring Fashion Ball last night.
Ooh. Tell us. Tell us.
Did you wear a costume?
Well, the theme this year
was under the sea...
Good morning. Front desk.
Yeah, I can't turn off my television.
I can't see where it's plugged in.
Yeah, so sorry about that.
It's powered from the wall.
Happens sometimes.
I can reset it from down here.
It'll just be a moment, Mr. Durst.
- It's Mr. Garvey.
- Oh, so sorry.
Uh, would you like us
to add your name to the room
so you can have access
to all the guest amenities?
Yes, that would be great. Thank you.
Well, I'm ashamed to say that I did, Pam,
but at least I get to be having pancakes
with you here this morning, right?
Do you like pancakes, Bruce?
Well, now, who doesn't like pancakes?
Well, no one in their right mind,
that's what I say,
which is why we are having
a pancake cook-off today
right here in the studio.
Now, how are you with a spatula?
You know, can you flip 'em?
- What kind of question is that?
- Well, it's tricky.
And I sure hope no one watching
is named Kevin.
Why is that, Pam?
Well, apparently, there's not one,
but two missing Kevins
in the Melbourne area.
Chief Inspector
Kevin Yarborough's police cruiser
was found abandoned
outside his home in Makara.
Meanwhile, this man, Kevin Garvey,
an American holidaying down under,
was last seen wandering the road
near Kurripa nearly a month ago.
If you have any information
on the whereabouts
of either of these men,
please contact the police.
Right, let's get to those pancakes.
Are you ready, Georgie?
Oh, yes, I am, Pam. Come on over.
Okay, now, tell us about the batter.
Well, we've actually got
three batters, George.
The, uh, the first one
is a plain buttermilk.
That's good.
Yeah, I like the classic pancake myself.
Because you're so boring.
Oh, that's not all true.
Uh, but the second one is banana.
Oh, yum. That's definitely for me.
And the third one, of course,
is a chocolate chip.
Oh, Bruce, you'll have...
- Can you hear me?
Fuck.
Good morning. Front desk.
Yeah, I need you to turn my television
back on right now.
Uh, sorry, Mr. Durst. I just reset it.
Just, uh, give it a few minutes.
G'Day Melbourne,
is that show live?
-Sorry?
-Are they shooting it right now?
-Uh, yes, sir. I believe so.
-Where?
Taxi !
Do you know when the bus
is supposed to get here?
Uh, any minute now.
Excuse me, miss.
Are you a mother?
-Yes.
-Thank God.
I have a job interview in that café.
My sitter didn't show up this morning.
If I go in there with a baby,
then they're never gonna hire me.
Could you please watch her?
-Just for five minutes.
-I'm waiting for a bus.
Please. I'll be in and out, I swear.
I really need this job. Please.
-Um...
-I'm begging you.
-Uh, okay. Okay.
-God bless you.
There we go.
Thank you.
Well, you're a good person,
taking a stranger's baby.
She could run off right now.
You'd never see her again.
Desperate times are these.
Just six days left, right?
Here's hoping.
Hey.
Oh.
--Oh.
Um...
Excuse me, when's the next bus?
Uh, should be another one
in about 45 minutes.
Um...
Please wait. I'll be right back.
Wait!
I'm so sorry. I have to go.
Discrimination is illegal.
Shit.
Wait! Hey!
Stop!
Hey! Stop!
Excuse me. Excuse me.
- Let's give it a go. Oh !
Got a man down. Pancake down.
Just when I thought
you were getting the hang of it.
Oh, I'm doing my best here, Pam.
Hey!
Evie! Evie?
What do you want?
-What?
-Just tell me what you fucking want.
Why is this happening again?
'Cause I fucking finished this.
So what do you want?
Did Patti send you?
Who is Patti?
I saw you on my TV.
You were looking right fucking at me.
Everything right?
Yeah.
Yeah.  I'm fine.
Is he bothering you, miss?
You can see her?
Would you step back, mate?
You're real?
Do you know him?
I've never seen this man
before in my life.
That's bullshit.
I know her. Her name is Evie Murphy.
You know me.
My name is Daniah Moabizzi.
Why are you doing this?
-Step back.
-Hey! Relax.
Do you hear me?
- Oi !
Get the fuck off me, asshole. I know her!
I fucking--
Miss Durst.
Yes?
Go on up. They're waiting for you.
-"Take on Me."
-Ja. From?
-A-ha.
-A-ha!
Ms. Durst.
I am so sorry. I did not hear you come in.
I'm Dr. Eden.
And that is Dr. Bekker.
Hi.
Thank you for coming all this way.
We are sorry about the building.
It's a little bit creepy, no?
What'd she say?
Oh, don't worry about her.
Um, let's go downstairs, shall we?
Okay.
This is Bernard.
If you would not mind
removing your clothes,
Bernard will conduct
a brief medical examination.
We have a gown for you.
What kind of medical examination?
It's very routine. It's noninvasive.
And once you're done, Dr. Bekker and I,
we will just ask you a few questions,
and then we can move on to the next step.
If you're a doctor,
why aren't you doing the exam?
Oh, sadly, I'm a physicist.
But Bernard is very professional.
I promise you're in good hands.
Okay.
Great. Well, we will see you in a bit.
She was ready to go.
She was ready to go,
and she wishes she could've told you.
and she wishes she could've told you,
but she just couldn't.
It was a stroke.
She was in a coma for three months
before he pulled the plug.
Tell him he set her free.
- Three months is a long time, man.
Uh-huh.
And she's grateful that you set her free.
- Thank you.
- Mmm-hmm.
Thank you so much.
My pleasure.
No, but while I'm here,
uh, could you kindly
try to contact my sister now?
-I'll pay extra.
-No, no, no.
That's okay.
Uh, what was her name?
Margery Prentiss.
Uh, there's five Margery Prentisses.
I need a DOB.
What was her birthday?
Uh, March, uh, 17th.
Oh, shit. She's a departure. Abort.
Abort.
Sir, did your sister disappear
on October 14th?
Yes. Why?
I'm so sorry,
but I can't make a connection
with those who departed.
They're in a different space, man.
Wish I could help you out,
but, uh, I can't.
I'm sorry.
Uh, I'm gonna take this.
Um, give him a hug and tell him
the dead wife wants him to move on.
Hey.
Laurie, it's Kevin. Are you alone?
-What?
-Are you alone? Is John with you?
He's downstairs. You okay?
I just saw Evie.
- What?
- Evie. Evangeline Murphy.
She's alive.
She's in fucking Melbourne, Australia.
You're in Australia?
Yes. Uh, Nora had to come here for work.
It doesn't matter.
She's here. She's here.
I talked to her, Laurie.
Okay. Okay, Kevin.
I just... I need you to slow down
and explain to me
exactly what you think you saw.
No, I don't think I saw anything.
I had a fucking conversation with her.
She's here. She's, uh...
I need you to do that thing
that you do on your computer
with the, uh... You know, go on Facebook.
I need you to find her.
She's in Melbourne,
and she's using a, um, a different name.
She's using, um,
Daniah Moabizzi.
Daniah Moabizzi. I...
I took a picture on my phone.
I'm gonna send that to you, okay?
Hang on. Hang on.
Daniah.
Did you see her at the Melbourne Library?
- Why? Does she work there?
Did you get the picture?
Yeah, I got it.
It's her.
I know it's her.
Did you talk to Nora about this?
Nora's not here right now.
-Why did you say she was at the library?
-Hey...
Kevin.
Under no circumstances
should you approach Evie again, okay?
It might scare her off.
We just... We need to figure out
what we're gonna do about this, okay?
We need to--
Kevin?
Excuse me. Excuse me!
You know where the public library is?
120 over 80. Optimal.
--Almost done.
Just need to draw some blood.
Why?
Anemia, glucose, potassium,
heavy metals, and pregnancy.
Well, I'm definitely not pregnant.
Oh, right. Your IUD.
You'll need to have it removed
before you go through.
-We can refer you to a--
-How did you know I had an IUD?
It's in your medical records.
Just gonna affix some sensors
for an electrocardiogram.
Oh.
Would you mind lowering your gown, please?
The event chamber of the device
requires an intense period of confinement,
so we're gonna simulate that now
while we're monitoring you
just to see how well you hold up.
It'll just be for a few minutes.
There's plenty of air in there.
I am gonna close the lid,
but you can get out at any time.
If you wanna take your money
in the box with you, that's fine.
Some folks worry
that we're gonna run off with it
while they're inside.
No, I trust you.
One, two, three, four!
Hi. Hey.
Uh, is Danyah working today?
Who?
Uh... Danyah or Daneeah.
-Daniah?
-Daniah, yes.
I'm not sure. Um, is there something
I can do for you, sir?
Yeah, she was helping me look for a book.
What book was it?
Um... Uh...
Assassins. Assassins, I think.
The title is Assassins?
No. If you call her,
she could probably help me.
We don't have a book by that title.
-I'm sorry.
-No, I know that... I know.
But if you just get a hold of Daniah,
then I think she could help me.
So, if you just do that,
that'd be fucking great, please.
Leonard?
Oh, uh, No. I...
He's being weird.
That so?
No. Um, I just...
I don't, I don't want any trouble.
-I was just--
-Fantastic.
Let's take a walk, mate.
I need to get a book that I was looking--
You're leaving.
It's okay, Leonard.
You know this bloke, Dani?
Yes.
I know him.
Let's talk, Kevin.
I am Evie Murphy.
I have started a new life.
I am asking you not to tell anyone
that you have seen me.
Not my mother, my father, my brother.
I just need you to leave me alone.
John's my friend. He thinks you're dead.
I have started a new life.
You don't have the right
to take that away from me.
Then you need to tell me
why you're doing this.
Because
there is no family.
Then why are you still using that accent?
- I have to go.
- No, no.
What the fuck is going on?
What?
I have compassion for you
because you are ill.
I wanted to help.
She told me to tell you
that I was who you thought I was,
and then you'd go away.
Who told you?
Mmm-mmm. No, no.
This one's on me.
Well, I hope you don't have
any expectations
because you took me out
to dinner, young lady.
I wouldn't dare.
-Who is it?
-Shit.
It's Kevin.
-Call him back.
-I, um...
I think I have to take this.
He's in Australia.
He's where?
Just... Give me, give me a minute.
-Kevin?
-What the fuck did you do?
Okay. I just... I need you to calm down
and just tell me what happened.
What happened is that I went to see Evie,
and she told me
that you fucking called her.
-Where are you?
-The library.
With her? Is she there?
Did you know about this?
Did you know that she was down here?
Okay, Kevin, I need you to listen to me.
I need you
to leave and go back to the hotel, okay?
Go back to Nora, and call me later, okay?
She told me that you said that I was ill.
What the fuck does that mean, Laurie?
Remember when you were seeing Patti,
and I told you that--
I'm not seeing anybody.
She's right fucking here!
You were seeing Patti,
and I told you that you never tell someone
in the midst of a psychotic break
that they are in the midst
of a psychotic break.
Remember?
You need to indulge that person's delusion
and find common ground.
Otherwise, it's very likely
that they will hurt themselves.
I don't...
I don't want you to hurt yourself, Kevin.
Just leave Evie, okay?
Just leave her,
and go back to the hotel, okay?
Or I hang up this phone right now,
and I call John,
and I tell him
that you just spoke to his daughter.
- Laurie, you there? Hello?
I need you to pull up
that photo you sent me.
-What?
-The photo that you took of Evie.
I need you to pull it up on your phone.
Can you do that for me, please?
Okay, I did it. What?
I want you to listen to me.
Okay?
I need you to listen to me very carefully.
You could've called anybody
you wanted when this happened,
but you called me.
Because I think you knew
that I could help you.
I'm gonna give you that help now.
This isn't real.
That girl is not Evie.
Look at the photo again.
I'm leaving now.
I don't understand what's happening.
I think that you projected Evie
onto a stranger.
And I think you chose Evie
because you understood
why she did what she did,
why she left her family, why she escaped.
I think a part of you
wants to escape, Kevin.
No, I, I don't want to escape.
Then why are you in Australia?
You are Chief of Police.
You have responsibilities here.
It is less than a week away
from the seventh anniversary,
and you just ran away
without telling anybody.
No, I... I came to be with Nora.
She's the one that needed to be here. I...
And she's the one that, uh, ran away.
Kevin, are you and Nora okay?
Ask John about the fucking book
he wrote about me.
Welcome back.
Your heart is very calm.
-What?
-Your heart rate.
- It's very even.
Most people panic after a few minutes.
Oh. Thanks.
Let's have a chat, shall we?
Okay.
Mr. Linn-Baker enjoyed talking to you
in St. Louis.
Where is Mr. Linn-Baker?
He went through.
Through the machine?
-Yes.
-Is it here in this building?
No, it's not here.
I'm happy to answer any other questions
you may have about the device, uh,
technical or otherwise.
Why haven't you used it?
Everything I need is here.
What about you?
I don't like the odds.
Odds?
All we know for certain is
that we are sending people
to the exact same destination
the others went seven years ago.
The odds that this destination
has a sustainable environment
with a breathable atmosphere
and ample food supply are very, very low,
so it is more likely
there are 140 million corpses
floating out there in space somewhere.
You make it sound so appealing.
Actually, um, several of our colleagues
did go through.
- Dr. Van Eeghen, the man who--
The man who designed the device,
he was one of the first people to use it.
Oh, yes.
And if you see him, tell him we said hello
and that Finland won the World Cup.
What did she say?
Dr. Bekker is...
Dr. Bekker thinks you have no intention
of using the device. Um...
She believes that you're curious,
but once the time comes,
you will get, uh, how do you say,
cold feet.
I won't get cold feet.
Good.
So do you want my money now?
No, not yet.
We have a question for you first.
Just one.
You wanna know
why I brought Kevin with me.
My boyfriend.
You know everything else about me,
so I just figured you'd be worried--
We know who Kevin is,
and we're not worried.
Okay.
What's your question?
Two infant twins are born.
One of them will grow up to cure cancer
but only if the other one dies now.
You don't have to kill the baby yourself,
but you do have to nod to make it happen.
Do you nod?
If I nod, how will the baby be killed?
Will it suffer,
or is it gonna be quick and painless?
Quick and painless.
Are they mine, the twins?
Irrelevant.
It's relevant if you want me to answer
your fucking question.
They're not yours.
She was working for you.
- Sorry?
- The woman at the bus stop
who gave me her baby.
That was a test, right?
We have no idea what you're talking about.
Mmm. Sure, you don't.
Please just answer the question.
Kids die every day.
What's one more?
And I get to cure cancer?
Of course, I nod.
That's it?
Yes, Ms. Durst.
That's it.
So how does this work?
You give me a name. I go to a hotel room,
explain what low-amplitude
Denziger radiation is, and then what?
Do I come back here or what?
That won't be necessary.
What? Why?
I'm afraid we will not be proceeding
any further.
What?
What, did I answer
your stupid question wrong?
Oh...  I get it. I get it!
You turn me down, and then you want me
to beg you to take my money, right?
Keep your money.
No.
Wait!
Stop!
Go home, Ms. Durst. This isn't for you.
George. George Brevity.
This is Nora Durst calling for him.
Yeah, I know! I am a fraud investigator,
and I need to talk to him
because I've uncovered a massive fraud.
Hmm. Well, then...
Well, then give me his home number
because it's an emergency.
No, I will not hold--
God damn it!
Hi.
What happened to your head?
-Are you smoking?
-Yeah, you want one?
- What happened?
- They turned me down.
-Who?
-The people who invited me here.
They, they told me that
I wouldn't be proceeding any further.
- Did they take your money?
- No.
-I thought it was a scam.
-Yeah !
And they must've known
that I knew it was a scam,
and that's why they fucking ran.
But I'm gonna find them.
I'm gonna find them,
and I'm gonna fucking destroy them.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Kevin.
What's wrong?
You can tell me anything.
No, I can't.
Why not?
The last time I told you everything,
I woke up handcuffed to a bed,
and you were gone.
Kevin.
I didn't know how to handle
you talking to a dead person.
-Oh, Jesus. Is it happening again?
-I, uh... I...
-We need to call Laurie.
-What?
I told her I would come
back here, and we would call her.
When did you talk to Laurie?
I needed help.
-With what?
-I saw...
-I thought that I saw someone.
-Okay.
-I needed to make sure--
-Who did you see?
That doesn't matter.
You won't tell me, but you'll tell Laurie?
Who else? Matt?
'Cause if you're having visions,
he's gonna wanna put it
in your fucking book.
It's not my fucking book!
No?
I think you like it.
I think you wanna be
Jesus Christ fucking Superstar
because it makes you feel important.
Like it? I fucking love it!
It's riveting !
I've read it fucking cover
to fucking cover!
There you go.
Book's gone.
We never have to talk about it again
because that's what we do.
We don't fucking talk about anything !
What do you wanna talk about?
Why didn't you stop me?
Stop you from what?
From giving her away. Lily.
I didn't stop you
because you decided you wanted to do it,
and you did it.
You never even asked me what I wanted.
And if I had, Kevin,
what would you have said?
You were relieved. Just say it!
And now you want a new baby?
Are you fucking insane?
Oh, are you afraid
you're gonna give that one away, too?
You can't have a kid
because then you'd have no excuse.
You couldn't be a victim anymore.
You... You'd have to be okay.
No one would feel sorry for you.
I do not want people to feel sorry for me.
Well, then how long, Nora?
How long before you move past it?
Move past what?
That you lost your kids.
I did not lose them !
My kids are not dead. They are gone.
They are just gone.
Then you should go be with them.
I need a taxi.
No taxis, sir.
Why not?
The explosion.
Yes, hi, uh...
- I'll be back.
Jesus.
I can't believe you're actually here.
I saw you on the TV in the window.
I turned to my friend, I said,
"Holy shit! That's my boy."
We called the local hotels,
and here you goddamn are.
Hey, there.
Son, that's Grace.
Is this real?
Of course, it's fucking real.
Where are you going anyway?
Home.
You didn't see the news?
All flights grounded.
Are you alone here?
Yes.
Well, you're not alone anymore.
Come on.
English - SDH