-Reverend.
-I brought a casserole.
...islands in the Pacific.
And early reports confirm
it was uninhabited.
The French government is denying any
responsibility, and details surrounding...
God bless you, Reverend.
Thank you.
...the person or persons
responsible for the launch
are not being made available
to the international community
despite overwhelming pressure for answers.
- How is she?
- Still fighting.
We've all been praying for her.
Thank you.
Arturo, I need you to fly me to Australia.
What?
A cargo plane with the donated food
for El Salvador
is sitting on the tarmac in Austin,
fueled up and ready to go.
I need to get to Melbourne immediately.
I'm asking you to fly me there.
But the explosion.
They said all flights have been grounded.
All nonessential flights.
Military and foreign aid are exempted.
And you, Arturo, are not only
a valued member of our congregation,
but licensed
by an internationally recognized NGO.
Randy's available to copilot.
Reverend, I...
I can't leave my mother.
That's $20,000.
It should be more than enough
to compensate you for your time
and get excellent care for your mother.
Something incredible is gonna happen
in the next few days
on the seven year anniversary,
but only if we go now, right now.
You said that we needed to be
in Miracle on the 14th.
We will be. We'll be back.
But there's a man, a very special man,
and he's supposed to be here with us,
but he's in Melbourne.
And because of this unexpected event,
he's stuck in Australia. He's stranded.
God has placed an obstacle in our way,
but He wants us to overcome it.
He wants us to demonstrate our faith.
We need to go get this man
and bring him home.
-So it's a rescue mission?
-Yes, a rescue mission, exactly.
Okay. Okay.
Bless you.
All right, let's go.
I have some friends
meeting us on the tarmac.
-How many?
-Just the three of us.
Three wise men.
Hi, this is Kevin Garvey. Leave a message.
Hello. It's me again.
I... I don't know
if you're getting my messages,
but I'm sure you're aware there's been
a nuclear incident in the South Pacific,
but I've secured transportation.
I'm coming to get you, Kevin.
What are you doing here?
I'm getting on your plane.
You invited her?
The only reason you even know
where Kevin is, is because he called me.
And we're immensely grateful
for that, Laurie.
-Oh, you're immensely grateful?
-Yes. But with all due respect,
I'm not sure you entirely grasp
what's happening here.
Okay, three years ago,
my ex-husband experienced severe delusions
and tried to kill himself.
And instead of acknowledging
his mental illness,
you turned it into fucking scripture.
And when he found out about it,
he relapsed
and ran halfway around the world,
probably to get the fuck away from you.
Is that what's happening here?
Am I grasping it, Matt?
Have you even talked to Kevin?
I left him a few messages.
He hasn't called me back yet.
What about Nora?
Nora?
Nora, your sister.
Yeah, she's not picking up the phone
either. But why would you know that?
Because you're too busy
chartering cargo planes to Australia.
Tell me, Matt,
does that seem reasonable to you?
Well, it must seem reasonable to you
since you're trying to get on it.
This is your fault,
you self-righteous shit!
Yeah, did you bring your whistle, Laurie,
'cause it sounds like
you need to blow off a little--
-Fuck you !
-Everybody calm down.
Look, this is my wife.
You want us to come, she comes, too.
We all want the same thing.
To make sure Kevin gets home safe.
Right?
Right.
Then let's get on the plane
and work this out like civilized adults.
When we find Kevin,
you don't speak to him, okay?
I will talk to him. He didn't call you.
-He called me.
-And what exactly did he say?
What did he specifically say
that leads you to believe he's delusional?
Did he see something or someone?
-Did she tell you?
-She said he was upset.
Upset about what, exactly?
Because I'm getting the feeling
we're not hearing the entire story.
No, the whole story, Matt,
is in your ridiculous book,
which somehow you convinced my husband
and my stepson to keep from me.
Yeah, well, they kept it from you 'cause
they knew this would be your reaction.
Do you think it's ridiculous, John?
It doesn't matter what I think.
We'll know in the next four days, right?
What happens in four days?
It's the seven year anniversary
of the Departure.
So?
This is my plane, my mission !
And I will speak to Kevin
because I absolutely refuse to believe
he's psychotic.
I was married to Kevin for 15 years.
He used to look
through all of our cupboards
before he found the wine glasses.
He has a tattoo that's misspelled,
and he shits four times a day.
So I refuse, Matt, to believe that he's
the goddamn second coming of Christ!
- Oh !
What are those?
For my allergies.
Michael,
I need to know you're with me.
-Where else would I be?
-No, no, no.
I need to know you're with me, that you'll
help me bring Kevin back to Miracle,
whatever it takes.
Maybe we should just ask him
what he wants to do.
We can't land in Melbourne.
What's happening?
The airport's shut down.
They're diverting us.
No, no. We're a relief mission.
We're authorized.
They don't care.
Where can we land?
Tasmania.
Tasmania?
Then how the hell do we get to Melbourne?
Is this where I get tickets
for the ferry to Melbourne?
-Yes, sir.
-Oh, thank God.
Our plane was forced to land,
and we're stranded here.
Not that Tasmania isn't lovely.
Uh, three tickets, please.
-Hey, fuck you, Matt.
-Come on, man.
Sorry. Four tickets.
-How long is the journey there?
-Eleven hours.
Okay, okay. Eleven hours. Not bad, huh?
Unfortunately, tonight's ferry is booked
for a private group.
I'm afraid our first available
is the day after tomorrow.
No, no, that's too late.
We need to get to Melbourne immediately.
This private group
must have a few extra seats.
They bought the boat, sir.
If you wanna get on, I'm afraid
you're gonna have to take it up with them.
Are they putting a lion on that boat?
Sure looks like it.
Hi. Nice to see you girls.
Come in, come in.
I know I marked you off. Right.
Hello. How are you today?
I'm 91 , and I'm having a son.
I'm sorry?
I think she wants you
to say something, man.
-Oh ! Uh, what is it you want me to say?
-Are you a member of our pride?
No, but if we could become members,
we're willing to pay.
Oh, no, no. No money allowed.
How come you didn't ask that guy
whether he's 91 and having a son?
Well, he's a friend of the captain.
Well, uh,
we're friends of the captain, too.
-Is that true?
-No.
Listen, we have a friend in Melbourne
who's in trouble.
He needs our help. Your boat
is the only way we can get to him.
I'm appealing to your sense of charity
to let us onboard.
No.
There's gonna be sex on this boat.
There's gonna be a lot of it.
Debased and sinful from port to port,
all without judgment.
-Is that gonna be all right for you?
-Absolutely. Yeah.
Well, then why don't you tell me
the filthiest joke that you know?
-A panda goes into--
-No, no, no. Not you.
Him.
What's the difference between a pimple
and a priest?
A pimple waits until you're 12
to come on your face.
Righty-o, then.
The lady has free reign.
No law can govern the lioness.
And as for you fellows,
there's only one rule, so learn it well.
When midnight comes,
let no man mention his name
lest that man become him.
Who's him?
Frasier.
Thank you.
Off you go now. Hello.
Terrorism? It was the French.
You think they're starting a war
with the English?
This is revenge for Agincourt?
Yes, you said that already,
but when will you--
No, no, I'm not at the airport. If I was
at the airport, why would I be calling?
Hello? Hello?
Flights are still grounded.
They refuse to sell tickets
over the phone.
I'm gonna go to the snack bar
to get some sandwiches. You want some?
I'm not hungry.
There's still time.
Even if we can't get a flight,
we can take this ferry back,
and Arturo can fly us home.
What?
We're not gonna make it back to Miracle
by the 14th, man.
Yes, we are.
Well, even if we find Kevin
right off the boat,
there's no guarantee
he's gonna come back with us.
I think we need to accept
that whatever's gonna happen,
is gonna happen here.
No, no. We're bringing him home.
He has to be in Miracle. You two
should know that better than anyone.
It was spared for a reason. It's special.
You know, it... It cured my wife.
It gave me my son.
And my wife left me,
and I lost my daughter.
It's got nothing to do
with where we live, man.
We've just got to let go
and see what happens.
We're not in control of this thing.
Yeah, well,
that's 'cause you gave control to Laurie.
Maybe if you'd given a little more control
to Mary, she wouldn't have left.
Mary leaving was a test.
A test of my faith in that place
to see if I'd leave.
So, if you think I'm gonna be in goddamn
Australia on the day of reckoning--
- Matt.
- What?
You're bleeding.
It's fine.
I'm fine. It's fine. I'm fine.
He hit you, huh?
-What?
-Your nose. God hit you.
No shame in it, mate.
I've seen God smite
many a man on this boat.
Ice bags in the infirmary if you need one.
Sorry.
Are you asking
if God punched me in the face?
Indeed.
The one true Lord, Yahweh. Holy of holies.
Voice of the Olympics.
Red hat and a beard. Likes the top deck.
But I'd steer clear if I were you.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir.
I'm sorry to bother you,
but are you telling people you're God?
"I am the one true God.
"I go by many names,
but Mr. Burton is fine.
"I will not take a photo with you.
"There was no big bang.
Just nothing, then light.
"Yes, I created you.
"No, I didn't create unicorns.
"Eve was not made from Adam's rib.
It was his tibia.
"I asked Abraham to kill Isaac
just to see if he'd do it.
"Yes, evolution is real,
but it doesn't work how you think it does.
"I won the bronze medal for decathlon,
"and the one you can't remember
is the hammer throw.
"No, I had nothing to do with the Crusades
"nor any type of genocide/holocaust."
Can you believe this guy?
It was just a joke.
It's blasphemy, is what it is.
You know he's not God.
Why does it bother you?
Because he's saying he is.
You know, he didn't even talk to me.
He just handed me a card and wandered off
like I was asking for an autograph.
I think you should tell Laurie
you're sick.
I'm not sick.
Yes, you are.
-You should tell her.
-Why would I do that?
My dad used to keep everything inside.
Even with my mom.
All that time, he was just pretending
he wasn't so angry.
Then he met Laurie,
and she made him better.
No, he got better because of us,
because of the work we've been doing,
because of the book.
Laurie gave him psychobabble.
We gave him faith.
She doesn't believe in the same thing
we do, but she wants to help Kevin.
I think she'd wanna help you, too,
if you just talk to her.
She's not part of this.
Matthew, John, Michael,
they were all disciples.
Maybe Laurie's one, too.
Hey, big boy. Wanna party?
Don't bother with those two.
-Hey, how's your nose?
-Oh, it's fine. It was nothing.
Do you mind
if I speak to Laurie alone for a minute?
Uh, sure. Of course.
I'll be inside with Michael.
That couple just asked me and John
to be part of a four-way.
How flattering.
Well, at least I learned about this pride
that we joined.
Yes. Apparently, back in the '70s,
there was a whole bunch of these lionesses
in some wild animal park in California
that refused to mate
with any of the males there.
They just... They wouldn't have it.
But then something amazing happened.
The park rescued
this old fleabag of a lion
from a bankrupt Mexican circus.
He was ancient. He was, like, in his 90s.
It was a charity case.
And they brought him to the park
so he could live out his days in peace.
By the next morning,
he had screwed each
and every one of those lionesses
and ended up fathering 35 cubs.
-Ah, the infamous Frasier.
-Ooh, be careful.
It's after midnight.
No man may speak his name--
Lest that man become him.
That lion that we saw
that they put on the boat
is one of his descendants supposedly.
They're taking him around the world to
different zoos so he can spread his seed.
Well, that is the foundation
of any respectable religion.
You know,
I think we should play it your way.
I'm sorry?
With... With Kevin.
I mean, letting him believe
that he's a messiah
might be our best chance
of earning his trust.
Let's be honest, you have a better story.
My story is true.
-Come on, Matt.
-It's all true. It's based on fact.
I just wrote down what Kevin experienced.
He experienced hallucinations.
He saw things that weren't there.
How do you know?
How do you know they weren't there?
Because Patti is dead.
Because Evie is dead.
If you wrote a book every time
somebody thought they saw--
Evie?
Is that what he said when he called you?
Did Kevin see Evie?
Please don't say anything.
John and Michael, they wouldn't...
-Just please, please, Matt.
-What kind of person do you think I am?
I...
-I think you're a good person.
-I think you're a good person, too.
-Can I buy you a drink?
-No, I'd just like a moment alone.
-To pray.
-Okay.
Well, we'll be at the bar.
If you can't find us,
just look for the orgy.
- Godspeed.
Stop! Stop!
Man overboard !
I saw you.
I saw what you did.
There's a man in the water!
I think he's jumped.
- Didn't he call?
- What are you doing, mate?
-What the hell were you thinking?
-I was trying to save a man's life!
You need to get the ship's manifest
and account for every passenger.
Whoever's not on the boat,
that's the man I saw go over.
There is no manifest, mate.
-Your people bought out the whole boat.
-My people?
I'm not one of those lunatics.
Listen to me.
There's a dangerous man onboard.
I can identify him.
He's wearing a red hat
and calling himself God.
You mean David Burton.
You know him?
That woman,
she said he was a friend of the captain.
I'd hardly call him a friend,
but I know him, sure.
We all do. He's a celebrity.
A celebrity?
He was a broadcaster in the Sydney Games.
Had quite the touch.
He was a decathlete back in the '80s.
-Medaled for Australia.
-Yeah ! Yeah, the bronze.
I read about it on the card he gave me.
Right after
he washed his hands of the Holocaust.
But what it fails to clarify
is how he went from being
a sports announcer to Yahweh.
It was after he died.
Yeah... What?
About three years back,
he went rock climbing with a mate
just outside Perth.
He fell 100 meters.
Broke his neck.
His mate dragged his body into the cave
so the dingoes wouldn't eat the corpse,
made his way back to civilization,
but when they got back there,
Burton was sitting
at the front of the cave,
not a scratch on him.
Said he felt absolutely fine
and that he was God.
People don't actually believe
this guy is God?
Some do, sure.
Most are just having a laugh.
I don't think he expected so many people
to be pestering him,
so he hands out those cards,
the frequently asked questions.
Spends most of his time in Tasmania.
He's got a little cabin down there.
He's quite a private sort of fellow.
Spends a bit of time on the ferry,
just to be amongst the people.
So he can murder them?
We don't have any other witnesses.
Nobody reported missing.
Well, those sex-crazed maniacs
wouldn't notice anyone missing.
Burton walks in here and confesses,
I'll be happy to contact the authorities.
We dock in Melbourne in a few hours.
Until then, mate,
I suggest you go and find some dry clothes
and enjoy the ride.
You believe me, don't you?
Yeah. Of course.
Like when I told you
I didn't molest my comatose wife?
Excuse me.
-What?
-Where's your list?
-When we got on the boat,
you had a list of your members.
Where is it?
Oh, I don't know. Somewhere.
One of your people has gone in the water.
We need to find out who he is.
Oh, no, thanks.
You don't care
that somebody's been killed?
No, not really.
Of course not. Why would you?
All you care about
is fucking each other and Frasier!
-What?
-You spoke his name.
He spoke his name!
He spoke his name! He spoke his name!
Become him!
- Become him!
-Become him ! Become him !
-Become him!
-Become him ! Become him ! Become him !
In darkest Tijuana,
at 91 years of age,
who, by the force of man,
was taken from his home?
Frasier!
Taken north across the border,
where the lioness awaits a worthy mate.
Who is the king that she awaits?
Frasier! Frasier!
Become him. Become him. Become him.
What are you doing?
- No!
- 91 and still in his prime!
-Please!
-91 to father a pride!
Who will give his seed?
Frasier!
No! Please. Please, no!
No!
No, no, no!
You people are sick!
One of your people is out there murdered,
floating in the water,
and you're in here doing this!
You ought to be ashamed of yourself.
Hey!
I saw you. I know what you did.
You think you can get away with this?
Don't ignore me. I'm talking to you.
Are you all right?
I heard what you said in there.
You're right. They're sick.
We're not all like them.
There's a plan.
When we dock, be sure you stay on the boat
until it's safe.
When we dock, stay on the boat.
-Jesus, Matt. You look terrible.
-I'm fine.
-I just need to speak to Michael and John.
-About what?
Please, Laurie. It's in your best interest
if you're not involved.
You know, whatever you got to say to us,
you can say to her.
No one seems to care
that I just witnessed a murder.
The man who perpetrated it
just assaulted me.
-He what?
-He hit me with impunity,
and he needs to be dealt with.
Dealt with how?
We need to compel him
to confess to what he did.
Be not deceived. God shall not be mocked.
For whatsoever a man soweth,
that shall he also reap.
No, we're not reaping anyone, man.
You used to burn men's houses down
for pretending to be things they're not.
What happened to you, John?
What happened to your wrath?
He found peace.
He thinks his daughter's still alive.
That's not peace.
What?
Nothing.
Kevin told her he saw Evangeline.
Here.
In Australia.
Is that true?
It...
It wasn't her.
What he saw was... Was, uh...
It was a manifestation of... It was...
She wasn't real.
And if I told you, you would've...
I didn't want to hurt you.
I understand.
I wouldn't have told me, either.
I understand, too.
She was protecting you.
That's what we're supposed to do
for each other. I'm sorry.
It's been a long day.
I haven't had any sleep.
We all need to get some rest
before we dock.
They've offered me a bed to lie down in
in the infirmary.
I... I think I'll take them up on it.
This is a distraction.
We need to focus on Kevin now.
Where's my book?
I threw it overboard.
Oh.
It was just getting good.
You know how it ends.
What makes you say that?
Because you know everything.
You're being sarcastic.
No. I was just wondering why I haven't
been struck down by lightning yet.
Why don't you transform those ropes
into serpents and free yourself?
I don't need to do that.
You're going to untie me
once you get what you want.
And what is it I want?
My attention.
I already have your attention.
No, not yet.
Not yet?
Well, you're finally talking to me.
Shh.
You're agitating him.
Admit what you did.
I've done lots of things.
You threw that man overboard.
Okay.
- Okay?
- Sure.
Say it.
I threw that man overboard.
You'll tell the captain
and the authorities?
No.
Why not?
Because I'm the authority.
Right, you're the authority on everything.
Creation, Isaac and Abraham,
the decathlon.
And yet you only won the bronze.
Well, that was before.
Of course. Because you weren't always God.
You had to die in a rock climbing accident
and come back to life
just like your son Jesus, who, strangely,
doesn't seem to get a mention here
on your little card.
He wasn't my son.
You're denying paternity?
Mary's word versus mine.
And yet you still see fit
to steal his story for yourself.
He was the one who died and rose again.
No, he rotted in the cave.
What?
Jesus had an identical twin brother.
That's who everyone saw a few days later,
thus the confusion.
So you take no responsibility
for your only son giving his life
for the sins of mankind?
Seems a lot to ask somebody.
Then what do you take responsibility for?
Dinosaurs?
The Black Plague?
Mount Everest? The Mona Lisa?
-The Sudden Departure?
-Yeah.
That was me.
The Sudden Departure was you?
Uh-huh.
Why?
Because I could.
You're gonna have to do better than that.
-No, I don't.
-You do.
-Why?
-Because there has to be a reason.
- Why?
- Everything in my life,
-I've done for a reason.
-Why?
To help people. To guide them.
To ease their suffering,
even though I suffered myself.
I sacrificed my happiness.
-I let my family abandon me.
-Why?
- For you !
Everything you've done, you've done
because you thought I was watching,
because you thought I was judging.
But I wasn't.
I'm not.
You've never done anything for me.
You did it for yourself.
Is that why you're killing me?
When I was a boy, I was sick.
And I prayed to you to save me,
and you did.
Why is it back?
I can save you again.
No, you can't.
Untie me.
Ta-da.
You're saved.
Ladies and gents,
we will be docking in Melbourne shortly.
Please dispose all rubbish
and collect your personal belongings
before you disembark.
Thank you for sailing with us.
We do hope you enjoyed the voyage.
There you are.
Fishing boat found a body.
Matches your description.
I've notified the police.
They'll be taking Burton into custody
when we dock.
They'd like you to go down to the station
and make a statement,
assuming you don't have
any pressing business in Melbourne.
No, I don't.
Relax.
Hey.
Did you get some rest?
Yeah, I did.
Thank you all for coming.
I'm glad you're here.
Are you okay?
Actually, Laurie,
I'm dying.
What?
David Burton, you are under arrest!
Out of the way! Out of the way!
All of you! Stay clear!
Get behind the barrier!
Ahh !
That's the guy I was telling you about.
English - SDH