Did the missing person use
an aluminum-based deodorant?
The man didn't shower
for five years.
Hygiene was not a priority.
Did the missing person
have visual impairment
or wear corrective lenses?
No. Uh, no, ma'am.
He had 20l20 vision.
He could see from the top of that pillar
all the way to the bridge.
Could you please describe
your relationship to the missing person?
He was my husband.
Your husband, what was he, uh, doing
up there on that pillar?
Is that on your little questionnaire, too?
No. I was just curious.
-Guess.
-What?
Guess. What do you think
he was doing up there?
I think it was an elaborate
coping mechanism.
Coping mechanism? For what?
For whatever pain he was suffering.
Honey, he wanted to suffer.
He settled for the pillar only after
we got arrested trying to crucify him.
I got one nail in
before those fuckers had me in cuffs.
Free country, my ass.
But that pillar did the trick just fine.
He stayed up there in the rain,
in the cold, in the burning sun.
And he ate, and he peed,
and he shit up there.
He never came down,
never touched another person,
not even his own wife.
That man never wavered.
He proved himself to God,
and last night he got his reward.
You saw him depart?
Yes, ma'am.
He looked so calm and at peace.
And all of a sudden,
he just kind of faded out
like he was on a dimmer.
And, um...
And he was gone.
And it was beautiful.
So, you just happened to be awake
and looking right at him
at the exact moment
that he, uh, dimmed out?
I wasn't the only one who saw him.
Ask around.
She says there will be
another departure here on the 14th.
I mean, I didn't actually see it happen,
but, uh, how else could he get down
from that thing?
And the man on the pillar
was the first to go
because he was the highest up.
I don't know how else to explain it.
He just popped like a bubble.
His wife was a woman of God,
and she spent all morning
with the preacher.
Thank God for the preacher.
Would you happen to know
the name of this preacher?
Hello?
It's open. Come in.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. Just a nosebleed.
I take it you're here
to yell at me about the book?
What book?
The one I gave Kevin. He didn't tell you?
Oh. No, he told me. I'm staying out of it.
So, you wanna tell me
where the man on the pillar is?
It's my understanding he departed.
I didn't witness it myself,
but that's what people saw.
People also saw you with his wife.
Sandy and I are friends.
- She lost a husband. I offered comfort.
Matt, I can literally see the lie wheel
turning in your brain.
When did I ever lie to you?
When I was five, I stood out on the street
while our house burned down
with our mom and dad inside
and you told me it didn't hurt
because they were already in heaven.
They are.
Where is he, Matt?
You know, that poor woman
lived across the bridge
in that horrible encampment
for three years
just to be close to her husband.
And when they finally allowed her back in,
she pitched her tent
right at the base of that pillar
and took care of him every single day,
even though he never acknowledged her,
never gave a word of thanks.
Her loyalty and devotion,
I've never seen anything like it.
Except when you did it for Mary.
I get it, Matt. She left.
My heart breaks for both of you,
but you making up this bullshit story
about some nutjob departing--
He had a heart attack.
He fell and he died,
and his wife brought him to the church
and asked me to give him
a Christian burial.
And she asked me to promise,
promise not to say anything,
but I didn't lie, Nora.
I did not lie.
He deserves a legacy.
Can't you give a man a little grace?
So, are you gonna dig him up or should I?
One's for dry cleaning,
one's for gym clothes,
and then the last one's
for everything else.
Honey, you don't need to justify
your desire to have three hampers.
It's not a desire, it's a need.
Well, maybe we should get a fourth hamper
just in case one breaks.
You're jealous. That's okay.
-It's hard to acknowledge my genius idea.
-Boy, is it.
- Ready?
- Yep.
All right.
One King James Bible
wrapped in Saran Wrap.
One thermos.
Empty.
What?
If I told you this was a picture of him
and a killer whale,
-would you believe me?
-No, I would not.
Huh !
Good morning.
Taking over up there?
Just cleaning up.
Came by to pay my respects.
He was friends with Michael.
Hey, John, I read your book.
-You did?
-Mmm-hmm.
Yeah, Kevin left it in the bathroom
and I picked it up,
and before I knew it,
20 minutes had flown by.
It's exciting.
Y'all have a nice day.
I didn't leave it in the bathroom.
If we can't have a sense of humor
about you being the Messiah,
we're gonna have a problem.
These are his personal effects.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
Me too, me too. I'm sorry for your loss.
Well, I appreciate that
very much, sweetheart.
If you don't mind, I'm just gonna sit here
and smoke my coping mechanism.
She's just hurt.
Of course she is.
You took him from his pillar,
now he sits in heaven by your side.
He departed from our world
to be rewarded in yours.
-Thank you, Lord. Thank you, Jesus.
-Excuse me. Hello.
Hi. You know what happened to him?
- What really happened?
- Come on.
Have a good day. God bless.
"God bless"?
Who gives a shit
if they wanna believe that he lifted?
It's not true.
Well, in 10 days,
when the world doesn't end,
they're all gonna go home
and they're gonna find something else
that's not true.
Till then, I need to keep things
nice and calm.
I am nice and calm.
Yeah. Hey.
You're the calmest
and the nicest person I know.
- Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
Hard part's over.
Just gonna crack this open, okay?
And you are free. Congratulations.
How's it feeling?
Can you wiggle your fingers, make a fist?
Good as new. Thank you.
Ms. Durst, I'm sorry
if this seems inappropriate,
but when you came in last month
to get the cast, one of the orderlies,
he said he saw you in the parking lot
before you came in.
I'm sure it's just a misunderstanding,
but he said that he saw you
slam your car door on your arm
on purpose.
Now, why in God's name would I do that?
- Hello?
- Hi. Is this Nora Durst?
Yes. Who is this?
-Is this a secure line?
-Who is this?
It's Mark Linn-Baker.
-Who?
-Mark Linn-Baker.
I'm, uh, calling on behalf of
a third party, and they...
--Well, they've asked me to ask you,
would you like to see your children again?
What?
Your children, Erin and Jeremy,
would you like to see them again?
I've got news for you, you shit.
Your third party obviously doesn't know
that I'm a fraud investigator for the DSD,
and I'm gonna have this call traced,
and I'm gonna find out
what exactly it is--
They know your kids' names, Nora.
I'm pretty sure they know what you do.
And they don't care.
You don't have to trace me.
I'm at the Crown Central in St. Louis.
Just ask for Mark Linn-Baker.
-St. Louis?
-Yes.
And I'm only gonna be here
for the next 24 hours,
so if you want to see your children,
you need to come and see me in person.
Nora?
Yeah?
This is real.
George Brevity. Hello.
-Hey, George. It's Nora Durst.
-Hey, Nora.
I just got your paperwork
on the pillar guy.
Extra credit
for sending the photos of the corpse.
Oof! What, did he land on his head?
Oh, is that Durst? Go and ask her, man.
Hey, Ocko wants to know
if you ever found out
what he was doing up on that thing
for five years.
Suffering, apparently.
Hey, George, listen.
Tell me, how do I know the name
Mark Linn-Baker?
The Perfect Strangers guy?
Who?
The sitcom.
Yeah, they were cousins.
One of them was a foreign guy, Yalki.
- Balki.
- Balki, right. Yeah. Yeah.
-Mark Linn-Baker was the other cousin.
-He faked his departure.
Yeah, Balki and the two actresses
who played their wives lifted on the 14th.
Mark felt left out
and ran off to Mexico for three years.
You know what he's doing now?
No. Why?
I think he's running a carrot stick
out of St. Louis.
No shit?
-Will you authorize my travel?
-Aw, jeez, Nora, I mean,
we got our hands full right now,
you know, with the seven-year itch coming.
-Well, can't it wait?
-I need to go now, today.
I think this is really big.
All right. Keep all your receipts, okay?
Okay. Thanks.
All right, bye-bye.
She's going.
-Hey.
What are you doing home?
Uh, I just came home to change a shirt.
Oh.
Sick of me already?
I have to go to St. Louis for work.
Just a couple of nights.
Oh.
I'm gonna miss you.
I'll miss you, too.
Oh, do you mind if I borrow this?
I need something to read on the plane.
Really?
-You don't want me to take it?
-No.
Uh, no. Matt said there's only one copy.
Maybe Matt should've gone to Kinko's.
Oh.
Are you... You busting my balls?
Can holy balls be busted?
I would love for you to take it.
We're on the same page about this, right?
That it's ridiculous?
Yeah, it's ridiculous.
Mmm. "And she did kiss the lips of Kevin.
"And lo, it was good."
Love you.
Try not to walk on too much water
when I'm gone, okay?
I won't.
And I love you, too.
Uh...
May I help you, ma'am?
Uh, this isn't letting me hit "No."
And are you traveling
with an infant today?
-No.
-Okay.
--Hmm.
It must be a dead spot.
Just go ahead and click "Yes."
It doesn't matter.
You're only taking up one seat.
May I use another kiosk, please?
All right, a deluxe room, one king.
Just a reminder,
we are a nonsmoking hotel.
And you requested that
a rental car be dropped off for you
-here at the hotel tomorrow morning?
-Yes, that's right.
Great.
Is there anything else
that I can help you with?
Actually, I'm here to meet
with one of your guests.
Oh, of course.
May I have the guest's name, please?
Um, Mark Linn-Baker.
Who is it?
They just called from downstairs.
You know who it is.
It's Nora Durst.
Please, come on in.
Did you know
they have a tailor here on premises?
I bought this suit yesterday.
They just sent a guy up, measures me.
Two hours later, it's back.
I never had a suit fit like this
in my life.
It's very nice.
May I have your cell phone, please?
-What?
-Your phone.
I just need to make sure
you're not recording this.
I'm not.
Please?
Ugh, okay.
Hey!
What are you doing?
--Sorry.
Uh, it's just hardware.
Everything that matters
is up there in the cloud, right?
Uh, please, have a seat.
Uh. . Sorry.  I took notes.
-I don't wanna mess up the science.
-Hmm.
Okay.
There are a couple types of radiation.
Non-ionizing and ionizing.
Now, there are a couple types of that.
There's alpha, beta, gamma, and neutron.
Neutron is rare.
You only find it near
particle accelerators or reactors.
And yet, trace amounts were cataloged
within the first 48 hours
following October 14th
at sites where departures occurred.
-You with me so far?
-Oh, absolutely.
All right, the guys who discovered this,
they bring their findings to Switzerland.
And the physicists,
the best physicists in the world,
-they confirm those findings.
-Mmm-hmm.
And they name it LADR,
low amplitude Denziger radiation.
So, great.
Big deal.
They found LADR at departure sites.
But it's a footprint.
A shadow.
You can't do anything with it
because it dissipated.
It's gone.
Well, what if they could make more?
If they could recreate it?
They could build a device
and whatever they put inside that device,
they could blast it with that radiation...
And it would go.
Go? Where?
Wherever they went.
The 2%.
So, they built it, this device?
-Yes, ma'am.
-Then why haven't I heard of it?
No one would let them conduct
beta testing on live subjects.
-You mean people?
-Right.
Because they were blasting them
with radiation?
Exactly.
So, they had to leave Switzerland.
The unit is mobile now.
They don't stay in one place for too long.
That was smart of them.
Ah.
I know what you're thinking.
They made me go to a hotel in Phoenix.
I felt the same way you do right now
when I heard it the first time.
Her name was Lauren.
Uh-huh. Where's Lauren now?
She went through.
-Through?
-Through.
So, what's the cost?
Well, it's different for everyone. Uh...
I think it's based on a percentage
of your overall net worth.
-I can tell you what I paid-- Yeah?
-Mark.
I don't know if you are a part of this
or a victim of it,
but if this is real,
if they've actually built this device,
they're not sending people
to some magical place
to be with their loved ones.
They're incinerating them.
They will call you on this
with a formal invitation and instructions.
All you have to do is answer it.
And this
is a digital record of the people
who have gone through.
A hundred and nineteen testimonials.
They are not hapless suckers, not victims.
Each and every one of them
had to pass an IQ test to qualify.
There's a Nobel laureate in there.
I have two degrees from Yale.
Are you married, Mark?
Not anymore.
You?
I'm in a committed relationship.
Oh. Well, then I guess
I am just wasting my breath, huh?
Yes, you are.
And I think you may be suicidal.
Four series regulars.
Three go, one stays.
Me.
You know what the odds of that are?
One in 128,000.
What happened was arbitrary.
It was purposeless.
It wasn't my fault.
I didn't do anything to deserve this.
So, no, Nora, I don't wanna kill myself.
I want to take some fucking control.
My name is Christopher Alan Trewitt.
Date of birth, 27-5-68.
This is a copy of this morning's
Wall Street Journal.
I hereby indemnify all other parties
as it relates to my physical well-being.
I am of sound body and mind,
and I give my full consent
for the journey I'm about to take,
whatever the destination.
My name is Maria Carmen Rodriguez.
Date of birth, 8-30-80.
This is a copy of
this morning's Las Noticias.
This was my choice and mine alone.
I indemnify all others.
I'm of sound mind and body,
and give consent to go...
To go wherever they went.
Amen.
My name is Paul Matiba.
I was born December 4, 1969.
This is today's Philadelphia Inquirer.
I'm of sound mind and body.
My name is Marilyn J. Oshima.
Date of birth, 20 January 1977.
My name is Edward Adam Drechin.
Born the 8th of August, 1974.
-I hereby indemnify all others...
-My name is Dev Joshi.
Date of birth, 14th April, 1985.
I have a copy of this morning's paper.
This was my choice.
...and I hereby indemnify...
Come on.
Hey.
Hey. I saw that.
That's not yours.
Thank you.
Hi.
This is yours, right?
Who are you?
Nora?
Christine, hi.
Hi.
What are you doing here?
I'm in town on business.
So...
It's great to see you.
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to Austin International Airport
where the local time is about 4:35 p.m.
If you're visiting Texas,
we're happy to have y'all with us.
And if you live here, welcome home.
Please insert your parking ticket.
--Please insert your parking ticket.
...your parking ticket.
I prepaid at the fucking machine!
What do you want me to do?
Please insert your parking ticket.
Please insert your parking...
Thank you.
Hi.
-Thanks.
-Mmm-hmm.
So, Michael said Tommy's party was fun.
Yeah, it was nice.
You were missed.
I see you got your cast off.
Oh. Yeah. Day before yesterday.
You know I would've done it for you.
I didn't wanna waste your time.
How'd you break it?
I'm clumsy.
Did I ever tell you how the day
after October 14th I broke my leg?
There was a picture of me on crutches
in the newspaper
once they found out about my family.
The headline was "Nora Cursed."
Rhymes with Durst.
-Nora.
-Hmm?
How'd you break it?
I don't wanna lie to you.
Then don't.
I broke it to cover something up.
Show me.
It's the logo for the Wu-Tang band.
-I think you mean the Wu-Tang Clan.
-Right.
Big fan.
What were you covering up?
Um...
My kids' names.
The artist did a beautiful job.
It was very tasteful.
Very understated.
And it didn't hurt, the needle.
It was... It felt good.
But, um...
Just as he was finishing up,
I played it out.
I thought for the rest of my life
people would come up to me
and they would say,
"Oh, what a nice tattoo.
"Who are Erin and Jeremy?"
And I would say, "They're my children."
"I'm Nora Cursed.
Ask me about my poor, departed children."
It was pathetic.
So, I pointed to
the first thing I saw on the wall,
it looked like a phoenix,
and I told the guy
to give me that one instead.
"Just cover it up, please,"
like it never fucking happened.
I was having a bad day.
I think I'm going crazy.
Mmm-mmm.
You are not going crazy, Nora.
How are you not going crazy after Evie?
Evie died...
And I got to bury her.
I got to bury her.
I bought a trampoline.
Come on.
Evening, ma'am.
License and registration, please.
Um, my boyfriend's the chief of police
in this town.
You think I can get off
with a warning, Officer?
Okay.
Consider yourself warned.
I just got off my shift.
Do you wanna go grab a drink?
Can I take a rain check?
I just got back from a business trip.
Business trip?
Christine called you?
I didn't go to see her.
I was in St. Louis on business.
They live in Kentucky.
How'd you even know where to find her?
She's not hiding, Tom.
She's putting pictures of Lily
on Instagram and Facebook.
Her name's not Lily anymore.
Christine just wants to know
if she should be worried.
She came after me.
She filed for custody because
she made the single
worst mistake of her life.
She wanted to fight me.
And did I fight back, Tom?
No.
No, I didn't.
I sat across from her at the deposition,
and all I saw was a mother
who had lost her child.
And I gave her child back.
And now she doesn't know who I am.
So, no, Tom, nobody has to worry about me.
Kevin adopted me when I was three.
I don't even remember that.
I grew up thinking he was my real dad.
Then, when I was 10,
he and my mom decided
that I should know about my real father,
my biological father.
I spent the next 10 years of my life
knocking on some asshole's fucking door
who wanted nothing to do with me.
He had moved on. He had a new family.
So, I wish they wouldn't have told me,
because I was already where I belonged.
Well, do you know what I wish?
I wish you'd never left her for me.
I didn't leave Lily for you, Nora.
I left her for my dad.
I didn't even know you existed.
Can I print a photo from this?
Which one do you wanna print?
This one, please.
-Jesus.
-How big can I make it?
You are a heartless bitch.
Hey! Hey! Hey, God damn you !
God damn you to hell !
You're home.
I thought you were gone till tomorrow.
I tear it off every time.
I just do it to feel...
I don't wanna die.
It's okay.
It is?
You don't need to explain, Kevin.
Hey, look.
I got a tattoo.
A couple hundred more
and I'll catch up with you.
Let's have a baby.
What?
I wanna have a baby with you.
I'm sorry.
Oh.
Hey.
Sorry.
Are you happy?
Yes.
I'm happy, too.
Let's not fuck that up, okay?
I need to get that.
Yeah.
- Yes?
- Hello. Ms. Durst?
Yes.
Thank you for answering the call.
Mark explained the opportunity
we're offering you?
Yes.
Someone is standing by to meet you
at the Crown Central
in Melbourne, Australia.
Can you be there by Tuesday
with $20,000 in cash?
- Yes, I can do that.
- Excellent. We'll see you then.
-Who was that?
-Work.
I need to go to Australia.
Just for a couple of days.
Can I come with you?
Yeah.
I can't be sure just yet, Jean,
but with the seventh anniversary of
October 15 fast approaching,
we may see some hellfire
moving up from the south.
And off the Gold Coast,
a high-pressure system of locusts
and perhaps blood boiling up.
Where you off to, then?
Oh, uh, just closing up, Chief.
Nothing's happening tonight.
You a psychic, Gerry?
Sorry?
Are you, like, clairvoyant?
Can you see into the future?
- Uh, no, Chief.
- No?
It's just that you've concluded that
nothing's gonna happen tonight
because nothing has happened?
Yeah.
It's just,
Ginny's not feeling well, so...
Ginny?
Who's that?
You know who she is.
I honestly don't.
I mean, it can't be your wife
'cause you haven't got a wife.
I mean, it...
Shit, I know who you're talking about.
You're talking about your dog, aren't ya?
Yep.
Yeah, well, I'm afraid little Ginny's
gonna have to wait for you to
come home tonight because
you're on duty.
- Yes, Chief. Yep.
- Good.
Cruiser one's got 'roo brains all over it,
so give it a wash, will ya?
I'm gonna take yours.
- This oughta be good.
Good evening.
G'day, sweetheart.
Ladies.
May I ask why you're blocking my driveway?
Are you chief of police?
Indeed I am.
Is your name Kevin?
Indeed it is.
"And He looked at them
and raised His hand,
"but they did not wave in response.
"And so He clutched the stone to His chest
and jumped into the water."
I don't know what the fuck
you're talking about.
I know who you are.
Well, I don't know who you are.
My name is Grace Playford
and I need your help.
Well, Grace, uh,
I'm off duty, so why don't
you and your girlfriends run along home
before I call Mr. Playford?
Will you come with us, please?
I can explain everything.
No, no, no, I don't want you
to explain fucking anything.
I want you
to get the fuck off my property, and...
--What the...
Jesus, Florence.
Well, he wasn't coming.
What the fuck?
What's happening?
- It's all right.
You're amongst friends.
We know who you are.
Let me go.
I don't know why you're acting this way,
but if I have to prove I know,
then so be it.
Maybe it's not him.
It's him.
Let me go, you fucking cunt!
I'll see you in two minutes.
Stop it!
No! Fuck off!
- Grace, what if it's not him?
- It's him.
But what if it’s not?
Okay, let him up.
Okay, let him up!
Kevin?
Kevin, you need to wake up now.
We know who you are.
Wake up.
Help me. Help me get the ropes off.
Let's get him off.
Get him off.
We've gotta get him...
Come on.
You all right, Naomi?
Kevin...
Hey.
What are you ladies up to?
English-SDH