You okay?
Yeah, just got clipped
with a beam.
What the hell do you two think
you were doing?
We thought we
heard someone in there!
You never go in
without authorization!
Captain, this is all me.
Amy just followed me in.
So torching your ass last year
wasn't enough, huh?
You need to stop trying
to prove how tough you are
before you get yourself killed.
Yes, sir.
Let the paramedics
look you over.
Come on, Derek. Let's get this ladder
to the second story. Let's go.
Derek! Derek!
Derek!
What's happening?
I'm freezing.
I'm fine.
ER docs don't think so.
Your temperature's been going up
and down like a rollercoaster.
How old are these skin grafts?
Last one was
about six months ago.
We're gonna run some tests and
we'll get a consult with Dr. House.
I'll be fine.
You'll be doing
what the doctors say. Got it?
I'll check in later.
Hey.
The way you
covered for me last night...
He's my brother.
I know how to eat it from him.
I'm gonna stop by
after my shift, okay?
Okay.
So where is this Dr. House?
Speaking engagement.
Not guilty.
And on the charge of gaining
control
of said medication
by fraud, how do you plead?
- Not guilty.
- Very well.
Preliminary hearing is set for
the 19th at 10:00 a.m.,
at which time I'll determine
whether there's enough evidence to
proceed to trial.
Next case on the calendar.
People versus Williams.
Charge is assault
in the second degree
with intent to cause injury
to another person.
I see the defense has
submitted a motion to dismiss...
You gonna go talk to him?
I was gonna ask him
where he gets his hair cut.
They have your signature
in the prescription log,
a security camera video,
and a pharmacist's sworn statement
saying you stole a dead guy's pills.
You're already looking
at 10 years.
You wanna add
a witness intimidation charge?
Go ahead, ask him
about his hair.
He suffered third-degree burns
over 54% of his body, a year ago,
and arrived in the ER last night,
disoriented and shivering.
For 12 hours his temperature
was bouncing between 96 and 102.
Why don't you contest the search
of the pharmacy records?
Yeah. You could argue it violated
doctor-patient confidentiality.
Except he wasn't the patient
or the doctor.
He was the guy who stole
from the patient and the doctor!
This was the third time he'd been
disoriented in the last two weeks.
Running into smoke-filled burning
buildings can be a bit disorienting.
Fortunately, I have the cure.
Stop doing it.
He's not in a burning building anymore,
and he's still shivering.
A hypothalamic tumor could cause
a vacillating temperature.
So could ER nurses
who were too busy to notice
that a patient likes
both hot coffee and cold sodas.
He tested negative for Hep C, TB, HIV,
Lyme, and his tox screen's clean.
In case you hadn't noticed,
not exactly in the mood to dance.
I'm not asking you to dance.
I'm asking you to do your job.
EKG showed arrhythmia.
Probably just a mild heart attack.
No chest pain. And smoke inhalation
already explains the arrhythmia.
The guy was in the burn unit for six
months and had multiple surgeries.
Could be a hospital-acquired
infection. Maybe MRSA.
Works for me.
Draw a blood culture,
start him on antibiotics,
vancomycin plus broad
gram-negative coverage.
If you called to see the design for my
prison tats, they're still in R and D.
You need to talk to Tritter.
Not according to my lawyer.
Your lawyer isn't gonna be able to get
the DA to drop the case. Tritter can.
Yeah, you know what else
Tritter can do?
You are not impressing anyone!
You may call yourself
principled,
but what you really are
is a stubborn adolescent idiot!
- This isn't his fault!
- I'm not the one who...
You used the
rectal thermometer on him.
You insulted him
instead of apologizing.
You flaunted your drug use in his face
and you refused to accept a deal...
I accepted the deal!
Not until after
you stole a dead guy's pills!
Allegedly.
Tritter has been opening doors
for you every step of the way
and you keep
slamming them shut.
There are no more openings
to give, House.
If you wanna stay out of prison,
you got to make one for yourself.
It's Vicodin.
You function better on it. Talk to him.
MRSA's a bacteria that often infects
hospital patients.
The burns on your chest and arm
exposed raw flesh that made you
a wide-open target.
But the antibiotics
would take care of it, right?
Depends on what strain it is.
We'll know more once we get the results
back from these cultures.
So this MRSA thing,
would it make everything
look blue?
He's seeing blue.
Who'd you get the scrip from?
Cuddy. You wanna know
what I gave her?
MRSA wouldn't change
his ocular palette.
Heavy metal poisoning could cause vision
changes, particularly thallium.
If it was thallium,
he'd be losing his hair.
So maybe it's menopause.
He's 28 years old.
Yes, his age is the reason
it's weird that a man has menopause.
Male menopause. High estrogen,
low testosterone.
Explains the temperature
swings, disorientation,
endocrinologically similar
to female menopause,
but without the vaginae
and the mahjong tiles.
Male menopause doesn't explain
the blue vision.
Blue vision isn't a symptom.
It's a side effect of Viagra.
It's right there on the label,
which I'd had no reason to have read,
except that I'm a doctor.
He's not taking Viagra.
You mean he didn't tell you
he was taking Viagra.
I don't care how sick he is. Trust me,
he still thinks he's got a shot.
Menopause causes temperature swings,
limpness, limpness causes pills,
pills cause the blues.
He's presenting no other signs
of premature aging.
Aging's not the only cause.
You said that he's got
burns on 54% of his body.
Sure it's not 55%?
Burns to his genitals could
cause testicular trauma.
Which could in turn cause...
Run a hormone panel.
When it comes back positive,
pump him full of testosterone
and send him home.
Stop following me!
Thank God my parents are dead.
If the old man had heard
I had menopause, I'd never live it down.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
Once these testosterone pellets
dissolve,
your system will be back to normal.
Yeah, but until then
I'm an old lady.
Okay to come in?
It's not MRSA.
He's not being isolated anymore.
Anyone not in a white coat
is welcome.
You're looking better.
How you feeling?
I'm good.
It turns out I got some hormone thing.
They're fixing it right now.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I think so, I just...
Derek, are you in pain?
- You need to get these out!
- Okay, hold on, what's wrong?
- Get these out!
- What's going on?
Looks like
an allergic reaction.
Hold on! We're going to get
you something to stop it.
- It's okay.
- No, just take them out!
- But you have to calm down. It's okay.
- Get them out!
- Derek!
Derek, let her go!
Two milligrams
of IV lorazepam, stat!
Get them out!
The complaint department
is across the hall.
I'm busy.
Can I just assume that you told me
how unfair I'm being and...
I'm sorry.
You could throw a dart at all the
adjectives
between arrogant and unhinged,
and I'm sure you'd hit one
that describes me.
There's a reason
I operate that way.
I live in pain.
Pain that on good days
is merely intolerable.
And on bad ones will suck the life force
right out of you.
It doesn't mean that
I've handled this right.
Actually, it means I was wrong.
Thank you.
I know that couldn't have
been easy for you to say.
Even if you don't mean
a word of it.
I'm sorry.
Look, you can hook me up
to a damn polygraph...
And I'm sure you'd pass.
The thing is I've never been interested
in what you have to say.
All I care about
is what you do.
I'll see you at the hearing.
It wasn't the medicine.
Contamination and allergy tests
both came back negative.
There was nothing to suggest
a pulmonary embolism.
And his EKG
showed the expected tachycardia
from the exertion of the attack.
And I'm fine, by the way,
thanks for asking.
Aggression that comes on that fast
has got to have a neurological basis.
We should do a CT for a frontal lobe
tumor and an LP for meningitis.
Great. Have at it.
That's it? No challenging our theory,
no tearing us down?
No need.
You got it under control.
- Where are you going?
- Upstairs this time.
To do what?
Check myself into rehab.
Did Tritter offer you
another deal?
Nope. This is all me.
So, no slaps on the back?
Encouraging words?
We're just trying to
understand what this is.
I hope it's me detoxing,
otherwise I soiled a perfectly
good pair of underwear
last night for nothing.
So this is for real?
It's not just a show
for Tritter?
Absolutely it's a show for Tritter.
And the judge.
And, unfortunately, unless it's real,
there is no show.
Hey, if it doesn't
help my case,
at least I can go to prison
with heightened senses.
All the better to enjoy
my strolls around the yard.
Time's up. Group's starting.
Gonna need to check that stuff.
When I lead
the big patient rebellion,
Voldemort here
is the first to go.
CT was normal,
no frontal lobe tumor,
LP was negative for meningitis.
We're back to square one.
What about something vascular?
Polyarteritis nodosa?
Brain lesions would have
shown up on the CT.
Legionnaire's explains
the chills and temperature.
Altered mental status
causes the aggression.
We would have seen
respiratory problems.
We're throwing darts.
We need to go to House.
We need to
deal with this ourselves.
He can make the time!
Derek's still his patient.
The man's life as he knows it
could be over.
I think you of all people
would want to cut him some slack.
We're treating a man who runs into
burning buildings for perfect strangers.
He didn't ask for what's
happening to him.
House did
everything to himself.
He's been cut more
than enough slack.
Right now, House has more
important things to deal with.
It was the first time
I'd seen him in months.
I guess I was hoping he'd put his arms
around me and tell me he understood.
But he said he wasn't
ready to forgive me.
Well, he may never be ready.
You're doing the only thing
you can do. You're trying.
How about you, Greg?
Have you thought about how to
fix things with people in your life?
No need.
The people in my life
have no expectations of me.
Makes all our lives easier.
Apparently not.
The first step in recovery...
Is admitting I have a problem.
I've obviously done that
or I wouldn't be here.
I've even embraced step two and accepted
that there is a higher power.
Maybe not a god per se, but that
André the Giant guy was powerful.
Where I start to butt up
against it is step three,
surrendering my will
to this higher power.
I'm sure André's ghost
has my back and all, but my free will,
I never leave home without it.
Kind of like your pills.
If you could do this on your own,
I assume you wouldn't be here.
True.
Everybody lies. His tox screen.
It's been clean every time.
Exactly. It shouldn't be.
He's had extensive skin grafts,
which hurt like hell.
Not everybody's House. People can handle
pain without medication.
But they do have pain.
This guy's worried about losing his job,
so he's hiding the pain.
We find out where the pain is,
maybe we find out what the problem is.
Or he doesn't feel pain.
Either way, it's something.
- When?
- Two minutes ago.
Pulse is 157, respiration 42.
He was fine.
He was just telling me a joke,
- just a minute ago...
- Get her out of here!
No fluid in his lungs!
O2 stat's 85. He's hypoxic!
We're gonna have to intubate!
It's not his lungs!
He's got marked ST elevation.
He's having a heart attack.
Pick a color.
Medication time.
"You are a ray of sunshine
on a cloudy day."
He's stable.
Won't stay that way.
His blood tests showed
troponins and CK-MB up.
Chase was right.
He was hiding chest pain.
He's been having a whole series
of heart attacks.
Heart attacks can't cause you
to reach out and choke someone.
Lack of oxygen to the brain
causes disorientation.
Increased adrenaline
causes rage.
The more important question is
what caused the attacks?
- Where are you going?
- To see House.
We have a 28-year-old with clean
arteries, no valvular abnormalities
having multiple heart attacks.
I'm not gonna wait for Chase to give us
another breakthrough.
- Maybe we should go.
- We don't have an answer yet.
I'm fine, by the way.
Thanks for asking!
Whoever came up with buprenorphine
to wean off Vicodin should be shot.
Then stabbed in the eye.
I think someone
needs to adjust my meds!
The heart shows no signs
of inflammation or...
If the cause of the heart attacks
isn't internal, it must be external.
Something environmental.
None of the attacks happened
in the same place.
Still must be something
in common.
First one happened
in an apartment building fire.
Fire, water, smoke,
oxygen masks...
The second and third ones
happened here.
There was no fire,
no water, no smoke.
His clothes were all different,
he'd been cleaned.
That's the "whats".
How about the "whos"?
His partner Amy was
at all three attacks, but...
Anyone else?
People don't
cause heart attacks.
Well, then you shouldn't
be worried about proving me wrong.
Amy? Would you come with me,
please?
Anything new on my brother?
We're not quite sure yet.
Could you come with me?
Yeah.
What's this all about?
I don't know.
They wanted to
talk to us together.
Derek!
House was right.
I don't get it.
How can I be causing
his heart attacks?
You may be carrying an agent
that triggered them.
It could be anything, mold spores,
poisonous plant residue,
something you picked up
at a fire site.
Until we identify the agent,
we can't allow you near Derek.
I can't believe that
I'm doing this to him.
You can't blame yourself
for this.
You know how he got
those skin grafts?
He was trapped in a fire.
We were clearing rooms
in an office building fire.
And the ceiling collapsed, and it cut me
off from the rest of the group.
And I kept yelling
that I was fine,
but Derek refused to wait for the team
to clear the debris,
so he took off looking for
another access point.
He got caught in a backdraft.
He almost died
because of me once.
And now it's happening again.
You're not my mom. You don't have to
keep checking up on me.
How you doing?
Not bad,
considering I've just learned
I'm completely powerless.
See this big fancy wing?
It was built because
this program works.
Faulty logic.
This big fancy wing exists because some
people with money think that it works,
wanna believe that
they can buy a better world.
This is nothing short
of idealized despair.
Let other people wallow in it.
I don't even know
what that means.
None of this means anything.
It's just nonsensical slogans
and platitudes.
Meaning takes time,
it takes work.
What do you think
I've been doing?
You've been here for two days!
Talk about wallowing in it!
We all get it.
We know how much pain you have.
You're here to deal with that
and get on with your life!
Right! I should have an affair with a
dying patient and move into a hotel.
You're a coward, House.
You find fault in everybody because
you're afraid to look at yourself.
Thanks. I was running short
on platitudes. You can leave now.
We tested Amy for
about a dozen different agents,
but they all came back negative.
So she's not causing
the attacks.
Derek, are you
in love with her?
What does that have to do
with anything?
Amy told me how
you got those skin grafts.
And the way you're always
watching out for her,
and I
see the way you look at her.
Have you told her how you feel?
She has a six-year-old
daughter.
Women with daughters
can still fall in love.
I know.
Because she did.
With my brother.
They're engaged.
Broken heart syndrome.
He's in love and it's killing him.
I thought that only happened
to 80-year-old widows.
Thanks to his menopause
and estrogen level,
he basically is an old woman.
BHS is an acute physical response
to an emotional experience.
Stress triggers
a flood of catecholamines...
That's a plain old stress
cardiomyopathy, not a heart attack.
But if you're too worried
about losing your job to get it treated,
they can devolve
into full-on heart attacks.
You think it's a coincidence
this started when Amy got engaged?
No, I don't.
But now that you
know the "why",
what are you gonna do
to stop the "how"?
I already put him on beta-blockers
and nitroglycerin. No effect.
We need to put him
on antidepressants.
Not if you're right.
Antidepressants would inhibit
his autonomic nervous system,
which would only speed up
the heart attacks.
We could try propylthiouracil,
slow down his metabolic rate.
Thyroid effect would
only weaken the heart.
The only other option
is blood thinners.
This is not a fat guy with plaque-filled
arteries and a swollen heart.
He's a guy whose brain
is trying to kill his heart.
So buy him a girlfriend,
make him happy.
That might make you happy.
The only thing that'll
make him happy is Amy.
So keep him away from her.
He has a myocardial infarction
every time she walks in the room.
What do you think will happen
to his heart
when we tell him
he can never see her again?
He needs a shrink.
Chase's idea is as good as any.
But short of frying his brain
and wiping Amy out, he's screwed.
We need Cuddy.
Why?
So you can tell her
why you need to fry a guy's brain.
The guy's heart isn't working
and you want to shock his brain.
Electroshock therapy is the only way
to erase his memories of Amy
and stop the brain's
chemical attack on the heart.
This isn't 1940!
The problem can be controlled
with antidepressants.
Cameron?
Antidepressants would inhibit
his autonomic nervous system,
speed up the attacks.
LMNO, PTU, blood thinners,
none of them will solve this problem.
The man's got a real-life
Harlequin Romance in his head.
We're gonna pull out
the 1940 playbook.
Bilateral electrodes,
high-stimulus sine-wave intensity,
turning that dial
all the way to 11.
It's basic brain chemistry.
We interrupt protein synthesis,
altering the neurotransmitter system.
End result, no memories,
no Amy, no problem.
Go ahead.
You heard the lady,
go plug him in.
Am I really that pathetic?
What are you talking about?
If I had pitched
electroshock therapy
as a cure for
broken heart syndrome any other time,
you'd have dug in, made me try a
hundred other useless things first.
So either you're actually
beginning to trust me
or you just feel sorry for me.
You presented
a reasonable argument.
You were clear-headed
and non-impulsive about it.
Never once
used the word "moron."
The rehab's working, House.
You'll still
be able to perform routine functions
like walking, talking,
tying your shoes.
The treatment targets
the anterior cingulated cortex.
It should only affect
your experiential memories.
So my parents? My childhood?
If this works,
you won't remember them.
Or your firefighting training.
And Amy.
Are you okay with that?
I wouldn't miss her, right?
Tell Amy how you feel.
Because if she loves you...
No. I won't do that to her.
Or to my brother.
You're effectively killing who you are
just to keep this secret.
She doesn't love me.
Caterpillar?
Lower intestine
with ulcerative colitis.
You crash art therapy classes
just for the adrenaline rush?
Cuddy wouldn't get off the phone until I
promised I'd come and see for myself.
I got to admit,
this move I did not expect.
Well, don't tell anyone, but the photos
of smiling people in the brochures,
it's just marketing.
Well, you're obviously
making an effort.
So I suppose the next step is
for me to talk to the DA.
Which you have
no intention of doing.
No.
So words mean nothing, actions mean
nothing, what the hell is left?
You son of a bitch!
What about your words,
your actions?
"Got to get House cleaned up.
Got to get him to show some humility."
But when it comes to actually
doing something,
you prove that all you care about
is bitch-slapping a guy
who refused to kiss your ass!
You ever trust an addict?
You ever give one
the benefit of the doubt?
How many times
did that work out for you...
Yeah, I get it.
And so you were screwed over by your
wife, your mother, your partner.
But you keep sending them
Christmas cards
while you
take it out on everyone else!
No more Christmas cards.
No, I learned.
People like you,
even your actions lie.
I'm scared.
I know.
I'm gonna give you a muscle relaxant
so your body doesn't convulse.
Count backwards from 10.
Ten, nine, eight,
seven...
Go.
What's your name?
Derek.
Heart sounds good.
Do you know what city we're in?
No.
Would you be okay with
a couple of visitors?
Derek, it's me. Brock.
I'm your brother, and when you get out
of here, you'll be staying with me.
I'm Amy.
I'm your friend.
I'm sorry,
but I don't remember either of you.
We've given him
four rounds of electroshock.
The charge made his voice a little
higher, but the EKG and BP are good.
Good.
We're gonna give him
his last round in the morning,
then be in court
for your hearing.
Thanks.
I'm gonna stay here.
Monitor Derek.
Thanks for the update.
My next condolence call is arriving.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
I got you something.
Nice.
I figured it might help make
a good impression on the judge.
It's not that nice.
I had no business blaming you
for any of this.
I know you were just
trying to help me. Protect me.
That's what friends do.
Is this an apology?
Part of the program.
- If you don't like it, I can stop.
- Not at all.
It's just so
unfamiliar.
Please, keep going.
He looks lost.
It's gonna take him a while.
Brock's pulling a double shift.
He can't stand to
see him this way.
Derek's gonna need him, Amy.
I know the timing isn't great
with a wedding coming up.
What wedding?
Yours. You and Brock.
We're not getting married.
We don't even date.
Why would you think
we're getting married?
When you first offered Dr. House
the chance to check into drug rehab,
how did he respond?
He told me to
get out of his office.
I warned him that he could end up in
prison and lose his medical license.
If he was concerned,
he didn't show it.
So you continued
your investigation?
Yes.
Which is what led me
to the hospital pharmacy.
- Turn it off.
- What did you tell the pharmacist
was the reason for your visit?
I thought I told you never to call me
when I'm on trial.
The memories were false.
We fried his brain for nothing.
Whatever was killing him
before is still there.
We did an MRI.
There's slight hypo-perfusion
in the anterior cortex.
What did you find when you checked
the pharmacy log?
Hold on, Mr. Vickers.
Thanks, Your Honor.
It's hard to hear.
Did you test for clotting time
and IV function?
I believe that this is
a medical emergency, Your Honor.
His blood's normal and his
heart's pumping it up to the brain.
But it's not all getting there.
Something's obstructing
the blood flow...
Dr. House, you were given
adequate notice
to make arrangements
for your patients.
There's no hyper intensity to suggest
a foreign body near the region.
And no signs of infection
or vascular malformations.
It's lower down.
Dr. House, hang up!
The cytology on the LP
doesn't suggest a tumor.
Now!
Hang on a second.
Does your voice always get that high
and annoying when you're angry?
Do you want to go to jail?
No, thank you.
Set him up for a selective vertebral
angiography. I'm on my way.
Dr. House.
House! Sit down!
Why? I'm bored.
There's nothing I can say or do
that's gonna make a difference here.
If you leave this room,
I will find you in contempt.
Get a recess.
Are you out of your mind?
They said they wanted me there,
but I don't think they like me.
His voice isn't high because
of the electrical charges.
It's another symptom
of menopause.
His system keeps getting hit
by women's issues,
so let's follow the pattern.
What might obstruct the blood flow
that's more common in women than men?
Is the catheter in?
Go back to court.
We'll let you know the results.
Shut up and wire him.
Center the image on the interpeduncular
cistern.
Keep it moving at
30 frames per second.
If you think the arteries are narrowing,
you're gonna need still shots,
which we can do without you.
The problem is not
how wide the road is.
There's a guy with a squeegee
on the sidewalk flagging cars.
That's what's causing
the slowdown.
We find him,
we find the problem.
- He's wired.
- Go!
Injecting the dye.
Blood's in the capillaries.
There.
Mr. Squeegee.
Spinal meningioma pushing on the nerves
to the vocal cords
creates the voice change.
And that nerve just happens to live
right near the meningeal branch
of the vertebral artery, obstructs
the blood flow to the brain.
The brain malfunctions,
creating false memories.
Memories cause love.
Love kills.
And we didn't completely
screw up.
Cleaning the slate bought us time
to find the real problem.
On the other hand,
if we had been better,
we wouldn't have
needed the time.
Schedule him for surgery.
Dig that thing out.
He can start enjoying real misery
instead of the fake stuff.
House.
I just heard that you
apologized to Wilson.
Detoxing. I didn't know
what I was saying.
Excuse me.
I have to go to jail.
What is your position
at Princeton-Plainsboro?
Chief Administrator
and Dean of Medicine.
And you're responsible
for oversight of the pharmacy?
Yes.
Sorry. I didn't mean
to interrupt.
I hope you don't mind
that we continued on without you?
I said I was sorry.
There's no need to be sarcastic.
What is this?
That's our prescription sign-out log
from December 24th.
Does that appear to be
Dr. House's signature?
Yes.
What has he signed for?
A prescription for oxycodone
in the name of patient Larry Zebalusky.
And did those pills
ever reach that patient?
- No.
- Why?
He was already dead.
And Dr. House knew this?
Yes.
So, Dr. House had no legal or medical
basis for acquiring that oxycodone?
Dr. Cuddy?
He never got the pills.
It's his signature.
The log is strictly controlled.
Dr. House did pick up a prescription,
but it wasn't for oxycodone.
It says oxycodone.
You testified...
I know,
but it wasn't oxycodone.
Dr. Wilson informed me that Dr. House
already tried to steal
the pain medication of this patient,
which made clear to me
that Dr. House was in a particularly
vulnerable and desperate state.
So I went to the pharmacy
and I swapped bottles.
Dr. House only got
a bottle with placebos.
I understand your impulse
to protect a valued colleague...
I have it right here
on the inventory report...
Your Honor, she's lying!
She's obviously forged that report.
In light of this evidence...
If this is real,
why didn't she mention it earlier?
I move to dismiss this case!
There is other evidence,
Your Honor!
Everyone shut up and sit down.
Dr. Cuddy, why are you
only now coming forward with this?
I guess I never expected it
to go this far.
The witness is excused.
Your Honor,
you can't seriously believe...
Dr. House, please stand.
My suspicion is your boss...
My suspicion is you have better friends
than you deserve.
Rules and laws
apply to everyone.
You are not as special
as you think.
But Detective Tritter
chose to make you so.
Detective, I don't know
exactly what's going on here,
but I am sure that this man
is not flooding the streets
with cocaine.
I'm also certain that,
knowing Dr. House,
he must have done something
to set you off.
But you're gonna have to
live with it.
Given Dr. Cuddy's testimony,
I'm not going to allow this
to proceed to jury.
Case dismissed.
Court is adjourned.
Dr. House,
you're still guilty of contempt
for that little walkout earlier.
You'll be spending
the night in jail,
and after that you're going right back
to your rehab.
Bailiff, take Dr. House
into custody.
Dr. House.
So should I be looking for you
in the shadows,
or flinch every time
a car backfires?
Good luck.
I hope I'm wrong about you.
They got the meningioma.
Your brain should start generating
real memories again.
What do I do when I get out?
You have people who love you.
They'll take care of you.
You start over.
I'm surprised to see you're not
spooning your way through the walls.
So, what do you say? How about
a conjugal visit to celebrate?
There's nothing to celebrate,
House! You made me perjure myself.
Fabricate evidence.
You make everyone around you
worse for being there.
The only bright spot is that
now I own your ass.
When you get out of rehab,
you're gonna be
pulling double clinic duty,
giving lectures to students,
helping me find donors,
pretty much anything else
I ask. You got it?
Your buprenorphine.
You get these from
the pharmacy or from Voldemort?
Voldemort. Why?
What difference does it...
That's Vicodin.
He's been slipping you Vicodin?
No! He'd be risking his
minimum-wage job to do that.
The whole time?
My higher power said
it was okay.
Nothing's changed?
Nothing's changed.
The apology.
You didn't need to do that
to make this work.
Believe what you want.
Good night, House.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Good night, Wilson.