So, you got a Green Beret,
a Navy SEAL and a sister from Brooklyn.
The general hands
each of them a gun and says,
"Your spouse is seated next door
in a room in a chair."
"In order to pass this test,
you must go inside and kill them."
Immediately
the Green Beret says,
"No, sir, I could never kill my wife.
I just can't do it."
The General looks at him
and says, "You know what?"
"You ain't got what it takes.
Take your wife and go on home."
Navy Seal then heads in.
Five minutes later, comes out,
tears strolling down his face.
"I tried, I tried, I tried,
I just can't do it,"
"she looked so beautiful
in the chair, I can't do it."
General looks at him and says,
"You know what?"
"You ain't got what it takes."
Finally, sister from Brooklyn
strolls in with a swagger.
Shots rang out,
there's banging, there's screaming,
it's going crazy!
Suddenly,
everything goes silent.
The General says,
"Well, what the hell happened inside?"
The sister from Brooklyn
screams back,
"The damn gun had blanks in it,"
"so I had to beat him to death
with my bare..."
What the hell?
A little bit of warning
would have been nice!
The sound of a saw
cutting a hole in the wall
wasn't warning enough?
Bite me.
What, are you kidding me? Tub of Goo
there's gotta be over six bills.
You ain't gonna lift him
with a couple of blankets.
You got a better idea,
Einstein?
Yeah, just roll him off.
What? He's already dead,
it ain't like he's gonna feel it.
How the hell's
a guy get that big?
You roll him off
from this high,
he's likely to go right
through the floor and take us with him.
Are you ready?
All right, one, two, lift!
Come on, man!
Me? You're the kielbasa king.
It wasn't me.
Whoa, it wasn't me, either.
Don't look at me.
Please tell me
dead guys can fart.
Of course. Dead bodies are full
of all sorts of gases.
But a dead body
can't tighten a sphincter.
You need a tight sphincter
to make a fart.
No, you need a loose sphincter.
A tight sphincter...
You check his femoral?
No. He peed all over himself!
Look, I've heard dead bodies
moan, groan, hiss,
hell, I've even seen them
sit straight up on a gurney.
Trust me, his skin's cold, pupils are
fixed and dilated, he's not breathing.
- He's got a pulse!
- No way.
All right, give me an Ambu bag and
an EKG. It's thready, but it's there.
Let's get him in a basket.
Ready?
One, two, lift!
Forty-six-year-old guy
in a coma.
Doesn't appear to be
anything wrong with him
except for the fact
that he weighs over 600 pounds.
What time
does he usually get in?
Any time between
8:00 and 10:00.
- Did you say 600?
- At least.
Biggest scale we got
only goes up to 350
but this guy's waistline
is over seven feet.
Which means he's a diabetic
with blood thicker than pancake batter.
No mystery there,
not much we can do.
Blood sugar's normal.
Cholesterol's lower than mine,
tox screen's clean, no sign of trauma.
Sure there wasn't
a mix-up at the lab?
Three times?
It's almost 11:00,
where is House?
Hello!
It's 11:00.
Which means my friend is ready for his
sponge bath and I shouldn't be here!
Hey, Gomer Pyle!
I know you can hear me.
I think you mean Barney Fife.
So many great idiot icons
to choose from.
You need time
to think of some more?
Either arraign me or let me go.
No problem.
Which do you prefer?
What took you so long?
Sorry. I didn't have 15 grand
in my loose change jar.
- What the hell did you do?
- Nothing.
Your motorcycle was impounded,
that explains the speeding, DUI,
and driving without a license.
The fact that you're you explains
the illegal possession of narcotics
and resisting arrest.
Where's your car?
What happened?
Some idiot cop with crotch rot
obviously thought
that I didn't treat him with the
deference due to a man of his stature.
He trumped up a traffic stop,
next thing I know
I'm sharing a cage
with a guy
who thinks that showers
are the way the devil
gets inside you.
Does Cuddy know?
Everything she needs to.
- I'm innocent.
- Till proven guilty.
Guy wanted to punish me,
he did it. It's over.
Gotta get yourself a lawyer.
Already got one.
You know what they say about the lawyer
who has himself as a client?
Same thing they say
about the doctor who lends 15 grand
to a friend he knows
can't pay him back.
Relax, you'll get it.
Where am I gonna take off to?
Does Salma Hayek
live in Mexico or Spain?
There's nothing abnormal in the EEG
or the neurological exam.
I'm guessing it's food-related.
Improperly prepared puffer fish
can have toxins
that could cause a coma
and might not show up
on the tox screen.
Where do you think he is?
He's probably at the track.
If he's at the track he'd tell us
so we don't have to page him,
and if it was a puffer fish, he'd
be dead in six to eight hours, tops.
He's been in a coma
at least 24.
And the guy didn't get to 600 pounds
eating a load of sushi.
What if he was
in a motorcycle accident?
Explains the coma.
But how'd he get back in bed?
Oh, Cameron's talking
about House!
You ever see how he drives?
No, we haven't.
But I have seen how many pills
he's been popping lately,
I wouldn't be surprised
if he's in a coma somewhere himself.
If I am, this is
one lame hallucination.
What happened to you?
If you ever end up in a bar with the
Cambridge Women's Heavyweight Eight,
do not accept an offer
of an upside-down kamikaze shot.
- We have a case.
- Fat guy in a coma, I know.
- Cuddy found you?
- Nope.
But the wall
between Wilson's office
and this one
is thinner than you'd think.
Which means
we need to stop talking
about what a pathetic loser
he is.
Start treating Jabba
for pickwickian syndrome.
His 96 double-Zs are probably putting
pressure on his chest, suffocating him.
CO2 and oxygen sats are normal.
For you and me.
What's normal for a hippopotamus?
And get
a detailed medical history.
From who?
He was brought in alone.
And I doubt a guy who weighs 600 pounds
bothers with annual physicals.
Talk to the neighbors
and search the house.
Let's see what else
Shamu's been up to besides eating.
This conversation is over
because I've officially run out
of clever things to call the guy.
It's hard to believe you can even attach
this much flesh to a human skeleton.
I wouldn't exactly
call this attached.
This is ridiculous.
A person shouldn't be able to
eat themselves into oblivion
and then just expect everyone
to pull out the stops to fix everything.
What are we supposed to do?
Refuse treatment to anyone who's obese?
Come on, give me a break.
This guy's not obese.
He's not even morbidly obese.
He's suicidal.
People who attempt suicide
get treated.
Plenty of noncompliant
diabetics don't.
We don't give
drug addicts dialysis
or alcoholics
liver transplants.
What is your problem?
You get beat up
by a gang of fat kids
when you were in grade school
or something?
Yeah. I'm the one
with the problem.
So, I think
his bedroom's through there,
and the kitchen's to the left.
Have you seen any changes
in his personality?
Any trouble with memory
or balance?
No, but I really
don't see him that often.
He's not unfriendly
or anything,
I guess he just likes
to keep to himself.
I think he only gave me a spare set
of keys 'cause I gave him mine.
What?
Nothing. Just reminds me
of someone I know. Who is unfriendly.
Does George have a job?
He has a headhunting business
he runs from home.
Occasionally
he'll interview people here,
but he does most of it
over the phone.
Wow!
Yeah, he loves to cook.
And eat, obviously.
Four-course gourmet meals
almost every night,
sometimes for lunch, too.
Do you know if he ever uses
any unpasteurized cheese or wild game?
I'm not sure.
He gets all his groceries delivered
from that market down on Alden.
They'd probably know.
- He have any friends?
- No.
I mean, sometimes women
do come by.
Young, attractive, never the same one
twice, if you know what I mean.
I see.
There can't be many women
who'd wanna be with a guy like him.
It's usually worst
in the morning.
Especially
if I've slept on my arm.
If I sleep on my back
or with my arms out, I'm usually okay.
So your arm only hurts
after you lie on top of it all night.
Yeah.
Well, have you thought about,
I don't know, not doing that?
Yeah. But it's how I sleep,
it's how I've always slept.
Well, there's always surgery.
To do what? Like, clean out
some cartilage or something?
You're not sleeping on some cartilage,
you're sleeping on your arm.
You wanna remove my arm?
Well, it is your left.
You know, a guy's gotta sleep.
Are you insane?
I see spending a night in jail
hasn't humbled you a bit.
While following
my every move is flattering,
a single rose on my doorstep
each morning would be more enticing.
Just bringing your boss
up to speed,
which I guess
you didn't feel was necessary.
You gonna add that
to my list of charges?
People who are innocent
tend not to try to hide their arrest.
Is that based on your years of
experience arresting innocent people?
The way
you're going at that gum,
it's obviously not having
the desired effect.
You're the addict. You're gonna be back
on the butts in a month.
You're just taking out your frustration
on me 'cause my meds actually work.
Why don't you quit
while you're ahead.
Before you end up
as a security guard
working the night shift
at some strip mall.
I think working around
a bunch of nurses
has given you a false sense
of your ability to intimidate.
Who was that?
Apparently Cuddy's widened
her sperm donor search
to include Neanderthals.
Cuddy's looking for
a sperm donor?
It was a joke.
Like Cuddy would ever want a kid.
Or a kid would ever want Cuddy.
Hello, that's why it's funny!
Why are you guys here?
It's not pickwick's.
Intubation and steroids
have had no effect.
Except maybe to cause
whatever it is to get worse.
He's got a fever now.
What'd you find out?
That you and George have the same taste
in home furnishings and women.
Danish Modern
and Russian gymnasts?
Pianos and prostitutes.
We should do an LP
and look for neurosyphilis.
- It's not syphilis.
- How do you know?
Because you get STDs
from people you trust,
people you don't feel
the need to protect yourself from.
Whatever he has is connected to his gut,
not what's below it.
MRI his brain, look for clots.
Weight limit
on the MRI machine is 450 pounds.
So do a CT.
Limit's 350.
Then just start treatment.
If we give him blood thinners
and the coma's caused
by a bleed instead of a clot,
we could kill him.
Either start treatment
or start building a stronger MRI.
Whatever you do, do it fast.
The longer
he stays in the coma,
the less likely it is
he'll ever wake up.
There's no way.
His head's the only part
that we have to get in the machine.
If we can just
get him on the table...
We get him on the table,
we break the table.
We break the table,
hospital's out a million dollars
and we're out of our jobs.
The weight limit's
obviously just an estimation.
It's not like if it can hold
450 pounds fine,
it'll instantly collapse
under 451.
He's not one pound over,
he's 150 pounds over.
I don't care! He still deserves the
same standard of care as anyone else.
Then you believe the machine
will stand on principle.
You guys gonna help or not?
How much does this guy weigh?
- 440.
- Looks like a lot more than that.
It's 'cause he's lying down.
You guys ready?
One, two, three.
- Here.
- What's this?
I made some calls for you.
The guy's the best criminal attorney
in Princeton.
Thanks, but I don't need it.
I assume
you told Inspector Clouseau
that I have a valid prescription
for the Vicodin.
Yeah, and I assume you did as well.
Did it make a difference?
The guy's pissed!
And with the DEA now treating
pain doctors like Colombian...
I'm not a pain doctor,
I'm a pain patient.
Tell it to your lawyer.
No midline shifts,
no bleeds, clots, infarcts.
I don't see any edema, either.
So what do we do now?
An LP.
Even if it's not an STD, a fever points
toward some sort of infection.
I'm not sure we can do an LP
on a guy his size.
What?
You have to be able to palpate the spine
to know where to go.
We could use fluoroscopy
to guide us.
He still wouldn't be able
to bring his knees up and bend forward
in order to open the space
between...
George, it's all right,
you're in a hospital!
Calm down, man, calm down!
- Get him out already!
- I'm trying!
Come on!
We're gonna get you out!
We still have no idea
why he was in the coma to begin with.
Or why he woke up.
It was probably
just some sort of head trauma
and we missed the swelling
because, well,
his head's already swollen.
Bump on the noggin
doesn't explain the fever.
An infection made worse by the steroids
we gave him for pickwick's does.
He's not worse, he's better.
We just replaced
the last MRI you broke.
Referring to the fund-raising funbags
by the royal "we" now?
Let me explain
cause and effect to you.
I specifically told them
to skip the boring testing part
and jump right to
the dangerous treatment.
You blow stuff up,
makes my life miserable,
makes me need to make
your life miserable.
He's telling the truth.
Kids these days, got no respect
for other people's property.
Repairmen cost less
than lawyers.
Morbid obesity
is a legally defined disability,
which means
if we'd denied access to the MRI,
he could have sued us for discrimination
as well as malpractice.
This was your idea?
Yeah.
Looks like Cameron's gonna be having
a lot more ideas in future.
Who knew that being bloated and bitchy
could actually come in handy?
- Shut up.
- What if it is hormones?
It's not hormones.
I'm talking about George.
Acute adrenal insufficiency
could cause a temporary coma.
A glandular problem would cause
his temperature to be low, not high.
Maybe the fever's not related.
If it's not related,
there's nothing to talk about.
We should do
an ACTH stimulation test
and check his skin
for acanthosis nigricans.
Or the fever is related
and so are the prostitutes.
We should do a full STD panel
and check his genitals for chancres.
We should do nothing.
Just keep him a couple of days
for observation.
If he doesn't get any worse,
it was probably just a hematoma
that dissipated on its own.
Or we do all of the above.
You check his belly
for patches.
You check underneath for sores.
And you just sit on your ass.
Acanthosis nigricans
is a hyperpigmentation of the skin,
usually indicates some sort
of hormonal imbalance.
There's nothing wrong
with my hormones.
It's the first thing every doctor
I've ever gone to has checked.
Then it's the blood pressure,
then it's gotta be diabetes.
They all figure there's gotta be
something wrong with me.
You having any problems
with your vision?
No, I have nystagmus.
I've had it since birth, I'm fine.
You're not fine.
You were in a coma for two days.
There's something wrong
with you.
Was something wrong with me,
now I'm better, now I'd like to go home.
A coma's not like
a stomach ache.
You can't just shrug it off
and hope it's not anything serious.
My company places
a lot of insurance executives.
There are over 300,000 deaths
caused each year by medical mistakes
and hospital-associated infections.
I'll come in for tests.
There are over 400,000 deaths
caused by obesity-related illnesses.
The CDC says those figures
are a gross overestimation.
George, you ever notice
you don't see a lot of obese old men?
If I'm gonna
have a heart attack,
I would rather it be caused
by a perfect pan-roasted ris de veau
than running 26 miles for no reason
other than to brag that I can do it.
Or to have an MRI machine
break in the middle of a procedure!
We're sorry about that.
It was the only way to rule out
a stroke or brain hemorrhage.
And now that you have,
when can I go?
It's probably her mom.
I bet she's huge.
She's from the Midwest.
Since when do you eat beets?
Since I was five.
And who are we talking about?
You know, just in case you need me
to chime in and tell you
you're a lunatic at some point?
Cameron. She's lying,
destroying hospital equipment,
telling Cuddy off.
I gotta find out
where she got the Fat Scratch Fever.
Yeah, you definitely better
get to the bottom of that.
I heard Cuddy gave you
the name of a lawyer.
Or it could just be pity. She feels
guilty about being born beautiful.
So she overcompensates
by being nice to ugly people.
Would explain why
she gets along so well with you.
From what I hear,
the patient reminds her of you, not me.
Call the lawyer.
Cameron sees a clump of dirt
and she thinks of me.
Or a lump of something else.
You're a lunatic. Call the lawyer.
- Very mature.
- You started it.
Skin exam and ACTH stimulation test
were both normal.
He has nystagmus
but it's congenital.
No way it's related
to the coma.
You say, "No way,"
I say... Yeah, no way.
Blood and urine were negative
for chlamydia, herpes, and syphilis.
Looks like
we got ourselves a mystery.
Not for long.
He wants to be discharged.
Oh, sure.
Places to go, people to eat.
He insists his chance of dying
from a hospital-acquired
infection
is greater than him dying
from whatever caused his coma.
Did you tell him that statistics
also say that he's a big, fat idiot?
- Yeah, I did.
- He's not backing down.
He says if we don't discharge him,
he'll leave AMA.
Selectively rational,
stubborn, uncooperative,
maybe you ought to
check his leg.
Do you see what he did there?
The patient's like me.
The patient's three mes.
If I were him...
Maybe it's not
such a mystery after all.
Enjoying your Salisbury steak?
Putting chopped parsley
in a hamburger
does not
a Salisbury steak make.
You must be Dr. House.
And you must be
full of baloney. A lot of it.
Right. Fat joke. Always fun.
The only people
you can still make fun of.
And Christians.
Oh, and black people.
No one in their right mind
comes out of a coma
and immediately asks to go home
with an unknown condition,
which means that either
you're not in your right mind
or it's not
an unknown condition.
So, what is it?
You tried to off yourself?
You figure I'm fat,
therefore I hate myself.
Yeah, that's a huge leap
of logic.
I don't wanna die.
I just don't wanna be here.
Then it's a condition
you've already had diagnosed,
or it's something
you know you've inherited.
Let's see, your stomach
has deep-seated feelings
of abandonment
written all over it,
which points toward
sexual abuse.
While a fear of hospitals, that points
to a more specific traumatic event.
So I'm gonna say, your mom
in the hospital with a candlestick.
And by candlestick, of course,
I mean inherited OTC deficiency.
My parents are both alive and well
and living in Boca Raton.
Thyrotoxic periodic paralysis?
I have no idea what that is.
- Leukoencephalopathy.
- Will you stop!
If I knew what was wrong,
I would tell you.
I'm not an imbecile,
and I'm not miserable.
I'm just overweight.
What?
When?
To be continued.
What are you doing here?
Executing a search
of the premises.
When you...
When you got bailed out
before we could get a judge
to approve this,
I almost didn't bother.
I thought for sure you'd come
straight home and throw everything out.
Rookie mistake. Never underestimate
the stupidity of an addict.
There's gotta be
over 600 Vicodin in here.
Which most DAs would say
proves intent to traffic.
Even if all you really intended was
to simply be wasted 24/7
while practicing medicine.
In case you hadn't noticed,
those are prescription bottles.
I'm not an expert
on linguistics per se,
but I think that means
they were prescribed.
All these
were legally prescribed
to a man who's in constant pain
but never misses a day of work?
Has it ever occurred to you
that's why I don't miss a day?
Yeah. Yeah, crossed my mind.
Among other things.
Like what an unprofessional,
unethical, arrogant ass you are.
Because if you're unprofessional
in one area,
it only makes sense.
Now maybe just a few of these
are in someone else's name.
Forged prescription,
or just, um, swiped from the pharmacy
when nobody's looking.
No, but, well,
you wouldn't do that. Right?
Send him home.
Why? You think he's healthy?
Either I'm right,
he knows what's wrong,
he's just too stubborn to admit it,
or I was right
and it's pickwick's.
The treatment
just had a delayed effect.
You don't have
delayed effects to oxygen.
And Pickwick's
doesn't explain the fever.
Being engulfed
in an electric blanket of blubber
could explain the fever.
Yesterday you insisted
we keep him here because of the fever.
We have no idea
what's wrong with the guy.
For all we know
he could be dead in 12 hours.
He does not want our help.
Which means
he doesn't want your help.
He's obviously just rationalizing.
And so are you!
You would never give up
this easy
if you weren't so busy dealing with
your own personal problems.
Send him home.
What did you tell that cop?
- Nothing.
- Nothing as in nothing?
Or as in nothing
that could cause him to think
I have a stash in my apartment?
He called to see if I prescribed
the pills, I said yes. That's all.
- Obviously not.
- What happened?
He searched my house,
found a buttload of pills.
Guy's gotta be prepared
for a rainy day.
Last I checked pharmacies
were still open when it rained.
And because I never know when
you're gonna be in one of your moods
- and cut me off.
- Oh, it's my fault.
I'm not the one
who talked to the cop.
Well, I'm not the one
who put a thermometer in his rectum.
So stop yelling at me
and start talking to your lawyer.
Is there someone
who can check on you?
Oh, don't worry.
There's gonna be a whole crew
of carpenters in my bedroom
for the next week at least.
You know, there's an Overeaters
Anonymous meeting here at the hospital.
If I wanted to jump out of airplanes
or climb Mount Everest,
would you be telling me
to go to Daredevils Anonymous?
I would be worried about you
just like I am now.
Don't be.
I enjoy food.
I like cooking it, I like looking at it,
I like smelling it,
and I especially
like eating it.
Listen, whatever happens
is gonna happen.
Ultimately it's all
out of our control anyway.
Why doesn't
that philosophy apply
to medical mistakes and
hospital-acquired infections as well?
I'm a complicated man,
Dr. Cameron.
But don't worry, I plan on staying
that way for a long time.
Wait, wait, let us take you
all the way outside.
I'm fine.
It doesn't matter,
it's hospital rules.
Oh, screw the rules.
I've been on my back for four days.
I need the exercise, right?
George, come on,
let us just take you to the taxi.
Don't worry, I may not be able
to climb Everest, but I can walk, okay?
- George...
- Now enough already.
George, are you all right?
George? You all right? George?
Disorientation
and loss of balance
could mean a neurofibromatosis.
- Where's Chase?
- Don't know.
Haven't seen him since you told him
to sit on his ass yesterday.
Interesting.
NF2 is also inherited,
which means I was right.
You kept saying
it was pickwick's.
Between the first pickwick's
and the second pickwick's,
I said it was inherited.
Whatever.
NF2 doesn't explain fever.
I think we should focus
on the coma and the fever.
Why? The disorientation
and loss of balance are more recent.
The coma was
the most severe symptom.
But he's not in the coma anymore
and he is disoriented.
No, he's not.
We have a rather large piece
of tempered glass that begs to differ.
I just mean it's not connected.
You don't know that.
Yeah, I do.
How could you possibly know...
Because I did it!
I didn't think
he should be discharged,
so I gave him
three grams of phenytoin.
I wasn't gonna just
let him leave.
But you were okay with him
crashing through a glass wall?
I tried to keep him in the wheelchair,
but he's tough to stop.
Nice audible, Peyton.
So, what do we do now?
Discharge report says
he didn't eat his breakfast.
Humpty Dumpty didn't get to be the size
of all the king's horses
by skipping
the most important meal of the day.
What causes coma, fever,
and loss of appetite?
It can't be Chagas',
he's never been outside the country.
But his stomach has.
The food we eat no longer
comes from America's heartland.
It comes from South America's
deforested jungle land
where lettuce now grows
and lettuce pickers now poop.
Get a sample of his CSF
before the bugs that are now feasting
on his brain move on to dessert.
How are we gonna do that?
He's too big to do an LP.
So go straight to the source.
You wanna drill a hole
in my head?
It's the only way.
It's gotta be something
other than a parasite.
I buy my produce at the best market
in town and I always wash it.
Leafy vegetables
can suck contaminated water
through their roots
right into the plant.
You could have
washed them in chlorine
and it still
wouldn't have mattered.
Then other people
would be sick as well.
The parasites could have been
on only a few items,
or maybe they just didn't eat
as much as you did.
It's always
about my weight, isn't it?
Why can't you people
come up with one theory...
This one fits, George.
It explains your coma,
your fever, your loss of appetite...
And the disorientation?
It's all explained.
And if we don't treat it
while it's still in the acute stage,
it'll be too late.
It could go on to infect your heart,
intestines, esophagus...
This is what I get
for eating salad.
Suction.
Aspirator.
Your turn.
Irrigation.
Sponge.
What did you do?
Nothing. Why, what's wrong?
I can't see.
Vision's blurry
or you've lost...
I didn't lose it,
you took it from me!
- George, calm down.
- I can't see!
Give me some lorazepam!
- What did you do to me?
- Hold still!
- George! George!
- What's going on?
- No. No. Calm down!
- What did you do to me?
There's no inflammation in
the optic nerve and his retina's intact.
The blindness has to have been caused
by something in his brain.
And not surprisingly
there was no sign of Chagas'
or any other
parasites in his CSF.
So we've ruled out his parents,
prostitutes, the arugula.
Means either...
I took the sample
from the prefrontal.
I was never anywhere
near his visual cortex.
Or you missed a tumor
on the MRI.
Not a chance,
the MRI was clean.
- You mind?
- Where are you going?
To get a $400 butt plug.
What about George?
He's gonna have to
get his own. Come on.
Let's see if we can
get this thing figured out
by the time
we get to the elevator.
It could be MS.
Would explain the coma,
the blindness,
loss of balance, and the fever.
Could also explain
his lack of concern for his health.
MS can cause
excessive cheerfulness.
Yeah, he's a delight.
You don't get to MS
with coma as the first symptom.
Blindness plus coma
says diabetes. Just in time.
No. Blood sugar, urine dip stick
and hemoglobin A1c are normal.
Were normal when you tested.
He's been in and out of a coma,
whatever's going on
is waxing and waning,
unlike his pants size,
which only waxes.
Which also points to diabetes.
Test him again.
And this time add
a glucose tolerance test and an HEC.
We already have a CSF sample,
we might as well check it for proteins
to rule out MS first.
Agreed. Except for the part
about doing it first.
Where are you going?
The butt plug was my way of saying,
"Mind your own business."
Apparently too subtle.
George, all it is
is sugar water, I promise.
Just because I'm overweight
doesn't make me diabetic!
You tested me,
everybody's tested me.
Sometimes the blood sugar levels
can fluctuate,
make it difficult to diagnose.
You stuck a needle in my brain
and 10 seconds later I was blind!
How is that difficult
to diagnose?
Who the hell knows
what else you guys done to me?
- I should have never come here!
- You didn't come here,
you were brought here because you were
in a coma and barely alive.
We didn't do that to you,
you need to let us figure out what did.
For someone who insists
he enjoys life as much as you do,
you certainly don't seem willing
to do much to prolong it.
Yeah,
because I don't agree with the brilliant
doctors, suddenly I'm suicidal!
Refusing to cooperate with us
does not make you suicidal,
it makes you an idiot.
You think
we want to see you blind or in a coma?
I've been fat all my life.
I've only been sick
for the past few days.
You look for a disease
that has nothing to do with my size,
and I will help you.
Otherwise, leave me alone.
Speeding, DUI,
reckless driving,
resisting arrest,
possession of a class three narcotic.
And now it looks like
they've added
another possession with intent
to traffic charge as well.
They found some pills
at your house.
All of which
I had a prescription for.
That's a lot of pills.
I'm in a lot of pain.
This is all because some cop
came into the clinic,
I was rude to him,
this is his way of getting back at me.
You've made it pretty easy.
His insane reaction to a simple
rectal thermometer reading
probably says a lot more
about his mother than it says about me.
I'm inclined to think
your particular charm
may not be immediately
appreciated by a jury.
I'm not interested
in a plea bargain.
It's your best bet
to make this go away.
There is no this.
There's a him.
The only thing I'm guilty of
is humiliating a bully.
I wasn't speeding,
I wasn't impaired, I didn't resist,
and I certainly was not
distributing narcotics
to anyone but myself,
because I need those narcotics.
Five grand retainer.
If we end up going to trial, there'll
be another 30 due before the first day.
My hourly is 450.
That work for you?
What'd your lawyer say?
I looked up butt plug
in a legal dictionary. What'd he say?
That a smile like mine
can't lose.
What did the tests say?
You were right about MS.
No myelin basic proteins in his CSF.
- What about diabetes?
- Don't know.
He says
we only think it's diabetes
because of his weight,
won't let us test him.
So, you would rather be a blind invalid
than admit the fact
that maybe you might have
a little problem with overeating.
By a little problem, of course,
I mean you've eaten yourself
half to death.
And you would rather let me die
than consider the fact
that whatever is wrong with me
has nothing to do with my weight.
I go where the symptoms
tell me to go.
And right now
they're asking why this stuff
is the first thing
you've ever refused to swallow.
I am not diabetic.
Grocery stores giving away medical
degrees with the free turkeys now?
The sooner you drink this,
the sooner I get to go waste my time
with something else.
Get the hell off of me!
No dessert
till you've finished your dinner!
George, just drink it!
Nurse!
Get this jackass off of me!
What the hell is going on?
Just trying to force
a horse to...
Let go!
What's going on?
Get X-rays of his hands.
Then bronc him, do a sputum cytology
and check his CSF
for anti-hu antibodies.
How are we gonna get him
to do all that,
we can't even get him to drink
a bottle of sugar water?
Tell him that lung cancer
is in no way connected to obesity.
You don't think
he'll realize we're lying?
You're not. Lung cancer's
got nothing to do with obesity.
I meant about him
having lung cancer.
You didn't notice his fingers?
I noticed they were fat.
You should have pissed him off,
he would have grabbed you.
Then you would have
felt the bones,
they're not just fat,
they're clubbed.
George,
it's me.
Your tests were positive.
You have a small cell
lung carcinoma.
It caused a paraneoplastic
neurologic syndrome,
which in turn
caused your blindness and coma.
The cancer's metastasized
to your lymph nodes.
It's inoperable,
but there are
radiation treatments available.
They might give you
a few more months.
I never smoked.
C'est la vie.
You were right.
- So was he.
- He said, "C'est la vie."
He's a complicated man.
What about you?
What are you gonna do
about your problem?
Nothing. Just got a call
from my lawyer.
He gave the DA copies
of my prescriptions.
Soon as they confirm
they're bona fides,
they're gonna drop the possession,
DUI and resisting arrest.
Soon as I pay
my $85 speeding ticket
and the impound fine,
I get my bike back.
I guess that's good.
- You guess?
- No, it's good.
You get to keep going
like you always have.
All right, I give up.
Who was it?
Who in your family
had the weight problem?
You think I can only care
about a patient
if I know someone else
who's been through the same thing?
You care for everybody.
You only lie
and stand up to Cuddy for a few.
You lie for everybody
and only care about a few.
You're avoiding the question.
I like damaged people,
remember?
It explains everything I do.
Almost everything.
It wasn't you, was it?
- Does it matter?
- Nope, but it'd be interesting.
Sorry to disappoint you,
but sometimes the answers
just aren't that simple.
I know he can be a real ass,
and he has no problem lying
when it serves him,
but he's not lying
about the pain.
He needs the medication,
which is why I prescribed it.
All of it.
Well, I see a lot of cases
where people who have
real injuries end up getting addicted.
And then, well, things kind of
spiral out of control.
And lives get ruined,
and not just their own.
I don't know what else
to tell you.
What about these?
This is getting...
If it's got my name on it,
it's a legit scrip.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
Because the signatures on these
look a little different
than the signatures on those.
You look surprised.
No, I'm just...
I hadn't thought about it.
I do sign my name differently sometimes.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
I just, I guess get bored
signing it the same way.
You know what they say
about doctors' handwriting.
I'm gonna give you a moment
to reconsider that answer.
Because if you are,
for some reason, mistaken,
we will find out,
and that will not be good for you.
Or Dr. House.
I am sure. Absolutely.
All right.
I guess that's it, then.
Thank you for your help.
Okay, no problem.