- See you Tuesday.
- How about right now?
What? What?
You wanna throw in the towel?
No, I don't wanna
throw in the... towel!
I thought that's what you said!
I'm not upset about anything!
Where the... are we going?
What are you doing down here?
I thought you usually
had lunch with Coma Guy.
This is Vegetative State Guy.
Better company.
Hey, hey, tell him
about those Sherpas
you dropped acid with
in Saint Patrick's Cathedral.
You stole my prescription pad
and you forged my name.
- What did you tell the cop?
- I lied.
They'd have put you away
for 10 years,
after they took your license
to practice medicine.
So, everything's good, then.
I lied. To the cops.
There is no case
unless they can prove
that either I got the drugs illegally
or I sold them illegally.
I didn't do the second,
you lied about the first. Game over.
Yeah, Tritter's just playing.
He's gonna see how clever you are
and then just walk away.
The important thing is
that you keep prescribing
the same amount of drugs to me
or it'll look suspicious.
Here's another way
to look at it,
having forced me
to lie to the police,
your first concern
is securing your drug connection.
Joining my father for lunch?
I should have called ahead
for a table.
Dr. House was just...
Enjoying a Reuben.
It's okay.
After 10 years, anything that'll
get doctors in the same room as...
- What are you doing?
- Nothing.
What are you doing?
Chips?
Wanna see something
really cool?
I saw you leaving last Tuesday.
You practically
tripped over two guys on your way out,
but you had no problem
opening doors.
It's called akinetopsia.
You can't see things
when they move.
Now, since you haven't been hit by
a bus, I assume that it's intermittent.
It's probably
accompanied by seizures,
which made me think that
I could set one off by flashing the...
God, I love this family.
I can see fine now.
I've had seizures before.
Most of the time they're small.
Doctors ran me through all the tests.
Couldn't find anything.
Any history of epilepsy
in your family?
The only things I know
that run in my family are
a lot of chutzpah
and the ability to sleep for 10 years.
Although
I'm not really an expert.
Dad never really liked
my mother's side of the family,
and after she died and he came here
I was raised by a guardian.
I wouldn't even know
how to get in touch with them.
How about your father's side
of the family?
Any relatives
we could speak with?
My father was an only child.
And my grandparents are dead.
Well, who did you put down
as the person the hospital
should contact in an emergency?
I left it blank.
There's gotta be someone,
a friend...
I have plenty of friends.
Just no one that would care
if I was here.
Say, do you mind passing me
my backpack?
Hair of the dog.
Could be infection.
Or a brain tumor.
Says he had a CT.
What's wrong
with the simplest explanation? Trauma?
He didn't report any injuries.
He didn't report
being an alcoholic, either.
Drinking equals falling down
equals trauma equals...
Maybe it's inherited.
How would you jump to genetics
from his EEG?
All you've got are some vaguely
epileptiform waves.
It's not his EEG.
It's his father's.
When it comes to cortical seizures,
like father, like son.
Small seizures
aren't unheard of
in a patient
in a vegetative state.
Similarities
are interesting, though.
What caused
the vegetative state?
His house burned down.
Went back in to get his wife,
firefighters
found him unconscious
three feet from the bedroom,
asphyxiated.
Not an inherited condition.
Test his DNA. Start with
adrenomyeloneuropathy.
Check out the home.
He has a single bed.
They still make single beds?
It could mean
he just doesn't have sex,
though there were condoms
in the apartment.
House asked you to check out
the home for toxins.
No mold, no leaks, no pets.
MRI and LP
are both inconclusive.
Infection's still possible,
tumor's less likely, but...
- DNA?
- The adrenomyeloneuropathy test
- was negative.
- DNA test again.
Try Unverricht-Lundborg
and late-onset Lafora's.
Genetic tests take forever.
You can't keep testing
for every inherited condition
you think it might be.
Well, not me.
I'll be leaving early. But you guys can.
You said no one's been sick but
what about delivery people, repair guy?
I wouldn't know.
I work from home.
Haven't been to the office
in over a month.
Visitors?
Haven't had any.
The only person
I've seen in the last week
was the pizza delivery guy
and he looked pretty healthy.
There's gotta be someone
you're close to.
Actually, the person
I see most often is my father.
He's asleep
so he can't stop me.
What is it?
I'm just feeling
a little nauseous.
I think his liver's failing.
God. Does that mean that I'm...
We need a central line kit,
two units of packed red blood cells
type O Negative.
He's unconscious
and heading for a coma.
He's at a four
on the RLAS scale.
Stop all treatment.
You think this is a reaction
to our meds?
Well, they're obviously
not helping.
Given the fact
that he's an alcoholic,
there's a good chance
his liver wasn't so hot when he came in.
Anti-seizure drugs could have
just pushed him over the edge.
We take him off those meds,
what do we put him on?
I was hoping you'd know.
It may be academic,
I just started him on dialysis.
Kidney and liver failure.
Not too many people come back from that.
Trauma's out of the picture.
Could still be infection.
- Or neurological...
- Or genetic.
We need a better history.
Did you miss the part
where the patient lost consciousness?
L-dopa?
You're not waking Kyle.
You're waking his father.
I commend
your observational skills.
You have no reason to think
any amount of drugs
will wake a man from a coma.
Vegetative state. Much easier.
This guy's no Terri Schiavo,
his brain's all there, he moves around,
his muscles
have barely atrophied.
He's just waiting
for a fairy-tale kiss.
After I do that,
I'll stick a needle in him.
The amount of amphetamines alone
would be dangerous,
besides whatever the hell else
you've got in there.
There are reports
out of South Africa
about a pill that would temporarily
revive someone in a vegetative state.
You've all seen Awakenings,
made me cry.
I wanna cry.
Put the syringe down.
I can outdraw you,
mysterious stranger.
We don't experiment
on helpless patients.
Be reasonable.
There's no way this is gonna work.
Even if you woke him,
it would only be for a few hours.
A day, two at the most.
You're risking his life.
I'm risking getting sued,
that's the only objection here.
You'll be torturing him
and his family.
Well, good news for Legal, the only
family he's got is upstairs dying.
Hey!
I want this patient monitored
for the next 24 hours.
I want someone with him
at all times
to make sure
you didn't kill him.
I want your ass in my office.
God, I'm starving.
I could really go for a steak.
Do you know your name?
Do you know where you are?
Gabriel Wozniak.
I don't know the name of this hospital.
How much are three and five?
Eight.
Also known as half of 16,
a quarter of 32, two to the third power.
Coolest thing ever.
Any history of seizure
in your family?
- No.
- Liver disease?
No.
How long have I been here? I...
I got the feeling
it's been a long time.
Interesting.
Your internal clock
kept ticking.
How deep
does that awareness go?
Pick up scraps
of conversations?
Do you have the vague sense
that the hospital administrator
dresses like a trollop?
Or that the new Star Wars movies
were a disappointment?
I know my wife is dead.
I don't know
how long it's been.
Ten years.
What's the last thing
you remember?
The fire.
My wife was in the bedroom,
she had taken a sleeping pill.
I got Kyle out,
went back in for her.
I knew I didn't make it.
I'm sorry.
What about your wife's side of the
family? Any history of seizures there?
Your son Kyle
is a patient here.
I'm afraid his condition is serious.
He may be dying.
No seizure issues
on my wife's side, either.
What about that steak?
Nobody ever answered me.
Rumor in the cafeteria
was Caustic Guy was waking up Coma Guy.
Technically,
Vegetative State Guy
was woken by,
yeah, Caustic Guy.
So what happened?
I gotta get him a steak
before I can ask him any more questions.
He doesn't wanna talk
about his son?
Didn't seem to emotionally register
that his son is sick.
Brain issue?
He was asphyxiated,
spent 10 years as asparagus,
- who knows what damage is in there.
- It's possible.
Of course there's always
the simple explanation.
Maybe he just
doesn't like his son.
Only in your world
would that be simple.
The delusion
that fathering a child
installs a permanent geyser
of unconditional love...
Maybe your father's feelings
were conditional, not everyone's.
Well, of course,
that would play into
your romantic vision
of human...
In terms you would understand,
we have
an evolutionary incentive
to sacrifice for our offspring.
Our tribe, our friends.
Keep them safe.
Except for all the people
who don't.
Everything is conditional.
You just can't always
anticipate the conditions.
Mind if we talk
for a few minutes?
How many pills would you say
Dr. House takes a day?
I'm uncomfortable
setting a number.
Well, try.
Six.
A day?
Has he ever had you
write prescriptions for him?
No. What is it
you want me to say?
That he takes too many pills
and is a danger to the hospital,
or he takes too few because
he's selling them on the side?
Either one is ridiculous.
I meant the former.
You're wrong.
Can I ask what Dr. House has done
to deserve your loyalty?
He's not known as a great boss.
He's not even much of a friend.
Look how he left
Dr. Wilson holding the bag.
It's odd.
You don't know about that?
You defend him, and he won't even
tell you what's happening in his life.
I was paged.
We saw you with the cop.
- What'd he want?
- How many pills does House take,
did I ever write him
a prescription?
That sort of stuff.
- I told him six.
- A day or in a mouthful?
I was just hoping you guys
would stay consistent with...
He wants to talk to us, too?
You're next.
We've gotta tell House
what's going on.
- Tritter says no.
- Then no it is.
Cops have a thousand ways
to make life difficult for you.
Quick. What's the kid's status?
I gotta get back to our sleeper
before he goes looking
for the orgasmatron.
See, if that were rhetorical,
it would mean that I can just
turn around and leave now,
which I'm not doing,
from which you should deduce...
He's off all drugs
except the antibiotics.
His liver's just managing
to hang in there.
He's still sliding into coma.
Your barber sucks.
Hey, Coma Diet,
I could make a fortune.
Vegetative State Diet.
Who gave you your clothes?
Dr. Cuddy.
I guess I'll need
all new ones, anyway.
Everything went in the fire.
Don't worry about it.
We use recyclable clothes now.
Wear them once, then eat them.
Your son's measles vaccination,
do you remember if he had it,
what type it was?
Man, you're a piece of work,
you know that?
You weren't gonna tell me,
were you?
I don't need new clothes.
Dr. Cuddy says my body
will adjust to the drugs,
that I'll be
a vegetable again by tomorrow.
If I'm really lucky,
the day after.
Yeah.
If I've got a day to live,
I'm not gonna spend it in a hospital
room being grilled.
Come on, where you gonna go?
Your house burned down,
your wife's dead. Business was sold off.
The only thing you have left is down
the hall, heading for a liver biopsy.
Used to be this little hole in the wall
run by a guy named Giancarlo.
Made the best hoagies
in the world.
Real Italian rolls,
prosciutto, provolone...
How far is Atlantic City
from here?
You have one day to live,
and you want a sandwich?
People on death row
get a last meal.
The state provides it.
Who's providing for you?
You got a car? Money?
You're negotiating with me.
Take out another 100 for me.
And I need your car.
I'm not doing you any favors.
You'll get it back tomorrow.
Two days, max.
Road trip.
This is like trying
to control the weather,
but I'd prefer it
if you didn't eat in the car,
I just had it detailed.
- I drive.
- Oh, the hell he does.
Sure.
Aside from the fact he just woke up
from a vegetative state,
the guy doesn't have a license.
How about this?
Cops stop us, we lie.
You know how to do that. Chips.
It's all the drugs
pumping through his system.
Right now his reflexes are better
than Dale Earnhardt Jr's.
What's this? It says ipod.
I'm coming.
So let's talk about
toxic exposure.
What was wrong with the old colors?
I trusted brown.
Do the purple ones
have chocolate inside?
Raspberry cocaine.
This house that burned down,
where was it?
Moorestown, New Jersey.
Listen, I really need to know about the
candy because I'm allergic to berries.
You didn't mention that.
Is it significant?
No. So where else did you live?
List everywhere,
including vacations,
start with
when your wife got pregnant.
We lived in Jersey. Then we moved
to Jersey, from there, Jersey.
What are you waiting to hear?
About the little cottage in the Amazon
with the mosquitoes
and the lead paint all over the walls?
Yes.
You know what?
I didn't let you come along
so you could suck all the fun
out of my one day of life.
Well, you're outta luck,
because that's totally why I'm here.
Okay, rule change.
Person with the money makes the rules.
Or in this case,
the person who's friends with the person
with the money makes the rules.
Well, you want answers
more than I want money.
All right, so here's the game.
Ask whatever you want.
But for every question I answer,
you have to answer one first.
Why would you care
about anything I have to say?
The day before I died,
I was a successful man.
I had a factory
with over 200 employees.
People listened when I talked.
I liked power.
Now, the only power I have left
is the power to annoy you.
I took Wilson's assistant
for coffee.
- Why?
- Something Tritter said.
She told me the police think
that House stole Wilson's
prescription pad and forged his name.
You believe it?
- Do you?
- Well, absolutely I do.
I'm just checking
how naive you are.
He's not gonna steal his best friend's
pad, jeopardize his career.
Until his best friend
says no to him.
House is a junkie.
Junkies do whatever they have to do
to get what they need.
Kyle's down to a three
on the RLAS scale.
He's only showing
localized response.
I'll call House, tell him
we're gonna need an answer soon.
Get in your right lane for 295.
And pass me the Twizzlers.
- I'm curious...
- No, you're not.
Why would
a man's first instinct
be to drive away
from the only family he's got?
No, this is no time
for you to do your thing.
We don't care about his state of mind,
we don't care if he's happy.
This factory of yours,
what did you make?
So ask me a question.
I'm thinking.
Only six left, by the way.
So sign my name.
You don't need a doctor, you need a pen.
What is up with you two?
Wilson lied to the bulls
to keep me out of the big house.
Are you out of your mind?
Well, who's he gonna tell?
By tomorrow night he's gonna be
a mindless stalk of celery.
Since I answered that one,
by the way, my turn.
What did you make
in your factory?
Luxury boats.
Have you ever been in love?
Wow!
Going right for the clostes
with the embarrassing stuff. Good move.
Yes. Describe the boats.
Thirty-five to 65-foot hulls, twin
engines, parquet floors in the galley,
staterooms with queen beds.
- How'd you meet?
- She shot me.
These boats, I assume you used
mildew-resistant paint on the hulls?
Naturally. Shot you?
Paintball.
Doctors versus lawyers.
Did you ever take your son
to the factory?
Sure. He used to run all over the place,
but it was perfectly safe.
Ever love anybody else?
No more questions,
I got my answer.
While Dad's in the office,
his son's watching them spray-paint.
And what kid wears a mask?
Mercury specifically targets
the central nervous system.
You're saying this is my fault?
Mercury poisoning
explains the seizures
and the liver's like
a big soup strainer.
The soup runs through,
chicken dumplings stay.
For soup, read blood,
for chicken...
I get it, I get it. Mercury.
Sits more or less idle
until your kid
pours tequila shooters into his liver.
When the liver goes, takes out
the kidneys, explains everything.
Yeah, it's me.
Foreman, draw blood.
Test for mercury poisoning.
Chase,
start heavy metal chelation
while we're waiting
for results.
Chase isn't here.
I'll start the...
Where is he?
The lab.
How many pills
does he take a day?
It's hard to say,
pain levels vary over time...
Could be six, eight, ten.
Ever write
any prescriptions for him?
- Yes.
- Why?
Did he tell you to?
He asked me to.
Medicine attracts people
who are attracted to power.
I know how he hates
when he is defied by a patient.
I doubt he handles defiance
from his staff any better.
Now you correct me
if I'm wrong,
but I don't think
Dr. House asks for anything.
I think he takes it.
And I think that you are stuck
lying to the police
to cover up something
you didn't wanna do.
We have been up and down
St. James like a Monopoly car.
It's not here.
Giancarlo has left the building.
We can still turn around
and go back to Princeton.
No. We've come this far,
I'm getting the hoagie.
If your son does
have mercury poisoning,
there's a good chance
he'll respond to the chelation.
You might be able to have
a few minutes with him before you lapse.
Why are you so concerned
about me?
Deep inside Wilson believes
that if he cares enough
he'll never have to die.
Your behavior isn't normal.
And you would know normal?
What could he have done
that you won't forgive after 10 years?
When this is your last chance?
My son is what he is.
His mother's side,
all drunken losers.
He's gone the same way.
House told you drinking
had damaged your son's liver.
I just said that.
But you didn't hear
him say that
until after
we left the hospital.
So why did you leave?
Maybe your son
takes after your side.
Seizures and an allergy
to emotional connections.
Okay, okay, okay. Enough.
We're in Atlantic City
and my time's not up yet.
We find a hotel with a casino.
BP's starting to drop.
O2-sat's down to 70.
Point-three milligrams
of epi in.
What are you trying to do,
make him bleed faster?
Check the pulse.
It's not his liver.
It's the heart.
I understand he's a French chef
but I'm sure
he can handle this.
You need a 12-inch
Italian roll,
oregano vinegar, no,
not balsamic vinegar, oregano vinegar.
Quid pro quo, Clarice.
Game's still on.
I thought the answer
was mercury poisoning.
What other questions
would you care about?
If you each had
one day to live,
you'd look for one last meal and House
would look for one last answer.
No, can you just
send the ingredients up here
and I'll make it myself.
Last 10 years,
how much awareness did you have?
I don't know,
I knew it wasn't the next day.
I knew that...
I recognized your voice.
How often were you in my room?
No, you're wasting a question.
I have a better one.
Why steal my pad?
Oh, my God, you're right.
I'm an addict.
Thanks for opening my eyes.
No, I mean why my pad?
Foreman, Cameron and Chase's pads
are just as convenient.
But their association with you
is involuntary, they're employees.
I associate with you
through choice
and any relationship
that involves choice
you have to see
how far you can push before it breaks.
This is easy.
You ask the questions,
answer them and make tasty snacks.
Let's go try the casino.
And one day
our friendship will break
and that'll just prove your theory
that relationships are conditional
and you don't need
human connection or deserve it,
or whatever goes on
in that rat-maze of your brain.
Sorry, if I'd known
he was gonna be this annoying,
I would have stolen
Dr. Cameron's pad
and Dr. Foreman's car.
At least she appreciates
my brooding melancholy.
House's House of Whining,
state your complaint.
The patient's BP
just dropped like a stone.
Do an echo.
Mercury isn't likely
to damage the...
It didn't.
Mercury test was negative.
Do an echo.
I was wrong.
Your son's still dying.
I need to go over
every relative you ever had. Again.
And this time, forget their diseases,
just tell me how they died.
And we don't have time
to take turns.
You give me the answers,
you get a big one at the end.
You can go
for whatever you want.
Destroy my privacy, my dignity.
Your grandmother?
Heat exhaustion,
Fourth of July picnic.
The woman was 92.
Does anyone in the kitchen
know the hoagie shop
that used to be
on St. James Place?
You sister-in-law
with the diabetes.
As far as you know, is she still alive?
She's not. She was killed
in a traffic accident
driving home
from a Phillies game.
I'm sure a lot of beer
was consumed.
- The Phillies lost.
- Your father?
Old age.
Heart finally gave out.
Your wife's father?
Hit-and-run,
walking the incontinent dog.
Hi, do you guys deliver?
Let me put it this way,
if you deliver, there'll be
a $100 tip in it for you.
Excellent.
- Victory.
- The night is finally going my way.
Wilson, toss me a soda.
Shall we go somewhere to talk?
House is an ass.
But he obviously needs
pain medication,
and how much pain
one person feels
is not a call
the government should be making.
So you think
I'm a bureaucrat with a badge
following
some arbitrary guideline.
Yeah, I do.
So you're saying
I should just trust him. Do you?
- You're not qualified to make that...
- I'm not sure you are, either.
I've been a cop for 20 years.
And not a day goes by
that someone doesn't try
to sell me some self-serving story.
If you had my job, you'd know.
Everybody lies.
I think
you've run out of relatives.
So, it's my turn.
Why did you become a doctor?
That's the big question?
I give you complete license
to humiliate me
and that's the best you can do.
Well, okay, let's discuss
the wonder of the human body.
No, no, no.
You're a curious guy.
You like to figure things out,
why not go into research?
Why work with people when you
obviously hate people?
Oedipal fixation.
I was seeking my mother's love
and she thought that Ben Casey
was just the dreamiest...
Okay, fine. You don't think
you'll need any more answers from me?
Give me a hard time.
When I was 14,
my father was stationed
in Japan.
I went rock-climbing
with this kid from school.
He fell and got injured
and I had to bring him to the hospital.
And we came in through
the wrong entrance
and passed this guy
in the hall.
He was a janitor.
My friend came down
with an infection
and the doctors didn't know
what to do.
So they brought in
the janitor.
He was a doctor.
And a buraku.
One of Japan's untouchables.
His ancestors
had been slaughterers, gravediggers.
And this guy,
he knew that he wasn't
accepted by the staff, didn't even try.
He didn't dress well,
he didn't pretend to be one of them.
The people around that place,
they didn't think
he had anything they wanted,
except when they needed him.
Because he was right.
Which meant
that nothing else mattered.
And they had to listen to him.
Thank you.
Need 20 milligrams of diazepam
in a syringe.
Heartbeat's irregular
and accelerating.
- He's at 200.
- He's gonna crash.
Allergic reaction
to the diazepam?
Better hope so.
It's either that
or his heart's done.
What happened
on the night of the fire?
Yeah. I'm sure it's a stressful,
emotional question.
Suck it up.
My wife had taken a sleeping pill
and gone to bed.
It was Christmas Eve.
I let Kyle pop corn
in the fireplace.
He managed to knock loose
some tinder.
Wrapping paper caught on fire.
It spread so fast.
I got Kyle out and...
When I went back in for...
You're a disappointment.
You act as though
you don't need anybody, you...
You just blame your son
for what happened.
I don't blame him.
He was a 12-year-old boy.
You don't blame a kid
for an accident.
Then what are we doing here?
Why aren't you with him?
Because it wouldn't matter.
I failed
to keep my family safe.
I couldn't stop the fire,
I couldn't save my wife,
now you want me to stick around watching
while I fail to save my son.
Thank you so much
for waking me up.
How did your son
dislodge the tinder?
God...
He dropped the popcorn tray.
He had been complaining it was
too heavy, I should have listened.
And the hit-and-run,
walking the pissy dog.
That happen at night?
I think so, yeah, why?
Car accident
after the Phillies lost.
Night game?
Ragged-red fiber.
It's an inherited condition.
Dropping things, muscle weakness,
poor night vision.
Makes people seem uncoordinated,
accident-prone, careless.
It's transmitted
in mitochondrial DNA
so it only passes
through the mother.
Your wife's family
weren't drunks, they were sick.
It wouldn't have
affected his liver.
The kid is a drunk.
He thinks that
he killed his mother
and turned his father
into a vegetable.
I might have
a few shots myself.
Foreman.
Test his DNA
for ragged-red fiber.
- It's not gonna...
- Here's a thought.
Why don't we not assume that the test
is negative until we actually do it?
House, the kid
has severe cardiomyopathy.
Alcoholic,
no shot at a transplant.
So yeah, maybe you figured out why,
good for you, but
he's gonna die anyway.
I want to give Kyle my heart.
This thing, whatever it is,
you said he gets it from the mother.
My heart's fine.
And it could go on being fine
for the rest of your life.
Yeah, it's not like he's gonna
do anything with it.
Well, you woke him up once,
maybe someone'll come up
with some other answer.
We've both seen breakthroughs
no one expected.
And ragged-red fiber's
treatable, but not curable.
Even if he gets your heart,
there's no guarantee.
He's my kid.
No!
Did you really expect
a different answer?
We have arranged transplants
before when a patient is near death.
Except he isn't near death, he's saying,
"Kill me and cut out my heart."
Are you out of your mind?
Fine.
I'll think of something else.
I'm sorry.
Wilson, get out.
No.
You lied to the cops
enough for me.
Maybe I don't wanna
push this till it breaks.
Pills are the simplest.
Hanging has less chance
of damaging the heart.
I'm okay with pain.
Strangulation is better
than breaking your neck,
which means this'll be slow.
I wouldn't get to see him
even if we got in the car right now
and broke the speed limit driving back,
would I?
No.
Tell him...
I don't know what to tell him.
I think it's my turn
to ask a question, isn't it?
I don't think so.
'Cause you just asked me that thing
about the speed limit.
What do you wanna know?
If you could hear one thing
from your father, what would it be?
It wouldn't help you.
Try me.
I'd want him to say,
"You were right."
"You did the right thing."
Yeah. It doesn't help.
- Hi.
I'm Dr. Wilson.
I'm Mrs. Schaffer.
I'm from Princeton.
My husband and I and our three children
live in Philadelphia.
So, do you like to swing?
No.
Well, if you
change your mind, I'm in...
House? House?
Is it room 622, 642?
622.
- 662.
- Yeah.
Alibi.
I figured.
They found an open bottle of aspirin
by the body.
Lucky he had a headache,
reduced trauma to the heart in transit.
Lucky.
That can't be all.
Well, you got a heart
out of it.
How many organs
do you want from the guy?
I mean, my father
must have said something.
He couldn't just...
He must have given you
some kind of a message for me.
He said you were right.
You did the right thing.
Right about what?
What does that mean?
How would I know?
He's your dad.
You know what I found interesting
about this case?
That it proved that people
can love unconditionally
and you can tell yourself
it's not true,
but you'll just end up
in a hotel room in Atlantic City
asking someone
to cut your heart out?
The hoagie.
You thought this guy
was emotionally confused,
and that the hoagie
was just a mask
to hide his real feelings
toward his son.
It was.
Did you know Tritter was talking
to your team while we were away?
Yeah.
And yet you moved
Heaven and Earth
to get him that mask
with mustard and prosciutto.
Which one of them told you?
All of them.
Which means that none of them
said anything I have to worry about.
Back to the hoagie.
You think that
my addiction's out of hand.
Your need to be needed is so strong
that you'll give people what they want,
what they need,
what they think they need.
I don't think my enabling is anything
you should be complaining about.
Yes, my name
is Dr. James Wilson,
account number 835687.
The ATM says I've got zero...
What does that mean, a hold?
Yeah, okay, thanks.
My accounts have been frozen
as part of a police investigation.
They can't keep
your money forever.
No, they can keep it till I agree
to help send you to prison for 10 years.
You're getting dinner.