1
00:00:03,405 --> 00:00:05,538
Don't you have a job or something?

2
00:00:05,574 --> 00:00:07,136
Yeah, on a freelance cargo ship.

3
00:00:07,139 --> 00:00:08,574
We go to Hong Kong, Spain,

4
00:00:08,610 --> 00:00:10,972
Buenos Aires, basically
wherever the boss tells us.

5
00:00:10,975 --> 00:00:12,244
Corrupt son of a bitch.

6
00:00:12,280 --> 00:00:14,184
We've awoken something,
something people are trying to

7
00:00:14,186 --> 00:00:15,214
hide about Michael.

8
00:00:15,250 --> 00:00:16,749
Who the hell is this Poseidon guy?

9
00:00:16,785 --> 00:00:18,117
A psychopath.

10
00:00:18,153 --> 00:00:20,212
A frustrated policy wonk

11
00:00:20,215 --> 00:00:22,281
in the CIA who created a cell

12
00:00:22,284 --> 00:00:25,090
within the CIA called 21-Void.

13
00:00:25,126 --> 00:00:26,625
And they needed my help

14
00:00:26,661 --> 00:00:27,860
breaking out people in prison

15
00:00:27,896 --> 00:00:29,629
all over the world.

16
00:00:29,632 --> 00:00:30,518
Before he was killed,

17
00:00:30,521 --> 00:00:32,665
Kellerman had been looking into 21-Void.

18
00:00:32,701 --> 00:00:34,513
I need you to look into the possibility

19
00:00:34,516 --> 00:00:36,336
that there was an insider involved.

20
00:00:36,371 --> 00:00:38,071
I wasn't expecting a call at this hour.

21
00:00:38,106 --> 00:00:39,372
I think we need to meet soon.

22
00:00:39,407 --> 00:00:41,174
I was looking for where the man went.

23
00:00:41,209 --> 00:00:42,242
What man, baby?

24
00:00:42,277 --> 00:00:43,509
The man that gave me this.

25
00:00:43,545 --> 00:00:44,677
Michael.

26
00:00:44,713 --> 00:00:46,946
What are you into?

27
00:00:46,982 --> 00:00:48,514
Just tell us where you're headed.

28
00:00:48,550 --> 00:00:50,984
300 miles across the desert, Phaeacia.

29
00:00:51,019 --> 00:00:52,952
Autonomous zone. No ISIL.

30
00:00:52,988 --> 00:00:54,153
I can lead you there.

31
00:00:54,156 --> 00:00:56,169
Phaeacia, we found it!

32
00:01:09,070 --> 00:01:12,772
Back in the city, I
told you you would die.

33
00:01:12,807 --> 00:01:13,840
Michael.

34
00:01:13,875 --> 00:01:15,675
He poisoned me.

35
00:01:39,467 --> 00:01:43,036
It's incredible how good
you've gotten at drawing, Mike.

36
00:01:43,071 --> 00:01:45,705
Really, that's...

37
00:01:45,740 --> 00:01:47,640
that's so good.

38
00:01:47,676 --> 00:01:50,043
It's a Greek hero.

39
00:01:50,078 --> 00:01:51,678
He looks hurt.

40
00:01:51,713 --> 00:01:54,113
They all get hurt sooner or later.

41
00:01:54,149 --> 00:01:56,803
That's what's great about Greek heroes,

42
00:01:56,827 --> 00:02:00,086
they're real, not supermen.

43
00:02:00,121 --> 00:02:02,021
They get hurt.

44
00:02:02,057 --> 00:02:03,423
They can die.

45
00:02:12,734 --> 00:02:14,834
Hey, I'm sorry, buddy, last little bit.

46
00:02:14,869 --> 00:02:16,869
I got to keep it clean, you know?

47
00:02:16,905 --> 00:02:18,538
It's looking much better though, okay?

48
00:02:18,573 --> 00:02:20,934
You're doing good. You
just hang in there, buddy.

49
00:02:21,376 --> 00:02:22,608
How we doing?

50
00:02:22,644 --> 00:02:24,277
Got something.

51
00:02:24,311 --> 00:02:26,296
Our friend over there has a boat.

52
00:02:26,332 --> 00:02:28,214
He's making a smuggling run to Greece.

53
00:02:28,249 --> 00:02:31,184
He says he can take your
brother to a first world doctor.

54
00:02:31,219 --> 00:02:33,386
First world thinks he's Kaniel Outis.

55
00:02:33,421 --> 00:02:34,926
They'll arrest him on sight.

56
00:02:34,962 --> 00:02:36,150
So?

57
00:02:36,181 --> 00:02:37,908
What's the alternative, let him die?

58
00:02:37,923 --> 00:02:39,256
What kind of a brother are you?

59
00:02:41,288 --> 00:02:42,995
You say something like that again,

60
00:02:42,997 --> 00:02:44,764
I swear to God, I'll kill you.

61
00:02:51,373 --> 00:02:53,473
There might be a third option.

62
00:03:02,439 --> 00:03:04,674
So how was your first day back?

63
00:03:05,987 --> 00:03:08,421
I have to say, it's
never been so rewarding

64
00:03:08,456 --> 00:03:09,689
to teach game theory to the tops

65
00:03:09,691 --> 00:03:11,090
of a bunch of 18-year-olds' heads

66
00:03:11,126 --> 00:03:12,725
while they're busy sexting each other.

67
00:03:12,761 --> 00:03:13,926
Ew.

68
00:03:13,962 --> 00:03:15,261
Ew.

69
00:03:15,296 --> 00:03:16,696
But...

70
00:03:16,731 --> 00:03:19,298
normalcy's threatening to come back,

71
00:03:19,334 --> 00:03:21,534
and I say cheers to that.

72
00:03:21,569 --> 00:03:22,869
Cheers to that.

73
00:03:24,606 --> 00:03:26,205
Come on, let's sit outside.

74
00:03:27,976 --> 00:03:29,609
I'll be right there.

75
00:03:34,983 --> 00:03:36,249
Hello?

76
00:03:36,284 --> 00:03:38,451
We found Michael.

77
00:03:38,486 --> 00:03:40,920
Is he our Michael?

78
00:03:40,955 --> 00:03:42,655
Yes, Sara.

79
00:03:44,726 --> 00:03:47,627
Sara, listen, he's been poisoned.

80
00:03:47,662 --> 00:03:48,861
We think it's antifreeze.

81
00:03:48,897 --> 00:03:50,129
He's lost a lot of blood.

82
00:03:50,165 --> 00:03:52,465
He needs a lot of blood.

83
00:03:52,500 --> 00:03:53,747
Okay.

84
00:03:53,750 --> 00:03:55,535
He needs a lot of things
if it's antifreeze.

85
00:03:55,537 --> 00:03:56,769
Listen, uh,

86
00:03:56,805 --> 00:03:58,143
we're heading to Greece.

87
00:03:58,146 --> 00:04:00,740
Is there any way we can get
some medical help off the books?

88
00:04:00,742 --> 00:04:02,682
No, no, no, no, no, this
isn't the kind of thing

89
00:04:02,685 --> 00:04:04,218
that you want to do off the books.

90
00:04:04,221 --> 00:04:07,113
Listen, Lincoln, he's
gonna need a transfusion.

91
00:04:07,148 --> 00:04:08,848
Michael's B negative, okay?

92
00:04:08,883 --> 00:04:11,884
It's maybe one percent of the
population with that blood type.

93
00:04:11,920 --> 00:04:13,653
You won't find it where you're going,

94
00:04:13,688 --> 00:04:15,688
and he won't make it while you look.

95
00:04:17,772 --> 00:04:21,060
Unless it comes to you.

96
00:04:21,095 --> 00:04:22,462
I'll call you back.

97
00:04:24,165 --> 00:04:26,365
Hey, what's going on?

98
00:04:26,401 --> 00:04:27,967
I, uh...

99
00:04:28,002 --> 00:04:29,869
I got to go.

100
00:04:29,904 --> 00:04:31,804
You got to go?

101
00:04:31,840 --> 00:04:33,239
Go where?

102
00:04:33,274 --> 00:04:34,674
To Crete.

103
00:04:35,810 --> 00:04:37,210
Michael, um,

104
00:04:37,245 --> 00:04:38,845
they found him.

105
00:04:38,880 --> 00:04:40,279
He's alive.

106
00:04:40,315 --> 00:04:41,514
He's poisoned.

107
00:04:41,549 --> 00:04:43,916
Michael? Your ex, Michael?

108
00:04:43,952 --> 00:04:44,962
Yeah.

109
00:04:44,985 --> 00:04:46,419
Wait, hold on a second,

110
00:04:46,454 --> 00:04:48,821
he really is alive?

111
00:04:48,857 --> 00:04:50,356
He contacted you just now?

112
00:04:50,391 --> 00:04:53,826
Yeah, and, uh, and he needs help,

113
00:04:53,862 --> 00:04:57,930
and I think I'm the only
one that can help him.

114
00:04:57,966 --> 00:04:59,999
Um...

115
00:05:00,026 --> 00:05:02,731
yeah, I can get there faster on
a plane than they can on a boat.

116
00:05:02,767 --> 00:05:05,368
Whoa, whoa, whoa, Sara?

117
00:05:05,403 --> 00:05:06,873
Y-You don't owe him that.

118
00:05:06,905 --> 00:05:09,225
Y-You don't know what you'd
be walking into, it's not safe.

119
00:05:09,240 --> 00:05:10,640
I'll be fine. I don't have a choice.

120
00:05:10,642 --> 00:05:11,941
I...

121
00:05:11,976 --> 00:05:13,676
This has been a hell of a week.

122
00:05:15,840 --> 00:05:18,080
Okay, look, I know you've
got a million questions,

123
00:05:18,116 --> 00:05:19,949
just like I do, okay?

124
00:05:19,984 --> 00:05:22,485
I can't look my son in the eye

125
00:05:22,520 --> 00:05:24,587
and tell him that I let his father die

126
00:05:24,622 --> 00:05:26,922
when I could've tried to save him,

127
00:05:26,958 --> 00:05:28,291
A father he's never met.

128
00:05:28,326 --> 00:05:30,893
I can't do that.

129
00:05:30,928 --> 00:05:32,828
And if I told you not to go?

130
00:05:36,434 --> 00:05:38,100
"If's" a big word in that sentence.

131
00:05:38,136 --> 00:05:40,202
Jacob, are you telling me not to go?

132
00:05:43,541 --> 00:05:45,107
No.

133
00:05:45,143 --> 00:05:47,076
No, of course not.

134
00:05:47,111 --> 00:05:49,078
Okay.

135
00:06:00,224 --> 00:06:02,758
Should've left her out of this, Linc.

136
00:06:02,794 --> 00:06:05,328
Shut up. You're about to
see the wife you haven't seen

137
00:06:05,363 --> 00:06:06,996
in seven years.

138
00:06:08,777 --> 00:06:10,833
- I got you, I got you.
- Cast off.

139
00:06:10,868 --> 00:06:12,668
You're ready.

140
00:06:12,704 --> 00:06:14,637
What do you mean?

141
00:06:16,607 --> 00:06:20,376
Been locked up for longer
than I can remember.

142
00:06:20,411 --> 00:06:22,311
Before Ogygia, it was
my apartment, my head

143
00:06:22,347 --> 00:06:24,413
and my phone.

144
00:06:24,449 --> 00:06:25,948
Walls all around me.

145
00:06:25,983 --> 00:06:29,118
Couldn't see the world.

146
00:06:31,823 --> 00:06:33,322
I like it here.

147
00:06:33,358 --> 00:06:34,757
No walls.

148
00:06:34,792 --> 00:06:38,327
Freedom, like I haven't
had in a long time.

149
00:06:38,363 --> 00:06:41,030
I can start over.

150
00:06:41,065 --> 00:06:43,999
And unless you say you need me,

151
00:06:44,035 --> 00:06:46,001
I'd like to stay.

152
00:06:46,037 --> 00:06:48,537
You're a free man, Ja.

153
00:06:48,573 --> 00:06:50,506
The choice is yours.

154
00:06:51,676 --> 00:06:54,577
I owe you my life.

155
00:06:54,612 --> 00:06:56,846
You gave me back the world.

156
00:07:00,084 --> 00:07:01,884
Get him healthy. Get safe.

157
00:07:01,919 --> 00:07:03,953
Yeah, I will.

158
00:07:03,988 --> 00:07:05,755
See you.

159
00:07:09,360 --> 00:07:10,559
Hey, hey, hey.

160
00:07:10,595 --> 00:07:12,061
I got to know,

161
00:07:12,096 --> 00:07:15,464
you really got Freddie Mercury's ashes?

162
00:07:15,500 --> 00:07:19,235
Is it true Keith Richard
snorted his dead father's ashes?

163
00:07:19,270 --> 00:07:20,703
I don't know.

164
00:07:21,873 --> 00:07:24,039
Exactly.

165
00:07:24,075 --> 00:07:25,875
Keep alive.

166
00:07:25,910 --> 00:07:28,043
You too, man.

167
00:07:36,254 --> 00:07:38,687
Linc,

168
00:07:38,723 --> 00:07:40,523
how far is it to Greece?

169
00:07:40,558 --> 00:07:42,591
12 hours.

170
00:07:42,627 --> 00:07:44,226
Sara's gonna be there in 12.

171
00:07:44,262 --> 00:07:47,897
I don't think I have 12 hours in me.

172
00:09:06,082 --> 00:09:08,887
I was right, we got problems.

173
00:09:08,922 --> 00:09:13,374
Apparently, State Department is
asking questions about 21-Void

174
00:09:13,377 --> 00:09:15,726
after our visit to NSA yesterday.

175
00:09:15,762 --> 00:09:17,596
They have no viable information.

176
00:09:18,398 --> 00:09:20,432
21-Void doesn't exist.

177
00:09:20,467 --> 00:09:21,866
Poseidon will clean house.

178
00:09:21,902 --> 00:09:23,655
The problem's not going away.

179
00:09:23,658 --> 00:09:25,270
That State Department
agent wants to meet

180
00:09:25,305 --> 00:09:26,738
as soon as we land.

181
00:09:37,451 --> 00:09:39,718
Chania, please?

182
00:09:39,753 --> 00:09:41,019
Thank you.

183
00:09:56,436 --> 00:09:58,236
It is safe here.

184
00:09:58,272 --> 00:09:59,804
I use when I come.

185
00:09:59,840 --> 00:10:03,018
You got any food for him?

186
00:10:03,054 --> 00:10:04,643
Come, it's in the boat.

187
00:10:04,678 --> 00:10:07,245
Great, thank you.

188
00:10:07,281 --> 00:10:08,980
Keep his spirits up.

189
00:10:09,016 --> 00:10:10,570
All right, man.

190
00:10:14,955 --> 00:10:18,290
Oh, man.

191
00:10:21,980 --> 00:10:23,847
Got to hang in there, buddy, huh?

192
00:10:26,433 --> 00:10:30,435
Still got a lot of things
to tell me, you know?

193
00:10:33,473 --> 00:10:35,340
You gonna tell me why
I'm your whip hand.

194
00:10:35,375 --> 00:10:36,833
Remember?

195
00:10:44,718 --> 00:10:46,484
I got a lot invested in you.

196
00:10:49,289 --> 00:10:52,090
You can't die on me
now, Michael, you know?

197
00:10:53,527 --> 00:10:56,261
Called you Michael.

198
00:10:56,296 --> 00:11:00,932
The first... first time I
ever really known your name,

199
00:11:00,967 --> 00:11:03,468
even though I feel like...

200
00:11:05,372 --> 00:11:08,139
I feel like we've been
brothers since we met, you know?

201
00:11:13,880 --> 00:11:16,181
You know, with... With Linc here...

202
00:11:19,886 --> 00:11:22,887
it was the first time I ever
felt like an outsider with you.

203
00:11:22,923 --> 00:11:25,090
You know, like...

204
00:11:25,125 --> 00:11:27,926
Like I lost...

205
00:11:27,961 --> 00:11:29,794
part of my family or something.

206
00:11:29,830 --> 00:11:33,932
So, you see, Michael, you can't die.

207
00:11:38,138 --> 00:11:40,372
Please?

208
00:12:31,358 --> 00:12:32,798
Linc.

209
00:12:58,752 --> 00:13:00,285
Hi.

210
00:13:00,320 --> 00:13:02,520
I missed you.

211
00:13:11,865 --> 00:13:14,599
I'm gonna fix you up.

212
00:13:14,634 --> 00:13:16,734
And then we'll talk, okay?

213
00:13:19,105 --> 00:13:21,439
I'm gonna make you okay.

214
00:13:23,610 --> 00:13:25,477
No.

215
00:13:25,512 --> 00:13:26,511
Shh, shh, shh,

216
00:13:26,546 --> 00:13:28,780
shh, shh, shh, it's okay.

217
00:13:30,016 --> 00:13:32,016
Hey, Lincoln, uh,

218
00:13:32,052 --> 00:13:33,985
would you pass me that coatrack?

219
00:13:34,020 --> 00:13:36,054
- Could I grab the chair, please?
- Yeah.

220
00:13:37,824 --> 00:13:39,324
Thanks.

221
00:14:00,180 --> 00:14:02,180
We'll do a transfusion.

222
00:14:06,686 --> 00:14:07,886
I'm O negative.

223
00:14:07,921 --> 00:14:10,488
It's the universal donor.

224
00:14:10,524 --> 00:14:13,391
Turns out it's the only other
blood type I could've given him.

225
00:14:16,029 --> 00:14:18,029
Maybe there's something to destiny, huh?

226
00:14:22,168 --> 00:14:25,202
Is he gonna live?

227
00:14:25,238 --> 00:14:27,872
Yeah.

228
00:14:27,908 --> 00:14:30,174
Yeah, he'll live.

229
00:14:30,210 --> 00:14:32,810
Give him a couple hours.

230
00:14:32,846 --> 00:14:35,246
He's strong.

231
00:14:38,485 --> 00:14:41,786
We'll, uh... we'll give you a minute.

232
00:14:41,821 --> 00:14:43,721
Yeah.

233
00:14:43,757 --> 00:14:46,925
I'm right here.

234
00:14:46,960 --> 00:14:48,660
I'm right here.

235
00:14:53,733 --> 00:14:56,234
We need to work out a way
to get off this island.

236
00:15:02,976 --> 00:15:05,577
What I said...

237
00:15:05,612 --> 00:15:09,252
um, about you...

238
00:15:09,288 --> 00:15:11,555
I was wrong.

239
00:15:14,825 --> 00:15:16,821
A man would be lucky to have a brother

240
00:15:16,823 --> 00:15:18,890
cares as much as you, you know?

241
00:15:20,760 --> 00:15:22,727
Wife like that...

242
00:15:24,497 --> 00:15:26,564
family.

243
00:15:29,636 --> 00:15:31,703
I wouldn't call it luck.

244
00:15:31,738 --> 00:15:34,439
You've been through
what we've been through.

245
00:15:34,474 --> 00:15:36,274
You're family now.

246
00:15:39,846 --> 00:15:41,179
I'll drink to that.

247
00:15:41,214 --> 00:15:43,648
Yeah.

248
00:15:45,051 --> 00:15:46,618
Flying's really out of the question?

249
00:15:46,653 --> 00:15:47,819
Yeah.

250
00:15:47,854 --> 00:15:51,756
Airports are worse than hospitals.

251
00:15:51,791 --> 00:15:54,792
And once the name Kaniel
Outis is radioactive,

252
00:15:54,828 --> 00:15:56,861
they'll shoot him on sight.

253
00:15:58,164 --> 00:16:00,498
So another boat?

254
00:16:00,533 --> 00:16:02,533
Across the Atlantic?

255
00:16:02,569 --> 00:16:07,772
Mm, I'm no sailor, but I know
that no boat in that harbor

256
00:16:07,807 --> 00:16:10,274
is gonna get us that far.

257
00:16:10,310 --> 00:16:11,776
We need a big boat.

258
00:16:13,480 --> 00:16:17,273
One that doesn't mind a
radioactive cargo, you know?

259
00:16:32,298 --> 00:16:36,000
Hey there, I wanted to
follow up on our conversation.

260
00:16:36,036 --> 00:16:37,735
Obviously, the CIA and State,

261
00:16:37,771 --> 00:16:39,771
we've been sharing
information on Kaniel Outis,

262
00:16:39,806 --> 00:16:42,006
but my question for you is:

263
00:16:42,042 --> 00:16:43,708
Outis killed Abu Ramal,

264
00:16:43,743 --> 00:16:46,110
did the country a service.

265
00:16:46,146 --> 00:16:48,746
So why were you still at NSA yesterday,

266
00:16:48,782 --> 00:16:50,782
trying to kill him?

267
00:16:50,817 --> 00:16:52,817
Why don't we get off the tarmac?

268
00:16:52,852 --> 00:16:55,119
We'll share what we can
about our investigation.

269
00:16:57,171 --> 00:16:59,871
This is all just
bureaucratic miscommunication.

270
00:16:59,883 --> 00:17:01,459
We can iron it out.

271
00:17:01,494 --> 00:17:04,387
So you know, we checked with CIA.

272
00:17:04,423 --> 00:17:07,131
The CIA didn't sanction
your visit to NSA yesterday.

273
00:17:07,167 --> 00:17:08,933
No one even knew you were there.

274
00:17:08,968 --> 00:17:11,469
Who are you working for, really?

275
00:17:11,504 --> 00:17:14,005
And why were you trying
to take out Kaniel Outis?

276
00:17:22,615 --> 00:17:25,083
Never thought I'd see this face again.

277
00:17:25,118 --> 00:17:27,552
You weren't supposed to.

278
00:17:29,189 --> 00:17:31,022
Why?

279
00:17:32,892 --> 00:17:36,327
I'll tell you everything
you want to know.

280
00:17:36,362 --> 00:17:38,863
But first, I need something from you.

281
00:17:38,898 --> 00:17:40,698
Anything.

282
00:17:42,368 --> 00:17:45,236
A picture of my son.

283
00:17:47,269 --> 00:17:49,117
We weren't at NSA yesterday.

284
00:17:49,153 --> 00:17:51,716
I'm telling you, this is a mistake.

285
00:17:51,748 --> 00:17:54,034
And it's a mistake to lie to me.

286
00:17:54,063 --> 00:17:55,701
I can have you prosecuted.

287
00:17:55,732 --> 00:17:59,851
I have a contact at the
NSA and she gave me proof.

288
00:17:59,886 --> 00:18:02,653
You're not calling him Junior, are you?

289
00:18:02,689 --> 00:18:05,757
I promised you I would never do that.

290
00:18:07,807 --> 00:18:09,707
He's an amazing kid.

291
00:18:10,597 --> 00:18:12,330
He's just like you.

292
00:18:21,174 --> 00:18:22,907
What's wrong?

293
00:18:35,054 --> 00:18:36,587
It's him.

294
00:18:42,886 --> 00:18:44,495
Your husband.

295
00:18:44,531 --> 00:18:46,737
Jacob?

296
00:18:46,769 --> 00:18:47,940
Jacob.

297
00:18:56,176 --> 00:18:58,442
Jacob is Poseidon.

298
00:19:06,408 --> 00:19:08,574
I knew it. I wasn't crazy.

299
00:19:08,602 --> 00:19:12,429
I caught him lying, but he-he...

300
00:19:12,465 --> 00:19:14,064
Oh, God, he covered it so well.

301
00:19:14,100 --> 00:19:16,766
He was... honest and hurt,

302
00:19:16,769 --> 00:19:18,736
and I bought it.

303
00:19:18,772 --> 00:19:20,170
Who is he?

304
00:19:20,206 --> 00:19:21,939
Really?

305
00:19:21,975 --> 00:19:25,409
He's a CIA operative, deep cover.

306
00:19:25,445 --> 00:19:27,678
He runs a splinter cell called 21-Void.

307
00:19:27,714 --> 00:19:30,080
What does this have to do with you?

308
00:19:30,116 --> 00:19:32,816
He targeted me for my skills,

309
00:19:32,852 --> 00:19:34,351
blackmailed me.

310
00:19:34,354 --> 00:19:36,520
He told me if I didn't
agree to come work for him,

311
00:19:36,523 --> 00:19:38,289
he'd go after you and Linc,

312
00:19:38,292 --> 00:19:40,848
put you both in jail.

313
00:19:40,884 --> 00:19:42,884
And then he proved it to me.

314
00:19:45,022 --> 00:19:47,522
He said I could never see
either one of you again.

315
00:19:47,558 --> 00:19:50,224
Or Mike.

316
00:19:50,260 --> 00:19:52,260
Made me fake my death.

317
00:19:52,296 --> 00:19:54,896
And then he just used me.

318
00:19:54,932 --> 00:19:56,431
He married me.

319
00:19:56,467 --> 00:19:58,266
If I'd known he was
your husband, I swear...

320
00:19:58,302 --> 00:19:59,367
No, no, no, no, no,

321
00:19:59,403 --> 00:20:01,402
this is not on you.

322
00:20:01,438 --> 00:20:03,472
I...

323
00:20:05,275 --> 00:20:07,608
Why now? Why did you come back now?

324
00:20:07,644 --> 00:20:09,744
The origami...

325
00:20:11,515 --> 00:20:14,282
Four years ago, he betrayed me

326
00:20:14,318 --> 00:20:16,884
and now I know why.

327
00:20:16,920 --> 00:20:20,421
He wanted me out of the way...

328
00:20:20,457 --> 00:20:22,157
so he could have you.

329
00:20:23,160 --> 00:20:25,526
How did he betray you?

330
00:20:25,562 --> 00:20:27,762
He set a meeting.

331
00:20:27,798 --> 00:20:30,665
We were supposed to
discuss my next assignment.

332
00:20:30,701 --> 00:20:32,770
What he didn't tell me was that

333
00:20:32,809 --> 00:20:34,803
we were meeting a man
named Harlan Gaines,

334
00:20:34,805 --> 00:20:37,672
a deputy director of the CIA.

335
00:20:37,708 --> 00:20:39,907
Gaines was investigating 21-Void.

336
00:20:39,943 --> 00:20:42,176
Looking for the traitor behind it.

337
00:20:42,212 --> 00:20:46,314
That's when I knew my work
wasn't sanctioned by the CIA.

338
00:20:46,350 --> 00:20:49,584
Poseidon shot and
killed Gaines that night,

339
00:20:49,620 --> 00:20:51,653
to stop the investigation.

340
00:20:55,192 --> 00:20:56,591
He told me to move the body,

341
00:20:56,627 --> 00:20:58,993
make it look like it never happened.

342
00:20:59,029 --> 00:21:01,262
I've seen the photos of
that part, they're damning.

343
00:21:01,320 --> 00:21:04,473
He chose images that showed
me moving Gaines' body,

344
00:21:04,520 --> 00:21:07,411
eliminated the ones that
incriminated himself.

345
00:21:07,447 --> 00:21:10,514
I knew I was being set up.

346
00:21:10,550 --> 00:21:12,416
He was tightening his control over me,

347
00:21:12,452 --> 00:21:15,786
but there was nothing I could do.

348
00:21:15,822 --> 00:21:18,756
At least, that's what he thought.

349
00:21:18,792 --> 00:21:21,558
When I knew Poseidon had gone rogue

350
00:21:21,594 --> 00:21:24,027
and was operating outside the CIA,

351
00:21:24,063 --> 00:21:26,630
that's when I started my
plan to get back to you.

352
00:21:26,666 --> 00:21:28,958
You're not.

353
00:21:28,996 --> 00:21:30,513
Some other man has your...

354
00:21:30,541 --> 00:21:32,536
Your face, your past, your whole life.

355
00:21:32,599 --> 00:21:35,506
Sara, there is a plan
to make this right,

356
00:21:35,542 --> 00:21:37,458
to protect our family.

357
00:21:40,380 --> 00:21:43,147
Michael, he's with our son right now.

358
00:21:43,175 --> 00:21:46,409
He's with Mike.

359
00:21:46,452 --> 00:21:49,320
I, uh, look, I have to go.

360
00:21:51,762 --> 00:21:52,827
Ah.

361
00:21:52,865 --> 00:21:54,925
Hey, Noah, you gonna build us a boat?

362
00:21:54,961 --> 00:21:58,662
Nope. I'm gonna do one better.

363
00:21:58,698 --> 00:22:00,264
Who you calling?

364
00:22:01,401 --> 00:22:04,602
A friend who actually has a boat.

365
00:22:13,079 --> 00:22:14,545
Hello?

366
00:22:14,581 --> 00:22:15,746
Sucre, it's me.

367
00:22:15,782 --> 00:22:17,781
Linc? I thought the Middle East

368
00:22:17,817 --> 00:22:19,049
was gonna swallow you up, man.

369
00:22:19,085 --> 00:22:21,685
Where's Michael? Did you find him?

370
00:22:21,724 --> 00:22:23,778
Listen, that's why I'm calling.

371
00:22:23,814 --> 00:22:25,372
We're on the island of Crete.

372
00:22:25,375 --> 00:22:27,381
We need a low profile
ride back to the States.

373
00:22:27,417 --> 00:22:28,880
I would love to help,

374
00:22:28,883 --> 00:22:30,885
but we're on the other
side of the world, brother.

375
00:22:30,887 --> 00:22:32,520
We just dropped a load in Morocco.

376
00:22:32,556 --> 00:22:35,022
What are you talking
about? Morocco's near Crete.

377
00:22:35,058 --> 00:22:37,925
Yeah, I know, of course it is,

378
00:22:37,961 --> 00:22:40,127
but what I mean is it's not my ship.

379
00:22:40,163 --> 00:22:42,964
Yeah, but what would
it cost to hitch a ride?

380
00:22:43,000 --> 00:22:44,665
You can't hitch a ride.

381
00:22:44,701 --> 00:22:46,400
You have to rent the whole ship.

382
00:22:46,436 --> 00:22:48,869
The boss charges 50K a leg, Linc.

383
00:22:48,905 --> 00:22:51,072
You want to get back
to the States, it's 50K.

384
00:22:51,108 --> 00:22:52,306
50K?

385
00:22:52,342 --> 00:22:54,609
We're just trying to get home.

386
00:22:54,645 --> 00:22:56,645
You know we don't
have that kind of cash.

387
00:22:58,281 --> 00:22:59,648
You do now.

388
00:23:00,951 --> 00:23:02,483
Here, this was my grandmother's.

389
00:23:02,519 --> 00:23:03,999
It's an heirloom worth at least that.

390
00:23:08,125 --> 00:23:10,425
I can't think of a better use for it.

391
00:23:11,328 --> 00:23:13,094
Thank you.

392
00:23:13,130 --> 00:23:16,371
We got it, Sucre. Get to Crete.

393
00:23:19,202 --> 00:23:21,035
He's not gonna hurt Mike,

394
00:23:21,071 --> 00:23:24,138
not unless he suspects
you know who he really is.

395
00:23:24,174 --> 00:23:25,606
If you remove his mask,

396
00:23:25,642 --> 00:23:27,274
he'll lash out.

397
00:23:27,310 --> 00:23:29,043
You know him better than I do.

398
00:23:29,079 --> 00:23:30,845
That's the point, no one knows him.

399
00:23:30,881 --> 00:23:32,647
So, what do I do?

400
00:23:32,683 --> 00:23:35,249
You play his game.
You wear your own mask.

401
00:23:35,285 --> 00:23:38,285
As soon as you get a chance
to get away with Mike,

402
00:23:38,321 --> 00:23:41,922
you take it, disappear.

403
00:23:41,958 --> 00:23:44,125
I'll get to the States as soon as I can.

404
00:23:44,161 --> 00:23:46,861
I'll find you.

405
00:23:46,897 --> 00:23:48,596
You're looking better.

406
00:23:48,632 --> 00:23:50,431
A little grayer, but better.

407
00:23:50,467 --> 00:23:53,535
I have an amazing doctor on call.

408
00:24:00,310 --> 00:24:03,244
I will wear the mask.

409
00:24:03,280 --> 00:24:05,780
I will play his game...

410
00:24:05,816 --> 00:24:09,484
and if he hurts our son I'll kill him.

411
00:24:12,389 --> 00:24:13,888
I can't...

412
00:24:31,108 --> 00:24:32,915
Please come back to us.

413
00:24:51,328 --> 00:24:53,294
She's leaving Crete alone,

414
00:24:53,330 --> 00:24:56,530
which means she left Outis
behind, and he'll try to follow,

415
00:24:56,566 --> 00:24:58,245
return to the U.S. in
the next day or two.

416
00:24:58,248 --> 00:24:59,152
Who called?

417
00:24:59,155 --> 00:25:01,362
Only be by ship or
plane, so plaster his face

418
00:25:01,365 --> 00:25:03,230
on all maritime and air channels,

419
00:25:03,233 --> 00:25:05,273
focusing on all vessels
departing from Crete

420
00:25:05,275 --> 00:25:06,307
in the next 48 hours.

421
00:25:06,343 --> 00:25:08,075
He's got to be on one.

422
00:25:08,111 --> 00:25:10,445
- He can't make it back inside the country.
- Jacob?

423
00:25:11,481 --> 00:25:13,414
Was that Mommy?

424
00:25:15,860 --> 00:25:20,029
Yes. Mommy's on her way home.

425
00:25:31,264 --> 00:25:33,264
Michael Scofield.

426
00:25:34,584 --> 00:25:37,267
My man, you got more lives than anyone.

427
00:25:38,504 --> 00:25:40,137
Think I might've used them all up.

428
00:25:41,007 --> 00:25:42,606
A damn phoenix.

429
00:25:42,642 --> 00:25:44,241
I can't believe it.

430
00:25:44,277 --> 00:25:45,809
I want to hear every damn thing

431
00:25:45,845 --> 00:25:47,545
that's happened to you since you died.

432
00:25:47,580 --> 00:25:49,246
Papi, you're alive?

433
00:25:52,385 --> 00:25:54,081
The skipper is a corrupt bastard.

434
00:25:54,084 --> 00:25:56,129
Don't mess with him.
He's got guns in the hold,

435
00:25:56,132 --> 00:25:58,914
all kinds of contraband. Captain.

436
00:26:00,760 --> 00:26:02,973
Here's the cargo I
was telling you about.

437
00:26:02,976 --> 00:26:04,428
Pay up.

438
00:26:04,463 --> 00:26:06,947
Where's the 50K?

439
00:26:06,974 --> 00:26:08,707
Here.

440
00:26:08,742 --> 00:26:11,610
I said cash.

441
00:26:11,645 --> 00:26:13,945
It's a sapphire, six carats,

442
00:26:13,981 --> 00:26:17,582
flawless, surrounded by 2.5
carats of bezeled diamonds.

443
00:26:17,618 --> 00:26:19,518
Street value is 125K.

444
00:26:19,553 --> 00:26:22,491
You can pawn it for half
that and still make a profit.

445
00:26:32,232 --> 00:26:33,398
If it's fake,

446
00:26:33,433 --> 00:26:35,387
you go under the sea.

447
00:26:38,438 --> 00:26:41,373
A boat is the last place I
expected to find you, buddy.

448
00:26:41,408 --> 00:26:42,974
I thought you hated the water.

449
00:26:43,010 --> 00:26:46,244
Yeah, you remember, but I got a record.

450
00:26:46,280 --> 00:26:48,914
Not a lot of employers lined
up to take a chance on me.

451
00:26:48,949 --> 00:26:51,349
Besides, this ship
provides opportunities

452
00:26:51,385 --> 00:26:52,830
for my side business...

453
00:26:52,833 --> 00:26:55,086
which is the real
reason I'm on this boat.

454
00:26:55,088 --> 00:26:57,022
This baby...

455
00:26:57,057 --> 00:26:59,190
houses my entire life savings.

456
00:26:59,226 --> 00:27:01,560
I'm telling you, it's gonna be huge.

457
00:27:01,595 --> 00:27:04,262
I'm a few months away from
putting all this behind me.

458
00:27:04,298 --> 00:27:06,531
If you guys are lucky, I'll let you guys

459
00:27:06,567 --> 00:27:08,647
take one of my ladies for a spin.

460
00:27:11,505 --> 00:27:12,904
Huh?

461
00:27:13,840 --> 00:27:15,070
What, sex dolls?

462
00:27:15,093 --> 00:27:16,424
No, have some class, man.

463
00:27:16,461 --> 00:27:18,799
The term is inflatables, high quality,

464
00:27:18,802 --> 00:27:20,695
expensive, very lifelike.

465
00:27:22,716 --> 00:27:25,250
Huh?

466
00:27:42,703 --> 00:27:43,902
Hey, honey.

467
00:27:43,937 --> 00:27:46,071
Hey, you.

468
00:27:53,464 --> 00:27:55,564
Mm.

469
00:27:58,719 --> 00:28:00,819
Mm.

470
00:28:02,022 --> 00:28:03,288
Where's Mike?

471
00:28:03,323 --> 00:28:05,690
Asleep.

472
00:28:05,726 --> 00:28:06,725
Kid had a big day.

473
00:28:06,760 --> 00:28:08,360
Oh.

474
00:28:08,395 --> 00:28:10,562
Most important, though,

475
00:28:10,597 --> 00:28:12,097
how's Michael?

476
00:28:12,132 --> 00:28:14,199
Were you able to help him?

477
00:28:14,234 --> 00:28:18,737
I mean, he was barely
alive when I got there.

478
00:28:18,772 --> 00:28:22,407
He, uh, slept most of the time.

479
00:28:22,442 --> 00:28:24,342
I-I did what I could for him. I, uh...

480
00:28:24,378 --> 00:28:28,313
I stabilized him, but he's changed.

481
00:28:28,348 --> 00:28:32,617
He, uh... he's just not the guy I knew.

482
00:28:32,653 --> 00:28:35,553
So, they dropped me at the
airport and that was that.

483
00:28:35,589 --> 00:28:37,494
They?

484
00:28:37,518 --> 00:28:39,618
Linc and some other guy.

485
00:28:47,100 --> 00:28:49,434
Mike?

486
00:28:51,546 --> 00:28:53,079
Where's Mike?

487
00:28:53,092 --> 00:28:54,892
- You said that he was asleep.
- He is...

488
00:28:54,922 --> 00:28:57,709
at a friend's house, a sleepover.

489
00:28:57,744 --> 00:29:00,578
Okay. Which friend?

490
00:29:00,614 --> 00:29:01,880
He's at Patrick's house.

491
00:29:05,585 --> 00:29:07,686
What happened to your
grandmother's ring?

492
00:29:08,755 --> 00:29:11,189
I'm such an idiot.

493
00:29:11,224 --> 00:29:13,091
I took it off on the
way over for safekeeping,

494
00:29:13,126 --> 00:29:15,060
'cause I didn't want it to get stolen,

495
00:29:15,095 --> 00:29:18,663
then when I looked for it
on the way back it was gone.

496
00:29:18,699 --> 00:29:22,500
Screamed so loud they nearly
threw me off the flight.

497
00:29:22,536 --> 00:29:25,503
Hmm.

498
00:29:52,365 --> 00:29:53,798
Yeah?

499
00:29:53,834 --> 00:29:56,367
We spoke to our man at the Pentagon.

500
00:29:56,403 --> 00:29:57,969
A naval alert just went out.

501
00:29:58,004 --> 00:30:00,105
Kaniel Outis has been located

502
00:30:00,140 --> 00:30:02,707
on a cargo ship in the Mediterranean.

503
00:30:02,743 --> 00:30:04,676
It was reported by the ship's captain.

504
00:30:04,711 --> 00:30:06,344
What's the navy gonna do about it?

505
00:30:06,379 --> 00:30:08,446
The nearest LCS combat craft

506
00:30:08,482 --> 00:30:10,030
is moving to engage.

507
00:30:10,061 --> 00:30:11,850
SEAL team's been deployed.

508
00:30:11,885 --> 00:30:13,451
Orders?

509
00:30:13,487 --> 00:30:16,888
To seek and destroy Kaniel Outis.

510
00:30:16,923 --> 00:30:17,996
Good.

511
00:30:18,038 --> 00:30:19,771
We've done our job
getting the message out.

512
00:30:19,816 --> 00:30:23,194
Now it's time for the
SEALs to do theirs.

513
00:30:23,230 --> 00:30:26,030
My God.

514
00:30:27,167 --> 00:30:29,400
You've been through hell, my friend.

515
00:30:32,539 --> 00:30:34,272
Have some faith, papi.

516
00:30:34,307 --> 00:30:36,808
Thanks, papi.

517
00:30:38,233 --> 00:30:39,344
What about you, Linc?

518
00:30:40,781 --> 00:30:42,781
I think Linc's got a secret girlfriend,

519
00:30:42,816 --> 00:30:44,749
the pilot lady.

520
00:30:44,785 --> 00:30:46,151
She's not my lady.

521
00:30:46,186 --> 00:30:48,720
Maybe Sucre will set you up
with one of his sex dolls.

522
00:30:48,755 --> 00:30:50,054
They're not dolls, man.

523
00:30:50,090 --> 00:30:51,374
Oh, sorry, inflatables.

524
00:30:51,377 --> 00:30:53,324
Look, let's just change
the subject, please.

525
00:30:53,326 --> 00:30:56,060
You know, might be something
to be said for settling down.

526
00:30:56,096 --> 00:30:59,426
Right, well... that's not in the cards.

527
00:31:05,906 --> 00:31:07,906
It's locked from the outside.

528
00:31:07,941 --> 00:31:08,973
They made you.

529
00:31:09,009 --> 00:31:10,975
You really are a wanted terrorist.

530
00:31:11,011 --> 00:31:12,243
What did the hell did
you think he was saying?

531
00:31:12,245 --> 00:31:13,211
I thought it was an analogy.

532
00:31:13,213 --> 00:31:14,445
Oh, for God's sake.

533
00:31:14,473 --> 00:31:16,017
There's no other way

534
00:31:16,064 --> 00:31:18,016
out of this cabin.

535
00:31:21,855 --> 00:31:26,117
All crew to the top deck. All hands up.

536
00:31:26,148 --> 00:31:28,734
Comply or be fired on.

537
00:31:28,749 --> 00:31:32,584
This ship is now under the
control of the U.S. Navy.

538
00:31:32,587 --> 00:31:33,832
Prepared to be boarded.

539
00:31:33,834 --> 00:31:35,466
We got company.

540
00:31:35,502 --> 00:31:36,734
I say we jump.

541
00:31:36,770 --> 00:31:37,902
That's a long way down.

542
00:31:37,938 --> 00:31:39,137
It's the only way out.

543
00:31:39,172 --> 00:31:40,104
It's too far.

544
00:31:40,140 --> 00:31:41,706
I have an idea...

545
00:31:43,476 --> 00:31:45,247
but it's gonna hurt.

546
00:32:04,564 --> 00:32:06,260
Hello?

547
00:32:06,291 --> 00:32:08,333
Hey, Heather, it's me.
Listen, I can't talk,

548
00:32:08,335 --> 00:32:10,501
but I need you to go pick
up Mike right now, okay?

549
00:32:10,537 --> 00:32:11,970
Do you know where Patrick Monroe lives?

550
00:32:11,972 --> 00:32:12,937
Yeah.

551
00:32:12,973 --> 00:32:14,172
Okay.

552
00:32:14,207 --> 00:32:15,707
Listen, I'll explain later.

553
00:32:15,742 --> 00:32:17,575
Don't bring him back here, okay?

554
00:32:17,611 --> 00:32:19,711
Keep him with you. I'll
be over as soon as I can.

555
00:32:19,746 --> 00:32:21,045
Can you do that for me?

556
00:32:21,081 --> 00:32:23,314
Uh, yeah. Uh, I'll leave right now.

557
00:32:23,350 --> 00:32:24,682
I-I-Is everything okay?

558
00:32:24,718 --> 00:32:25,750
No.

559
00:32:34,194 --> 00:32:35,493
Go.

560
00:32:37,998 --> 00:32:39,931
Six. The rest with me.

561
00:32:43,203 --> 00:32:44,435
Go.

562
00:32:50,610 --> 00:32:53,478
One, two, three, four.

563
00:32:55,815 --> 00:32:57,315
Go, go.

564
00:33:04,858 --> 00:33:06,858
I'll go left, you right.

565
00:33:15,024 --> 00:33:16,534
They went out the window!

566
00:33:16,569 --> 00:33:17,835
They went out the window!

567
00:33:17,871 --> 00:33:20,138
What do you see?

568
00:33:20,173 --> 00:33:21,673
No visual.

569
00:33:22,976 --> 00:33:26,010
Alpha One, Alpha Two to portside, now.

570
00:33:26,046 --> 00:33:28,513
Copy that.

571
00:33:30,483 --> 00:33:31,849
Okay!

572
00:33:31,885 --> 00:33:34,552
Take... Take it off!

573
00:33:34,587 --> 00:33:35,902
What's your name?

574
00:33:35,933 --> 00:33:37,421
Fernando.

575
00:33:37,457 --> 00:33:39,023
Fernando Sucre.

576
00:33:39,059 --> 00:33:41,159
I'm a member of this crew.
Check the roster, man.

577
00:33:41,194 --> 00:33:42,994
I got no part in any of this.

578
00:33:43,029 --> 00:33:46,864
Check the roster for Fernando Sucre.

579
00:33:48,368 --> 00:33:50,512
Suspect seems to check out.

580
00:33:50,543 --> 00:33:52,503
Take him to the bridge.

581
00:33:52,539 --> 00:33:54,205
Yes, sir.

582
00:33:54,240 --> 00:33:56,607
Let's move.

583
00:34:00,647 --> 00:34:03,235
Absolutely no one gets
off this ship, understand?

584
00:34:03,264 --> 00:34:04,530
Sir.

585
00:34:18,775 --> 00:34:20,508
I don't know any Kaniel Outis.

586
00:34:20,572 --> 00:34:22,113
The guy's name is Scofield.

587
00:34:22,148 --> 00:34:23,413
Haven't seen him in years.

588
00:34:23,449 --> 00:34:25,416
He calls me, he says he needs a ride.

589
00:34:25,451 --> 00:34:28,386
We got active pursuit on engine deck.

590
00:34:28,421 --> 00:34:29,553
Watch him.

591
00:34:29,589 --> 00:34:32,123
The guy's name is Scofield!

592
00:34:35,728 --> 00:34:38,429
That's the door Sucre told us about.

593
00:34:39,365 --> 00:34:40,765
There they are!

594
00:34:40,800 --> 00:34:42,400
Freeze! Freeze!

595
00:34:43,688 --> 00:34:45,870
Look alive, look alive!

596
00:34:45,905 --> 00:34:47,905
We've got them bottled up.

597
00:34:47,940 --> 00:34:50,708
Guys, come on! Hurry!

598
00:34:50,743 --> 00:34:51,776
Hurry!

599
00:34:51,811 --> 00:34:52,977
It's stuck!

600
00:34:53,012 --> 00:34:54,411
- Come on!
- It's stuck!

601
00:34:54,447 --> 00:34:56,513
It's stuck!

602
00:34:56,549 --> 00:34:57,882
Smoke them out, go!

603
00:35:09,262 --> 00:35:11,796
Tear gas.

604
00:35:11,831 --> 00:35:15,366
That hits the ventilation,
it's gonna ruin my cargo.

605
00:35:18,371 --> 00:35:20,471
You've always been a loser, Sucre.

606
00:35:20,506 --> 00:35:21,806
Worst shipmate I ever hired.

607
00:35:21,841 --> 00:35:23,474
You brought this scum on board my ship.

608
00:35:23,493 --> 00:35:25,043
They're your friends.
Where are they going?

609
00:35:25,045 --> 00:35:26,477
They're associates of associates.

610
00:35:26,479 --> 00:35:28,345
I haven't seen them in years.

611
00:35:28,381 --> 00:35:29,680
But that's a good point.

612
00:35:29,715 --> 00:35:32,216
Why don't you tell the nice SEAL here

613
00:35:32,251 --> 00:35:34,418
how you accepted payment
for their passage?

614
00:35:39,358 --> 00:35:41,992
Maybe they're your friends, not mine.

615
00:35:42,028 --> 00:35:44,195
Okay, okay.

616
00:35:44,245 --> 00:35:47,780
I heard them say something
about container 17.

617
00:35:53,206 --> 00:35:54,672
Oh.

618
00:35:54,707 --> 00:35:57,041
That container 17.

619
00:35:57,076 --> 00:36:00,911
The one with your
super secret cargo, huh?

620
00:36:00,947 --> 00:36:02,413
Weapons and munitions?

621
00:36:02,448 --> 00:36:05,683
Vincent, tangos may
be arming themselves.

622
00:36:05,718 --> 00:36:08,552
Man, they're not gonna like
you if they find that, are they?

623
00:36:08,588 --> 00:36:10,287
Vincent.

624
00:36:10,323 --> 00:36:12,923
You might just end up on the
terrorist watch list, too.

625
00:36:12,959 --> 00:36:13,924
Vincent, do you copy?

626
00:36:13,960 --> 00:36:15,860
Can't read you.

627
00:36:15,895 --> 00:36:19,730
Good-for-nothing
Mexican. You planned this.

628
00:36:19,765 --> 00:36:20,865
Stay here.

629
00:36:29,384 --> 00:36:30,984
17's still sealed.

630
00:36:35,615 --> 00:36:36,947
Captain?

631
00:36:40,019 --> 00:36:42,553
I'm Puerto Rican.

632
00:36:46,559 --> 00:36:48,893
12:00. You hear that?

633
00:36:56,068 --> 00:36:57,301
Come on!

634
00:37:02,742 --> 00:37:04,475
Go, go. Move!

635
00:37:08,714 --> 00:37:10,014
What's going on?

636
00:37:10,049 --> 00:37:11,615
The ship's changing course.

637
00:37:13,152 --> 00:37:14,151
I did it, papi.

638
00:37:14,186 --> 00:37:15,928
No going back now.

639
00:37:17,366 --> 00:37:20,624
See what their next move is.

640
00:37:33,372 --> 00:37:36,206
Do you remember our honeymoon?

641
00:37:40,880 --> 00:37:42,680
Yeah, of course.

642
00:37:42,715 --> 00:37:44,648
How you opened up.

643
00:37:44,684 --> 00:37:48,419
Told me you carried shame
for what you did at Fox River.

644
00:37:48,454 --> 00:37:51,689
How some days you
wished you'd never heard

645
00:37:51,724 --> 00:37:53,857
the name Michael Scofield.

646
00:37:55,397 --> 00:37:58,162
Even admitted to lying,

647
00:37:58,197 --> 00:38:00,331
keeping it all from me.

648
00:38:00,366 --> 00:38:02,918
How you finally came clean

649
00:38:02,957 --> 00:38:05,703
and put it all behind you?

650
00:38:07,440 --> 00:38:09,239
Sure.

651
00:38:09,275 --> 00:38:12,376
I forgave you for the lies.

652
00:38:12,411 --> 00:38:14,511
Your past.

653
00:38:14,547 --> 00:38:16,280
Accepted you.

654
00:38:16,315 --> 00:38:18,415
Loved you and Mike.

655
00:38:18,451 --> 00:38:20,417
How is that not enough for you?

656
00:38:37,503 --> 00:38:38,736
Hi.

657
00:38:38,771 --> 00:38:39,870
Hello?

658
00:38:39,905 --> 00:38:41,605
I have him.

659
00:38:41,641 --> 00:38:44,274
Thank God.

660
00:38:44,310 --> 00:38:45,843
He's fine.

661
00:38:45,878 --> 00:38:47,378
Headed home now.

662
00:38:47,413 --> 00:38:48,646
Hi, Mom.

663
00:38:48,673 --> 00:38:51,122
Oh, Heather, thank God.

664
00:38:51,151 --> 00:38:53,284
I'll be there soon.

665
00:39:36,294 --> 00:39:38,365
Navigation's been trashed,

666
00:39:38,401 --> 00:39:40,501
the controls damaged.

667
00:39:42,538 --> 00:39:43,837
Damn it.

668
00:39:43,873 --> 00:39:45,472
Tramp's off course.

669
00:39:45,508 --> 00:39:48,409
Moving toward Algerian
waters, top speed.

670
00:39:48,444 --> 00:39:49,613
Can we fix it?

671
00:39:49,616 --> 00:39:50,911
It'll take time.

672
00:39:50,947 --> 00:39:52,513
And by then we'd be out

673
00:39:52,548 --> 00:39:53,714
of international waters.

674
00:39:53,749 --> 00:39:56,784
Falcon One requesting orders.

675
00:39:56,819 --> 00:39:59,519
We have a situation.

676
00:40:01,303 --> 00:40:02,736
Yeah.

677
00:40:02,771 --> 00:40:05,005
The SEAL team failed
to neutralize Outis.

678
00:40:05,008 --> 00:40:07,837
Somehow the ship's
controls were damaged.

679
00:40:07,840 --> 00:40:10,477
It's headed for Algerian waters
with our soldiers on boards,

680
00:40:10,479 --> 00:40:12,012
but it'll cause a diplomatic incident

681
00:40:12,047 --> 00:40:14,348
if they stay to finish the job.

682
00:40:14,383 --> 00:40:16,817
The navy just made the
call to pull the team.

683
00:40:16,852 --> 00:40:18,418
All right, all right.

684
00:40:18,454 --> 00:40:20,320
The SEALs couldn't do
it. We escalate our move.

685
00:40:20,356 --> 00:40:22,255
Shouldn't have brought
a knife to a gunfight.

686
00:40:22,291 --> 00:40:23,824
I will handle from here.

687
00:40:23,859 --> 00:40:25,658
Thank you.

688
00:40:37,873 --> 00:40:38,972
Sir.

689
00:40:39,007 --> 00:40:40,474
Yes.

690
00:40:40,509 --> 00:40:43,410
I have an ask, one that's imperative.

691
00:40:43,445 --> 00:40:46,580
I believe you'll find that
our interests are aligned.

692
00:41:01,964 --> 00:41:03,363
What are they doing?

693
00:41:03,399 --> 00:41:04,364
They're leaving.

694
00:41:04,400 --> 00:41:05,665
Why?

695
00:41:05,701 --> 00:41:06,867
Run!

696
00:41:06,902 --> 00:41:09,936
Oh, God. No, no, no, no!

697
00:41:12,867 --> 00:41:14,100
Hey!

698
00:41:14,127 --> 00:41:15,994
You're gonna want this.

699
00:41:45,207 --> 00:41:48,308
Mike is safe where you can't
touch him, and this is over.

700
00:41:49,445 --> 00:41:52,512
The life, the lies, the mask.

701
00:41:52,548 --> 00:41:55,248
You're gonna tell me everything.

702
00:41:55,284 --> 00:41:57,584
Like who you really are,

703
00:41:57,619 --> 00:42:00,687
what this was, all of it.

704
00:42:00,722 --> 00:42:04,591
It was our life.

705
00:42:04,626 --> 00:42:06,726
It's not over, Sara.

706
00:42:06,762 --> 00:42:09,496
Not even close.

707
00:42:09,531 --> 00:42:12,098
And Mike was never in danger.

708
00:42:12,134 --> 00:42:14,434
I love him.

709
00:42:14,470 --> 00:42:17,103
He is my family.

710
00:42:17,139 --> 00:42:19,239
I raised him.

711
00:42:19,274 --> 00:42:20,540
What have you done?

712
00:42:20,576 --> 00:42:22,742
No.

713
00:42:22,778 --> 00:42:24,845
It's what you've done, Sara.

714
00:42:24,880 --> 00:42:28,682
All of this could've been avoided.

715
00:42:31,620 --> 00:42:32,886
Good sleepover?

716
00:42:32,921 --> 00:42:33,920
Yeah.

717
00:42:33,956 --> 00:42:35,555
Is Mommy coming to pick me up?

718
00:42:35,591 --> 00:42:37,603
Yes, sir.

719
00:42:39,495 --> 00:42:42,496
Michael's dead.

720
00:42:42,531 --> 00:42:45,665
Your Nightingale trip to
Greece led me straight to him.

721
00:42:46,953 --> 00:42:50,670
So... it's all on you, Sara.

722
00:42:50,706 --> 00:42:54,007
And your plan with Heather didn't work.

723
00:42:54,042 --> 00:42:56,276
Where's my son?

724
00:42:56,311 --> 00:42:57,377
I have him.

725
00:42:58,372 --> 00:43:00,347
And whether or not I
have to threaten him...

726
00:43:00,349 --> 00:43:02,249
Which I don't want to do...

727
00:43:02,284 --> 00:43:05,919
Is entirely contingent upon
you putting the gun down.

