1
00:00:03,136 --> 00:00:06,003
- LINCOLN: I didn't kill that man, Michael.
- The evidence says you did.

2
00:00:06,006 --> 00:00:08,318
- I was set up.
- Swear to me.

3
00:00:08,320 --> 00:00:09,586
I swear to you, Michael.

4
00:00:11,137 --> 00:00:12,923
[over bullhorn]: Put down your weapon!

5
00:00:12,925 --> 00:00:14,357
JUDGE: I find it incumbent that

6
00:00:14,359 --> 00:00:15,926
you see the inside of a prison cell,

7
00:00:15,928 --> 00:00:17,320
Mr. Scofield.

8
00:00:17,323 --> 00:00:19,462
I'm looking for someone...
Guy named Lincoln Burrows.

9
00:00:19,465 --> 00:00:21,541
Why you want to see
Burrows so bad anyhow?

10
00:00:21,544 --> 00:00:22,699
'Cause he's my brother.

11
00:00:22,701 --> 00:00:25,302
- I'm getting you out of here.
- That's impossible.

12
00:00:25,304 --> 00:00:27,437
MICHAEL: Not if you designed
the place, it isn't.

13
00:00:27,439 --> 00:00:29,001
[C-Note laughs]

14
00:00:29,004 --> 00:00:30,373
You one mixed-up cracker,

15
00:00:30,375 --> 00:00:31,408
you know that?

16
00:00:31,410 --> 00:00:32,642
Are we in business?

17
00:00:32,645 --> 00:00:35,212
Now... it's all about timing.

18
00:00:35,214 --> 00:00:37,949
T-BAG: Scofield. You just
as pretty as advertised.

19
00:00:37,952 --> 00:00:39,349
When do we get started?

20
00:00:39,351 --> 00:00:41,585
- I need your help.
- You're asking me to break the law.

21
00:00:41,587 --> 00:00:43,186
I'm asking you to make a mistake.

22
00:00:43,188 --> 00:00:44,988
Forget to lock up.

23
00:00:46,291 --> 00:00:47,557
- [alarm wailing]
- Come on.

24
00:00:50,329 --> 00:00:52,429
LINCOLN: We did it, Mike.

25
00:00:52,431 --> 00:00:55,899
MICHAEL: However this plays out...

26
00:00:55,901 --> 00:00:57,501
I have no regrets.

27
00:00:57,503 --> 00:00:58,918
LINCOLN [echoing]: Michael!

28
00:01:00,779 --> 00:01:03,280
Well, if you're watching
this, that means you're safe.

29
00:01:03,283 --> 00:01:05,142
I wish I could be there with you,

30
00:01:05,144 --> 00:01:08,411
but as you know now, I
wouldn't have had much time.

31
00:01:08,413 --> 00:01:10,046
I made my choice.

32
00:01:10,048 --> 00:01:11,515
I don't regret it.

33
00:01:11,517 --> 00:01:13,517
We're free now.

34
00:01:13,519 --> 00:01:14,646
We're free.

35
00:01:14,647 --> 00:01:16,248
_

36
00:01:20,125 --> 00:01:22,692
Freedom has a price.

37
00:01:26,865 --> 00:01:30,433
I died seven years ago.

38
00:01:30,435 --> 00:01:33,069
Left behind a brother...

39
00:01:33,071 --> 00:01:35,772
a wife...

40
00:01:35,774 --> 00:01:37,274
a son.

41
00:01:39,378 --> 00:01:41,978
But the dead talk...

42
00:01:41,980 --> 00:01:44,347
if you listen.

43
00:01:45,417 --> 00:01:48,685
They're there with you...

44
00:01:48,687 --> 00:01:51,087
reaching out...

45
00:01:51,089 --> 00:01:54,124
trying to tell you something.

46
00:01:54,126 --> 00:01:56,893
Because not all deaths are the same.

47
00:01:57,830 --> 00:02:00,230
Some are real.

48
00:02:00,232 --> 00:02:02,399
Some are a story.

49
00:02:03,535 --> 00:02:06,115
Question is...

50
00:02:06,118 --> 00:02:08,405
do you believe the story?

51
00:02:08,407 --> 00:02:11,193
Was the man who died

52
00:02:11,196 --> 00:02:14,511
who you thought he was?

53
00:02:14,513 --> 00:02:17,280
The dead talk...

54
00:02:17,282 --> 00:02:19,216
if you listen.

55
00:02:22,590 --> 00:02:24,495
_

56
00:02:28,293 --> 00:02:30,527
Still tight as...

57
00:02:30,529 --> 00:02:32,495
scales on a snake.

58
00:02:32,497 --> 00:02:35,298
Must have friends in
high places, Bagwell.

59
00:02:35,300 --> 00:02:38,602
How a cesspool like you gets his
walking papers I'll never know.

60
00:02:39,938 --> 00:02:43,640
This cesspool has been a model citizen.

61
00:02:43,642 --> 00:02:45,490
Model citizen.

62
00:02:46,378 --> 00:02:47,544
[closes zipper]

63
00:02:47,546 --> 00:02:51,214
$71.31.

64
00:02:51,216 --> 00:02:53,784
Laptop.

65
00:02:53,787 --> 00:02:55,652
Pack of gum, three pieces.

66
00:02:55,654 --> 00:02:57,487
How about you keep that?

67
00:02:57,489 --> 00:02:59,489
Whatever you bring in, you bring out.

68
00:02:59,491 --> 00:03:03,026
And one last piece of correspondence.

69
00:03:05,147 --> 00:03:07,414
Something really wrong with
the world when I'm receiving

70
00:03:07,417 --> 00:03:09,366
dozens of letters a
week for guys like you.

71
00:03:09,368 --> 00:03:12,669
Nothing compared to the e-mails.

72
00:03:12,671 --> 00:03:14,838
What is it with you
killers that put the satin

73
00:03:14,840 --> 00:03:16,439
on women's panties anyhow?

74
00:03:17,376 --> 00:03:18,975
[exhales]

75
00:03:18,977 --> 00:03:21,211
♪ ♪

76
00:03:30,582 --> 00:03:32,355
Lackaday!

77
00:03:34,441 --> 00:03:35,724
_

78
00:03:35,727 --> 00:03:38,061
[car engine roaring]

79
00:03:40,999 --> 00:03:42,032
[tires squeal]

80
00:03:48,373 --> 00:03:49,539
[car doors closing]

81
00:03:49,541 --> 00:03:50,573
[panting]

82
00:03:50,575 --> 00:03:52,976
[weapon cocking]

83
00:03:54,947 --> 00:03:56,379
Burrows!

84
00:03:56,381 --> 00:03:58,581
How about you step out and pay us

85
00:03:58,583 --> 00:04:00,817
the hundred grand you owe us?

86
00:04:02,154 --> 00:04:04,104
Take that as a no.

87
00:04:04,107 --> 00:04:06,489
Lincoln Burrows...

88
00:04:06,491 --> 00:04:08,058
says no.

89
00:04:08,994 --> 00:04:11,194
Big tough guy...

90
00:04:11,196 --> 00:04:13,396
who made it out of the neighborhood.

91
00:04:13,398 --> 00:04:16,099
And look at you now...
Back to your roots,

92
00:04:16,102 --> 00:04:17,867
the way you've always been.

93
00:04:17,869 --> 00:04:21,538
A small-time crook who
can't pay his debts.

94
00:04:21,540 --> 00:04:23,440
We're gonna find you, you know,

95
00:04:23,442 --> 00:04:25,569
and we're gonna open you up.

96
00:04:25,572 --> 00:04:27,138
[car door closes, engine starts]

97
00:04:33,952 --> 00:04:37,020
[dog barking in distance]

98
00:04:39,191 --> 00:04:42,092
T-BAG: Lincolny-linc.

99
00:04:42,094 --> 00:04:44,995
All huffin' and puffin'.

100
00:04:44,997 --> 00:04:47,973
Don't you look at me like I'm trash.

101
00:04:47,976 --> 00:04:50,543
My house is in order. I'm
clear with the government,

102
00:04:50,545 --> 00:04:52,411
the D.O.C. and my God.

103
00:04:52,413 --> 00:04:54,380
Doesn't appear to be the same with you.

104
00:04:54,382 --> 00:04:56,282
Look at you, all backslid.

105
00:04:56,284 --> 00:04:58,751
You're supposed to be going
up in the world as you age,

106
00:04:58,753 --> 00:05:00,586
or did you not get the memo?

107
00:05:00,588 --> 00:05:03,556
You don't get off my deck,
I'm gonna crack your skull.

108
00:05:03,558 --> 00:05:05,057
I wouldn't do that.

109
00:05:05,059 --> 00:05:07,026
Seems fate has deigned

110
00:05:07,028 --> 00:05:09,662
to join us at the hip once again,

111
00:05:09,664 --> 00:05:12,598
despite our mutual contempt.

112
00:05:17,482 --> 00:05:19,238
Have a look-see.

113
00:05:28,583 --> 00:05:31,050
[sighs]

114
00:05:31,052 --> 00:05:32,952
Where'd you get this?

115
00:05:32,954 --> 00:05:35,188
Received it on release
earlier this week.

116
00:05:35,190 --> 00:05:36,756
No return address.

117
00:05:38,126 --> 00:05:40,426
If you're playing me, I'll kill you.

118
00:05:40,428 --> 00:05:42,595
Take a look at that postmark on that.

119
00:05:43,965 --> 00:05:45,865
T-BAG: I may be a sophisti-cat,

120
00:05:45,867 --> 00:05:47,667
but not so sophisticated

121
00:05:47,669 --> 00:05:49,835
as to forge something like that.

122
00:05:51,139 --> 00:05:53,372
Besides...

123
00:05:53,374 --> 00:05:56,809
what angle could I
possibly have in coming here

124
00:05:56,811 --> 00:05:58,711
and telling you that it
looks like your brother

125
00:05:58,713 --> 00:06:01,280
might just be alive?

126
00:06:01,282 --> 00:06:04,784
♪ ♪

127
00:06:09,424 --> 00:06:11,657
♪ ♪

128
00:06:43,026 --> 00:06:44,459
It's impossible.

129
00:06:44,462 --> 00:06:45,703
That's what I thought.

130
00:06:45,705 --> 00:06:47,304
Why'd he send it to you?

131
00:06:47,306 --> 00:06:49,306
Again, what I thought.

132
00:06:49,308 --> 00:06:52,643
And then I gave the
words another look-see.

133
00:06:52,645 --> 00:06:54,612
Maybe that's the answer.

134
00:06:57,149 --> 00:06:58,983
"By your hand

135
00:06:58,985 --> 00:07:00,985
you shall know the
glories of your Progeny

136
00:07:00,987 --> 00:07:03,420
and our world will be

137
00:07:03,422 --> 00:07:06,290
made right forevermore."

138
00:07:06,292 --> 00:07:08,492
Hell if I know what that means.

139
00:07:08,494 --> 00:07:10,928
But just like that
envelope's addressed to me,

140
00:07:10,930 --> 00:07:13,306
those words are addressed
to me. Got to be!

141
00:07:13,309 --> 00:07:14,098
Get out.

142
00:07:14,100 --> 00:07:15,833
I'm trying to work with you here.

143
00:07:15,835 --> 00:07:18,075
Is there any possible way
your brother could've survived?

144
00:07:20,506 --> 00:07:22,306
My brother's dead.

145
00:07:22,308 --> 00:07:24,708
Th-Then who sent this? And why?

146
00:07:26,045 --> 00:07:27,778
Get out.

147
00:07:30,917 --> 00:07:33,951
Least let me take my
rightful correspondence.

148
00:07:36,155 --> 00:07:37,421
[scoffs]

149
00:07:37,424 --> 00:07:39,711
Oh, I made a copy, Burrows.

150
00:07:39,714 --> 00:07:42,781
I knew you'd be the same
obstinate son of a beyotch

151
00:07:42,784 --> 00:07:44,851
you always been, but I'd
hoped you'd seen the light.

152
00:07:44,854 --> 00:07:46,964
But you are what you is
and you is what you are.

153
00:07:46,966 --> 00:07:48,532
[scoffs]

154
00:07:50,036 --> 00:07:51,669
Still, I'm telling you...

155
00:07:51,671 --> 00:07:54,638
fate has got us joined
at the hip somehow.

156
00:07:59,712 --> 00:08:00,711
[door closes]

157
00:08:00,713 --> 00:08:02,046
[takes deep breath]

158
00:08:02,048 --> 00:08:03,414
[exhales]

159
00:08:08,521 --> 00:08:11,155
♪ ♪

160
00:08:16,065 --> 00:08:17,831
MAN: Where you in from?

161
00:08:17,834 --> 00:08:18,862
LINCOLN: Chicago.

162
00:08:18,864 --> 00:08:20,698
MAN: Love Chicago.

163
00:08:20,700 --> 00:08:23,834
- There you go.
- Thanks, man.

164
00:08:52,298 --> 00:08:54,565
[engine roaring]

165
00:09:00,106 --> 00:09:02,306
[exhales]

166
00:09:11,050 --> 00:09:12,649
[laughs softly] I didn't think

167
00:09:12,651 --> 00:09:14,618
I was ever gonna see you again.

168
00:09:14,620 --> 00:09:17,021
You didn't come to the wedding.

169
00:09:17,023 --> 00:09:19,390
I mean, I figured I... I get it...

170
00:09:19,392 --> 00:09:22,326
He hates me for marrying someone
other than his brother, but...

171
00:09:23,496 --> 00:09:26,163
I haven't been in a good place, Sara.

172
00:09:26,165 --> 00:09:29,538
My brain, it's... it's been a mess.

173
00:09:29,541 --> 00:09:31,035
That's why I didn't show up.

174
00:09:31,037 --> 00:09:34,605
And... I didn't want my
nephew to see me like that.

175
00:09:34,607 --> 00:09:36,340
[sighs quietly]

176
00:09:36,342 --> 00:09:39,476
But now it's impossible to stay away.

177
00:09:39,478 --> 00:09:42,479
SARA: Someone's got
a sick sense of humor.

178
00:09:43,557 --> 00:09:45,690
I know you want it to be true.

179
00:09:45,693 --> 00:09:47,426
Losing a brother...

180
00:09:47,429 --> 00:09:49,796
The massive hole that
leaves in your life.

181
00:09:49,798 --> 00:09:52,732
Like the same massive
hole losing a husband is.

182
00:09:52,734 --> 00:09:54,035
[sighs]

183
00:09:54,038 --> 00:09:56,272
- Maybe.
- [door opens, closes]

184
00:09:58,874 --> 00:10:00,840
Lincoln Burrows?

185
00:10:00,842 --> 00:10:01,908
Jacob.

186
00:10:01,910 --> 00:10:03,210
I haven't seen you in what,

187
00:10:03,212 --> 00:10:04,126
three, four years?

188
00:10:04,129 --> 00:10:05,378
- Yeah.
- MIKE: Uncle Lincoln!

189
00:10:05,380 --> 00:10:07,581
Hey-hey! Buddy!

190
00:10:07,583 --> 00:10:09,049
Oh...

191
00:10:09,051 --> 00:10:10,717
so good to see you.

192
00:10:10,719 --> 00:10:13,386
Did you bring me any sunken treasures?

193
00:10:13,388 --> 00:10:16,022
Sunken treasures?

194
00:10:16,024 --> 00:10:17,992
Oh. The dive shop.

195
00:10:17,995 --> 00:10:19,993
- Panama.
- Yeah, I've been telling him stories

196
00:10:19,995 --> 00:10:22,862
about being down there before
we came back to the States.

197
00:10:22,864 --> 00:10:24,331
You've become kind of like

198
00:10:24,334 --> 00:10:26,890
a mythological hero to
him. Let me get some beers.

199
00:10:26,893 --> 00:10:29,436
- I want to know what you been up to. Okay.
- Sure, man. Yeah.

200
00:10:29,438 --> 00:10:30,870
Come here.

201
00:10:30,872 --> 00:10:32,706
I want you to go wash up, okay?

202
00:10:32,708 --> 00:10:35,239
And then you can catch
up with your uncle.

203
00:10:39,181 --> 00:10:41,047
He hasn't just mythologized you.

204
00:10:41,049 --> 00:10:42,849
He mythologizes Michael, too.

205
00:10:42,851 --> 00:10:45,752
It's like someone thinking
he was born to a god,

206
00:10:45,754 --> 00:10:48,188
a god he's never met...

207
00:10:48,190 --> 00:10:50,657
and who isn't here.

208
00:10:52,361 --> 00:10:54,561
And who never will be again.

209
00:10:55,764 --> 00:10:58,098
I can be pragmatic.

210
00:10:58,100 --> 00:11:00,467
Michael was sick.

211
00:11:00,469 --> 00:11:02,869
He was terminally sick,

212
00:11:02,871 --> 00:11:05,372
and he died.

213
00:11:06,441 --> 00:11:08,742
[sighs]

214
00:11:12,206 --> 00:11:15,174
Sara...

215
00:11:15,177 --> 00:11:17,284
how do you explain that?

216
00:11:17,286 --> 00:11:19,753
[sighs]

217
00:11:21,456 --> 00:11:23,290
It's Photoshop, Linc,

218
00:11:23,292 --> 00:11:25,258
or something.

219
00:11:25,260 --> 00:11:27,961
You got to consider the source.

220
00:11:27,963 --> 00:11:30,497
This came from T-Bag.

221
00:11:31,560 --> 00:11:34,534
I know you want it to be true.

222
00:11:34,536 --> 00:11:37,434
I want it to be true.

223
00:11:42,177 --> 00:11:44,044
[loud, indistinct music
plays in next room]

224
00:11:44,046 --> 00:11:47,147
How about a date tonight, model citizen?

225
00:11:47,149 --> 00:11:49,070
[groans]

226
00:11:49,073 --> 00:11:51,251
[sighs] A little well-earned love

227
00:11:51,253 --> 00:11:53,286
after a long time at sea.

228
00:11:53,288 --> 00:11:55,622
Jeh... boop.

229
00:11:55,624 --> 00:11:57,691
Miss Dorothy.

230
00:11:57,693 --> 00:12:00,160
E-mailing her undying love

231
00:12:00,162 --> 00:12:03,463
from Aurora, Illinois.

232
00:12:04,296 --> 00:12:05,795
I-eesh.

233
00:12:06,847 --> 00:12:08,601
[sighs] How about this one?

234
00:12:08,603 --> 00:12:12,072
"Love Cannon Alonzo in Champaign."

235
00:12:12,074 --> 00:12:15,008
Ooh. Hop on that just on the name alone.

236
00:12:15,010 --> 00:12:18,044
[computer chimes]

237
00:12:18,046 --> 00:12:19,649
- _
- What the hell?

238
00:12:19,652 --> 00:12:22,220
Prosthetic research?

239
00:12:25,908 --> 00:12:29,446
[sighs]

240
00:12:29,448 --> 00:12:32,449
[crow caws, birds sing]

241
00:12:32,451 --> 00:12:35,419
Smart girl, your Sara.

242
00:12:35,421 --> 00:12:36,820
She's right.

243
00:12:36,822 --> 00:12:39,723
I'm just desperate to see your face.

244
00:12:39,725 --> 00:12:44,127
My life's been a mess
ever since you left.

245
00:12:44,129 --> 00:12:46,630
Fallen back into my old ways.

246
00:12:46,632 --> 00:12:49,600
Something you wouldn't tolerate.

247
00:12:49,602 --> 00:12:52,002
But I got good in me, Michael.

248
00:12:52,004 --> 00:12:54,304
I got good in me.

249
00:12:54,306 --> 00:12:56,473
[Lincoln sighs heavily]

250
00:12:56,475 --> 00:12:58,875
It'd just be nice if

251
00:12:58,877 --> 00:13:02,279
you were here to... help me find it.

252
00:13:05,851 --> 00:13:08,285
So... yeah.

253
00:13:08,287 --> 00:13:09,853
[crow caws]

254
00:13:30,376 --> 00:13:32,809
"Ogygia."

255
00:13:32,811 --> 00:13:35,712
[keyboard keys clicking loudly]

256
00:13:41,887 --> 00:13:44,655
Telling me where you are.

257
00:13:46,651 --> 00:13:48,518
There's only one way to find out.

258
00:13:55,734 --> 00:13:58,735
[groans]

259
00:14:15,421 --> 00:14:18,689
MAN: Theodore Bagwell.

260
00:14:18,691 --> 00:14:22,192
And you're Dr. Whitcombe,

261
00:14:22,194 --> 00:14:24,995
the man who invited me
to this mystery meeting

262
00:14:24,997 --> 00:14:29,800
at 9:30 at night when the
rest of the building's closed.

263
00:14:29,802 --> 00:14:31,802
I know what you've done.

264
00:14:31,804 --> 00:14:34,771
That's why I don't want to be
seen associating with your sort.

265
00:14:34,773 --> 00:14:36,940
Just want to know why I'm here, and...

266
00:14:36,942 --> 00:14:39,376
if this has anything to do
with that special envelope

267
00:14:39,378 --> 00:14:40,677
I received in the prison.

268
00:14:40,679 --> 00:14:42,979
I know nothing about an envelope.

269
00:14:42,981 --> 00:14:45,649
I can only tell you my work.

270
00:14:45,651 --> 00:14:48,251
Targeted muscle reinnervation.

271
00:14:48,253 --> 00:14:51,288
Using the brain to manipulate prosthesis

272
00:14:51,290 --> 00:14:53,156
as it were a natural limb.

273
00:14:53,158 --> 00:14:55,092
But as with any cutting-edge work,

274
00:14:55,094 --> 00:14:57,894
funding is not easy to find, and yet,

275
00:14:57,896 --> 00:14:59,763
incredibly, I got the grant

276
00:14:59,766 --> 00:15:02,343
in the form of a
considerable anonymous grant

277
00:15:02,345 --> 00:15:03,400
on one condition...

278
00:15:03,402 --> 00:15:07,037
The first recipient of my procedure...

279
00:15:07,039 --> 00:15:08,839
is you.

280
00:15:11,610 --> 00:15:13,610
I can equip you

281
00:15:13,612 --> 00:15:16,012
with a fully articulate prosthetic,

282
00:15:16,014 --> 00:15:18,648
operationally indistinguishable
from a real hand.

283
00:15:18,650 --> 00:15:23,220
All of this because
of an anonymous donor?

284
00:15:23,222 --> 00:15:25,589
Someone seems to have
plans for both of us.

285
00:15:25,591 --> 00:15:28,592
I've reserved an
operational lab for Monday

286
00:15:28,594 --> 00:15:31,261
if you decide you are interested.

287
00:15:31,263 --> 00:15:33,196
It's your hand, ultimately.

288
00:15:43,742 --> 00:15:46,143
By your hand,

289
00:15:46,145 --> 00:15:51,081
you shall know glories of your progeny.

290
00:15:51,083 --> 00:15:53,683
What's that?

291
00:15:56,288 --> 00:15:57,778
Nothing, Doc.

292
00:16:00,626 --> 00:16:03,093
[panting]

293
00:16:03,095 --> 00:16:05,629
[shovel thudding hollowly]

294
00:16:05,631 --> 00:16:08,231
[shovel clanks on ground]

295
00:16:21,413 --> 00:16:23,280
[grunting]

296
00:16:23,282 --> 00:16:25,348
[creaking]

297
00:16:39,096 --> 00:16:40,929
[panting]

298
00:16:44,374 --> 00:16:47,804
Come on, Michael.

299
00:16:47,806 --> 00:16:49,739
You must have left me something.

300
00:16:49,741 --> 00:16:51,507
Come on!

301
00:16:51,509 --> 00:16:55,311
[panting]

302
00:16:55,313 --> 00:16:57,113
Come on.

303
00:16:57,115 --> 00:16:59,582
[panting]

304
00:17:01,319 --> 00:17:03,820
[sniffs, panting]

305
00:17:17,435 --> 00:17:19,359
[brakes squeak]

306
00:17:32,450 --> 00:17:33,950
[computer chirps]

307
00:17:33,952 --> 00:17:36,085
[clack, tires squeal]

308
00:17:37,122 --> 00:17:39,255
[computer chirps]

309
00:17:40,986 --> 00:17:42,525
What's going on?

310
00:17:44,664 --> 00:17:46,197
[groans]

311
00:17:49,400 --> 00:17:51,200
[groans]

312
00:17:52,804 --> 00:17:55,505
[groans, tires squealing, horns honking]

313
00:17:55,507 --> 00:17:57,640
[groans]

314
00:17:59,477 --> 00:18:01,110
[grunts]

315
00:18:10,188 --> 00:18:12,155
[loud gasping]

316
00:18:12,157 --> 00:18:14,157
[water gurgling]

317
00:18:14,159 --> 00:18:17,160
[groans, pants]

318
00:18:18,962 --> 00:18:20,995
[vehicle approaching]

319
00:18:22,233 --> 00:18:25,301
[panting]

320
00:18:39,551 --> 00:18:41,817
Oh, my God, what happened?

321
00:18:41,820 --> 00:18:44,719
I'm not sure. I'm gonna call

322
00:18:44,721 --> 00:18:47,056
- the police.
- [man speaks indistinctly]

323
00:18:47,058 --> 00:18:48,206
[panting]

324
00:18:48,209 --> 00:18:49,853
[indistinct chatter,
car door opens, closes]

325
00:18:49,855 --> 00:18:52,452
[car engine starts]

326
00:18:58,544 --> 00:19:00,978
[phone ringing]

327
00:19:02,733 --> 00:19:04,207
Hello?

328
00:19:04,210 --> 00:19:06,800
I dug up Michael's grave.
He's not in it.

329
00:19:06,803 --> 00:19:07,959
He... What?

330
00:19:07,962 --> 00:19:09,779
Sara, someone just tried to kill me.

331
00:19:09,781 --> 00:19:11,047
They've been watching.
They've been watching,

332
00:19:11,049 --> 00:19:12,928
- probably for...
- Who tried to kill you?

333
00:19:12,931 --> 00:19:14,383
It started at the airport. I...

334
00:19:14,385 --> 00:19:16,752
There was a... a red sedan.

335
00:19:16,754 --> 00:19:18,054
It started following me.

336
00:19:18,056 --> 00:19:20,089
Then they... they... they swapped

337
00:19:20,091 --> 00:19:21,457
down to a...

338
00:19:21,459 --> 00:19:23,392
What was it? A pickup.

339
00:19:23,394 --> 00:19:25,194
[vehicle engine approaching]

340
00:19:26,764 --> 00:19:27,997
What color was the pickup?

341
00:19:27,999 --> 00:19:29,449
LINCOLN: Black.

342
00:19:29,452 --> 00:19:30,967
- Why?
- [phone beeps off]

343
00:19:30,969 --> 00:19:32,268
- [dial tone sounds]
- Sara?

344
00:19:32,270 --> 00:19:33,502
Jacob?

345
00:19:33,504 --> 00:19:35,238
- Yeah.
- Behind one of

346
00:19:35,240 --> 00:19:37,807
the pictures on the brick wall,
there's a hole, and there's

347
00:19:37,809 --> 00:19:39,709
- a gun in it. I need you to get it.
- What?!

348
00:19:39,711 --> 00:19:42,026
Right now! Right now!
Someone's coming for us!

349
00:19:42,029 --> 00:19:45,401
A gun? What do you mean, a gun?

350
00:19:46,684 --> 00:19:48,323
Mike?

351
00:19:48,326 --> 00:19:50,765
WOMAN: 9-1-1. What is your emergency?

352
00:19:50,768 --> 00:19:51,921
I have an armed intruder in the house.

353
00:19:51,923 --> 00:19:53,055
I need you to send people right away.

354
00:19:53,057 --> 00:19:55,091
I don't have time. Please, come.

355
00:19:56,761 --> 00:19:58,628
- Mike?
- JACOB: Sara?

356
00:19:58,630 --> 00:20:01,063
What's going on, Sara?

357
00:20:02,535 --> 00:20:04,268
[panting] Hey.

358
00:20:04,271 --> 00:20:06,302
- Mom?
- Come here.

359
00:20:06,304 --> 00:20:08,104
[door slams open]

360
00:20:12,076 --> 00:20:13,476
[panting]

361
00:20:14,727 --> 00:20:17,027
Sara? Sara!

362
00:20:20,485 --> 00:20:22,685
[panting]

363
00:20:24,856 --> 00:20:27,056
[Jacob groans]

364
00:20:27,058 --> 00:20:30,860
[Jacob groaning]

365
00:20:30,862 --> 00:20:33,496
[pained groaning]

366
00:20:33,498 --> 00:20:36,399
It's just me. There's
no one else in the house.

367
00:20:36,401 --> 00:20:38,901
- JACOB: What do you want?
- Get in the tub.

368
00:20:40,305 --> 00:20:43,005
Who's here, Mom? What do they want?

369
00:20:43,007 --> 00:20:45,675
[Jacob groaning]

370
00:20:45,677 --> 00:20:47,777
I don't know, baby.

371
00:20:49,380 --> 00:20:52,348
[door squeaks open]

372
00:20:52,350 --> 00:20:54,750
[metal creaking, Sara groans]

373
00:20:57,184 --> 00:20:58,888
Okay, listen to me, if anyone comes

374
00:20:58,890 --> 00:21:01,123
through that door, you don't move, okay?

375
00:21:01,125 --> 00:21:03,759
I will put this through them,
and you will not be harmed.

376
00:21:03,761 --> 00:21:06,929
You understand? Good boy.

377
00:21:19,744 --> 00:21:21,844
[sirens wailing in distance]

378
00:21:25,550 --> 00:21:27,850
[groans]

379
00:21:37,028 --> 00:21:38,394
Jacob?

380
00:21:38,396 --> 00:21:39,528
[Jacob groans]

381
00:21:39,530 --> 00:21:40,863
MIKE: Mom.

382
00:21:40,865 --> 00:21:42,365
Go get every towel you can find.

383
00:21:42,367 --> 00:21:43,833
Right now, right now.

384
00:21:44,582 --> 00:21:46,015
Please, Jacob.

385
00:21:46,018 --> 00:21:47,736
Okay. I think it got an artery.

386
00:21:47,739 --> 00:21:49,572
Stay with me. I want you
to look at me, all right?

387
00:21:49,574 --> 00:21:51,749
Don't close your eyes and
don't go to sleep, all right?

388
00:21:51,752 --> 00:21:53,642
I'm gonna need you to stay with me.

389
00:21:53,644 --> 00:21:55,243
I need an ambulance!

390
00:22:00,406 --> 00:22:02,973
[indistinct chatter]

391
00:22:05,712 --> 00:22:08,212
- How is he?
- The shot almost completely

392
00:22:08,214 --> 00:22:10,514
severed his femoral artery so
they're trying to stabilize him.

393
00:22:10,516 --> 00:22:12,016
And him?

394
00:22:12,018 --> 00:22:13,351
SARA: He's seven.

395
00:22:18,624 --> 00:22:20,691
How you doing, Mikey?

396
00:22:20,693 --> 00:22:22,226
Something's happening, isn't it?

397
00:22:22,228 --> 00:22:23,594
First, you come

398
00:22:23,596 --> 00:22:26,664
and that person came in our house.

399
00:22:26,666 --> 00:22:30,768
It has something to do with
my real father, doesn't it?

400
00:22:30,770 --> 00:22:32,236
Why do you say that?

401
00:22:32,238 --> 00:22:35,072
Because I can see it in her face.

402
00:22:39,299 --> 00:22:41,990
I'm gonna need to talk to your uncle.

403
00:22:41,993 --> 00:22:43,614
I'm gonna be right over there

404
00:22:43,616 --> 00:22:46,417
where you can see me. Okay?

405
00:22:51,124 --> 00:22:52,523
What's going on?

406
00:22:52,525 --> 00:22:54,191
We've awoken something.

407
00:22:54,193 --> 00:22:56,093
Something people are trying
to hide about Michael.

408
00:22:56,095 --> 00:22:57,528
Your brother's dead, Lincoln.

409
00:22:57,530 --> 00:22:59,797
Or is he dead? Where is the body?

410
00:22:59,799 --> 00:23:02,400
Then why did he leave?

411
00:23:02,402 --> 00:23:05,970
If he's been out there
for all of these years,

412
00:23:05,972 --> 00:23:08,339
why did he abandon his own son?

413
00:23:08,341 --> 00:23:10,274
You know I'm right.

414
00:23:10,276 --> 00:23:12,443
It wouldn't be like this if
something wasn't happening.

415
00:23:12,445 --> 00:23:14,545
- It wouldn't, but...
- Let's fight back.

416
00:23:14,547 --> 00:23:16,046
I don't know who we're fighting.

417
00:23:16,048 --> 00:23:17,448
Let's go to Yemen and find out.

418
00:23:17,450 --> 00:23:20,191
To Yemen? I have a son, Lincoln.

419
00:23:20,194 --> 00:23:22,886
My husband's in the ER. Right?
Look, leaving them is exactly

420
00:23:22,889 --> 00:23:24,828
the wrong thing for me to do right now.

421
00:23:24,831 --> 00:23:26,821
Ma'am. He's ready to see you.

422
00:23:26,824 --> 00:23:28,793
One second.

423
00:23:32,241 --> 00:23:33,874
I'll do it.

424
00:23:33,876 --> 00:23:35,876
I'll go to Yemen.

425
00:23:35,878 --> 00:23:38,211
You don't know a damn thing about Yemen.

426
00:23:38,213 --> 00:23:40,313
I'll find someone who does.

427
00:23:41,650 --> 00:23:43,784
See ya, Mikey.

428
00:23:49,425 --> 00:23:51,391
_

429
00:23:51,393 --> 00:23:54,528
[praying continues]

430
00:24:02,604 --> 00:24:04,771
LINCOLN: I envy you.

431
00:24:04,773 --> 00:24:06,873
You changed your life around.

432
00:24:06,875 --> 00:24:10,677
C-NOTE: A man gets tired of
living a profligate life.

433
00:24:10,679 --> 00:24:14,025
So I took up jihad. Real jihad,

434
00:24:14,028 --> 00:24:17,384
not that madness that
you see on the news.

435
00:24:17,386 --> 00:24:19,124
War within.

436
00:24:19,127 --> 00:24:23,790
The spiritual struggle
to clean up your act.

437
00:24:23,792 --> 00:24:25,892
Finding and serving God.

438
00:24:27,796 --> 00:24:30,897
That's good, man.

439
00:24:30,899 --> 00:24:32,999
The world needs it, Linc.

440
00:24:33,000 --> 00:24:35,801
I mean we're, uh, we're small here

441
00:24:35,804 --> 00:24:37,337
but we do what we can

442
00:24:37,340 --> 00:24:39,573
to help the peace efforts
in the Middle East.

443
00:24:39,575 --> 00:24:43,243
Working on anti-radicalization
campaigns here at home.

444
00:24:43,245 --> 00:24:46,246
Like I said, the struggle.

445
00:24:47,382 --> 00:24:48,982
That's why I'm here.

446
00:24:48,984 --> 00:24:51,184
If I needed to get to Yemen,

447
00:24:51,186 --> 00:24:52,886
that something you could help me with?

448
00:24:57,993 --> 00:24:59,626
C-NOTE: I thought he was dead.

449
00:24:59,629 --> 00:25:02,997
So did everyone.

450
00:25:02,998 --> 00:25:04,765
But Ogygia?

451
00:25:04,767 --> 00:25:06,199
I mean, that's for heavy hitters,

452
00:25:06,201 --> 00:25:07,434
political prisoners.

453
00:25:07,436 --> 00:25:09,936
In Yemen, it doesn't come any worse.

454
00:25:09,938 --> 00:25:12,606
I mean, do you know what it
would take to stage a death?

455
00:25:12,608 --> 00:25:15,408
Not to mention keeping
a man who is not dead

456
00:25:15,410 --> 00:25:17,344
under the radar for seven years.

457
00:25:17,346 --> 00:25:19,679
Some very powerful players.

458
00:25:19,681 --> 00:25:24,551
Sayed, what do you make
of this mosque right here?

459
00:25:29,031 --> 00:25:31,465
Aksa Mosque. It's one of
the main ones in Sana'a.

460
00:25:31,468 --> 00:25:33,201
- It's very distinct.
- Ah.

461
00:25:35,063 --> 00:25:36,997
SAYED: Sightlines seem pretty consistent

462
00:25:36,999 --> 00:25:39,432
with what it would probably be
from the prison to the mosque.

463
00:25:39,434 --> 00:25:42,736
Now, you ask me, that photo's legit.

464
00:25:42,738 --> 00:25:46,640
Then that's the
building my brother's in.

465
00:25:46,642 --> 00:25:49,676
Easiest way to find out is
to call the prison and ask.

466
00:25:49,678 --> 00:25:53,046
Mafi Michael Scofield.

467
00:25:53,048 --> 00:25:54,981
Shukran.

468
00:25:57,853 --> 00:25:59,888
There's no Michael Scofield.

469
00:25:59,891 --> 00:26:01,521
Punch up an image from the Internet.

470
00:26:01,523 --> 00:26:03,089
Michael Scofield.

471
00:26:03,091 --> 00:26:04,324
Send it to the prison.

472
00:26:04,326 --> 00:26:06,193
Maybe he's under a different name.

473
00:26:06,195 --> 00:26:07,260
C-NOTE: Listen, Linc,

474
00:26:07,262 --> 00:26:09,495
I got to say something, man.

475
00:26:09,498 --> 00:26:11,031
Man, you got to slow your roll.

476
00:26:11,033 --> 00:26:12,332
Yemen is in a civil war.

477
00:26:12,334 --> 00:26:14,167
They're really close to collapse.

478
00:26:14,169 --> 00:26:17,270
It's no place for a white
man with an American passport,

479
00:26:17,272 --> 00:26:20,173
no command of Arabic, to
just show up on a whim.

480
00:26:20,175 --> 00:26:22,890
And yet, apparently, my brother did.

481
00:26:22,893 --> 00:26:25,211
Got a picture. Your
brother's intake photo

482
00:26:25,214 --> 00:26:27,681
from the Fox River Penitentiary.

483
00:26:30,018 --> 00:26:33,553
Here's his DMV photo

484
00:26:33,555 --> 00:26:36,222
and here's a photo from
his old workplace Web site.

485
00:26:36,225 --> 00:26:37,791
LINCOLN: It's not him.

486
00:26:37,794 --> 00:26:39,927
None of them are.

487
00:26:42,911 --> 00:26:45,165
Someone's erasing him from history.

488
00:26:49,426 --> 00:26:52,468
- Lincoln, where are you going?
- Hotel, to grab my stuff,

489
00:26:52,470 --> 00:26:54,069
- then the airport.
- Hey, listen.

490
00:26:54,071 --> 00:26:55,671
You're not going to Yemen.

491
00:26:55,673 --> 00:26:58,273
- Stop me.
- You won't make it three days.

492
00:26:58,275 --> 00:27:00,209
We need to go through
the proper channels.

493
00:27:00,211 --> 00:27:01,610
The proper channels?

494
00:27:01,612 --> 00:27:03,946
Someone's erasing his existence.

495
00:27:03,948 --> 00:27:05,981
Who does that? Who has that ability?

496
00:27:05,983 --> 00:27:07,382
I'm telling you, Michael's caught

497
00:27:07,384 --> 00:27:08,784
in the middle of something big.

498
00:27:08,786 --> 00:27:10,552
What if he's not caught in the middle?

499
00:27:10,554 --> 00:27:12,387
What are you saying?

500
00:27:12,389 --> 00:27:14,423
Michael has never been anyone's sucker.

501
00:27:14,425 --> 00:27:17,359
He's always been in control. Always.

502
00:27:17,361 --> 00:27:19,094
You saying he faked his own death?

503
00:27:19,096 --> 00:27:20,863
I'm saying you need to look

504
00:27:20,865 --> 00:27:22,231
at all of the possibilities

505
00:27:22,233 --> 00:27:24,166
before you walk into a war zone.

506
00:27:34,245 --> 00:27:36,578
[sighs]

507
00:27:36,580 --> 00:27:38,147
I wasn't sure you'd come.

508
00:27:38,149 --> 00:27:42,684
Sometimes a man has
to surrender to fate.

509
00:27:42,686 --> 00:27:46,221
See what it has in store for him.

510
00:27:46,223 --> 00:27:47,956
[monitor beeping]

511
00:27:50,394 --> 00:27:52,094
WHITCOMBE: We'll need to put you under.

512
00:27:52,096 --> 00:27:54,797
No, no, no. I don't do
general anesthetic, compadre.

513
00:27:54,799 --> 00:27:57,266
It's mandatory for a
procedure like this.

514
00:27:57,268 --> 00:27:58,634
You'll forgive me

515
00:27:58,636 --> 00:28:00,636
if I have a problem lying unconscious

516
00:28:00,638 --> 00:28:03,338
before a man with sharp
items at his disposal.

517
00:28:03,340 --> 00:28:05,340
It cannot be done without
a general anesthetic.

518
00:28:05,342 --> 00:28:07,042
Oh, I've done it before, friend.

519
00:28:07,044 --> 00:28:08,410
And look what it got you.

520
00:28:08,412 --> 00:28:10,379
[sighs]

521
00:28:10,381 --> 00:28:13,615
You do anything untoward to
me while I'm under and I'll...

522
00:28:13,617 --> 00:28:15,384
You are the last man I'd run afoul of.

523
00:28:15,386 --> 00:28:17,886
- Okay?
- Mm.

524
00:28:17,888 --> 00:28:21,924
Oh, fate, you mysterious bitch.

525
00:28:21,926 --> 00:28:24,693
Why you doing this to me?

526
00:28:26,697 --> 00:28:30,299
[monitor beeping]

527
00:28:30,301 --> 00:28:33,335
Hi. Dry cleaning. Nice jacket.

528
00:28:33,337 --> 00:28:34,736
Thank you, sir.

529
00:28:34,738 --> 00:28:36,171
Have a good day.

530
00:28:56,861 --> 00:28:58,360
[door creaks]

531
00:28:58,363 --> 00:29:00,463
[grunts]

532
00:29:00,466 --> 00:29:02,232
What the hell was that for?

533
00:29:02,235 --> 00:29:05,200
Sucre, what the hell are you doing here?

534
00:29:05,202 --> 00:29:08,136
C-Note told me what's going on.

535
00:29:08,138 --> 00:29:09,938
He tell you to talk me out of it?

536
00:29:09,940 --> 00:29:13,375
No. I'm coming with you.

537
00:29:13,377 --> 00:29:14,607
LINCOLN: You're not coming.

538
00:29:14,610 --> 00:29:16,478
SUCRE: Michael's my best
friend. If he's alive,

539
00:29:16,480 --> 00:29:17,913
if he's in trouble, I want to help.

540
00:29:17,915 --> 00:29:19,248
Don't you have a job or something?

541
00:29:19,250 --> 00:29:21,483
Yeah, on a tramp. Not great work,

542
00:29:21,485 --> 00:29:22,918
but hey, I'm an ex-con, right?

543
00:29:22,920 --> 00:29:24,286
Tramp?

544
00:29:24,288 --> 00:29:25,621
Yeah, I've been riding her for a while.

545
00:29:25,623 --> 00:29:26,955
What are you, a pimp?

546
00:29:26,957 --> 00:29:28,857
What? No. No, no, no.

547
00:29:28,859 --> 00:29:30,926
A tramp is a freelance cargo ship.

548
00:29:30,928 --> 00:29:33,241
We go to Hong Kong, Spain, Buenos Aires,

549
00:29:33,244 --> 00:29:34,545
basically wherever the boss tells us.

550
00:29:34,547 --> 00:29:35,979
Corrupt son of a bitch.

551
00:29:35,982 --> 00:29:37,232
Well, I suggest you
get back on that tramp,

552
00:29:37,234 --> 00:29:38,616
- 'cause you're not coming.
- I'm telling you,

553
00:29:38,618 --> 00:29:41,162
- I can help!
- Listen to me, this is the Middle East.

554
00:29:41,165 --> 00:29:43,272
Lots has changed. I'm an
international hitter now.

555
00:29:43,274 --> 00:29:44,606
A raconteur.

556
00:29:44,608 --> 00:29:46,608
I don't think that means
what you think it means.

557
00:29:46,610 --> 00:29:48,477
Don't speak to me like I don't
know French, I know French.

558
00:29:48,479 --> 00:29:49,678
And I'm brown, that's something.

559
00:29:49,680 --> 00:29:50,779
I'll fit in better over there

560
00:29:50,781 --> 00:29:52,648
than you will, snowflake.

561
00:29:52,650 --> 00:29:54,283
I decided I was wrong when I said

562
00:29:54,285 --> 00:29:56,184
you would be dead inside of three days.

563
00:29:56,186 --> 00:29:59,855
You go over there, you'll
be dead inside of one.

564
00:29:59,857 --> 00:30:02,157
But with me, we have
people at the mosque

565
00:30:02,159 --> 00:30:03,625
that have worked over there,

566
00:30:03,627 --> 00:30:05,027
people with legal connections

567
00:30:05,029 --> 00:30:06,662
that can get us inside of that prison.

568
00:30:06,664 --> 00:30:09,731
Hold on. You're not
saying he gets to go.

569
00:30:09,733 --> 00:30:11,233
He's not any browner than I am.

570
00:30:11,235 --> 00:30:13,535
[speaks Arabic] _

571
00:30:13,537 --> 00:30:14,569
Huh?

572
00:30:14,571 --> 00:30:16,271
No?

573
00:30:16,273 --> 00:30:18,307
I managed to pick up a little Arabic

574
00:30:18,309 --> 00:30:20,208
while I was serving in Iraq.

575
00:30:20,210 --> 00:30:22,344
AIRLINE EMPLOYEE: This is the
final boarding call for Flight 39

576
00:30:22,346 --> 00:30:24,846
to JFK, connecting to Yemen.
This is the final boarding...

577
00:30:24,848 --> 00:30:26,548
Listen, man.

578
00:30:26,550 --> 00:30:28,430
There's gonna be a time
when I'm gonna need you.

579
00:30:31,355 --> 00:30:32,788
[plane taking off in distance]

580
00:30:33,757 --> 00:30:36,058
You better find him.

581
00:30:36,060 --> 00:30:37,926
And you better call me when you do.

582
00:30:37,928 --> 00:30:39,795
I will.

583
00:30:44,535 --> 00:30:45,901
You really got contacts?

584
00:30:45,903 --> 00:30:48,837
Contacts with contacts.

585
00:30:52,650 --> 00:30:54,876
WOMAN: Could just follow
'em into the bathroom,

586
00:30:54,878 --> 00:30:57,612
ragdoll him in one of stalls
and be done with it.

587
00:30:57,614 --> 00:31:00,115
Then we'd have a body to deal with.

588
00:31:00,117 --> 00:31:01,850
And we want him utterly

589
00:31:01,852 --> 00:31:05,787
and irrevocably gone from this world.

590
00:31:05,788 --> 00:31:09,457
Where no amount of digging
will bring him back.

591
00:31:09,460 --> 00:31:12,041
[yelling, glass breaking]

592
00:31:12,044 --> 00:31:16,893
_

593
00:31:17,434 --> 00:31:19,334
[indistinct chatter]

594
00:31:22,072 --> 00:31:23,972
We're the only ones
coming into the place.

595
00:31:23,974 --> 00:31:25,774
C-NOTE: Yeah, the
country's falling apart.

596
00:31:25,776 --> 00:31:27,119
Everyone wants out.

597
00:31:27,122 --> 00:31:28,477
Who's that contact again?

598
00:31:28,479 --> 00:31:29,711
A woman named Sheba.

599
00:31:29,713 --> 00:31:30,689
Our handler.

600
00:31:30,692 --> 00:31:32,447
She helps us track
Americans that come in

601
00:31:32,449 --> 00:31:33,748
to fight the jihad fight.

602
00:31:33,750 --> 00:31:36,718
[explosions, panicked chatter]

603
00:31:36,720 --> 00:31:39,855
[car alarms blaring]

604
00:31:39,856 --> 00:31:42,323
Welcome to the civil war.

605
00:31:42,326 --> 00:31:43,625
[man whistles loudly]

606
00:31:43,627 --> 00:31:45,627
Mr. Franklin,

607
00:31:45,629 --> 00:31:47,429
Ms. Sheba sent me to collect you.

608
00:31:47,431 --> 00:31:48,563
As-salaam alaikum.

609
00:31:48,565 --> 00:31:49,765
Wa alaikum as-salaam.

610
00:31:49,767 --> 00:31:52,534
Uh, this way, gentlemen. Follow me.

611
00:31:58,381 --> 00:32:01,884
_

612
00:32:04,915 --> 00:32:08,016
GUIDE: Yemen very dangerous.

613
00:32:08,018 --> 00:32:10,886
You never know who's
enemies, who's friends.

614
00:32:10,888 --> 00:32:14,489
Everyone scratching each other's backs.

615
00:32:14,491 --> 00:32:16,591
ISIL is starting to attack the city.

616
00:32:16,593 --> 00:32:19,761
They have been building up
out in the desert for months.

617
00:32:19,763 --> 00:32:21,481
If they... take the city,

618
00:32:21,484 --> 00:32:23,418
they will kill all the secularists,

619
00:32:23,421 --> 00:32:25,220
install Sharia law.

620
00:32:25,222 --> 00:32:26,755
Huh. You know.

621
00:32:26,757 --> 00:32:28,590
You don't seem worried.

622
00:32:28,592 --> 00:32:29,892
[chuckles]

623
00:32:29,894 --> 00:32:32,695
I scratch backs, too, my friend.

624
00:32:41,339 --> 00:32:43,706
C-NOTE: No, no, no, no. This isn't right.

625
00:32:43,708 --> 00:32:45,374
Hey, wait a minute,

626
00:32:45,376 --> 00:32:46,709
this-this isn't the address.

627
00:32:46,711 --> 00:32:48,744
- I get cigarettes.
- No, no, you don't.

628
00:32:48,746 --> 00:32:50,579
You take us straight to
the address right now!

629
00:32:50,581 --> 00:32:51,613
I-I get cigarettes.

630
00:32:51,615 --> 00:32:54,249
C-NOTE: Linc, this is a setup.

631
00:32:54,251 --> 00:32:55,684
Grab your bag now.

632
00:33:09,356 --> 00:33:12,760
♪ ♪

633
00:33:21,989 --> 00:33:23,569
[C-Note speaking Arabic] _

634
00:33:24,843 --> 00:33:26,538
_

635
00:33:26,541 --> 00:33:28,240
[man speaks Arabic]

636
00:33:28,242 --> 00:33:30,176
[grunting]

637
00:33:30,178 --> 00:33:31,844
[man speaks Arabic]

638
00:33:33,581 --> 00:33:35,848
[grunting, yelling]

639
00:33:45,426 --> 00:33:46,659
[shouts in Arabic]

640
00:33:58,706 --> 00:34:01,540
Greetings from the U.S.
prison system, bitches.

641
00:34:06,414 --> 00:34:07,580
What is it?

642
00:34:08,538 --> 00:34:10,104
Someone set us up.

643
00:34:10,885 --> 00:34:12,485
Come quickly.

644
00:34:12,487 --> 00:34:14,386
- [gunfire]
- Or we'll all be dead!

645
00:34:14,388 --> 00:34:16,222
Go, go. She's one of us.

646
00:34:16,224 --> 00:34:18,475
Come on, grab your
bag. Come on, let's go!

647
00:34:18,478 --> 00:34:19,733
How did you find us?

648
00:34:19,736 --> 00:34:21,195
SHEBA: A contact at the airport saw you

649
00:34:21,197 --> 00:34:23,197
get into the wrong taxi.

650
00:34:23,199 --> 00:34:25,132
You're lucky I found you.

651
00:34:25,134 --> 00:34:28,268
This is very radicalized neighborhood.

652
00:34:28,270 --> 00:34:31,243
Whoever set you up couldn't
have set you up in a worse way.

653
00:34:34,377 --> 00:34:36,744
[panting]

654
00:34:36,746 --> 00:34:38,946
Throw your phones out the window.

655
00:34:38,948 --> 00:34:41,448
I don't want anyone tracking us.

656
00:34:44,153 --> 00:34:45,326
Do it!

657
00:34:45,329 --> 00:34:47,988
[opens, closes door]

658
00:34:47,990 --> 00:34:50,457
Sheba, this is Lincoln.

659
00:34:50,459 --> 00:34:53,160
Lincoln... Sheba.

660
00:34:56,932 --> 00:34:59,266
[monitor beeping steadily]

661
00:35:14,417 --> 00:35:16,316
[footsteps approaching]

662
00:35:17,686 --> 00:35:20,354
You've been made whole, Mr. Bagwell.

663
00:35:20,356 --> 00:35:23,123
You're free to go.

664
00:35:25,928 --> 00:35:29,463
Not till you tell me
what you've put in me.

665
00:35:29,465 --> 00:35:31,832
You feel an unease, do you?

666
00:35:31,834 --> 00:35:35,302
I'd venture that's what's
always been in you since birth.

667
00:35:35,304 --> 00:35:38,455
Your soul. I just put
the hardware into you.

668
00:35:38,458 --> 00:35:40,758
You're the thing that runs it.

669
00:35:42,545 --> 00:35:44,144
- Who's behind...
- Nobody!

670
00:35:44,146 --> 00:35:45,746
Nobody's behind this.

671
00:35:45,748 --> 00:35:47,014
[groans]

672
00:35:47,016 --> 00:35:48,749
What does that mean?

673
00:35:48,751 --> 00:35:51,118
I got a single word. That's it.

674
00:35:51,120 --> 00:35:54,354
Just... my benefactors ID'd
themselves by a single word.

675
00:35:54,356 --> 00:35:55,889
Outis.

676
00:35:55,891 --> 00:35:58,091
[grunts] I looked it up.

677
00:35:58,093 --> 00:36:01,228
It's Greek for "nobody."

678
00:36:06,001 --> 00:36:08,435
That's who your
benefactor is, Mr. Bagwell.

679
00:36:08,437 --> 00:36:09,570
[panting]

680
00:36:09,572 --> 00:36:11,505
Nobody.

681
00:36:14,243 --> 00:36:17,478
[Muslim call to prayer over speakers]

682
00:36:23,748 --> 00:36:25,815
[siren wailing in distance]

683
00:36:29,058 --> 00:36:31,558
[car horns honk in distance]

684
00:36:39,763 --> 00:36:42,560
_

685
00:36:43,873 --> 00:36:46,006
[footsteps approaching]

686
00:36:46,008 --> 00:36:47,841
Okay. [clears throat]

687
00:36:47,843 --> 00:36:49,076
LINCOLN: Who's this?

688
00:36:49,078 --> 00:36:52,513
Omar has connections in Ogygia Prison.

689
00:36:52,515 --> 00:36:54,147
He says he can arrange a visit.

690
00:36:54,149 --> 00:36:55,382
That mean Michael's in there?

691
00:36:55,384 --> 00:36:56,650
There's apparently an American

692
00:36:56,652 --> 00:36:57,618
in there matching

693
00:36:57,620 --> 00:36:58,785
your brother's description.

694
00:36:58,787 --> 00:37:00,420
There's just one thing.

695
00:37:00,422 --> 00:37:04,591
Arranging such a visit
is hard. Very difficult.

696
00:37:04,593 --> 00:37:06,560
- Comes at a price.
- Money's not a problem.

697
00:37:06,562 --> 00:37:08,161
[clicks tongue] Not money.

698
00:37:08,163 --> 00:37:09,843
Your passport.

699
00:37:09,846 --> 00:37:11,545
My passport?

700
00:37:11,548 --> 00:37:12,499
What, did...

701
00:37:12,501 --> 00:37:15,302
- you want to hold it?
- No. Straight trade.

702
00:37:15,304 --> 00:37:17,137
Visit for your passport.

703
00:37:17,139 --> 00:37:20,140
Uh, U.S. passport is like gold here.

704
00:37:20,142 --> 00:37:22,843
A few changes, and it can
be a ticket to freedom.

705
00:37:22,845 --> 00:37:24,511
Don't do it, Linc.

706
00:37:24,513 --> 00:37:25,913
C-NOTE: Mm-mm.

707
00:37:28,250 --> 00:37:31,385
I know it is not ideal, but...

708
00:37:31,387 --> 00:37:34,288
ideals as of right now
are history in Yemen.

709
00:37:35,275 --> 00:37:37,876
You cannot get out of the country

710
00:37:37,879 --> 00:37:39,660
without a passport.

711
00:37:39,662 --> 00:37:41,595
Don't do it.

712
00:37:49,104 --> 00:37:50,571
Inshallah...

713
00:37:50,573 --> 00:37:52,611
you will see your brother soon.

714
00:37:59,214 --> 00:38:03,850
I told myself I'd never
step foot in another prison.

715
00:38:03,852 --> 00:38:06,587
As long as we walk out of it.

716
00:38:09,920 --> 00:38:12,433
_

717
00:38:12,661 --> 00:38:14,494
[man grunting]

718
00:38:14,496 --> 00:38:16,530
[screaming]

719
00:38:16,532 --> 00:38:19,232
[shouting in Arabic]

720
00:38:19,234 --> 00:38:21,368
[man screams]

721
00:38:35,050 --> 00:38:36,650
[speaking in Arabic]

722
00:38:41,624 --> 00:38:43,256
[speaks in Arabic]

723
00:38:45,894 --> 00:38:47,694
[speaks in Arabic]

724
00:38:53,342 --> 00:38:54,801
There's no Michael Scofield.

725
00:38:54,803 --> 00:38:57,337
It was a scam to get my passport.

726
00:38:57,339 --> 00:38:59,473
Omar is one of my
most trusted operators.

727
00:38:59,475 --> 00:39:01,274
Listen, lady. Trust doesn't seem to mean

728
00:39:01,276 --> 00:39:02,542
a whole lot in this country.

729
00:39:02,544 --> 00:39:03,710
Give me a second, okay?

730
00:39:03,712 --> 00:39:05,612
I'll figure out a way
to work this thing out.

731
00:39:05,614 --> 00:39:07,247
An image.

732
00:39:07,249 --> 00:39:08,738
Right? The one that they sent to you?

733
00:39:08,741 --> 00:39:10,240
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
- Do you have it?

734
00:39:13,522 --> 00:39:14,721
Look.

735
00:39:14,723 --> 00:39:16,227
There. [clears throat]

736
00:39:17,292 --> 00:39:19,192
Kaniel Outis.

737
00:39:19,194 --> 00:39:22,095
Yes, Kaniel Outis. Is he here?

738
00:39:22,097 --> 00:39:24,665
[speaks in Arabic]

739
00:39:29,972 --> 00:39:32,606
He says, yes, the man
in the picture is here

740
00:39:32,608 --> 00:39:34,875
and we can see him, but only
'cause we're dealing with Sheba.

741
00:39:34,877 --> 00:39:36,176
Why did you say that name?

742
00:39:36,178 --> 00:39:37,911
Because of my brother's jacket.

743
00:39:37,913 --> 00:39:40,247
Thought you were on the
right side of God on this.

744
00:39:40,249 --> 00:39:42,215
Sheba. No, hey, hey. Sheba...

745
00:39:46,055 --> 00:39:47,988
Hey. Kaniel Outis

746
00:39:47,990 --> 00:39:49,523
is a big-time terrorist.

747
00:39:49,525 --> 00:39:51,024
They got him in here for murder.

748
00:39:51,026 --> 00:39:52,325
He's been working with ISIL

749
00:39:52,327 --> 00:39:53,760
trying to take down the government.

750
00:39:53,762 --> 00:39:55,362
Come on, C.

751
00:39:55,364 --> 00:39:57,564
You know that's not Michael.

752
00:39:57,566 --> 00:39:59,966
Well, whoever he is...

753
00:40:01,103 --> 00:40:03,270
we're about to meet him.

754
00:40:03,272 --> 00:40:04,538
[thunder crashes]

755
00:40:04,540 --> 00:40:06,740
MIKE: What was my father like?

756
00:40:09,011 --> 00:40:10,877
My real father.

757
00:40:13,716 --> 00:40:15,348
[sighs]

758
00:40:15,350 --> 00:40:17,517
Michael Scofield...

759
00:40:19,221 --> 00:40:21,321
was like a storm.

760
00:40:22,658 --> 00:40:23,990
Grab the camera.

761
00:40:23,992 --> 00:40:25,759
I want to prove he's alive.

762
00:40:28,697 --> 00:40:32,165
He was beautiful

763
00:40:32,167 --> 00:40:35,502
and frightening

764
00:40:35,504 --> 00:40:37,738
and mysterious.

765
00:40:38,874 --> 00:40:41,475
And he would show up in your life

766
00:40:41,477 --> 00:40:43,543
out of the clear blue sky

767
00:40:43,545 --> 00:40:48,348
and then he would
disappear just as quickly.

768
00:40:48,350 --> 00:40:51,124
But storms, they can come back.

769
00:40:51,127 --> 00:40:52,679
Can't they?

770
00:40:54,156 --> 00:40:55,655
Mm-hmm.

771
00:40:59,228 --> 00:41:02,562
Question is, if they come back,

772
00:41:02,564 --> 00:41:05,899
is it the same storm,

773
00:41:05,901 --> 00:41:08,301
or has something changed?

774
00:41:08,303 --> 00:41:10,137
[thunder crashes]

775
00:41:13,142 --> 00:41:14,641
Michael.

776
00:41:22,831 --> 00:41:24,197
New tats.

777
00:41:24,200 --> 00:41:26,953
What do you mean, new?

778
00:41:26,955 --> 00:41:28,822
We're gonna get you out of here.

779
00:41:30,225 --> 00:41:33,527
My name isn't Michael.

780
00:41:33,529 --> 00:41:35,750
And I don't know who you are.

781
00:41:39,468 --> 00:41:41,138
Sorry.

782
00:41:43,551 --> 00:41:46,906
[speaking in Arabic] _

783
00:41:46,909 --> 00:41:48,708
Michael.

784
00:41:54,850 --> 00:41:56,526
Michael.

785
00:42:05,260 --> 00:42:08,228
Michael, talk to me. Michael...

786
00:42:08,230 --> 00:42:09,830
Mike.

787
00:42:09,832 --> 00:42:11,832
Mike! What are you doing, damn it?!

788
00:42:14,203 --> 00:42:15,869
[door closes]

789
00:42:15,871 --> 00:42:17,737
[crying]

