TEACH: I'm prepared to
prosecute a defense of the harbor
and repel the navy
from here definitively
if you agree to join me in
sailing away from here for good.
I stole it from
you, the Urca gold.
Whatever happens out
here, one thing is certain...
you and I would be a
hell of a lot better off
as partners than as rivals.
I will have a launch ferry
me to the sand alone,
and I will make
the pardon address.
It shouldn't be you.
If you send someone
known to the men on
that beach, it might work.
Be it proclaimed that
any man on this island
who will renounce
piracy will be offered
a full and unqualified pardon.
All of you, that is, but one.
There shall be a bounty
of £10,000 sterling
for the capture of Charles
Vane, dead or alive.
FLINT: Since we've been becalmed,
our rate of drift has suggested
we had a good chance of making
landfall on one of these islands.
(SEAGULLS CALLING)
(WAVES CRASHING)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(MAN SHOUTING COMMANDS)
(GRUNTING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(GROANS)
Does it hurt?
Less so.
You know, fresh water helps.
The men have been
asking questions.
Soon we'll need an answer.
What's next for us?
I've been thinking about our
engagement with Captain Hornigold.
He offered pardons
to our entire crew.
He had no way of knowing
how many men we even had,
which suggests he had the
number covered by a wide margin.
And once someone's
given him 100,
what's to say they
haven't given him 200?
500? More?
Go on.
And Billy said something to me.
Said that someone else likely
procured those pardons for Hornigold.
I started wondering.
If you're Whitehall and
you have it in your head
you want to finally retake
Nassau from the pirates,
isn't the opening
move in that attack
the introduction of
a universal pardon?
You been putting this
together all this time
and never saying
anything to me about it?
Well, you and I
haven't exactly been
on the warmest of terms lately.
No, I... I suppose not.
Well, then it's clear.
The men must be prepared to
return to an embattled Nassau.
They must know we're about to
join a fight to resist a British incursion.
It's likely over already.
The fight. If there
was one at all.
It's likely it didn't last long.
(GASPS)
The pardons will be tempting,
but our men resisted.
Our men resisted because
you and I told them to.
For whatever reason, when
you and I speak with one voice,
we seem to be able to
compel them to any end.
But Nassau will not be able
to maintain that sort of resolve.
Not without you or I
there to help instill it.
How can you be
so sure about this?
(MEN MURMURING)
(MEN MUTTERING)
When I assembled my staff
of advisors for this enterprise,
I spared no expense.
Some of the most promising sons of
the most prominent families in London.
Brilliant minds.
Full of ambition.
In this moment, I
think it fair to say
I wouldn't trade you
for any 10 of them.
You're very kind.
No, I'm very accountable.
By daybreak tomorrow, I'm
told more than half of the pirates
will have accepted
the King's pardon
and we will be ready to
move my flag onto the island.
In the 30 days that follow,
I will need to accomplish
90 days worth of progress
just to keep schedule.
I will need someone
by my side at all times
to aid in seeing it done.
A senior counselor
serving without portfolio.
At the moment, I believe you
represent the best candidate for it.
(CHUCKLES) Because I suggested
sending Hornigold to the beach?
Because you're smart
without needing anyone
to explain to you how to be.
And because you're not afraid
of being thought to be wrong
when you know that you're right.
Won't the promising sons
resent my presence in
such a senior capacity?
I'm fairly certain I don't care.
Do you?
No.
Good.
Then you're hired.
Let us begin.
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
MAN: £10,000 they're
paying for Vane's head, Jack.
Now, I know you ain't
got no need for the money,
but for fuck's sake,
don't be greedy.
You and I have known
each other for years.
It's the least you
could do for a friend.
Who is he?
MAN: Look, sooner or later,
there's gonna be 100
more men out here, Jack,
and this ain't gonna be
your decision anymore.
(MEN SHOUTING)
Open it.
You recognize him?
MAN: What the fuck, Jack?
Paul something or other.
- MAN: Come on, Jack. Let us in.
- Why just you?
Island full of
murdering, thieving fucks
and you were the only
one they can't forgive?
How does that make
any sense? I don't know.
But whatever the reason,
the men behind that door
will soon be joined by hundreds
more seeking the bounty.
- In an hour.
- We'll be besieged.
The men have cast their lots.
They are resolved that
you convince Captain Vane
to depart the fort.
They believe that turning him over
might convince the British commander
to allow them to keep
the fort and the gold.
Safe to say the fight to defend Nassau
is off to an inauspicious beginning.
Teach is still on the bay.
There may yet be a way
to salvage some defense.
It's over.
Now all that remains is that we
escape this place and survive.
All the doors are covered
by men seeking the bounty.
And I have to imagine the tunnel
exits are being watched as well,
given Hornigold's
familiarity with them.
Then I suggest we
manufacture a new exit.
♪
(MEN CHATTING)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(GROANING)
You all right?
No.
Who are they?
Maroons. Escaped slaves.
They must have a camp upriver.
Judging by their
numbers, a large one.
BILLY: They must have
spied the ship from a distance.
From up in the hills there.
DOOLEY: We've taken
slaves onto the crew before.
Freed a lot of them. Won't that
put us in good stead with them?
We've sold more than
we've freed, and they know it.
And even if we hadn't,
they'd assume we did.
(GROANS)
Pick up your man.
It's all right.
Shit.
Ah!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(BLOWS HORN)
(HORN BLOWS)
(MEN WHOOPING)
(DOG BARKING)
(INDISTINCT MURMURING)
(SHOUTS IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
Which is your captain?
I am.
What is your name?
Flint.
Which one is your quartermaster?
I am.
(ROOSTER CROWS)
You speak for your men?
Yes?
Then I speak with you.
How did you find this place?
We were defeated in battle.
Thrown by a storm
onto your shore.
There was no design in it.
Who else knew your position?
Who else knows
where to find you?
No one.
We're alone.
I give you my word.
Were you me, would
you wager the lives
of all those in your care
on the word of a pirate?
That one.
(SHOUTING IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
DOOLEY: Where
are they taking him?
FLINT: They'll
interrogate us one by one,
make sure our stories jibe.
And then what?
MAN: For those that survive
the first purge, it'll be hard labor.
Though not like any
you've ever known.
But of the kind they've known.
Cruel and violent.
Whatever methods they've
seen done to their own kind,
they feel resolved to repeat it
upon those they deem complicit.
Who are you?
My name is Ben Gunn.
I'm the last of 13
crewmen on a slave trader
captured whilst careening on
the windward side of the island.
I've learned 12 hard
lessons from that woman.
Each with the same end.
That sooner or later,
death awaits any man
who lays eyes on this place.
And that before it arrives, she
is determined to make you fear it.
We need to get out of here.
Rapidly.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Where the fuck have you been?
- Just putting some things in order.
- You said you'd put him out, Jack.
Quite right. Quick goodbye.
Last cigar. Surely you don't mind.
- ANNE: Did you do it?
- Yeah.
Fuse is lit.
In a few minutes, that wall
is going to be a lot shorter.
Finding it hard to believe there is
near enough material in that magazine
to cause the sort of damage
you seem to think it will.
Believe it.
I have lost years of my
life these last months
trying to rebuild this place.
I'll be goddamned
if the new governor
is going to inherit the
fruits of all that labor.
Not whole, at any rate.
Now, when it happens,
we should have a clear
path over the rubble.
We'll cover your
escape to the jetty.
It's not going to be easy.
The whole island is
seeking that bounty.
My escape?
You plan to stay?
Teach respects you.
You'll sail with him without looking
over your shoulder the whole time
wondering whether he's gonna
back someone else to take your place.
But me, I have no interest
in living as a target of his.
Jack, you know there's no
way I'd ever let that happen.
Nor would I be a ward of yours.
I've made something
for myself here.
I'll make it again somehow,
but I've come
too far to go back.
You'll take the
pardon, I presume.
Who knows? I
haven't got that far yet.
But wherever we land, Anne
and I will be taken care of.
Taken care of? How?
You set aside some of the gold?
She did.
How much?
Mmm.
Quit fucking
around. Put him out.
Right, just a moment.
Fucking never liked you.
(MEN SHOUTING)
What?
I was just gonna say,
"I'll see you soon,"
but that would probably
be a lie, wouldn't it?
Probably.
(HANDS CLASP)
Godspeed, Charles.
Fuck you, Jack.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Commodore reports no
change in their posture,
but he believes it's
only a matter of time
until we can expect
their surrender.
Teach and his men will
never take the pardons.
His crew will be
filled with fanatics.
Even fanatics need to eat.
With the beach secured
and no escape possible,
they have no means
to replenish supplies.
Time is against them.
You haven't asked.
About the status
of Captain Vane.
I understand that there are a great
many elements to this operation,
of which Charles is just one.
I trust that if there's any
development on that issue
you will let me know.
Good.
Then may I ask what it is that's
causing you to make that face?
My appointment as your advisor.
I understand that you don't care
what reaction your
people may have to it,
but your people, I'm afraid,
are only half the issue.
I have enemies on that island.
Enemies who may be far less
likely to accede to your authority,
seeing me beside you
offering my counsel.
I have no idea what the
future may hold for me here,
but I believe your
success is key to it.
The last thing I would
want to do is undermine you.
(EXPLOSION)
(MEN SHOUTING)
(BELL RINGING)
(MURMURING)
Jesus Christ.
Mr. Dufresne, pass
word to the men.
Captain Vane is
very likely at large.
Remind them of the prize
that awaits his captor, please.
(SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
GUNN: She's everything here.
Priestess, governess, warlord.
They say there's a
king, her husband,
that he exists abroad,
salvaging those rare items
necessary for life here,
but impossible to produce.
I've seen no evidence of him.
Here her word is supreme.
She's not to be underestimated.
What about the other one?
Down there.
GUNN: Daughter, I believe.
From the deference she's shown,
I imagine she's next in line.
Why?
If we do nothing,
they likely kill us.
If we attempt to
escape, they likely kill us
or the forest does it for them.
Oughtn't we be searching for a
third option with a better ending?
Like what?
I think they want us to think
they're all of one mind here.
But in a place like
this, how can that be?
There is a sympathetic
ear out there.
We just need to find it.
(HORSE WHINNIES)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
♪
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(PANTING)
(GUNSHOT)
(GROANS)
(BODY THUMPS)
Pass word to the commodore.
Resistance within the
fort has been defeated.
The fort wall already breached,
there was little chance to resist.
And the gold?
What will I say was
the effect of the blast
on our efforts to retrieve it?
Jesus, I don't know.
Tell him... tell him it
didn't help matters.
MAN: Name, please.
MAN 2: William Tennyson.
MAN: Where were you born?
- Please prepare a document for Mr. Scott.
- Of course, sir.
Good to see you, friend.
Glad you'll be
joining our efforts.
If this is what Nassau is to be,
I see no value in resisting
what is clearly inevitable.
Hardly a ringing endorsement.
I admit, I have my reservations
with the new regime,
but I sleep better on
this side of the pardon
than I did on the other.
So how can I be of help to you?
Funny you should ask. I've
just returned from the fort.
Damage is extensive.
I know you were tasked
with restoring it the first time.
- And I would be happy to do so again.
- Don't be too eager.
Captain Rackham's slave
laborers are nowhere to be found.
They escaped?
Someone must have
left the pen unlocked.
They overran a
handful of guards.
Well, perhaps I can help in
finding them and bringing them back.
You'd do that?
I oversaw them for
weeks. They know me.
They might be
persuaded to return
knowing that they
would be treated fairly,
rather than risk
being caught by, uh...
less-understanding redcoats.
Can we slip through the east
channel when the tide rises?
They've maneuvered a
frigate around the Hog.
They'd rake any ship that
emerged on the other side.
Don't think there's any
way we can challenge
that blockade directly, do you?
Not exactly.
We're working on something,
though, to even the odds a bit.
But there's something else
that you should know first.
What?
Is she on deck?
Yes, sir.
There's good
reason, it would seem,
that you were the only one to
whom they refused a pardon.
The Delicia, quarterdeck.
♪
(ALL SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE)
It's been hours.
Imagine they're
through interrogating us.
Well, they've tortured the same
story out of four different men now.
I imagine that'll convince
them of the truth of it.
Ben says this is how
it went with his crew.
Killed a handful
to show they could
and then the chains
and hard labor.
If they put them to work,
how did they all die?
Trying to escape.
Escape?
How far did they get?
Not far, most of them.
Overseer shot all but half a dozen
before they made it to the tree line.
Four of those six that
made it into the woods
died within a few hours...
traps, dead ends, hunted down.
The other one made it
a full two days before
they recaptured him.
Him?
Couldn't find a way out.
But if he made it that long,
maybe he knows enough
to piece together a plan.
I hate to be the
one to say this,
but is it possible we've
missed the point of that story?
They all died.
So why are we entertaining this?
It may be flawed,
but it's a plan.
Gives him focus.
Keeps his mind off the fact that
there might not be a better plan.
Why would we want to
take that away from him?
I see no way out of this.
No matter what I do, it
leads to the same outcome.
And I wonder if
it wouldn't be best
just to accept that I have
no choice in the matter.
You're curious again.
Ready to follow
me through a door
that is somehow less frightening
knowing I await you
on the other side.
I miss you.
I miss you, too.
When we arrive out there...
I am to leave you behind?
Yes.
What if I were to stay?
ANNE: I hear Brussels is nice.
Paris, maybe.
Though I don't speak French.
Whatever the fuck it is
they speak in Brussels.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, fucking hell, Jack.
Is it really as bad as all that?
Tomorrow we can be on our
way to anywhere in the world
with enough money
to live however we like.
Even where we
was when we started.
Some people might
even call that success.
Fuck those people.
We got the world right now.
Any part of it we choose.
We were so close to
accomplishing something
that would have written
our names into history.
There's no piece of the world
for sale that can replace that.
It ain't good and it ain't fair.
But it is what it is.
We need to leave
Nassau behind us.
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(GASPS)
Up.
Go, please.
Do you know who I am?
You're her daughter.
I understand from your men
that you were defeated in battle.
Then you were offered
pardons for all your men.
- Is that true?
- Yes.
But you refused. All of you.
To a man you refused
to be pardoned. Why?
Why did we refuse the pardons?
Every man has his own reasons.
Some remember the injustice
of the merchant service
and are too angry
to ever to return to it.
Some hate England too much
to ever call themselves
English again.
And some, I suppose, feel
Nassau's been theirs for so long,
they have no interest
in signing a document
that would surrender
it to the king.
No.
There are 1,000
men and women here.
Among them there is
no shortage of anger
or hate or fear.
Perhaps you have noticed.
They have suffered cruelties
you cannot possibly imagine.
Sisters separated from brothers.
Husbands from their wives.
Mothers from their sons.
No one has greater cause
to swear England an enemy
and desire vengeance
against her as we do.
Yet I believe if we were offered
the same choice as yours faced,
a chance to be made
free in the eyes of the law,
it would not have been
so roundly rejected.
I'm asking you why
you think that is.
I'm very much aware my
men's lives hang in the balance.
So I would like to give you
the answer you're looking for,
but I don't think you're
going to want to hear it.
Perhaps you are
mistaken in this moment
as to which of the two of
us is in need of protection.
Answer the question.
Your men are filled with
anger towards England,
as are mine,
but my captain wanted
England to see that anger
and make them fear it.
And for whatever reason,
your mother would prefer
your men fear England.
I see.
Take him back, please.
You asked the
question. I answered.
Wait a minute. Wait...
wait... wait a minute.
I think you see our interests are more
closely aligned than your mother does.
I have two dozen
men in a cage out there
of the opinion that
she intends to kill us all
sooner than later.
And you're going to
do nothing about it?
(GRUNTS)
TEACH: You done this before?
VANE: No, you?
No.
I suppose she's due some credit.
Dragged off to
London in shackles
and returns in a
governor's service.
And convinces him to turn the
whole of the world against you.
I don't doubt your
anger towards her,
but I have to ask...
if, in the course
of our maneuver,
we are forced to choose
between escape and her death,
where are you?
She was on that
deck for a reason.
So I'd see her.
To provoke me into
making a mistake.
What matters most
is achieving our goal.
To exit this bay
with the fleet intact
and to move on from this place.
Charles Vane sees past his anger
to achieve the greater end.
How did that happen?
I was taught a lesson once.
It's been effective.
Taught by whom?
Her.
MAN: It's ready.
They are without option now.
Sooner or later they'll
realize their only escape
is to surrender Captain
Vane and stand down.
Gentlemen.
ELEANOR: I should be going.
What would they say?
Who?
Your enemies on the island.
You seem concerned about what
I'm gonna hear them say about you.
Maybe it would be
better to hear it now
while all else is quiet.
They would say
I'm untrustworthy.
That I would turn on
anyone at any time,
no matter how close
they were to me...
no matter who it
hurt or how severely.
That, given my history,
only a fool would allow me
to get close to them again.
Would they be right?
You tamed this place once.
Despite what anyone
may say of you,
and I desire your counsel,
despite what anyone
may say of you.
So let us move forward,
despite what anyone, whether
from your world or from mine,
may say of you.
(KNOCKS ON DOOR)
What is it?
CHAMBERLAIN: She's under a
white banner. Gunports closed.
How the hell did
she get so close?
She was hidden
behind their line.
By the time she emerged,
she was fully underway.
She's subject to
our full broadside.
She's either surrendering,
or we have her dead to rights.
Slip the anchor cables.
Break our line over the
approach of a schooner?
I think you overestimate...
While there is still time,
cut the goddamn cables.
(WHISTLES)
♪
MAN: Fire ship!
Bloody hell. Cut the anchor
cables! Get us underway.
Cut the anchor! Cut
the anchor cables!
Starboard batteries, fire!
Fire! Fire!
(MEN SHOUTING)
(CANNONBALLS WHIZZING)
Captain, our fleet is underway.
(MEN SHOUTING)
(CANNONS FIRING)
Too high.
You're aiming too
high. Forget the rigging.
Aim at his hull.
At the waterline.
MAN: Aim for the waterline!
Gun crews, redirect
to the waterline!
Redirect to the waterline!
- Fire!
Lieutenant! Get
her inside! Go! Go!
(MEN SCREAMING)
(SHOUTING CONTINUES)
♪
(FROGS CROAKING)
(DOG BARKING)
(PANTING)
I was right.
There is conflict amongst them.
I don't know how deep it runs,
but it is there to be exploited.
The daughter?
This seems to be a significantly
more promising option
than charging into
a trap-laden forest.
I'm not sure why I
needed to say that out loud.
Where are you?
Earlier I told you
that I was certain
that the pardons would eliminate
all resistance in Nassau
and you asked me
how I was so certain.
It's because I
helped build them.
Peter Ashe, Miranda,
her husband, and I,
we worked to obtain
a universal pardon
and introduce it to Nassau
to eliminate piracy and
restore colonial rule there.
I moved away from those things.
Inch by inch,
I forgot it all.
And now, in this cage,
in the belly of this thing
that has swallowed us whole...
I wonder...
if the civilization of Nassau
isn't exactly what I tried to
achieve all those years ago.
If resisting it doesn't
set me in opposition
to everything I once
understood to be good and right.
To forgive.
To make order of chaos.
I wonder if the
pardons are the victory
and that the most enlightened
thing that I can do is
sit still.
Accept what appears
to be inevitable
and let this be the
end of Captain Flint.
No.
No, no, no. Nothing
is inevitable here.
I'm showing you a way in
which we can survive this.
You're new to this,
being responsible
for men's lives.
But I know what the
woman who leads this place
is facing right now.
The weight of her people's
welfare on her shoulders.
She will not let us
leave this place alive.
She simply won't permit it.
We'll all face certain death
with our own kind of lie.
Billy's is that he can
fight his way out of it.
Yours is that you can
talk your way past it.
But for me...
I don't know that I have
any more lies left in me.
I know all you
want is to protect us,
to protect me,
but what you intend to do
tomorrow toward that end,
I think it is a grave mistake
and I'm asking you once
more to please reconsider.
- Madi.
- We share a common enemy.
- Does that not make us friends?
- Madi!
The men in that cage
are deceitful men.
They will say things that
will sound appealing to you,
especially to you.
But you must not
let them sway you.
Your father and
I built this place
to separate ourselves
from their world.
But we rely on the things that
father sends back from their world.
We're not that
separate from them.
We are separate enough that
we have no need to see them.
To steal from them.
To fight with them.
To know their chains again.
I have worked so hard
to ensure that you've never
had to see those things.
But I have seen those things.
And I will hold them at bay
for as long as I'm able to.
For every day that we
avoid colliding into their world
is a day children are born here,
is a day families exist here.
I'm in no hurry to see that end.
Nor should you be.
Come.
That separation rests entirely
on our existence
remaining a secret.
The pirates, for as long
as they draw breath,
could and would for a profit
compromise that secret.
So they must be eliminated.
Why not consult father?
You can get a message to him.
He knows these men.
He sailed with them.
He might have something
to say about killing them.
Your father aids us from
his position in Nassau.
He might have lived
among these men.
He may have fought
beside these men.
He may have even called
some of these men friends.
But when it comes to the
safety of the people in this place,
your father knows the
final decision is mine.
- You know where you're going, yes?
- Yes.
When you reach the beach,
make no attempt into the trees.
They will find you
and guide you through.
Once you reach the camp,
my wife will see
you are taken care of.
Thank you.
MAN: Who's there?
Go. Now. Go!
It's all right.
Stop. The rest of
you, disembark now.
I will explain to
Captain Hornigold.
Please, come with me.
Lower your weapons. Now!
No! No!
- (GUNFIRE)
- No, no, no!
(MAN GROANING)
(LABORED BREATHING)
(GROANING)