Visualizing?
All right. You're up, tiger.
You feel all right?
You look a little pale.
I'm fine.
Does your neck still hurt?
It'll be fine.
Maybe you should do
the two and a half instead.
I'm gonna do the three.
Well, it's better to nail
the two and a half than...
I'm gonna nail the three.
All right.
Well, let's show these senior citizens
what a well-coached
twelve-year-old can do, huh?
The next diver. Two-time National
Junior Champion Mary Carroll.
Damn it, you can do this,
come on. Just...
see it, see it.
Big jump, let it count. Rip it.
Call 911. We need an ambulance!
I saw the light on.
It's daytime.
Yeah, it's a figure of speech.
Always so literal.
Got a new cane.
Yeah. Guy in the store said
it was slimming. Vertical stripe...
Why are you here?
Vogler is dead.
What? What happened?
Again with the literal translation.
Vogler the idea, Mr. Destructo,
Mr. Moneybags, bow down before me.
He is gone from the hospital,
so things can go back to the way they were.
The way they were was kind of weird.
Weird works for me.
What are you saying? Literally?
I want you to come back.
Why?
Please unclench.
You're not on the clock,
and when you do that,
I clench, and then it's
the whole thing...
Could you look at your pager?
It's no big deal, some sort of epidemic.
Not my area.
You should go. It's important.
What I'm doing now is important.
Why do you want me back?
Because you're a good doctor.
That's it?
That's not enough?
Not for me.
Go deal with your plague.
"You are in a quarantined area."
Please remain calm and stay in line.
A doctor will see you shortly.
When you see a doctor,
you will receive a blue or yellow form.
Patients with blue forms must
immediately enter the parking lot...
Dr. House! We need you here.
Sorry, lot of sick people.
I might catch something.
A judge at the campus
pool center collapsed,
LP revealed a virulent form
of bacterial meningitis.
Great, got it diagnosed,
you don't need me.
2500 people at the pool
center were exposed.
They're being bused to
all the neighboring hospitals.
That's a problem of resources,
not diagnostics.
No, I'd be completely lost,
get in everyone's way.
Joe!
Dr. House doesn't have a blue slip.
No one leaves the quarantine area
without a blue slip.
You are a doctor at this hospital:
Act like one. And take these.
102. You win a trip to
the second floor. Next!
All right, no fever, no rash,
you're fine. Take these two pills,
and show this blue slip to Security
on your way out. Next!
Take these, go home,
talk to your daughter.
What?
Your pants, your blouse, your scarf
are all freshly dry cleaned.
Everything except your jacket,
it's got a smudge on it.
Probably two days old.
Which means you didn't know
the jacket had been worn.
So either your husband
is a crossdresser
or your daughter has been borrowing
your clothes without telling you.
Probably wants to
look older to get into bars.
I don't have a daughter.
Next!
So I have it.
Yellow form to the second form,
you're gonna be fine.
I'm gonna die!
It's treatable as long as
you go to the second floor. Next.
Yow.
Fever. Does that mean I have it?
You have a rash? Come on.
It's from my new bathing suit,
I've had it a week.
Yeah. Does your neck hurt?
If it does, you get the trifecta.
It's nothing. I pulled it trying
to do a three-and-a-half tuck.
Where are your parents?
We live in Chicago.
I'm here with my coach.
I wanted to see what you were writing.
Go like this.
Now like this.
Take these pills.
A blue slip will get you out of here.
Next!
You're coming with me.
You're going to need a CT scan.
Second floor, take the elevators,
follow the parade. Next!
Maybe something systemic.
Or maybe it's meningitis.
She's had the rash a week.
If it was this meningitis,
she'd be dead by now.
You guys figure we're done down there?
The 800 people milling around are
just waiting for the bathroom?
12-year-old female. Fever,
rash, neck pains. Not meningitis.
It's the definition of meningitis!
Sure, pus in the spinal canal makes it
hurt to move your head up and down,
but her head only hurts
moving side to side.
Oh, side to side.
Doesn't fit.
The three of you, lobby, now.
Those little pills you're
passing out so efficiently
aren't going to do
Miss Louganis squat.
You just don't want to
deal with the epidemic.
That's right. I'm subjecting
a 12-year-old to a battery
of dangerous and evasive
tests to avoid being bored.
Okay, maybe I would do that, but I'm not.
If it turns out she does have meningitis,
you're right, you win, but if we
go back downstairs and she dies...
your face will be so red.
You have one hour.
Get a lumbar puncture.
Some brain infections can be
pretty clever at hide-and-seek.
- I'll get on her bloodwork.
- No you won't.
You, sir, will research all the causes
in the universe of neck pain.
The list is, like,
two miles long!
Start with the letter A.
And put her on rifampin.
Rifampin is for meningitis.
You just said...
In case I'm wrong.
It has happened.
Brenda, I need a CBC count 7 and 2046.
Hold on.
Hey, hey, there's a line here!
That's why I said 'excuse me'.
Brenda, I need a bed, and...
We all need stuff.
Push me again.
Brenda, I need a bed and
a nurse for a lumbar puncture.
No beds, no nurses for at least 4 hours.
I've only got one.
Your patient only has an hour to live
unless she gets a lumbar puncture?
Cuddy only gave us an hour
to work on the patient.
Back of the line.
This novocaine will numb you
for the lumbar puncture.
Sorry this has to be so public, Mary.
Normally I'm in a bathing suit
with 5000 people staring at my butt.
I can block this out.
These kids are all very mature.
Travel around the country
from event to event.
Okay, I need you to hold
your knees and tuck your head.
Like a dive?
Exactly.
Good, great. Don't forget to breathe.
Sorry!
Geez! Coach, help me out here, play a little
defense before I poke the wrong thing?
Okay, here we go.
I feel, I feel it!
Try to relax, Mary, try to relax.
What letter are you up to?
A.
Torture combing through
all that stuff, ain't it?
Real dull. Awful.
It's no problem.
Well, thank goodness.
A lot of people would
resent having to do this.
Where's the 12-year-old
girl that was here?
Needed the gurney.
She just had a lumbar puncture,
she's not supposed to be moved!
Sorry, we needed the gurney.
Hey.
You okay? How's your head feeling?
She's got a headache,
and she's dizzy.
She shouldn't have been moved
after the procedure, I'm sorry.
I'm fine, what did the test show?
No meningitis,
no other infections.
But you're not carrying a blue form.
I have something else, don't I?
Something's causing your symptoms.
We're going to keep you overnight.
I know it's a little crazy
here, but hopefully
things will settle down
and we'll get you a room.
I'm sorry. I'm not usually
all emotional like this. Just...
You're doing great.
Your folks will land in a few hours.
I just... I haven't slept, I'm so tired.
Oh my God, my eye's bleeding.
What is it, what's happening?
Oh, don't worry.
The antibiotic we gave you in case you had
meningitis can turn your tears reddish.
That's not blood.
But that... that's blood.
That's going into my stomach?
The vials showed blood in your GI tract.
We need to find out where it's coming from.
You won't feel it.
I'm going to numb
the back of your throat and.
Dr. Foreman is going to
give you a sedative. Open.
Swallow. Now lay on your side for me.
And here we go.
Yell "fire," or something.
People, this area is
highly contagious.
Please step back.
Highly contagious.
All right. Try to relax, Mary,
this shouldn't take too long.
Don't see any tears or lesions.
All right, I'm in her stomach.
There's no bleeding.
There was more than a tablespoon of blood
in her mouth, so it's got to be there.
Maybe her small intestine.
30 feet of digestive tract,
it could be anywhere in there.
We're not going to see it with this.
Believe it or not, this is a camera.
You swallow it, and it goes
all the way through your system.
The antennae pick up
the signal from the pill.
We're going to look at
the video of your intestines,
see where the blood is
coming from, and fix it.
Alright?
Water? Down the hatch.
Think I've seen this movie.
The ending's kind of dark.
You want one?
How come you did the endoscopy?
He asked for help!
Her blood pressure was high,
I was worried...
Foreman is not your boss.
When I tell you to do something...
whoa. Hold it there. Back
it up a couple of frames.
Oh, yeah! That's your money shot.
I don't see anything.
Really? Ginormous thing on the right side
of her intestine doesn't even intrigue you?
Does ginormous mean really big or really,
really small, 'cause I don't see anything.
There? A Dieulafoy?
Oh. Well, we can burn off
the swollen blood vessel,
but it still doesn't account
for her other symptoms.
No, but it does tell us something.
Though I have no idea what.
Could be a precursor to
intestinal intussusception.
Precursor isn't causing all of
her other symptoms. What else?
You, in the lobby, now.
I hurt my leg. I have a note.
You had your hour. Three, actually.
Dr. Chase, I told you to tell us
when our time was up.
She has intestinal bleeding.
She'll wait. Two more buses just arrived.
We need you downstairs.
No, you need more nurses.
But you cut back on the
nursing staff so you could have
doctors doing what the
nurses should be doing.
That's true.
I wonder if that has anything to do
with you costing us $100 million.
Attention. If you do not have a blue form,
you will not to be allowed to be
in the quarantine area.
Go, be free.
It's not the intussusception,
what about stomach cancer?
- Does she have any abdominal pain?
- No.
Then it's not stomach cancer.
Have you ruled out sepsis?
The LP and blood smear showed
no signs of infection.
Here. Take these two pills and you can go.
Well, the lab's working at double their
capacity, maybe someone screwed up.
No fever, no neck pain.
Take the elevator to the third floor.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wrong form.
No fever, no neck pain, she's fine.
Smell her hair, no chlorine.
Which means she wasn't at the pool.
Which means she's come to a quarantined
area because she's a idiot or she's insane.
No one is that stupid.
East wing, psych ward, bye-bye.
Neck pain could be
a symptom for bone cancer.
You up to Bs? Well done!
It would account for all her
meningial symptoms. Rash, fever...
You're fine. Take these two pills...
Get a sample of her bone marrow.
From here?
Break time.
Need more than 15 minutes.
Use Chase's break, too.
Go.
You should just fire Chase.
What, and miss out on all this fun?
So you're going to torture him
for a while and then fire him? That's cold.
You don't think he has it coming?
Hey, I said fire him.
That's cold. All he did was save his job.
What? He completely screwed you over!
Right rudder.
Bank, bank, bank!
Good coffee?
The rest of this hospital is
busting it's tail, and you're...
What are you doing?
Trying to think of anything except
the produce department at Whole Foods.
I am... working, it got hot,
stop acting like a 13-year-old!
Sorry, you just don't usually see
breasts like that on Deans of Medicine.
Oh, women can't be heads of hospitals?
Or just ugly ones?
No, they can be babes.
You just don't usually see their funbags.
Your 3 o'clock interview for
Dr. Cameron's position is in your office.
Ah, not interviewing today.
I don't know if you've heard,
but there's this big time epidemic.
Many sick people puking
in the hallways, it's crazy.
I'll send the interview home,
we can reschedule.
No, you won't.
You will interview this person,
and if he can put two
sentences together you will
send him to the lobby
where he will do his job.
Unlike the two of you.
Come on, you know I can't do
a bone marrow aspiration in the hallway.
And I can't give you a procedure room.
I just need something at least
close to a sterile environment.
I need 10 more nurses.
Brenda, listen, listen. She'll die.
At least she'll have a bed, then.
Put that over there.
Are there dead people in those cabinets?
I hope that's who's in there.
Just be calm, relax.
Hang on.
Hang on. Almost done.
You know, I really admire the way
you don't care what anyone thinks.
You just do what you want,
the way you want.
So, you went to Hopkins for
both undergrad and med school?
That's right.
He's in a band.
You into music?
Totally.
What kind of music do you play?
Mostly blues, you know.
James Cotton, some original stuff.
Oh, dude. You are so hired.
Really?
Not a chance.
Why?
Tattoo.
Wow. I thought you'd be the last person
to have a problem with nonconformity.
Nonconformity, right.
I can't remember the last
time I saw a 20-something
kid with a tattoo of an
Asian letter on his wrist.
You are one wicked free thinker.
You want to be a rebel?
Stop being cool.
Wear a pocket protector like
he does and get a haircut.
Like the Asian kids who don't leave
the library for 20 hours stretches,
they're the ones who
don't care what you think.
Sayonara.
So should I go through
all the resumes looking for Asian names?
Actually, the Asian kids are
probably just responding
to parental pressure, but
my point is still valid.
So when do they think
you're getting out of here?
I don't know.
You don't look sick.
Better hope you're not, this equipment
looks like it's 100 years old.
Just got it out of storage.
It is the previous generation,
but it works just fine.
Could you guys give us a sec?
If it's good news,
you can tell them.
Okay. We're pretty sure
it's not cancer.
Hey, that's great.
I'll call your parents.
Well, we still can't release her.
We still don't know yet
exactly what's causing the...
Mary?
What's wrong?
She's having an absence seizure.
Mary, you okay?
She looks fine.
I need some help over here!
Push two milligrams Ativan, stat!
Are you sure it was
an absence seizure?
Absolutely.
She was totally unresponsive
and unaware
of what was going on around her.
Do you mind?
We're trying to work.
We should get back out there.
Cuddy's going to be looking for us.
Looking, but not finding.
You do an EEG?
Seizure frequency's increasing.
They're almost constant now.
5 in the last half hour.
Which tells us...
It's definitely in the brain.
And it's getting worse.
And?
Good lord, are you having a
bowel movement or a baby?
Could be barbiturate withdrawal.
No, can't be drugs. She's tested
at every meet she competes in.
A bleed in the brain
can cause seizures.
Rat poison.
Could also cause the neck pain.
You think she's eating
off the floor of her folks' garage?
Doesn't have to be.
Who would poison a 12-year-old?
Well, let's see now,
there's the 18-year-old
has-been that she beat
out to make Nationals,
the has-been's parents,
jealous siblings, sociopathic swim fan,
and then there's just
your plain old garden variety whack job.
Hey! You know
what a hemorrhoid is?
No.
Well, google it.
And try some Raisin Bran
instead of the donuts.
Okay, do a CT scan, check
for intercranial bleeding.
Not a chance,
radiology's totally swamped.
If our patient's bleeding into her brain,
she's gonna be dead in 8 hours.
She could be, but a meningitis
patient will be without a CT scan.
When I was in med school,
I had this old professor...
who touched you
in the naughty place?
Before the CT scan was introduced,
he specialized in transcranial ultrasound.
Ancient, but if there's
enough bleeding it might work.
Okay, do what the guy who didn't
specialize in neurology said.
It was my idea!
You've still got to cover Q-Z.
Sorry I'm late,
I was taking a dump.
I'm guessing I'm better off interviewing
right after than right before.
Dr. Petra Gilmar,
Dr. Gregory House.
You actually speak four
languages, or you just banking
on never being interviewed
by anyone who does?
It's true.
And I can swear in two more.
Why are you leaving Dr. Hazel?
Did you fall for him and can't handle it,
or is it the other way around?
Yes, well, pretty much
every fellowship ends that way.
No, it was nothing like that.
You Jewish?
Yes.
Is it true what they say
about Jewish foreplay?
Two hours of begging?
I heard four.
Well, actually, I'm only half-Jewish.
Look, I know you like to
play games with people.
I know you like to say outrageous
things and study how they react.
What you should know about me
is that I grew up with four brothers.
Keep your hands to yourself,
I'm okay with anything
that comes out of your mouth.
Well, that's great.
I think that's all we'll need.
- Thank you for coming by.
- Thank you.
That's our Hitler!
No way.
Are you kidding?
Her background's perfect, she's smart,
she can obviously
deal with your insanity...
Did you see her shoes?
Her shoes?
What, did your horoscope in Vogue tell you
to avoid women wearing green shoes?
The eyes can mislead, the smile can lie,
but the shoes always tell the truth.
They were Prada.
It means she has good taste.
They were not Prada. You wouldn't know
Prada if one stepped on your scrotum.
Okay, well, they were nice, pointy...
Exactly, they were stylish,
and very painful to wear.
Only an incredibly shallow and
insecure woman would rather be in
pain all day long then wear a
decent looking, comfortable shoe,
and that's exactly the type
I don't need around here.
No, someone who can handle a lot of pain
is exactly the type you do need.
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
I'm ultrasounding your head.
You're still having seizures.
This should help us
figure out what's going on.
Blue form to the security guard.
You're not going to be
happy with anyone.
So what, your advice is...
hire someone I'm not
happy with and be happy?
No, my advice is much more subtle.
Stop being an ass.
You always find some tiny little flaw
to push people away.
Now it's people. I thought we were
talking about fellowship applicants.
You have a history of this.
Well, when I do decide
to push you away,
I hope there's a small
person kneeling behind you
so you fall down and hurt your head.
Take these, there's water over there,
blue form to the guard, and you're done.
You had the perfect person,
and you blew it.
You saw the shoes!
I'm not talking about her.
You're talking about Cameron.
I'm talking about every woman
you've ever given a damn about.
Cameron is so not perfect.
Well, nobody's perfect.
- Mother Teresa?
- Dead.
- Angelina Jolie?
- No medical degree.
Now who's being picky?
You're going to
wind up alone, House.
You were right, there's a significant
bleed in her temporal lobe.
No poisons. Did a tox screen on her blood,
urine and hair,
nothing. Did 'em twice.
He's a little dehydrated,
put him on a
saline drip and give him some orange juice.
I need an operating room
and a neuro surgeon.
Oh, well, given the current
crisis I'm tempted to say
no, but since you've been
so sweet to me today...
Our little mermaid is bleeding
into her temporal lobe.
How fast can you have her prepped?
20 minutes.
You'll have a surgeon
in the room in 10.
Mr. And Mrs. Carroll?
Are you Dr. House?
This is Dr. Foreman.
Is Mary all right?
The operation went well.
The intercranial pressure's been relieved
and the swelling's already going down.
Thank God.
Well, what happened?
Did she bang her head
at a meet, or did she...
No, nothing like that.
Then why is she bleeding?
Is she going to be all right?
We're sorry, we still don't know.
No toxins, no tumor,
no bone cancer.
Adrenal failure could cause
the rash, fever and muscle pain.
Maybe it's some sort of
genetic kidney disorder.
No family history, and
no blood in her urine or uremia...
Not yet.
You want to do a differential based
on symptoms that might happen?
You got a better idea?
Stop it.
Stop looking for things we don't know
and focus on what we do know.
What do we actually know
besides what's up there?
Come on, how hard can it be to
tell me what you already know?
She's 12.
She spends a lot of time at the pool,
so exposure to chemicals.
She travels a lot.
But never out of the country.
What else?
Come on!
We're missing something.
What?
Well, if I knew that
it wouldn't be missing.
Maybe she's adopted and
we've got the wrong history.
No, she's got her mom's eyes
and a red patch of hair just like dad.
What about an allergic reaction?
Could explain the rash and muscle pain,
but not the bleeding or seizures.
That's a lot of balloons.
Think she's allergic to polyester?
Not unless she's been competing
in the nude all these years.
Then what are you thinking?
What do the balloons mean?
What if the rash isn't a rash?
What are you talking about?
Who gave her the balloons?
Some of the girls from her team.
They've been visiting her pretty regularly,
but none of them are sick.
What about the guys?
None of them are sick either.
Which guys visited her?
Actually, none.
She's cute, she's nice,
she's a kick-ass diver.
You'd think the guys would be falling
over themselves to get close to her.
She's 12.
The youngest guy on her team is 16.
Okay, so maybe they're
just not interested. Or...
They're avoiding her.
There any cell fragments
in her blood smears?
No, red blood cells were intact.
Check 'em again.
Blood looks like it's been
put through the blender, now.
You done yet?
You were right. Rash wasn't a rash,
she's bleeding into her skin. It's purpura.
Thrombocytopenia purpura?
Starts with T.
You were so close.
What could have set it off?
She had no trace of
E. Coli in her cultures,
she's obviously not
menopausal, so no estrogen.
There is one other possible cause.
Oh, God.
Pregnancy cause all kinds of chemical
and biological changes in a woman's body.
Or a girl's body, as the case may be.
In extremely rare cases,
everything goes haywire. It's called TTP.
Blood starts clotting like crazy, clogs
the vessels in your brain and kidneys.
Red blood cells end up
getting shredded as they
squeeze past the clot like
a fat guy in a crowed bar.
I'm sure you know what that's like.
You're only 12,
but you're all grown up, right?
Travel on your own,
hang out in hotel rooms
getting room service
with your teammates,
maybe someone sneaks
in a couple of beers,
you start playing spin the bottle...
next thing you know you're waking up
in nothing but your socks.
It wasn't like that.
Of course not. You wanted it.
Yeah, I did.
He turned out to be a jerk, but...
Actually, under New Jersey law
the term is 'felon'.
I knew what I was doing.
We're going to have to do
something called plasmapheresis.
It cleans the antibodies
from your blood.
We're also going to have to
terminate the pregnancy.
You're going to tell my parents?
Someone should.
Rock paper scissors?
They don't need to know.
I'll be all right.
Of course you will.
If you're old enough to
bleed out of your vagina,
obviously you're mature enough
to handle a simple thing
like an abortion without
Mommy and Daddy's help.
You're going to tell my parents?
Under New Jersey law,
you're the boss.
Your daughter has TTP.
Don't worry,
it's curable, she'll be fine.
Well, wait! What does TTP stand for?
Some really big words that
you've never heard before
and when we're done we'll never
hear again. Have a nice day.
Well, when can we take her home?
Uh, in a few days.
She needs some minor surgery to remove the
underlying cause before we can do the...
another really big word.
What's the underlying cause?
She has an abnormal growth
in her abdomen.
What kind of surgery?
It's very simple.
We do it here all the time.
Could you be a little more specific?
Actually, no.
I'm sorry.
Almost done.
Hang in there.
You're doing good.
Feeling okay?
Yeah.
You should be,
your platelet count's up.
How's your neck?
Looks good.
Anything else we can get you?
No thanks.
Okay.
Yeah.
Can I see my mom and dad?
Plasmapheresis is working,
she's going to be fine.
I know.
- Hi.
- I got these.
I checked all down the hall. It was
pretty much clear, you do the cleaning?
Yeah.
I can't even tell you how much I appreciate
the opportunity to meet with you.
The moment I heard you had
another fellowship opening, I...
There is no opening.
House, you have to hire someone.
I know.
The position's been filled.
Why am I interviewing for a position
that's already been filled?
Exactly.
I called to confirm
the interview this morning.
You figure if you keep arguing
I'm gonna cave, admit it's
all a lie, and hire you?
Do you need your
parking validated?
I don't want to interview anyone else.
You're interviewing?
I thought you'd just have them
send a headshot along with their CV.
That's good.
And why I need you around.
To keep me in my place.
I can't come back,
I told you that.
Wasn't listening.
Right.
You want me to listen to you more?
I can do that.
Right. I already accepted
a position somewhere else.
With who?
Yule, at Jefferson.
Unaccept it.
Why?
Because Yule is boring.
He's pedantic and preachy.
Because he's short.
Because I want you to come back.
Not good enough.
Want more money?
A car allowance,
better parking space?
Dinner.
And not just a meal
between two colleagues.
A date.
You'll come back to work
if I go out on a date with you?
Yes.
Okay,
it's a deal.
See you tomorrow morning.
Don't be late.
I won't.