If you testify,
no one can protect you.
Especially the Feds.
- We'll keep you safe, Joey.
- Right. Witness Protection.
This great new life he's giving you?
You're sacking groceries at some
goat-town Stop and Shop
when one of the Talli guys comes up
and puts two in the back of your skull.
Counselor, are you advising a witness
to withhold evidence from
a federal grand jury?
He came forward. He volunteered.
I'm advising him not to testify
until I'm satisfied you can protect him.
Hey, you guys mind?
I got money on this.
What do you want?
We gave you everything you asked for.
I asked for pasta.
You got steak, enjoy it.
What are you doing?
Where's your quit candy?
I just gave you a pack.
Yeah, sorry, I forgot.
Joey, whatever they give
us, what they tell you,
you get popped, what am I going to do?
Sue them?
That's not what this is about.
You're gonna miss me.
- I'm your lawyer, Joey.
- You're my brother.
And I do this, you know,
I go into Witness Protection,
we're never gonna see each other again.
That doesn't bother you?
Kills me.
Hey, I gotta take a leak.
You all right?
Yeah, yeah,
just, little dizzy...
Get some air.
And hot.
Joey!
What did you say to him?
Yeah, nice try.
Come on.
Let go of me! Let go of me,
can't you see he's sick?
Joey! Joey!
Something's wrong with him!
Come on, you're not
getting out of this that easy!
Either you're dead,
or you're testifying.
Don't have it.
Budget?
House has been very busy.
Saving New Jersey
from leprosy, yes, I know.
Getting me his numbers,
that's your job.
We're in a meeting.
Need the lawyer.
Who'd you kill?
Nobody, but it's not even lunch.
Got served with a federal court order.
Some witness went into a coma and
they want me to take a look at it.
What?
They want you to examine a sick person?
This is a public relations nightmare.
Folks think our staff do
that kind of thing around here...
this place would be
crawling with sick people!
I'm a doctor, I'm not a lapdog for
the feds. I don't play fetch.
Nobody tells you what to do.
Am I right, Dr. Cuddy?
You have three choices:
Hire a lawyer to fight the order,
treat the guy, or go to jail for contempt.
Up to you.
Jail. You'd like that.
No more naughty schoolgirl.
Conjugal visit,
that's her new fantasy.
We're not leaving until he's gone or you
show me one good reason for keeping him.
He's really out of it, huh?
Causes of coma:
Metabolic, structural...
He had his stomach pumped!
Why would they do that?
Rule out poisoning.
Huh. Not the typical first guess.
No, the first guess was faking it.
Patient's a federal witness,
reluctant, I'm assuming.
He's also an 8 on the Glasgow coma scale.
That's barely alive.
Pretty tough to fake it.
Any recent history of head trauma?
Bad car accident, fall?
They tell me no,
but do an MRI to be sure.
Metabolic causes.
Liver, kidney, diabetes...
Check for everything,
feds are paying.
We're gonna turn a profit
on this one, boys.
Dr. House, Bill Arnello.
I'm a lawyer,
I represent Mr. Smith.
What's wrong with him?
Do I come to you with my problems?
He's also my brother.
What, you changed your name?
"Smith" wasn't good enough for you?
His name's Joey,
he's my only brother.
He's important to you, got it.
So, no placebos for him,
we'll use the real medicine.
Well, this was fun,
let's do it again soon.
Brother in the Mafia?
So, just Joey?
I was hoping for a nickname.
Joey Mango. Joey the Wrench.
People know where I am.
I want you to do your job.
Diagnose him, fix him,
and keep him here.
We're a bit of a specialized hospital.
We generally only deal with patients
when they're actually sick.
If you release my brother
to the government, and he
does what they want, even
if you fix him, he's dead.
I need time to convince him of that.
Good news is,
if you screw up you don't have to
worry about a malpractice suit.
If he's dead, one by one,
I'll take away the things you love
'till there's nothing left.
So, on the Mafia thing, that's a yes.
Did House seem weird to you?
Are you expecting him to be weird?
We spoke about how we felt.
- You told him you liked him?
- No, of course not.
What are you talking about, then?
I asked him if he liked me.
Why would you do that?
Because... I like him.
You like him, like him?
Doesn't matter, he doesn't like me.
Hey, he doesn't like anybody.
And nobody likes him.
MRI showed a subdural hematoma.
Bleeding around his brain caused pressure
inside his head which caused the coma.
These look like pseudomembranes.
Those take time to form.
If it was an old injury
it wouldn't have caused the coma.
Patient history indicates
he was hit with a tire iron in 1996.
Brother says he was
changing a tire and it slipped.
Subdural hematoma placed where this one is,
it could have caused his coma.
What about his liver?
LFTs are slightly elevated.
Key word is slightly. As in, not high enough
to cause the coma. It's the subdural.
I say we evacuate the cavity,
see if he wakes up.
The neurologist thinks it's his brain, wants
to open up his head. Frankly, I'm shocked!
You get to use the big boy drill
and Daddy's big red toolbox.
No drilling.
Hi.
Mr. Smith!
Call me Joe.
Can you not do that?
So, we're clear about the no drilling?
He's okay now, he can leave.
I'm not releasing him.
Because the brother doesn't want you to?
Or because he had an unexplained
coma, which sounds better?
The hematoma caused the coma.
That's a catchy diagnosis,
you could dance to that.
I think Chase is right.
It still should be evacuated,
but it's not an immediate threat.
Cameron's my girl.
I'd release him.
Are you disagreeing with me because...
I'm disagreeing because
that's my medical opinion.
Of course it is.
But unless I've been
named as the fourth part of
the Axis of Evil,
invaded and occupied,
this is still not a democracy.
He's staying.
Send for Hepatitis serologies
and an autoimmune panel.
Hey. I'm with you.
Old enough to drink,
old enough to do something
really stupid and make yourself a baby.
He's my brother. I'm watching him
while my parents are in Barbados.
He's having trouble breathing
and there's a lot of wheezing.
Whistling, technically.
Upper airways, nose.
If he's got the croup,
that could become meningitis, right?
Absolutely.
I was just studying and all of a sudden
I hear him crying and sounding all weird.
My parents are going to kill me.
I doubt it.
You don't know them.
No, I doubt you were studying
while your parents were away.
Hello, officer.
You might want to rinse this off
before you let him play with it again.
What happened? Where is he?
Vogler called admitting, admitting called
Justice, Justice came and took him away.
And who called Vogler?
He loses money.
So does ophthalmology.
Who cares, this is a hospital.
You can't just cut a department!
You can't control him.
I am the only one that can control him.
Dr. House in the House!
Impeccable timing as always.
You had no authority
to release my patient.
My colleague has just informed me
that she has a singular talent.
You are just in time
for a demonstration.
Dr. House, from what I understand, your...
From what you understand?
He's not your patient.
How the hell do you understand anything?
That's sad.
You're not even a doctor.
John Smith is here only
because of court order.
I had the records faxed to the judge;
She recinded the order.
Why bother, just to piss me off?
- Keeping the government off our ass.
- Hmm. Yeah.
That makes no sense for
a public institution.
Okay.
Okay what?
Okay, sir. Carry on.
He really cares about his patients.
Yeah, and he just walked out of here
with nothing. Something's up.
He just started vomiting and passed out.
35-year-old male,
vital signs are stable now.
Gave him 2 liters en route.
He's just released
from here two hours ago.
You said he was good to go.
So, your junior G-man badge
isn't looking so good.
His liver's worse.
Comatose?
No, completely different symptoms
than the first time.
Serology tests came back
positive for Hep-C.
Hep-C is a chronic condition.
You don't think
this is an acute situation?
Coma, vomiting, abdominal pain,
Hep-C explains everything.
Except for the suddenness of the onset.
What's wrong with the timing?
You get home one night.
Your wife hits you with a baseball bat.
Likely cause is the fact you haven't
thanked her for dinner in eight years,
or the receipt for fur handcuffs
she found in your pants.
Sudden onset equals proximate cause.
He also has high estrogen
levels in his blood.
That's indicative of
a chronic condition, not acute.
One test.
What do his other liver tests tell us?
Normal albumen levels point toward acute.
And why is her test better than mine?
Because she's cuter.
Though it's close.
Do a liver biopsy. When the results come
back we'll know what we're looking at.
Why wait to treat the Hep-C?
If I'm right,
Joey gets better that much faster.
Right. Then he gets to testify,
and you get a gold star from Cuddy.
Then what's the downside?
Or is that the downside.
Do I have a reason for
not wanting you to get any stars?
Fine, start the treatment.
It's all your idea.
Don't even mention my name.
There's nothing wrong
with your theory, go.
But in the "humor me" department,
get a biopsy while you're at it.
Foreman, we need to talk.
You're off the case.
What? Why?
Somebody told Vogler that
I lied to the transplant committee.
You think I did?
You're too careful.
You wouldn't jump ship
unless you knew what was in the water.
Stop, you're embarrassing me.
But I want Vogler to
think I think it's you.
And I want Cameron and Chase and
Cuddy and Wilson and the nursing
staff and the cashier in the
parking lot to think that, too.
Right.
The bloodtests show
you have Hepatitis C.
It's a virus that infects the liver.
No way.
Well, it's not all bad news.
It can often be cured,
and even if not, it's manageable.
How'd my brother get this?
Usually it involves the exchange
of bodily fluids, the...
Bodily fluids, what are you talking about?
There are many ways
the virus can be transmitted.
Sharing needles,
blood transfusions...
Hey!
Nobody talks to my brother like this, okay?
Fine. I've no idea how he got it.
But he has Hepatitis-C.
We're going to start him on Interferon...
He doesn't have it, don't mention
it again, don't treat him for it.
House has some directed donations,
foundation support...
It's around here...
He makes you miserable.
Eight years he's worked here, never made
a dime for you, never listened to you.
He can changed, he's...
He hasn't changed in eight years.
Either he can't change,
or you can't change him.
You have no idea
how many times he's lied to you,
undercut your authority,
made you look like crap to other doctors.
Yes, I hate him, and here I am,
desperately trying to protect his job.
What does that tell you?
That you don't hate him.
I do not protect people I like.
I protect people who are
assets to this hospital.
No. That's me.
You, you're softer.
Right. There are three female
Chiefs of Medicine at major hospitals
in this country and we all got
there using our feminine wiles.
It's human nature to
wanna protect people we like.
I don't like him!
We think if we can just
form the right team,
we'll all get along, be
able to pull the boat...
I don't get along with him!
Well, this is not a team, it's not a boat,
it's not a machine that has a lot of parts
that have to work together.
The metaphors are all crap.
This is a business. That's all it is.
You like him,
that's bad for business.
Ah, this is all my fault.
Took another homework break with Betty Lou?
No, last week I showed him a magic trick.
Pulled a quarter out of his nose.
It's a classic.
Yeah, now he won't stop
shoving stuff up there.
Dr. House.
Got a crisis here!
It's okay.
Stop!
It's a neat trick.
You have to believe
you'll actually hurt them.
Your people insulted my brother.
What, they put romano
in the parmesan cheese shaker again?
Said he was a crackhead
or a homo or something.
Those idiots.
How many times am I going to have to
send them through sensitivity training?
Nobody's saying he's a homo,
that would be really, really bad.
So let's put a nice,
friendly spin on it.
Let's go with:
He got raped in prison.
I saw the jailhouse tats,
put it together with the blood tests...
There were rumors, but
Joey never said anything about it.
If people find out
he's being treated for Hep-C?
Feds get that chart, someone says
something to somebody, word'll get out.
And then Joey's manhood,
his rep is destroyed.
You're worried about how his coworkers
will react in the Walmart in Demoyne.
He's not going into Witness Protection,
I'm not gonna let that happen.
Listen, I don't know
if you know about this,
but mob businesses sometimes
keep two sets of books.
One legit, one not.
Exactly.
You jerking my chain?
Doctors are busy, sometimes they forget to
write things down, it happens all the time.
Thanks.
Oh, and...
whatever you're not giving him
for whatever he doesn't have,
is that going to fix him?
I doubt it.
On your way to polish Vogler's car?
Gone are the days of the grumpy
old docs seeing patients
in the basement of his house,
getting paid a few chickens.
How will I eat?
You know what Cuddy has been locked in with
Vogler about all day today, and yesterday?
Floor polish costs through the roof?
You. Her secretary's been to the
photocopier all day with your records.
It's all they're looking at in there.
My car has been stolen.
Or rein-CAR-nated.
Pink slip.
"A gift from the Arnello brothers."
You know, they're gangsters, sure,
but they're thoughtful, too.
You can't keep it. It's graft.
No, no, no, no.
Graft is if I tell them I'll only make
it better if he slips me a couple bucks.
A payoff for something
I'm not supposed to do.
If I'd asked for the
payoff, which I didn't.
I would have done the bad thing anyway.
So there's nothing wrong with this.
Right.
Damn. '65. Perfectly restored.
What do you think a guy like Joey would do
if someone turned down a gift?
That's kind of an insult, isn't it?
He might hurt you.
It's definitely possible.
I'm screwed. Gotta take the car.
Did you see House's new car?
From Joey.
He obviously can't keep it.
You don't mind the hospital
taking money from Vogler?
That's different, Vogler's legit.
That's worse.
Vogler's money came with strings.
Vogler doesn't set me up to have
a mobster take a swing at me.
I'm sure House didn't know...
Joey's pressure dropped.
Pushed IV fluids,
now he's holding 100 systolic.
Septic?
No, looks like he's
bleeding into his liver.
Varices.
You see it with chronic Hep-C all the time.
Biopsy's back. Two findings.
Number one: Lymphoctic infiltrate
and no bridging fibrosis.
Well, whatever's killing him
is not Hep-C. It's acute.
Who said that? I forget.
What are you doing here?
I told you you were off the case.
Right. Your diabolic plan to
convince the evil genius
he's in the clear so he'll let his guard
down and make a fatal mistake, sure.
Well, it's clearly not going to work now.
What evil genius?
If we knew that, then we wouldn't
need a diabolic plan now, would we?
House thinks someone
ratted him out to Vogler.
Oh, what? One of us?
No, you guys love me too much.
All right, look, if it's not the Hep-C,
then what's the problem?
What's causing the liver failure?
Finding number two: Toxins.
No. He's only 30 years old and
his job doesn't expose him
to heavy metals or environmental...
He's a 30-year-old mobster.
He doesn't have a job that results
in accidental exposure to toxins,
he has a job that results
in intentional exposure to toxins.
Someone's poisoned him.
Whatever this toxin is,
it's doing its job and fast.
How long do we have until
the next round of test results?
About four hours.
Too bad his liver's only
going to last another two.
We're going to have to
get him a new one.
What, in two hours?
There is another way.
Relax, it's kosher.
This is so bizarre.
Not really. We just take the blood out
of Joey's body and run it through a pig.
The pig's liver does what
Joey's can't, cleans
the blood, which we
send right back to him.
And the pig makes him better?
No, just buys us some time to figure
out what's poisoning your brother.
Like nothing.
Like you do this all the time?
Oh, we've basically got
a barn in the basement.
Cross off hemlock.
You thought he was being
poisoned by hemlock?
Dr. Euripides tell you
to check for that?
It grows wild
by the highways out here.
So...
How much do you like House?
Chase has a big mouth.
Yeah. He's probably
the one who ratted to Vogler.
I don't think that he would...
Does it hurt when you're with House?
Little pain in the tummy,
but it sort of feels good, too?
I don't have the right to show
interest in someone?
You absolutely do, and I absolutely
have the right to humiliate you for it.
Anything?
White blood count's low;
Probably a result of
the illness, nothing to
connect to the liver.
Is he a smoker?
Let me check.
Early signs of emphysema.
He's been smoking at least a dozen years.
18. You got that from the white count?
Nope, got that from the chest x-ray.
White count just tells me he's quitting.
Two weeks ago.
How's your tummy?
Flat and taut.
I've been on the job for 12 years.
You put $3,000 in your wife's
checking account this morning.
I want to know where it came from.
I got a perfect record.
Where did you get the money.
Cancel the thumb screws,
I've got our culprit.
Who?
Not who, Hu.
Huh?
Thanks for playing along. Chai Hu, a
Chinese herb in his quit smoking candy.
Reduces cravings, also
reduces his white blood count.
Oh yeah, he also took enough
of them to poison himself.
We'll keep him on the pig
for a few more hours,
then take him off the
candy, he'll be fine.
Pig won't be. Oh no.
Hey.
Hey, you feeling better?
I'm famished.
I think they've got
fish sticks on the menu.
Ah, yeah. Makes me miss prison.
So, the mobster's good to go?
I'll keep him over night,
then let the fed's
know he's good to rat
out whoever he wants.
Brother won't be happy.
Maybe have to give back the car.
You should let Vogler tell the feds.
Why?
Because it matters to him.
Because you humiliated him
the first time Joey was released.
You think you should still
be in third there, ace?
He humiliated himself.
And because your job depends
on the kind of mood.
Vogler's in at the end of
his marathon with Cuddy.
Seriously, man, have you ever
driven an automobile before?
There are four gears, you know.
The '66 came with a Shut Up button.
It is my medical opinion that the
patient is healthy and can be released.
Thanks for letting us know.
Give me the U.S. Attorney's office.
I see you've found out
what we're meeting about.
You're having a meeting?
Well, whatever the reason,
the coat looks good on you.
Chai Hu lozenges cause
this kind of liver failure, no way!
Not by themselves, but in combination with
the Interferon it's like gas to a flame.
What Interferon?
For the Hep-C.
What Hep-C?
Oops.
Is hiding a mobster's
Hep-C that important?
Is letting the feds know everything
that important?
You know, you are
a piece of work, even now.
Ed!
Edward.
Joey's back in a coma.
He's stable, but comatose.
Worse than before,
he's on a ventilator.
Question is, why?
It's not his brain, it's not a toxin.
Our friend Babe
helped with that one.
So what else?
The Hep-C.
We never really treated
it, we stopped the.
Interferon when it started
poisoning his liver.
Am I going to have to
write a song about it?
His chronic Hep-C was not bad enough
to produce these symptoms.
The estrogen level indicates it is.
Indicates something else entirely.
We can't give him Interferon now.
There's still traces of the
lozenges in his system.
It'll just poison him again.
Genetics. We don't just treat
the virus, we change it.
A non-nucleoside allosteric inhibitor.
It's never been tried on a human being.
It could kill him.
Well, what's the difference?
He's dead without it.
They're running a trial on dogs
at St. Sebastians in Philadelphia.
I'll make the call.
What else could cause
his estrogen level to be that high?
Nothing.
We're going to put the medicine here.
We don't want it to burn
his veins when it goes in.
You have no idea if it will work.
It's shown promise in testing.
Maybe there's nothing up there,
I watched him like a hawk.
Pretty sure you didn't.
I didn't let him play
with any more little toys.
Thus forcing him to shove
a big one up there.
Stop or I snap your nose off!
He's not too smart.
Genetics is a powerful force.
On the other hand, maybe
he's smarter than you think.
What's going on?
Just give me a second.
Always wanted to use one of these.
Tilt his head back.
I don't know. I don't...
Just tilt his head back.
Nice grasp of concepts,
relationships. Very smart, very cool.
First the policeman, fireman, fire truck.
Your brother was sending
in teams to save the cat.
Wow.
Sometimes the simplest answer...
What types of comas
do you just snap out of?
He's not snapping out of this one,
he's not improving.
You crossed out estrogen,
you've got an explanation?
Yes, I have. A very simple one.
And?
It's private.
You think I'm the one
running to Vogler.
You're currently top of the list.
Toxic comas, person's away from the
cause long enough and they recover.
The feds checked for poisons,
we checked for poisons.
I didn't do it.
It's not a poison, then.
An allergy, then.
Did you hear me?
How about a food sensitivity?
All of his food is strictly controlled.
There's no correlation between
his meals and his condition.
He had steak and potatoes
before the first coma,
and the hospital served fish sticks
before the second one.
You can trust me.
Problem is,
if I can't trust you, I can't trust
your statement that I can trust you.
But thanks anyway,
you've been a big help.
So where did you get the money?
What?
Someone paid you off.
What are you talking about?
It wasn't poison, you told us that it...
You're talking about poison.
I'm talking about payoff. Graft.
Leave him alone.
You paid the Marshall off.
I didn't pay him
to poison my brother.
No, it just worked out that way.
I gave the guy some money to
get him some decent food.
Better than fish sticks?
I'm thinking steak.
We asked for pasta.
Those stupid feds could care less...
He had steak before both comas.
Your brother has
Ornithine Transcarbamylase Deficiency.
You want me to write it down?
Good, because it takes a while.
It's genetic, it can present at any time.
The patient eats a large amount of protein,
especially if he's not used to it.
That's it?
He stays off the red meat
and he's going to be fine?
Yes. If I'm right, and we stop
the current treatment, he gets better.
If we stop the current treatment
and I'm wrong, he dies.
Why would you be wrong?
His estrogen level.
OTD doesn't explain his estrogen level.
But I have a theory.
There is one chemical that, if ingested,
can cause a person's estrogen
level to increase dramatically.
What is it?
It's called estrogen.
Joey's taking estrogen?
What, he wants a sex change?
No, nothing like that.
It's called Male Flame.
It's probably more consumer
friendly in the original Chinese.
It's an herbal aphrodisiac
marketed to gay men.
Oh, here we go.
And sold on the same website
that sells his Chai Hu lozenges.
Guess what's in it?
Starts with an "e".
You want to get hit, too?
That would be quite a trick.
"He slapped me so hard
his brother turned straight."
Joey's a big-time mobster.
Guys like that don't get raped in prison.
They get gifts, they get food,
drugs, cigarettes, cable TV...
Joey is not gay.
Well, maybe not gay,
but certainly delightful.
You, on the other hand, hitting a doctor,
even if it was only Chase...
and asking another one
to keep his chart
fresh and homo-free.
Well, that's a bit of an overreaction,
wouldn't you say?
It's almost like you're scared
that it might be true.
You're wrong.
Okay. Then don't stop the treatment.
But if you're wrong, he dies.
Okay.
He never said anything
to me about it, not once.
That's what I love
about you mob guys:
So tolerant of others, so accepting.
Only way he was coming
out was way, way out.
Lose the tattoos, change his name,
move to another town...
how's a guy like him going to do that?
Witness protection.
It's not just for witnesses any more.
You can go in now,
sit with him if you want.
How much longer?
It's only been three hours.
If it's the OTD...
If it's the OTD?
What if House is wrong, huh?
That severe a reaction,
it'll take some time...
He makes assumptions about people,
talks you into things.
Mr. Arnello. He's awake.
He wants to see you.
You look like crap.
That's a joke, see. I'm sick,
I said you look like crap...
You have no idea
what I just went through out there.
You kept getting worse, and
Dr. House kept saying all this crap.
If I think you're normal,
then he's going to keep
giving you the medicine,
and if you weren't...
Weren't what?
Normal?
Yeah.
He said you were a fag.
Witness protection,
that's your big chance to be one.
You believe him?
I don't know what to believe.
You were sick.
I had to make a decision.
I thought you were gonna die.
You believed him.
He stopped the medicine.
Here I am.
- I wanted to talk to you about this...
- There's nothing to talk about.
You ordered some
Chinese internet health crap,
they sent the wrong pills,
you took 'em.
Yeah, yeah, that,
that must be it.
You want to testify, go ahead.
I told the doc,
he said it's okay.
I don't expect you to understand...
I don't.
All I need to know is
you're my brother, Joey.
If you think this thing, whatever,
is going to make you happy,
I think you should do it.
You should.
Vogler wants to fire you.
Lose the whole department.
Good thing you fought
for me, though, right?
The dress was a nice move,
but you've got to follow it up.
Nasty weekend in Vegas,
something that
shows off your real administrative skills.
He threatened to fire me.
I'm sorry.
So, how long do I have?
I've a lot of personal stuff to pack up.
I assume you're going
to want to throw a party.
I told him I know where the
bodies are buried,
the stuff he needs to know
that's not in the books.
Told him he can't ditch me.
He's only keeping you on because
you know the secret handshakes.
He's a quick study.
Six months, he'll
have the moves down.
Then he won't need you any more.
I'll deal with that then.
So I stay.
Yes.
But some things are going to change.
Profits. New world order.
Everything's about profits.
Yeah, that's real new.
You could rent out the Corvette every
once in a while, or lend it to a friend.
That would be easy,
and it would be wrong.
But Cuddy stood up for you.
To a point.
To what point?
I gotta do six more clinic hours a month.
So do two of them.
Why only two?
'Cause one of them's gone.
I gotta fire somebody.
Good morning.