So now the plan is either find
ourselves a new counselor,
stick it out with the old
one but go more often,
or resign ourselves to the fact
that she's never gonna be happy
no matter what I do, so let's
just take the money we're wasting
and put it towards a membership
at Lakeview, you know?
I'm guessing the last option
obviously formally present her.
Yeah. Jeez.
What's with you?
It usually takes about half
speed to stay with me.
I didn't get a lot of sleep last night.
How are things with Elise?
Great.
Great?
Yeah.
Simple answers. You're either out
of breath or you're lying to me.
Yeah... we have our moments,
but they usually work out.
Can I get some water?
Yeah...
So how do you work things out?
Talk, someone apologizes.
Man I shouldn't have drank last night.
Hey, you mean you apologize.
Yeah, I guess.
How often do you guys have sex?
Enough...
You do it this morning?
You did, you did it this morning,
maybe that's why you can't stand up.
Come on!
Elise!
Honey, I'm dehydrated.
We have anything with electrolytes?
Sleeping beauty, wake up,
this is an emergency.
The fridge is empty.
Come on, it's almost four!
Elise, sweetie...
Call Jacques, tell him
I'm not feeling well.
It's Saturday.
You haven't been to work
in three days, remember?
Just let me sleep.
Come on. You haven't been
out of bed since Wednesday.
Leave me alone...
Come on, lets go.
I said leave me alone!
I think there's something wrong with me.
She's been averaging 18 hours of
sleep a day since her admission.
Clinical depression.
Incredibly contagious.
Every time I'm around
one of them I get blue.
It's not clinical depression.
Great, you got it all figured out.
You don't need me.
Three ER doctors, two neurologists and a
radiologist have all figured out what its not,
we need to figure out what it is.
Well, maybe if above mentioned
doctors were interested
in my opinion they would
have asked for it.
None of them are willing to
subject themselves to you.
No pain no gain.
The blood work showed no
signs of inflammation,
and no one can figure out
what's actually the cause of...
Huh.
What?
Husband described her
as being unusually irritable recently.
And?
I didn't know it was possible for a woman
to be "unusually" irritable.
Nice try, but you're a
misanthrope, not a masochist.
What's the first thing you ask a
doctor who's referring a patient?
Are you questioning my
ability to take a history?
"What's the primary"...
Not "what?". "Why?"
Diseases don't have motives.
No, but doctors do.
Why this patient, what interests you?
Give me the chart.
Why?
I find your interest interesting.
She's irritable, sleeping 18 hours a day.
What's interesting about that?
Hypersomnia is usually accompanied
by irritability in depressed patients.
True, but not relevant.
She's not depressed.
Hello! She's sleeping 18 hours a day!
Fever.
Clinical depression does not cause fever.
She could be sick and depressed?
She's sick! Dammit,
why didn't I think of that?
Yeah, that's what I mean...
Elevated SED rate indicates inflammation.
Hypersomnia and personality
changes point toward the brain.
Not the spleen.
Thank goodness we hired a neurologist!
Brain symptoms... hmm, could
this be a brain problem?
No other systemic signs of
inflammation, probably not vasculitis.
What about parasites?
Malaria, chagas?
The patient's never been outside the
United States, especially the tropics.
You mean she claims she's
never been outside the U.S.
Very good.
Doesn't matter, blood and c-sub
smears show no sign of parasites.
Has to be a tumor then.
A tumor sitting directly
on top of the brain stem.
That three ER doctors, two neurologists,
and a radiologist missed?
Partridge in a pear tree missed it too.
Redo the blood work and
get a new MRI with 2
millimeter cuts through
the mesodiencephalic.
And check for evil stepmothers.
This much sleep usually
indicates poisoned apples.
Anything else beside the
shortness of breath?
Not really, its actually
just kind of a tightness.
You smoke?
No, never.
Exercise?
Eight hours a day.
I teach preschool.
Sounds fun.
Any history of heart
disease in your family?
Not that I know of.
Take a deep breath.
Been under a lot of stress lately?
None more than usual.
You're probably just a little anemic,
but I'm going to do an
EKG just to make sure.
Do I need to take this off?
No, you can just pull that down in front.
Good. Lord. Are those real?
Do they look real?
They look pretty damn good.
They were a present for my husband's 40th.
I figured he'd enjoy them
more than a sweater.
That's so sweet.
I'm afraid the cause of your problem
could be staring us right in the face.
Actually I guess I'm the
one doing the staring.
Of course I can't be sure,
I'd like to consult a colleague.
He's actually somewhat of
an expert in these matters.
Can I get a page on Dr. Wilson?
A tumor?
We don't know, we're
checking just to be safe.
They already checked for that.
The previous MRI had a broader view.
Some tumors are almost impossible to see
unless we know exactly where to look.
That means it would be small, right?
Yes.
So you'd be able to operate? Take it out?
If it is a tumor, there are a
variety of treatment options,
but there are variables
other than just size.
Don't worry...
Too late.
Try to remain as still as possible.
The less distortion there is,
the more detail we'll be able to see.
Ok.
Well. That's what breasts look like.
Is a lie a lie if everybody
knows it's a lie?
Well, if a tree pretends
to fall in a forest...
House, come on, they're breasts.
They're a birthday present,
not a philosophical treatise.
Lie number one,
she did not do that for her husband,
she did that for herself.
She thinks if she looks
different, she'll be different.
No, she thinks if she
looks different, she'll
be more attractive,
which, I have to say...
Not to her husband.
Cosmetic surgery is so that everyone
else will look at us differently.
Same reason you're wearing that tie.
Well exactly, that was
going to be my next point.
Last three months, same five ties.
Thursday should be that paisley thing.
It's a gift from my wife.
No its not. Julie hates green.
You bought that yourself.
You want to look pretty. At work.
Wilson's got a girlfriend...
Stop! Stop. I don't.
It takes two department heads
to treat shortness of breath?
What, do the complications increase
exponentially with cup size?
I want an EKG and blood tests
including tox screen on Mrs...
Exam Room 1.
You're ordering tests
to cover your lechery.
Interesting.
Very tricky case.
You love everybody.
That's your pathology.
There were no lesions and no
mass effect that we could see.
What does that mean?
It means we're still not sure what's
causing your neurological problems.
I know some thing are hard to cure,
but what I just don't
get is why it's taking
so long to figure out
what's wrong with her.
I know you're scared, I would be too.
I don't feel good...
You feeling nauseous?
Honey? You all right?
She's seizing!
Get her on her side.
I need some Ativan!
I'll get it!
What's happening?
She's having a seizure.
She's aspirating, suction!
Elise!
Come on Elise!
The MRI reveals nothing.
That we were able to detect.
It's not a tumor.
A small glioma could hide from contrast.
We could do a PET scan.
Yes, that's how a responsible doctor
would waste his time in the situation.
Suddenly tests and radiologists
aren't capable of error?
A glioma not presenting
on a contrast MRI
would have to be smaller
than a grain of sand,
which does not a gravely ill person make.
It could be just postictal disorientation.
We would have seen improvement by now.
Late stage Lyme Disease can cause seizures.
Does the husband care about her?
He hasn't left her bedside.
No way... it also means she
doesn't have Lyme Disease.
What? Love conquers all?
Lyme Disease initially
presents with a rash.
Mr. Clingy would have noticed.
We've looked at everything else.
Did you look at her breasts?
Men.
Could be paraneoplastic.
She have any family
history of breast cancer?
Her mother died of it.
The brain, but not
the brain. Clever, huh?
How can breast cancer cause
problems in her brain?
There are molecular similarities
between brain cells and tumor cells.
Paraneoplastic Syndrome causes the body's
own antibodies to get thrown off track.
They end up attacking the
brain instead of the tumor.
So if you do find the
tumor, what do you do?
We treat the underlying malignancy.
Once there's no tumor to
attack, there's nothing
for the antibodies to
get confused about.
If the tumor's treatable.
Exactly.
I'm sorry,
I know it's uncomfortable.
The tighter we go,
the better the image will be.
Least it'll keep me awake.
Don't worry, it's almost over.
I wish people would stop
telling me not to worry.
I'm sorry.
My mom was the same age.
We've been trying to get
pregnant for over a year.
I guess we're lucky we didn't.
A lot has changed since your mom died.
Don't worr...
Don't give up.
No tumor?
The MRI and mammogram only showed
a few benign calcifications.
It's most likely a small cell tumor,
its no surprise we're
having trouble finding it.
We should do a PET scan.
Start with her lungs,
and maybe her bones...
Sometimes it presents with no tumor at all.
How can a disease caused by a tumor
present if there's no tumor?
It happens. Twelve percent of cases.
And how do you treat it
if there's no tumor?
You don't. Those twelve
percent have no treatment.
They were too busy looking for the tumor,
right till they put the
patient in the ground.
What choice do we have?
Treat the symptoms.
IV Immunoglobulin.
So we're just
going to ignore the tumor?
Eventually it'll get bigger.
Then it'll be really easy to find.
One of you needs to check
out where she works.
Why?
Cause the husband's not sick.
Meaning?
If it's not paraneoplastic
and it is a reaction to some
sort of toxic, it's obviously
not coming from their home.
Foreman, you do it.
Why are you riding me?
It's what I do... has
it gotten worse lately?
Yeah. Seems to me.
Really. Well that rules out the race thing.
Cause you were just as black last week.
How long has Elise worked here?
Three years, she's my best rotisseur.
What's that?
The rotisseur prepares the
roasted meats and gravies.
How do you clean your grill?
(SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE.)
They say elbow grease.
Do you use chemical cleaners?
Ah, no. Absolutely no, our chefs
don't do the cleaning, anyway.
What about pesticides?
You must spray for roaches
and that sort of thing?
Nope, my kitchen is clean. No roaches.
(SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE.)
I need to get back to work.
So the fact that I'm here asking you
these questions, it doesn't worry you?
Look at me. I'm here 18 hours a day.
That guy practically lives here,
he does live here...
I use the same detergents for 15 years
and everyone is healthy as a horse.
Whatever Elise has she didn't get here.
Tell her I hope she feels better,
and I had to get a new rotisseur.
Where's Ed?
He went down to the gift
shop to buy a shirt.
I told him I'd stay up
here in case you woke up.
You must have better things to do.
I send my laundry out.
You're not married?
No.
Waiting for the perfect guy?
Let me guess.
You've already found him.
He threw my towels out the window.
What?
It's how we met.
Freshman year, he came to a
party my roommate and I threw.
He spent most of the night
on the bathroom floor.
He figured I wouldn't notice vomit on
the towels if I didn't have any towels.
I'm assuming he came back
the next day to apologize?
No way. We had to track him down.
Conflict resolution has never
been one of Ed's strong points.
Nobody's perfect, right?
I guess.
Oh my neck hurts.
You've been in this bed
for a really long time.
We're gonna do the same
test we did last night, ok?
Do you know what day it is?
My arm itches.
It's probably just a mild skin irritation,
I'll get you some
hydrocortisone in a minute.
Do you know what day it is?
Tuesday. It really itches.
How about get you that cream right now.
Oh my God! Get them off! Someone!
Get them off of me!
Elise calm down.
- Get them off!
- I need some Haldol, 5 milligrams.
Elise, what's wrong?
Get them off! Get them off!
There's nothing there, Elise.
There's nothing there!
We had to sedate her.
You gave sedatives to a patient who's
already sleeping 18 hours a day?
It was better than letting her
scratch all the skin off her arms.
Or supposed to be.
Creepy-crawlies are consistent
with paraneoplastic syndrome.
Onset immediately after IVIG isn't.
There is a simple explanation. Maybe
she really has bugs under her skin.
Infection?
That's what the worsening of symptoms
after immunotherapy would suggest.
Blood cultures and the timeline
rule out most bacteria.
If a patient throws up on your shoes
do you clean up "most" of it?
The symptoms rule out the rest.
Serology rules out viruses,
CSS smears rule out parasites.
In the final stage of
African Trypanosomiasis
almost all the parasites
are inside the brain.
It's possible they wouldn't show on smears.
But it's not possible for
a patient who's never
been to Africa to have
African Sleeping Sickness.
I'm just saying it fits the symptoms.
She could have got it from a transfusion.
Or I'm just saying she could
have got it from a transfusion.
Which she never had.
Okay...
What about toxins?
No, the kitchen she works in is
cleaner than some hospitals.
But they do serve rabbit.
Rabbit Fever fits her symptoms.
Tularemia initially presents with a
rash or ulcer near the infection site.
Not if she inhaled it.
Chopping the meat with a cleaver could
easily aerosolize the bacteria.
No, then she'd have respiratory symptoms.
Maybe she ignored it,
figured she had a cold.
We rejected Lyme Disease because the
couple would have noticed a rash,
but a wet hacking cough is
just going to slip right by.
Hey, it's either that or she missed her exit
on the turnpike and wound up in Africa.
Ok. Two lousy ideas.
Unfortunately they're better
than all the other ideas.
Tularemia. Bizarre.
Very nice.
That's why I ride you.
Did he just turn on the TV?
He needs to think.
So this should tell us whether
or not she's got rabbit fever?
For a diagnosis of Tularemia you need a
four-fold increase in serum antibody levels.
To measure an increase you need a
before, all we have is an after.
A single titer over 160
would be a big clue.
"That's why I ride you."
What does that mean?
Even when I have a good
idea it's because of him?
Actually I think he said
your idea was a lousy idea.
It has to be one of these two conditions.
I say we take our best guess and
just start treatment. Or treat both.
The treatment for Tularemia
can cause aplastic anemia.
How come he doesn't ride you guys?
He's got a crush on you.
He just doesn't know how to show it.
Get over it, he rides everybody.
And the treatment for sleeping
sickness kills one in ten patients.
So we start with the safer treatment.
By "safer" you mean the one that's
slightly less likely to kill her?
Foreman got the gang testing for Tularemia?
Yep.
Probably inconclusive, but worth doing.
So what's her name?
When do I get to meet her?
There's nobody. Give it up.
Your lips say no,
your shoes say yes.
Well they're French.
You can't trust a word they say.
Solid, yet stylish.
A professional woman would be impressed.
I'm thinking accountant, actuary, maybe.
It's somebody in the hospital.
Patient?
No, chemo's not sexy.
Daughter of the patient?
She would certainly have
the neediness you need.
I'm not gonna date a patient's daughter.
Very ethical.
Of course, most married men would
say they don't date at all.
There was no date!
I had lunch with one of the nurses.
It's her first time in an oncology unit
and she's having a tough time,
emotionally.
Perfect.
I wanted to be nice.
That's all. I mean it.
You always do.
It's part of your charm.
Hi boys.
Mrs. Campbell's test results.
Oh, you remember her, the preschool
teacher with the heart of silicon.
Nope, doesn't ring a bell.
They came in yesterday, I figured
you guys would have been all over them.
I know how concerned you are.
She's all upset because we paid
more attention to the other girl.
You check out her ass,
I've got the chest.
The tests were normal.
'Cause that's just my
opinion, you may want to call
a couple of guys from
maintenance in for a consult.
You check her EKG results
before she left the other day?
You ordered it.
You're the responsible one.
What's wrong? They look normal to me.
Where is she?
Waiting downstairs, why?
I was right.
Do I have to get rid of the implants?
Surprisingly, no.
But your EKG shows a slightly
decreased heart rate.
Is that a problem?
You told me you hadn't changed your
diet or exercise, were you lying?
Lying?
Does your husband have high blood pressure?
My husband?
Yeah.. see, if you're gonna
repeat everything I say
this conversation is gonna
take twice as long.
Yes, he was diagnosed six mouths ago...
He do a lot of cooking at home?
Not really, other than
oatmeal in the morning.
Did you happen to notice a slightly
odd taste to the oatmeal lately?
Wait, are you saying that...
That it looks like your husband
stirred in some of his
blood pressure medication
along with brown sugar.
You think my husbands trying to poison me?
No, nothing like that.
He just doesn't want to have sex with you.
Decreased sex drive is one
of the most common side
effects of the beta
blockers he's been taking.
I'm guessing he figured if you're
both frigid, no harm no foul.
You should have gotten him the sweater.
That's ridiculous.
Fine.
But if you're still concerned
about the shortness
of breath, I'd start
making your own breakfast.
Wait!
What should I do?
If you care about your husband at all,
I'd do the responsible thing:
Buy yourself some condoms,
go to a bar, find...
Lab tests inconclusive?
Not surprisingly.
No. But too bad.
Luckily, I have the answer.
To what?
Thanks for asking.
The life itself. Sex.
Anything that can be transmitted via the
blood can be transmitted through sex.
Sleeping sickness from sex?
It's not without precedent.
I'm pretty sure it is.
Unless you're talking about going to Africa
and having sex with the tse tse fly.
A Portuguese man was diagnosed three years
ago with CNS affected sleeping sickness.
His only connection with
Africa was through a
girlfriend who served under
the military in Angola.
Oi, where'd you find that?
The journal de Instituto de
Higinay Medicina Tropical.
You don't read Portuguese?
You do?
I'm pretty sure that's what it said.
Either that or
it was an ad for sunglasses.
Her husband has never
been to Africa either.
Oh, stymied again.
Your logic is bulletproof.
I think ignoring respiratory symptoms
is more likely than cheating.
Because?
They're completely devoted to each other.
They love each other.
Or?
They're overcompensating for guilt.
Find out which it is.
You want me to ask a man whose wife
is about to die if he cheated on her?
No, I want you to be
polite and let her die.
Actually, I don't want
you to ask her anything.
Foreman take the husband,
Chase take the wife.
You don't trust me to do my job?
We all formulate questions based
on the answers we want to hear.
And how exactly do you re-formulate
"Have you screwed around?"
Did you know she's been
trying to get pregnant?
Yes.
After you got so freaked
about the sick babies
a while ago I figured
that was your thing.
But you've never been
prescribed folic acid,
and you can't lose a baby if
you've never been pregnant.
You pulled my medical records?
You coughed the other day,
I was concerned.
You were curious.
Like an eight-year old
boy with a puzzle that's
just a little to grown-up
for him to figure out.
To-MAY-to, to-MAH-to...
So... it's either sleeping
sickness or this rabbit thing.
They're both fatal without treatment.
And unfortunately the treatment
for both is extremely dangerous.
Are there test you can do?
Not at this stage.
But each condition has a unique history.
We're hoping your answers to a
few questions will help us.
Sure. Whatever you need to know.
Before the sleeping problems,
did you have any trouble breathing,
a cough that wouldn't go away,
anything like that?
No.
Are you certain?
Absolutely.
I've never been away from her
for more than a night,
if she had breathing troubles,
I would have noticed.
The other condition is
significantly more likely if...
if you've had an affair.
Have you ever had an affair?
Of course not.
You sure?
I think I'd remember cheating on my wife.
You might be reluctant to admit it...
No.
I just want to be perfectly clear.
If your wife has sleeping sickness
and we don't treat her, she'll die.
I would never do that to Ed.
I love him.
Absolutely not.
I love her.
Alright then.
They say no cheating,
we cross of sleeping sickness.
Any new ideas?
Ok, we go with Foreman's Tularemia.
Start her on IV-Chloramphenicol 25
milligrams per kilogram four times a day.
Good night.
Where's Ed?
Right next to you.
Well you are two down, two to go.
Two days?
No, doses.
You have about twenty
more days of this fun.
What time is it?
About four a.m.
I pulled the short straw.
Flow rate looks good.
No rash or flushing...
What time is it?
4 a.m.
Do you not remember just asking?
I don't know...
Elise...?
Elise? Elise? Elise!
What are you doing?
Trying to wake her.
She fall asleep again?
In the middle of a sentence.
Elise!
What's happening?
Patient's not responding.
Pulse is fine, airways open.
Check her blood pressure.
Pupils are reactive.
Elise wake up.
You gotta wake up.
What does that mean?
What are you doing?
She's not responsive to pain.
Come on Elise!
Is she dying?
I don't know.
She's in a coma.
There's only one way a Tularemia patient
goes into a coma
while on IV-Chloramphenicol.
The patient doesn't have Tularemia.
And then there was one.
Patient comes in because
she's sleeping too much.
It takes ten doctors and a coma
to diagnose sleeping sickness.
And then there was none.
We still have the problem
of explaining how a white
chick from Jersey who's never
traveled south of D.C.
Has African sleeping sickness.
Well, the obvious explanation?
I made it clear.
If this guy's lying about sleeping around,
he knows he's murdering his wife.
Does seem unlikely...
Go away.
What are you doing?
Checking for lymphadenopothy.
And waiting for you.
Who are you?
I'm Dr. House.
Your wife has human
African Trypanosomiasis.
Sleeping sickness.
You mean its not Tularemia.
A virus, tumor or cancer.
Nope.
I've never had an affair.
I believe you.
And I trust Elise.
The treatment for this
disease is a drug that's...
fatal on its own ten
percent of the time.
Which is why I need your written consent
before I can legally prescribe it.
Why would she lie if she
knew it could kill her?
I don't ask why patients lie,
I just assume they all do.
But why?
To protect you, because she
didn't think it mattered.
It just seemed easier because...
that's what people do.
Now, If you're absolutely certain that your
wife has never had sex with anyone but you
since you've been married,
then I'm wrong.
But if you think there's a possibility
that just one time she wasn't perfect...
one weekend you're out of town...
one fight when she ran to a friend,
one stupid Christmas party...
then you need to allow
me to start treatment.
Because if we don't...
she's gonna be dead by tomorrow morning.
Do you trust your wife that much?
I don't know...
I'll start the treatment.
Glass syringes?
And special IV tubing.
Why do we need this stuff?
Because Melarsoprol melts plastic.
This stuff's supposedly arsenic
mixed with antifreeze.
What doesn't kill us
makes us stronger, huh?
At least you wouldn't have been so glib
if you'd been prescribed Melarsoprol.
Can cause vomiting,
abdominal pain,
blood toxicity, neural damage,
cardiac arrhythmia...
I forgot to say it's gonna
hurt like all hell.
She's lucky she's in a coma.
How long before we know its working?
It's tough to say.
It's a good sign that she
hasn't gotten any worse.
Does she even know I'm here?
She knows you're always there for her.
Yeah...
If she gets better it means she
wasn't always there for me.
It means she made a mistake.
I can't help it.
Part of me, a big part of me...
can't handle that.
Doesn't want her to get better.
Does that make me a terrible person?
Yes.
So we're treating her for
African sleeping sickness
because you don't think it's possible for
someone to be faithful in a relationship?
And you do?
Yes.
And you need to tell me that?
Look, I'm not having an affair.
I had lunch, with someone I
work with, at work. Once.
I believe you.
What I don't believe is
that it'll be just once.
I love my wife.
You certainly love saying it.
I'm sorry.
I know you love your wife.
You loved all your wives.
Probably still do.
In fact, you probably still love
all the women you ever
loved who weren't your wives.
You can be a real jerk
sometimes, you know that?
Yeah. And you're the good guy.
At least I try.
As long as you're trying to be good,
you can do whatever you want.
And as long as you're not trying,
you can say whatever you want.
So between us, we can do anything.
We can rule the world!
Mixing up some margaritas?
Mines a double, Senorita.
That's Portuguese, you know.
Spanish.
What's going on?
I'm re-calibrating the centrifuge.
Turn around.
It's a very sad thing,
an un-calibrated centrifuge.
It makes me cry too.
I'm not crying.
Ok.
I told the husband he was a jerk.
Why?
When I was in college, I...
I fell in love, and I got married. And...
At that age the chances
of a marriage lasting...
It lasted six months.
Thyroid cancer metastasized to his brain.
There was nothing they could do.
I was 21, and...
I watched my husband die.
I'm sorry...
But that's not the whole story.
It's a symptom, not your illness.
Thyroid cancer would have been diagnosed
at least a year before his death,
you knew he was dying when you married him.
Must have been when you first met him.
And you married him anyway.
You can't be that good a
person and well adjusted.
Why?
Because you wind up
crying over centrifuges.
Or hating people.
Fever spiked at 104.
Echo shows global hyperkinesis.
Blood pressure?
Barely 90 over 40.
You give her gilpamine?
Started 270 micrograms per minute
ten minutes ago, still no change.
Killing her parasites isn't gonna do much
good if we kill her heart at the same time.
A heart can be replaced, a brain can't.
Right now were killing both.
If she's gonna die, we
should at least let her do
it without that acid
flowing through her veins.
What's happening?
We would have expected your wife's
condition to show some improvement by now,
but it hasn't.
It's going the other way.
Please don't die...
please don't die...
She's awake!
Hey. She's gonna be ok.
Yeah, sure.
What are you gonna do?
Were you always honest with her?
Do you know how lucky you are?
Your wife is alive, she loves you!
What she did...
you can't love a person
and do that to them.
She loves you.
I need to know
who you had the affair with.
He has to be notified so he
can get treatment as well.
Why did you lie to us?
You knew your life was at stake.
He's not coming back, is he?
We all make mistakes,
and we all pay a price.
I need that name.
Hi, there...
How you doing?
Fine.
Do you know where your dad is?
Can I help you?