Can you breathe?
Yeah.
Shame, that. Turn around.
Babylon beast!
You're a lying pig, Luther.
You ain't no better than me.
Get me out!
Whatever you are!
-See you SOON. Bye.
-Bye.
-Take care.
Wait! Miss.
Miss! It's Lee Peck.
You taught me in English.
Sorry, Miss.
Did I just scare you?
Yeah, you did. Yeah.
Miss, I'm sorry...
Go home, Lee.
What?
Oh, sh...
Miss! Miss, let me in!
Miss. Miss, just let me in yeah?
Miss! Miss! Let me in, Miss.
Miss, let me in.
-Lee, go home.
-Miss, please!
I'm calling the police.
-Miss, please...
-I'm doing it right now, Lee.
I'll get you fixed up, honest.
All right, all right, all right.
Hold on.
Just relax, all right? Don't... Don't!
Cuff him!
Take him.
Oh, God!
George, what is all this bollocks?
Where is he?
Where is who?
Fuck off.
-Where is he?
-Who, George, who?
I don't know who you're talking about.
That's my son.
-Alastair.
-Alastair, yes.
The elder one. Washes...
Washes the money for you, yeah.
What about him?
Allegedly. Okey-dokey.
Massey, please.
So, what we're gonna do is...
I'm gonna ask that question
a maximum of five more times.
Cornelius, I've no...
Where's my boy? Come on, John.
Hurry up. Where is he?
I have no clue.
And that's twice.
All right. I don't know. I don't know.
Last chance. Come on. Wake up, John.
Give me that.
Put your hands where I can see 'em.
So, what's going on?
-You really don't know, do you?
-No, I really don't know.
Where was he when he got taken?
Alastair? Where was he? Who was it?
Ah, see, now you're fishing.
Well, if you tell me who did it
then I might be able to help you.
I'm not a 12-year-old girl.
I take care of my own business.
You started this, George!
I'm just doing due diligence,
making sure you're not part of it.
What'd you say?
Part of it? Why would I be a part of it?
-We've got history.
-Not that kind of history.
Says the bloke who kidnapped me
and cuffed me to a radiator.
Yeah, fair dues.
-So, are we good?
-Are we good?
He's my boy, John.
Do me a favour, let me get on with it.
George. I don't care about you
and I don't care about your boy.
All I care about is going home.
Leave me alone.
Tell the Spice Girls
to back off as well.
DCI Luther.
I'll put the kettle on, shall I?
I see you're settling in.
Yeah. Yes, of course.
Listen, uh... Milk's in the fridge.
You know where everything is.
I'll be back in a second.
So... How's Catherine working out?
DS Halliday?
She's okay, I suppose. Why do you ask?
You don't like her?
Oh, it's not that. I'm...
Look, John, this,
uh, direct entry thing...
Head-hunting people
from the public sector,
fast-tracking them through the ranks...
None of us like it,
but that's the way it is.
Give it 10 minutes and DS Halliday
will be Superintendent Halliday.
Boss, are you, um,
telling me to behave myself?
I'm saying that we're the dinosaurs
and she's the meteor.
So, yes.
Don't show her how it's done.
Show her how it's supposed to be done.
-Noted.
-Good.
I hope so.
It is so. Luther.
All right. We're on our way.
Think we gotta go somewhere, boss.
DS Halliday.
Morning.
-Can I borrow a pen?
-Yeah, sure.
The killer took his eyes
and cut his tongue out.
All right.
Keep it.
-No, I couldn't. It's a lovely pen.
-Honestly. It's my gift to you.
Thanks.
The killer chased him from
Ballarat Street just around the corner.
All right.
Um, can I ask... Um, is...
Is this normal?
Normal?
Thanks.
Witness hasn't a clue
as to what happened.
The victim's an ex-pupil, Lee Peck.
He followed her home.
Next thing she knows,
he's banging on her door,
pleading to be let in.
Seems like the killer came from nowhere.
I would like
to talk to the witness.
Benny.
Mate, um... I need a favour.
An off-the-books type favour.
Oh, yeah? I thought
we're behaving ourselves these days.
No, we are. It won't be a problem.
Says who?
Well, then. What do you need?
Someone's got George Cornelius
on the hook.
All right? I need to find out who it is.
Why do we care?
I don't know. I, um...
It just doesn't feel right.
So, I'm just gonna have
a little nose about,
and not fuss with warrants
or anything like that?
No, no, no, no.
Go on, then. You talked me into it,
you silver-tongued devil.
Cheers.
All right. So, where are we?
First victim's Paul Redford,
29, landscape gardener.
-Single and ready to mingle.
-What does that mean?
Oh, he used a number
of online hook-up sites.
Oh, let's hope we're not looking
at another Steven Port.
Lab's looking for GHB
and other drugs.
But Port, he liked to incapacitate,
rape and then murder his victims.
He didn't do anything like this.
-Nothing similar on the books?
-No, nothing close.
All right. Well, you know,
this isn't our boy's first disco.
I mean, even Jack the Ripper
had to work up
towards what he did to Mary Jane Kelly.
And our boy hasn't got to this place
from a standing start.
Nope.
Okay, first up, um...
Let's see if there's an up tick
on people being assaulted in public.
Stabbed in the groin, the buttocks
with a pen-knife or big pin...
Like a hat pin.
-A what?
-A hat pin.
It's like a long pin, um,
like, this big. You can use it for...
I've seen those.
And then let's check, uh,
recent prison releases
of men that generally fit the pattern.
What about the other victim?
- Any connection?
- Uh, no.
It looks like an acute case
of wrong place, wrong time.
Hmm.
What does this say to you,
the eyes and the tongue?
Uh, symbolic punishment?
For what?
Intruding on a private act, maybe?
And this business, how has he done that?
That's LEDs sewn into his hood,
it confuses CCTV.
Ah, okay.
So, this isn't random, is it?
Which means there's gonna be more.
Couldn't keep them out.
Nowhere near it.
Yeah, man. Yeah, man.
Yeah. Who's this?
-It is I, Krampus.
-Benny?
The half goat, half demon creature
who punishes naughty children.
Bad time. What's up?
-Listen, mate. I need a favour.
-Of course. Totally.
-What? Seriously?
-No.
Then you leave me no alternative,
but to huff and puff
and blow your walls down.
How are you gonna do that, then?
By telling Mr Cornelius
that you're on the skim.
Well, I haven't.
And that's mad because he'd kill anyone
who did something like that.
How do you even know this shit?
Big lad, you need to brush up
on your online security. Hmm.
Benny?
Yeah.
Oh, cool. Nice one. All right.
All right, um...
If anything comes up,
you let me know, okay?
Okay, sure. Um, cool. Where will you be?
-Out.
-Yep. Cool. Sure.
Errol.
If they catch me wearing this,
I'm dead about 18 times.
He'll feed me to his dogs.
-I'm not joking.
-Well, don't get caught, then.
Actual dogs.
He's got dogs, like them '70s dogs.
-Errol...
-Dobermanns.
I just need to know
what's going on, all right? That's it.
I don't even know anything. Huh?
He just wants me there for a bit
of extra va-va-voom. That's all.
I'm numbers, mate. I'm muscle.
I just need you in the room, listening.
That's all. All right?
Don't say nothing,
don't go asking any questions,
just let us listen.
Everyone, keep your wig on. Keep schtum.
Afternoon.
Look, we all want the money,
but my son has nothing to do with this.
It's not how we do things
in the civilised world.
Or what's left of it.
All right, all right.
You get your money. I get my boy.
And that's it.
I'll meet you there. Close of play.
Right.
I want this place watched.
Like a hen-night in Saudi.
All right, off we toddle.
Are you all right, Errol?
You're looking a bit peaky.
No, I'm good, George.
Really?
You're coming across as a bit clammy,
to be honest.
Yeah, uh, just... Just sweaty.
It's a family thing.
On my mum's side.
Delightful.
Somebody point a gun
into Errol's face, please.
Just one.
Oh, mate.
Do me a favour, Errol. Lift your shirt.
Oh, you don't have to bend over, mate.
Just lift your shirt.
I can't do that.
- Stop. All right. All right.
- Fair enough.
Bloody hell.
Hello, hello, hello.
What's all this?
Oh, the German.
I suppose this goes to show
you really don't have a scooby
about what's going on.
But you're still curious,
me little tinker.
So, here's what we do.
You can follow me if you like.
Or you can save poor old Errol here.
Remember what happened to Harry Samson.
What happened to Harry Samson?
What did happen to Harry Samson?
Harry Samson.
They blew his head off.
So, where do you think
they're taking him?
Somewhere quiet, privacy,
a bit of distance,
a bit of real estate, where...
Where would they go?
Come on. Come on, John.
No, no, no, no.
Come on!
Hello.
Police.
Come on, man!
What? What is this thing? What is it?
Ten minutes?
What happens in ten minutes?
-It goes off.
-No. No!
-The key.
-Wait, wait. No. You can't do that.
Hey! Wait!
Minty, where are you?
I've got this...
This thing around my neck.
This metal thing. I think it's a bomb.
- Minty, calm down.
- I can't calm down.
-I've got this thing around my neck!
-Relax.
We lost you at 10 Cory Road.
-We turned on Brandon Street.
-Where?
-I think, then... Then, uh...
-Brandon?
All right. Okay, okay.
I know where he is.
Benny... Benny!
Benny!
-Miss Halliday.
-God, where are you?
Um, tip line got a call
from a consultant psychiatrist,
a Dr Vivien Lake.
She's worried about one
of the patients, "escalating risk."
Okay, do you like him for it?
I dunno. It sounds interesting.
-Well, excellent, bring her in.
-I know, I've already sent a car.
Good. Okay, as soon as I can,
I'll be back.
Yeah.
What's he doing up, by the way?
- Minty!
- I'm in here.
-You better be alone.
-Yeah, yeah, I'm alone. Come on, man!
Come on. Go, go, go.
All right, let's have a look.
-Go, go, go, go. Oh, God.
-Just shut up. Just shut up.
- Shh.
- Come on, man!
-I can't help you, man.
-What? No.
Wait, wait, wait. There's a key.
He threw the key over there.
-Where?
-Over there in the corner.
Benny, you have a quick look.
Come on. Come on, man.
-Come on!
-Just relax.
All right.
-Come on.
-I don't think I can open this.
Yeah, man, you can do it.
-I'm not gonna be able to...
-Yes, you can do it.
No lock's unpickable.
-This might be. It's pick-resistant.
-What does that mean?
It means I can't pick it, Minty, relax.
Of course, you can open it.
Of course you can.
That's not the attitude. Pick it.
Get the job done.
-Come on!
-Benny, how are you looking?
I swear to God, I can't see it.
-In the corner!
-What corner?
Corner, corner, corner... Hurry up!
Hurry up.
Oh, my God. Oh, come on, man.
Come on!
- Relax, okay? Just relax.
- All right!
Benny?
What's that? What does that look mean?
What's that look?
What does that look mean?
-Benny?
-Yeah.
-You should go.
-Come on, come on, come on!
- Start moving!
- Find the key!
-Find the key!
-Oh, I've got it.
Look, he's got it. He's got it.
-Come on!
-Go, go. Right there.
Open it, open it. Unlock it.
Come on, come on.
Yes, yes!
All right. Come on.
In there!
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Errol.
I'll make sure you're looked after
until this is all put to bed, all right?
It won't be put to bed, though, will it?
You've opened up a can of...
Not worms. I don't know, geese.
I'll sort it.
-I promise.
-Yeah. Yeah, you do that.
Because everyone knows
you do magic, yeah?
Yeah, you run.
I'll find you.
I'll get you.
Dr Lake, I'm DCI Luther.
-Did they offer you tea, coffee?
-Yeah, they have. Thanks.
Um...
You wanted to bring one of your patients
to our attention.
James Hauser, yeah.
So, what can you tell us?
He's a very troubled man.
Dealing with a number
of intersecting paraphilias,
he was the victim of profound
and systematic childhood abuse.
Unspeakable abuse, really.
And to avoid any doubt,
um, paraphilia means...
Sexual fetishes,
abnormal sexual impulses.
-The nature of his...
-Impulses?
Piquerism.
From the French piguer, "to prick."
At the age of 13, he stabbed a classmate
in the buttocks with a school compass,
and experienced his first orgasm.
-Classmate, female?
-Male.
He attended boarding school,
but there were female victims
during his student days,
and later, sex workers
of both sexes and genders.
He paid to stab them in the buttocks,
thighs, particularly the area
around the navel.
- Using a...
- Usually the point of a scalpel.
Just the tip.
There isn't a person in the world
without a sexual secret. DS...
Uh, Halliday.
You know, we all have a fantasy.
We all have a fetish.
We all regret something we've done.
Something we never had
the courage to do.
So, what's changed? Why come in today?
His condition's been escalating.
He hasn't made
his last couple of appointments.
And last night, he turned up
at my house uninvited.
He...
- There was blood on him.
- His blood?
I presumed so, at first, yes.
Self mutilation isn't uncommon in people
struggling with extreme desire. But...
I went to wash his wounds.
There were no wounds.
I asked him to wait in the lounge
while I went into my office to call
the police to take him to a safe place.
Before I could place the call,
he'd gone.
He's not answering his phone or e-mails,
so I decided to seek the advice
of a colleague and come forward.
As his fantasies became more extreme,
he became too ashamed
to articulate them.
So, I asked
if he could draw them for me.
Freeze. Nobody move.
Stop the bus!
Cheers.
We think it's him.
The driver tried to intervene.
We're going after him with full force.
We've got aerial units,
ground units, dogs.
We've got his house, his workplace,
all of his usual haunts
under surveillance.
-Are you...
-Yeah, I'm fine.
You're not fine. Nobody is.
No, I'm fine.
Well, good. He's not going home, is he?
I mean, not now.
It's not gonna stop. Not after this.
Not until we stop him.
So, what next?
Now, we play dirty.
The psychiatrist.
Did she seem normal to you?
I don't know. I guess
she came across a bit intense,
a bit too invested in her patient.
Well, she did come forward
with his name.
Yeah, but reluctantly.
‘Cause I think she had to.
I don't know how deep it goes,
but I don't think we're looking
at a normal doctor-patient relationship.
Well, it does happen sometimes
between patients and their therapists,
they call it countertransference.
It can get intense.
Ah, good.
Whatever psycho-sexual thing
they got going on, we can exploit it.
- Wait. Can we do that?
- Within parameters.
Okay. Bring her in. Push her buttons.
See what pops up.
Have you done this before?
Yeah. Well, something like this.
And you're definitely okay with it?
Like, ethically?
I don't know about ethically,
but as long as it's legal,
I'm okay with it.
Okay.
Dr Lake, we're sorry
to have to do this to you,
but we urgently need to know
the whereabouts of your patient,
and we believe you might be able
to help us with that.
Has he been in contact with you
since we last spoke?
No.
And do you have any idea
where he might be,
-where he might go to hide?
-Well, I'm hardly his keeper.
Uh, no. No. But you do have
a responsibility to him.
Which I believe I exercised
by coming forward.
Boss.
James Houser's phone's just come on.
He's in Hampstead woods.
This is Schenk.
Get a CO19 to Hampstead woods
and have them take up position.
And what about
your responsibility to his victims?
Well, I'd imagine it's "alleged victims"
at this stage, isn't it?
Okay. Why don't you just show her?
Well, this really is a tawdry form
of manipulation, isn't it?
Frankly, I expected better.
Dr Lake, look...
You know him.
I care about his well-being, yeah,
but I have
no emotional attachment to him.
- Which is a good thing.
- Why?
I don't think he's gonna stop
until we kill him.
Oh, dear God, how clear can I be? Look.
I'm happy to give you any information
that might help in protecting
the lives of others, but...
It's your job to actually catch him.
I cannot, and I will not
help you do that.
That girl on the bus
was 23 years old.
Now, I could tell you
exactly what he did to her,
before he slit the bus driver's throat
and ran away,
but I don't wanna hear myself
saying those things.
Do you understand that?
I don't wanna hear myself
saying the things
that your patient did in there.
Well, look, I'm happy to suggest
a good therapist, if that's any help.
And what if we were to arrest you?
-On what grounds?
-Obstructing justice.
Okay, um...
Call me if you change your mind.
Come on.
Oh, God. So, it turns out I'm not fine.
All right, look,
she's not gonna help voluntarily, okay?
She's good and spooked on his behalf,
you guys listening in?
7am,
and you're bang on the money.
He's talking to her right now.
- From where?
- Hampstead Woods.
Seventy acres of open woodland.
Multiple points of ingress and egress.
If he gives us the slip there,
we'll never find him again, John,
so we need her to lead us to him.
Yeah, I know, she's good and primed.
She thinks she's saving him
from the filth.
She could be right.
James, remember,
you can control this.
You have to think ahead.
You have to think of the consequences.
-I don't think I can stop.
-Yes, you can.
You can.
You need to remember what we discussed.
You need to remember your strategies.
You didn't call me
because you were aroused,
you called me because you know
you shouldn't be putting yourself
in this situation.
You need to remember
what we talked about.
Can you come here?
Can you do that?
Now?
James, if you don't let me help you,
they're going to hurt you.
And I couldn't bear that, so, please.
Let me come to you.
I'll hide you.
I'll keep you safe.
Please.
Hampstead Wood.
She's leaving.
And the CO19 are in position.
- Stay with her.
- Two minutes away.
You want him dead?
I don't care. I just want him.
She's entering the woods
just south of the basketball court.
James?
Come with me, please.
You can hurt me, if you like.
All units.
On my signal.
I'd like you to cut me.
- I didn't. I wouldn't. I wouldn't.
- No!
James! Don't do it.
Go, go!
James!
Oh, my God.
God, he's cut his own throat.
God. Jesus Christ.
Look at me. Look at me.
I'll call it in.
You followed me.
Yeah.
And asking for my help, what was that?
Manipulation? Gameplay?
Yeah.
You have no idea what he endured,
what was done to him.
He was a good man.
Pig. Filth.
Take her away, please. Get a statement.
Oh.
Who do we have here?
Wow.
You didn't have to cut me.
Are you listening to me?
Look what you did to my arm.
That is the last time
I humiliate myself for you.
Okay?
That is the last time you ever hurt me.
James better be dead.
Catherine?
It's way past time you went home.
Yeah. No, yeah. Sorry.
Is everything all right?
It's just... Something's wrong.
It's not right.
Have you discussed this with DCI Luther?
Well, I've tried calling him
over and over,
but he's not answering, so...
-How convinced are you?
-Nine out of ten.
Eight.
No, nine. Yeah, nine.
Then let's go and see him together.
Okay.
Luther. He knew. He must have known.
All right, all right.
Wotcha.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::