Shit.
Ooh, John, it's getting late.
I need to get my kip.
I do hope you're not playing for time.
Oh, I, er...
I'd leave Alastair to sleep for a while.
The poor thing's quite exhausted.
Yeah, I'll bet he is.
Cheeky.
Good night, chaps.
Alice.
What have you done?
Guess.
- Why?
- Why do you think?
We were out from under it.
We were clear.
And now?
Come with me.
I don't think
I'm going to do that, John.
No.
Oh... Come here!
Oh, God, you...
So you like it like this?
You just have to say... Oh, ow!
Oh!
# Love is like a sin, my love
# For the ones
that feel it the most
# Look at her
with her eyes like a flame
# She will love you like a fly
# Will never love you again #
Shush, now.
Still awake?
Barely.
I'm too tired.
Come on.
Listen.
Look,
I know what you went through yesterday.
And I know it was my fault.
Won't happen again.
I worry about you, that's all.
I want you to be safe.
I am.
I just get carried away.
It's like, er...
Do you remember
the hitchhiker in Australia?
Little Miss Birkenstock.
That was something we did together,
according to the rules, far from home,
on holiday.
We did it spontaneously,
spur of the moment.
-Yeah, but we discussed it.
-Briefly.
But it was still within the parameters
of our agreement, Jeremy.
If that still means anything to you...
Of course, it does.
Because the balance of risk has shifted.
You're being too reckless.
I need you to understand that.
To really understand it.
The risk to me, to my life,
to my career,
my liberty.
I do.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Are we there yet, John?
Are we there yet? Are we there yet?
Oh, you have to be kidding.
So I take it I'm being arrested.
Because you do remember how many crimes
we've committed together?
Is that a threat?
Absolutely.
Okay.
I'll be watching you.
Just be here when I get back.
Wait, wait, wait.
My wig is making my scalp itch.
Would you please remove it for me?
Please?
Stay there.
Looks like your mate's come through,
old sausage.
All right,
meet me at Milton Arches
in 45.
Once she's in my care, I'll make a call.
Your old pal here is free to go.
Alice, whatever you're doing
in there, stop it.
It itches.
No, listen.
Stay still and wait.
Yes, okay.
Address is...
Freedom.
Shit!
Hold still.
Yeah.
Come on.
Hop in, John.
-So who's Person X?
-What?
I'm tired, what does that mean?
Well, I was handcuffed in the back seat
with an itchy wig and nothing to do
except chew things over,
and it occurred to me
that George Cornelius
must know you well enough
to be acquainted with your weaknesses.
-Which are what?
-Other people.
So if I were him, what would I do?
I'd say, "Bring me Alice Morgan,
"or I will do something absolutely
dastardly to Person X."
Am I warm?
-Toasty.
-Mmm.
And you actually considered doing it,
didn't you?
-Yeah.
-Giving me to him.
Oh, yeah.
But you couldn't go through with it.
-No.
-Why not?
You know why not.
Then say it.
Fine, then. Super.
Where are we going now?
Darling?
Darling.
Darling, are you awake?
I don't know how else to say it.
We have guns.
It's not gonna happen.
You do know they won't be so generous?
They'll kill you as soon
as they look at you.
And you are very nice.
Alice, I don't care who gets hurt.
All right? Knock yourself out,
break legs, but no one dies.
I really don't see
why it matters.
-I know you don't, but it still does.
-Fine.
Where's the key? Ha!
Come on.
Please.
Emergency.
What service do you require?
Oh, good evening.
A concerned citizen
has absolutely insisted
that I let you know about a fire
at the Lock N' Roller storage
on the Wolcott Road.
Cheerio.
Come on, my pretty.
Come here, my pretty.
That's it. One.
Two.
Move!
Drop it.
Drop it!
Benny comes with me.
What?
Fucking what?
What are you doing?
Minding my own business.
Oh, dear God above.
- Halliday?
- Morning, boss!
-I've been trying to get a hold of you.
-I bet you have.
-Excuse me?
-Mmm-hmm.
- Do you mind?
- Sorry?
No, not you. Sorry, listen,
I've had a bear of a morning.
Erm, I've been thinking,
whose head was Jeremy Lake looking at
on the MRI scan? It feels wrong.
Great minds! I'm on my way
- to find out now.
- How?
It's not enough for a warrant.
Er, no worries, erm,
I don't need one.
Well, don't do anything stupid.
Well, no promises,
but I was actually aiming
for the opposite of stupid, so...
All right, you let me know.
Oh, will you keep your phone on?
Yeah, no,
I'll call back as soon as I can.
Now, listen, can you
cover for me?
Okay, bye.
Oh, my God, she's chirpy.
Must be insufferable.
We need to lay low until this is sorted.
Where we can go that's safe?
Nowhere where Cornelius
can be watching us,
which rules out your place or my place.
And Alice's.
Jeremy Lake's office.
Hello, can I speak
with Dr Lake, please?
I'm afraid Mr Lake's
not yet in the office.
I'm sorry, could you just hold the line
for a moment?
Hi. Sorry, sorry.
I think I left my glasses
in here yesterday.
They're roundish and tortoise shell.
Well, Mr Lake would usually
give them to me. He didn't say anything.
Oh, right.
It's just that I'm pretty sure
I had them when I went in there.
Do you think I could just have
quick squizz around
and I won't break anything.
Fine. Please try not to.
Thank you.
- Hello, Mr Lake's office.
- Dr Lake, please?
It's a matter of urgency.
Okay.
Would you mind calling back?
- Ah!
- How'd you get on?
I can't find them.
Such a shame. Thank you.
Okay.
So you brought the devil
around for breakfast.
Mark, I need a favour.
Who did you say these belong to?
It belongs
to a person of interest.
Which doesn't quite
answer the question, does it?
It doesn't really, does it?
What did you think of the cake?
Well, whoever it belongs to is very ill.
-How ill?
-Look.
I'd need to confirm it, of course,
but this here...
-Uh-huh?
-...looks to me
like a frontal lobe tumour.
Okay.
And what are the symptoms of that?
Hello, I'm Jeremy.
What are you going to do to me?
What do you think?
Why?
Because I like it.
It's basically all I've ever thought
about since I was about yea big.
Jeremy.
Oh, that's terribly good.
I just dangle my name
and you swim along and snatch it up.
I expect you're trying
to humanise yourself.
You'll be telling me
about your husband next.
Your mum and dad,
maybe the babies you want to have.
I've got money.
I can get you money.
No, you can't.
I don't need money.
What I need right now
is to head off to work.
And all day,
as I'm slicing into people...
No, don't. Please, don't.
- I'll be thinking about...
- Don't say that.
I'll be thinking about
what I want you to do for me.
Do you want to know what that is?
-Hmm?
-No.
I don't know. Don't do this, please.
There's a phenomenon
known as Stockholm syndrome.
I expect you've heard of it in a meme
or something.
So in the spirit of scientific inquiry,
I'm going to keep you down here
until you fall in love with me.
Er, what?
I know it sounds difficult
to believe at first blush,
but it will happen.
And in the end...
What? No.
When you've learned
not only to love me, but to adore me,
when you've cast aside all desire
ever to leave me,
that's when you get to leave.
When you no longer want to.
Right, off to work.
Oh, and one more thing.
My wife is very jealous.
Very possessive.
If she finds out
I've got, well, a mistress down here,
she'll strangle you
with your own ovaries.
So, quiet as a mouse, eh?
Errol, it's Benny.
Look, I know you're probably sleeping,
but I need you to lay low
till I get home.
Okay?
Make yourself at home.
Oh, you're very nice.
Er, do you have any bacon?
I've been a vegetarian
since I was 17.
Of course you have.
So the last I heard you were...
Well, quite,
but apparently only the good die young.
Well, then, congratulations.
You can expect to live forever.
Well, I'm certainly
gonna give it a whirl.
Mark, I'm really sorry
to do this to you.
My wife's at work.
You need to be done
by the time she gets back.
She won't even know we're here.
Just do what you need to do and move on.
Don't drink all the orange juice.
And don't get blood on the sofa.
Massey, stop by the gate.
You looking for business, darling?
You know, the last time
we had a chat like this off the record,
on the QT,
I swear you were wearing flares.
And you were wearing a sheepskin coat
and a pair of Foster Grants.
So what were you doing there, George,
mop-handed at a copper's house?
A police officer? One of your own.
Tell me. What did he do, rob a bank?
Possibly. I don't care.
Oh.
Well, you make me nostalgic
for the dead days,
Martin, time was you'd
have dragged me out of this motor
and beaten my tripes out
with a pickaxe handle.
As you say,
dead days.
Well, you tell that to your lad.
He's bent as a pin.
I met his lady friend.
God above.
Well, I can't answer
those questions, George,
without knowing precisely the nature
of your allegation.
And of the many crimes
I know you've committed
down the years, being a snitch
was never one of them.
Now, I don't know what's
going on between you and Luther,
but you need to stay away
from my officer, George.
Or I'll have you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Have you managed to get a hold of Errol?
No.
It's going to be okay.
There's no way Cornelius is sending
his boys to your flat.
And to be fair, that's easy
for you to say.
You haven't spent half the morning
spitting your teeth out.
Benny, I'm going to put this right.
Okay, I'm... I'm going to make it right
by you, mate.
How?
This isn't the militant wing
of the National Trust
we're dealing with here.
It's George Cornelius.
You don't go up against him.
You know, I always thought
she'd be the end of you.
I didn't think
she'd be the end of us all.
Yeah, well, Benny...
It's going to get worse.
A lot worse.
There's something Cornelius
doesn't know yet.
Shift's over, Donnie.
Go home and get some kip.
His Nibs all right up there?
Fine.
I haven't heard a peep since, er...
Since what?
The present.
The what?
The welcome-home present you asked for.
No.
George.
She was just...
I didn't know.
She just...
She just walked in.
Oh, Mr Lake.
The police were here again.
Mmm.
- Yes?
- Mr Palmer,
we spoke once before.
Just convenience, that's all.
What are you doing?
Work.
Can't avoid it. John.
What am I avoiding?
- Yes, Halliday, how'd you get on?
- Er, pretty good,
I think. Well, enough to be confident
that James Hauser
didn't kill anyone.
Er, boss?
-You there? Erm...
-Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I'm here. Go on.
Okay, so I was looking through
the file last night and I saw something.
Just a small thing, really,
but on the back of it
I got some analysis done.
A CCTV image of the killer
and one of James Hauser.
And they're stood next to what
turned out to be identical lampposts.
It's two men. Similar heights,
but not identical.
Well, yeah, that doesn't mean
Hauser wasn't good for any of it.
I had this thing once,
it was two brothers...
Er, I think
this is a whole different thing.
I was talking to Celia yesterday
at the autopsy,
and she was talking about
what it takes to slice your own throat
without hesitation. Now, yes,
James Hauser was into self-mutilation,
but with pins and needles.
He liked insertion.
But slicing your own throat
with a scalpel,
that's a whole different proposition.
Now, who uses a scalpel?
And who's in a position
to manipulate James,
to put him exactly
where they want him to be?
Now I think he was a patsy,
and I think they've set him up
to look responsible for the crimes
committed by Jeremy Lake.
And the MRI scan.
Now, I think Jeremy was looking
at his own head.
Because whoever it is has a non-operable
tumour on his frontal lobe.
And now, if it is him, it could
be affecting his... His behaviour,
his judgment, disinhibiting him.
DCI Luther?
Yeah.
John, we've got a missing person.
Penny Leyton.
Her partner came home from work
last night and declared her missing.
Yeah, the local police have accessed
some CCTV footage.
I'm sending it through to you now.
I'll meet you as the hospital.
All right. Yeah, I'm...
Yeah, I'm coming.
You have to be joking.
There's a woman missing.
So?
So I knew who took her.
- She's not your responsibility...
- She is my responsibility.
-We are.
-I knew, Alice.
I looked this prick in the eyes and I...
What, how? Did he forget to yawn?
-I let him go because I was...
-Of me?
Well, I'm flattered.
But I do hope you remember
that if it weren't for me,
you'd be dead or in prison.
Either way, you wouldn't be
galloping to anyone's rescue.
-I can't let this go. I just can't.
-You have to, John.
-George Cornelius is...
-I can handle George Cornelius.
No, you can't, John.
Not in the way you'd like to.
We're past that.
Oh.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
-DCI Luther.
-George.
I'm sorry it's come to this,
but we are where we are.
Now, you have two options,
you bring it back from the brink, or...
- Or what?
- I take you down.
I take you, your family, everything.
Brick by brick.
You'll be the king
of a smoking hill, mate.
-You understand?
-My son is dead, John.
I know.
I know and it shouldn't have happened,
but it did.
Now take a step back.
Don't make me go to war.
You should have lied,
arranged a meeting.
No.
No point lying to him.
He'd have known.
Confirm transfer.
Here you go.
I had to try.
I know.
But you're right.
It's too far gone.
-He won't stop now.
-No.
I have to end it.
Yes.
Now.
Just got to take care
of this other thing first.
-John, you can't...
-Take it, leave it. I don't care, Alice.
Tonight, then.
Tonight.
Do you know how?
I do know how.
-For what it's worth, I am sorry.
-No,
you're not.
Give this to Benny
and don't let Mark see it.
I'm not apologising for what's happened,
I'm regretting what's to come.
- Good morning, sleepyhead.
- I can't believe
you did that, after everything you said,
all your promises.
- Viv, I'm not sure what you mean.
- I mean
the bitch in the basement.
Viv, darling, er, sorry,
but things have taken a turn.
You have to get rid of it.
You have to do whatever you can
as quickly as possible to get rid of it.
I'll explain when I can.
DCI Luther, how lovely of you
to put in an appearance.
Sorry, boss, I've had a funny old day.
Jeremy Lake left before we arrived,
but his car is still here.
I should have nicked him
when I had the chance.
There were no grounds.
- I should have made grounds.
- So,
what made him run?
Sir, I was here earlier today.
Erm, yeah, maybe that spooked him.
You were here earlier?
Doing what?
Nothing, really.
Erm, I asked DS Halliday to interview
the secretary before
he came into work.
I mean, that couldn't have spooked him.
That was hours ago.
So why did he run?
What does he know
and how does he know it?
See, I don't think
that is the question
that's going to find him.
Then I'd like to know what is.
It's what she knows. Vivien Lake.
I don't think
that Vivien is his accomplice.
I think she cleans up for him
and she hates him for it.
So does that mean
Vivien doesn't know about Penny Leyton?
Let's find out.
It's okay.
Oh, God.
-Cheers.
-You're very welcome.
Hello, who's this?
Errol, it's Ben.
I'm just checking in.
- Did you not get my messages?
- Yeah.
I got the messages.
Where've you been?
My leg, mate.
Listen,
take whatever you want from the fridge,
don't scratch my records,
but whatever you do,
keep your head down, all right, brother?
No worries. You okay?
Yeah.
Tickety-boo.
Sweet.
Cheers then, Ben.
-Cheers.
So there's the number, okay?
It's a landline.
-Can I go now?
-In a moment.
Right now I need you to relax
for a few seconds, Errol.
Just a few seconds. We're nearly there.
I need you to trace a landline for me.
I'm sending the number now.
Okay, is that it?
Are we done?
That's it.
Vivien?
Nothing.
I'll put a trace on her phone.
I'll dig up CCTV
within a quarter-mile radius
and find out what time she left.
With an ANPR.
Boss.
Her car's still here.
Shut up!
-S
hut up! Shut up!
-No! I
Basement.
See if you can find a window,
or an open door or something.
I'm down here!
Listen.
I was trying to save you from him.
From Jeremy. Please, don't say anything.
Please.
Shh...
-I'm in here!
-Shut up!
Shut up!
Penny?
Penny!
Go!
Where is Jeremy?
Where is he? Vivien, where is he?
Boss.
She needs medical attention.
Come here.
It's okay. It's okay.
Come here. Stop. Stop. Give us a second.
Look. Look,
you still have a way out of this.
Okay, you got a very solid defence,
coercive control.
You... You led your life in fear
of him, okay? So,
Help me to find him.
I will help you, I promise you that.
I think you're in need
of psychiatric assistance, Officer.
Get her out of here. Go on.
We've put out an urgent appeal.
His face is all over the media.
We'll find him.
Not without her. Not in time.
- John?
- Ambulance.
Jeremy Lake.
He got away in an ambulance.
He must have. He must have.
Call the paramedic cruisers
and see where they dropped him off.
He must have done a ride-along.
Boss, I've got to take this. I'm sorry.
Mark, what's up?
John,
I need you to come back here.
Er, mate, I promise, as soon as I can,
I will, okay?
No, right now.
-I've got big problems, Mark.
-Well, I have a big problem here.
Yeah, what?
John, my girlfriend is on her way home,
I need you
to get your friends out of here.
Er, Mark, listen,
I'm at the office, okay?
Erm, can you...
I can't get out of that now.
Can I... Can I come back to you
on this?
When is that?
I don't know, Mark.
Two, three hours?
No, that's no good, John.
Remember what
she told you. If she sees you and Alice
around here...
Oh, yeah, okay.
Erm,
I'm about to step
into an autopsy, all right?
Can you give me two hours?
Can you do that?
John.
Yeah?
Mark tried,
but he oversold the lies.
But at least this way
we know where we stand.
I have a message for you
-from Mr Cornelius.
-I think I've got the message.
Hmm. I'm going to need you here, John.
Why, so you can kill everyone?
Not everyone.
Just you and Alice.
Assuming you listen and do as I ask.
Er, he's lying, John. Er, oh...
Listen to me,
all right? I'll go to Cornelius.
I'll go to Cornelius right now.
I'll hand myself in, all right?
You can do what you want
to Alice, but you leave Benny
and Mark alone. Do you understand me?
John, I need you to focus.
You're not in control here.
This isn't a situation you can leverage.
Listen to me, you piece of shit!
If you hurt them, I swear to God
I will rip your fucking heart out.
Do you understand me?
I'm not here to listen.
This isn't a dialogue.
And now your friend is dead.
John.
Mark. Just stop.
Just stop right now.
Leave him be.
None of this is his fault.
Benny, right?
That's right.
You're killing yourself, Benny.
Benny? Benny? Don't you fuck...
Don't you
say another word, Benny.
Boss, I need you to kill
this prick for me.
No, Benny! Don't
-say another word, Benny.
-White.
- 6'1".
- Benny.
- Dark hair.
- No.
Brown eyes.
Muscular build...
Jesus!
Here. Now. No more chat.
You... All right, I'm coming,
I'm coming.
No!
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::