Previously on Dexter:
Who's the guy that dropped you off?
We didn't sleep together.
You are certainly allowed
to be a player.
You remember Cassie, right?
Yeah.
New neighbour. Hi.
Hi.
I kind of need to leave.
I'll take care of Jamie.
Maybe we could reschedule?
Yeah. I'd like that.
Any reason why you
haven't taken the exam?
I got your brother on my ass
about taking the sergeant's test--
What is so wrong about
bettering yourself?
You nailed it, bro.
Is he your choice for sergeant?
I'm ready for more responsibility.
I want you to strongly consider
making her sergeant.
I think you may be my father.
Family showing up out of nowhere?
A lot of times, they want something.
I you to do a background check
on someone.
You think she's here to rip you off?
I don't know.
Norma Rivera.
She'd been having an affair
with the boss, Ed Hamilton.
Dad, what's going on?
The Hamilton's son.
Did you go to where
Norma Rivera was killed?
I did.
What did you see in your analysis?
Leave the kid alone.
He killed her.
You don't know that.
Your only witness recanted.
No reason to make enemies
unless we really have to.
Where's Yates?
So this is finally over.
My tormenter's dead.
Thanks to you, Dexter.
And Deb.
I'm glad you found your way
back to each other.
Well, the family that kills together...
A few days ago, everything seemed
hopeless between Deb and me.
But through Dr. Vogel,
I've got my sister back.
It's beautiful out here, Dexter.
I wanted to be with family.
Accidents happen,
shattering our sense of control,
if not our lives.
It's no accident
that Zach Hamilton is here.
He's drawn to blood, like me.
Did he kill Norma Rivera?
After a week of vetting him, I haven't
been able to find definitive proof.
But I'm sure if I keep following him
the truth will become clear.
Or it could get murkier.
Dexter.
Have you taken on
Zach Hamilton as a patient?
It's nice to see you too.
I have to protect you from another
murderer? How did he get to you?
His father contacted me
because of my reputation
for working with psychopaths.
He's concerned about his son's
behaviour, his propensity for violence.
It's more than a propensity.
I think Zach Hamilton
killed Norma Rivera.
And I take it that
you followed him here today
because you're planning
to kill him?
The thought had
crossed my mind, yes,
if I can find solid proof.
Well, then it would seem
that we have a conflict of interest.
I don't believe this.
You're going to work with another killer
after what happened with Yates?
Dexter, I appreciate your concern,
but I'm not going to talk about
Zach Hamilton with you any further.
It wouldn't be ethical.
Suddenly,
you're worried about ethics?
I know. I threw them out
the window when I met you
because my life was on the line.
Now the threat is over.
You're bringing another threat
into your life.
It's my work. What can I say?
I treat dangerous people.
It's a hazard of the job.
Besides, you have no proof
that Zach Hamilton
is guilty of anything.
I will.
If you do,
then come to see me first,
before you do anything,
and we'll have
another conversation.
Would you do me that favour?
We'll see.
Maybe this is why
she tracked me down, for money.
You don't know that.
I mean, maybe she genuinely
wanted to get to know you.
What, at the same time
her Hyundai's being repossessed?
Has she asked you for money?
No.
But she always seems
to be missing her purse
when the check comes.
I thought we had a real connection.
You like having Niki in your life?
I do.
Then why don't you wait it out
and see how it plays out?
In the meantime,
you can enjoy her company.
Okay.
Hm, heh.
Thanks, Deb.
Welcome.
Deb, got a new case.
Let me guess, someone suspects their
significant other is fucking around.
Yeah, but this one
is a bit different.
How?
Because the person is me
and the significant other
is my sister's ass-chasing,
shithead boyfriend.
Kevin Wyman, notorious player,
frequents a singles bar in a hotel
where he keeps a suite.
Have you tried talking to her?
Susan doesn't listen to me.
It'd just push her
more quickly into his arms.
So that's off the table.
Well, going behind her back
seems kind of fucked up.
It's gotta be this way.
I gotta catch this guy in the act.
Okay, but you're doing it
by yourself.
I need your help on this, Deb.
It'd be a lot less conspicuous
if we work this as a couple.
Well, I'm not sure if I'm comfortable.
Well, are you comfortable
getting a pay cheque?
Okay, boss.
Thank you.
Where does this piece go?
Right here.
Very good.
Dex?
Don't forget, my birthday picnic's
in a few days, okay?
On the beach, outside of Papa's.
Bring Harrison.
Yeah, we'll be there.
Great.
You know who else
will be there? Cassie.
I heard you have a date with her.
No, it's not a date.
I felt like I owed her one after we both
bailed on your dinner the other night.
Why won't you just admit
that you like her
and that I am an
awesome matchmaker?
I admit that you're an awesome nanny.
You'll have to settle for that.
We'll revisit this after the date.
Oh, by the way,
the TV remote has
been missing since yesterday.
I think somebody hid it
but I can't get anything
out of him.
Harrison, did you
take the TV remote?
No.
Do you know where it is?
He says he didn't take it.
Right.
Guess I'll just keep looking for it.
Homicide in Liberty City.
It looks like you're gonna have
to finish that puzzle on your own.
I'm doing all the work anyway.
Yeah, you are.
Bye.
Welcome to spatter-land.
Hope you brought extra string.
Never leave home without it.
Good news.
We have the victim's boyfriend
in custody.
A witness saw him
taking off from the scene,
and he forgot to change
his bloody socks.
Heh. God bless stupid killers.
Once again, drawn to blood.
Looks like Zach has just given me
the in I need.
Zach Hamilton, right?
You were at my house.
That's right.
You guys find out
who killed Norma?
No luck. It's a dead end.
You like to shoot crime scenes?
Yeah, I got a police scanner
app on my phone.
Better than playing video games.
You ever been on the other side
of the yellow tape?
Nope.
This is as close as I've gotten.
Well, come on.
Are you serious?
Yeah, just don't touch anything.
Whoa.
This is amazing.
I remember that feeling.
Awe, wonder.
It only fed the urge.
Hey, can I take some pictures?
It's usually against protocol,
but what the hell? Go ahead.
Cool. Thanks.
So, what happened to her?
She was stabbed.
Yeah, obviously.
But, like, you know, how?
If I open up to him,
maybe he'll open up to me.
Come on. I can handle it.
Well, the victim
tried to defend herself.
There were defensive
wounds on her body
but you can also tell by these
big, round drops on the ground.
And this multiple cast-off spatter
suggests that she was
stabbed several times.
And the arterial spurting here
indicates that the killer
severed her carotid artery
with the first stab.
You can tell all that
just by looking at the blood?
Pretty much.
Awesome.
So I heard you caught
the guy who did it.
Yeah, her boyfriend.
How?
He was sloppy.
Left a bloody print and DNA.
He was spotted
driving away from the scene.
Oh, yeah? What kind of car?
Must have heard his Porsche
was seen at Norma's apartment.
No one noticed.
So the killer,
he should've worn gloves
and long sleeves,
made sure
he was covered up.
He's making this a teaching moment.
Well, yeah, if he was smart.
The kid's a quick study,
but that doesn't prove
he killed Norma Rivera.
So, hey, I gotta get going,
but thanks.
Hey, why don't you give me a call
when you print those up?
I'd love to take a look.
Yeah.
Yeah, I guess I could do that.
Time to make another connection.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Thank you
for doing this with me.
When you own a food truck,
you have to scope out
the competition.
Plus I just really love to eat.
Yeah, no problem.
I wouldn't miss these peanut butter
and Nutella fries for anything.
Mm-hm.
So you're indulging me
in my favourite pastime.
What do you like to do for fun?
You know, normal stuff.
Like what?
Um...
Heh, heh.
I like spending time with my son.
I already know you're
a great dad. What else?
I love my job.
But that's work.
What are you passionate about?
I like to bowl.
You're passionate about bowling?
No. Heh.
Heh, heh.
Of course not.
I just do it for fun, once in a while.
What about your weekends
or your free time?
Oh, I have a boat.
Oh, I love to sail.
No, it's a motorboat.
Oh. You water-ski?
No.
Race?
Do you scuba dive?
No.
Heh, heh.
What do you do on your boat?
I just...
Take it out and...
Turn around and come back.
That's it?
That's all I can tell you.
I think we may need
some alcohol.
Right.
Dating is harder than I remember.
Oh, this guy is fucking pathetic.
I get that you hate the guy,
but looking isn't cheating.
It's a slow night.
Give him a minute.
So you said Susan
doesn't listen.
Does that mean you all
have a strained relationship?
Not from my end, no.
But from hers?
Yeah, you know, probably.
I mean, look, I couldn't wait
to get away from my old man,
and Susan was just a kid.
You know, I should have
at least picked up the phone.
But I never did,
you know, so...
Well, you can't undo the past.
And families fuck you up.
That's just the way it is.
I can stop Susan from
fucking up her future.
I can do that.
It looks like he's
packing it in for the night.
If you wanna catch this guy,
why don't I set him up?
We can see if he takes the bait.
No, I don't want you doing that.
I worked Vice. I've done
worse than that before.
I just need pictures
of him hitting on you.
Certainly nothing
more than that.
Are you sure?
I mean, I could marry him,
maybe pop out a couple of babies.
Let's go.
Dexter, thanks for coming.
Sure.
Couldn't wait to show you
these photos.
Yeah, no problem.
It's on my way to work.
Doughnut?
Fucking A.
Mm.
Well?
He treats the blood
like a swimsuit model.
Well,
very colourful.
You know, a lot of photographers
like to mute down their reds.
You know,
find it too distracting,
but I like to ride the saturation.
Hm.
You think I overdid it?
No way. These are you.
That's the important thing.
Well, I can work you up
some prints, if you want.
I wouldn't have them
if it weren't for you.
Actually, I think I have
plenty of my own.
Right.
Of course.
I forget it was a crime scene.
Keep thinking that dead chick
spilled all that blood just for me.
Who's she?
Uh, it's nothing.
Just a lens test.
New 300 millimetre.
Fucking monster.
Wow.
Excuse me.
Yep?
Jesus, you still drunk from last night
or are you starting a new bender?
Yeah, okay. Yeah, I said okay.
Uh, I gotta go.
Anything wrong?
It's fine. I just gotta go.
Sure, some other time then.
I'll have to find another way
to get to him.
Ah, lieutenant.
Tell me something.
Did you decide
you don't need a sergeant?
Sir?
I expected an announcement by now.
What's going on?
To tell you the truth, I'm having trouble
narrowing down my choice.
I know you want me to pick Miller,
and on paper, I can't argue with that.
Scored higher on the test,
got the experience, the record--
She's African-American,
a woman.
Here's the thing,
Quinn has his attributes too.
Name one.
He's street-smart.
Look, I know what's going on here.
What do you mean?
You want me to be the bad guy.
You want me to insist
that you promote Miller.
That way you can tell Quinn,
"I had no choice."
I'm not sure that's--
You're lieutenant now.
Time to grow a set of balls.
I wanna hear something
by the end of the day.
Just like old times, huh?
You, me, steak, beer.
Yeah, it's been a while.
So how are things?
Good, great. You?
Fine. Better.
Good. I'm glad.
Me too.
I think these are done.
Well, how's work?
Uh, crazy.
Elway wants to catch his sister's
boyfriend fucking around on her,
so I offered myself as bait
so he'd get it done.
What--? You did what?
I used to do it
all the time in Vice.
Yeah, and you hated it.
Why put yourself
in that position again?
Because he's my boss.
And because I can only take
one control freak at a time.
Sorry.
This is tough.
A little.
Not exactly worth living for.
What?
You said that once
when you tasted one of my steaks,
that it was worth living for.
For some reason,
I've always remembered that.
It'll get easier, Dex.
We're just getting
back in the saddle, you know?
Yeah, I think we might be
eating a saddle.
Are you still seeing Dr. Vogel?
Yeah, it's too bad for me
there's no magic pill to cure PTSD.
Well, as long as she's helping you.
Like, she knows everything
about our lives because of Dad,
but I know jack shit about her.
Where'd she get
that fucking accent?
And who the fuck is Rich?
Her husband.
She was married?
When I first looked into her,
I found out some stuff
about her background,
and she was married
to a Dr. Richard Vogel.
Huh.
Okay, so Harrison's asleep.
And look what I found under his bed.
Ooh, someone's in trouble.
He lied about it.
At least now we know why.
I hope it's under warranty,
or I'll be stuck with whatever's on
PBS Kids for the foreseeable future.
I'll talk to him.
Okay.
Enjoy your dinner, guys.
Bye.
Should I be worried
that Harrison's lying?
He's 4, doofus.
Right.
This steak tastes like asshole.
Yeah.
Let's order pizza.
With pineapple, please.
Not on my half.
Sorry, cow.
What's up?
I'm promoting Miller to sergeant.
Say that again?
I'm giving Miller the job. I'm sorry.
I just think she's
the most qualified candidate.
Are you fucking kidding me?
I mean, after all the quizzes,
and the speeches
about bettering my life?
You actually made me want this,
and now you're gonna take it away.
Why, because I didn't solve
the Rivera case?
No, of course not.
It's just a lot of other stuff
I can't ignore, man.
The Nadia thing,
shooting Novikov.
You know what? Fuck it.
You did what you thought was right.
Leave it at that.
Hey.
I need everything you got
on the Norma Rivera case,
anything that points
to Zach Hamilton.
Uh, well, forensically,
there's not much.
There's nothing, actually.
Fuck it. I'll just tail the little prick 24/7
until I get what I need.
If Quinn's stalking Zach, how can I?
Won't even know I'm there
till I bust him.
You mind if I come along?
You want to come along?
Things are slow here.
I'm going a little stir-crazy.
Maybe you could use
another set of eyes?
Sure.
I mean, you think
Miller's clean? Come on.
You dig deep enough
on anyone in this department
and you know what you find?
What?
The shit.
It's there. I mean, we all got it.
I know you know
what I'm talking about.
Yeah, I can't argue with that.
We've all got the shit.
Yeah.
Big difference is some people
get away with theirs
and some people don't.
You're a good detective.
It'll work out.
Yeah, I'm just worried about
how Jamie's going to take it.
I think she was all excited
about me moving up in the world,
making something out of my life.
She'll probably break up
with my ass now.
Jesus Christ, how many pictures
of fucking women in tights
does this pervert need?
Apparently, a lot.
How's Deb doing?
I've been worried about her.
She's good. She's much better.
You guys work out
whatever your issue was?
What do you mean?
I mean, you guys have
been connected at the hip
for most of your lives.
All of a sudden, you're not talking,
you don't see each other.
Somebody shit
in somebody's Cheerios.
Yeah.
Just typical brother and sister stuff.
It's no big deal.
Something had her fucked up.
How weird was it that
she confessed to killing LaGuerta?
I should have stayed in my office.
What was that about?
That's the woman in the photo
that Zach didn't want me to see.
And he isn't looking at the class,
he's looking at her.
You know what I'm saying?
Fortunately, Quinn isn't.
Well, people do weird stuff
when they're under a lot of stress.
We may never know
what that was all about.
All right, see you guys later.
Looks like they're done.
- So is our guy
.
Buckle up.
Hey.
Wow. Okay. Uh...
What?
You look incredible.
Good job.
Well, that's the point.
Don't look so fucking surprised.
Didn't leave me a lot of places
to put the transmitter.
Are you bitching? I'm the one
helping you, remember?
I just don't wanna touch
anything I'm not supposed to.
Here.
Thank you.
Mic?
There you go.
I'm not looking.
Okay.
Okay?
Yep.
All right.
Quickly
,
just say something for me.
You blush like a little girl.
Heh, heh. Okay, just...
Just get him alone.
That's all I need, okay?
Okay.
Thank you.
I'm really glad we met.
Me too.
You know, I didn't know
if I mentioned it,
but tonight's kind of a celebration.
Yeah?
Closed a huge deal.
Two blocks downtown,
prime views of the bay.
It's gonna rent through the roof
and I get a big piece of it.
Something tells me you like
getting a big piece of everything.
Whenever I can manage.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I just wish I had a present for you.
What do you say we migrate
to my suite?
Got a nice little private bar.
It's a lot quieter than this place.
All done here.
You're gonna love the views.
It's beautiful.
Nice, light music.
It'll be real nice.
No, save it for the room.
What, you playing hard to get?
I don't kiss in public.
You're bashful.
Mm-hm. Maybe.
Get your fucking hands off of her!
Jesus, Elway.
The hell is going on?
She's wired, douche bag.
You're done.
You fucking son of a bitch.
You're gonna call Susan tonight.
Tell her it's over.
If you don't, she's getting an e-mail.
You got it?
Yeah, I got it.
Good.
You're an asshole.
The fuck are you thinking?
I'm sorry, all right? I just--
Seeing him paw all over you like that,
I don't like that shit.
I'm sorry about your top.
That's okay. It's all right. I got it.
Sofia Fuentes,
current place of employment:
the Cypress Harbour Yacht Club,
which is owned by Zach's family.
That's where Zach must have
first laid eyes on her.
If Zach takes pictures of his victims
before he's killed them,
chances are he likes
after photos as well.
If he did kill Norma Rivera,
then he's got the photos to prove it.
Sofia. Probably his next victim.
Now I just need to find
any photos of Norma Rivera.
Norma Rivera.
Taken seconds after she was killed,
the pool of blood around her head
growing from one image to the next.
Zach Hamilton,
murder weapon in hand.
All the proof I need.
You wanted proof. There it is.
Zach Hamilton killed Norma Rivera.
Yes. I know.
You know?
Mm.
Zach told me
during our first session.
But you didn't tell me
because of your sense of ethics?
Oh, forget ethics.
Why would I help facilitate the death
of someone I see potential in?
Potential? He's a killer.
He deserves to die.
Heh, heh.
Isn't that a little intolerant,
coming from you?
I don't kill innocent people.
But you might have,
if it hadn't been for Harry and me.
You could even
be on death row right now.
Right.
But you were spared.
Yeah, spared because of the code.
That's an interesting idea.
What do you mean?
What if we were
to teach Zach the code?
You can't be serious.
Why not?
It never occurred to me to try again,
because I didn't have Harry.
But now I have you.
Maybe it's time to see
if the experiment will work.
This isn't a science project.
No, but it's a matter of life and death.
Zach's life is on the line.
What possibly makes you think
Zach could be taught the code?
I told you, I see something in him.
And it worked with you.
Zach and I are nothing alike.
No, of course not.
You are definitely one of a kind.
He killed an innocent
and he's getting ready to do it again.
He needs to die.
Harrison.
I never intended to have a son,
but now he's the one thing in my life
that seems most right.
There she is!
Hi!
Yay! Aw. Mwah.
Happy birthday.
Aw, thanks, Dex. Thank you.
Can I go play?
Yeah, sure. Have fun.
Stay close, Harrison.
Yeah, I'm--
I'm not sure if he's a date
or just a friend.
I mean, what I do know
is that she's very attractive,
and men like her,
so if you want a chance,
you better move fast.
Right.
I think I'm gonna go grab a beer.
You know, this may sound weird,
and I don't mean
to sound creepy or anything,
but I think I really like you.
Aw, I like you too.
I'm not really ready
to call you "Dad,"
but you're cool.
"Cool"? Usually, I'm the only one
that calls me that.
So that's awesome.
Oh, hey. I got you something.
What?
It's really not a big deal.
It's not a big deal?
You're giving me $5000? Why?
Hey, I know
you could really use it.
But you should know that
that's really all that I can afford.
I don't understand.
How do you know that?
Well, you know,
I just did a little research on you.
You checked into me?
Like a criminal?
No, I just wanted to make sure
you were who you said you were.
And that I wasn't after you
for your money?
I just--
Look, I have debts,
but they're soon to be paid,
and that's not really
any of your business.
I wouldn't ask you for this.
I'm really sorry.
Do you understand that it was
hard for me to do this?
To find my father?
But I felt like it was worth it
to get to know you.
You know, maybe I was wrong.
Here you go. No, thank you.
Hey, Niki--
All right, everyone.
I'd like to make a toast.
To the best kid sister
a guy could ever have, Jamie.
Aw.
Aw. Thank you.
I love you.
Happy birthday.
I love you too.
Aw, thank you, guys.
Thank you so much for coming.
You guys are the best,
and it really is so nice
to have you all
here in one place together.
I love you guys. Cheers.
Happy birthday.
And here's to you, Sergeant Quinn.
I know it's premature--
Way premature.
You didn't tell her?
I didn't want to upset her
on her birthday.
No.
You didn't get the job?
You didn't give it to him?
I had to go with the person
best for the job.
And how is that not Joey?
Hey, it's okay.
He gave the promotion to Miller.
It's, you know...
But going for sergeant
was your idea in the first place.
You set him up.
I didn't mean to.
Jesus, Angel.
Hey.
Dexter, hi.
How are you?
I'm great. You?
Great. Nice party, huh?
Yeah.
The beach.
Yeah. Harrison looks like
he's having a really nice time.
Yep.
Uh, Dexter, this is Oliver.
Oliver, Dexter.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah, you too.
I didn't know if you wanted
the Belgian brown or the pilsner,
so I got you the one
with the moose on it.
Can't go wrong with a moose.
Heh, heh, heh.
I'm gonna go check on Harrison.
Okay, take care.
- Is that okay?
- Yeah, that's great.
- That's your neighbour, right?
- Yes.
What happened with Susan?
Wyman break up with her?
Yeah. Yeah, he did.
So it's a win.
Why do you look like someone
just ran over your dog?
I just got off the phone with her
and she couldn't stop crying.
She thinks it's all her fault,
like somehow, she's not
good enough or something.
Well, she would've caught him
cheating eventually.
The result
would have been the same.
Yeah, but it wouldn't be me
that made her cry.
Jesus, I just feel like shit.
People can't help
sticking their noses in
when it's someone
they care about.
I know.
I know. You tried to tell me.
So does that mean
you care about me?
Only to the extent
that you sign my pay cheque.
Touché.
Okay, what are we
gonna read tonight?
Let me guess, Wee Monkeys.
Wee Monkeys!
Before I read to you,
I gotta talk to you
about the TV remote.
You said you didn't take it,
but Jamie found it
under your bed.
I didn't mean to break it.
I was pretending
it was a Thunder Blaster
and I dropped it in the kitchen.
Well, yeah, that's okay.
Accidents happen.
But you lied to me.
That's a big deal.
We should never lie.
But, Daddy,
you lie.
What do you mean?
You told me Doggy got lost.
I saw you throw him in the trash.
I had to rescue him.
You're right. I lied.
Doggy got dirty,
and I tried to clean him up,
and when I couldn't,
I threw him away.
I'm sorry I lied to you, Harrison.
That's okay.
But can I keep him?
I really love him.
He's soaked in blood
that links me to a murder.
Yeah, but maybe
he should live under the bed.
Okay.
Wee Monkeys.
Wee Monkeys!
It's no accident,
Harrison catching me in a lie.
I can live with my lies,
but how long can Harrison
before he finally sees through?
I should be back
in a few hours.
Sorry to keep you late
on your birthday.
Trust me, it'll probably be
the highlight of my day.
Vogel doesn't want me to kill Zach,
but she's wrong about him.
He deserves nothing but my table.
He's here.
Hey, Zach, it's Dexter.
Where is he?
Why would Zach buy a car
for $1200?
Because the one mistake
he made with Norma Rivera
was showing up to kill her
in a red Porsche.
He's going to kill Sofia tonight.
Cypress Harbour Yacht Club.
Hi.
Could you tell me
if Sofia Fuentes is working tonight?
She gets off here in a few minutes.
Thank you.
Zach, waiting to make his move.
And Quinn,
still trying to prove he's a good cop.
Hey, Dex.
Hey.
Look, this is probably
none of my business,
but I feel like I should
tell you about Quinn.
Okay.
He thinks you're gonna
break up with him.
Break up with him? Why?
Because he didn't make sergeant.
That's crazy.
Why would he think that?
Maybe you should, um, invite him over.
I think he's feeling pretty down.
Yeah. Yeah, of course.
Thanks, Dex, for calling.
That really is so sweet of you.
Sure.
Quinn problem solved.
And there's Sofia.
Zach's father.
Sofia is Hamilton's mistress,
just like Norma before her.
What is he doing?
Hey.
I know what you're doing.
Quinn.
You playing detective?
Watching Zach?
Yeah, you caught me.
I'm going to see Jamie.
Keep an eye on Zach.
Jesus. What the fuck?
What are you doing?
Why were you going
to kill your father?
What? I wasn't trying to kill my--
I know you killed Norma Rivera.
I thought you were going to kill Sofia,
but you were going after your father.
Why?
You're crazy.
I didn't try and kill my father.
You tell me one more lie,
and I'll kill you.
I had to.
Why?
Because he's killing my mother.
She's drinking herself to death
because of him.
Over the years,
one affair after another,
and he doesn't
even try and hide it.
I thought killing Norma
would put an end to it,
but two days later,
he's banging some hostess
from the club.
I knew if I wanted it to stop,
I had to kill Dad.
So that's what this is all about,
you trying to protect your mother?
You actually care about her?
Of course I do. She's my mother.
But showing up at crime scenes,
accidents,
taking pictures of all the blood.
This is about more than
just your mother.
No, I had to protect her.
Yeah, I believe you.
But you killed because you want to kill.
No.
Yes.
To take a living person
and make them dead,
imagining that you can
actually hear the moment
when their heart stops beating,
smell the blood
as it pools across the floor.
I can't help it.
It just builds up inside me
all these years.
But Norma was the first time
I ever followed through.
And how was it,
once you'd killed her?
It felt like this huge weight
was lifted off my chest,
this release of something
horrible inside me.
Like you were finally in control.
Yes.
You should just
go ahead and kill me.
Why?
Because if you don't,
I know I'll do it again.
I don't want to be like this,
but I can't help it.
I just am.
I'm some kind of freak.
A monster.
Yes.
You haven't told anyone else
about this?
Besides Dr. Vogel.
No, I couldn't.
You never had a Harry.
A what?
Someone to talk to.
Someone to teach you.
Some things happen to us
by accident.
Others are choices.
There are parts of me that I can
never share with my own son.
But with Zach,
could I teach him?
Am I ready for this,
to be a spiritual father?
So how'd your sting go with Elway?
Terribly.
Didn't work out?
No, it worked out fine, but--
What?
He likes me.
Oh.
That's a bad thing?
Well, he likes me because he doesn't
know a fucking thing about me.
"Yeah, I killed two people
and tried to kill myself and my brother.
But, sorry, what kind of wine
would you like to order?"
I mean, what the fuck?
Yeah, I kind of know what you mean.
How are things with Cassie?
Um...
I don't think there's
much of a future there.
Maybe the Morgans just
aren't meant for relationships.
Yeah, maybe not.
But, hey, life is good.
I'm feeling optimistic
for the first time in a while.
I'm even thinking about
taking on a kind of...
Intern.
Hm...
Well, that's a big step for you, right?
Letting some novice
into your private lab.
Yeah.
Hey, are you okay?
I don't feel so good.
What's wrong?
I feel kind of dizzy.
Deb?
Hello, Dexter.
Remember me?