Previously on Dexter:
What did you do to Yates?
He has a scar exactly
where your killer has been
harvesting brain fragments.
High heels are
a far cry from brains.
It's not exactly
your killer's usual MO.
Albert wouldn't be
the first to alter his methods.
She's found herself a hero.
I know her. Janet Thorton.
Think the girl will be all right?
I stemmed the bleeding,
dropped her off in front of the ER.
Patient files. Your patient files.
Dexter, don't.
"Somehow he's deluded himself
into thinking
his feelings for his sister
are genuine."
You're trying
to keep me from Deb.
It's another way to isolate
your subject.
See what he'll do.
When Yates is dead,
you are out of my life.
You understand?
What about you?
What makes you crazy?
Family shit.
Nothing says family like shit.
I see a lot of your father in you.
Harry wrestled
with the same doubts
regarding Dexter.
The code is a theory.
What Dexter did--
What we did--
I don't think I can live with this.
Did Dad kill himself?
He OD'd on his heart medication.
He thought he'd created
a monster.
I think I know how he felt.
But he only got it half right.
Well, we're never
gonna get anywhere
unless one of you starts talking.
Okay.
Debra, it seems that you tried
to kill Dexter as well as yourself.
Yes, but then I saved him.
You saved me?
You only had to save me
because you tried to kill me.
I know, but--
You almost left my son an orphan.
Harrison.
Who's gonna take care of him?
Who?
I don't know.
All I've done my whole life
is try to take care of you,
to protect you.
Protect? Jesus Christ.
If this is your way of protecting me--
Okay, so I'm not perfect!
You think it's easy
being your brother?
You're not even listening to me.
You don't understand.
I've been trapped in a fucking fog--
No, I don't understand.
Haven't you heard
anything she said?
I'm stupid that way.
My brain is limited.
So when my sister tries to kill me,
for some reason, it doesn't make sense.
It's true, Dexter, what she said.
While in the throes of PTSD,
one's thinking becomes cloudy.
The weight of what
she has been through
has been too much for her to bear.
Debra has been in such a turmoil
that she sought out the first solution
that presented itself.
I had just found out that Dad
killed himself because of you.
Because of what you are.
I was fucking traumatised
by all this shit.
Yeah, so try to kill us both.
That solves everything.
You are overlooking an important part
of what happened, Dexter.
Yes, she tried to kill you,
the both of you.
And that was Debra
hitting rock bottom.
But ultimately, as she said,
she saved you.
And that was Debra's
first step toward recovery.
You should see that as
a promising sign for your sister.
Great.
I'm so fucking happy for you.
I was trying to catch a serial killer
before you tried to drown me.
I think I'm gonna get back to that.
Which, to you, is all I'm good for.
Don't, Dexter.
To hell with both of you.
Don't forget to write all this down.
I've never seen him so mad.
That wasn't just anger.
Fuck, it wasn't?
No.
Underneath all that is hurt.
Dexter is deeply hurt
by what you did.
Well, that makes two of us.
Family therapy. Who needs it?
Family. A burden.
They interfere.
They annoy.
Daddy, I wanna watch cartoons.
They interrupt.
You need to get ready for school.
I wanna watch cartoons.
School.
Yates could be anywhere now.
He could've left Miami.
Dexter, do you have
any plans for tonight?
Um...
Not sure.
Dexter Morgan.
Please leave a message.
It's me. Can we talk?
Fuck.
Harrison, apple or banana?
Banana.
I was thinking of having
Cassie over for dinner.
Okay, go ahead.
I mean here.
Why?
I think you'd hit it off.
Five minutes of cartoons.
No minutes of cartoons.
You need to get dressed.
So is that a yes?
Is what a yes?
Dinner tonight.
Two minutes of cartoons?
This is not a negotiation.
Now.
Eight o'clock?
Please, please, please?
Yeah, fine.
Harrison, last warning.
I gotta go.
Okay, bye.
This is one of the first days
I'm glad Deb isn't here.
I can lock myself in the lab,
don't have to listen
to anyone's voice but my own.
We gotta go
to the briefing room.
Now?
Now would be good.
Probably wondering
why I'm smiling.
I'm never wondering
why you're smiling.
I've just confirmed
that I have a daughter.
Someone let you impregnate them?
Made a donation
to a sperm bank 20 years ago.
You're not saying there's
a female version of you?
You met her. Niki.
The one you showed in.
That chick in your lab? No way.
Yes way.
That beautiful girl
came from you?
Yes, indeed.
Are you sure she's yours?
Who you talking to here?
She came in with the paperwork.
I pulled a piece of her hair.
I just finished testing it.
She's a Masuka,
through and through.
That poor sweet child.
So you and me, Dex,
both dads. How about that?
Great news, Vince.
You know, I'm sure it's all fine,
but just be careful, you know?
Family showing up like that,
out of nowhere?
Hey, what do you mean?
Sometimes it's just because
they want something, you know?
Money, a place to stay,
a fucking kidney.
Or they wanna kill you.
Lieutenant Batista is currently
with Janet Thorton,
the, uh, stabbing victim
who was dropped at the hospital.
She came to
and is ready
to make a statement.
She survived.
One less trophy for Yates.
So I'm running the briefing.
The Norma Rivera case.
The victim had sex with someone
before she was killed.
We're following the theory
that whoever she had sex with
is her killer.
Were you able to identify
anyone via the semen?
Uh, no matches in any
of the criminal databases.
Whoever had relations
with Ms. Rivera
has never been arrested.
ME's report showed
no defensive wounds?
Correct.
It's most likely not a rape.
She was probably friendly
with whoever killed her.
What about
the ex-boyfriend?
No, we ruled him out.
He's been locked up in Orlando
for the week on assault charge.
We questioned the staff
of Ms. Rivera's former employers.
They led us to believe
she'd been having an affair
with the boss, Ed Hamilton.
When we tried to speak to him,
he lawyered up immediately.
So we got a court order
to compel a DNA sample from him,
see if Hamilton was
Rivera's last visitor.
You think Hamilton killed Norma
to cover up their affair?
We're looking into it.
Old, rich men don't like
having their dirty laundry aired,
especially when it's the maid.
Dexter, I'm gonna need you to join me
and Miller in paying Hamilton a visit.
Janet Thorton gave us
the name of her abductor.
Albert Yates.
We got a home address.
I'm grabbing some unis now
and heading over there.
You won't find him home.
All right, let's get moving.
Lieutenant, got a minute?
Yeah.
You had Quinn run the briefing.
Yeah, how'd he do?
He was fine.
Really? Good.
Is he your choice
for sergeant?
I haven't yet
made that decision.
I used to run
the morning briefings
back in the Gang Unit.
I'm ready to take on
more responsibility.
Good to know. Thanks.
I just wanna make sure
you're aware
that the Hamiltons are
good friends to Miami Metro.
Sure.
Be respectful.
Any of Mr. Hamilton's
indiscretions
should take a back seat
to solving Ms. Rivera's murder.
I understand.
Good.
We're here for Mr. Hamilton.
Mr. Hamilton.
Mm-hm?
These police officers
are here to see you.
Thank you, Claudia.
My lawyer made it clear
I wouldn't be speaking to you.
You don't have to say a word.
We're just here for a cheek swab.
A what?
It's a DNA sample.
We have a warrant.
Failure to cooperate
will give us no choice
but to arrest you.
Why do you need DNA?
Ms. Rivera's autopsy revealed
she recently had sexual relations.
My forensics partner is here
to see if it was with you.
Wait, wait. There's no need for a test.
Norma and I were having an affair.
My wife found out
and insisted she be dismissed.
A scorned spouse. Was it the wife?
- So your wife knew?
- Just how upset was she?
No. My wife's been in Atlanta
visiting her sister
for the past two weeks.
Which is giving you time
to visit Ms. Rivera.
No. Yes.
I mean,
I didn't visit her.
She came by here
to pick up a few things
she left behind...
and one thing
led to another, and, uh...
we did have sex that day.
But she left here alive.
You, uh, didn't visit her apartment
later that day, did you?
I was here all day.
The Hamiltons' son.
Can anyone corroborate that?
Dad?
Dad, what's going on?
Go inside.
You want me to call someone?
I don't want anything. Go inside.
All right.
Sorry about that.
Where were we?
You were saying you have proof
that Ms. Rivera left the premises.
My security cameras.
You'll see Norma
arrive and leave
through the main gate,
alone.
I never, ever
would hurt Norma.
I loved her.
But does he love his son?
It's Deb.
Hello--
Damn it.
Hey.
So you're, like, what, the DNA guy?
I'm a forensic technician,
specialising in blood
spatter analysis.
Whoa.
So did you go to the place
where Norma Rivera was killed?
I did.
And what did you see in,
you know, your analysis?
She was beaten to death.
Confidential, huh?
Well, for what it's worth,
you're wasting your time
investigating my dad.
He's an asshole, but not a killer.
That's quite a testament.
In my family,
it's about as good as it gets.
One more happy family.
[CASS ELLIOT'S
"MAKE YOUR OWN KIND OF MUSIC"
PLAYING ON COMPUTER]
♪ Nobody can tell ya ♪
♪ There's only one song worth singin' ♪
♪ They may try and sell ya ♪
♪ 'Cause it hangs them up ♪
♪ To see someone like you ♪
♪ Make your own kind of music ♪♪
Try and get away, and I'll kill you.
You've reached Dr. Evelyn Vogel.
I'm not available at this time.
Please leave a message.
Dr. Vogel, it's Debra. I'm--
I need to talk to you, so...
I'm gonna come by.
Dr. Vogel?
Fuck.
Graves marked by rosebushes.
Yates' previous victims.
He liked to keep them close.
Three bodies so far.
A rosebush planted
on top of each.
You think there are three more?
Count on it.
The sick bastard turned his basement
into a torture room.
Yo, Dex, check this out.
All of his victims
have broken phalanges.
And it looks like the bones were
broken in sequence, not all at once.
Look. This bone here had
begun the process of mending.
So he kept them there
in that room for what, weeks?
Looks like it.
He broke each of their toes
until he was done, then--
Finished them off with
a single stab to the chest.
We think this was
one of his first victims.
We believe it's Kendall Jaynes,
been missing since 2008.
He buries the victims' purses
and IDs with the bodies.
And, get this, with each one,
the left shoe.
I mean, heh, I like feet,
but this is just cray-cray.
Deb. Looking to get
your old job back?
We could use you.
We have six bodies.
I need to talk to Dexter.
Dex.
Thanks. Deb, this isn't--
It's an emergency.
Vogel's been taken.
What do you mean?
I went to her house.
Someone had smashed the window.
She's gone.
Have you called her?
A fucking dozen times, no answer.
It's Yates. He's still in Miami.
I should've killed him already.
I wanna help.
No.
Dexter--
You tried helping, it didn't work out.
That was about killing.
This is about saving.
It's dangerous.
I fucking know it's dangerous.
Vogel's life is at stake.
You can hate me,
but can we just set that aside
until we know that she's okay?
I don't hate you.
Why'd you save me?
Why didn't you let me drown?
I saw the car going underwater.
I knew you were gonna die.
I couldn't imagine my life
without you in it.
So now what? Everything
just goes back to normal?
It was never normal.
I need to do this.
I really need to help.
We need to find Vogel.
We should bring
the police in on this.
They're already doing
everything they can
to find Yates.
This is his work log.
These are all the houses
he's worked in,
some of which might be empty
during the summer.
That's the perfect place
to go with a hostage.
That is a lot of places
to search, Dexter.
We need Metro's help.
They'll be helping us.
They just won't know it.
Just plot those places out on a map.
Don't do anything on your own.
You still don't trust me, do you?
I don't want you hurt.
So who's the guy?
What guy?
A.J., this is very serious,
what you're doing.
The guy who broke
into my house!
He's a friend of mine.
I don't like him in my house
going through my things.
No. I understand.
Good!
A.J., I think I know
what this is about.
It's your surgery.
You blame me.
What? This little thing? No!
I liked having my skull sawed open
and a chunk of my brain carved out.
Who wouldn't?
Well, you had a lesion
on the limbic area of your brain.
And I thought
it was causing your--
Your violent episodes.
I was only trying
to make you better.
Well, it worked really well,
didn't it?
You're a hell of a doctor!
I only wanted
what was best for you.
I still do.
That's why you sent your friend
after me.
I asked him to protect me.
I had no choice.
You should've just left me alone.
I will. I will.
You made your point.
There's no reason for us
to go any further.
If you do, you'll be caught
and you'll go to jail and--
Or worse.
My friend is looking for you.
Ah.
Good!
I can't wait till he finds me.
No, no!
The way I hear it,
the sergeant spot is going
to be between you and me.
That so?
Not gonna ruin our friendship
when one of us gets it
and the other doesn't?
I didn't know
we had a friendship.
Excuse me.
Miami Metro Homicide.
Don't worry, you're not in trouble.
What's your name?
Armando.
I'm Quinn. This is Detective Miller.
There was a murder here
a few days ago.
Take a look at this.
We were wondering
if you saw that man
around this time of day,
early afternoon?
Sí, I saw him.
Can you point him out to me?
Uh, this one.
Are you sure?
Yes. He drive a Porsche.
You don't see many
Porsches around here.
Would you be willing to give a statement
that that's the guy you saw?
I can come by later today.
Yeah, that's fine.
Here. Ask for me at the front desk.
Great.
Wanna get his information?
Hey.
Hey, what's up?
Just got an eyewitness to place
Zach Hamilton at Norma Rivera's
around the time of her killing.
The son?
I wasn't expecting that.
- Me neither
.
Hm. I'll let Matthews know.
He's been all over me
about this case.
All right, bye.
All right.
This is awkward, isn't it?
Heh, heh. Ahem.
Uh, why'd you decide
to look me up now?
Ahem.
Um...
Well, you know,
partly because I moved down here
from St. Augustine for school.
Oh. And what's the other part?
My mom passed recently.
So, um, it's just me now.
Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
Thanks.
And, uh, your mom
never married?
No, it was always
just the two of us.
So now that she's gone,
I guess I've been feeling
kind of alone.
Well, I'm glad
you reached out.
Me too.
What about you?
Are you still single?
Yep. Ahem.
Heh, where do you live?
Oh, I've got a house
down in Coconut Grove.
Fancy.
Are you, like, Mr. Rich-Guy?
Ha, ha.
Well, uh...
I bet you drive a Ferrari.
Masook, what can I get for you?
Hey, Marty, um, just a coffee for me.
And, uh, Niki?
Um, can I have
a double cappuccino
and a blueberry muffin?
And a veggie burrito to go, please.
I left my bag in the car.
I'm sorry. Can you get this one?
Yeah, no, no. Heh, heh.
I'll get the next one.
No problem, my treat.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Oh, hey, uh, can you add, um,
cheese to my burrito?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
Yates has installed cable and Internet
from one end of Miami to the other.
If I only look at homes he worked on
in the past two weeks,
it'll still take days to figure out
which homes are vacant.
If he's even in one of them.
And with Vogel being held by Yates,
doing what he does...
Batista should be done looking
into Yates' money trail.
Time to see if Miami Metro
can help me narrow this down.
Yeah, I'm on hold. Come in.
Just checking to see how
your end of the hunt's going.
Well, just got his credit history.
He hasn't used his charge cards
in the last three days,
so that trail is cold.
So he's using cash?
Yeah.
He's on the run.
He'd probably have to be
withdrawing his funds
from his bank or ATM.
I got a judge to expedite
a warrant on his accounts.
I'm on hold with the bank.
Thank you for holding.
Withdrawals were
in Morningside Park.
Would you like receipts?
That would be fine.
Thank you. Bye.
Thank you.
Good news?
Yates hit up an ATM
near Morningside Park
two times in the last couple of days.
He could be holed up in that area.
We'll get some unis out there.
If he shows his face, we'll get him.
Yeah, we'll get him.
No, it's a clusterfuck.
We had a witness place Zach
at the murder scene
within the time of her death.
We bring him in,
he can't remember anything.
Not unusual for a witness
to change his mind.
Someone paid him off.
Rich parents like Zach has,
it's not hard to put
two and two together.
Hm. You have any other witnesses
that put Zach at the scene?
No. I'll bring that kid in for questioning
and get a confession out of him.
Waste of time.
You have nothing to go on.
His lawyers won't let him say a word.
He killed her.
You don't know that.
Your only witness recanted.
You have no case.
Now, look, you find
something more concrete,
you'll have my full backing.
But until then,
leave the kid alone.
No reason to make enemies
unless we really have to,
especially when there are people
trying to move up to sergeant.
Capiche?
Yeah.
What exactly are we looking for
in the Morningside Park area?
We need to start figuring out
what kind of buildings these are.
Any apartments or condos
or businesses can be
scratched off the list.
And why are we...?
I can't.
I know, got it. Top-secret shit
between you and your brother.
Understood.
Look at that, a paying client.
I guess I should go and--
Oh, that's a friend of mine.
Good. Hope he needs a favour.
Masuka, what's up?
I pass by here all the time.
I figured I'd finally
see where you work.
This is it.
It's nice.
Yeah.
Can we go somewhere
more private to talk?
Sure.
Okay.
What's up?
I wanna hire you to do
a background check on someone.
You do background checks
all the time.
Why would you waste your money?
I know, right.
It's more of a personal situation.
Right. Who are we stalking?
Heh, heh, heh.
It's, uh, a family member.
Ooh, gotta be careful.
Don't always wanna know
everything about family.
Yeah, well, I really need this.
All right.
Give me a name.
Niki Walters.
Who is it? A cousin?
Daughter.
I know, right?
I donated sperm
back in college.
I've got a 20-year-old daughter.
She just showed up out of the blue.
Wow, that's fucking weird.
I mean, she seems
really nice, you know?
She's smart. She's pretty.
Seems normal.
But I keep asking myself,
"What's the catch?"
Maybe she just wants
to get to know you.
Maybe.
Or maybe she saw an easy mark
to hit up for money.
You really think
she's here to rip you off?
I don't know what to think.
I've got no family
except for my parents.
And they're off, retired,
living la vida loca in Tampa.
So it's just me.
And now Niki shows up.
I mean, I like the idea
of having a daughter,
family, right?
But if she's here
just for my money...
I'm sure it's fine.
And either way, it's--
It's really nice to have family.
Trust me.
You'll be discreet?
I don't want her to know
I'm looking into her like this.
She'll never know.
- Yes, please.
- Oh yeah
,.
Hey.
You want a beer?
You remember Cassie, right?
Cassie, yeah.
New neighbour, hi.
Yes, it's good to meet you again.
Jamie, can I talk to you for a sec?
Sure. Joey, keep stirring that.
What are they doing
in my apartment?
Did you forget we had plans?
Plans?
Dinner, remember?
Right.
I figured we'd make it
a double date.
Less awkward this way.
I'm gonna have to reschedule.
Excuse me just a sec.
Joey, keep stirring that.
I'm stirring it!
Dexter. You can't do this.
Do what?
I went out of my way
to set this up.
I made platanos fritos.
I planned this whole night for you.
I'm sorry, something came up.
No. No, you do this to me
all the time.
And I don't mind, I really don't.
But I invited Cassie and Joey.
You can't be rude to them.
Jamie, really, I have to go.
If you even try
to walk out that door,
Dexter, I will leave.
You'll be stuck here
with Harrison all night long.
Jamie--
This is for your own good.
You haven't gone out with anyone
since Hannah. Stay for dinner.
When we're done,
I'll stay with Harrison
so you can go do
whatever you have to do.
Serial killer bested
by 100-pound nanny.
Born and raised.
Dexter's lived in Miami
his whole life.
I'm gonna get some more wine.
Deb.
I've got 12 potential homes
Yates could be using as a hideout.
Shit. I've got seven.
That's a lot to cover.
Let's go.
I'll call you back in five minutes.
- So another S.
- Yeah to you
,.
Saving Private Ryan.
I love blunt things in my mouth.
Oh, jeez.
Excuse me.
Hey. Want some help
opening the wine?
Ah, actually, this is a little embarrassing,
but I kind of need to leave.
Oh, work? I get it.
When I worked in finance,
I was at it 24/7.
Yeah, 24/7.
But the thing is, Jamie's put
a lot of time into this whole thing.
Right, you don't wanna piss off
the nanny. Look, um, go.
I'll take care of Jamie. We'll be fine.
Maybe we could reschedule?
Yeah. I'd like that.
Perfect.
Okay.
I'm really sorry to be the party pooper
but I've got an early morning.
Mind if I call it a night?
Yeah, turns out
I have to take off too.
Thanks for watching Harrison.
I'm sorry.
I know you went to so much trouble.
What the fuck took you so long?
It's a long story.
We have 19 houses
we have to look into.
At night? Fuck me.
How are we even gonna see
if Vogel and Yates are in a house,
if they're even holed up
in one of these?
What if he's already killed her?
He hasn't. She's fine.
He keeps his women alive
for weeks. We'll find her.
Yeah, we will. We have to.
I'll pick you up in five minutes.
We'll find her.
Stay still.
Unless you want me
to restrain you.
You're not angry with me, A.J.
You're angry with her.
Shut up.
And you have every right to be.
Your mother abused you horribly,
beat you.
Probably caused the lesion.
Don't talk about her.
But I understand, A.J.
I understand the terror you felt.
She hit you, slapped you.
You'd find a safe place
under the bed.
And she'd look for you, raging.
And you'd curl up under there,
looking out, waiting.
She'd pace back and forth
in front of the bed.
Yes.
Shoes clacking.
Feel the panic rising.
The pain you knew awaited.
Hm.
Don't say another fucking word.
No, no.
Now, you can take the pain
and live a little longer
or you can stop struggling,
and I'll kill you right now.
Good.
So...
which little piggy
won't be making it to market?
Albert, stop it!
Don't call me that.
Only my mother called me that.
Stop that, Albert, now.
No.
Don't you talk back to me,
you little shit!
I'm not afraid of you.
All you ever do is disappoint me.
Enough!
Stay.
Don't know this number.
Not this house.
Morgan.
Here.
Let me help you with that cut.
You shouldn't call me Albert.
My name is A.J.
I'm sorry.
It's Vogel. She's alive.
What?
She is with Yates.
She called me.
She left her phone out
or something.
Oh, my God.
You're still bleeding.
It's local. You think Elway
can trace this?
I don't know. I can fucking ask him.
Let me take care of you.
Deb, what's up?
Look, I don't wanna
explain to you
why I can't go
through the police,
and I know it's illegal,
but I need you to trace
a number for me.
What's the number?
You're no different than Mom.
Yes, I am. I understand.
How long is this gonna take?
Fuck if I know.
What if he kills her?
I thought you said it takes
like a week for him--
I know what I said.
It's bullshit.
You're angry.
Let's not think like this.
You had a horrible childhood.
But you don't have to live your life...
Yeah?
One-five-seven Montgomery.
You're a fucking saint. Thank you.
You know where that is?
You shouldn't have hit me.
She hit him?
I was scared.
I can still help you.
You don't have to be angry at me.
You can't help me.
I can.
I understand
what you've been through.
No child should ever have to hide
under a bed from a parent.
You sought connection with her,
and all she gave you
was pain.
What-- What you do
for your women,
it's a search
for that same connection
that you never got
from your mother.
But what we have here now,
in this moment, you and I?
This is real human connection.
What you have with your victims,
that only pales in comparison.
Do you understand?
My poor, poor boy.
All you want is to belong, don't you?
I can help you.
I can, trust me.
Oh, what did you do?
I didn't.
Who did you call? Is this your friend?
Dexter, Dexter!
Yeah, you call him. Fuck you, Dexter!
Fuck.
You okay?
Yeah.
Oh, fucking Christ.
Are you all right?
Yeah, I think so.
Did he hurt you?
No.
No. Thank you. Thank you.
Where's Yates?
Let's get you out of here.
Then we can find Yates.
Debra, are you okay?
I'm good.
Really, I'm good.
Let's just get this cleaned up
and get out of here.
Brain cores.
I'll dump them
with Yates' body.
So this is finally over.
My tormentor is dead.
Thanks to you, Dexter.
And Deb.
Yes. And Deb.
I'm glad to see that the two of you
have managed
to find your way back to each other.
Well, the family that kills together...
You're doing well, Debra.
You're very resilient.
We'll see.
You are.
And you never
gave up on her.
I'm impressed.
I know Harry would be too.
He was always concerned
that, as you grew older,
you might drift apart.
Well, we never really
had a choice.
If anyone really knew us,
they would run screaming.
This is everything.
Okay.
So is this it?
A few days ago, everything seemed
hopeless between Deb and me.
But through Dr. Vogel and Yates,
I've got my sister back.
Not like things were before.
It's something different.
But for now, it's enough.
It's beautiful out here, Dexter.
I like it.
It's peaceful,
alone on the water.
Tonight, you brought us.
Yes. Why?
I wanted to be with family.