Previously on Dexter:
You can't kill me.
Why?
Because I don't fit Harry's code.
Trust me when I say that there's
a place in this world for your son.
You're perfect.
How can you still say that
when you know what I've done
to Deb?
I shot the wrong person
in that trailer.
Why did you save me?
Why didn't you let me drown?
I couldn't imagine my life
without you in it.
I'm glad that you have
managed to find your way
back to each other.
The family that kills together...
Zach's killer is related to you.
The Brain Surgeon is related to you.
Daniel.
He's going by the name Oliver Saxon.
What are you going to do?
What do you think?
He's my son.
I still have feelings for you.
No, I just--
Remember me?
Where do you think you'll go?
I haven't decided.
Argentina.
Me, you and Harrison
are gonna move to Argentina.
I've got a line on Hannah McKay,
but I'm gonna need help reeling her in.
He's onto you. Move fast.
I tried to get an earlier flight,
but it's booked solid.
I have a proposal.
We walk away.
You kill your mother in front of me,
and you just expect me to forget?
Evelyn?
This is usually
my favourite moment, the kill.
Now I don't even wanna be here.
Hey, Deb, change of plans.
Go get on a plane.
Last site someone visited
on this computer
was Aero Sudamerica.
I'm gonna tail the Morgans,
see if they'll lead me to her.
What the fuck is going on here?
Help me, please.
Unh!
Don't move.
I used to live my life at night,
in the shadow of my dark passenger.
But over the years, my eyes adjusted,
and I could see.
And now what's in focus is my future.
Bright. Brighter than it's ever been.
This is Detective Debra Morgan.
I've been shot.
Are we almost there?
It's, uh, Gate 209. Just a couple more.
I want some Oreos.
There'll be food on the plane.
Come on, you promised
to help me count.
Two hundred ten.
There you go.
I always thought if I ever left Miami,
I'd be running for my life,
not running towards a new one.
Two hundred and eleven.
Heh.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we'll begin boarding Flight 691
to Rio de Janeiro in a few moments.
We ask that you have your tickets
and passports ready for the attendant.
Where's Hannah?
Hannah?
Hey, where are you?
I'm at the gate. Where are you?
I'm in the ladies' room.
Elway is in the boarding area.
Come here, buddy.
Attention, passengers:
We will begin pre-boarding
for Aero Sudamerica Flight 691
to Rio de Janeiro.
He didn't see me. Did he see you?
I don't think so.
He's got a clear view of the Jetway.
He must have bought a ticket.
We won't be able to board
without being spotted.
And he's right between you
and the exit.
Dex, I just heard them.
Our plane is boarding right now.
Stay where you are. I'll call you back.
Okay.
Hey. You want some Oreos?
Yay!
Come on.
Why don't you grab something
for the flight?
Nothing too big.
Okay.
The storm is coming fast.
We'll now be boarding
all passengers in business class.
All passengers in business class,
please make your way toward the gate.
Hey, excuse me.
Hi. I have, uh, tickets on this flight.
I'm a forensic analyst, Miami Metro.
Yes?
I don't wanna tell you how
to do your job, but I just saw a guy
drop that bag under that chair
and then just walk away.
I thought he forgot it, but it really
looked like he left it there on purpose.
Did you see where he went?
Yeah, he's right over there,
on the phone.
I know it's probably nothing,
but like they say:
"If you see something,
say something."
Thanks.
Security, this is Casey
at Gate 21 1.
There's a Caucasian male
who just came in with a backpack...
Deputy marshal, it's Elway again.
I'm still at the airport.
I still think Hannah McKay's trying
to leave the country.
Call me as soon as you can.
Thank you.
Sir. Airport security.
Need you to come with us, please.
What? What happened?
Just gotta ask you a few questions.
What is this about? I'll miss my flight.
Sir, I need you to do what I ask.
This way.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
Hey.
Hey, the coast is clear.
Elway's gone.
Okay.
Due to a security concern...
Let's go see Hannah.
it is necessary at this time
for all passengers
to exit the boarding area...
Clear this area right now.
What did you do?
Put Elway on the no-fly list.
Unfortunately,
now we're not flying either.
Come on, bud.
All right, let's move her.
Stabbed in the heart. Pretty quick.
Unh.
His gun is missing too.
We can assume Saxon still has it.
I'm calling your brother.
No, he's leaving with Harrison.
If you tell him, he'll stay.
Deb--
I swear to God,
I'm not getting on that ambulance
if you call.
Okay.
Can I ride with you to the hospital?
No problem.
Do not argue with me.
I'm in the ambulance.
You're such a fucking asshole.
Yeah, he signed it.
I'll meet you at the hospital.
I'm right behind you.
Miami Central,
this is Rescue 6 for transport...
You're all right.
Hurts like a motherfucker.
Ohh...
You know, I really hate getting shot.
You need to stop that.
Unh.
I really thought that was it.
I thought I was gonna die, heh.
No. You're gonna live forever.
I thought maybe I was
getting what I deserved.
What you deserve?
Why would you think that?
I've done shit I'm not proud of.
Stuff I can't take back.
Think I haven't done shit
I'm not proud of?
No.
It's not the same.
I know.
You went through a bad time.
But I fucked up too, Deb. A lot.
But I think we get
to make up for it, you know?
How?
You do enough good in the world,
it sort of cancels out the bad.
I think I would need to save
a busload of nuns or something.
You're a good person.
A lot better than most.
Now that you're back on the force,
you're gonna have a million chances
to do good.
Maybe even save
that busload of nuns.
If they're like the ones
I had in school, let them go.
Come here.
Hey.
I'm gonna be right here, okay?
We both are.
Her vitals are stable.
Let's get her into surgery.
I love you, Joey.
What's that?
So?
She's on her way to surgery now.
She took one in the gut.
We don't know how bad it is yet.
Where's Dexter?
Deb asked us not to call him.
She what?
He's on a trip with Harrison.
She didn't wanna worry him.
But he's gotta know.
Damn right he's gotta know.
Due to a possible security concern,
we are evacuating the terminal.
It's Matthews.
Hello?
Dexter, Saxon escaped
after shooting Debra.
No. Well, thank you for telling me.
I'll be right there.
What's wrong?
It's Debra.
What?
Come on, bud.
Saxon shot her and got away.
Is she okay?
She's in the hospital
getting ready to go into surgery.
Is Aunt Deb sick?
Just a little.
But the doctors are
fixing her up right now.
You need to go to her.
I'll take you back to the hotel.
We should fly
into a different country.
They're only gonna
hold Elway so long.
He's gonna hit all the flights to Rio.
There may not be more flights.
I heard they were gonna close
the airport to wait out the storm.
Leave from another city.
See what you can find online.
What about you?
I'll join you when I can.
But--
Don't worry. We'll make this work.
One bag of ice
and one gallon of water.
- Can I get one more?
- Only one bag.
Hi, Jamie.
Hey, Harrison.
So tell me
all about your adventures...
How is she?
Still in surgery.
Yeah, we weren't able to speak
to the doctor before she went in.
Your sister's tough.
Just like your old man was.
Yeah, Dex.
She's gonna pull through.
Due to severe weather...
This is Deputy U.S. Marshal Clayton.
Please leave
your name and number.
Clayton, it's Elway. Again.
I don't know where you are,
but I'll tell you this:
McKay's still in town.
With the flights cancelled, I'm sure
she's looking for another way out.
I put the word out to my contacts,
and with what I pay these people,
if she walks through a hotel,
a car-rental agency, a bus,
I'm gonna hear about that shit.
All right. I'll try you at your field office,
see if I can get you there.
U.S. Marshals Service.
How may I direct your call?
Yeah, this is Jacob Elway.
I've been working
with Deputy Marshal Clayton.
I've been trying like hell--
I guess you haven't heard the news.
What?
Clayton was involved in a shooting.
I'm afraid he was killed
in the line of duty.
Why aren't you in Argentina?
Why do you think?
I told them not to call you.
Well, I'm glad they did.
How come we never went hiking
when we were kids?
Hiking?
Climbing...
mountains.
Hiking.
I don't know.
Because it's hard to find
a mountain in Florida?
There are mountains
in South America.
All over the place.
Why are you looking at me
like that?
Or is that just your face?
I should never have
left Saxon alive.
It's not your fault.
Clayton fucked everything up.
Bad luck.
No, it's more than that.
Ever since you found out
who I am...
I've screwed up your life, Deb.
It's not yours to screw up, Dexter.
I am responsible for my life.
Do you hear me?
I don't want you to feel guilty
about this.
about anything. You hear me?
You were meant to be happy,
so you need to go fucking be happy.
Okay.
Hello there.
Dr. Kruper.
Dexter. I'm Debra's brother.
Oh, nice to meet you.
Okay, I'm just gonna
check your stomach.
So how are you feeling
otherwise?
I wanna go hiking.
I wouldn't recommend that
for at least a few hours.
How is she?
That bullet bounced around
quite a bit.
But it missed
hitting anything important.
You are very lucky.
So she's gonna be all right?
There is a lot of recovery time ahead.
But I'd say we're looking pretty good.
I'm optimistic.
Thank you.
Mm-hm.
I bet Hannah loves Argentina.
Pretty blond, lots of attention.
Just her thing.
Hannah didn't make the flight.
Elway was there,
and we had to lose him.
That's my fault, Dex.
I put him on her.
That rat-face fuck.
I'm sorry.
No, don't start blaming yourself.
Coming from
Mr. "I screwed up your life, Deb."
I need to find another way
for Hannah to get out of the country.
I'm thinking of sending Harrison
with her now
and meeting up with them
after you get out
and Saxon is taken care of.
You heard the doctor. I'm fine.
You should go. We'll get Saxon.
No.
Dex, we'll get him.
Your life is waiting on you.
You should leave.
Deb...
The next word
I wanna hear you say is "goodbye."
Say it already, or I'll crawl out
of this bed and kick your fucking ass.
Goodbye.
I'll see you soon.
How's Aunt Deb? Can I see her?
Oh, she needs to rest.
But she's gonna come visit us
real soon.
Hey, did you know that this
is the hospital where you were born?
Really?
Yeah. Right down there.
It was the first time I saw you.
I was with Aunt Deb.
Holy fucking shit.
There's another Morgan now.
Yeah.
Congratulations.
You're a father.
Yeah, and you're an aunt.
Jesus.
Did you and Rita land
on a name yet?
Harrison.
Dad would love that. Harrison.
I wanna hold him.
Which one is yours?
I, um...
That's your son.
Do you wanna hold him?
Yeah, I wanna hold him.
He's sleeping.
Let him sleep.
He has his whole fucking life
to sleep.
He's so small.
Don't worry. He'll grow.
How does it feel to be a father?
I have no idea.
Heh.
Everything's gonna be different now.
I know.
Hey, thanks for your call.
No problem.
How's Debra?
The doctor's optimistic.
That's good to hear.
Dexter, if there's anything
I can do...
Well, I'm probably being paranoid,
but Saxon is still out there.
Think you could put a couple unis
on her room?
I'm already on it.
Thanks.
No problem.
Hey. Hey, I just heard about Deb.
What happened?
Uh, it's a long story.
I don't really have time to go into it.
In a hurry to get back
to Hannah McKay?
I don't know what you're talking about.
That's why Clayton was following Deb.
Figured she was helping you
and Hannah leave the country.
You're partially responsible
for his death.
Just stay away from me.
Storm's coming, buddy.
And it's gonna be real hard
to find a way out.
Don't go down with her,
Dexter.
Son of a bitch.
The National Hurricane Centre
is reporting
that Laura is now just east
of Cuba
with sustained winds
topping 100 miles per hour.
If it keeps on this current course,
it could hit the Keys by sundown.
Shh. It's okay.
Hurricane Laura shows
no signs of slowing down.
Hey. It's okay. It's okay.
Hey, we're closed.
Only reason I'm here
is to keep the animals calm to--
Stitch me up.
Okay.
Okay, I'll do whatever you need.
Miami's entire coast
is being evacuated,
so we can use the craziness to get
out of here without being spotted.
They're lining up evacuation buses.
The bus?
The highways are parking lots.
Buses have their own lanes.
We can take one all the way up
to Jacksonville and fly out from there.
We'd better leave for the bus station
soon if we're gonna make it on time.
What is it?
Nothing. It's a good plan.
You're still worried
about Deb, aren't you?
The doctor said
she's out of danger.
Hey, we can, uh...
We can stick around, you know,
ride out the storm here.
It's not safe with Elway on the hunt.
You need to get out of here,
the faster the better.
Well, I could leave now
and you could meet me there.
I could even take
Harrison with me.
Or I could, um, go alone.
I have no problem
with you taking Harrison.
I'd be happy to know
that he's with you.
It's that I don't wanna
lose you again.
Even if it's just
for a couple of days.
--as well as Cuba
and Grand Cayman Island.
We're staying with you through
the morning and into the night...
Hurry up.
Tropical Storm Laura
is picking up speed...
Almost finished.
One more stitch.
The storm is threatening the coast
sometime in the next few days,
according to
the National Hurricane Centre.
Many local residents are
already preparing for the storm.
As the storm comes in,
it's important that people stay
in their homes and off the highways.
There's going to be a lot of wind
and rain.
It's going to be over the next few...
Please.
Just go.
I won't say anything to anyone.
--for this special report about
one of Miami's finest, Debra Morgan.
That's her.
I'm here at Miami Central Hospital,
where a detective
with Miami Metro
is recovering from surgery
after having been shot.
We have learned that
a deputy marshal died on the scene.
The suspect, Oliver Saxon,
is still at large,
and may have carjacked
a blue pickup truck.
If you have any information about...
Get your car keys.
We're taking a drive.
Can't you just let me go?
Do what I said,
and you won't get hurt.
Mockingbird Bus 24
from Miami to Tallahassee...
All right, keep it moving.
No pushing.
WOMAN
Oh, no, it's okay.
Wait.
Come here.
All right, everyone,
please keep moving the line.
It's Saxon. He's still out there.
I can't leave until he's caught,
until Debra is safe.
I'm sorry.
You need to get back in line.
It's okay. I understand.
Here. Take Harrison.
I'll meet you down there.
You sure?
Yeah. He'll be safer with you.
Take this. It's just water,
snacks. A few essentials.
Call me from the airport
as soon as you know
that you made your flight.
I will.
No one will be allowed
to board without a ticket.
Harrison, you're gonna leave
with Hannah.
You're not coming with us?
No, of course I am.
I just forgot a few things
I need to take care of.
As soon as I do,
I'll meet you there, I promise.
I'm gonna miss you.
It's just for a little while.
It'll be fun.
We're all going to this cool place,
and you're gonna get there first, okay?
Now, I want you to mind Hannah.
You do what she says.
You know what, Daddy?
What?
I love Hannah.
So do I.
I'll see you in Buenos Aires.
We'll be waiting.
This is the final boarding call
for Mockingbird Bus 24 to Tallahassee.
Come on, Harrison.
I'll check on Deb,
and then I'll deal with Saxon.
This is the hospital.
I've done everything
you've asked.
I just wanna go home.
So this is it.
I promise,
I won't say a word to anyone.
No, I know.
We need a doctor over here!
Let me get that.
He's choking.
I need a suction canister.
Right away.
- Doctor?
- Jesus.
His tongue, it's been cut out.
Let's get him to the OR.
My God, why would anyone
cut his tongue out?
All eyes on the victim.
The perfect distraction.
Saxon.
In order to conserve power,
the south wing has been closed.
At this time, we ask all visitors
to make their way towards the exit
in the north wing.
All surgical staff are to report
to their current assignments.
Drop it.
We got this, Dex.
Quinn?
Dex, I...
Where's Deb?
I don't know. Something went wrong.
There was a problem,
and they rushed her to the ICU.
What happened?
They're working on her now. Um...
She stopped breathing.
Mr. Morgan, I'm afraid
I don't have good news.
There were complications.
What kind of complications?
We think a clot formed during surgery
that triggered a major stroke.
Debra's brain was deprived
of oxygen for a period of time.
What do you mean?
You said she was gonna be fine.
I had hoped so.
I'm very sorry.
Is she going to recover?
It's possible that
she could breathe on her own,
but she won't be able to eat
without a feeding tube,
and according to the brain scans,
she won't be able to think, reason,
or even know that you're there.
Now, we've intubated her,
and I've lowered
her body temperature
so that we can preserve
as much brain function
as possible.
You don't know Deb. She'll--
She'll pull through this.
You hear about
miracles all the time.
Well, that's just it, I'm afraid.
It would be a miracle.
I've never seen a miracle.
Hello, Harrison.
Wow.
He's so fucking small.
I'll have to watch what I say
around you, little man. Heh.
Don't you wanna
hold your son?
You won't break him.
Heh.
Okay.
Talk to him.
Hello, Harrison.
See? He knows you.
I don't know how to do this.
Just keep his head up.
No, I mean everything.
How to be a father,
how to take care of him.
You'll be great.
How do you know?
Because you've always
taken care of me.
I have?
Ever since we were little.
Don't you remember
the monsters?
Uh, no.
Every time Mom turned off the lights,
they'd be running all over the walls.
I couldn't fucking go to sleep.
I thought they were gonna
eat me or something.
I don't remember.
They were the shadows.
You came in and explained it
in your dorky little voice.
"Oh, it's just the absence
of light, Deb." Heh.
I don't even know
why I remember that, but I do.
And even then,
you stayed in my room
and slept on the floor by my bed.
You made me feel so fucking safe.
You were always taking care of me.
You're gonna be a great father,
because you've always been
a great big brother.
You really believe that?
With all my heart.
You were so wrong, Deb.
Tell me about Argentina.
Well, uh, they have their own
special kind of cowboys.
They're called gauchos.
Maybe you'll get to meet one.
You know what else they have?
Penguins.
I like penguins.
They're not just in a zoo.
They're wild ones,
kind of roaming around
because Argentina is close
to the South Pole,
which is where Santa Claus
has his summer home, and...
And because he's on vacation,
he's always in a good mood,
so he says yes to everything.
Who knew you'd be
so good with kids, huh?
How did you find me?
One of my contacts
finally came through.
Look, let's be civil about this, all right?
No need to upset Harrison.
All right, please take your seats.
We're pulling out now.
Next stop, Daytona.
So this is what's gonna happen.
We're gonna sit here quietly
until we get to Daytona.
Then we're gonna
very calmly get off the bus.
I'm gonna drive us
to the marshals field office,
turn you in and hand Harrison over
to Child Protective Services.
And I'm gonna collect
what's turning out to be
a very hard-earned reward.
Dex, we're gonna nail
this asshole to the wall,
I promise you.
For Deb.
Oliver Saxon.
Or would you prefer to be called
by your given name, Daniel Vogel?
You know, there are
several ways we can do this.
Given that we have footage
of you killing other people,
it would be in your best interest
to cooperate.
It's up to my lawyer
how cooperative I am.
Are you sure?
Because if you have any hope
of staying out of the electric chair,
you should
probably start talking.
Just fucking admit it.
You killed Cassie,
you killed Clayton,
and you shot Deb.
How did you hurt your arm?
This? It's just a scratch.
No.
Deb's a good shot.
Who's Deb?
Fuck you!
You fucking shot her!
And you left her there to die!
Just like you killed your mother
and left her to die,
you fucking piece of shit!
Quinn. Out.
I'd like to, uh, speak
to my attorney, please.
You know,
he was right about one thing.
You are a fucking piece of shit.
Batista and Quinn will be able
to make a case against Saxon.
I could leave now for Argentina
and let the state of Florida kill him.
Folks, we will be arriving
at the Daytona station momentarily.
After a short stop,
we will proceed on to Tallahassee.
Anyone making a connection
to Jacksonville
should disembark
and proceed to Boarding Bay 3.
Hey, hey.
I'm just getting some tea.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Do you want some?
How stupid do you think I am?
Here's what's gonna happen.
The horse tranquilliser
I just gave you is gonna
kick in in eight seconds.
You're gonna fall asleep
and wake up in Tallahassee
with a slight headache,
feeling humiliated and cranky.
Come on, sweetie.
It's time to go. Let's go.
Come on.
Hi. I'm here to do a GSR test
on Oliver Saxon?
Sign in, please.
Would you like an officer with you?
No, I'm good.
Okay. Hit this button if you need us.
Got it.
I wish I could blame you
for everything.
For what you did to my sister.
But I know it's all my fault.
Should have walked away.
You know, what you've actually done
is opened my eyes.
Forced me to look at myself.
And what do you see?
A trail of blood and body parts.
What a pretty picture.
In one sharp moment,
you took away
this foolish dream
that I could have a happy life.
Is that why you're here?
To tell me all this?
No, I'm here to kill you with that pen.
In here.
You all right?
He tried to kill me.
Dexter...
help me out here.
What were you doing with Saxon?
I went in to do a GSR test.
But you don't even work here anymore.
How are we gonna explain this?
I'm officially here
till the end of the week.
Okay, but why would you
personally do this test?
After what he did to Deb--
It's exactly because of what he did
to Deb that I went in there.
I wanted to make sure everything
was handled perfectly, by the book,
no mistakes.
And I wanted to look him in the eye.
Okay.
I get that.
It's obviously self-defence.
Yeah.
We got everything we need.
I'm glad he's dead.
I wish I could have done it myself.
You should go, Dex.
I know that you have
a lot to deal with.
Yes.
Hey.
I'm praying for her.
As much as I may have
pretended otherwise,
for so long, all I wanted
was to be like other people,
to feel what they felt.
But now that I do,
I just want it to stop.
Attention, all staff
and hospital personnel:
The National Hurricane Centre
estimates the current...
Just so you know, patients
in the south wing are being moved.
We have to consolidate
space and power.
--at 150 miles per hour.
It has been elevated to Category 3.
At this time, all staff must report
to their preassigned stations.
I would change everything
if I could.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
But I can't leave you like this.
I'm your big brother.
I love you, Deb.
Dexter.
Hey, where are you?
At the airport, about to board.
We're gonna make it.
That's great.
Where are you?
I'm still in Miami.
But I'm gonna be leaving soon.
I can't believe
this is actually gonna happen.
Once we get there,
we should start making our way south.
They have 3000 miles of coastline.
We can just keep going
until we find the perfect spot,
or maybe some penguins.
That sounds great.
I am so happy right now, Dex.
Me too.
Do you wanna talk to Harrison?
Please.
Okay, here.
Hi, Daddy.
Hi, Harrison.
I just wanna tell you one last time
that I love you.
I love you too.
I want you to remember that
every single day until I see you again.
Daddy loves you.
Okay. Bye.
I destroy everyone I love.
And I can't let that happen to Hannah,
to Harrison.
I have to protect them from me.
Good morning, Miami.
Hurricane Laura has passed.
Everything is going back to normal.
There is no longer any threat.
Hurricane Laura is slowly dissipating
over the Atlantic.
The majority of destruction
is along the harbour.
There have been some reports...
The cleanup has begun
as the city returns to normal,
with Coast Guard teams going
as far north as Daytona Beach...
Cutter 6, go ahead
and turn to your 1 o'clock.
There's something there.
I can't make it out.
We're stopping in five seconds.
- Okay, I think we got a visual.
- Copy that.
Turning northwest.
We've surveyed the wreckage.
There doesn't appear
to be any survivors.
We're heading back.
Batista.
This is the U.S. Coast Guard.
We just wanted to call and report
the wreckage of Dexter Morgan's boat.
Dexter?
Hey, how about we go
get some ice cream, yeah?
Okay.
Yeah. Come on.