Previously on Dexter:
I should be focused on
who bludgeoned Cassie and why.
But instead, since Hannah came back
into my orbit, she's all I can think about.
Have you seen that kid
around Cassie?
I don't know him. I'm sorry.
Joey, my friend was murdered.
Once I catch the killer, you won't
have to be scared anymore.
If Deb were asking you to stay,
you wouldn't put up a fight.
She'd want to catch
the killer as bad as I do.
Sorry I'm not Deb.
I think Hannah McKay
is back in Miami.
Are you interested?
Very.
What are you doing here?
I came here for her.
Who the fuck are you?
I don't wanna know. I don't want
to know anything else ever.
She's your problem now.
I can't go to jail, Hannah.
Lose my kids again? I couldn't take it.
We've always stuck together.
That's not gonna change now,
is it?
I found your blood
underneath Cassie's fingernails.
Zach had nothing to do
with Cassie's murder.
How did my blood end up there?
Your plane leaves at 8:00.
Twenty-seven minutes later,
you'll land in Nassau.
From there,
where you go is up to you.
Where do you think you'll go?
I haven't decided.
Argentina?
Every contact leaves a trace.
But the changes,
they're never what we anticipate.
I believe Hannah McKay
was just in Miami under
the alias of Maggie Castner.
Stay with me.
I just want to stay here with you.
I know, but you can't.
Dexter, I'm so sorry about Zach.
I know how much he meant to you.
I need to see Dr. Vogel
and figure out our next move.
You should stay here,
inside, out of view.
I have to see Arlene
this afternoon after her shift.
Why?
It's not safe for me to draw money
out of Maggie Castner's
account anymore.
The only money I have is what I've been
sending away to Arlene to hold for me.
And I'm gonna need that money
to start a new life.
Okay.
"Be careful." I know.
Actually, I was gonna say,
"I love you."
I love you too.
Poor child.
I'm gonna have to find a way
to let the family know.
Just give me a little time
before Miami Metro
gets brought in.
I will.
This is the song that was playing
when I found Zach's body.
[MAMA CASS ELLIOT'S "MAKE YOUR
OWN KIND OF MUSIC" PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
Do you know it?
Of course.
I used to play it all the time.
Still do.
Does it mean anything?
It was just a pleasant song.
Possibly my patients
heard me playing it.
♪ They may try and tell ya ♪♪
There are some signs of a struggle.
They fought here.
This table is out of place.
But whoever did this cleaned up
after himself. There's no blood.
I wish I could understand
what this is all about.
Why he's doing this.
I mean, it's clearly not simply
to frighten me.
He's trying to send a message.
But what is it?
I don't care what his message is.
He killed Zach.
He broke into my apartment
and dumped his body there.
What if Harrison
had been home?
I will find who did this,
and I will kill him.
I'm sure you will, Dexter.
But you need to remain focused.
I am focused.
Blood. He missed it.
And a few hairs pulled out
by the roots.
There's a big fingerprint
in the middle of it all.
Zach's, most likely.
Almost like
it was put there deliberately.
Zach learned from me.
He knew the importance of DNA. It's
possible that he ripped these hairs
from whoever attacked him
and stuck them there for me to find.
If this is a clue, as you said,
then Zach acted with
extraordinary calm, rational thought.
Yes.
Something I'm not sure
you're doing right now,
Dexter.
What?
Your desire to avenge Zach's death,
that's an emotional response,
possibly fuelled by having
to say goodbye to Hannah.
I didn't say goodbye to her.
How do you mean?
We're going to make a life together.
Dexter, how?
I don't know. We'll figure it out.
Over the time I've spent with you,
I've come to realise
that you're not
the perfect psychopath
I thought you were.
You have a depth of emotion
I never thought possible.
It's true.
I'll find the Brain Surgeon
and I'll kill him.
But once I do, I'm gonna focus
on a life with Hannah.
I think you misunderstood my point.
Straddling two worlds as you are,
it's dangerous.
Killers cannot have
a full emotional life.
I think you underestimate me.
So this is Maggie Castner's
passport photo.
That's Hannah McKay's.
I won't ask how you got those.
Good. Please don't.
They look pretty much
the same.
Have you had contact?
I have not.
Her boat left for St. Kitt's yesterday,
but I don't think she was on it.
What makes you think that?
Just a hunch.
A lot of good that does me.
Her husband?
Supposedly in New York City,
but no record of his jet landing
or taking off from here. Don't know.
All right, then. I'll look into this.
There's one more thing.
I'd actually like to be
a part of the team on this.
Heh. Thanks, but the marshal service
doesn't take on partners.
I understand--
If I do find her,
you'll get your reward money.
Fair enough.
All right.
Deb.
Hey.
I saw you from my car
and I had this moment
where it was just like old times.
Tell me you're here to see me.
Quinn, actually.
I meant what I said the other day.
We'd love you to come back with us.
I don't think Matthews would go for it.
He was pissed that I left so abruptly.
You never know, Deb.
I'll leave you two be.
Thanks for coming.
I need to ask you for a favour.
Yeah. Anything.
I think I know who Cassie's killer is,
but Matthews asked me to lay off.
The guy's from this rich family.
Could you look into him for me?
Sure. This all you have?
Yup. His info.
Social, address,
his name's Zach Hamilton.
Kid's a serial killer
in the making.
I think Cassie's
the second person he killed.
Yeah, I'll get right on it.
I'm gonna go say hello to Dexter.
The sooner I can identify Zach's killer,
the sooner I can be done with all this
and get back to Hannah.
You can't go in there. Sorry.
Who the fuck are you?
Hey, hey, hold it.
Deb, uh,
this is my daughter, Niki.
Niki, this is former lieutenant
Debra Morgan.
Oh, shit. Sorry.
My dad says you're a total rock star.
Why'd you leave?
She's a curious one.
Let's go see some files over here.
Nice to meet you!
What the fuck are you doing
with Zach Hamilton?
Quinn called.
He thinks Zach killed Cassie.
I thought so too,
but I checked it out.
Zach didn't.
What was Zach doing
with you and Hannah in the Keys?
Serial killers convention?
I was helping Dr. Vogel out.
I don't know why I even
ask you these questions.
No one else knows.
Zach's dead.
Now I know.
I don't want to know, because now
I have to explain how I know.
Kind of, yes.
I was thinking
about coming back here.
About being a detective again,
doing something good for a change.
But...
It'll just lead me into another
fucked up situation, won't it?
A familial match...
to Dr. Evelyn Vogel?
What?
The hairs we found in Zach's studio.
I ran a mitochondrial DNA match on
them. It tests a person's mother line.
Yeah, I'm aware of those tests.
Well, it's a direct match to you.
Zach's killer is related to you.
The Brain Surgeon is related to you.
How is that possible?
I have no family.
Well, not anymore.
Anymore.
Well, I was married
and I had two sons.
Daniel and Richard.
And now?
They're gone.
What happened to them?
One day, I found Richard,
he was my youngest,
at the bottom
of our swimming pool, dead.
At first I thought it was
an accident.
He wasn't a strong swimmer.
But then I realised the truth.
My older son, Daniel...
he...
He killed Richard.
Yes.
Daniel was--
Daniel was highly intelligent.
But he was also very troubled.
No, it was much more than that.
He was devoid of empathy,
had a complete lack of fear
or the sense of right and wrong.
He was a psychopath.
Realising this and wanting to...
find a way to help Daniel
led me into this field.
I failed Daniel. I...
I was never able to treat him.
Maybe that's one reason
I was so determined to help you.
This is Daniel.
My husband and I covered up
his involvement in Richard's death.
Said it was an accident
and then we put Daniel
into a mental health institute.
He was only 14.
Here in Miami?
No.
No, I sent him back to England.
Three years later, he was dead.
How?
A fire broke out in the wing
where Daniel was living.
Some idiot nurse had left
the door locked to take
a coffee break.
The children couldn't get out.
Seven of them perished.
One of them was Daniel.
Did you see the body?
No. My husband did.
He was horribly burned.
If it was his body.
That's preposterous, Dexter.
He can't be alive.
You said yourself
he's highly intelligent.
Could've faked his death.
But after all these years,
why would he do
these terrible things now?
The brain cores.
Do they mean anything to you?
Well...
Well, even as a child, Daniel was
aware that he lacked empathy
and how I felt about it.
It's possible he boxed some up...
and left it at my door.
Daniel Vogel would be in his mid-40s.
Anybody. Nobody.
That guy Cassie was dating.
He was interviewed that night.
Oliver Saxon.
Is it possible this is Vogel's son?
Daniel Vogel is Oliver Saxon.
You created half a dozen fake IDs.
He could've done the same.
The easiest way is to assume
the identity of a dead person.
Oliver Saxon,
death certificate.
The guy's a fake. Doesn't mean
he's your brain surgeon.
I need to get a DNA sample
from him.
Dexter, this is
Deputy Marshal Clayton.
He's here on a tip that
Hannah McKay is back in Miami.
Uh, sorry if I don't
seem glad to meet you,
this is kind of a shock.
I guess you haven't talked to her.
Why would I?
I told him that you dated Hannah
before you turned her in
for the Sal Price murders.
Wasn't the smoothest breakup.
I guess not.
And that makes you a target.
Frankly, the Hannah McKay I knew
would be too smart to risk
coming back to Miami.
Could be. Look, I got no
definite information she's here.
I'm just following up on a tip.
But until we know for sure,
we should put unis
on you till this plays out.
That's the last thing I need
trying to help Hannah hide.
On the other hand, the Brain Surgeon's
still out there. He knows where I live.
I don't need unis to watch me,
just my apartment
and my son when he goes to school.
Don't worry,
we'll watch Harrison like a hawk.
Deputy Marshal Clayton,
how do you plan to find Hannah
even if she is here?
Getting her picture out
with local media, asking anyone
to call if they spot her.
Okay.
But if by some chance she decides
you two need to talk things over,
be sure and give me a call,
won't you?
Of course. I want her behind bars
as much as you do.
Okay.
This is exactly
what Vogel warned you about.
Trying to straddle both worlds.
You should be following up
on Saxon right now.
Let Hannah handle her own problems.
I can do both.
Hey.
Have you gone to see Arlene yet?
No, I was just about to leave.
Don't. I just had
a federal marshal in my office.
They know you're here.
Oh, God.
You can't go to Arlene's. Lay low.
I can't start a new life
without that money.
I can give you money.
Half a million dollars?
Well, no.
I'll drive you.
I'm not letting you go by yourself.
Okay, but hurry.
This marshal changes everything.
We can never be together here.
I know.
What are we gonna do?
Let's get your money,
figure it out later.
You were right, the hotel manager
in Key West positively ID'd Zach.
He was down there
when she was killed. Where do
you get your information?
I have my sources.
Wish I had your sources.
Thought I had this one nailed.
Well, you're at square one. You've
been there before. You'll close it.
Just after the whole
sergeant dick dance, you know,
I got something to prove.
You're a good cop.
You don't have to prove anything.
Then there's Jamie, you know,
I'd kind of like to solve it for her.
She was really close to Cassie.
Yeah.
I just haven't
been there for her lately.
I thought she moved in.
I mean, like, emotionally.
Heh. Since when are you Mr. Sensitive?
Fuck you.
It pours right out of you.
You know, she's always accusing me
of comparing you to her.
Oh. Um...
Well, I mean, I can't really
advise you on that.
Puts me in an awkward position.
Why?
Because of our history, asshole.
I mean, history is history, right?
Jamie knew Cassie
better than anyone.
Question her again
.
Maybe something'll turn up.
She's been a wreck, it's hard walking
the line between boyfriend and cop.
I'll talk to her.
Really?
Yeah. Be fun to play cop again.
That'd be great. Thanks.
You can buy me lunch.
And two fucking desserts.
Nice place.
Found that when you're a fugitive,
asking somebody to hold half
a million dollars, incentives help.
So Arlene gets a cut?
She gets what she needs
to keep the kids off welfare,
I get--
The bank of Arlene.
Exactly.
Hey, babe.
Hey, Arlene.
Huh.
You're the asshole who turned her in.
That would be me.
Long story.
Can we come in?
Yeah.
So now we're
back together, huh?
How's that gonna work out?
We're figuring it out.
I told the kids
there's snakes in here
so they wouldn't go near it.
There you go.
Ah, shit.
Who's that?
Federal marshal.
Stay here. I'll handle this.
You answer the door.
Come with me.
Like you've got nothing
to hide.
Can I help you?
I'm Deputy Marshal Clayton.
You mind if I ask you
a few questions?
- Uh, Yeah.
- Yeah.
Dexter Morgan.
What are you doing here?
Arlene's a friend.
We met through Hannah.
Really now?
Yeah, I stopped by
to tell her what you said,
Hannah might be in Miami.
Yeah, I gotta keep
an extra eye on the kids.
Looks like you recently
changed your address.
Seems like a step up.
Better school district.
Says here you work part-time
waiting tables at Denny's.
That's right.
That won't buy you a doll's house,
let alone pay rent on this.
You sure
you haven't gotten help
from Hannah McKay,
who just happened
to have married a man worth
over half a billion dollars?
Didn't even know she was married.
Says here you got a record.
Do you have any idea
how many years
aiding and abetting a fugitive buys?
I'm the one who's been...
helping out Arlene.
Heh. Now I see what you two
really bonded over.
You sure can pick them.
Listen, do me a favour.
Either of you hear from
your old friend, Hannah McKay,
you give me a call.
Of course.
Yeah, we will.
Hey, Deb. Dexter's not here.
I know, I was driving by.
Wanted to say hello
to the little man.
Oh.
Look, Aunt Deb, I can write my name.
That's awesome.
I am so sorry about Cassie.
You doing okay working here
and everything?
Honestly, no. Not really.
The cops are watching
the place, which helps.
She have a lot of friends?
Yeah. She's pretty popular.
Everyone's just in shock,
you know? Especially Oliver.
Who's that?
This guy Cassie was dating.
Were they dating for a long time?
Just a couple weeks.
I guess it was love at first sight.
At least for him.
What do you mean "for him"?
Between us,
I think Cassie was gonna
break it off with Oliver.
Then he was all,
"Let's go to the Bahamas for a week."
After two weeks of dating?
He kept pushing her into it.
He wouldn't take "no" for an answer.
You weren't a fan, I take it.
I thought he could be
a little clingy.
But he was great to Cassie.
Hey, we should all have someone
who worships us like that, right?
Hm.
When was the trip
supposed to happen?
This week, I think.
Hey.
Quinn, it's me. I just talked
to Jamie. We need
to revisit the boyfriend.
Oliver Saxon.
So you think Clayton
bought your little story?
I'm not sure.
Either way, he's got your
photo all over Miami.
It's not safe to go to the hotel.
You need something private.
Yeah, but where?
I do know of one place.
Something tells me it's
the last place I'll want to go.
Debra's, if I can talk her into it.
I was right.
I can't think of a better option,
can you?
Unfortunately, I can't.
Answering more questions?
Anything I can do to help find
who did this to Cassie.
This must be hard on you.
The last few days
have been a nightmare.
I still can't even believe it.
I just wish I had time to breathe,
I'm so busy at work.
I'm already late for an appointment.
Won't take long.
What is it you do, exactly?
Building inspections.
Where you were when Cassie died?
Yes.
You're welcome to look
at my workbook,
I was in Sunny Isles
inspecting a new condo.
- Just a few minutes from here
.
Yes.
You must be pretty busy, huh?
I'm booked wall-to-wall
for the next few weeks.
Oh, really? I thought you and Cassie
were planning a trip to the Bahamas.
How were you gonna
work that in?
I guess that was a little crazy.
Cassie kept pushing,
I didn't want to disappoint her.
Oh, it was her idea?
Yeah. She wanted a romantic getaway.
Seems a little fast, don't you think?
After a few weeks of dating.
I know it's hard
for most people to understand,
but we had something special.
And we both knew it.
Look, I'm really sorry, you guys.
I've got to get going.
Maybe we can pick this up later?
Yeah, no.
We'll come back another time.
That would be great. Thanks.
He lied to us.
About what?
Jamie said
that whole Bahamas
thing was his idea.
A way for Cassie
not to dump him.
That doesn't mean he's a killer,
you know.
He just could be
fucking obsessed with her.
It wouldn't hurt to look
into it.
Look a little deeper into his alibi.
I'll get on that.
Feel that?
What?
Us, you know,
working together again.
It's nice, you know?
Yeah, it's a lot better than
doing background checks for Elway.
Yeah.
I forgot how much I like it.
Shit. Uh... I'm sorry.
I don't know why I did that.
Let's just pretend you didn't.
Okay.
What the fuck?
Sorry, we let ourselves in.
You two should talk alone.
I need a place
where Hannah can stay.
And you want that to be my place?
There's a federal marshal
after her.
He knows she's in Miami.
He's gonna do everything
he can to find her.
It's the only move I could think of.
To bring Hannah to my house?
I know.
It's only for a couple of nights.
Just until I can get her out of Miami.
Please?
A couple of nights, that's it.
Thank you.
You could also thank me
for getting Quinn off Zach's trail.
How?
Simple. Get him
to focus on the boyfriend.
Oliver Saxon.
Saxon? You think he did it?
Well, he's a damn good suspect.
Quinn and I talked to him today.
If Saxon thinks the police are onto him,
he'll know that I'm onto him.
You should stay away
from Saxon, Deb.
He could be more dangerous
than you think.
What are you talking about?
I can't go into it right now,
but please, just do as I ask.
I knew going back
to the force would put me
in a fucked up situation.
Here it is, ahead of schedule.
He's all yours.
You'll be okay here?
Sure.
We'll just hang.
Heh.
If Deb and Quinn did anything
to spook Saxon, I have to act fast.
I'm too late.
He's already moved out.
But if this has his DNA
I can check it against the hairs
I found at Zach's studio.
Here you go.
Are we going to see Hannah?
Hannah? Why?
I saw her on TV.
They said people are looking
for her. Is she in trouble?
No, she's fine.
Hannah's just popular.
You miss her?
Yeah. I liked playing with her.
She was nice.
I wish she could be my mom.
It's a match. Saxon is Vogel's son.
Daniel.
He's going by the name Oliver Saxon.
He dated my neighbour
until he killed her
in her apartment
two doors down from mine.
Do you have any idea where he is?
No, he cleared out
of his place.
He could be anywhere
right now.
Suppose you do find him,
Dexter.
What are you going to do?
What do you think?
I don't know how I feel about that.
He's murdered
four innocent people
and he killed Zach Hamilton.
He's my son.
There's nothing you can do for him.
I can try putting him
back into a safe facility
where he can't hurt himself
or anyone else.
I'm not going to let you kill him.
I'm sorry.
You brought me into this.
I didn't know who he was then.
Try and understand,
my youngest son is gone forever.
Maybe I have a second chance
with Daniel.
You really believe that?
You have a son.
Wouldn't you believe it?
This second chance she wants
could get us both killed.
For her own sake, I have to tell her
what she wants to hear.
Fine, we'll do it your way. Just...
Help me find him.
Is there a way to reach out to him?
I don't know.
Think.
The Mama Cass song that he left
playing in your apartment...
What about it?
One of the few
happy memories I have with Daniel
as a boy was, every Saturday,
I'd take him to
the King's Bay Cafe in the marina.
There was a juke box there.
And Daniel would
always play that song.
Maybe it's more than a happy memory.
Maybe it's an invitation.
King's Bay Cafe. It's still there.
Saxon's been one step
ahead of us this whole time.
We know he stole
your computer files.
But how could he have known about
Zach Hamilton? We met him after that.
The detailed notes
you keep on your computer...
Yes?
I think Saxon's
been monitoring your laptop.
It wouldn't be hard.
You just need the right spyware.
We can use this. Write an entry
in your journal saying you're going
to King's Bay Cafe tomorrow morning.
You think he'll read it and go?
You said yourself he's been
trying to send you a message.
He wants to see you.
I don't like deceiving Vogel,
but if it's the only way to get to Saxon...
You had no choice, Dex.
You had to lie to her.
I just can't believe Vogel
still thinks her son can be helped.
Well, it's not that crazy.
After everything he's done.
You would
want to help Harrison,
wouldn't you?
Vogel pretty much
made the same point.
She's right. I mean, look at what
your own father did to protect you.
Right or not,
Saxon needs to be stopped.
I'm putting him on my table.
And how is Vogel
going to feel about that?
I can't worry about it now.
At least she'll be alive.
Well, you'll figure it out.
I'm glad you're here.
I wanna be able to keep
being here for you, Dex.
But?
But there's no life for me here
in Florida, we both know it.
I can have a life somewhere else
far away from here.
In Argentina.
Maybe we all can.
You and Harrison could
meet me there.
We can start over.
It would be hard on Harrison,
uproot his whole life.
At first, it might be,
but sometimes change
is a good thing.
Sometimes it can--
Yes.
Me, you, and Harrison.
We're gonna move to Argentina.
We'll make it work, Dex.
I can give my notice
at Miami Metro,
say I'm burnt out.
I'm taking Harrison
to travel for a while.
Only Debra will know the truth.
Lieutenant.
Have you heard anything on
the whereabouts
of Zach Hamilton?
Zach Hamilton? You made it pretty
clear that we back away from him.
I just got a call from his parents.
They haven't heard from him in days.
Did they file
a missing persons report?
They just did.
Look, in case he does turn up,
I wanna be the first to know.
I'll make sure of it.
Deb, thanks for coming in.
Yeah. What's up?
Welcome back
to Homicide, detective.
You'll earn your way back up.
You don't know how happy
this makes me. Like the family
coming together again.
We gotta celebrate.
Yeah.
What?
It's all happening so fast.
And? Would you rather
it happened slow?
I just need some time
to think about it.
What's to think about?
Thought this is what you wanted?
It is.
I mean, I thought it was.
I don't get it.
I just need a little time, you know?
Take all the time you need.
Hey.
Hold on to this.
Heh.
I, uh, tried getting in touch
with Saxon,
but he's not answering his phone.
Went by his place. He cleared out.
Shit.
Yeah.
At least we're on the right track.
Good luck with that.
Deb.
I, uh, wouldn't have
gotten this far without you.
I'm glad I could help.
You cleaned.
A little.
Well, I hope I can still find shit.
I used to know where everything was.
Hungry?
Are you kidding?
Totally fair.
Well, I am gonna eat,
and I made enough for you too.
You going back?
How the fuck can I go back?
My brother's a serial killer.
And I have another one
hiding out in my house, eating salad.
Sorry.
It was stupid to think
that I could go back.
Well, I know a lot about
wanting things that you can't have.
I wish somewhere I'd learned
to take "no" for an answer.
Would have made my life
a lot easier.
But you didn't.
I'll take that one.
Right.
Well, it's just who I am.
And, uh...
Something tells me
you might be the same way.
Maybe that's the one thing
we have in common.
Heh. I can't believe
I'm eating food you made.
It's not bad, though, right?
No.
All right,
two-minute warning, Harrison.
Swim lessons are calling.
Almost done.
Sorry about this
police-protection business.
No, it's good.
I'm actually glad
that they're here.
If Hannah were to stop by,
poor Harrison would probably
run right to her.
He's not the only one.
Dexter,
hope I'm not intruding.
No, not at all. Come in.
All right.
What can I do for you?
Checking in,
making sure
everything's okay.
Yeah, everything's fine.
Well, good to hear.
I'm thinking the Hannah McKay threat
has pretty much died down.
Oh, yeah?
I mean, if she was here
I'm sure she's gone.
I'll recommend we pull off
your protective detail.
Okay.
All right.
And what's your name?
Harrison.
Huh. Is this your family?
Mm-hm.
Is this your daddy?
That's you, right?
Mm-hm.
Now, who's the pretty lady?
That's my mom.
Your mom?
Hey, why don't you go
grab your towel, bud.
Swim time.
Come on, let's go,
little shark man.
He lost his mother when he was a baby,
drawing her helps him feel closer to her.
Sure.
Well, we really do need
to get going.
Thanks for checking in.
All right, take care.
Hey, you got a sec?
Sure.
Closing the door.
That's never a good sign.
Hannah McKay dated your brother?
You didn't think to mention
that to me at all?
Never crossed your mind?
I didn't think it was important.
What else are you not telling me?
I don't know, but if I told you--
Drop the bullshit, Morgan.
What happened in the Keys?
You see her?
No.
I don't believe you.
You either saw her or your
brother told you to lay off.
What if he did?
What does it matter?
I'll give you 250,000 reasons why. But
clearly we have different priorities.
My brother? We do.
After all I've done for you,
I find it hard to believe
you could do this.
And maybe you need
to ask yourself if this is
the right job for you.
And if not, why don't you
get the fuck out.
Because I could use the office space
for somebody that gives a shit.
Oh, Dexter.
Sorry, I know I'm early.
I'd make you coffee,
but I only have tea.
That'll do.
I warn you,
it's strong.
I need all the help
I can get this morning.
Thanks.
Just so we're clear,
I'm meeting up with Daniel
and I'll lead him out of the cafe,
where you will sedate him.
And then we'll take him to a facility.
Every time I close my eyes,
I still see his face.
Daniel.
Yes.
Now to learn that he's alive
is so difficult to accept.
It is hard to believe.
But another part of me
knows it's true.
And I'm going to see him.
My son.
My little boy.
He still exists.
No matter what he's done. Unh.
I thought one of Hannah's potions
would be gentler than my needle.
Now Vogel will never
have to face what her son has become.
Can I get a cup of coffee please?
I'll bring that right over.
Here you go.
[MAMA CASS ELLIOT'S "MAKE YOUR
OWN KIND OF MUSIC" PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
♪ Nobody can tell ya ♪
- Hey, Lucy.
- Hi.
♪ There's only one song worth singing ♪♪
[MAMA CASS ELLIOT'S "MAKE YOUR
OWN KIND OF MUSIC" PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
♪ Nobody can tell ya ♪♪
He's played that song three times.
When is he gonna give up?
I'll follow him until I find
a quiet place to grab him.
For Vogel's own good,
it's time I kill the messenger.
Saxon must have spotted you.
He's good at this.
He might think Vogel
sent you, Dexter.
He could be going
to her house right now.
You've reached Dr. Evelyn Vogel.
I'm not available at this time.
Please leave a message.
Evelyn!
You drugged me.
You have every right to be upset,
but I was trying to protect you.
Where's Daniel?
He got away. That's why
I'm here, to warn you.
Well, I consider myself warned.
And I think it best from here on out
that I handle this myself.
It's not safe. Or smart.
I appreciate your concern
and I'm grateful for everything
you've done. But this is a family matter.
You once called yourself
my spiritual mother.
Doesn't that make us family?
Well, after what happened
this morning, Dexter,
how can I trust you?
Well, trust me or not,
I'm going to take care of Daniel.
Your safety and mine depend on it.
And after that,
I'm on my way with Hannah.
On your way?
Leaving Miami with her.
We're going away with Harrison.
That won't end well.
And you trusting Daniel,
that he's not gonna hurt anyone again?
How will that end?
Leave this alone, Dexter.
Vogel thinks I'm unique,
caught between two worlds,
my humanity and my darkness.
Maybe I always will be,
but I can't imagine
a life without Hannah in either one.
After this morning, I won't have to.
Vogel is on her own, and so am I.
I'll kill Saxon
and leave Miami forever.
So now do you believe me?
Yes.
You didn't send him.
Are you hungry?
How about
a little breakfast?
Okay...
Mom.