‐ Previously
on "Good Girls"...
‐ So we wanted to talk to you
about doing some
custom work for us.
Casino night!
‐ If it go into the wrong
hands, it's kind of, like...
counterfeit.
‐ So you mean, like,
if someone wanted
something special printed,
you would draw it?
What's up, ladies?
‐ You cannot finish that plate.
‐ He said he'd let me go‐‐
‐ He won't!
Wait.
You need us.
You need all of us.
‐ Not all of you.
[gunshots]
♪ ♪
‐ Hers.
‐ Oh, oh!
‐ Take it out,
Elizabeth.
That's what we used
to take care of your friend,
by the way.
‐ Why?
‐ Incentive.
‐ Why did I touch it?
‐ Why did you touch it?
‐ What if we pay someone
to blow his brains out?
A professional.
‐ So how's a lady like you
get involved
with a guy like that?
‐ I was just bored.
‐ Third one this month
out of Detroit.
Car paint?
‐ Or nail polish.
It's a woman.
You know this bitch
is hiding in a cave somewhere.
We just got to root her out.
‐ Have you guys
seen my phone?
‐ Is that hers?
‐ They got nothing
in their bank accounts.
‐ So?
‐ They're making
some of the best fake money
I've ever seen.
You don't live a little?
‐ To hit men.
‐ Good luck and Godspeed.
‐ No way!
You did my nails.
‐ Oh.
Hey.
‐ So...
what are you guys celebrating?
‐ You had pizza
with your therapist?
‐ He's helping me.
It's like a study buddy.
‐ Before we get started,
I wanted to introduce you
to Lila.
‐ I'll see you at home.
♪ ♪
‐ I proposed to Lila
a couple nights ago.
‐ We would like to buy
your place, Gayle.
Where are we gonna get
that kind of money?
‐ I don't know.
‐ I just don't want him
involved again.
‐ Okay.
Hot tubs.
He gets to feel like a man,
and we have a new way
to wash our cut.
‐ Welcome to Boland Bubbles.
‐ When does it get to be mine?
‐ When does what
get to be yours?
‐ I made all of this happen.
‐ Next time
empty the clip.
♪ ♪
[soft upbeat music]
‐ ♪ Pressure ♪
♪ Pushing down on me ♪
♪ Pressing down on you ♪
♪ No man ask for ♪
♪ Under pressure ♪
♪ That burns a building down ♪
♪ Splits a family in two ♪
♪ Puts people on streets ♪
♪ Um ba ba be ♪
♪ De da da ♪
♪ Ee day da ♪
♪ That's okay ♪
‐ ♪ It's the terror
of knowing ♪
[thud]
♪ What the world is about ♪
♪ Watching some good friends
screamin'‐‐ ♪
‐ [screaming]
[dog barking]
‐ I'm gonna color in the first
part of the fraction,
and you guys can do the rest.
[flatulence]
[laughter]
‐ Does someone need
to use the restroom?
[flatulence]
[laughter]
‐ Okay.
Who's the comedian?
[flatulence]
[laughter]
‐ Hand it over.
‐ Is that silly putty?
‐ Squeeze it.
[flatulence]
‐ It's not silly putty.
‐ He hid under my desk
last week.
‐ He and his sister
play hide‐and‐seek at home.
‐ I had the whole school
looking for him.
[flatulence]
‐ I'm sorry.
‐ We were drawing
the SpaceX rocket‐‐
‐ Mm.
‐ Oh, well, he loves art.
‐ He added testicles.
‐ Don't worry.
We're all over this.
‐ Mm‐hmm.
Like the wind.
‐ I'm afraid there's something
deeper at play.
‐ What do you mean?
‐ Have you ever heard of ADHD?
‐ Okay, hold on a minute.
‐ Fart putty
is a disorder now?
‐ Yeah, I mean...
[rapid flatulence]
Stuff's addictive.
‐ He treats my classroom like
it's his own YouTube channel.
‐ Yeah, okay.
But he's not deficient.
‐ There are 20 other students
that are here to learn.
‐ He loves it.
‐ Okay.
If you're not
gonna handle this,
then we might have to take
a different course of action.
‐ Huh.
‐ Like what?
Kick him out of school?
‐ Just have him tested.
‐ [breathes deeply]
‐ What about a magician?
‐ 'Cause I'm turning eight?
‐ Oh, what about
the bingo hall?
‐ 'Cause I'm turning 80?
‐ Fine, well, you tell me.
What do you want to do?
‐ Nothing.
‐ Nothing?
We're not gonna
not celebrate your birthday.
‐ Birthdays are lame.
‐ Well, I'm trying
to un‐lame them.
What about just a dance party?
‐ In our living room?
‐ Yeah, we do it all the time.
And, you know,
Janet down the hall,
she could DJ.
I mean, we always listen
to her music
through the walls anyway.
‐ She plays the organ.
‐ Just... just send me
your friends' Instas,
and I will slide
into their DMs,
and I'll plan
the whole thing.
All you have to do
is show up...
get turnt up...
while we celebrate you
growing up.
‐ Nancy has a stupid
dinner planned.
‐ Oh.
‐ Birthdays just kind of
aren't my thing anymore.
I'm gonna dip.
Later.
[door opens, closes]
‐ [sighs]
He has no friends.
‐ Um, have you talked to him?
‐ [scoffs]
Uh, yeah.
‐ About what?
‐ You know, him.
‐ Mm, of course.
‐ Me?
‐ Of course.
‐ It's a lot of me.
‐ Aha.
‐ It's mostly me.
‐ Mm.
‐ It's 100% me.
‐ And how is that an issue?
‐ Don't tell me.
This is the part where you want
me to realize out loud
that I'm some kind
of narcissist
and I've been ignoring my son?
‐ The out‐loud part
is optional, but...
‐ Perhaps we could talk
about something else?
‐ Your time.
‐ Okay.
What happened to your face?
‐ I shaved.
‐ For her?
‐ For me.
‐ You picked a date
for the wedding?
‐ No.
‐ Venue?
‐ Guest list?
‐ Not yet.
‐ Am in invited?
‐ Nope.
‐ Ouch.
‐ Would you want to come?
‐ Nope.
‐ Ouch.
[breathes deeply]
Um...
is there anything else
you'd like to cover?
‐ What day is it today?
‐ Um...
Tuesday.
‐ You sure?
‐ Yeah.
‐ What was yesterday?
‐ Monday.
‐ Tomorrow?
Come on.
‐ Wednesday.
‐ Mm.
[chuckles]
So you do understand
the concept of time.
Where my cut at?
‐ I said we were almost open.
‐ Mm‐hmm.
Kind of like being
almost pregnant, right?
‐ We have been killing
ourselves
printing money for you
seven days a week.
Don't touch that.
It's still wet.
‐ It's just a bunch
of pretty paper.
‐ You know,
you can't just start
selling hot tubs willy‐nilly.
The city has rules.
‐ And that's not your problem.
‐ Well, then
what is my problem?
[dramatic music]
‐ It's the school carnival.
♪ ♪
‐ Uh, okay.
I'll make cookies.
‐ Oh, um...
so we were thinking
more, like, mini Khanom Chans.
‐ What's that?
‐ The traditional Thai dessert?
‐ "Chan" means "layer."
‐ Why?
‐ To go with
the fundraising theme.
‐ "One Night in Bangkok."
‐ It'll be so cute
with the song playing
while the kids ride rickshaws.
‐ [gasps]
Ooh, we should all wear
Chut Thais!
‐ Oh, but we'd have to
make 'em, though.
‐ You love to sew, right?
♪ ♪
‐ You didn't forget
about our little
incentive program, right?
♪ ♪
‐ No, I did not.
‐ Good.
Just trying to keep you
motivated.
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
‐ They just found 'em,
it's all over the news.
‐ Didn't she work with you?
‐ Who?
‐ That girl who disappeared
a few weeks ago.
‐ They just found her body.
♪ ♪
‐ What?
‐ They think
some gang killed her.
‐ I don't get it.
Who dumps bodies
in a graveyard?
‐ To hide them on top
of other dead people
is super smart.
‐ Oh, my God.
I would be so livid
if there was a dead person‐‐
[conversation continues
indistinctly]
♪ ♪
‐ Beth.
Beth, what's wrong?
‐ I can't see.
[woman gasps, plate clatters]
‐ Oh, my God, Beth.
‐ Been under
a lot of stress lately?
‐ Tiny bit.
‐ Her blood pressure's up.
Liver enzymes are elevated.
Cortisol level's high.
Your body's telling you
to slow down.
‐ Message received.
‐ Join a gym.
‐ [gasps]
It's that bad?
‐ Cut back on coffee,
booze...
In the meantime,
try to avoid
what's causing you
so much anxiety.
‐ We're on it, Doc.
‐ Someone will be in
to discharge you.
‐ I got to get my hands
on that gun.
‐ Jesus.
‐ My fingerprints
are all over it,
and now there's a bullet.
‐ What did the lady just say?
‐ Yeah, I'll go to that
mom boot camp
in the park or whatever.
‐ The one that weirdo
was talking about?
‐ Well, I'm not giving
up the booze.
‐ Where is our hit man?
‐ His appointment girl
called me.
He's on a job in South America.
‐ Well, how about we let
that freaky bitch know
that we're gonna put a hit
on her hit man
if he doesn't hit our man?
‐ Yeah, why don't you get
right on that?
‐ Okay, I'm sorry.
What else makes
that gun go away?
‐ If I give him something
he really needs.
‐ You're gonna hit
baloney town again?
‐ I mean, way to take one
for the team.
‐ Not that.
How quickly can we open?
‐ We still need inspections,
codes, new signage.
‐ You're overthinking this.
‐ The health department
has to give us the all‐clear
on Legionnaire's.
‐ The money has run out.
‐ What does that mean?
‐ It means we have to sell
some hot tubs, Dean.
I know.
Spas.
‐ What if that can't happen?
‐ Well, then I have
to go to him.
‐ Are you serious?
‐ ♪ We're running with
the shadows of the night ♪
♪ So, baby, take my hand,
it'll be all right ♪
♪ Surrender all your dreams
to me tonight ♪
♪ They'll come true
in the end ♪
♪ ♪
♪ You said, "Oh, girl,
it's a cold world ♪
♪ When you keep it all
to yourself" ♪
♪ I said, "You can't hide
on the inside ♪
♪ All the pain
you've ever felt" ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Ransom my heart,
but, baby, don't look back ♪
♪ 'Cause we got nobody else ♪
♪ We're running with
the shadows of the night ♪
♪ So, baby, take my hand,
it'll be all right ♪
♪ Surrender all your dreams
to me tonight ♪
♪ They'll come true
in the end ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Sometimes it feels like ♪
♪ It's all moving
way too fast ♪
♪ Use every alibi
and word to deny ♪
♪ That love ain't meant
to last ♪
♪ You can cry, tough baby ♪
♪ It's all right ♪
♪ You can let me down easy,
but not tonight ♪
♪ We're running with
the shadows of the night ♪
♪ So, baby, take my hand,
it'll be all right ♪
♪ Surrender all your dreams
to me tonight ♪
♪ They'll come true
in the end ♪
♪ ♪
‐ Feel the burn?
‐ [breathes heavily]
Everywhere.
You're kicking my ass.
‐ That's my job.
[door closes]
‐ Mm.
‐ He out?
‐ One song, two books,
and a dissertation
on velociraptors.
‐ You think
he talks too much?
‐ Um, have you met the boy?
‐ I mean, like, in general.
‐ Kid's a damn chatterbox.
‐ He doesn't lose stuff,
does he?
‐ Well...
he lost that blue jacket.
‐ But then he found it.
‐ Yeah, but then
he lost the hat.
‐ You think he does that
occasionally,
often, or very often?
‐ What are you doing?
‐ There's a prelim form
to fill out.
‐ He doesn't need a test, Ruby.
‐ You heard what she said.
‐ You know what I heard?
That his white teacher
can't tell the difference
between an energetic kid
and a misbehaving Black boy.
‐ What if it's not just that?
‐ What else would it be?
‐ Us.
‐ What, like, we gave him ADHD?
‐ We dropped the ball.
‐ I thought
that was with Sara.
‐ Could be both of them.
‐ Mm‐mm.
Ain't nothing wrong with him.
And I don't need some test
to tell me how I'm doing
as a father.
‐ Look,
installation's free.
I'm gonna send my guys
over to your backyard.
They're gonna turn it
into paradise.
You're never gonna
want to leave!
‐ Welcome to Boland Bubbles,
where we
"tropic" like it's hot.
[upbeat music playing
over speakers]
♪ ♪
‐ Hi.
If you have any questions,
I'd be happy to help.
‐ Y'all under new management?
‐ Family owned and operated.
‐ Looks different.
[laughs]
‐ Out with the old,
in with the new, right?
‐ New paint!
‐ Yeah!
And lots of new inventory.
I'm Beth, by the way.
‐ Terry.
Tell me about this bad boy.
‐ Oh, you've got a good eye.
‐ [laughs]
‐ This is our Insignia X5‐‐
35 jets, individual seating.
Comes in bronze, walnut,
and sandstone.
‐ Mm.
♪ ♪
What kind of voltage
does she pull?
‐ Uh...standard outlet?
Just plug and play.
‐ Where's the
little girl's room?
Got to tinkle.
‐ Uh, just there on the left.
♪ ♪
‐ Great turnout, right?
It's crazy!
‐ I'm trying to close an X5.
‐ Nice!
♪ ♪
‐ Ooh.
Heads up, that was fast.
‐ [clears throat]
‐ Well, Terry, you seem
to know your way around a spa.
So I would love to introduce
you to my husband
and have him walk you through
some of the technical features
and see what you think.
‐ I think you're shut down.
‐ I'm sorry?
‐ I'm a building inspector
with Wayne County.
You folks got yourself
a load of violations.
♪ ♪
Painted over
your sprinkler heads.
Gonna have to dock you on that.
[upbeat jazzy music playing
over speakers]
Got a residential power strip
juicing all your units.
Got to dock ya!
♪ ♪
Centerline of the toilet
in your tinkler
is less than 15 inches
from this wall.
That's a two‐fer‐‐
plumbing and ADA.
So what do I got to do, Dean?
‐ Dock me?
‐ Mm‐hmm.
♪ ♪
So that's sprinklers, wiring,
construction, plumbing.
‐ This could take months.
‐ If you're lucky.
Can I get another one of these
for my niece?
♪ ♪
‐ Yeah, a‐at the front.
‐ All right, folks!
That's a wrap
on Boland Bubbles.
Don't have to go home,
but you can't stay here.
♪ ♪
‐ All right, ladies.
Now pick up those buns.
No slacking.
Let's go.
‐ It's like a friends
and family discount.
‐ I didn't know
y'all were open.
‐ Oh, we're not.
But, you know, you guys are,
like, tastemakers.
I'm telling you...
once you step foot
in the hot and steamy Boland,
you will not be able
to keep it a secret.
‐ We just put in a new deck.
‐ Well, you know what goes
with a new deck.
‐ Lily just started
private school.
We can't afford it.
‐ I'm not even supposed
to be selling them.
I'll work with you.
‐ Less mouth, more ass.
‐ [whispering]
I have brochures.
‐ You got to breathe!
You want to stop peeing
when you sneeze?
‐ You can just pick 'em up
and pass 'em out at drop‐off.
‐ Tuck your butts!
‐ I'll hook anybody up.
[hip‐hop music playing]
‐ Selling hot tubs
in my class?
‐ [breathing heavily]
Sorry.
♪ ♪
‐ Do I count as
friend and family?
‐ Uh...
yeah, sure.
‐ How low can you go?
I mean pricing.
‐ Oh.
Um...
Lower than my pelvic floor
after four kids.
‐ You take Venmo?
‐ I'll take anything.
[breathing heavily]
♪ ♪
‐ Hey.
‐ [sighs] Hey.
‐ Where's Ben?
‐ Cleaning the house.
‐ Alone?
Why?
‐ We need to talk about him.
‐ [sighs]
It's not cool, right?
‐ He told you?
‐ [sighs]
[door closes]
What do we do?
‐ I don't know.
Nancy thinks we should
make him switch schools.
‐ Yeah, I mean,
maybe she's right.
‐ Over one party?
‐ Huh?
‐ Didn't the cops call you?
‐ What are you talking about?
‐ Ben threw a rager
at our house.
‐ Well, where the hell
were you?
‐ We were just
at Nancy's parents' cabin.
What did you think
we were talking about?
‐ That he has no friends.
‐ [laughs]
He had, like, 100 people
at our house.
‐ Who?
‐ Sam, Eddie, Janice,
the whole lacrosse team.
I don't know,
the usual suspects.
‐ I don't know
any of those suspects.
‐ Okay, well, they all had
their shoes on in our house,
and Nancy is losing her mind.
‐ He plays lacrosse?
‐ Yeah.
How do you not know that?
‐ How did you know that?
‐ 'Cause I bought him the gear.
‐ [sighs]
‐ Sorry, look,
you've been really busy.
‐ That's not why.
‐ W‐we just know
all the parents
around the neighborhood
and stuff.
‐ And lacrosse.
‐ Don't go there.
‐ Already there.
‐ He just knows you wouldn't
really be into it.
‐ What? His whole new secret,
fancy life?
‐ Well...
he's got a game next weekend
if you want to come.
You could meet
all the usual suspects.
‐ Can I borrow something
from Nancy to wear?
‐ No, your boobs are too big.
[both chuckle]
‐ We would love for you to take
another look at our facility.
‐ You couldn't have possibly
fixed everything that fast.
‐ Well, we came up
with some creative solutions.
‐ Well, I've been doing this
for 19 years,
and, believe me,
I've seen it all.
[chuckles]
‐ Have you seen this?
‐ Looks the same.
Are you trying
to waste my time?
‐ Um, we're...trying...
to make it worth your while.
‐ [clears throat]
Yes, uh...
we know how, uh,
how tricky wiring can be.
So please just let us know
if there's anything
you'd like us to do.
‐ And, obviously,
we can't knock down
the whole tinkler.
[laughs]
So we...
got a new toilet.
‐ We haven't installed it yet.
What do you, uh‐‐
what do you think?
‐ Did we pass?
‐ [breathes deeply]
[mid‐tempo music playing]
♪ ♪
[door opens and closes]
‐ Buy you a drink?
‐ I own the place.
♪ ♪
‐ Well, why don't you
buy me one, then?
‐ Why would I do that?
‐ Boland Bubbles
is in business.
♪ ♪
‐ That's what he's calling it?
‐ Yeah, I think it's cute.
‐ Yeah.
Real panty‐dropper.
♪ ♪
‐ Yeah, well,
it's fully operational.
Your money is being cleaned,
laundered, folded,
and pressed as we speak.
Um, a tequila for the chief.
Top shelf.
And, um...
Do you have anything
without alcohol or caffeine?
♪ ♪
Just bourbon, neat.
Could be more excited.
‐ It ain't always
about you, is it?
‐ It's what you wanted!
‐ You know what?
I got other stuff on my mind.
‐ I need that gun.
♪ ♪
‐ I'm sorry, what?
‐ We're up and running,
I'm making you bank.
Doesn't make sense to hold it
over me anymore.
♪ ♪
‐ You know what?
You're right.
♪ ♪
‐ I am?
‐ Yeah.
I'm not gonna hold it
over you anymore.
♪ ♪
‐ Thanks.
‐ Cops might, though.
♪ ♪
Yeah, see, the lawyer says
I got to go in
about that friend of yours.
♪ ♪
Apparently they think
I had something to do with it,
which is just crazy.
♪ ♪
[chuckles]
‐ And what are you gonna
tell 'em?
♪ ♪
‐ I'm not sure I got to say
anything.
♪ ♪
‐ If you give it to them,
I'm not the only thing
that goes away.
♪ ♪
‐ Mm‐hmm.
Priorities, huh?
♪ ♪
‐ I'll take another one.
‐ There's a one‐way
to St. Petersburg.
Leaves at midnight.
‐ Florida?
‐ Russia.
‐ Why Russia?
‐ Because they'll
give you asylum.
‐ How do you even know
he's gonna turn over the gun?
‐ How do I know he's not?
‐ Exactly.
It's why we got to get your ass
on this plane
to Sheremetyevo Airport, now.
‐ She's gonna live
in Russia now?
‐ Yeah, I mean, Snowden
lived in the terminal.
‐ Her kids?
‐ We'll sneak 'em out
one by one.
‐ So it's gonna be
one big happy family
living in a terminal.
‐ Snowden did.
‐ Eating Sbarro's.
‐ 'Cause they have Sbarro's
in Russia?
‐ Since 1997.
The point is,
you can't be extradited
for murder.
‐ You just need a lawyer.
‐ I was the last person
she was seen with.
‐ Okay, a good one.
‐ And I lied to the police.
‐ A real good one.
‐ And I stole her bird.
‐ Technically,
I stole her bird.
‐ Okay, where's her
power‐walking boyfriend?
He'll back you up.
‐ He's probably
still in diapers
since the last time
he saw gang friend.
‐ You didn't pull the trigger.
‐ I may as well have.
‐ What are you looking for?
She's making me mental.
[Adult's "Nite Life"]
‐ Dear Dean,
I've spent the last two years
cooking and cleaning.
I've learned I'm excellent at
both, and you will be, too...
because I'm going to tell you
exactly what to do
and how to do it.
My friends will make
the money.
You're gonna buy hot tubs
with it, a lot of 'em,
from as many wholesalers
as you can, just in case.
Spread it around.
This is where you shine, Dean.
Price doesn't matter.
It's all profit.
Now you're gonna sell 'em.
♪ ♪
And this is how you hide it.
Inflate the sales price
or the number
of the units sold,
ideally both.
It's pretty simple.
I know you can do this.
You can still live the dream.
Nobody needs to know
how you got there.
Love, Beth.
‐ ♪ In my night life,
I don't think twice ♪
♪ Everything is so nice ♪
♪ Loving the luxury
of the night life ♪
♪ Everything is all right ♪
♪ Blinded by the headlights,
driving past midnight ♪
♪ Looks like a still life ♪
♪ Give me something cheap ♪
♪ Not enough sleep ♪
♪ Which one do I keep? ♪
♪ You or my night life? ♪
♪ ♪
‐ Remember when those raccoons
tracked the mud
all over the downspout?
♪ ♪
‐ I need to tell you
something.
‐ Look at this‐‐I have
to repaint the entire door.
And it's all over,
everywhere that inspector
woman touched!
I have to redo the bathroom,
the front area over there.
It's, like, what?
Did she change the oil
on her car
before she came here?
And Eric, I mean, he's already
returned the stuff,
and we're never gonna match
the color.
I mean, it's Swiss coffee
and pale avocado.
[continues indistinctly]
[Muzak playing]
Hey.
What do you want to tell me?
‐ Nothing.
[door closes]
‐ Stopped by the school today.
‐ What for?
‐ Tell little man's principal
that if Ms. Jackson
can't take an honest fart joke,
then maybe our son's
not the problem.
‐ How'd that go over?
‐ He starts in Ms. V's class
on Monday.
Bad people,
not bad parents.
‐ What happens when he does
the same thing in her class?
‐ Well, she sees kids as kids.
‐ Mm.
‐ What's this?
‐ [pops lips] Science homework.
‐ He didn't do it?
‐ Oh, he did it.
‐ Why did he draw
a picture of a cactus?
‐ It's not a cactus.
‐ Meerkat?
‐ Nope.
‐ Prairie dog?
‐ Penis.
Math.
‐ I'm guessing
this is not a number.
‐ And history.
‐ [gasps]
‐ I'm gonna
get ahead of this one
and let you know right now,
it's not
the Washington Monument.
‐ I was really hoping it was.
‐ Me too.
‐ Uh‐uh‐uh.
I'll call
about the test tomorrow.
[man speaking indistinctly
on TV]
‐ Hey.
‐ Hi.
[door closes]
‐ How was Dad's?
‐ Boring.
‐ How was the dinner?
‐ Plant‐based.
Um, I got homework, so...
‐ Hey.
I thought...
maybe next weekend we could,
like, go to the movies?
You know, buy one ticket
and then sneak into five?
‐ I think I might go
to Dad's again.
‐ You were just there.
‐ I know, but I have
a school thing.
‐ Oh.
Sick.
Can I come?
‐ It's sort of
not for parents.
‐ Yeah, no, that's‐‐that's
totally cool.
‐ But I'm still totally down
for the movie thing.
‐ Hey, Ben?
Happy birthday.
‐ Thanks.
[door closes]
‐ Sure you don't want a fork?
‐ Mm‐mm.
‐ Just thought it might be
a little more...
efficient
for your, uh...
situation.
‐ What do you want?
‐ Do you got kids?
‐ Got a little girl
in Cincinnati.
‐ You get to see her at all?
‐ I try to get there
for her birthdays.
‐ That sucks.
‐ She's got a good mom.
It's better this way.
‐ I need a favor.
‐ [scoffs]
You sound like your sister.
‐ She's a really good mom, too.
‐ So?
‐ So it really shouldn't be
her prints on that gun.
‐ Dumpling?
[engine stops, car door opens]
‐ [sniffs]
‐ When are you going in?
‐ Soon.
‐ I've been thinking
a lot about it.
‐ I'll bet you have.
‐ It's hard to wrap your
brain around, actually...
that each of our fingerprints
is totally
and completely unique.
Snowflakes too.
And tiger stripes.
Like, why?
‐ Don't know,
but it really works out
in my favor.
‐ Does it?
Forgot one.
‐ What's this?
‐ You can keep it.
I've got the original
somewhere safe.
Just crazy...
that there's
a way to get everyone...
even tigers.
Let me know what the cops say.
‐ Is that booze?
‐ This boy
has worked a penis
into almost every one of these.
‐ [sighs]
What did the specialist say?
‐ You're probably gonna
want some of this.
‐ It's that bad?
‐ It's pretty bad.
‐ [sighs]
Like special‐school bad?
‐ Mm‐hmm.
The real expensive kind.
‐ This says he should be
in eighth grade.
‐ Yep.
‐ But he's in second grade.
‐ Yeah.
‐ No.
‐ Boy's a damn genius.
‐ What are we gonna do?
‐ How are we gonna afford
that school?
‐ And I went ahead and made
some Khao Tom Mud‐‐
banana leaf sticky rice thing,
it's delish.
Oh, but the dye still needs
to dry in the Chut Thais,
so that'll take a minute.
Yes, I am feeling much better.
I just needed to
take control of the situation.
[knock at door]
Wait, can‐‐I'm sorry,
can I call you back?
‐ You called.
May I?
‐ Uh... yeah.
Let me just grab you a plate.
‐ I lived off of these
on Koh Samui.
Where's your furniture?
‐ It was stolen.
‐ By whom?
‐ Your target.
Remember?
Although, by this point, he's
gonna die of old age first.
‐ I have other clients.
‐ I am paying you
a lot of money.
‐ For you.
From Chile.
I don't support
how they're made,
but their little hands are...
so precise.
‐ Move me up on your schedule.
‐ Try them on.
‐ [sighs]
You've done the leg work.
‐ It's harder than I thought.
‐ He is not hard to find.
‐ He's not the problem.
‐ Well, who is?
‐ You.
‐ [sighs]
‐ Stunning.
All of it.
‐ What?
‐ You're distracting.
‐ How?
‐ I can't stop thinking
about you.
Mmm.
[speaking Thai]
And if I'm honest...
That's why I've been
dragging my feet.
‐ Well, what am
I supposed to do here?
‐ Have dinner with me.
‐ When did they get in?
‐ This morning.
‐ DL Dave, too?
‐ The whole posse.
‐ Is he pissed?
‐ You charged a hot tub
to the United States
government.
‐ How do I look?
‐ Like you're gonna cry.
‐ Well, I'm not.
‐ Don't.
‐ I won't.
‐ You haven't cried
in three days.
‐ So?
‐ You're due.
‐ I promise, okay?
[crying]
They bought the place in cash,
and they're selling 'em,
like, way below cost
and the only way
that works is if the plan
is to go out of business,
so before you send me home,
just, like, please put
forensic accounting on it,
'cause, I swear to God,
if I'm wrong about this,
I will resign if this isn't the
best give I've ever given you.
Just trust me.
‐ What do you think, Dave?
‐ No one is shipping you home.
‐ Thank you.
‐ Let's get the team on it.
‐ Yes.
‐ There's a pattern here.
‐ Yes!
‐ His car dealership
got busted, too.
‐ Wait, sorry.
What?
‐ Put a tail on this guy.
‐ Guy?
Wait, wait.
W‐why is it the guy?
‐ And, fellas...
let's tighten the net.
Last time he got off
on a technicality.
[Jerry Reed's
"I Feel for You"]
‐ Let's get out of here.
[indistinct chatter]
[laughter]
‐ ♪ To see you there
crying, boy ♪
[door closes]
‐ ♪ Brings to mind ♪
♪ ♪
♪ All the things I told you ♪
♪ One time ♪
♪ ♪
♪ The way that I did
one time ♪
♪ ♪
♪ And wish
you could die, boy ♪
♪ To get that woman
off of your mind ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Go on and fall
all to pieces, son ♪
♪ The way
that she made me do ♪
♪ I know what you're going
through, and I feel... ♪