[LAUGHTER]
So, I'm about to go
on the road for a while.
Isn't it weird how, when
you're away from home,
you start missing the little things
you never really thought
about, like your kids?
-[WEAK LAUGHTER]
-Oh.
I thought that would do better.
I guess you all like kids.
To each his own.
Okay, well, I have kids.
And, you know, everybody
seems to get so angry
when you bring one on a plane.
But if the airlines don't want them,
why do they provide those
little child-size bottles of booze?
-[WEAK LAUGHTER]
-Wow.
Not in a laughing mood tonight, huh?
You know, th… there's a Bergman
film playing down the street.
It's about black death.
Maybe you should've gone to that.
Maybe something's missing from my set.
What could it be?
Oh, I know.
A catchphrase.
Yeah, that way I could
do a bunch of crappy jokes,
then save them with one
of my patented zingers.
Something like "Have
yourself a scoop of that!"
-Or "Dock that in your harbor."
-[LAUGHTER]
Or "Stuff that in your pierogi." Yeah.
Guess I'm a little nervous.
I'm opening for Shy Baldwin.
-[ENTHUSIASTIC APPLAUSE]
-Oh, yeah, him you like.
But I won't be on the road by myself.
I'll have a support system.
My manager Susie Myerson.
[LOUD BOOING]
I see you've met.
You know, she's always
believed in me, Susie.
She's pushed me to get better and better.
Sometimes off a cliff, but irregardless,
I'm loyal to her for that.
Because, really, if there's no loyalty,
what's the point of a partnership?
They say if you want loyalty, get a dog.
But even the most loyal
dog will stick its head
in your neighbor's cooze
'cause it wants to get scratched.
I mean, it doesn't mean
the dog doesn't like you,
it just means the dog
isn't that fucking picky.
All right.
Thanks, everybody.
I'm Mrs. Maisel. Good night.
[APPLAUSE]
Good job, Midge. Really good.
I'm sorry, were you even listening?
Oh, no, don't get me
wrong, you were awful.
It was like sitting at my
grandmother's deathbed
all over again, but without snacks.
Thanks for the feedback.
Hey, better to crap
out now then in front of
a thousand people in Vegas.
That would be disastrous.
Really, Jackie, you're
giving me a big head.
Yeah, your head
looked bigger tonight, too.
So what was that,
exactly, all that loyalty stuff?
Just trying to be
inspirational to my audience.
Well, maybe skip
trying to be inspirational
when you open for Shy
and just stick to the funny.
I mean, you're not opening
for the fucking Buddha.
Always a help. Thanks.
-Is that what you really think?
-What?
That I'm sticking my head
in Sophie Lennon's cooze.
I was speaking in general terms.
Okay. Well, try to be specific.
Maybe that'll get you some laughs.
-Okay.
And by the way, "irregardless"?
It's not a word.
-Yes, it is.
-No, it's not.
It's "regardless." That's the word.
Well, I say irregardless.
Just trying to be inspirational.
Well, you've inspired me.
-Go announce the next act.
-I don't want to miss anything.
Go.
Look, I…
JACKIE: Okay, if you
think multiple ocarinas
playing at the same time is depressing,
then you really should have
gone to the fucking Bergman film.
[LAUGHTER]
Miriam Weissman!
God. Mrs. Fulber, you scared me.
What's with all the noise
from your apartment?
There's some sort of party going on.
Let me check. I'm just getting home.
-From where?
-I was out.
-On a school night?
-Yes.
-With boys?
-I got to go, Mrs. Fulber.
-Brush your teeth.
-You're not my babysitter anymore.
ABE: …despite laws.
EZRA: 'Cause the laws
are set by capitalists.
ALAN: The rich have
been using the Constitution
to justify their crimes against the poor.
MADELINE: Marx was the true purist.
Lenin's the little boy
who dumped his bowels
on Karl's genius.
I've never heard it put quite that way,
but I agree with the general sentiment.
Hello… all.
Ah, Miriam.
Let me introduce you to some new friends.
This is Ezra, Alan, and Madeline.
Everybody, this is my daughter Miriam.
-Hello.
-I met my lawyer
at the White Horse Tavern
and fell into a conversation
with these three,
and it was getting late,
and they were closing up.
So I invited them here.
They're starting a weekly paper.
More of a revolutionary broadsheet.
And we think Abe should be a part of it.
Sounds great.
It's nice you're making friends.
We were all just
debating what to call it.
And the final choices are The New Jive
and It's the Sixties, Man!
Two timeless names.
MADELINE: Alan came
up with both of those.
He's so expressive.
This was a little distracting
at first, but you get used to it.
And the comrades in the study?
I did not know they were there.
Yeah, that's Corey and Bishop.
We invited them to come and bunk here.
Okay, gang, so… carry on.
But if you could
carry on a little quieter.
Ideas are thunderclaps.
Right, but maybe smaller
thunderclaps for now
and louder ones another time.
Good night.
Okay, guys, the first edition
should include a mission statement.
I agree.
There's no point in being subtle.
It's the '60s, man.
ABE, GUESTS: ♪ And the last fight ♪
♪ Let us face ♪
ABE: Everybody!
♪ The Internationale ♪
-What?!
-♪ Unites ♪
[ABE, GUESTS SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Your arrest was a gift from God, Abe,
but now we got to exploit it.
Publicize it, get you out there
and make you the face of free speech.
I want that. I want to be the face.
You're the perfect image for the cause.
Someone people can trust.
An éminence grise.
I've always wanted to
be an éminence grise.
I'm gonna get your work
notebooks back from Bell Labs.
I'm peppering the shit out of
them with motions, hearings.
In fact, I got something
you got to sign right now.
They're my ideas, my thoughts.
They belong to you.
This is the last of the butter cookies.
All right.
Hey, you're communists,
for Christ's sake.
Share.
-Sorry.
-Of course.
I can make eggs for
anyone who wants some.
It's all right, Zelda.
I'm sure having a maid
waiting on them like this,
serving butter cookies,
is such a violation
of their proletariat values.
No, Abe, it's good, it's fine.
Yeah, it helps us understand
what we're fighting against.
You've yelled, you've argued,
you've counterargued,
you've banged tables,
you've banged walls, you've sung.
"The Internationale."
And a Chuck Berry song?
We were taking a well-earned break.
You've clapped hands,
you've clinked glasses.
Someone was loud in the bathroom.
-Sorry?
-ABE: You used the bathroom?
-There was more singing.
-Which bathroom?
-Miriam.
-Michael?
You know Michael Kessler?
How do you know Michael Kessler?
What are you doing here?
-What are you doing here?
-I live here.
How do you know Michael Kessler?
-He's my lawyer.
-What is he to you?
-My father.
-Miriam's your daughter?
-Why do you have a lawyer?
-He was arrested.
-Why were you arrested?
-For protecting a man's rights.
-What man?
-Lenny Bruce.
-Come again?
-The man you're dating.
-You're dating Lenny Bruce?
No, I am not dating Lenny Bruce.
Excuse me, is Zelda part of this,
or can she go make the eggs?
Study.
Move, move, move.
Zelda. Eggs, now.
Yes, miss.
What is happening?
You told me to go see
Lenny Bruce, so I did.
This is too much for my brain.
And more guys got in.
-ABE: I'll speak to Ezra.
-And where is Mama?
How is she sleeping
through the revolution?
-She went home.
-This is home.
-No, she went to see her family.
-She went to Providence?
She wants to talk to them
about her share of the trust.
Oh, boy, she hates Providence.
But she needs a minimal lifestyle,
and that takes money.
You know me.
I would sleep on the
cold street if need be,
without bedding, forage for food.
How do you want your eggs
this morning, Mr. Weissman?
Uh, toad in the hole might be nice today.
I see your shoes are off.
-Are your corns bothering you again?
-A tad.
We'll wash your feet, and I'll use
-that pumice stone on them again.
-Perfect.
But your mother,
she's not hearty like me.
She needs her creature comforts.
-And she's coming back?
-From Providence?
Of course she's coming back.
-And you're sure?
-Of course I'm sure.
I'm pretty damn sure.
Yes. From Providence, she will come back.
♪ The everlasting hills of Oklahoma ♪
♪ They hold a million treasures ♪
♪ To be found ♪
♪ Golden grain on hills of green ♪
♪ Wave to valleys ♪
♪ Cool and clean ♪
♪ Too bad some folks ♪
♪ Have never seen ♪
♪ The everlasting hills ♪
♪ Of Oklahoma ♪
♪♪
♪ The everlasting tales ♪
♪ Of Oklahoma ♪
♪ Are told in clouded statues… ♪
Howdy, Rosie!
-[BELL CLANGING]
-Rosie's home!
♪ Pioneers ♪
-♪ Who long have gone ♪
-[WHISTLE BLOWS]
♪ Their wagon wheels ♪
-Rosie's home.
-♪ Still rumble on ♪
♪ When thunder peals… ♪
Welcome home, my little Rosie.
Hello, Helda, good to see you.
Please let me help
you out of the car, miss.
Oh, I can get out just fine, John.
Watch your step, miss. Watch your step.
I'm watching it, thank you.
Are you tired, miss? You must be tired.
I'm a little tired, John.
Do you need me to
hold you up, little one?
No.
-Or John can carry you.
-I can walk on my own.
You look exhausted, miss.
-Your bag.
-I'm okay, Helda, I just…
You truly must be on
the verge of collapse.
Your coat.
Well, I'm weary, John,
but not collapsing.
You look flush.
Well, the car was warm.
Do you have heatstroke?
You're prone to heatstroke.
I don't think so. Do I look like…
Do you have the chills, miss?
You're shivering.
Am I? I didn't think I was.
Is Mr. Weissman coming, miss?
-No, not this time, John.
-That's for the best.
The staircase incident
is still talked about here.
Yes, well, what happened
with the staircase
was blown all out of proportion.
You look sickly pale, miss.
Do I? I don't feel like I am.
-Like a ghost.
-Where's Oscar? Is he around?
Working.
Your brother is always working, miss.
-I would love to talk to him.
-Yeah.
You look ruddy, miss.
Do you have a fever?
No. Uh, maybe. I feel a little warm.
We need to… we need to get you upstairs.
-I'll send a cold compress up.
-Yeah. And call the doctor.
Well, I guess you could call the doctor.
Remember how the stairs work, miss,
it's one right after another.
I remember how the stairs work, Helda.
ANNOUNCER [ON TV]: All it
takes is a little Winky Dink magic…
Get your coat on, kiddo.
We got to get you uptown.
Okay.
Hey, I got some information
on that club of yours
in Chinatown; dug super deep.
Great, let's hear it.
I tracked down that guy that
was there before… my button guy.
He moved his operations up to Canada.
You believe that? Canada, of all places?
Canada's cold. Coats need buttons.
I met some Canadians in the Army.
They put cheese curds on top of fries.
-Is that even legal?
-[SCOFFS]
And they put the queen on their money.
Not even their own queen. Someone else's.
What'd he say about the place?
Come here. Come here.
There's something
sketchy going on in the back.
I know there's something
-But he doesn't know what it is.
-I know what it is.
It's a gambling operation.
Oh.
Well, then you know more than he does.
This has been incredibly helpful.
Do you mind if I tell him
about the gambling operation?
He'd get a big kick out of that.
Knock yourself out. Come on, Ethan.
Hey, what's with the attitude?
You're the one that signed the lease
with some old guy who
was speaking in tongues.
He was speaking Chinese,
and, yeah, it was pretty stupid.
-I'm hungry.
-I know.
-Daddy…
-Did the Canadian button guy
at least say anything about the owner?
Is it the old guy who showed us around?
-Said he never met him.
-Perfect.
I'll be back later.
-[ESTHER BABBLING]
-Come on, Ethan.
I'm hungry.
Lunch is at Mommy's today, kiddo.
-Hang on for 20 minutes.
-There's Mommy.
We're going to Mommy's.
Mommy's at her apartment.
-There's Mommy.
-You got to learn a new song, buddy.
Mommy!
What the hell?
MAN: Uh…
What, you sick of your
own wife's underwear?
BEATNIK: I mean, open your eyes.
It's over for the Village.
It's a bunch of tourists
with their goddamn Kodaks
looking for junkies and
"poets" to take a picture of.
Now, now, you go to
Reggio, it's not poetry…
MADELINE: Zelda, this coffee's stale.
-We'll need fresh.
-Right away, Miss Madeline.
Second time I've asked.
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
BEATNIK 2: What else do you have?
Take a stand, man.
-Anti-industrialization.
-Now you're talking.
See, that's where Stalin was 100% wrong.
Total bullshit that
accelerating industrialization
was gonna make conditions fertile
for communism and shared wealth…
-Papa?
-ABE: Ah, thank God.
A familiar face.
-What is happening?
-I don't know.
I think they're breeding.
And you let a banjo in the house.
They snuck that in here.
I don't know how.
This is a banjo-free zone, guys.
Please tell me they're
not using my bathroom.
They're not using any bathroom.
-They're using your bathroom.
-What? For crying out…
Hey, I told you to use
the super's bathroom
-in the basement!
-I walk into the wrong apartment?
Depends on how you feel about
overthrowing the government.
Zelda?!
Could you take the kids to their room?
After she pours the coffee, dear.
Now, if you don't mind.
♪ Which side are you on? ♪
Zelda?
-Zelda.
I… I'm sorry. Yes, yes.
♪ Which side are you on? ♪
-EZRA: You know…
-What?
This may not be the best
environment for a young child.
♪ Oh, workers, can you stand it? ♪
-Well, we're out of everything.
-Except smelly beatniks.
You'll contextualize all
this for me another time?
Sure, if I ever figure it out.
So, before I go, thought
you might want to see this.
Oh, my God, what is this?
It was taped to one of the guys' lockers.
-Came out of some local paper.
-This is the USO show.
You wanted to give the boys a peek
at what they're fighting for?
The wind blew up out of nowhere.
Lighting's good.
Your underwear really glows.
[STAMMERS] I didn't even
know they took a picture.
And the angle. Pretty sexy.
It's not funny. Why is it sticky?
Neither one of us wants to know.
[SIGHS] How did she let this happen?
-Who?
-Susie.
She's off her game. Distracted.
Aren't I dealing with enough right now?
Come on. I've got some stuff for the kids
you're gonna want at your place.
I specifically asked that you
people not use the bathroom.
-I specifically…
-They're both asleep.
Thank you, Zelda.
♪ Which side are you on? ♪
[WHISPERING] So, this is phase one.
Extra blankets, extra toys.
Ethan has different
toys for different seasons.
You have different bobby
pins for different seasons.
Touché.
Moving out must be weird.
Lived in this building all my life.
On top of all the logistics
of getting ready for the road,
I'm saying goodbye to
a really pretty apartment.
Again.
And then tomorrow, there's…
There's what?
Court, for the divorce.
It's being finalized tomorrow.
That soon? I thought it was later.
It was, but with the tour
and all, we got it moved up.
It's tomorrow at 3:00.
Right.
Okay.
Good thinking. Get it done.
It is good. Good to get it over with.
Yeah. So I'll see you there.
-Where?
-At the proceeding.
-Tomorrow, three o'clock, right?
-Joel, this is just a formality.
They stamp a piece of paper.
You don't have to go.
I got you into this, I'll
see it through to the end.
You sure?
It's just a stamp on a piece of paper.
It's more than that.
I know.
I'll see you at 3:00.
[DISTANT] ♪ Which side are
you on, which side are you on? ♪
[MUSIC PLAYING FAINTLY]
-You're late.
-No, I'm not.
-You mind?
-Mush it.
Okay. You usually don't
like me mushing your stuff.
[SIGHS]
I've been waiting ten minutes.
I'm early. I'm two minutes early.
I was ten minutes early.
♪♪
Enjoying your soup?
It's a bit salty today.
-Yeah, you and the soup.
-What?
I thought we were eating together.
I thought we were just meeting.
We eat when we come to the Stage Deli.
It's a restaurant.
You weren't specific.
Hey, let's start the meeting.
-Shall we?
-Fine.
So, I've been talking a
bunch to Shy's guy Lou.
The more I talk to him,
the more I'm convinced
the train has left the station,
but everyone I talk to
seems like that, so whatever.
I'm not distracting you, am I?
What is that?
You haven't seen it?
-That you?
-It's a whole lot of me.
-That's the USO.
-The soldiers tip you off?
What is this, the Daily Mirror?
They shouldn't have printed this.
Why is it sticky?
Someone should have stopped them.
-Who, me?
-Who else? Verla?
Hey, don't pull me into the middle
of your fucking bicker-fest.
-I got my own problems.
-We're not bickering.
I can't control everything.
We're not talking about
changing the course of an asteroid,
Susie, we're talking
about having some control
over my image.
Well, what could I
have done to stop this?
Check every picture that every
photographer took that day?
There must have been at
least a half a dozen of 'em.
Well, you should figure something out.
Fine. I'll figure something out.
I mean, forget about me, I'm
not important, but Sophie Lennon,
she wants total control over her image.
She told me so herself,
so if there's a cheesecake
photo of her out there,
she is gonna be pissed.
Look, the only cheesecake
photo Sophie Lennon's gonna have
out there is a picture of her eating
a giant fucking
cheesecake, and I don't think
guys are gonna be rubbing
their willies over that.
She doesn't eat cheesecake.
It would be a picture of her
making someone else eat
cheesecake, then her
being judgmental about it.
But you'll learn.
Anyway, everything's set
for the first month of the tour.
I have to go.
-Really?
-I thought we'd be done by now.
You haven't even finished your soup.
Hand me my stuff?
Keep me posted.
Sure. Maybe we can have a meeting.
♪♪
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
[MAN SHOUTS IN DISTANCE]
OSCAR [IN DISTANCE]:
Everything well, Chester?
CHESTER: Everything's well, Mr. Lehman.
OSCAR: Very good.
[MAN SHOUTS INDISTINCTLY]
OSCAR: Everything well, Landry?
-Everything's well, Mr. Lehman.
-Very good.
-[BELL RINGING]
-JOHN: Rosie's stepping out!
HELDA: Rosie's going out!
EMPLOYEE: Rosie's leaving the building!
ROSE: Oscar!
-[LAUGHS]
-Rosie! Hello.
Hello.
Mind your step, now.
It's treacherous territory out here.
It's nothing I'm not used to.
Got gopher holes in New York City now?
No, but I grew up out here, don't forget.
[MAN SHOUTING IN DISTANCE]
-[CHUCKLES]
-Everything well, Joseph?
-Everything's well, Mr. Lehman.
-Very good.
Now, Rosie, you should
be lying down, resting.
Oh, I've been resting
ever since I got here.
I need to talk to you.
How's our little Miriam?
Terrible thing about her marriage.
Well, she's coping. She's a strong girl.
Strong? Where'd she get that?
Oh, I don't know. Grandmama, I suppose.
-Everything well, Landry?
-Everything's well, Mr. Lehman.
Very good. And Abe?
Last time I saw him, he was crumpled
-at the foot of the stairs.
-Oh, he's fine.
-Miracle he didn't break his neck.
-He knows how to roll.
Still blaming the staircase for the fall?
Well, the staircase is very
close to the guest room door.
-He wasn't expecting that.
-But he had come up, though.
I mean, he had come up the stairs.
It was the middle of the
night and it was quite dark.
I… It's the same stairs that
bring you up that take you down.
I know.
Surprised he didn't blame
the floor for hitting him.
-It's all forgotten.
-Well,
if he chooses to come back,
we'll put him on the ground floor.
He just has to mind the
stairs coming up from the drive.
-Can he handle those?
-I think he can.
-There's three of 'em.
-I know.
Third one's a doozy.
Well, here it is.
The spot where
Grandmama set down to rest.
Eternally.
They don't make gals like that anymore.
-We owe everything to her.
-[SIGHS]
So, little Rosie wants to talk?
Yes, I do.
It's the trust fund, Oscar.
I've been getting the
same amount for years,
and now I need a little more?
Figured that's what this was about.
I wouldn't ask if I didn't need to.
Rosie, do not be nervous.
I've already called a special meeting
of the trust board for later today.
It's pro forma. You will go home happy.
-Really? Oh, thank you, Oscar.
-Now, excuse me,
but I've got to get back to work.
Oh, of course. I'm interrupting.
Morning, Carlos. Everything well?
-Everything's well, Mr. Lehman.
-Very good.
Everything well, Bo?
BO: Everything's well, Mr. Lehman.
OSCAR: Very good.
[PHONE RINGS]
-Hello.
-SUSIE: Hey, Ethan,
-it's Susie. How's it hanging?
-Good.
-Ah… put your mother on.
-Okay.
Mommy, it's Susie!
-Yep?
-Just, uh,
calling to remind you about
the photo session today.
-4:00 sharp.
-I know. I'll be there.
It's three hours 'cause it's everything.
Uh, headshots, publicity
photos, the whole works.
Time's gonna be tight.
You got outfits picked?
-I'm bringing three.
-Good.
We can meet early so we can talk about…
I can't meet early. I'll be in court.
-You get arrested again?
-For my divorce.
-Before the photos?
-I told you I was doing this.
-I don't think you did.
-Maybe I should've called Sophie
and told her what my
schedule is, and she could have
told you, and then you'd remember.
No, that wouldn't be a
good system, Miriam.
And you got to do it today?
Susie, I don't want to fly
back in the middle of the tour
and miss shows to get this done.
I've got to do it now.
Okay. It's just, I made
a nonrefundable down
payment to the photographer.
It'll happen, unless you
keep me on the phone.
Okay, go, but you better
not cry and fuck up your face.
I won't. I'll see you later.
JUDGE: And who took these pictures?
LAWYER: Oh, the pictures
were taken by a man
hired by Mrs. Daly to
follow Mr. Daly, Your Honor.
Meaning a private investigator
licensed by the state
of New York, I assume.
-Correct, Your Honor.
-Very good.
-Mrs. Daly was forced…
-It should just be another minute.
-He's wrapping up here.
-Great. Thank you, Leslie.
Another minute.
You okay?
Okay-ish. And you?
I wore the wrong tie.
-What's the right tie?
-I don't know.
-Not this one.
-Hey.
-Susie.
-I know you don't want me here,
I just got to get you to that photo shoot.
We on time?
Why is this judge talking so slow?
Has he been talking
this slow the whole time?
Someone need to put
another quarter in him?
I don't need a fucking babysitter.
Actually, princess,
you kind of fucking do.
You her lawyer? You talk fast?
-Let's hear you talk.
-Jesus.
Hi, Susie.
-That's not our relationship.
-Go wait outside.
CLERK: Calendar number nine.
-Maisel v. Maisel.
-SUSIE: Good.
Go, go, go.
Is she going into labor or something?
Let's just do this before she
has a complete conniption.
Judge Wagaman, good afternoon.
My name is Leslie Nunberg,
and I'm representing
Miriam Maisel in this matter.
Well, good afternoon,
Mr. Nunberg, Mrs. Maisel.
-Good afternoon.
-So these proceedings
were originally scheduled
for a couple months from now,
but they've been moved up.
Yes, Your Honor.
There were extenuating circumstances.
And we thank you for your understanding.
-Yes. Thank you, Your Honor.
-So let's jump in here.
Now, I've read the affidavits
and they look straightforward
and in order, so this
shouldn't take long.
Yes.
We need silence from the gallery, please.
And I see no indication that
Mr. Joel Maisel is contesting this.
-That's right, Your Honor.
-I asked for silence.
I'm sorry, Your Honor. I'm Mr. Maisel
and I was just… Sorry about the tie.
-Mr. Maisel? You're the husband?
-I am, yes.
What are you doing here?
Are you contesting?
No, sir, I'm not contesting.
-Then why are you here?
-Just moral support for my wife.
-While she divorces you.
-That's right.
-For adultery.
That's very modern. It's almost French.
But now all this seems a
little less straightforward.
Your Honor, the arrangement
between Mr. and Mrs. Maisel
is completely amicable.
Well, that'd be a first.
Well, they are ready to move forward.
Ah, I'm not so sure of that.
The couple before you,
th… they were at each other's throats.
That's the norm.
It seems like the two of
you are something different,
and I want to make sure you're
not making a mistake here.
-Ticktock, ticktock.
-Quiet!
We are not making a mistake, Your Honor.
But your husband is here
lending moral support.
Explain to me how that fits into this?
It doesn't.
Joel, get the fuck out of here.
Hey, you're the one who's
not supposed to be here.
Whoa! Order, right now.
Who is this person?
That is my manager, Your Honor.
Manager? Of what?
Your Honor, I'm a performer, a comedian,
and I'm about to go on the road.
-Comedian? Why?
-Yes. I don't sing.
Your Honor, she's downplaying this.
She's going on the road with Shy Baldwin.
-It's a huge thing.
-And you're okay with this?
-I am.
-You both seem okay with everything.
-We are.
-Which brings me back to my point.
-Why are you divorcing?
-[GROANS]
I just can't be a wife right now.
Okay. But what about your children?
Ethan,
and Esther.
Are they going on the road with you?
-No. I'm taking care of them.
-But you're the father.
-I know.
-He's the father.
-What am I missing here?
-The fucking photo shoot.
-MIDGE: He's the father,
he's going to take care of the kids.
You're not missing anything.
Okay. [CLEARS THROAT]
Last try. Take some time.
Cool down. Rethink things.
Come back later.
No, they're ready.
Come on, and talk faster.
I want you gone from this courtroom.
Look, I didn't just commit
adultery once, okay?
I slept with a ton of other women.
-Had 'em lined up from here to Sheboygan.
-What?
-Just go with me here.
-Really?
-Yes.
-I'm one of them, Your Honor.
We had a hot, sexy thing going on.
I'm talking dungeon stuff, barnyard stuff.
He's a bad guy.
You should go ahead and
grant that lady a divorce.
-Go on. Bang the gavel.
-Susie, sit down.
The two of you, I would grant
a divorce, no questions asked.
Now, everybody, just clam up, okay?
Look, if you two don't want
more time to think about it,
I can't force you.
The petition for divorce is granted.
Next case.
-Thank you, Your Honor.
-Yes, thank you, Your Honor.
Yes, thank you. I'm… I'm leaving.
WAGAMAN: Let's proceed here.
Next case, please.
CLERK: Yes, Your Honor.
Calendar number 11.
Livingston v.
The Estate of Jonathan Gregorio.
WAGAMAN: Very good.
Now, if I remember correctly,
this was delayed from December.
Are all the…
Oh, will you two leave, please?
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
OSCAR: Have a seat back there, Rosie.
All right, gentlemen.
I call this extraordinary
meeting of the board to order.
Look who we have with us
today, a very special guest,
Little Rosie from the North.
Hello, Rosie.
-ROSE: Hello.
-Hi.
Hello, all. Hello, Liev.
Hello to you, baby sister. Are you well?
I'm very well. Thank you.
-And how's Abe?
-[LAUGHTER]
Abe is fine, Liev. Thank you for asking.
He ever go near a staircase again?
-[LAUGHTER]
-Yes, he uses stairs all the time.
It's a demanding concept, stairs.
He fell that one time, Liev.
Oh, Rosie, we're just teasing you.
We all like Abe.
-What's not to like?
-Don't need that. Thank you.
Now, fellas, Rosie's come
here today with a special request.
Oh, yes, um, I'm here today
-because I just want to ask…
-OSCAR: [CLEARS THROAT] Rosie.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
I will let Oscar explain.
[CLEARS THROAT] Our
little Rosie's here today
because she'd like a little
more money from the trust.
You see, Abe's been fired from his job,
and additional funds are needed
for Rose to maintain her quality of life.
He wasn't fired.
Just to be clear, he's
making a change in his life.
Okay, I stand corrected.
He's making a change in his life.
From employed to unemployed.
[LAUGHTER]
They move his classroom upstairs?
Liev.
Okay, okay, let's just
proceed on this now. Rosie?
Thank you.
Just to elaborate, in my own words…
Nope, I meant: could
you give us the room?
-Why?
-We're about to vote.
LIEV: Votes are done in secret.
Rosie, you know that.
Th… This is a family matter. I'm family.
It's the rule.
Well, how come he gets to stay?
OSCAR: That's Mendel, that's Jacob's boy.
-So?
-He's on the board.
-Yeah!
-ROSE: He's a child.
Yes, and someday he'll be a man.
Plus, Uncle Mordecai retired
and we had an empty seat.
You had two empty seats.
You never filled Grandmama's.
Well, we were gonna
make Mendel Grandmama,
but then Mordecai retired,
and so we made him Mordecai.
And now we're out of men.
-What about me?
-What about you?
I could fill Grandmama's seat.
-[LAUGHTER]
-What, that's funny?
That I deserve to be
considered for the board?
Board seats are filled
by the men of the family.
-You know that.
-Grandmama was a girl.
-Kinda.
-Grandmama started the business.
They had to put her on the board.
Well, how did Mendel earn his seat?
-Oh, come on now, Rosie.
-Come on, what?
Why have I never been
asked to be on the board?
I'm a senior member of the family,
there's an empty chair here
and some dumb little boy.
She's mean. I vote no.
That's not how you make
a decision, you little nitwit.
-Stop.
-Rosie, don't get hysterical.
I'm not hysterical.
LIEV: You live in
New York, little sister.
You don't know a thing
about the business.
I could learn.
I think your learning years
have long passed, Rosie.
He doesn't know anything
about the business either.
Excuse me?
Come on, Oscar, you
walk around the fields
asking workers if things are well.
They say, "Yes." You say, "Very good."
Then you come back inside.
I could do that.
Rosie…
"How are things, Bobby?"
"Well." "Yes." Done. Bye.
Rosie, why don't you go
lay down and let us vote
and give you your goddamn pin money.
-Bad word!
-Shut up, Mendel.
-Pin money?
-You want it or not?
You know what I want.
As a member of this family,
I want a seat on this board.
It doesn't work that way.
As a member of this
family who doesn't eat paste,
-I demand a seat on this board.
-That's not gonna happen.
Then clearly I'm not part of this family.
And since I'm not a part of this family,
I don't want anything
to do with this family.
I don't care how much money
you throw at me, I'm done.
-Rosie…
-It's very simple, if I don't get a say,
I don't want your money!
Any of it!
Come on, Grandmama.
Women aren't welcome here.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER IN DISTANCE]
What the fuck?
[BAT THUDS]
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
Hey!
[CHATTER STOPS]
My name's Joel Maisel.
I'm the sucker that
rented the space upstairs,
and I'm not a cop.
I'm just a guy.
A guy in, uh, in need of information
and, uh, a shower.
Uh, I called the number on the lease,
but it was disconnected.
And there's only a post
office box and it's in Delaware,
so I'm out of options.
Now, I… I need to speak to the owner.
And here's to hoping one
of you understands me.
Thanks.
Carry on.
[CHATTER RESUMES]
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
-Hello there.
-Don't look at me.
-I saved you a spot.
-You should have saved me two spots.
-What are you talking about?
-This. This.
I look like one of my
father's prize heifers.
Imogene, you look just
like you did before the baby,
tiny and perfect.
CLAIRE: Ladies, take your place.
-Doesn't she look great?
-Glad you're here, Imogene.
Everyone, arms to the sky.
Rag doll down.
Shake it out.
The divorcees are out in force, I see.
-The new moms, too.
-Saved you a spot.
Thanks, but no thanks, Isabelle.
Now pick up your Hula-Hoops and… pulse.
So what was the urgency
to come here today?
Well, I heard how you let yourself go,
and I had to see it for myself.
-That's not funny.
-I have to get in shape for this tour.
Oh, I want to hear more about the tour.
-And to the right.
-It's 18 cities.
And to the left.
And again.
18 cities? Wow.
You'll send me 18 postcards?
-Of course.
-CLAIRE: Arms, ladies.
Write down everything you experience.
Everything you see and hear and eat.
[GASPS] No, wait, not eat.
CLAIRE: And change.
You can't get fat from
reading about food, Imogene.
You aren't a scientist.
Now grab your isometric cords, ladies.
I hope your weird little troll
of a manager's going with you.
You need a guard dog.
Things happen on the road, dirty things,
-and write them all down, please.
-Mount your boards.
-Yes, Susie's going.
-Why the tone?
CLAIRE: And twist.
We're on the outs right now.
She took on a new client, Sophie Lennon.
Wow, Sophie Lennon, that's big.
I hate Sophie Lennon.
Oh, right, we hate Sophie Lennon.
I forget that.
CLAIRE: Figure eights down.
It was just too much too soon,
her taking on Sophie.
I need her full-time.
It's like she abandoned me.
Abandoned you?
She dropped you? What a jerk.
No, she's still my manager,
but I shouldn't have to share her.
So you're saying she
makes enough off of just you
that she doesn't need
to have any other clients?
Well, not quite.
I think she only made about
20 bucks off me last year.
-Swing arms.
-So you're saying
she has enough of a savings
to have you as her only client?
Well, not quite.
I don't think she has any savings.
She probably doesn't
even have a bank account.
But going out on tour
opening for Shy Baldwin,
the money's gonna come pouring in, right?
Well, not quite.
It's not even a living for me.
-But Susie gets half, right?
-CLAIRE: And saw.
-Well, not quite.
-IMOGENE: Oh.
But, no, I agree.
You're Miriam Maisel,
you should be enough.
Yeah. I should be enough.
Can you move? I can't see.
I had a baby four weeks ago!
And your husband drinks.
Feel better?
Little bit. Yeah.
ABE: Rose? Rose!
Wonderful, you're back.
I mean, I knew you were coming
back, I looked in your closet,
but sometimes you don't come back.
So it's nice that you came back.
It is you, isn't it?
You don't look like yourself.
Can I get you something?
Something to drink?
Something to eat?
Rose?
I have just come from a travel
odyssey of biblical proportions.
Oh, dear.
Hieronymus Bosch couldn't
have conjured the world
I've inhabited for the past 25 hours.
-Oh, you had a bad flight.
-I suppose you could say that.
My first plane sat on
the tarmac for five hours.
-Oh.
-The second plane hit turbulence
that felt like the very hands of God
were tearing the plane into shreds.
A suitcase fell on my head and
a child threw up on my handbag.
-Oh, your poor handbag.
-We had to land at San Diego,
which is in the opposite
direction of New York City.
So, 12 hours in, I'm
1,300 miles farther away
from where I'm trying
to go, and who is that?
ABE: Oh, that's Ezra.
He had an argument with his old lady.
Just needed a place to
crash for a couple of days.
MIDGE: Is that Mama?
-Is she home?
-Kind of.
From San Diego, all that was available
was a plane to Philadelphia,
so I took that and thought I'd
train from there to New York,
but the boiler men are on strike,
which forced me to take a bus,
where I was groped by
a little man in a fedora.
And, I'm sorry, who is that?
Uh, that's Mr. Curtis.
He's from Columbia.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm just getting some measurements
for the next occupant, a Nobel Laureate.
Exciting stuff for us.
Oh, I'm glad you're
excited, Mr. Curtis, very glad.
Say, are you planning on taking
these drapes with you? They're nice.
Yes, we're taking the
drapes with us, Mr. Curtis.
We're taking anything
and everything of value
which we could possibly hock,
or in the case of drapes,
make into clothing.
I don't understand.
I'm gonna have to get
some Butterick patterns.
May I use that to measure
my husband for pants?
Did the family not extend you more money?
Whoa. Mama, what happened to you?
What happened to me?
My condescending, sniggering
family was so goddamn awful,
I gave up my trust fund entirely.
That's what happened to me.
-I'm sorry, what?
-I gave up the money. I don't want it.
It's blood money.
-But…
-But what?
Well, Rose, we need that money.
We can't live without that money.
What's a little blood?
That money was a yoke. Now I am unyoked.
Untethered. Free.
I don't believe this.
What?
Miriam, what… what don't you believe?
You. Th… The both of you.
You quit Columbia,
you lose the apartment.
You go to beef up your trust fund,
you come back without a trust fund.
I mean, what is going on with you two?
What's going on?
Did you say "What's going on?"
-No.
-I'll tell you what's going on.
You.
You are what's going on with us. You.
Me?
Everything that's
happening is all your fault.
I was very happy being me.
I didn't need to be equal
or stand up for myself.
I was fine.
I have gone my entire
life with other people
making all my decisions, and I loved it!
You, you put this in my head.
You made me passionate and independent
and broke!
You're welcome.
Sorry, it was just sitting there.
I think it's really cool
she gave up that money.
Shut up, Ezra.
I don't know.
I don't know, this just feels too stuffy.
-Is it too stuffy?
-JACKIE: I like it.
Fits you nice.
I like the tailored look on you.
Usually, your stuff's so
baggy, you can't see your figure.
I still don't understand
why the fuck you're here.
This was the move-in date you gave me.
I told you Wednesday the 13th.
I heard Wednesday.
You know, your sheets are like sandpaper.
I'm gonna burn those sheets,
with you possibly still in 'em.
Oh, that reminds me. Midge called.
-What? When?
-About an hour ago.
Woke me from a sound sleep.
She said she's gonna meet up with you
at whatever this
party is you're going to.
Great.
So I guess we're not going together.
Fine.
What? You need her to
hold your hand or something?
No, I don't need her to hold my hand.
I'll go with you if you want.
I'll push you around in
a fucking baby stroller.
I'm fine by myself.
My mantra since I was three.
Good for you.
Hit the light on your way out.
Mm, my pleasure.
Can't open the door with the bed down.
Can't put the bed up without you
seeing me buck-fucking-naked.
Quite the conundrum.
["COME ON BACK, JACK" BY
NINA SIMONE PLAYING IN DISTANCE]
♪ I didn't know I'd miss you so ♪
♪ But, baby, I was wrong ♪
♪ Those nights without your love ♪
♪ They ain't worth thinking of ♪
♪ Come on back, Jack ♪
♪ Hey, Jack, come on, come on back ♪
♪ Oh, woman, save your breath ♪
♪ Little woman, save your breath… ♪
-REGGIE: Susie Myerson?
-Yeah?
Of Susie Myerson and Associates?
-Yeah.
-Really?
-Who are you?
-I'm Reggie.
Shy's manager. We need to talk.
I guess I can take a
break from all the fun.
♪ They ain't worth thinking of ♪
♪ Come on back, Jack… ♪
So, are you gonna be
something happy in my life
or something unhappy?
I look after my girl.
That's all you got to know.
-And what's your girl like?
-Hey, isn't Lou Shy's manager?
Lou?
[GIGGLES] No.
Lou's the white guy that record
labels are willing to deal with.
Lou's the white guy that
Nabisco likes to talk to
when they want Shy to front for 'em.
Lou is the white guy
that glad-hands mayors
when they want my man to
get a key to the city. Lou's…
-White. I got it.
-Yeah.
-Lou's extraordinarily white.
-So, listen to me,
Susie Myerson and Associates.
I run things. You get me?
-Sure.
-So you gonna be talking back like that?
I'm not talking back, I said "Sure."
Everything goes through me.
-I am the god at the gate.
-Got it.
-You gonna keep talking back?
-I'm not talking back,
-I'm just talking.
-Let me tell you what kind
of manager I am, Susie
Myerson and Associates.
I've been looking after
Shy since we were kids
tossing rocks in vacant lots.
We was running numbers
for Stephanie St. Clair
before we were ten.
When he found his singing,
I collected the money,
kept him out of trouble, kept
people from bumping him.
I'll be at his side when
he draws his last breath
unless I get there first.
I would lay down my life for him.
That's what's going on here. You hear me?
You don't hear me?
Fucking afraid to say anything.
It's been a good meeting.
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER, LAUGHTER]
-You got any questions?
-Mm.
I got one, if it's okay.
Uh, we had these pictures taken.
I got the proof sheets, but I
need money to have 'em printed.
So go get yourself some money.
I thought you guys could front the money.
Do I look like your grandma?
Why would I hand you money?
She doesn't have any
professional pictures.
Then you should go get her some.
I can't without money.
Look, it was not my idea
to have some fluffy
white girl open for my boy,
but this was Shy's call,
and now it lands on me.
Reggie, nothing's landing on you.
Sticking a five-dollar bill
in your pocket for cab fare
is how "Let Uncle Lou" does it.
It's not how I do it.
You bring me receipts, and I
tell you what gets reimbursed.
Fine. I think this is coming back around
-to "you run things" again.
-Good.
You were listening.
Look, when she gets here,
will you at least meet her?
-She is fluffy, but you'll like her.
-[LAUGHTER]
Isn't that her?
SHY: [LAUGHS] I swear
that night was cursed.
[LAUGHTER]
This was at the Half Note,
and this girl named Sandra…
Yeah.
All I meant was I wanted to introduce you.
I know where my boy is at all times.
SHY: …was giving him the
stink eye the whole night.
[LAUGHTER]
Then, we got one more encore, right?
So Billy whips around
to empty his spit valve,
and empties it right on Cab Calloway.
-[OOHING]
-MIDGE: That's disgusting.
You know, that cat's always smiling,
but he wasn't smiling this time.
[LAUGHTER]
The cat sent me the
dry cleaning bill, too.
Thank you for that, boss, I owe you.
And this is Slim.
-[OOHING]
-Ah, Slim.
-Faithful to a fault.
-I knew this was coming.
-SHY: Loyal, royal Slim…
-He'll never get over this.
Left me for six months to go out
with that Southern boy, what's his name?
The… The kid with the hips
who stole our people's sound?
[LAUGHTER]
-Elvis!
-Elvis.
SHY: Then he regained his senses…
And the true king was kind
enough to allow me to return.
-All right.
-[CHEERING, APPLAUSE]
So, Midge Maisel, that's the group.
And, group, this is Midge Maisel.
This is a funny lady.
Stand up, Midge, so they can pay respect.
SLIM: Hey, Midge, welcome to the family.
Hello, all. Nice to meet you.
Thank you for making me
feel like one of the gang.
[CHEERING, APPLAUSE]
[RHYTHM AND BLUES PLAYING FAINTLY]
[PHONE RINGS]
You again.
-Me again.
-I got the note.
Thanks for meeting with me.
No English?
Sit.
Your name is Joel Mai-sel?
It's Maisel. Accent on the "Mai."
Hmm. That's my name.
-Maisel?
-Mei.
My name is Mei.
Okay. Hi.
-[LAUGHS]
-What's funny?
-You thought my name was Maisel.
-Can we get on with this?
These are the owners.
-What are their names?
-You couldn't pronounce them.
-What's this for?
-To forget what you saw.
No, no, no. I don't want money.
That's not why I wanted to meet.
-[SPEAKS CHINESE]
-I just need to know
how this is going to work.
[SPEAKS CHINESE]
And they're definitely the owners?
Yes.
It's a gambling parlor, right?
[SPEAKS CHINESE]
-Yes.
-Is it legal?
[SPEAKS CHINESE]
Look, I'm opening a club.
It'll be music, comedy.
I'm going after a liquor license,
and I just need to know
if there could be raids
or the FBI knocking down
the door or something like that.
Don't worry about that.
That won't happen.
How can you be so sure?
The cops on the beat,
they don't care about us.
They only come when
there's a murder or something.
Has there been a murder?
[SPEAKS CHINESE]
MEI: That was a joke.
They're actually very funny people.
They're putting you on.
There's been no murder, no.
So my club's gonna be okay?
I'm not gonna bust my ass
building it into a success
to just have it all fall apart.
[LAUGHS]: Oh, it's not
gonna be successful.
What?
[SPEAKS CHINESE]
[LAUGHTER]
-Wait, what, what'd you say?
-I told them what you said.
The club will work.
I'm gonna make it work.
No, see, you're perfect for us
because you'll have
very few customers, see?
That's not true. I'm gonna make money.
[SPEAKS CHINESE]
[LAUGHTER]
I am.
[SPEAKING CHINESE]
They're asking if you're gonna stay,
'cause if not, they'll
rip up the lease and find
some other money-losing
business to come in.
I'm staying. Okay? I'm staying.
And I'm gonna make money off of this.
You'll see.
[LAUGHTER]
Wait, that was English.
They understand English.
[SPEAKS CHINESE]
Are they really the owners?
See you around, Maisel.
[SIGHS]
[RHYTHM AND BLUES PLAYING IN DISTANCE]
-Hey.
-How long you been here?
-A while.
-I didn't see you.
-Yeah, I was in the other room.
I could see you over where you were.
Yeah, as soon as I got here,
Shy kind of pulled me into his group.
That's good, that he
included you like that.
You should get to know him.
Yeah, it was nice of him.
This is such a beautiful place.
Yeah, must have a
pretty interesting history.
Ooh, yeah, definitely.
Look, Miriam, I can't take this.
I'm weird with a lot of people,
and it's fine, I don't care,
but it's too fucking weird to
be weird with you. I can't do it.
If this is how it's
gonna be, then fuck it,
I won't manage her, a… and
I'm fine with that, really.
So… these are the proof
sheets from the session.
I circled the ones I thought were good.
See what you think.
I never thought you
could take a bad picture,
but there's some really
bad pictures of you in here.
Most of 'em are really good.
Just have to figure out
how I'm gonna print them,
but it's gonna happen
and it's gonna be great.
Susie, I want you to have "Associates."
I want you to have a suite of
offices and windows with views
and a sign out front and
someone fetching your coffee.
I want you to have your own car…
and a driver
'cause you are a bad fucking driver.
I want you to have a big apartment
with hot water and a
closet full of blazers.
I want you to have a bank account.
I can deal with Sophie Lennon.
You'll always be my number one.
♪ Love, love, love! ♪
We are the whitest people in the world.
♪ Day after day ♪
♪ I must face a world of strangers ♪
♪ Where I don't belong ♪
♪ I'm not that strong ♪
♪ It's nice to know ♪
♪ That there's someone I can turn to ♪
♪ Who will always care ♪
♪ You're always there ♪
♪ When there's no getting over ♪
♪ That rainbow ♪
♪ When my smallest of dreams ♪
♪ Won't come true ♪
♪ I can take all the madness ♪
♪ The world has to give ♪
♪ But I won't last a day ♪
♪ Without you ♪
♪ So many times when
the city seems to be ♪
♪ Without a friendly face ♪
♪ It's a lonely place ♪
♪ It's nice to know
that you'll be there ♪
♪ If I need you ♪
♪ And you'll always smile ♪
♪ It's all worthwhile ♪
♪ When there's no getting over ♪
♪ That rainbow ♪
♪ When my smallest of dreams ♪
♪ Won't come true ♪
♪ I can take all the madness ♪
♪ The world has to give ♪
♪ But I won't last a day ♪
♪ Without you ♪