ANNIE: Previously on Good Girls...
SARA: I got fired from tutoring.
They said I took their stupid pen.
She's not me.
I tried to seduce my therapist.
He straight up rejected me.
You have a storied history
of pursuing inaccessible men,
which is a defense mechanism
to protect you from rejection.
You're gonna like her.
She has birds.
"Bye."
So we wanted to talk
to you about doing some
custom work for us.
Casino night.
LUCY: /f it got into the wrong hands,
it's kinda, like, counterfeit.
That did not even occur to me.
He's alive. I'm dead!
Word is, you do the best work.
I'd like to see how it's done.
What do you think?
I think I need you alive.
Customer's here for you.
Who is it?
Lewis baby shower.
I'll be right there.
Congratulations, Mr. Lewis.
Everything in order?
You'll Know if it isn't.
THUG: Yo.
Welcome to the Paper Porcupine.
Here for the Shapiro bris announcements.
Of course, Mr. Shapiro.
Back-to-school night, right?
Northfield Christian Academy.
Back in a jiffy.
MICK: Morning, sunshine.
Wow, they don't build them
like this anymore.
Pickup's not today.
Is this where the ink goes?
Oil.
(CAMERA CLICKING)
Can I help you with something?
Please...
Please don't do that.
Okay, my bad.
What tension do you set the rollers at?
Why?
Just curious.
'Cause I'm a Curious guy.
Well, you could look at the manual,
but there isn't one because
this is older than the Bible.
(CHUCKLES)
See you soon.
RUBY: Ew.
They didn't give me a knife.
I don't want your grubby-ass
house key on my BMT.
Gym locker key.
Gross.
I barely use it.
Why didn't you just get two six-inch?
Because the foot-long comes
with chips and a drink.
All good, thanks.
You know, I would love
to be rolling in six-inchers,
but instead I am working
my ass off for nothing.
Yeah, 'cause I just love being
homey's indentured servant.
Coming home covered in ink
and self-loathing.
Where is she?
Voila.
Thanks.
Lock the doors.
What?
Hit the locks.
But they don't work.
They're broken.
What's going on?
Take this home and hide it somewhere.
Why?
And only take it out when we're printing.
What is happening right now?
This is insurance.
For what?
Anyone can run a printer, right?
But you need these plates
to make our money,
so if one of us disappears...
Why would we disappear?
When he's done with us.
Jesus.
Yeah.
Oy.
You guys get me a sandwich?
Yeah.
(SIGHS)
(SARA LAUGHING)
(STAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Oh, my God, Sara.
What are you doing?
Two fingers? Really?
So much cream cheese.
(LAUGHS)
STAN: (STAMMERS)
It's a lot of cream cheese.
What's all this?
Hey, baby.
Got you poppy seed.
They have chocolate cream cheese.
STAN: I'm sorry, did you just put that
with your lox?
No! Oh!
(LAUGHS)
How long you guys been awake?
Uh, baby girl wanted to go
to the early-morning service.
She did, did she?
STAN: Yeah, I didn't wanna wake you.
Daddy said you worked late.
Now...
Lil' Money, he still in there sawing logs.
I went in there with his video game music,
put it to the boy's ear. Nothing.
You could have woke me up.
STAN: Where's that chocolate stuff?
SARA: I put it in the fridge.
STAN: Okay, I see what you doing.
Trying to keep your own stash.
(CHUCKLES)
Okay, now, I'm gonna put
this stuff under his nose,
and if this sugar shock
doesn't wake that boy up,
nothing will.
Oh, Harry!
So you just found God?
What?
Game recognize game, peanut.
I'm just saying.
STAN: Nope, that didn't work.
Okay. Oh, time to pull out the big guns.
(WATER RUNNING)
(MOANING)
(PANTING)
Break's over.
Go again?
You can do that?
Yeah. I'm like a chick.
Let's just leave it on a high note.
Hey, uh, can I...
And I'm not complaining, but, uh...
What's happening here?
I'm getting over someone
by getting in front of someone else.
Cool?
Happy to help.
Good man.
Hey, uh, do you mind
if we just do it at your place next time?
I have a kid.
Yeah, and I have this,
like, back thing, and tiles just...
Okay. So we'll go to your place.
We already did that.
You live in your car.
(SIGHS) That's kinda how I got
this back thing.
You're homeless.
I'm experiencing homelessness.
Got it.
You mind if I take a shower here?
We don't have a shower.
The sink?
Thank you.
(SIGHS)
Wake... Wake up.
What?
What is it?
It's a massacre.
What did you do?
I killed them all.
How much did you feed them?
Too much.
Or not enough.
I don't know.
They're not ready for this.
DEAN: I read about this thing.
They can get an STD.
BETH: Ew, gross.
DEAN: No, it's called sudden tank death.
It's gotta be the water.
I tested it with those little
strip thingies.
One, two, three, up.
Easy.
(SIGHS) We'll just
tell them they were sick
and we took them to the fish doctor.
And pick up some new ones
on the way home from work.
DEAN: They're gonna know.
They're goldfish, Dean.
They all look the same.
DEAN: What's this?
Nothing.
Doesn't look like nothing.
It's for work.
Then why is it hidden
in the laundry room?
Where are those towels?
Is this what you're doing?
Will you flush these?
Are you making money?
Could I get that back?
No.
What do you mean, no?
He didn't waste much time, did he?
Dean...
How do you not see
what's happening here again?
It's different this time.
You're like the damn fish
with a castle thinking it's new.
You don't understand, okay?
Oh, look, a castle.
Oh, look, another castle.
Give it back to me!
No!
(GASPS)
Don't.
We can't go back.
He's gonna kill me.
You don't kill something you love.
(METAL CLATTERS)
MEG: Hey, Beth?
Customer's here for you.
(PRINT CONTINUES WHIRRING)
There's been a bit of a snafu.
You don't say.
The press needed to be serviced.
So we couldn't make your invitations.
It's more than a snafu.
Well, you'll get them.
It'll just be a little bit of a delay.
See, here's the thing.
I get it.
We don't do delays.
I know.
And if that's what I'm looking at here,
then my boss has been
pretty clear on how to handle it.
What if I made it up to you?
Like,
not him, but you?
You mean if I wanted my own invitations?
No event's too big.
It'd be a huge order.
Try me.
Hundred thousand.
Easy-peasy.
I'll hold him off as long as I can.
Thanks again for your understanding.
MAX: Which kind?
The super absorbent ones?
Uh, maybe just get the variety pack.
It only gives you eight of each.
Yeah, that should be fine.
How heavy is your flow?
LUCY: Like, medium.
MAX: I can get you options.
What about pain relief?
How are your cramps?
Babe, I'm fine.
I'll pick up some Midol,
just to take off the edge.
LUCY: Thank you.
That's very sweet.
Oh, bubble bath when I get back?
Only if you join me.
(BOTH LAUGH)
Isn't he awesome?
Like nothing I've ever seen.
Quite a catch.
So, um, remember that project you did
for us a while back?
Mm-hmm.
Well, you did such a great job
that we wanted to hire you again.
Uh, what's the project this time?
You're not gonna believe it.
(CHUCKLES)
It's another casino night.
LUCY: Uh, I can't.
We'll pay you more.
That's not it.
I can cover you at work if it's time
that's an issue or...
I'm not comfortable doing
what you're asking me to do.
It's for a really good cause.
Gambling addicts, right?
I'm so sorry I brought you into this.
Why did you?
Okay, well, let me lay it out
for you, Lucy.
That piece of paper
that you found in the dumpster,
shredded, that's gonna be us.
Yeah, except you won't be
able to tape us back together again.
Hey, babe, I'm gonna pick you up
some pads, too,
'cause I know you hate leaving
those things in overnight.
I'll come with you.
Oh, awesome.
Lucy.
Please.
Just go.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(TV PLAYING INDISTINCTLY)
He's so happy.
Why aren't you in bed?
Shh. It's the finale.
Why isn't she in bed?
Shh. America's voting.
She has school, Stan.
STAN: It's just one night, baby.
Um, tiny country guy with the glasses?
No, old lady who raps.
STAN: (LAUGHING)
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, my God. You should see
this old geezer rhyme.
(TV SHUTS OFF)
Mom!
Woman!
Bed, now.
What the hell's got into you?
Close the door, Stanley.
You know, she finished all her homework.
Oh, I know.
Little heifer's on the honor roll.
She loves animals.
She pops out of bed for church.
You know what else our little angel does?
She takes pens.
Expensive ones.
Yeah, she did it.
(EXHALES)
I Know.
You know what?
She told me.
When?
A while back. (SIGHS)
And you're just cool with it?
No, I'm not cool.
You're not not cool.
You know what I am?
I'm relieved.
The staying up late and the cream cheese?
At least she was too guilty
to live with it.
What are you trying to say, Stan?
(CHUCKLES)
Come on, Ruby.
Wait, you're mad at me now?
When you lie, you sleep like a queen.
We're just lucky she knows the difference.
BETH: This is so wrong.
ANNIE: We gave her a chance.
BETH: She doesn't deserve this.
Well, we tried asking nicely,
so now It's either this
or the funeral home.
I want to make it very clear
that we have hit a new low, even for us,
and once you cross over,
you don't come back the same.
Do it already.
We've done worse.
What's it gonna be, baby girl?
(SIGHS) Go.
Go.
What if she kills him?
She can't.
Oh, believe me, she can.
He's no good to us dead.
I meant by accident.
How much time do we have left?
I don't know.
What do you mean?
I hit lap timer.
What's a lap timer?
I don't know.
(BIRD CHIRPING)
Well, what if we add up all the laps?
I'm afraid to stop it.
Lucy said he only power walks
for 10 minutes.
Oh, God, I'm sorry.
It's okay. It'll be fine.
No, it's not.
Stan's gonna leave me.
Come on. Why?
This. Literally this.
Birds?
Birds. Bodies. Robberies.
It's ruining our marriage.
He loves you.
He will get over it.
He always does.
That's the thing.
He's okay with it.
This is who he thinks I am now.
Oh, God.
It'll be okay.
No, he's back.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Come on, girl.
Get out of there.
RUBY: Let's go, Annie.
Come on.
BETH: Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on.
Oh, goodness. Where is she?
Where is she? Where is she?
Does she have it?
Drive.
Why didn't you take the cage, Annie?
Just drive.
(ENGINE STARTS)
(BIRD CHIRPING)
There are matching envelopes in the back
if you need them.
Hi there. Welcome to the Paper Porcupine.
I like your tattoo.
Oh, thank you.
What does it mean?
Well, it's, uh, sort of for this club
that I'm in.
Cool. Super cool.
(CHUCKLES)
I used to sling ink to pay for art school.
Slung ink. Slang?
I think it's slang.
(CHUCKLES)
That's cool.
So you're an artist?
Yeah, I do all the work
design stuff here.
Uh, custom orders, stuff like that.
Oh.
Wait, so you mean, like,
if someone wanted
something special printed,
you would draw it?
But you'd pick the paper, the colors.
Yeah, but you'd draw it?
Yeah, and then we'd make
an engraver's plate
and print it all on-site.
Cool.
Yeah.
Cool, cool, cool.
Yeah, uh, one-stop shop.
Yeah.
You know, that's good, 'cause I'm, um...
I'd really like to get rid
of the person I'm using now.
Really?
Yeah, not so reliable.
Well, won't happen on my watch.
Just let me know if I can help.
Actually, Lucy, I think you can.
Hey. How was school?
That good, huh?
You're mental.
What?
Wait, hey, uh, wait.
Uh, hey, dah-dah-dah!
Don't go in there!
I can't go in the bathroom?
You can, but...
Your boyfriend
just asked me for toilet paper.
Who?
Chris, Kevin?
(SIGHS) Kevin.
He's outside in his car.
Oh, God.
He said he wants to live closer to you now
that you guys are dating.
We are not dating.
He's living on our curb.
He's going through something.
You said you were done with this.
He's homeless!
You're an addict!
Ben, Ben!
We study people like you in psych class.
Ben, Ben, Ben!
(BIRD CHIRPING)
BEN: What the hell?
(SIGHS) It's not mine.
(BIRD CHIRPING)
I don't understand
anything that's going on here.
His name's Au Jus.
Give this to your boyfriend.
BETH: Oh, my God.
RUBY: Damn.
Yeah.
Yeah, I tried to get one
with his head actually
in the disposal, but...
Oh, Jesus.
I didn't do it.
He freaked out every time
I turned him upside down.
How'd you even take these?
Ben's selfie stick.
Are we supposed to show
all of these or just choose the best one?
The one with the carving knife.
See, I don't buy that one.
Well, sorry, Ansel Adams.
What don't you buy?
I don't know.
Maybe if it was scissors or something.
It's just not believable.
Well, here, just scroll to the end.
I did, like, a whole thing
with the microwave and tinfoil.
Let's just stick with the disposal.
She's gonna cave.
Okay.
(ARGUING INDISTINCTLY)
I already had to kidnap a freaking bird.
I'm not doing it.
What's up, ladies?
How we doing, champ?
My hand keeps shaking.
Yeah?
It's okay.
Just take your time.
There's no rush.
She doesn't need to be involved.
Oh, 'cause you can do this?
How about you two?
Don't have the software.
RIO: No?
All this time, I thought
you were the one doing the heavy lifting.
Just let her go.
And here you are
stealing my girl's thunder.
(CHUCKLES)
Ain't bitches supposed to be,
like, lifting each other up these days?
So much for feminism.
(RIO LAUGHS)
Maybe you don't need to be involved.
(DOORBELL CHIMING)
MRS. HARRIS: Hello! Lucy!
It's Mrs. Harris.
I told her I'd stay late
so she could pick up her order.
Go tell Mrs. Harris
that we're closed, okay?
Okay' Okay.
Yeah.
Go with her.
Oh, and...
Be smart, yeah?
MRS. HARRIS:
Oh, my God. (CHUCKLES)
They're almost too beautiful to send.
Wish Henry a happy retirement for us.
Now, what do you
have in the way of place cards?
Uh, we're all out, actually.
What are these?
It says place cards.
Oh, boy.
What do you think would go best?
Blue plaid.
Okay, but the invitations
are red. Should we...
LUCY: Uh, red gingham.
Right here.
Oh! These are perfect!
All right, now, should I just give you
the guest list?
Uh-huh.
MRS. HARRIS:
Okay, great.
Um, definitely the entire office.
We'll start there.
Uh, Bob.
Uh, George.
Uh, Troy, Stanley,
Richard, Ellen, Hakim...
All right, I love you, babe.
Good night, sweetie pie.
Good night, bug.
I'll see you in the morning, okay?
JANE: Daddy?
Yeah?
When do Reddy, Bluey and Greeny get back
from the fish hospital?
Hmm.
It turns out that...
The fish doctors discovered
they have superpowers.
Really?
Yeah, and they were accepted
at a very special fish magic school.
It's half X-Men, half Harry Potter,
but it's top secret, so we can't see them
or visit for a really long time.
Kenny said you flushed them.
Huh.
He saw you do it.
Well, yeah, that's how you get
to the fish school.
The toilet is the portal.
Can we get a different pet?
Fish smell.
Yolanda, Javier, Esme,
Hannah and Tom.
Should I just wait for these?
Friday.
Friday. Perfect.
(CHUCKLES) Thank you.
You cannot finish that plate.
He said he'd let me go.
He won't.
Trust me.
Can I ask you a question?
Like, as a friend?
How could you take Au Jus?
I am ina real situation here.
But I promise you,
I! would never, ever hurt him.
Why would I believe
anything you say anymore?
LUCY: (SIGHS) All done.
Um, feel free to email me any questions,
but it's all on there.
Cool.
Uh, GraphicFarts89@gmail.
I spelled it wrong and then,
uh, got stuck with it.
Come on.
We'll give you a ride.
We can walk.
We have a car.
Let's go.
(KEYS JINGLING)
RIO: All right, rock star.
We'll drop you off wherever you want.
Least we could do.
Lucy, don't.
Here's the thing.
I've been doing this a long time.
The only way someone like you
gets hurt is if you talk.
You're not gonna talk, right?
No.
I got your word?
Cross my heart.
Then you'll never see me again.
Unless I got questions about
that plate, yeah?
GraphicFarts89@gmail.
Ah. (CHUCKLES)
My girl.
All right, who's next?
Wait. Wait!
What kind of packing
are you gonna put on the plates?
What?
What if the press gets too hot?
Not your problem anymore, is it?
How you gonna stop ghost marks
on the rollers?
What happens if you get slur
with the half tones?
It means your ink's too thin.
So even with a perfect plate,
it's gonna look like your son made it.
How long did it take you
to get the security glow?
Um, a while.
You think they sell that color
at Home Depot?
What if you add too much water
to the mulch?
Starch builds up.
BETH: And why don't we like that?
Why don't we like that?
Because the paper won't feel right.
You wouldn't even be able
to pass it off at a bodega.
Just because she gave you a cookbook
to a five-star restaurant
doesn't mean you can make the dishes.
You need the chef.
You need us.
You need all of us.
Nah.
No?
Not all of you.
(GUN FIRING)
Get up.
What?
We gotta do this.
Now?
Get up.
All right.
I'm up. I'm up.
I'm not a lost cause.
What are you talking about?
When you look at me,
I don't know who you see anymore.
I see my wife.
You can't leave me.
She's acting crazy
in the middle of the night.
That's how it happens, you know?
It's not any big thing.
You just wake up one day
and you stop caring
that I don't put the remote back
in the same spot
'cause you just got used
to looking for it.
Well, who says I'm used to it?
I couldn't watch anything tonight.
Marriages don't end, Stanley.
They fade, little by little.
Okay, come here.
You don't even see it happening.
(SNIFFLES)
Until it's over.
Get in here.
Tell me where that remote is,
and we're good forever.
Just don't give up on me.
(DOOR OPENS)
What are you doing?
(SIGHS)
Can I sleep with you?
Aren't I kinda old for this?
Please?
Jordan called an Uber from the mall
and Chris-Kevin picked her up.
Oh, no.
She rode home in his living room.
(SIGHS)
I'll get rid of him.
I'm still mad at you.
Don't be.
Not tonight.
Can we get rid of the bird, too?
It's nesting in the bath mat.
(CHIRPING)
Who's that little guy?
Meet Dorito Boland.
When did you buy a bird?
He's a rescue.
Did you tell the kids yet?
I thought we could surprise them together
after school today.
I wasn't trying to make things worse.
I Know.
I just... I really hate you being around
that guy again.
Me, too.
Really?
So what happened?
Was he pissed?
Yeah.
I told you he won't kill
something he loves.
It's not me, though.
What is it?
Money.
How long's this guy gonna be around?
Um, about 50 years.
We'll have to put him in Our will.
(CHUCKLES)
He's cute.
(DOOR OPENING)
MAX: Beth?
Hey.
Have you heard from Lucy?
She's off today. Why?
She didn't come home last night.
What?
Yeah, cops say it's too early
to do anything.
Maybe she's with friends.
Oh, she didn't really have friends.
Except for you.
Well, keep trying her.
I'm sure she's fine.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
If you hear from her or anything like...
Of course.