BETH: Previously on Good Girls...
We suck up to the gang leader
who we stole from
and convince him to pay us a living wage.
ANNIE: Which we then use
to pay someone else
to blow his brains out.
I am here to see Mr. James Fitzpatrick.
He left something for you.
Eleven thousand in incidentals?
How much cut have you got now?
I don't know.
Where's it all going, Elizabeth?
I can't tell you.
Then, I can't cut you in any more.
I quit my job today.
Why?
DEAN: I kissed my boss.
Hot tubs.
It's not regulated.
Any idiot can sell them.
Welcome to Boland Bubbles.
STAN: This is the crime jar.
Do something good with the money.
I figured out who we should help.
I got their daughter's kidney.
How about a car?
Pardon?
I had him recall the nail polish.
PHOEBE: Nail salon robbed.
Guess what they took.
(OBJECT THUDS, BREAKS)
Get smart, leave school
Grow hard, be cool
Keep it in your head
Don't get in debt
Don't fret or forget
To wish your neighbor well
Ooh, mother, it ain't like
the way you said
Ooh, sister, well it seems
we've been misled
Ooh, baby, is it worth it?
Is it hell
Old lady, you could tell us
So tell us well
(DOOR OPENS, BELL DINGS)
(DOOR SHUTS, BELL DINGS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
How're you doing today?
WOMAN: Better than these guys.
RUBY: Then, you came to the right person.
Let's hope so.
Ooh, mother, it ain't like
the way you said
Ooh, sister, well it seems
we've been misled
Whoa!
RUBY: What do you think?
Bold.
Go red or go home.
Yeah, baby. Go red.
(SPUTTERS) That's just
the name of the polish.
Oh.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
And go easy on the high fives
till you're dry.
Okay. Oh, hey, can I get some change?
Oh, yeah.
Thanks.
Jeez, you gotta check tens now?
You never know what's out there.
Hmm. I wouldn't even
know what to look for.
Oh, there's little tricks.
Obvious stuff.
Security strip. The ink.
But here's the real giveaway.
You see right below little Hammy there?
Mmm-hmm.
Tiny micro print.
Wow. You really know your stuff.
They'll smudge.
I'll be right back.
Thanks.
So, what can I do for you guys?
I guess you could say
we're in the market.
You came back for a hot tub?
We want all of them.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Excuse me?
Uh, we would like
to buy your place, Gayle.
ERIC: Yo, pimp.
Hey.
How's the delivery biz treating you?
Really sucks, Eric.
Word.
I'm not following.
DEAN: So, we took
monthly sales plus the equity
left in the franchise,
we netted out the SG&A costs,
and projected a 5% cash flow growth.
And, according to the National Pool
and Spa Association,
he's being very generous.
DEAN: (SPUTTERS)
That's how we got the number.
It's pretty fair.
Why would I be looking to sell?
Because my husband's looking to buy.
Maybe he should look somewhere else.
Why is that?
You didn't.
Two ways we can handle this.
One, you bow out discreetly
and spend a little time with your family.
What's the other?
Pretty much exactly the same.
Only we would be less discreet
and your family would just hate you
for the rest of your life.
On page three, you'll see we let you
keep the awards.
If I sold,
it would be for way more
than what you're offering.
Try us.
DEAN: Where are we gonna
get that kind of money?
I don't know.
Like, a loan or...
I'll find it.
No. No, no, no, no, no, no...
Why?
If we're doing this, it has to be legit.
Okay.
For real?
I believe in you.
ANNIE: How is that a win-win?
He gets to feel like a man
and we have a new way to wash our cut.
Have you guys seen my phone?
Okay. But in what universe
are they gonna give
a business loan to a Postmates driver?
Whose last business was raided by the FBI.
Do you even have a credit card right now?
(CUTTER RASPING)
I have lots of them.
And they're all maxed out.
How is it just gone?
Look, he's got to believe
this thing is his, okay?
Again, so he can feel like a man.
But, eventually, he'll have
to come to me for the money.
Which we don't have.
Few more runs.
And we'll all be taking steamy Bolands.
I swear I had it this morning.
Well, did you check your purse?
Obviously.
Car?
I looked.
Because your case is
the same color as your seat.
Not in the car.
Find My Phone?
Don't get mad at us.
Yeah, we have our phones.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
Your pocket.
(SOFTLY) My pocket?
You think I didn't check my pocket?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON TV)
(DOOR LOCK CLICKS)
Where have you been?
You likey?
We're done.
Too slutty?
Not slutty enough?
He's pulling the plug.
Why?
Because we don't have anything.
How about the third best pad thai
Detroit has to offer?
It's not enough. (SIGHS)
I'm just so much hotter here.
A DC 6 is like a Detroit 9.
How about this?
Is that hers?
Cute kids.
They're okay.
I'll unpack.
So, how's your system going?
It's...
Good. It's fine.
Just fine?
It's great.
We're almost up and running.
So, how does it work?
What do you mean?
Walk me through it.
Hot tubs are sort of like mattresses.
That right?
Brands aren't apples to apples.
So, there's no way of knowing
what the real price is,
and my books can say anything.
Free delivery?
Whatever the customer wants.
Got my tub the same day.
It's all profit.
You have my cut?
Yeah, about that. Um...
I'm thinking it'd be better business
if you just wash everything on your end.
And like you said,
car wash thing's bad news, right?
Yeah, IRS is all over that.
And we don't want to fight
with Uncle Sam, right?
That guy'll mess you up good.
(CHUCKLES)
But my system is just for me.
RIO: Oh, no, no. No.
Were consolidating.
So, you want me to print and wash?
Mmm.
There's a business term
for that. What is it?
Synergy?
Synergy.
Synergy. That's right.
(CHUCKLES)
So, same time, yeah?
For what?
My cut.
(DOOR OPENS)
RUBY: Please tell me
you've seen my phone.
Nope.
(RUBY SIGHS)
(KEYS JANGLING)
Been looking all day.
Well, maybe it's with all the money
that used to be in here.
Oh. You think 'cause you stashed it
in a Chico's bag at the bottom of the bin,
I wouldn't see it?
They needed a car.
You know what I did to fill this thing?
She put me on the spot, Stan.
All the shady hustles...
Our child wouldn't even be here.
I left my soul in that jar.
Okay. It's my money, too.
Our money.
It went to the right people.
That's not the point.
Okay. What if you had said no?
That's the point.
What?
You didn't give me the chance.
You didn't see her face.
You know what?
You deal with the kids in the morning.
What do you want from me?
I've got a late shift.
Stan.
I want you to be the woman that I married.
I don't even know what that means.
You're paying me back.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
Or what, Stan...
There is no "or what."
Excuse me?
Do it.
Synergy?
What does that even mean?
It means it was never our system.
Flipping his game.
Flipping it again and again.
We've been building it for him.
I mean, it sounds more like
vertical integration.
Just if you wanted to be technical.
Why would you tell him it's operational?
I said almost.
And we needed the cut.
That we didn't get anyway.
Sorry. Is something burning?
BETH: Danny.
I said, out in the driveway.
It's a science project.
Where is the hitman when you need him?
Oh. Let me tell you.
"Rasta pasta at the Rainforest Cafe.
Oat milk lattes at Great Lakes."
He went bananas at Home Depot.
At least he put us back on the schedule.
When?
Well, I don't know.
Because his appointment girl
won't call me back.
How many people is he
booked to kill in a week?
Okay, you know what?
Let's just not freak out
because all we have to dois...
If we take the... We can...
What do we do?
We're going to go old school.
We're going to wash it
little by little till we can
afford to buy the place.
Can't do that.
BETH: Why?
I need it Sooner.
It's not like that bitch has
any other offers coming in.
It's for my marriage.
(ANNIE SIGHS)
I've got a bigger balance
on my Starbucks card.
What's in her email?
Nothing.
It only took me 22 hours
and a case of RedBull to break in.
Texts?
(SIGHS)
Husband, playdates, carpool, church.
Emojis. So many prayer hands.
Mmm. Those are actually
two people high-fiving.
So, when my friend, Melissa,
was at the vet with her cat
who was hit by a car,
I high-fived her like,
"Yay, they got him good"?
Unless she thought they were prayer hands.
How do I know?
What happened to the cat?
She never responded.
You high fived its death.
I mean, who hangs out
with friends this much?
Where'd you eat lunch in high school?
On the bleachers. Why?
Say no more.
You know, none of this is admissible.
Don't need it for court.
(MUFFLED HIP HOP MUSIC PLAYING)
Something wrong with the potato salad?
Nope.
Because it's your mother's recipe.
Already ate.
You could've saved me the trip.
You could have asked me first.
Oh, right.
That's not your thing.
Hey, Ruthy.
Hey.
Ooh. Is that Cherise's potato salad?
Have mine.
Oh, yum.
I have that same cream.
It's yours.
It's so dope, because when you have to
pick up all the money
from the stage, your hands get so dry.
Thank you.
My pleasure.
KRYSTAL: It's super silky.
Oh, I know it is.
KRYSTAL: You know, it feels expensive.
Very.
(CAR HORN HONKS NEARBY)
Hey. Could you tell Neal
I'll be out there in a second?
You bet, Stanimal.
(LOCKER CLICKS)
KRYSTAL: Bye.
(SAFE BEEPING)
I Know you're dying for me to Say,
"You could've asked."
What if you had said no?
Perfect.
I Know how we're gonna wash that money.
We do the traditional square,
but the pillow party box
is also very popular.
I will be right over here
if you have any questions.
We're robbing Stan.
Literally anything else would be better.
Okay. Quick brainstorm sesh.
Okay.
BETH: Okay.
What do you got?
ATM spree.
We hook a chain up to the back of a car...
Then what?
Okay. What about something like the, uh...
the pizza guy with the bomb vest?
Oh, yeah.
But that guy robbed a bank.
Yeah. Yeah.
But, you know, I saw a whole
Netflix documentary about it.
He was in on it, and he walked out
with a huge bag of cash.
And then he got his head blown off.
Oh, I didn't know that part.
I must have fallen asleep at that point.
Ugh. I'm so mad at Stan.
This makes the most sense.
What makes the most sense
is couples therapy.
Not grand larceny.
You didn't see the way he talked to me.
Look, Stanimal aside...
I mean, that place is
pretty much a trash heap.
The whole hell hole
should be burned to the ground.
At this point, I don't
even know who we owe.
Is it a hit man, homeboy, hot tubs?
So, whatever, I'm down.
BETH: I just don't get it.
What's not to get?
It's an armored truck.
Swap fake for real.
But the fake cash goes
straight to the bank,
and we go straight to jail.
So, there's a few kinks to work out.
(JAZZ SONG PLAYING)
How's the sisterhood
of the traveling pants?
Always together.
DL Dave's gonna want more
than their favorite tabes
at Cheesecake Factory.
Here's what I know
about girls who are this tight.
Literally nothing.
But they know everything about each other.
She's not in this alone.
Get your own.
What?
DEAN: Beth.
Yeah.
High risk.
Uh, hello.
It's what I heard all day.
From whom?
Banks, credit unions.
Those payday places.
Even that d-bag all over the bus stops.
You know how it says,
"Instant approval" or
"No credit score too low'?
Guess what?
They never met Dean Boland.
So, what're you gonna do?
(SIGHS)
I don't know.
My mom's gonna give us her ottoman.
We don't have a couch.
I told her that.
Good.
The ottoman will be here tomorrow.
(SIGHS)
I Know. I'm sorry.
I just don't want him involved again.
Okay.
Now, could you...
Sorry.
(MUFFLED MUSIC PLAYING)
What are you doing here?
You've still got to eat.
I'm fine.
Cheetos aren't lunch.
I'm gonna pay you back.
Every cent.
Is that pot roast?
Ten hours in the slow cooker.
BETH: Excuse me, sir.
Sir, have you seen that man?
Did you see the man go in there?
Uh, I didn't see anything.
BETH: Said he's here
for the Caesar salad.
Like that's why a man
spends all night in there,
for the tableside Caesar salad.
I used this merlot marinade.
It's literally going to
melt in your mouth.
(CAR HORN HONKING NEARBY)
Oh. Be right back.
No. One bite, one bite.
Do they even have a Caesar salad?
I mean, do they have a Caesar salad?
Maybe?
Yeah, maybe.
Maybe it's a nasty-ass thing
they do on his face, huh?
Yo, Neal.
I got two for you today.
Oh, man, that's good.
Now, the potatoes.
I gotta go.
Just one bite. One bite.
Neal's waiting.
Mmm!
Who are you, again?
I'm from corporate.
You know, they send me down
when they're in a pickle.
I'm sorry. Excuse me, Neal.
I'm so sorry to put you in this position.
But I'm going to need you to go in there.
I'm gonna need you
to get him out for me, okay?
That's not my job, lady.
(BETH CRYING)
I gotta go.
(SIGHS)
ATMs.
Making it rain.
It's Monsoon season.
Am I right?
Uh, tell Stan feel better.
Yeah, will do.
Hey, take 'er easy now.
You gotta try the Brussels sprouts.
Mmm-mmm.
No, the man's got runs to make.
STAN: I'll make my drop
and I'll be back for the Brussels, okay?
Wait.
You can't go out there.
(SIGHS)
Hey.
NEAL: Hey, buddy, I thought you were sick.
Yeah, I had a stomach thing.
Uh, you all good?
Yeah, I think so.
Mind if I check?
Your money.
(CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS) Let's see here.
Everything kosher?
STAN: Yeah.
I just wanted to check the deposit slips.
Well, feel better.
A lot of bugs going around.
Yeah.
(ENGINE STARTS)
Huh.
Is there a problem?
Just didn't know you can get checks
with dolphins on 'em.
The kids love 'em.
Whatever works.
So, do we have a deal?
(SIGHS)
That's up to you.
What do you need?
A week or two?
I mean, ideally, we
would like to transition
as soon as possible.
Can I ask you something?
And we'll need a release
from the franchise agreement.
Why would you do this for him?
Because he is my husband.
That's enough?
No. I need you to initial
here, here and here.
I'm sorry. You just take
"standing by your man"
to a whole new level.
Well, you don't know him.
I Know if he told you
what really happened between us,
you wouldn't waste
a cute dolphin check on him.
Oh, honey...
What?
I'm not the first, am I?
We can finish this up later.
Should I hold on to this?
I'll take that.
I think that's smart.
(DOOR SHUTS)
Got a new phone.
What'd you do with the rest of it?
(SIGHS)
So what?
We just good now?
You told me to pay you back. I did it.
So, you steal from me
to pay back what you stole?
It wasn't really from you.
It was from where I work.
It's not a church, Stanley.
That place runs on sin.
It's still my ass on the line.
It never made it to the bank.
Oh, great.
SO you can say however much you want
was in those bags.
Thanks for having my back.
I'm just making my man happy.
You know, following orders.
Come on.
Because you're the boss now, right?
You run the house.
I don't want that.
That's what I heard.
I want old you.
Okay? The way you used to be before.
The whole point of this stupid thing
was to make us better people, babe.
And you stole from it.
To pay for a car
for someone that needed it,
which makes me a better person!
It's ruining us.
So, what do you want?
You want to go back?
I don't know.
You want to go back to the mall?
I go back to slinging donuts.
I don't know.
Because I got to tell you,
there's not enough donuts in the world
that's gonna cover our baby's meds.
(SNIFFS) But hey,
maybe Paul Blart can save the day.
DEAN: Oh, hey.
The kids' smoke detector
hasn't had a battery
in God knows how long.
(TAP RUNNING)
Well, there's really
nothing left to lose.
Right. Only our whole family.
Can I ask you something?
I'm sure there was
a spare nine volt in here somewhere.
Would you have ever slept with her?
What?
Like before, when we
were really not doing well.
Um...
Found it.
I! mean, she's not...
not pretty.
Okay. You look amazing.
That's not what I asked.
Would you have ever slept with her?
(SIGHS) Uh...
She wears this...
perfume.
Sexy.
And she's got...
a really nice ass.
And...
perfectly sized...
boobs.
And she's kind of crazy,
which could go either way
in the sack and...
You know, overall,
it seems,
you know, worth the gamble.
So, you would have.
Probably.
(SIGHS)
Thanks for being honest.
Where's the chief?
Art class.
Really?
Yeah.
You know, pencils and chalk and whatnot.
And then he's going to aerobics.
Is that good enough for you?
Where the hell is his cut?
It was my son's diaper bag.
Just bring it back next time.
Hey.
I need another favor.
(CHUCKLES)
Are you serious?
I'm obviously good for it.
I have to add it to your tab?
Yeah, fine.
What do you want?
When you took my furniture...
I didn't take nothing.
How did you do it?
GAYLE: They don't know who it was.
They completely took everything.
I'll call you back.
Oh, my God, what happened?
What do you want?
Well, I wanted to buy
a hot tub place. But...
this place doesn't have any hot tubs.
So...
(SCOFFS, CHUCKLES) Wow. Um...
Not what I was expecting, you know.
Uh...
I mean...
how's that?
We already agreed on a number.
Well, yeah, but...
that doesn't seem fair.
I mean, why would I
pay that much when it's
just an empty showroom?
I mean, if you're not interested...
Sea lions, huh?
Oh, yeah, it's a whole
marine life series.
(KIDS LAUGHING)
BOTH: Let's go!
Hey.
Those aren't church clothes.
We're not going to church.
Oh. You're not?
Says who? Jesus?
Daddy.
He says we're going go-karting.
Oh, yeah, they got so good on your Jazzy
I figured it was time
to take it up a notch. Shoes.
(KIDS SQUEAL, LAUGHING)
Shoes!
Put on your shoes!
They have Sunday school.
And the rest of their life to be good.
Where's all that going?
I'm giving back.
To who?
People who deserve it.
Last chance.
You were right.
Oh, I know.
I don't know where we're going.
I just want to go there together.
It's like a star.
Jackets, bathroom, car!
Let's burn some rubber.
You already tried
to return it, didn't you?
Oh, yeah. They were gonna hose me good.
RIO: Almost up and running, huh?
We had an issue with the previous owner.
No, I... I love it.
You do?
(CHUCKLES) Yeah.
Get away with anything you want
in a place like this.
Well, it'll look even better
when I get the spas back in.
Oh, yeah?
And the barbecue accessories.
Cool. I'll take the deal.
Okay.
You want to join me?
I would be happy to have
a sales representative
walk you through all the features.
Nah. Those things breed diseases.
When does it get to be mine?
When does what get to be yours?
I made all of this happen.
Next time, empty the clip.
See you soon, yeah?
Classy.
(CHUCKLES) Always.
(CHILDREN CLAMORING)
Hey, let your sister have a turn!
To being small business owners.
Kind of.
Very small.
Like, micro.
Okay.
To hitmen.
Wherever they may be.
Good luck and Godspeed.
WOMAN: No way.
You did my nails.
Huh?
Go red or go home, remember?
Oh. Hey.
You guys probably know this, but your
girl here is like Picasso.
My hands are a work of art.
Oh, wow.
Gorge.
So, what are you guys celebrating?
(SLOW ROCK SONG PLAYING)