RUBY: Previously on Good Girls...
BETH: Guess we're back in business.
Lemonade?
We have an employee, okay?
Where did this guy go to prison?
He's gonna wash in ways that we can't.
RUBY: So he just showed up
with all of it?
BETH: Minus his cut, yeah.
So your sister was trying to protect you?
Who's gonna protect her?
You know what they call this in the biz?
A breakthrough.
Your principal says
that you and some girls shoplifted this.
Like mother, like daughter, I guess.
We're not bad people.
No, baby, we're good people
who do bad things.
I gotta show you something.
(GASPS)
Lung.
Spleen.
Shoulder.
Yeah, we both know how this ends.
I'm pregnant.
So you have a nine-month solution
to a permanent problem.
Three months.
Maybe four.
Congratulations.
Paternity test.
Oh, you can do that in about a month.
I tried telling him to leave.
Says his boss needs him
to keep an eye on you.
Who's his boss?
There's something I have to tell you.
DANNY: Are we going to school today?
Uh...
We're already late.
Where's Kenny?
Upstairs, pooping.
Go get him.
Good morning.
I called the cops.
(CHUCKLES) Okay.
I have kids.
I ain't got no issue with them.
You don't wanna do that.
Oh, I think I do.
(CHUCKLES)
It's up to you.
Fine.
Get arrested.
Okay.
But you know what I gotta do
when I get out.
How we doing, folks?
Ma'am, got a call
about someone in the neighborhood?
I called, yeah. Um...
It's...
Everything's okay.
(CHUCKLES) Officer.
Thank you. Sorry.
Y'all have a good day, then.
Okay.
MAN: Looking for some firepower?
I'm looking for something.
'Cause it's not the gun
that does the damage.
It's the caliber of the bullet.
Mm-hmm.
So just depends on your needs.
I need to kill a man.
Oh, oh, okay, uh...
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
There are certain things
you can or can't say when buying a gun.
Mm, right.
And, uh...
Well, you just said
the only thing you can't say.
What if I'm dealing
with a really aggressive moose.
Oh, like an Alaska Yukon or...
The kind that attacks you.
That'd be the Shiras.
Now, this moose...
He also has a thing for my wife.
Wait, what exactly
are we talking about here?
We're talking about
a moose, Sean, who breaks into my house.
He threatens my kids,
has his way with my wife,
and I can't seem to ever do
anything about it.
All right, well,
that will (CLEARS THROAT)
narrow your selection down
to the Prairie Hawk,
the Liberty single-shot...
Whichever's your favorite.
Uh, just a few easy questions for you,
like have you ever been
convicted of a violent crime?
No.
Ever get a not guilty verdict
by reason of insanity?
No.
Okay, well, just check "no"
for the rest of these,
and we'll get back to you
in a few days, maybe a week.
Well, what if I need it sooner?
Well, with this type of firearm,
they require us to do a background check.
What could I walk out with today?
He reads?
Is that an US Weekly?
BETH: /n Touch.
Mrs. Karpinski gave it to him
after he brought in her recycling bins.
Jesus.
How does he even go to the bathroom?
BETH: Mrs. Karpinski.
That bitch.
You guys, I can't live like this.
Okay. Okay, here's what we do.
We go to Canada and get a baby.
Get a baby?
Well, she said she's having his baby.
We're gonna need a baby.
RUBY: What are you gonna do?
Pick one up with a cruller
from Tim Hortons?
Oh, my God.
ANNIE: That's where we got that fake cash.
I mean, who knows what else
they're hiding up there?
Although we could just pay for one.
I mean, the cash exchange rate right now
up there is actually...
You wanna buy a baby?
I want my sister to not die.
I wanna go to bed.
RUBY: Nuh-uh.
ANNIE: What?
RUBY: You cannot be serious,
Mrs. Karpinski.
ANNIE: Oh, dude.
It's like she wants him
to use her bathroom.
Oh, look at this.
She got snacks on snacks now.
(RUBY SIGHS)
We'll figure something out, okay?
I'm sorry.
Am I in the wrong house?
What is happening?
Dad's mad.
About what?
I got fired from tutoring.
STAN: Tell her why.
They said I took their stupid pen.
We gave you a backpack
full of school supplies.
Mm-mm.
It's not like that.
Was it used to sign
the Declaration of Independence?
STAN: Maybe.
What?
Yeah, they said it's some
platinum engraved fountain deal
that costs as much as a Car.
I didn't do it.
Hmm, where have we heard that one before?
How about their own daughter
who's always vaping and skipping class?
Okay, why don't you go
to your room so I can talk to your daddy?
You don't know she did It.
And you don't know she didn't.
Okay, well, what do we do from here?
Oh, it's a "we"
situation now?
And that means what?
You're the resident crime lord.
(DEAN SNORING)
MAN: Can't sleep?
Oh, God.
Give me aride.
What's up?
(CLEARS THROAT)
Can I get a shot of tequila?
You might wanna slow down, yeah?
We never got to toast.
One for my baby daddy here, too.
What are you doing, Elizabeth?
I lost it.
When?
Does it matter?
All right, then.
So what comes next?
Nothing good.
How much would it cost?
For what?
My life.
Ah, nah, too late for that.
You haven't been in the game for,
what, two months?
Don't worry about it.
No pills, no cars, no cash?
It's gotta hurt.
You don't know my interests.
I Know they need capital.
And your guy could chop me up
ina million pieces whenever you want,
so what do you got to lose?
How much am I worth?
You couldn't afford it.
What if I could?
Okay.
Pros and cons.
Pro. You're not dead yet.
How are we gonna get 100 grand?
Another pro.
How is that a pro?
Well, he could have said, like, $100,
which would have been way easier,
but said a lot less about you
as a person.
Do you know how many ones
we're gonna have to get
to print that much?
RUBY: Con.
Thank you.
RUBY: It's a lot.
Not to mention washing it.
Con.
Okay, there are gonna be
a lot more cons than pros.
How firm was he on this number?
(DOOR OPENS)
Hey, ladies.
What is going on?
I got floss.
Oh?
We were out.
What else did you get, Dean?
Hmm, got some razors, deodorant.
I'm gonna try these
breathe right nose strip thingies...
Why is there a shotgun on our bed?
It's the only gun I could get without
a waiting period.
What if the kids find it?
I'll hide the ammo.
And what if they find that?
They won't.
Kenny's found every one
of his Christmas gifts
for the past five years.
That's 'cause you hide them.
I Know you're upset...
No.
I'm terrified.
And I get that.
But this isn't gonna make him go away.
Then tell me what will.
I don't want a gun in my house.
And I don't want the tweaker
on the front lawn
reporting back to the guy
who emptied a clip in me,
but hey, that's the world
we're living in.
Time.
Nine minutes, 38 seconds.
Mm.
Not bad.
Yeah, it's for preschoolers,
but congrats.
What else you got around here?
We could talk about stuff.
How do you talk about something
that you can't talk about?
Well, just start.
I'm really worried about my sister.
Okay.
She's dealing with something that's
very life-threatening.
Well, they say when someone gets sick,
it might as well be the whole family.
It's just that we thought
that it was gone,
and now it's back.
The big C, huh?
Mm.
What kind?
It's Super rare.
I lost my mom the same way.
Oh, God.
So, I've been down the road.
Yeah, it's just...
It's not, you know, one of the...
Like a breast cancer or a lung...
Not one of the super popular ones, So...
Try me.
(EXHALES SHARPLY) I...
I just...
I...
Eye...
Ball...
Cancer.
It's eyeball cancer.
Just the, uh...
Just the one.
Left one.
Retinoblastoma?
If I never hear that word again...
That's how my mum died.
Oh, no.
Has she lost her vision yet?
Ish?
Mom always wanted to see
the Grand Canyon.
I planned a whole thing.
We'd stay at the lodge
on the valley floor.
It's Supposed to be great.
Yeah, but, um, I got this cat
'cause I was having a hard time dealing,
and it wouldn't sleep,
so I pushed the trip by a week.
She went completely blind
the night before our flight.
Did you still go?
I! mean, she said it smelled amazing.
(CHUCKLES)
That's just who she was.
Um...
This made me wanna be a therapist.
The Eye in Survivor.
You're gonna make it
whether your sister does or not.
Okay, I feel much better.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Same time, same place next week.
I'm gonna grab Timmy.
Timmy!
Timothy, come on in.
Add $350 to that.
You know you don't have to put
the dot zero zero, right?
I'm aware. Thank you.
Plus $200. Stan's working
a bachelor party.
And I get time and a half for nights,
so put half, like, another...
(CROWD CHEERING)
For, like, another hundred.
No dot zero zero.
Okay, I like to see
the whole number, all right?
Where we at?
BETH: So that puts us at... (SIGHS)
Still way off.
If we didn't hit Fine & Frugal,
I had another plan.
Okay, this general attitude
is why I keep things to myself.
What?
You remember when that Kardashian
got, like, a bazillion-carat
diamond necklace stolen
from her hotel room in Paris?
All right, I gotta pee.
Do you still wanna hear it?
Ooh.
(INHALES)
Let's go. We gotta go.
It's insane, but...
If we had explosives, a hypnotist,
and a military helicopter,
we might be able to pull this off.
Hang on. Did you...
Dd you change?
Yeah. I got our money.
What?
It's Gordie Howe's.
That means nothing to me.
From the 1955 Stanley Cup.
Even less.
Oh, we gotta go.
Let's go.
(CROWD CHEERING)
Oh, my God.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay. It's old.
I grabbed the only thing
I could think of.
What was that?
A toilet plunger.
Smart.
But I had to use
the wood part to break the glass.
Uh, but what'd you hold on to?
Toothbrush.
You didn't.
I did.
Vinegar, baking soda, lemon juice.
Did you at least wrap some
toilet paper around it?
There was so much pressure
from the knocking.
ANNIE: Plunger's seen some things.
There's a volcano burger on that menu.
Double bison patty
smothered in habanero sauce.
It comes with bottomless chili fries.
(GROANS)
BETH: Okay. (SIGHS)
Now what?
We wait.
It's gonna be worth it.
(SIGHS)
Hey. How we doing tonight?
How do you think we're doing?
How do you even know
what this thing looks like?
The guy sent me, like,
four different angles of it.
Hmm?
Apparently, it belonged
to his grandfather.
At what point are we taking this too far?
This is our job, Ruby.
She's a straight A student.
Yeah, smart like a fox.
She tutors, volunteers.
Good cover.
The other day, I watched her bring in
the Connors' trash cans
without even being asked.
Casing the joint.
She's a perfect kid.
Yeah, and so were you.
She's not me.
(SIGHS)
I need to get in there.
Please.
(DOOR OPENS)
Hi.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Um, uh...
I read it, So...
Already?
It's...
It's a real page-turner.
Okay.
Um, hey, can I ask you something?
Now?
Yeah. Uh...
What's going on with...
With us?
What do you mean?
Well, you hugged me.
Okay.
With both arms.
That's how I hug.
It felt a little...
Long.
Ah, right, um, maybe I overstepped.
Maybe...
Maybe I liked it.
Um, I know you're going through a lot.
Oh, no. No, no.
There is still a line here.
Oh, come on.
Grow a pair.
We shouldn't cross it.
And where is that line,
just so I'm aware?
And to paraphrase Freud...
Don't you need a real degree to do that?
Sometimes a hug is just a hug.
(SCOFFS)
Okay. Thank you so much, Dr. Cohen.
I'm gonna go back
to the office and count to 50.
Little spot of something red here.
I think it's blood.
Probably from that brawl
in the third period.
Cool.
So are we good?
Let me run it past my guy.
Late night?
Couldn't sleep.
Weren't you wearing that yesterday?
Okay, I can see where this is going,
so, just gonna cut it off at the pass.
I tried to seduce my therapist, okay?
Like, sexually.
Bone town.
He straight up rejected me,
so I went home alone,
drank a lethal amount of Goldschlager,
and fell asleep in a pile
of my own Cheetos dust.
So if you wanna rip me anew one
for being four minutes late,
you go right ahead,
but I'm not gonna feel
any worse than I already do.
You're in therapy?
Like, physical therapy?
Why would I be in physical therapy?
I don't know.
'Cause of how you run?
What's wrong with how I run?
All right, ladies.
Where'd y'all say you got this?
Oh, it's been in my family
for many generations.
Yeah, our grandfather
taught him how to skate.
Our great-great-great-great grandfather.
Was he Chinese?
Huh?
'Cause that's where this jersey was made,
like, two years ago.
Excuse me...
Wait, it's a fake?
How much for it?
Twenty bucks.
Twenty bucks?
CLERK: All right, $25.
Excuse me.
Where did you get this?
Limited edition.
Solid platinum barrel.
18 carat nib.
Who brought it in?
Some girl.
Like, a little blonde druggie type?
What is going on?
Okay, I'm not interested.
Fine, we'll take the 20.
I'd like you to leave.
Was it her?
You guys cops?
(DOOR CLOSES)
Guess what.
(SIGHS) Jesus.
Language.
You're home early.
Got some good news.
What's that?
They found the pen.
Wow.
Yeah, so I made you these.
I Know you've been worked up.
How is it?
Awesome.
Jesus.
What?
How do you do that?
Eat that like you deserve it.
Where's the money?
Does Dad know?
Where did you hide it?
I don't have...
Where?
Same place you hide yours.
I don't Know what you do,
but it doesn't come from painting nails.
What do you talk about?
Just stuff.
Like what kind of stuff?
More lo mein anyone?
Mm, mm-hmm.
Like me?
I'm probably gonna stop going.
Oh, my God.
It's 100% me.
Okay, you know what?
Let's do fortunes.
Well, mine doesn't have one,
so that's probably not good.
Huh, let's see.
"You are smarter, prettier,
and much cooler than your sibling."
Wow.
That's not what it says.
No, it does.
Says it right here.
Show me.
Give it to me.
No! That's like telling you
my birthday wish.
Fortune wants what it wants.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
And now it shall be written forever.
You're the worst.
Hey.
Thank you.
Thank my derelict daughter.
What are you gonna do to her?
Um, I haven't devised it yet,
but it is definitely gonna be illegal.
Okay, let's bring home some bacon.
(9 TO 5 PLAYING)
(SONG CONTINUES ON CAR STEREO)
(HUMMING TUNE)
(GRUNTING)
RIO: Afraid we got a problem.
So here's the thing, man.
If you wanna move
your funny money through my guys,
we gotta get some stuff straight, yeah?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah?
All right, for starters,
there is a licensing fee,
but, you know, if that's gonna be
an issue for you,
we can just...
Mm-mm.
No problem?
Mm-hmm.
Good. Good, good, good,
good, good, man, good.
I was hoping you'd say that.
Mm-hmm.
Now, I need to know who your employer is
'cause I don't know you.
(CHUCKLES)
And you don't know me.
I feel like I should know everybody
that I work with, right?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah?
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
What's that now?
(YELLING INDISTINCTLY)
So who made your money?
I'm home.
Hey, babe.
I got your food warming in the oven.
Ah, okay.
You got a test tomorrow?
Algebra.
So your mama told me what happened.
(SIGHS)
So what now?
Stevensons gonna give her that job back?
It's up to her.
I mean, either way, they owe
our family an apology.
All right, gotta wash this day off first.
I love you.
Why didn't you tell him?
Because it would break his heart.
What if he runs into
Mr. Stevenson somewhere?
Well, that's the problem, isn't it?
You make up one story,
then you gotta make up another
to cover that story.
Before you know it,
you can't keep any of them straight.
Am I grounded?
That's for kids.
You're big-time now.
You're a criminal.
So what's that mean?
You're gonna owe me.
(DOOR OPENS)
Hey, need a hand?
Well, aren't you full service.
You've missed two sessions.
Stalking included.
I got worried.
Look, there's no point, okay?
I made it weird.
We should talk about that.
And make it weirder?
It's called transference.
When people make progress in therapy,
it's not uncommon to...
You know, develop, like,
a crush on the person helping them.
Okay, well, this right now
is definitely not helping,
and I have stuff to do, so...
All right. See you.
I'll, uh, go back
in my apartment, count to 50.
You Know what I think'?
You have a storied history of pursuing
inaccessible men,
which is a defense mechanism
to protect you from rejection.
In fact, you do that
with a lot in your life.
I mean, why pursue anything that would
make you happy
when there's a chance
you might not get it, right?
And you put all that
under a nice thick layer
of sex and sarcasm
that makes you bulletproof
to any real emotion.
But, uh, you know, hey.
What do I know?
I graduated bottom of my class online.
You can't charge me for that.
If you don't come back,
I've gotta fill your spot.
Hey, have you seen my purse?
The ammo's in the office.
The gun is in the garage
with the lawn stuff.
How would you ever get to it?
I just like knowing it's there.
Okay.
We were so good with him gone.
Purse is on the couch.
I'll be right with you.
Hey, now.
I don't have it all right now, okay?
I'm not here for that.
I'm just here for some custom printing.
Word is you do the best work.
I'd like to see how it's done.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Oh, no?
'Cause your friend says you do.
I wanna see.
Well, he's got it wrong.
(GUN CLICKS)
Show me.
Pulp's gotta dry now.
Okay.
Takes a while.
I got time.
What do you think?
I think I need you alive.