ANNIE: Previously on Good Girls...
You better give me that money, bitch.
Hey!
(SCREAMS)
Am I gonna make it?
Here we go. This is it.
It's go time.
You saved her leg.
I did?
And how much of my cut is from Cartier?
All of it.
What?
How'd you get insurance to cover it?
I tried to seduce my therapist.
He straight up rejected me.
I want to get better.
Friday at 8:30.
I couldn't make as much.
Why is that?
BETH:
The price of ink went up.
You stole from a man
who blew a little girl's
brains out for fun?
BETH: 10% off the top.
RUBY: What if he finds out?
BETH: He won't.
DEAN: What's it say?
You sure about this?
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
Well, I'm going down
Going down a hard road
Just don't know
Don't know where I've been
Mmm.
WAITRESS:
Can I get you anything else?
I think we're probably good.
What didn't I order?
Oh, let's see.
Chef's got an ambrosia salad.
Bingo.
Mmm.
I'm really sorry, Leslie.
Mmm, yeah, thanks.
Cop railroaded you good, man.
Oh, yeah.
Lady Justice has got
a real Woodrow for guys like me, hmm?
(CHUCKLES)
Some people at the store were happy,
but they don't know you like I do.
Who?
Jessie.
Hmm.
Frozen foods?
Mmm-hmm.
And Marta.
Seriously?
What's her problem?
She saw you do an impression of her
in front of the whole bakery.
Oh, man. Before I knew
it was a birth defect!
You know what?
I can't wait to get out
of this hell hole.
All this woke culture.
WAITRESS:
Ambrosia salad?
Oh, yeah.
Thanks.
Dig in.
I'm keto now.
Oh.
Yeah, that explains it.
Your fingers look more regular.
I'm really gonna miss you, Leslie.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Listen.
I uh...
I need you to do something for me.
Name it.
I can't go in looking like this.
You look great.
You know what they'll do to me.
You've seen the documentaries, right?
What can I do?
Your sister still got that shop?
Come and take me home
What do you think?
I'd add a scorpion to the pentagram.
I'm out in the woods
Said I'm lost in the woods
Oh
JOSH: Okay, how many seats
in the House and Senate?
ANNIE:
Hmm, how many seats on a plane, Josh?
I have no idea.
Exactly.
But you fly a lot more
than you pass bills in
the Senate. Am I right?
Right. I'm sensing it's not the material
that's been the problem here.
So do you have study buddies
over there across the pond?
Oh, you mean a quiz chap.
(LAUGHS) Yeah, yeah.
I've always been a lot more
chap than quiz, you know?
Hmm, right.
Next subject.
Josh Cohen.
No.
(SIGHS) Come on.
You know everything about me.
That's how this works.
All you, no me.
Just, like, one little crumb.
Your middle name.
Twitter name.
Porn name?
Huh, is that pineapple?
That was mine.
I just wanted a bite.
Of my pizza.
There are four other slices.
Well, I didn't want a whole piece.
Yeah, but my mouth touched that one.
I'm not following.
Your mouth touched my mouth.
I just wanted to try the pineapple.
We just kissed, my friend.
We certainly did not.
Oh, it is not so certain.
We should do chemistry.
Aren't we?
Never mind.
Okay, Doc.
You know, you could talk about
transference all you want,
but you just pizza transferred
your tongue into my mouth.
Hard.
And I don't think it was just
about the pineapple.
I think we're done for tonight.
Mmm.
You're the best quiz chap I ever had.
Hmm. Do we look any different?
Better.
Older.
Sexier.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Happy almost anniversary.
Oh.
What, now look at this.
Toaster's broken.
Had to microwave them.
Mmm.
Harry tried to write a poem
about famous marriages.
Where is that animal?
It started with Bert and Ernie,
and then he went back to sleep.
Okay, well, we feel loved.
But go wake him up.
Get ready for school.
STAN: Thanks, baby.
Yeah.
So what do you wanna do?
What do you mean?
Sara said she would babysit
if we wanna go out.
You trust that child
in our house all alone?
Okay, so here's what it is, all right?
I'm gonna rent a Bentley.
Oh, really?
Uh-huh.
Convertible, ostrich seats.
Okay.
And I'mma drive you up to Birmingham,
and we're gonna go have dinner
at the Townsend Hotel.
Hmm?
I think that's the place
they got the bourbon that nobody can get.
Like 70 bucks a glass.
Smells like a forest fire.
Mmm.
We're gonna get that.
And then when the check comes,
I'mma charge it to the room.
Oh, we're getting a room now?
We're gonna get not a room.
Presidential suite.
Ooh.
And then, wake up, breakfast in bed.
Home to the kids by noon.
You can't afford any of that.
(SIGHS)
But we deserve it.
Let's just go halfsies
on the new hot water heater.
Hmm, nothing like a good, hot shower.
(SIGHS)
I gotta work anyway.
Yeah, same.
What if we turn it length-wise?
It's a square, Annie.
(SCOFFS) Is it?
Or is it...
A diamond.
Take it easy on my floors, okay?
I need the practice.
They're all she has left.
So what are we gonna do here?
I made a to-do list.
That is a battle cry if I ever heard one.
(CHUCKLES)
She means business.
Yo, Murderball.
You wanna park it
and join the conversation?
RUBY: I hear you just fine.
Number one.
Gain back his trust.
How?
Softly, just break it to me softly
Be straight with me but gently
Tender before you kill me
Pow-pow
And once we do number one,
then we move on to number two.
RUBY: What's number two?
Get a cut of the money.
(TIRES SCREECH)
No skimming, no stealing.
We'll just earn it.
Like we used to.
What a joke What a joke you make me
What's a queen to a joker Tell me
What's a laugh to a self-destructive me?
What's a prayer to a death wish?
You're So...
Oh, I talked to my mom.
The kids are great.
I think we should just leave them there.
Forever?
Well, until we figure this out.
Where are you going?
I am going to get our lives back.
Well, you gotta look that good to do it?
You trust me?
(LOUD CLUB MUSIC PLAYING)
Excuse me.
Shouldn't you be making money?
Just here having a drink.
Questions, notes, comments?
So in sum,
we suck up to the gang leader
who we stole from,
and convince him to pay us a living wage?
Which we then use to pay someone else
to blow his brains out?
A professional.
Not someone who's gonna
wet himself in my car.
It's all I could come up with
at 4:00 a.m.
on an air mattress.
(SWITCHES ON)
(BEEPING)
Max has that cousin.
Makes sense on paper.
RIO: Rough day?
Mmm, I've had better.
Yeah, well, nothing a good night's sleep
won't fix.
I'd have to have a bed.
That's a problem.
Well, the least of them.
That right?
I screwed up with my boss.
Never good.
I'm still valuable,
though, and he knows it.
And I only did it because
he works me to the bone
and doesn't pay me anything.
What do you want, Elizabeth?
Just what's fair.
Af, fair.
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah, I don't owe you.
It's the other way around, remember?
Can't we just go back?
Well, that's up to you.
What do you mean?
Yeah, you gotta earn that.
Okay.
Yeah?
I'll do anything.
Anything, huh?
Within reason.
You still got that minivan?
Why?
I might have got something for you.
My ottoman?
(CHUCKLES)
No. (CLEARS THROAT)
Hey, where are my keys?
How would I know?
You know where everything is.
Look in the fridge.
I'm not an idiot.
Oh, and Dad is gonna pick
you up from school today.
I have some errands to run.
Why'd you get in so late?
I was in therapy.
At 10:00 at night?
Well, yeah, it was GED prep.
You know, it's...
Oh, by the way, there's pizza
for you for lunch.
You had pizza with your therapist?
And a couple beers.
So what?
He's your therapist.
He's helping me.
It's like a study buddy.
Like your last study buddy?
Okay.
But instead of passing dummy algebra,
he got you knocked up with me.
Have a great day at school, okay?
You had to drop out.
Got married, divorced...
Love you.
And here we are.
This does not make you right
about everything, okay?
Love you.
Bye.
RUBY: / mean, that's what it has to be.
'Cause we've already delivered his drugs,
his money, his bodies.
She even boned him, for God's sakes.
What does that have to do with anything?
And if he's trying
to punish us, which he most certainly is,
what is the one thing we're all against?
Microplastics in the ocean.
Okay, the one other thing.
The Rohingya crisis in Myanmar.
It's the GED.
She's trying to be up on stuff.
Okay, why did we march downtown
for three hours in the rain last year?
With the vagina hats on?
That was for women, Annie.
We're not against women.
What is every sane person against?
Oh.
ALL: Guns.
Genetic cloning.
Oh, I give up, I can't.
Listen, it doesn't matter what it is.
If we wanna get rid of him,
we're gonna do it.
How do we even know
we're in the right place?
Because the pin thingy dropped here.
It is a weird place
to deliver a bunch of guns.
Maybe they're coming by helicopter.
Yeah, or some kind of drone.
For all we Know,
there could be a full convoy
barreling down the road.
Nope.
Right up there.
Are you high?
That's a commercial flight.
Exactly.
Smart.
Hiding in plain sight.
You think they're gonna land
a 747 in a wheat field?
No, a cabbage field.
See, there's way more water.
You know, it's like when they spray foam
on the runway.
You know, it creates...
Yeah, for crashing.
Exactly, but the package
still gets there whether you crash the...
Annie Bananie?
Annie Bananie!
(LAUGHS)
Well...
Where do we go?
Let's get going.
This is the car.
Same car, I see.
Uh, you might have
to throw down some towels.
(HORNS HONKING)
I mean...
I Know.
I would have preferred guns.
Grenades.
Cruise missiles.
Anything else.
And what is up with the living hell
that is etched all over his face?
It's like you can't do neo-Nazi
with Santeria and voodoo.
It sends a totally mixed message.
It makes sense actually.
Dude, nothing on that face makes sense.
No, I mean the assignment.
'Cause we couldn't take care
of Boomer before,
so now he's gonna take care of it.
Why didn't he just have
somebody do it in prison?
I mean, you know he's got
a whole network of killers in there.
Because he is testing us.
If we deliver this "package,"
then we're back in.
RUBY: Oh, God.
Oh, they're looking for him.
Hang a U-ey.
(SIREN WAILS)
RUBY:
Don't hang anything.
BETH: What are we gonna say?
That we didn't see anyone?
What if they wonder why we're out here?
BETH: Just three moms out
for the day antiquing.
ANNIE: Ew.
What would you like us to fake be doing?
Berry picking.
Fine.
Way more believable.
It's berry season.
Hi, Officer.
Afternoon, ladies.
What's going on here?
Some inmate started a fire this morning
at Saginaw Correctional.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, it's still a mess up there.
They think a few guys
may have jumped the wall,
so just taking precautions.
Jeez, well, we appreciate it, Officer.
Your kid's an Arctic Grizzly?
Uh, travel team.
Schedule's brutal.
My son's a Bay City Penguin.
Oh, my gosh.
That's so funny.
We're playing you in the semi-finals.
I'm Beth, by the way.
Kenny Boland's mom.
We'll see you on the ice.
Oh.
Oh, it is hot in there.
Wait a minute.
That sign is in dollars.
Well, yeah.
What did you expect?
Loonies.
What are you talking about?
You're supposed to smuggle me to Canada.
Says who?
Your gang leader.
Okay, first of all,
he's not our gang leader, and...
His guy on the inside said
that if I lit the fire,
my debt would be paid,
and he'd get me to Canada.
Why?
What did he tell you?
Same thing.
We just thought you'd wanna pee first.
(SIGHS IN RELIEF)
Ooh. (CHUCKLES)
Well, man, I wish you would've
asked me five minutes ago
because it's a mess in here.
BOOMER: Oof.
Oh, Jesus.
You know what, though?
I am super horny.
Let me just...
(GRUNTS)
Oh, my God.
Back in a jiff.
Ugh.
Unbelievable.
That is deeply stupid.
It's Boomer.
Talk about a lamb to slaughter.
To be clear...
I know, I know.
This is not Mary's
fuzzy, cute, little lamb.
It's a dirty, mangy, feral...
Serial raping lamb.
If anyone deserves it...
BOOMER:
Sorry it took so long.
I've been in solitary the past few weeks.
Jesus, why?
What did you do?
It was more what was being done to me.
Can we please go?
I needed time to heal.
All right.
They wanted to make sure
I could pass a solid, you know...
Let's get back in the bag.
Come on, move it.
Oh, I need a favor.
Come on, let's go.
Are you kidding?
Look, since we're still state-side,
I wanna see Nana.
Real quick.
With that face?
You'll kill her.
We're all going to
Saskatchewan in a grain truck.
I may never see her again.
And she's getting up there.
Call her from the road.
She's in a nursing home.
Wait, what?
Since when?
She had a bad fall.
Well, what happened?
I don't know.
No one was taking care of her.
I was locked up.
No.
He should say goodbye to her.
She should say goodbye to him.
We have a job to finish, Annie.
And you-know-who is not gonna wait.
Manolo's good people.
He'll wait, right?
He's solid.
He's a solid dude.
It is her last chance.
One hour.
Thank you.
All right, back in the bag.
Go on.
Deeply stupid.
WOMAN: You can't just
barge in here, okay?
Why don't you ask that prick
where he put his hands?
'Cause by the way,
he fully knew the rules.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
What's up, y'all?
Do you mind staying outside?
Wait, are you sixth precinct?
I was 13th.
Thirteen?
Yeah.
Is that O'Brian?
Is he the captain there?
Well, I heard he retired.
I went to academy with his son.
Oh, great cop.
Will you please tell this guy
he can't just go through our stuff?
What's the problem, man?
Dude said his wife's earrings got stolen
at some birthday party.
Don't you need, like,
a warrant or something?
Well, that's really
not how it works for girls like you.
(LAUGHS)
Why don't you bitches take a seat?
All right, all right.
Thank you, but I got this.
Yeah, well, if you need some
help searching those lockers,
man, I'm happy to help.
Stan...
I said sit your ass down.
They're over there.
You have a key?
Oh.
(KEYS JINGLING)
Here you go.
Now I gotta tell you,
I was at that party,
and there were some
super shady people, so...
Just keep an eye on them.
Yeah.
Why'd you leave the 13th?
Oh, my man.
You know, the pay isn't
what it used to be.
Tell me about it.
Downside here is, what?
A heel to the face.
(LAUGHS)
Hey, listen.
If you or any of the boys
wanna come down,
I'll hook you up with some bottle service.
Yeah?
Yeah, man.
Appreciate that.
You got it, man.
What the hell was that?
That was me throwing him off the trail.
Our entire haul from
last night is in these lockers.
You know what?
From now on, nothing but cash.
Okay.
Maybe we should just cool it for a while.
What do you mean?
We almost got arrested, Stan.
I can't do that.
Well, I can't go to jail.
(SIGHS)
Ruby and I, we're gonna
be married for 22 years this Saturday.
Is that the diamond one or platinum?
She wants a water heater.
I think it might be leather.
Yeah, I'm not gonna
give my wife an appliance
for our anniversary.
As long as you got our backs.
You know I do.
Hi, what room is Marion Petersen in?
I'm her grandson, Leslie.
Let me call you back.
He's asking where the package is.
We're not Amazon Prime.
How long is this gonna take?
Just tell him it's en route.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
What do we do?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Do we stay?
I don't know. I don't know.
Should we run?
What is going on?
She's dead.
A week ago.
In her sleep.
RUBY: I'm sorry.
In a place where 2/3
of the residents can't walk,
you put the ramp 1/2 mile away
from the main entrance?
RUBY: What'd I miss?
Where Nana at?
(CRIES)
BETH: She lied, Annie.
RUBY: For months.
BETH: And she chose him over you.
And she's kind of racist.
She's mostly racist.
She was here because she fell on ice.
RUBY: So?
She was going to the salon.
It could have happened anywhere.
I used to take her there.
All right.
Let's roll.
Uh, hold Nana, would you?
She always liked you.
Here.
What's this?
Her final wish.
Lake Okoboji?
Yeah, that's where
she wants to be... scattered.
By the waterfall.
That's beautiful.
That's three hours away.
It's where she married Grandpa John.
We don't have time for this, okay?
No, I gotta see it through.
Lookit, she's a wonderful
lady and whatever,
but we gotta get you to...
BETH: Canada.
Yeah, right.
I'm not going.
Uh, yeah, you are.
No, I'm not.
We don't answer to you.
Yeah, we answer to someone
way scarier than you.
Why does that guy
give a turd where I go, huh?
You know what?
Thanks for the ride.
You're off the hook.
Uh-uh. No way.
Annie, I dig your new hair.
It's not really new.
Well, I like that you
let the roots grow out.
Hey, hey.
Beth.
Hey. Turn off the child locks.
ANNIE:
Beth, what are you doing?
Give me Nana back!
Get back in the bag.
No, don't.
Get back in the bag, Boomer.
If we didn't have
enough reasons to go to hell.
I swear to God this will be
her final resting place.
Beth, don't!
Oh, she's gonna go so well
with all this old people stuff.
Please...
Leftover prunes, lots of wound care,
and honestly, I don't know if this goo is
from sponge baths
or just straight up phlegm.
No!
Don't!
You will never be able
to siphon her out of this ooze.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Put him in.
We're not going to Canada, are we?
What's going on with you and my mom?
Sorry, who are you?
How many other moms see a kid shrink?
Oh.
Hello, Ben.
She thinks you care about her.
I, um...
I care about all my patients.
So you drink beer
late at night with all of them?
Well, most are in bed by 8:00, so...
Maybe you haven't gotten
to this part in your sessions yet
or whatever, but let me
break it down for you.
She's really into you, okay?
Like, the only reason
she's doing any of this stuff
is, like, to impress you or something.
Okay, look, it's natural
to worry about your mom...
I just know her.
Well, uh...
Rest assured, we're trying
to work on these issues.
Okay, but when she realizes that
you're "working on issues"
and not in love with her,
she's gonna get in bed for three months,
eat a whole lot of mac and cheese,
stop waxing, stop paying the bills,
stop making my lunches.
And forget about this GED thing.
I, um...
I hear what you're saying.
Good, 'cause if you don't,
I have ways to turn those
five star Yelp reviews into one-ers.
Yelp terrorist, eh?
Freedom fighter.
Definitely your mom's son.
Oh, but how are you getting home?
I rode my bike.
BOOMER: Is this it?
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Who's got Nana?
I do.
BOOMER: Sorry, who's talking?
(GROANS) It's me, Boomer.
BOOMER: Annie. Annie.
Listen... You gotta listen to me, okay?
I Know you hate me.
But I also know you loved my Nana.
Just stop talking.
BOOMER: She wouldn't have made it as long
as she did without you.
So I need you
to take care of her now, okay?
And do what she wanted, okay?
Annie?
I need you to say "okay."
Annie, can you hear me?
Can you hear me?
Hockey bag in the trunk.
Pop it.
BOOMER: No, please, please.
Please, just...
Please say something!
Just, anything, Annie!
Waterfall, south of the Mackinac Bridge.
They got married at sunset.
No, no, no, no...
please, please.
Annie, I need you to promise.
Annie!
Please! Oh, please.
Okay, please, please?
Guys...
Stop.
BOOMER:
Whoever is carrying me,
I'll do whatever you want.
You don't have to do this again.
We're all good now.
It's basic management, right?
The best employee, the most loyal,
they're the ones who get a second chance.
That's why you're back on payroll.
12% off the top.
I don't mean me.
BOOMER:
Guys, where are you taking me?
Can someone just tell me
where you're taking me?
Oh, him.
Yeah, I got different plans for him.
BOOMER: Ow! Don't throw
me around, at least, okay?
Could you be
a little bit more responsible?
(WHIMPERS)
(MICROPHONE FEEDBACK)
Salt and Pepa's here
Salt, salt, salt, salt
Salt and Pepa, Salt and Pepa
Salt and Pepa's here
Salt, salt, salt, salt
Now, now, now, now Wait a minute, y'all
This dance ain't for everybody
Only the sexy people
So all you fly brothers
Get on out there and dance
Dance, I said
Salt and Pepa's here And we're in effect
Want you to push it, babe
Coolin' by day, then at night
Working up a sweat
C'mon girls Let's go show all those guys
that we know
How to become number one
In a hot, hot show
Now push it Ah, push it, push it good
Ah, push it Push it real good
Ah, push it, push it good
Ah, push it
P-push it real good
Ah! Happy anniversary, babe.
(LAUGHS)
Where did you rent this?
Bought it.
Wait, what?
Club Hill, open for business!
(VOCALIZING)
Ooh, baby, baby
Ooh, baby, baby Ooh, baby, baby
Baby, baby Ooh, baby
(EXCLAIMS)
Happy anniversary.
Push it real good
What is that?
It's an upgrade.
Real?
100%.
Wow.
What do you think?
I think you're in
over your head at these private parties.
Try it on.
You coming up like that?
Try it on, baby.
No.
No?
It doesn't feel right.
'Cause that matters now?
You were just giving
me grief about how I slept at night.
So?
So why don't you check yourself?
Excuse me?
You opened this door.
Swag money?
A professional karaoke machine?
That boulder...
And then you opened it again.
You opened it again, and then
you bashed down the damn wall.
One of us has to be good!
Why, hmm?
What do you mean, why?
All my life, I've been swimming upstream.
Fighting it.
And you know what that gets you?
That doesn't get you respect.
It doesn't get you a badge.
It doesn't get you a proper wedding ring.
It just gets you tired.
And then you get washed
right back down again.
Baby, I'm not wearing that.
I'm not returning it.
Baby, baby Ooh, baby, baby
-Ba-baby, baby
-Pick up on this
How do I look?
Uh... like a girl?
Hmm.
Anything on my teeth?
Is that important?
Very.
Okay, well then, a little right here.
Here?
Good looking out, Timster.
(DOOR OPENS)
Annie. Hey.
Ah.
Wish me luck.
Hey, so we can totally skip
the rest of government
because I watched this
mini-series last night
on John Adams, which was way too long
and extremely boring.
But it pretty much...
covered everything.
Sorry, did I get the wrong time?
Before we get started,
I wanted to introduce you to Lila.
Hello.
What's up?
Lila's a teacher.
Sixth grade.
Very cool.
And she's also American,
so she has a much firmer grasp
on your people's sordid history.
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, and by the way,
I think it's awesome that
you're getting your diploma.
Oh, thanks.
It's never too late.
Hmm.
I thought you could use a real tutor.
I thought we were making progress.
Well, it's better this way.
Don't you think?
I don't know what to think.
Well, that's what I'm here for.
He'll give you my number.
I'll see you at home.
LILA: Bye.
Bye-bye.
Oh, okay.
All right, why don't we
start with what's bothering you today?
Chairs were on sale.
DEAN: Nice.
Just have to put them together.
I figured the kids could do it
when they get back.
Getting a jump, huh?
Look at this.
BETH:
Is that our anniversary?
No. Valentine's Day.
Three years ago.
Oh, with the sitter
who yelled at us for coming home too late.
(LAUGHS)
We got sitter-shamed.
Uh-huh.
We should shut more bars down together.
Like, in general.
We're real good at it.
I can't remember the
last time I had that much fun.
And you wore jeans.
So?
It wasn't that dress.
I didn't need anything from you.
I really wish you did.
It's just a dress, Dean.
Well, I'll start on the chairs.
I can tell by your face
That you're looking To find a place
To settle your mind
And reveal who you are
And you shouldn't be shy
For I'm not gonna try
To hurt you or heal you
Or steal your star
(LAUGHS)
Open your eyes
Get up off your chair
There's so much to do In the sunlight
Give up your secrets
And let down your hair
And sit with me here By the firelight
Third one this month out of Detroit.
Labs came back. Butyl acetate,
chromium oxide, and camphor.
Car paint?
Or nail polish.
Ew.
It's a woman.