ANNIE: Previously on Good Girls...
Let me tell you something
about my husband.
Stanley Lamont Hill is a Cop,
whether you give him a badge or not.
He couldn't commit a crime
if his life depended on it.
Well, what'd they say?
That they'd be honored
to have me back on the force.
Then I came home, tried on my uniform.
It made me feel like a fraud.
Will you have dinner with me?
Talk strategy, or...
Whatever you need to tell your wife.
I really want to, but I can't.
Are you making money?
It's different this time.
Looks a little light.
I couldn't make as much.
The price of ink went up.
Gonna need to see that invoice.
Thought you might.
Remember that project you did
for us a while back?
Gambling addicts, right?
ANNIE: She's not gonna do it
unless we take something she cares about.
Meet Dorito Boland.
What's up, ladies?
You cannot finish that plate.
He said he'd let me go.
He won't.
Wait. You need us.
You need all of us.
RIO: Not all of you.
(GUNSHOTS)
Have you heard from Lucy?
I'm sure she's fine.
Lucy Lulu?
She's not here.
She just texted me this morning.
And then I drove her right
to the airport.
Where'd you get your bird?
My wife rescued her.
(WHISTLING FRERE JACQUES)
(BIRD CONTINUES MELODY)
What is this?
BETH: Ours.
You stole from a man
who blew a little girl's
brains out for fun?
BETH: 10% off the top.
RUBY: What if he finds out?
He won't.
What if he does?
He still needs us.
Until he doesn't.
And then we all end up in that van.
We have to pay our bills.
We print day and night, and for what?
To stay alive.
That's not a life.
What did you say?
Materials went up.
Tell him they went back down.
It's not the NASDAQ.
You remember Missy Taylor?
With the eye patch?
Our class bowler.
Full ride to Ohio State.
For bowling?
She was real good.
She gave up her scholarship
to stay home with her friends,
and now she's waxing balls
and deodorizing shoes.
Bomb.
Free food, a sick arcade,
and 15 lanes of unlimited bowling...
All she could talk about
is how she missed her moment.
This is ours, our moment.
We started this.
He can't just come in
and shoot everything up
and just take it all away.
He kind of can.
You know who stole?
He did. From us.
Mmm-hmm.
Pay your bills.
STAN: Hey, criminals.
No need to hide that.
Got a private party.
Then I gotta do a shift.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Bye.
Hmm, bye.
He's under a lot of pressure at work.
Do you realize?
Can't show anyone
Eye for an eye
Do you ever rise?
ANNIE: Cash tips, leftover birthday cake,
full control of the jukebox.
There's a scholarship for bowling?
She was real good.
American dream.
It's just like if I'd been
born with some kind of gift or something,
you know, my life would be
totally different.
How old are you?
You cannot ask a lady that.
You're no lady.
Thank you. I'm 33.
Big one.
Is it?
Yeah, Jesus year.
What's that?
Died a carpenter, regrouped,
then turned himself into
the most successful brand
in modern history.
Okay.
Jesus juice, Jesus hair, the sandals.
I got it.
Then the expressions.
Come to Jesus.
Jesus, Mary, and Joseph.
And don't forget the classic--
Jesus.
That's the one.
Hmm. Well, I think I see where
you're going with this,
but believe me, I am no saint.
Hmm. All right.
You're a boy's medium, right?
Seriously?
That's all I got left.
Gee, thanks, but I've already got one.
You're adrift, okay?
We've got to right your ship
and find a port.
And children fall for this?
We'll see.
It's a new thing.
Hmm.
Oh, by the way, how's your sister's
retinoblastoma?
Full remission.
Are you serious?
That's amazing.
That never happens.
Yeah, well, some guy
at Whole Foods gave her an herb, so...
we'll see if it lasts.
And yes, thank you.
I am a boy's medium.
Oh, dry clean only.
The ink runs.
It doesn't work.
Duh.
That's a chow, baby.
(STAN LAUGHING)
What?
We play Szechuan style.
You--
Damn it. How'd you guys
get so good at this anyway?
Locked in those freight containers
for months.
Needed something to pass the time.
(ALL LAUGHING)
See, that's not...
Oh, y'all got jokes tonight?
That's very funny.
Suck it, bitches.
Wow.
No.
Yes.
Really?
Pay me.
Oh, man, you ladies cleaned me out.
I gotta get back to the floor.
Oh, wait. I gotta pay you for the party.
Okay.
Szechuan style.
Is all that for one night?
You're worth it.
Yeah, but...
okay, who was that dude?
Oh, he had a sick house, right?
Yeah, I mean, the man had full-grown trees
in his living room.
You could smell the cherry blossoms.
And did his friend look
a little shady to you?
I think it's his bodyguard.
How do you know that?
I saw a gun under his jacket.
What?
Yeah.
We tried to say it's not cool,
but he only spoke Russian.
Krystal, what do you got me into?
Does it matter?
I used to be a cop.
And I used to teach preschool.
This pays way better.
Midst in our travelling hell
Just after Sweden
Floats on the Neva
St. Petersburg
Hey, you.
Craziest thing happened
to me today after the vet.
Want to take a shower?
Do I need to?
I think you do.
You know, I switched
to that natural stuff
'cause of all the aluminum--
With me.
Oh.
Yeah.
Really?
Why not?
But... I don't know.
It's just...
it's been kind of weird after, you know.
Just 'cause he's back
doesn't mean that...
you and I can't stay weird.
(DEAN CHUCKLES)
Yeah, I'll just put this boy to bed--
This girl. Who knew, right?
It's okay.
What happened at the vet?
Oh, this nutjob.
He got in my face and then followed me
back to my car.
Why?
He kept saying that Dorito was his
'cause she was singing some French song.
And I was like, "Dude,
she knows lots of songs.
My kids taught her Don't Worry, Be Happy."
I was like, "Back off."
But he get getting in her beak,
and calling her Abdul or Apu or Abu.
Au Jus.
Yeah. How'd you know that?
Here. Order anything you want.
It's on me.
Not hungry.
What's in the bag?
You look like you could use some coffee.
They make a mean Arnold Palmer.
I'm sure you have a lot of questions.
Just one.
Seriously, Max, what's in the bag?
Where is my girl?
We told her not to get
in the van, but she...
she trusted him.
Sounds like Lucy.
If it wasn't for her, we would all be...
It's true, Max.
She's a hero.
Y'all get a chance to think about food?
We did not.
We're gonna need another minute.
Well, the chef's got
a few yummy specials,
help kick your morning off right.
Got an eggs B that's to die for.
All set.
Uh, here.
I'm gonna do the eggs B.
WAITRESS: Yeah, okay.
I mean, if it's that good.
What do we do about this guy?
Well...
That's the tricky part.
I mean, we can't exactly go to the cops.
Or we'll all end up in that van.
And it's back.
I don't want to go to the cops.
Okay. Good.
I want to kill him.
Max, it's not that easy.
Take it from her.
BETH: If you miss,
which you will--
Again, she would know.
We're all back in that van.
So he just gets to do this
to innocent people?
And we just sit here and we do nothing?
WAITRESS: Arnold Palmer?
Over there.
Thank you.
I've got a cousin.
He's a former Navy SEAL.
You mean like a...
He'll do it.
How much?
MAX: Going rate is 30.
Grand?
He won't miss.
Do you have that kind of money?
I was hoping you did.
(SCOFFS)
We don't.
Then I have to do it myself.
WAITRESS: Eggs B, coming in hot.
Jesus.
Oh, and just some hot sauce.
No, you don't.
I've got nothing else left to lose.
Max.
Who's your cousin?
You got the bromine charts
for the Spa Master 50?
I do, yeah.
Come on, man.
Crazy about Jeff, huh?
What?
Called up to the big show.
He got Vegas?
ERIC: Regional Sales Manager.
Seriously?
And they are setting him up fine.
Even paying relocation for the pugs.
You ever think about transferring?
And give up 11 years
at this party palace?
My wife and I, we're going through
something right now.
There's this guy.
I don't want to get into details.
Anyways, this guy is...
he's bad news.
It's bad for my marriage.
It's bad for my family.
I mean, we...
we could really use a change of scenery
right about now.
You know what I'm saying?
Well, then you gotta get your sales up.
How'd he do it?
(LAUGHING)
Boned Gayle.
Well, how'd you do it?
Oh, I don't.
I'm buried in credit card debt
and live with my aunt.
There's gotta be a middle ground.
You find it, let me know.
An!
Found it.
Great. Thanks.
Yeah.
Hey.
Who gets Jeff's leads?
They just go back to corporate.
Not if we get to them first.
Well, we can't do that.
Would you rather bone Gayle?
I'm gay.
Exactly.
ANNIE: Oh, you want to talk dumb?
What's dumb is stealing from
a Known murderer.
Shh!
He's not even here yet.
Man pops up like a genie.
(SIGHS) It would be SO easy.
How many times can three people
who look like us
commit a robbery without getting caught?
Law of averages.
I'm not up on that law.
You're not up on any laws.
There's at least 30 grand in the safe.
Oh, my God.
Do you not remember the last time
you thought there was
"30 grand" in a safe?
My way's easier, all right?
We skim from a few more runs,
and we'll have it.
And then what?
We issue a fatwa, and go home
and make our kids dinner?
Would it be the worst idea?
It would not.
How's it feel?
Still light.
Some fancy ink.
Pigment's from India.
Why I get the feeling
this ink guy's robbing me blind?
I can't control the world market.
Well, bring him by.
Why?
I'd like to meet him.
You know, see if we could
work something out.
He's in Oklahoma.
Thought you said Kansas City.
Isn't that in Oklahoma?
Missouri.
I'll see what I can do.
Cool.
What about the next run?
Yeah, nah, that's not gonna happen
till I get my costs down.
You're still making a profit. It's still
good business, right?
Not if you don't trust your partners.
Nah.
No one even said anything.
Something off with your energy.
We need a loan.
It's collateral.
How much you after?
30 grand.
For what?
Independent contractor.
You doing a remodel?
Uh, teardown.
I mean, it's smarter
to go through your bank
or your credit union
for a home equity loan.
That's not possible.
You gonna pay through the nose here.
It's for a hitman, okay?
Or we could just waste time
on finance metaphors,
and the next thing you know,
we're back in that van.
So you're looking for a personal advance.
Right.
Yeah.
It's not enough collateral
in the world for a loan like that.
Why?
I mean, when you end up dead,
which it sounds like there's
a real strong chance of,
guess who gets stuck with the tab.
Metaphor would've taken
five seconds longer.
And been way more effective.
Why don't y'all dust off those pretty
OJ masks of yours?
Like I've been saying...
We don't do that anymore.
Why?
Because we've evolved.
We're entrepreneurs now.
With no money.
We are not gonna rob your store, Annie.
Dude, it would be so easy.
I would do it myself
if there weren't cameras.
How easy?
Like, no security.
In and out.
It would take longer
to fill up a Slurpee.
Like Lionel Richie easy?
I literally just need
someone to hand the cash to that isn't me.
Okay, I see.
You know, I wish you all
would've led with that.
I might be able to help y'all after all.
Really?
Is there a different kind of loan?
Everybody, on the floor!
Chill. It's just me.
Better give me that money, bitch.
(SIGHS)
In and out.
Quicker than pouring a Slurpee.
I mean, how big is this damn Slurpee?
Bogey on our left.
Showtime.
Hi, do you have
time to save abandoned babies?
Uh, kind of in a hurry.
You can't spare a moment?
For abandoned babies?
I just want to get a water.
You know who would love a water?
The more than 22,000 infants
that are thrown in dumpsters every year.
Um, definitely against that.
I just, uh...
(SIGHS) All right.
I'm happy to work a volume discount.
How many units are we talking about?
Dean, I need a word.
Sounds great.
You name the time,
and I will have my guys there to install.
Now.
You know what, Richard?
Let me get into this,
and I'll call you right back.
Great. All right, thanks. Bye.
DEAN: I just don't get why
all that money has to go
back to corporate.
So you're calling the shots now?
No, but I can't make
my numbers just selling barbecue tongs.
And I can't have my men going rogue.
It's not how we do things here.
Oh, I know.
What's that supposed to mean?
I think you know what it means.
Pack up your desk.
Seriously?
Forward me your open projects.
That's how you're gonna play this?
Keys in the night box.
No.
Excuse me?
No, what, Dean?
I'm not gonna pretend
like you're firing me
for a legit work reason when the truth is
you're only pissed off
'cause I won't tap that.
Get out of my office.
Oh, come on, Gayle.
I'm about to call corporate
and have you blacklisted
from every showroom in the country.
Great. Put it on speaker.
What?
I'll tell them how
you promote using only your vagina.
(CHUCKLES)
You think I'm Roger Ailes?
No one cares about me.
And they certainly don't care about you.
They care about Eric.
He's a lifer.
So?
So he knows everything.
Why would he risk his job for you?
Because I promised him yours
once I get you out.
So here's what's gonna happen.
I'm gonna walk back over there.
I'm gonna complete that sale
you so rudely interrupted.
I'm gonna take another of Jeff's leads
and another and another
and I'm gonna turn
this joke of an operation
into the number one leader
in Southeast Michigan's regional sales.
Open or closed?
Leave.
Is there a website I can go to?
Your donation today
helps get a baby out of the trash.
I don't have any cash on me.
How were you gonna buy the water?
We're happy to take a card.
Maybe next time.
How much longer can we do this?
ANNIE: Deep breaths.
Everybody just stay calm.
We can figure this out.
Don't worry, ladies.
I'm licensed to carry.
Where is it?
Get out of here.
Not until I get it all back.
Hey, man, we don't want any trouble.
Yeah? Well, you should've told her that
before she cleaned out
my wife's jewelry box.
What's he talking about?
So go to Cartier and buy her some more.
Or I'll just go to the cops.
Okay, yeah, then they can take
my statement.
I'm not gonna leave out
any details for your wife.
That was my soup.
Oh. Oops. Sorry.
STAN: What the hell was that?
Those guys are all dicks.
Is that where the money came from?
I'm doing his wife a favor.
He's gonna replace it
with something better.
What do you got me involved in?
These guys are all the same, okay?
They send their wives off
to New York to see Dear Evan Hansen
while they hump Detroit.
Jesus, Krystal.
They totally deserve it.
And how much of my cut is from Cartier?
All of it.
They don't tip, either.
I got another one this weekend
if you're still down.
Do either of you ladies have a phone?
Because I don't.
Mine's in my truck.
Uh...
Let me look.
Hands where I can see 'em!
Okay, go ahead, honey.
Nothing's been stolen, right?
Not a dime.
Okay.
How about...
before this gets real ugly,
we just let him go?
Yeah, that sounds about right.
He looks sorry.
You have no idea.
Call the cops.
What?
No bars.
Hey!
(GUNSHOT)
(SCREAMS)
MAN: Is everyone okay?
No.
Okay, thank you.
They're on their way.
What do I do?
BETH: Okay, thank you.
Try to stop the bleeding.
How?
Can I get a Gatorade?
Anything you want, baby girl.
When you get your permit,
it's just a stupid class.
The green kind.
They don't let you practice.
Get the woman a Gatorade, Jason.
Okay, okay.
All right.
Can you make it tighter?
I'm trying.
Where's my drink?
JASON: Okay, they're out of green.
They're out of green, baby girl.
Anything else sound good, huh?
Frappuccino. Mocha.
Frap! Mocha!
JASON: Uh, got it.
This isn't working.
There's still too much blood.
Okay. Sponges.
Aisle three.
And behind that, Saran wrap.
Here we go.
Ice scrapers.
Back wall.
You want a straw, mama? Huh?
Does that sound yum?
Am I gonna make it?
Will you shut up and drink your frap?
Here we go. This is it.
It's go time.
Need a fluids run up.
And get a blood ox, please.
Is she gonna be okay?
Jesus. Who did this?
Why?
You?
Bullet almost nicked the femoral artery.
I mean, you saved her leg.
I did?
Maybe her life.
(GASPS)
Oh, no.
PARAMEDIC: Let's go.
Someone call Stan.
Of course.
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
Dial it down a notch.
"Lionel Richie easy"?
No one knows you were there.
We even did it on a Sunday.
Yeah, because we don't get
deliveries on Sundays.
Until you did.
He was supposed to come tomorrow.
And I asked for a knife.
Yeah, well, what the hell is that?
This is something you split a bagel with.
What do I look like? Rambo?
Okay, I did the job.
I want my cut.
Okay.
I'm sorry, what the hell are you doing?
Oh, what's 10%
of zero, again?
Oh, yeah, zero!
I believe I'm owed something
for my pain and suffering.
You know, at least
you didn't take a bullet like your girl.
Bunny got shot?
She gonna be okay?
Yeah.
Thanks to me.
STAN: You are a lucky lady.
'Cause I got you.
You got grazed.
Want to know what happened?
Mmm...
Mmm-mmm. Not now.
Did you get the hospital bill?
(SIGHS) Can't look.
I told those ambulance guys
I'd get an Uber.
After being shot?
(CHUCKLES)
I'd have got an SUV.
(LAUGHING)
At least the crutches were free.
Yeah, I stole those.
What?
They were just sitting
by themselves next to the elevator.
Stanley.
They wanted to charge us
400 bucks for them things.
(LAUGHS)
BETH: Hey, how's the patient?
Flying high on painkillers.
Ooh. What color are they?
Hey.
It wasn't supposed to--
Yeah, tell that to my kids.
RUBY: The universe has balanced itself.
Telling you, it's karma.
Dude, you gotta hear this.
Remind you of any Canadians you know?
Oh, stop.
I shot a man.
A man shot me.
I don't think the universe
is keeping score for Big Mike.
The circle is complete.
Well, almost.
I did save your life.
Now I wish you had let me bleed out.
So what do we do here?
Well, JT says he's down
to try again if we are.
Are you out of your mind?
Well, his nephew still needs a saxophone.
We are done with that.
Okay, So we just go sit on the curb
and wait for the van to pull up?
Because, you know, that's what happens
when you steal from a gang.
We should let tampon boy take his shot.
Yeah, and then he misses, and gosh,
this looks familiar.
Where am I?
Oh, I'm back in the van with all y'all.
RUBY: He might not miss.
ANNIE: Max-y Pad's gonna miss.
Have you ever fired it?
When I was little.
With bullets?
Well...
we'll just walk through the basics.
Max.
Yeah.
Grab the gun.
(ROCK SONG PLAYING)
Oh, boy.
Pro tip.
Exhale before you pull the trigger.
Why?
Well, most people hold their breath,
which increases your pulse
and makes your hand shake.
How'd you learn that?
Him.
You can buy expensive cars
(GUNSHOT)
Oh, oh, oh, no! Oh, wow!
It's okay!
Oh, that's loud. I can't--
Shake it.
Wow.
Here. I brought these.
Oh, yeah.
Thank you.
You want some of this?
Exhale.
Blow his head off
In your dreams
Show no mercy
(INAUDIBLE)
And all your bad...
Just do a little shoulder roll.
Feel good? Feel loose?
I'm good-- (GUNSHOT)
Oh! I'm sorry.
(SCREAMS)
Who's a badass?
You are.
Oh, me.
Yes.
That was good.
Die.
I don't know if I could do this.
Just kidding.
Your bad days will end
(INAUDIBLE)
(SONG CONTINUES PLAYING)
We'll just get you
close enough so you won't miss.
What is this?
You wanted to meet my ink guy.
You want something?
Sprite. No ice.
Hey, can you hook my man
up here with a Sprite, no ice?
So you fly private or commercial?
Pardon?
Oklahoma, right?
And based on what you're charging me,
I figure you must got, like,
a G6 or something.
Well, I talked to Max here
about your cost concerns.
Oh, yeah?
And I think he has a solution
to make it all go away.
That right?
MAN 2: Here you go, guys.
Sprite. No ice.
RIO: I'm all ears.
Go ahead.
I need to tell you something.
Okay.
Just...
give it to him straight.
I've made a mistake.
I shouldn't have tried
to raise my prices on you.
You almost lost a customer.
(STAMMERING) I am sorry.
All good.
Glad we could work it out.
BETH: Wait.
That all?
Thank you for the pop.
Yeah, on the house.
You work with really smart people.
MAX: I wet myself.
That's okay.
Are you mad?
My kids do it all the time.
Not about that.
It wouldn't have made you feel better.
Just makes you feel nothing.
That sounds nice.
It's not.
How do you know?
(SIGHS) I just know.
Can I ask for one thing, please?
But we just got her.
I Know.
You can have my allowance
to buy her food.
Sweetie, it's not about money.
I'll clean her cage.
Where's Emma?
She says she doesn't care.
Well, Mommy didn't know,
but Dorito already had a family.
Then why'd they give her up?
We love her.
She was sick, and we made her better.
And now she has to go home
to her real family.
Aren't we her real family?
Well, you know what?
We'll get another pet.
We will?
Only this time, you choose.
Anything you want.
Snake.
Snake. Yes!
How about a gerbil?
Or a hamster?
Oh, remember that cute rabbit
that you wanted
from the farmer's market?
Yeah.
And then we can feed him to the snake.
(LAUGHING)
Yeah!
Let's go look up snakes.
Yeah, let's go.
I'm sorry.
This is the last thing he takes from us.
Hey, kids, movie night.
Sam Jackson on a plane.
It's educational.
Hey, Stanimal.
You want in?
Make sure no melds drop out
of your G-string this time.
If I do this, I'mma do it right.
Always two parties.
First one, you earn their trust.
You treat 'em like kings
while I case the castle.
Then say you had such a great time,
you're gonna come back,
bring more girls. Do it up.
That's when we take 'em down.
But only the most expensive piece.
'Cause with one, they're rich enough
to think they just lost it.
Let me know what time Saturday.
Stan.
Are you sure?
STAN: We're talking two horsepower,
zero to 60 in half a day.
What?
But faster than them damn crutches.
(HONKING)
Careful. Watch the corner.
Watch the corner! Hey!
That might've been a mistake.
How'd you get insurance to cover it?
DEAN: All right.
KENNY: Have to go so bad.
DEAN: I Know, I know, I know.
Give him the keys.
BETH: Here, here.
DEAN: There you go.
There you go. Go, go, go, go.
Hey, real quick.
Let me ask you a question.
What do you think about Las Vegas?
I think we can't afford a vacation.
No. Like, to live.
Why there?
It's not here.
(CHILDREN YELLING)
What is that?
KENNY: Come on, come on!
You're still in here?
A little privacy, please.
The door was open.
Just give me, like, one more minute.
What are you doing?
(SIGHS) Righting my ship
and finding my port.
Ew. Light a match when you're done.
But I don't know
It's simple and so complicated
I could walk all day
On the railroad tracks
But there's much more
So how'd you pay for it?
To it than that
You really want to know?
You want to know
what happened in that store?
Why throw stones, right?
You know all of my Secret ideas
The ones I'm giving up on
And the ones I'll keep
I'd tell you why But I don't know
It's simple and so complicated
I could walk all day
On the railroad tracks
Where's all our stuff?
Shh.
To it than that
I'm so lucky 'Cause I asked you once
What are you doing?
Do you want to come up
For a cup of tea?
Come visit with me
We'll play guitars
And I will give you My number
I'd tell you why
What's it say?