RUBY: Previously on Good Girls...
Did you remove a pen cap
from the evidence locker?
I failed. It's over.
I tried to seduce my therapist.
He straight-up rejected me.
You've missed two sessions.
There's no point, okay?
I made it weird.
If you don't come back,
I've got to fill your spot.
There's been a bit of a snafu.
You don't say.
What if I made it up to you?
Not him, but you?
It'd be a huge order.
You would draw it?
We make an engraver's plate
and print it all on-site.
Cool.
You cannot finish that plate.
He said he'd let me go...
He won't.
Wait. You need us.
You need all of us.
RIO: Not all of you.
(GUN FIRES)
Have you heard from Lucy?
I'm sure she's fine.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
What is it?
(SIGHS) Her and the boyfriend.
So happy.
Little do they know.
We're just torturing ourselves.
Why did you take all this?
I couldn't leave it there.
Why not?
Her phone was ringing.
Someone would notice
something horrible happened.
Something horrible did happen.
And we just stood there and watched.
I didn't watch.
Honestly, neither did I.
I did.
Saw the whole thing.
Annie.
It could've been us.
She never even used this.
What are we gonna do?
Print.
JANE: Mommy, where are you?
Here.
Something happened with Dorito!
Oh, my God, what?
He can sing!
No way.
ANNIE: Wow.
Let me just drop my bag.
Uh, Dorothy wants to see you.
Oh, Dorothy's here?
In the back.
Is everything okay?
She's the one who saw her last.
I wouldn't say we're
best friends, exactly.
Lucy would.
Sisters, more like.
She's just the sweetest little thing.
I wish there was something I could do.
You could head our media coverage.
DOROTHY: Consider it done.
MAX: Like, start a hotline.
DOROTHY: I could print beautiful posters.
Oh, do they still do those
adorable pictures on milk cartons?
Okay.
Who will lead the air search, Officer?
Pump the brakes, folks.
We really can't do much
till it's been 72 hours.
Now where'd you last see her?
We worked together the other night.
Anything unusual?
BETH: No.
I left, and she stayed and locked up.
DOROTHY:
Well, no more of that.
What do you mean?
Well, I'm closing early
till we get Some answers.
Well, how will we work nights?
We're not, sweetie.
Hmm.
What about everything
that was in her fridge
or, like, her laundry
that was in the dryer.
I mean, does someone fold that now,
or does it all just end up
in a trash bag out on the curb?
Well, how are you all related again?
She was someone my sister worked with.
I meant Gregg and Nancy.
I wrecked their marriage.
Ah, that's right.
And what about, like, her Instagram?
Or any of her social media?
Just frozen in time now
like those clocks at Chernobyl.
She had this lipstick.
She never even opened it.
Like, it was from France or something.
I mean it must've cost her
like half her paycheck.
You know?
It's like a Cinderella level
lip scenario.
You can tell that she thought
she was really going
somewhere special with it,
but instead she just went poof.
Can I ask you something?
Please.
(SNIFFS)
Are you wearing perfume?
Excuse me?
I'm smelling something floral.
Uh...
From the moment you sat down.
I don't wear perfume.
Body wash?
Just plain soap.
Hmm.
So I guess what I really
want to know is...
When do I stop seeing it in my brain?
Any lotions or fabric softeners?
Are you being serious?
Sometimes the boxes
for scented and unscented look the same.
Someone died.
I wanna help you.
Thank you.
For that to work,
I need complete and total honesty.
Okay.
Let's start over.
Great.
Are you wearing perfume?
HARRY: It's not fair!
SARA: That's how you play.
Last game.
Heads hit pillows in ten.
Uno!
SARA: Uh, you got two cards.
HARRY: So?
"Uno" means one, dummy.
Remember when we thought
the age difference
would help them get along?
My suspension is up for review.
How?
Uh, maybe with Turner gone,
the DA doesn't have enough.
So what's it mean?
They might give me my badge back.
Do you want it back?
You're gonna be a cop again, Daddy?
Well, they gotta
talk to Mommy and me about it first.
Why do they wanna talk to me?
Not about egg roll.
Then what's it about?
I don't know.
Make me look good.
All right, chop-chop.
I don't have it.
Really? Again?
I don't Know what to say.
I don't have it.
(RIO SIGHS)
She was a good person.
Seemed like a really sweet girl.
You didn't have to do it.
Kinda did.
She never would've said anything.
Rotten egg's a rotten egg.
It's just business, darling.
Well, now you've screwed
your entire enterprise.
Oh, yeah? How's that?
Her boyfriend,
who is also a very good person,
by the way
is beside himself and has called the cops.
Mm. (CHUCKLES)
Yeah.
And he's got the woman
who owns this place so freaked out,
she's got it on lockdown,
so great job, Mr. CFO!
So who's the boyfriend?
Why?
'Cause he's gonna need an address.
No.
We gotta get back up and running.
I got my own debts to pay, all right?
No!
Oh, you still think you get
a say in this, huh?
Nah, see that ship sailed when
you put three slugs in me.
This is your fault!
You, me, we?
It's just business.
I'll print.
But what happened?
I thought you were on lockdown?
I'll find a way.
Gee, thanks.
That'll make it easier on everybody.
(CAR DRIVING OFF)
ANNIE: Are you sure this is hers?
BETH: It was in her purse.
RUBY: 1-2-3-4?
ANNIE: Nope.
What's her birthday?
BETH: I have no idea.
RUBY: 4-3-2-1.
What's Au Jus's birthday?
Oh, like I'd know that.
And I'm locked out again.
What were you gonna text him anyway?
I don't Know, like,
"I need space, and so I left town."
Oh, like an Eat Pray Love situation?
Oh, that's good.
I mean, it's, like,
he's been smothering me
and loving me too hard
and maybe I wanna buy
my own tampons for a change.
Hey, hold up.
He's buying you tampons now?
Not me. Lucy.
She's gonna dump his ass
so he calls off the cops
before they go all CS/.
It's Kinda harsh.
Yeah, better than kinda dead.
I'm sorry, why did you think
we were trying to break into the phone?
For everything you guys just said,
just I thought we were gonna
slide into his DMs.
Oh, hello!
What's the boyfriend's birthday?
How would I know that?
Don't you wanna ask the bird?
Okay. I'm just trying to be a team player
and get into that phone.
Okay, well, there's
a million possibilities,
and we're never gonna guess it.
It's the new one.
So?
What?
There's another way to get in.
You want some?
I'm good.
Can I get some more bronco sauce?
Yeah, one sec.
So...
Can you get it?
She's not in one piece.
I don't need all of her.
What do you need?
I just need her face.
WAITER:
Bronco sauce.
You still owe me for the last favor.
I expected you would bring that up,
so I thought I would triple
your invitation order.
(CHUCKLES)
How you gonna do that?
You can't even make your regular delivery.
Exactly.
It's a vicious cycle, don't you see?
I can't help you if you don't help me.
Or...
Or?
You can give me something I Know you got.
It's been on my mind for a while now.
What's that?
(LAUGHS) Your husband won't like it.
I have herpes.
I want a hot tub.
Oh.
You say your prayers?
In my head!
That works.
(BEEPING)
What is that, sir?
Nothing.
That better not be my phone.
I've been to hell and back
looking for that thing.
Give it to me.
One more game!
Better give me that phone
before I "one more game" you.
Go to sleep.
Good night.
Mm, how's this gonna work?
How's what gonna work?
How's Daddy supposed to be a cop again?
What do you mean?
He'll have to arrest you.
I mean, right?
Like, at some point.
Don't forget to floss.
Hey, do you have a second?
He won't eat.
Since when?
The kids said he stopped singing.
Come on, Dorito.
Come on, lick it.
Come here, lick it.
Lick it for Dada.
How long does it take to get a hot tub?
Um, um, depends on the model
and the upgrades?
Is there, like, a floor model you could
get right away?
He's just not himself.
What if he is sick?
I need your help.
I can't watch another thing die.
Dean.
Neither can I.
How many does this one hold?
Um, that particular brand
has four contoured lounge seats.
But how many people can you fit?
I guess that would depend on you.
Okay.
Yeah, I'm also gonna need
that laser filtration.
Ooh, that's a much bigger
price point. (CHUCKLES)
Is that a problem?
Welcome to the Four Star family.
Whoo! All right.
Let's do this.
Well, I...
I just have to transmit this.
It's gonna just take me a...
(CHUCKLES) Not this.
That.
Now?
RUBY: Uh-oh.
What?
Too dark, too quiet,
too perfect a place to kill some suckers.
Man, why you gotta put that in my head?
Because unfortunately,
I have been in way too many
of these situations,
and now I know what to look for.
Following a murderer
two hours through cornfields
in the middle of the night?
Cool it.
I'm sorry, what more did you need to see?
Just that. Drive.
He's not gonna kill us.
He knows Dean's not putting in the order
till we get back.
You should've seen his face.
He really wants a hot tub.
Which one is it?
I didn't bury her.
How many fresh ones left?
Two more.
Okay.
I can't do another one.
This is the one.
I can feel it.
Hey. We need the light.
Sorry. We've got that
review thing tomorrow.
Stan doesn't Know what to wear.
What are you gonna say?
I don't Know. Suit?
I mean, to the police review
people or whatever.
He's wanted to be a cop
since third grade.
He'd still be one if it wasn't for me.
So you go in there and you make it right.
What happens the next time
he has to cover for my criminal ass?
It'll be more than probation.
Well, maybe there won't be a next time.
We're digging up the body of a girl
who would still be singing to her bird
if she hadn't met us.
There'll be a next time.
(SIGHS)
He doesn't wanna wear a Suit.
You know he can't be a cop again.
You know that, right?
What am I gonna do?
Yo. Give me some more light.
They're hers.
Ugh. Ugh, ugh, ugh. Oh.
We're gonna have to uncover her face.
Give me a wet wipe.
(COUGHS)
Give me another one.
Give me her phone.
We're in.
Oh, God.
(SIGHS)
I'm gonna tell Stan to wear
a sweater and khakis.
Always classy.
DEAN: It's a tumor.
What?
Stage four.
What are you talking about?
He's got a hard, hot lump
right where he poops, you can feel it.
I'm not doing that.
Wing MD says it could be a feather cyst,
but the Beak Brothers,
they have this YouTube channel...
Why don't we make
an appointment with a vet
instead of YouTube?
There's only, like,
one avian guy in all of Detroit.
Make an appointment.
Just gonna say chemo.
It's probably a lot more
expensive than human chemo.
(CHITTERS)
Little guy's a goner.
What did you say?
He's toast.
Dunzo. It's over.
That's not gonna happen.
It's like we're built
on an Indian burial ground or something.
Look at me.
I'm officially cursed.
Dean.
What?
I will get the money.
(SCOFFS) How?
If I have to rob every bank in the city,
I will do it.
This bird is gonna make it.
Oh, okay.
Dorito can't die.
I'll make an appointment.
Thank you.
It's okay.
(SOBBING)
It's gonna be okay.
I read that the human body
starts decomposing
within a matter of minutes.
Like, one second you're this grape,
all juicy and plump.
And the next, you're just
a shriveled-up raisin.
Mm-hmm.
I can't get away from it.
Ever tried to talk to her?
Who?
The face you keep seeing.
She's dead.
She ever talk to you?
Again...
What other faces do you see?
This isn't like a, uh...
Like a Sixth Sense thing,
if that's what you're...
I don't think you're talking
to dead people, Annie.
Oh. Good.
Hallucinatory psychosis
can present for many reasons.
Let me ask you a question.
Can't wait.
Is the face in the room
with us right now?
(SIGHS)
What's the last thing he texted?
"Where are you?"
"Please call me."
"I'm worried."
There's a whole lot of those.
Before that.
"I'm scared you're dead."
"Toppings for taco night."
What did they choose?
The usual.
Cheese, lettuce, tomato.
Hard or soft shell?
No one chooses soft.
Yeah, they do.
Flour or corn?
They do not.
They do bowls, too, with rice.
Then it ain't really taco night, is it?
And what would you Call it?
Mexican food.
BETH: All right, let's get this over with.
"I'm sorry it's taken so long
to get back to you,
"but I needed some time."
No, you can't say that.
He's gonna think she's coming back.
Right.
"I'm not in a place
"to be in a relationship right now."
That's good.
Yeah, say the "it's not you,
it's me" thing.
No one says that.
Everyone says that.
"It's not your fault."
Aka, "It's not you, it's me."
"And..."
Just do it.
We're saving his life.
Jugular.
"I'm not in love with you anymore."
Shrug emoji.
BETH: No.
Broken heart emoji.
Why do I need an emoji?
It lessens the blow.
Oh, to the moon with a smiley face,
like, "Good night, goodbye, it's over."
Fine.
Now what?
We wait and see if he buys it.
Bubbles.
Wow, he really misses her.
Oh, they went away.
They're back.
What's it say?
"I think we should have
this conversation face-to-face."
Oh, no.
Say she's out of town.
Bubbles.
"Don't be mad."
Why would I be mad?
I mean, Lucy.
Bubbles.
"I used Find My Phone.
I Know you're at your friend's house."
Turn it off.
Now?
What does that do?
Give me the SIM card.
Why?
So I can smash it.
So this is the last known location?
Okay, so what are we gonna do
when he shows up here?
Tell him she's napping?
It's not the worst idea you've ever had.
Yeah, it is.
Might buy us a night.
What are you doing?
Beth.
What'd you say?
To come over.
Why would you say that?
Because at this point,
it is either him or the cops!
I'm sorry, but this is definitely
the worst idea
any of us have ever had.
What could we possibly tell
that child right now?
That she's gone.
STAN: Thank you, everyone.
I appreciate your time.
(SIGHS)
How'd it go?
We'll see.
You're up next, baby.
I'm gonna be frank with you, Mrs. Hill.
Although he was never formally charged,
you can understand
we have a few reservations
about reinstating him.
Right.
The department had reason
to believe that your husband
was compromised
by some kind of outside influence.
Can I geta glass of water?
Quick top-off.
We're ready when you are.
Has your family experienced any kind
of financial hardship
since Mr. Hill's probation?
What does that have to do with anything?
Can be a risk factor.
(SIGHS) We've got it pretty bad.
Do you feel your husband's
under a lot of pressure because of it?
I mean, I don't know
if you've ever been in a situation
where you can't pay your bills.
Add to that two tiny mouths to feed.
It's a pressure you can't imagine.
How do you both manage that stress?
We dream about robbing banks.
Excuse me?
Yeah, plan the whole thing.
Which banks, disguises,
hostage negotiations.
Stan being a cop, he knows all the tricks.
And don't get me wrong,
it's not just banks.
Jewelry stores, art galleries.
We wouldn't even rule out a home invasion
if, you know, it was the right zip code.
What's kept you from doing it?
Nothing. I'd do it in a heartbeat.
The problem is, um...
He would lock me up
and throw away the key.
Let me tell you something
about my husband.
This is aman who let Richie Green
copy off his geometry test in ninth grade
and is still sick about it.
It haunts him.
When they're giving out
free samples at Costco,
he takes one, even if no one is looking.
He couldn't commit a crime
if his life depended on it.
And if you knew him,
you wouldn't question his moral fitness.
Hell, you wouldn't have
suspended him in the first place.
Because Stanley Lamont Hill is a Cop,
whether you give him a badge or not.
So,
if there's nothing else,
I have nails to paint.
Thank you for your candor.
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
Is she here?
I just wanna see Lucy. Lucy!
Lucy! Lulu!
She's not here.
Why don't you sit?
So where is she?
I don't know.
She just texted me this morning.
And then I drove her right
to the airport after that.
She left?
Have you ever been dumped?
I married my first boyfriend.
Then you don't know.
You want it?
Sure.
(SNIFFLES)
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
Arizona.
Huh.
Why do all shrinks suck?
Here's another five star.
"I found Dr. Sears on Groupon."
Next.
Okay.
This one has three stars.
First session is free.
Hmm, me likey.
Uh-oh.
What?
Someone says his couch pulls out.
How far away, though?
No!
Fine. Next.
This guy seems cool.
How many reviews?
Pages.
I'm listening.
"Sense of humor."
Love.
"Feel like he cares."
"Great with difficult personalities."
Okay. Hit me.
2.2 miles away.
Done and done.
Dr. Josh Cohen.
(SIGHS)
No.
You don't mind, right?
Just, uh...
Just a moment, Tim.
(SIGHS)
I wanna come back.
Window's closed.
But I've seen, like,
every therapist in Detroit.
That can't be true.
Fine. Two.
There are others.
I can refer you.
You can waste their time.
(SCOFFS)
What is wrong with you?
You quit me.
Yeah, and now I'm trying to un-quit you.
Already gave away your session.
You're the worst.
Excuse me?
How are you not gonna help someone
who is standing in front of you
literally begging for your help?
Oh, now you want help?
It's, like, against your oath
or whatever.
You sit on that beanbag making jokes,
while real people come in here...
Children.
And do the work 'cause they wanna
get better.
I want to get better.
You hijack appointments,
and you get off on making a scene.
You only want attention.
I'm just scared.
Of what?
That if I died tomorrow,
the only thing that people
would remember about me
is what was in my purse.
What's in it?
Some parking tickets,
an old cheese stick,
a single googly eye,
sunglasses case.
I lost the sunglasses.
That's quite an obit.
Right?
Friday at 8:30.
A.m. or p.m.?
It's kind of early.
I'll make it work.
Why'd you change your mind?
'Cause that was so sad.
Pathetic, really.
Okay.
A real therapist
would probably have you committed.
Well, guess I'm in luck, then.
Better not get any of that fruit gunk
on Daddy's cap.
He said I can keep it.
Well, what'd they say?
That they'd be honored
to have me back on the force.
(CAN POPS)
That's a good thing, right?
Yeah.
Then I came home, tried on my uniform.
Just didn't feel right.
So I'll let the pants out.
I'll fit it.
No, it made me...
It made me feel like a fraud, Ruby.
Can't fix that.
NURSE: Dorito Boland?
That's me.
I'm Dorito's dad.
Soon to be grandpa.
What?
It's not a tumor.
She's laying an egg.
Wait, what?
Got caught in her oviduct.
That's the lump you felt.
Dr. Cromwell's gonna aspirate,
but she'll be fine.
Dorito's a girl?
Oh, thank you.
Okay, have a good night.
Okay, you, too.
(LOCK CLICKS)
I have all this extra birdseed
and I don't need it anymore.
Do you guys take donations?
RIO: Looks a little light.
I couldn't make as much.
Why's that?
The price of ink went up.
Gonna need to see that invoice.
Thought you might.
How's the boyfriend?
He got over it.
They always do.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
MAX: Hold the elevator!
Thanks.
Where'd you get your bird?
Oh, my wife rescued her.
What's its name?
Dorito.
(WHISTLING FRERE JACQUES)
(BIRD WHISTLES FRERE JACQUES)
(ELEVATOR DINGS)