RUBY: Previously on Good Girls...
I think you could be something.
And he's making money off our backs.
Yeah, and with our asses on the line.
Why don't you just tell me
what you're looking for.
Fifty-fifty.
Do we have a deal or not?
Mm-hmm.
Great.
They're counterfeiters.
The paper's all totally legit,
but the bills are all in sequence.
TURNER: How's it going with the sister?
ANNIE: And you're FBI!
I love you.
So what happens next?
RUBY: Stan is in a jail cell.
ANNIE: Because of us.
STAN: I'm out on leave.
Can't even get my old job
back at the mall
because they think I'm a felon.
Never again though, right?
Okay.
What do you want?
Her.
Are you going to arrest me?
Thanks for the coffee.
Oh, my God, and then what?
Let's see how you do.
I made you something.
It's literally like nail-polish remover,
hydrogen peroxide, and bleach.
What's that thing I always tell you
when you make a big ol' mess?
MARCUS: That I gotta clean it up.
All right, come on.
No more grown-up talk.
That's your problem.
Take care of it.
He's not my problem!
Shut your mouth, bitch,
okay? And just hand...
(SCREAMS)
Go!
What do you say I call 'em now?
You still got odds.
(GRUNTS AND LAUGHS)
We got a deal?
We can totally do this without him.
We're free.
It's a shock when someone dies.
The lights go out.
One last breath.
That's it.
The end.
So quick.
But it stays with you.
(ENGINE STARTS)
Wait, what color is that?
Bubblegum Bellini.
I wanted Kiss My Lips Pink.
But you said Bubblegum Bellini.
B-R-B.
This person that you knew, or whatever...
They're just gone.
And it's so weird.
'Cause, like...
Did you ever know him at all?
Yeah, I didn't.
He just worked for my mom.
She said get one of those sad cards.
On the back wall.
To the right.
Between "Bar Mitzvah"
and "Just Because."
(TIRES SCREECHING)
That'll be 15 bucks.
All I got are ones.
Gracias.
(ENGINE REVS)
Kiss My Ass Pink.
LUCY:
Mommy loves you.
Now be a good boy
and go night-night, okay?
Oh, say good night to Au Jus.
Good night, Au Jus.
"Bye."
(LAUGHS)
(CLICKS TONGUE)
Love you.
Why don't you go home?
Uh, it's my turn.
I gotcha.
But you've been closing every night.
Go have dinner with your boyfriend.
He doesn't eat on Tuesdays.
He does intermittent fasting.
What's wrong with this one?
Serif on the S.
Lucy, it's perfect.
Well, just didn't feel right, so...
Well, it will all be here tomorrow.
Tomorrow, we have that quinceañera.
Oh, my God. Go home.
Okay, I... 1, uh...
I'll do this at home.
Good night.
Good night!
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
It's freezing out here.
I was about to slice up
a horse and crawl in Revenant style.
Where you gonna find a horse?
Fine. A big dog.
Or a hunting knife?
At this hour?
It's a good thing
I'm also starving to death.
'Cause I'll use my teeth,
and I'll eat my way in.
You'd never get through the rib cage.
Well, I wouldn't start there.
Oh, she's gonna eat some horse ass.
Least I'd be warm and full, bitch.
Let's do this.
(MACHINE STARTS)
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
Paper feels right.
What'd you do different this time?
Scrabble tiles in the dryer.
On delicate?
Permanent press for 30, air fluff for 10.
Hmm. It's got that glow now, too.
One part Sassy Apricot,
two parts Creamsicle Sunset.
Mm.
Mm...
Is that a good "mm"
or a bad "mm"?
Yeah, nuh-uh.
What do you mean,
"Yeah, nuh-uh"?
This ain't gonna fly.
Why not?
Your Hamilton's whack.
Wha...
Just test it in the machine.
Don't need to.
It would help if you could
pinpoint what exactly is whack
so we could make adjustments.
All right.
Check it. First up.
Your boy's bouffant is wildin' out.
What? Where?
Hairline's off about 17 microns.
What program did you use this time?
You know...
I don't know.
How do you not know?
It was Editor's Choice in Macworld.
And what's going on here?
Looks like you got
an extra shadow right there.
No, that...
That is exactly his little thingy.
You trippin' if that's how you think
our founding father wears his cravat.
These are microscopic inconsistencies.
It's close enough.
Okay, boo.
Close enough 'll get you 10 to 20
in the state pen.
Can you please just put it
in the machine?
How long did this batch take?
Three weeks.
(ANNIE SIGHS)
How many ones you shred?
(BEEPS)
Denied.
Ugh.
Rome wasn't built in a day.
It burned down in a night.
(ENGINE SWITCHES OFF)
And I was like,
"Gwen, when we're talking about my child,
"you do not wanna see
my temper get away from me."
And what did she say?
That it was a pre-existing condition.
Hmm.
But she would appeal
the decision with the powers that be.
Babe, I got us covered this month.
That's not the point, Stanley.
We shouldn't have to pay for meds.
We pay for insurance.
KRYSTAL: Hey.
Hey, Krystal.
Hey, how do I heat from frozen again?
Hit baked potato twice,
and you wanna stir it in between.
KRYSTAL:
Thanks, Stanimal.
(MICROWAVE DOOR CLOSES)
(MICROWAVE BUTTONS BEEPING)
(KRYSTAL SIGHS)
Little man at dance class today.
Come on now.
Oh, and he says he hates hip-hop
and wants to do tap next year.
We worked so hard on that stanky leg.
KRYSTAL: Is that your kid?
STAN: Mm-hmm.
(KRYSTAL GASPS)
That's Little Money right there.
Aw.
And that's Miss Sara.
Aw, she looks like you.
And he looks like you.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
KRYSTAL:
Aw, I just want to eat
their little faces.
You know?
(LAUGHS)
So sweet, aw.
Mm-hmm, yeah.
I wanna have five kids.
(GIGGLES)
(STAN LAUGHS)
I hope they look like that.
Here you go, baby.
Bye.
See ya.
Oh, don't forget,
we have to go to that
rummage sale at the church on Saturday.
I told them that we would try...
KRYSTAL: Oops, you're right!
One more on baked potato.
I tried to tell you.
(WHISPERS) It's for our baby girl.
(KRYSTAL SIGHS)
What do I hit for popcorn?
Popcorn.
(SOFTLY) Wow.
(TV PLAYING INDISTINCTLY)
Guys, socks and shoes.
We're going to the park.
I'm sick of the park.
My socks are dirty.
Mine, too.
Turn them inside out.
KENNY: We already did that.
Hey, you're home early.
Yeah, I snuck out on break.
I gotta get back. Here.
Another blue envelope came.
Thanks, honey.
(SIGHS) They're gonna take the house.
We just need to make a payment.
It'll get 'em off our backs.
I'll ask for Some more hours.
Can you sell some more hot tubs?
It's spas.
Spas, sorry.
NEWS ANCHOR:
And coming up at 5:00,
Channel 4's own
Kristi Dooling joins the FBI
on a dangerous raid,
as they continue their mission
to clean up gang activity
on the East Side...
You guys, now, come on.
KIDS: Mom!
Hey!
Now, in the car.
I think they've officially OD'd
on the park.
Well...
It's free.
So he would cry every time
the ball hit his foot,
and I was like,
"Sweetie, it's okay.
"It's soccer, it's Supposed to do that."
Ugh, he's my hero.
So there's an opening on the team.
Oh, my God.
I could talk to Coach Freddy.
You don't have to do that.
It could be a good distraction.
How's he sleeping?
Last night, he crawled in with me,
asking to call Daddy.
Poor thing.
EMMA: Can Marcus have a juice box?
Papi, we've got our own in the car.
Don't be silly.
Hey, you want some animal crackers, too?
What do we say to Jane's mommy?
Thank you, Mrs. Boland.
You're welcome.
You're too good to him.
No kid should be without his daddy.
It's one of those tank killers, right?
You know it could land
even if it's missing a wing?
Here you go.
I just think it looks dope.
Think about what you want?
Pistons.
Season tickets, courtside.
So every fool you've put away
can see you up there on the jumbotron?
You wouldn't make it to halftime.
White sand beach.
Warm blue water.
Couple beers and a chair.
The farther, the better.
Mm-hmm.
One last name popped up.
Okay.
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
BEN: Mom, your friend's here.
Hey you.
Hey... You.
Yeah, so I was in your hood and thought
I'd say what's up.
What's up?
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah, uh, sorry.
Do we... Do we know each other?
Uh...
Yeah, you...
You crashed into my car on the freeway,
and then we pulled over
and, uh, exchanged information.
You know, in the back seat.
Chris!
Kevin.
I'm out.
Uh, love you.
Text me from Dad's.
Hey, guy, there's a Statute of limitations
on booty calls.
You said,
"Let's do this again sometime."
Well, still, I...
I don't do that kind of thing anymore.
An.
Okay, uh...
Would it be cool if I just
kind of did my own thing,
and you watched?
Daddy!
What's up, Li'I Money!
'Sup, buddy? Ah!
(LAUGHS) Ah, what's up, dude?
Ooh, you smell like SweeTARTS.
STAN: It's a hazard of the job.
Did you see the president today?
He doesn't guard the president.
He guards the mayor.
HARRY: Does he like candy?
They all do, son, they all do.
'Sup, baby.
What happened to your face?
Oh, um, somebody
got a little handsy with the mayor.
All right.
RUBY: Here.
STAN: Hey.
They make me gag.
You have no idea what we're doing
to get those.
Yeah, baby. Bottoms up.
ANNIE: She could be an undercover cop.
BETH: She is not a cop.
ANNIE: You don't know that.
She could be wearing a wire.
She doesn't even know
what we're gonna Say.
You don't know that.
She just works at a paper store, okay?
Noah "just" worked at a grocery store.
She has birds.
How many?
More than one.
Great, so she's a nutcase.
Or worse.
What if she's a Mary Pat.
Well, we're not gonna
tell her what we're doing.
We didn't tell Mary Pat, either.
You guys, we don't have to do this, okay?
I talked to the dork at the Apple Store,
and I can fix the design issues.
I haven't paid my mortgage
in four months.
And Stan's gonna have
to get on that pole.
I just need a little bit
more time, and I can fi...
You're not an artist.
None of us are.
She has a masters in graphic design.
(SCOFFS)
I could do that.
After you graduate from high school?
And apply to college?
And attend college?
It's a vocation, okay?
You guys, you're gonna like her.
She's cool.
Looks like the gang's all here.
So, we wanted to talk to you
about doing some custom work for us.
What's the project?
Casino night.
For what?
Just a local charity.
What charity?
Gambling addicts.
You want to do a casino night
for gambling addicts?
Hair of the dog.
(CHUCKLES)
Anyway.
We need you to design the money
that we'll bet with.
I was thinking something simple,
like tens.
Look, I'm really good at what I do,
and if it got into the wrong hands,
you know, it's kind of like...
Counterfeit.
Oh, you guys.
I never even thought about that.
Wow.
Huh.
That did not even occur to me.
Oh, what if we put on the bill,
"There's more to life than gambling."
They just
wanna be treated like people.
They don't really wanna be judged.
Oh, we could put,
um, one of those old-time croupiers
with the wax mustache and armband on it.
I think we're just gonna
stick with the president.
Hamilton wasn't a president.
He was, actually.
No, he wasn't, actually.
They all were, you know,
like Franklin and...
Also not a president.
Jesus, any presidents
make it onto our currency?
Washington, Lincoln, Jefferson...
Okay.
What if
we print it all
on different colored paper?
Then I'm good.
Great! Great.
Okay.
Uh, hey, thank you though
for that, uh, heads-up.
Criminals. (CHUCKLES)
Can you even?
(ANNIE, BETH AND RUBY LAUGHING NERVOUSLY)
Yeah, I know, right?
(ALL LAUGHING)
Well.
(INAUDIBLE)
What's wrong with it this time?
Not a damn thing.
(MACHINE WHIRS AND BEEPS)
(LAUGHING)
You bitches just leveled up.
(LAUGHS)
I'mma keep this one.
I'm so sorry.
I had to dig.
Danny hid it in the back of the closet.
He's probably scared
you're gonna sign him back up.
Right?
Uh, by the way you never told me
Coach Freddy was hot.
Oh, you think we're watching
our kids at those games?
Man, thanks again for working your magic.
I wish I could do more.
His daddy's gonna be proud, too.
What do you mean?
Well, if he shows his face
before the season's over.
I thought you said he was gone.
Well, then he'll pop back up
like he always does.
And the poor kid won't know what hit him.
That's probably why
it didn't work out with us.
I'm so sorry.
Will you stop?
We're fine.
I think I have cleats, too.
Oh, hell no.
What size is he?
I'm not gonna tell you.
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
RUBY: Why are you blocking the door?
ANNIE: Move, move.
I can't keep this in my trunk.
ANNIE: Dude.
Mine doesn't even open, So...
My car almost got towed.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY) Yo.
Hey.
This is my...
I'm Rhea.
Hey.
Mrs. Boland, I made this for you.
Thank you.
BETH: / murdered the kid's dad, all right?
The least I could do
is get him into intramural sports.
You plunged into the way-deep end
of the pool
on this one, sis.
It's not gonna bring him back.
I don't wanna bring him back.
Then what's the point?
Maybe I can make their lives
a little bit better.
By lying?
By helping.
You know how you help
the family of the guy you ended?
Yeah, you get a teardrop tattoo
and you Call it a day.
You do nothing.
You guys don't know what it's like, okay?
Hey, I shot a guy, too.
ANNIE: I mean,
in the foot.
I'm just saying, kid lost a father.
Your guy lost a toe.
Okay, you know what?
Don't lose your chicken over it.
What does that even mean?
You Know what it means.
I literally don't know what that means.
Exactly what it sounds like.
It's like "having a cow,"
ya know?
Then say "having a cow."
Well, a cow is like, totally chill,
so you're not gonna just lose it
'cause it's just gonna stand there,
and a chicken is like
running around crazy,
you know what I'm saying?
No, I don't know what you're saying.
Well, that's your problem.
(DOOR CLOSES)
She's so weird.
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
LUCY: Oh, uh, we're closing.
TURNER: I just need a card.
I got it.
What's the occasion?
Thinking of you.
Right this way.
How ya been?
Busy.
Why don't you take that vacation?
Well, that's the thing about this gig.
Just when you think
you're finished, something new pops up.
There's funny, religious, dirty.
Still part-time?
I had to take on a few more hours.
It's not easy making an honest living.
You know, maybe a card's not enough.
We have, um, gag gifts up front.
Nah, I think I just need
to make an effort, you know?
Drop in on people more often.
LUCY: Tiny hands, rose gummiies...
I think he's good.
The travel straw?
All set, Lucy.
Be good, okay?
I hate a pop-by.
It's always when I take my face off.
The worst part is you never know when
they're gonna leave.
Or come back.
Maybe the man just needed a greeting card.
Throw it on.
(SIGHS)
Mortgage.
Credit card.
(CRACKLING)
Hopes and dreams.
(SIGHS)
That breakfast?
Appetizer.
Mm. Wash it down with some juice,
would you?
Who was that guy?
Nobody. Chris.
Kevin.
Whatever.
Is he like your new Noah?
No.
Good, 'cause that
whole thing kinda sucked.
Yeah, well, no more Noahs, okay?
No more Chrises or Kevins.
No more Brad-Brians, no Diegos...
Greggs?
Definitely no Greggs.
I am done with Greggs.
You know, you change the name,
they're all the same.
Okay.
They mess with your head,
and then they ghost.
I mean, who needs it?
Not you.
Not me.
Have some bread.
You know why?
I am a fierce, independent,
superfly, bossed-up,
weapons-grade...
Llama.
Wait, what?
The ones at the zoo
that eat from your hand.
The fuzzy camels?
Remember I was like,
"They love me,"
and you were like,
"Nah, that's just 'cause you have kibble.
"They come up to anyone."
Yeah, but how's that me?
It's just like you were
saying, it's like,
anyone who shows you a little affection,
next thing you know you're
being shaved for a sweater.
That is not exactly
what I was saying.
Wanna make mac and cheese for breakfast?
Just do it.
Don't think about it.
(GAGS)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Can I get it?
Look before you open.
(GAGS)
I'm seriously gonna barf.
Stop.
Hi, you must be Stan's little guy.
Hey. Hey, Ruthie.
Ruby.
KRYSTAL: Oh.
As long as we're doing names,
I'm actually Diane.
Is Stan home?
No, he's, uh, running errands.
Oh, okay, I just wanted
to say thanks for having my back
in the champagne room.
There's all sorts of goodies in there,
and lots of little treats
for the kids, too.
What's a champagne room?
Uh, that's where the mayor celebrates.
Mayor, athletes, cops, dads.
Uh-huh, yeah, um...
Can you take him to the kitchen, please?
Come on.
And take your pill.
They make me choke.
Oh, you know what that is, honey?
That's your gag reflex,
and you can totally fix that.
You just want to completely relax
the "fur-angel" muscle,
right here under the jaw.
Pharyngeal.
You feel it?
Then you wanna open up
your throat really wide,
and stick the pill,
at the back of your tongue.
(GULPS) You won't even
feel that sucker go down.
Now, it's gonna take some
practice, for sure,
and at first, it's gonna feel like
that thing is jammed
way too far back in your mouth.
(HEART THUMPING)
But if you just close
your eyes, let it happen,
before you know it, girl,
you can swallow anything.
Then take your ass
to Red Lobster and bring her back!
WOMAN: (OVER PHONE)
She's just not answering,
Mrs. Hill. If you'd like to...
I'm not talking to anybody else!
Gwen already knows
my daughter's situation.
Please hold.
GWEN: Hi, Ruby.
How was the popcorn shrimp?
I get the admiral's platter.
You know that's not why
I'm calling, Gwen.
Your appeal was denied, so...
We'll only cover the medicine
in case of an emergency.
She takes the meds
to prevent an emergency.
What am I supposed to do,
call you when her kidney explodes?
I understand your frustration.
Oh, you do?
So, you have a sick kid too.
And your husband works
a disgusting, humiliating job
that demeans you as a woman and a mother
all to pay for something that
anybody on planet Earth
would expect to be covered.
I've never been married.
Okay, this is how
it's gonna go down, Gwen.
You're gonna appeal my appeal,
and if that doesn't work,
you're gonna appeal that appeal.
And when we're done appealing...
They're shutting down our division.
What does that mean?
My department's going to Sri Lanka.
That's a big commute, Gwen.
(SOBBING) Yeah, my last day Is Friday.
Yeesh, that's quick.
Yeah.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna move back home.
(SNIFFLES)
At least you have family.
Yeah, it'll be tight.
My grandma's there, too.
Mm. Grannies make everything better.
She's in my old room.
So, I'll probably just sleep on the floor.
Well, they say it's really good
for your back.
Yeah? It's never been
the same since the accident.
Okay, you... Uh...
I'm rooting for you, G.
Thank you.
Yeah, you're gonna get through this.
And I'll make sure the folks in Sri Lanka
know about your da...
All right.
BETH: / already read you three.
Please!
Are we gonna have to move?
Can we paint our room purple?
(SIGHS)
I'll ask Daddy.
Night.
EMMA: Good night.
JANE: Good night, Mama.
BETH: They were a gift.
(RHEA GROANS)
They don't fit.
Well, he'll grow into them.
I'm gonna have to dedicate
a wing of my house to you.
(LAUGHS)
You don't have a wing.
Fine, a statue? A plaque?
So weird.
I don't want any of your stuff, okay?
I just want a friend.
Well, it's either you
or the county sheriff.
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
Nothing. We're downsizing.
By choice?
Do you want some more wine?
What's going on?
We're just a little behind
on our mortgage.
Stop. I'll be fine.
I'm sorry, it's just, all this time...
(SIGHS) I thought you were so put together
and perfect.
Oh, believe me...
And you think I'm this poor,
sad, single mom.
I do not.
I would never.
Now, you get to see how it feels.
How much?
What?
You can pay me back.
Absolutely not.
Marcus' dad, he sets us up.
What if he doesn't come back?
Then he'll send the money.
I'm not taking your money.
How much?
MAN: (ON TV)
Unfortunately, sometimes
I can't bottle my emotions.
And when it comes to someone
I can trust, I do, I open up...
Hey, baby.
Hey.
Stanimal.
Uh...
That better not be the new season.
It certainly is.
What episode?
Four.
Wow.
You just gonna go around my back
like that?
You're gone all night.
Okay. All right, I see.
(SIGHS)
(TV CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
There's a new crew this season.
(SIGHS)
If you want me to quit, I'll quit.
And do what? Porn?
What else pays that kinda cash?
Well, clearly you have a problem with it.
Everyone's got problems
they have to live with.
Not just me.
(SIGHS)
Wh...
What's, uh, what's Hannah's
baggage this season?
She's down a stew.
Don't tell me that.
You just asked,
and you know it's always something.
Ah, nope, nope,
La, la, la, la, la, la, la.
Don't be tellin' me stuff.
Hannah, you remember
what happened the last time,
Conrad, he...
He got all crazy.
MAN 1: (ON TV) ...South Dakota
originated a dish called chislic.
MAN 2: Hard work is easy.
Helping p...
WOMAN 1: The thing about...
MAN 3: Just fill the resev...
MAN 4: That's why...
MAN 5: Whether you're expecting
out-of-town guests, or just a drop-by
from neighborhood friends,
proudly serve Wisconsin cheese.
(VIBRATOR BUZZES)
(SCOFFS)
(CARNIVAL MUSIC PLAYING)
CLOWN: Open wide,
time to brush your teeth!
Ahhh!
(THUDS)
(SIGHS)
I'm gonna ask you guys something,
and I want you to be honest.
Remember last winter when we saw
that Celica slam into the pickup truck
on 194?
Uh-huh.
And the minivan couldn't stop
and smashed into the Celica?
Right.
And the semi went sideways,
took out the SUV,
crashed into
all of 'em, and caught on fire.
Is that my life?
Which vehicle are you in this scenario?
DEAN: Hey.
Whoa. Purple.
If we have to sell the house,
I don't Know if purple is the best idea.
Dean, I paid it.
Wait, all of it?
No, the interest and the penalties.
How'd you do that?
A friend.
Okay, can we not use
the phrase "a friend" anymore.
Not that friend, you know,
like a mom friend.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, obviously.
Sorry, that was a trigger...
Okay, I'm sorry.
All right.
Remember Kenny's video game
with the Nazi zombies?
He's dead.
Right, but what if he reanimates?
I don't know, I think we could take him
'cause I'm guessing he's mostly skull.
Yeah, skull and tats.
So it looks like your room and incidentals
are all covered.
Awesome, thank you, Angela.
How am I doing on loyalty points?
Well, after this day,
you are Officially gold status.
Congratulations.
Neat.
So any fun plans for the rest of your day?
Nah, nah, just some business.
Well, we hope to see you
again soon, Mr. Kowalski.
You, too.
Thank you, Angela.
Bye.
(INAUDIBLE)