ANNIE: Previously on Good Girls...
I had him recall the nail polish.
What's that?
We had to change the formula.
Change it back.
There is a nail salon selling
them for $200 a bottle.
Nail salon robbed.
Guess what they took.
I figured out who we should help.
I got their daughter's kidney.
You had pizza with your therapist?
He's helping me.
It's like a study buddy.
I wanted to introduce you to Lila.
Thought you could use a real tutor.
What are you guys into?
We have fun.
Dr. Cohen.
I quit my job today.
Why?
I kissed my boss.
We have enough to hire Max's cousin.
You're going to need a Sniper.
I Know a guy.
How does this work?
Say I'm your lawyer.
Trial itself will run you 60 grand.
So how is Friday... morning?
That works.
(KIDS SQUEALING)
ANNIE: How are we gonna know?
It's not like they're gonna
run his mugshots in the obits.
I mean, do we get a phone call or...
He just said 11:00 on Friday.
It's 10:56.
EMMA: You're dead.
No, you're dead.
EMMA: You are.
JENNA: Give me that!
EMMA: No, it's mine.
10:57.
BETH: It'll be good to be normal again.
Be whatever we want to be.
Finally. sud.
I just want to be a good person again.
Just some... normal mothers
with a lucrative side hustle,
minus the... serial-killing,
extortionist psychopath.
Know what I mean?
The deed is done.
How do you know?
Dog just looked at us.
So?
So dogs don't just stop and stare.
His spirit has passed.
What time do you have?
11:01.
It's over.
Darrel sees all the action
because he's a center.
Well, guess what. If you don't
feed Darrel the puck,
he doesn't see anything.
A great defensive man
keeps his team in the game.
That's way more valuable
than scoring a couple points.
Do you remember when...
Darrel peed himself in the third period?
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
We all saw that.
We had to Zamboni.
Ah, ah, ah!
Don't eat the fries.
Okay.
Here you go, my man.
I threw in a little extra
hot sauce for you.
So...
Where's the ranch?
Did you request that?
I put it in the notes area.
Oh, I see the problem here.
You put it in the delivery notes,
not the menu notes.
What's the difference?
Well, delivery note's more
for, like, a gate code,
or if the dog's out.
Can't eat wings without ranch, dude.
Oh, yeah. Sorry.
We don't do returns.
Fries are yours.
Yo, what's good, dog?
You remember Uncle Darren, right?
Thought you were gonna be
with your tutor today.
I leveled up.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
I also offer college prep,
you know, when it's time.
Oh, he's gonna need
all the LSATs, GMATs, MCATs, all the ATs.
'Cause I'm gonna be a lawyer,
doctor, Wall Streeter?
Okay, go do your homework please. Go on.
Dream it. Believe it. Be it.
(WHISTLES)
Intense.
Yeah.
But, you know, he's really counting on me
so I got to pass this thing.
All right, so check it.
$300 for the ID, another hundy
for travel and incidentals.
Then there's my fee.
That's another grand.
Well, how much to just not
look like a dummy?
Uh, same fee, but, you know,
for friends and family...
Yeah, I could finagle
a low-interest student loan.
You know what?
I'll just pay it.
(BOTH HUMMING GRADUATION SONG)
Congratulations.
Couldn't have done it without you.
WOMAN ON TV:
Two, three, four...
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
And exhale.
Two, three, four...
You sweat like cold cuts on a counter.
Hey, put that back.
I'm thirsty.
It's 10 bucks.
You have to pay?
You don't?
DL Dave said I could put stuff
on his tab.
What?
(PHOEBE GRUNTS)
Who can I plough to get that arrangement?
Lisa from counterterrorism's game.
Take it easy.
Now, what do we got?
Most of the women there
that day live in a shelter.
Mmm, easy to pin it on.
Or they just need the money.
Convenient.
That nail polish goes for a lot on eBay.
God knows why...
it's dreadful.
Why were they there?
Some weird church event.
Who planned it?
You're fishing.
Figure out who brought 'em in.
What are you going to do?
Raid your minibar.
Threw it all up already.
Well, you got to stop doing that.
RUBY: I need you to go
to the fancy grocery store.
My parents are coming?
It's way worse.
Who?
Donor family.
Sara invited them to dinner.
No.
She's cleansing her soul.
What?
Can't she, like, save
a rainforest or something?
I told her to do it.
We danced...
I Know.
The day their kid died.
Baked potatoes, yeah?
Every holiday, every birthday.
Twice baked.
Everyone loves those.
Whenever I see my baby girl,
I wanna dance.
I Know.
So how am I supposed to look
those people in the eye
when I danced on their daughter's grave?
They're coming in from Madison.
Call it off.
Our souls could use
some housekeeping, too.
I still need a dessert.
I'll make my sweet potato pie.
Don't make me over
Now that I'd do anything for you
Now that you know how I adore you
Don't pick on the things I say
The things I do
Just love me with all my faults
The way that I love you
I'm begging you
Don't make me over
Now that I can't make it without you
RIO: What are we celebrating?
Nothing. (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
I would just really like
to know where we're going.
Oh, you will.
When?
When we get there.
If there's some kind of problem--
How much cut have you got now?
I don't know.
Where's it all going, Elizabeth?
What do you mean?
What are you buying with it?
Yeah, see?
That's why we're here.
Set me up, please. Thank you.
Everything okay with the last batch?
Mmm-hmm.
We're actually printing tonight,
so if you, uh, like if you wanted to,
we could do the drop-off early.
That won't be necessary.
So last time you were cash heavy,
things got tricky,
'cause you and your girls
went stupid and burned it with the Feds.
Here you go.
You don't turn this properly,
you will attract attention.
You need a system.
I'mma ask you again.
Where's it been going?
Somewhere safe.
What, like a mattress?
Yeah.
Except you ain't got one.
Where's the money going?
I can't tell you.
Then I can't cut you in anymore.
You hungry?
No.
Mind if we stop at IHOP?
ANNIE: Who does he think
he is anyway, your father?
I mean, taking away your allowance?
How?
It's like, what's next?
You know? Put away your toys
or you're grounded?
How is he still alive?
Hey, Dad, it's my money.
You know?
It's like... (SCOFFS)
And, like, what am I supposed to say?
"Don't worry about it.
It went to a good cause."
I put a hit out on you.
That did not happen.
Unkillable.
Unhuman.
You know what I would really love
is if he would just show up
at one of your houses next time,
so you know what it's like
to think on your feet.
There shouldn't be a next time
'cause we already paid.
Old boy's gotta go.
Hi. I am here to see
Mr. James Fitzpatrick.
Who may I ask is inquiring?
Uh, a customer?
Yeah. A very upset customer, so...
Do you know how much overnight costs?
I don't work here.
I'm sorry. I just, I thought
'cause of your shirt.
CLERK: I can help you, sir.
You see?
I'm sorry, but Mr. Fitzpatrick
is not available at the moment.
But he's back there?
But not available.
Tell him that Beth is here.
Again. I am so sorry, but I...
Boland.
Oh, hold on.
He left something for you.
What the hell is this?
He said it was like hiring a lawyer.
They charge by the hour.
And then do nothing?
Yes, like a lawyer.
11,000 in incidentals.
I'm sorry. Why does he need
the omakase to not kill gang friend?
And what is "OT"?
Occupational therapy
for manual dexterity.
What, like his trigger finger
is sore or something?
How's that on us?
You guys.
That's him.
That's him?
Well, I'm telling his clown ass
that we're not paying
for his spray tan sessions.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, hold up.
Oh, he plays the cello?
That's a guitar.
It's a cello.
The case gives it away.
Has a much narrower neck
and a more cambered fingerboard.
That's no cello.
Think he's gonna smoke someone?
Oh, boy.
Here we go.
(PUNK MUSIC PLAYING)
It's a mob hit.
Classic.
RUBY: Nope.
Huh.
ANNIE: Oh God. Oh, my God.
Jesus.
Who would want her dead?
She looks so sweet!
I'd feel a whole lot better
if he carried a wallet.
(PUNK MUSIC CONTINUES)
RUBY: Oh, my God.
It's a school,
No, no, no, no.
GIRL: Daddy!
It's a cello.
Uh-oh.
We should get out of here.
How?
He's already seen us.
And we've seen too much.
(KNOCKING)
Do not.
What's he gonna do?
Give us a lollipop?
All right, fine.
Open it.
I didn't know your daughter went here.
It's got a great music program.
Ms. Marks, Ms. Hill.
Hey.
'Sup?
Why are you following me?
Um...
Just curious...
about the state of our lawsuit.
It's not moving forward.
We already paid for it.
Yeah, and you billed us for more.
If you refer to article 3-A
in the contract you signed,
I have the right to terminate
due to breach.
How did we breach?
Failure to disclose the nature
of your relationship with the target.
What does that mean?
Which one of you engaged
in flagrante delicto?
Excuse me?
Who boned him?
He go for a ride on the jazzy?
What about you, little bird?
Why does it matter?
I don't do jilted lovers.
Uh, okay.
No one was jilted.
There it is.
Come on, man.
It was one and done.
I mean, for the most part.
So this is where you draw your line?
Crimes of passion get messy.
Okay, again.
The word passion--
Clients...
They have regrets.
They start talking, before you know it.
I have to dispose of everyone involved.
And on my own dime no less.
We're not paying for this.
You don't want this going to collections.
Oh, my.
Is that his tongue?
It's a nasty process.
DARREN: So here's your registration.
Check the box for Muskegon.
That's where my hookup is.
Cool.
Oh, hey, you know, you have that friends
and family loan?
How sick is this?
Look at this.
Made the middle name Annie
so it's like, you know,
named after my mom or something.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
That's tight.
Instead of a loan--
Same social, though.
What about like, a scholarship?
You know, for high achievers
such as myself.
(CHUCKLES)
You don't have the money, do you?
I...
I will.
When?
(SIGHS) That's the gray area.
Bruh!
Dude, Dude, Dude, I had it.
Dick move!
No, no, no, no.
I just got hit with something majorly big.
Okay?
You know, you still owe me for the ID.
Come on, Boo. It's just...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I do this for you,
every loser jonesing
for a diploma's gonna want
a piece, so no. Uh-uh.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
How am I supposed to do this without you?
I don't know.
Maybe study.
Thanks again for making the trip.
Uh, I hope you brought your appetite.
I hope this wasn't too much trouble.
It was nothing.
Looks like Thanksgiving.
And we have so much to be thankful for.
Well, dig in, everyone.
(LAUGHING)
Let's see what happens, right?
Mmm-hmm.
I'm sorry.
Would you mind?
Ever since uh...
We always say a blessing.
Where did my manners go?
Must be somewhere.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Okay.
Okay, here we go.
Bless us, oh Lord,
for these thy gifts we are
about to receive.
Give us grateful hearts
for all thy mercies
and bless our loved ones,
especially our dear Heather
who we know would love
to be here tonight...
but she is here, right hon?
And we thank you, Lord,
for carrying her spirit
on in beautiful Sara.
(SIGHS) Wow.
(STAN CHUCKLES)
That ham, though.
Mmm-mmm.
Thank you, Lord.
Stan.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
And Lord, you know...
um, know everything Carl said...
(CHUCKLES)
And I just wanna thank you
for blessing us
with the opportunity
to meet these guys and so happy
and glad my baby girl
could make this happen.
Obviously, you know, we wish it was under
different circumstances.
But, you know, you work
in mysterious ways
and God bless the food, amen.
Now, can we eat?
(ALL LAUGHING)
Yes.
So how was the trip down?
Oh, we took the bus.
That's s a 16-hour trip.
Oh, not for us.
We could only afford to go
as far as Kenosha,
so we did a bit
of a rideshare situation from there.
Where's your car?
Um...
We sold it after Carl lost his job.
But, you know, I've been
doing so much walking.
I dropped my cholesterol 50 points.
Doctor's pleased.
(ALL CHUCKLING)
And the people at the church
have been real kind, pitching in.
Yes, and what can you do?
When life gives you lemons,
you can't rob a bank.
(LAUGHTER)
Mmm, boy.
So how are you going to get back?
Can we buy 'em a bus ticket?
Yeah.
Oh.
We can work something out.
No, no, we're not here for handouts.
Although I would try
some of those delicious
looking mashed potatoes.
(ALL CHUCKLING AWKWARDLY)
No, from here, it's easy.
A daughter of a friend
of ours, has offered
to drive us as far as Lansing.
And now from there,
it's what many would call
a scenic hike up in God's country,
where if my wife's ankles hold up,
we'll just take one day
to get back to the interstate.
We'll work this off, huh?
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Good heavens.
We'll have to.
Such good people.
I Know.
We're not.
How do we get back to that?
Sweet potato pie comin' in hot.
Do we still have that pressure washer?
What is that?
Everyone wants hot sauce.
So I went to Costco.
I got a vat of the stuff
and those little plastic cups
so I could just dispense it
from the back seat.
That's pretty smart, right?
It's why you're five star.
Hot sauce in a hot car.
Oh, my God. Ugh!
Just everywhere.
I'm so sorry, Beth.
Why?
Because I... I can't do it.
Then don't.
How are we supposed to, I mean...
Well...
What do you want to do?
Hot tubs.
Rich people love 'em.
Negotiable prices.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Financing plans, layaway...
There's, like, a million ways
to cook the books.
It's not regulated.
There's no licensing.
Any idiot can sell them.
And I know just the guy.
You said I needed a system.
This is my system.
(CHUCKLES) Sistema.
Go ahead and hate it
because you didn't think of it,
but your stupid carwash,
it's one of the IRS's
first targets, right behind
coin laundromats.
I googled it.
Guess what's not on the list?
Hot tubs.
They're called spas.
Pay her. Deduct the artwork.
Good morning, Mrs. Boland.
Get him.
I don't believe that
I have another package for you today.
Get him.
I have his money.
I just have a few questions.
Hmm.
What does omakase have to do with it?
It means entrusting yourself to the chef.
Typically off menu,
locally driven, sushi grade...
I mean, how does it help...
with killing a man?
Your lover enjoys a two-hour
omakase lunch every Friday.
Never misses.
After, he goes out into the parking lot
and has a chat with the chef.
It's an opportunity.
He then does various business
with people who would make
my work difficult.
Not an opportunity.
On Tuesdays, he plays tennis
at a very posh country club.
You'll see the charge
for the valet in there.
He does shower after
in an unattended locker room.
It's another opportunity.
You see where I'm headed with this?
I didn't put in all the details
because then I would have
to charge you for the time
it took to explain them.
Story of my life.
What's that?
Missed opportunities.
One thing I couldn't figure out.
Married mother of four,
Junior League, PTA,
winner of the state fair
mini muffin baking competition
three years running.
You dig deep.
So how's a lady like you
get involved with a guy like that?
I was just bored.
Tomorrow at noon,
I'll text you the address.
Let me get that for you.
WOMAN: Thank you.
JAMES: I am gonna replace this thing.
Oh, my Lord!
I didn't know what you guys like, So...
I've never had crepes.
I did a bit of everything.
Mmm.
So you sleep okay?
Harry's bed's a little tight.
That comforter is like,
sleeping on a cloud.
Right? His grandma gave it to him.
Aw.
You guys are so lucky.
So I made some sandwiches
for the road, and we can
pack up some treats.
You are amazing.
If there's anything
we can do, don't hesitate.
How about a car?
Pardon?
Carl's too proud to ask...
I Know it seems like we're doing okay,
but I promise you, the struggle is real
everywhere.
Is it?
We work triple shifts
and juggle bills, max out credit cards.
Your daughter is sleeping safe
in her bed.
Ooh, is the duchess coming to breakfast?
'Cause this can't be for us.
Is it?
Honey, that is just
the kind of people they are.
Well, it's like having
our own restaurant.
JENNY: Look at that.
I think it's fresh squeezed.
What is this?
It's Naked and Afraid, dog.
You should be studying.
Look, this girl just ate part
of a dead monkey.
Why are your books in the trash?
I think it's a foot or a thigh
or something, but now
she can't stop pooping.
Hey, hey, whoa, whoa, whoa!
They were just about to airlift her out.
You have a test.
Can you relax?
It got called off.
By who?
Me.
Why?
Because I'm just not ready.
You've been studying for months.
Look, it's my life, okay?
Fine.
Great.
If you're done, so am I.
Well, well, what does that mean?
I'm not ready either.
Hey, hey.
What... dah-dah-dah...
Do not.
Lord of the Flies essay is in here.
Didn't you back it up?
Handwritten.
No.
Biology book.
No more boring homework
about chloroplasts.
That is like half your grade.
Who needs it? I'll just work
at the mini mart.
That is not happening.
Why not?
Good enough for you.
Open your eyes
Careful surprise
A dream in disguise
You know we can have it
Well, I know we can do it
You know we can do it too...
How many Supreme Court
justices are there?
Eleven.
But there's work to be done now
Work to be done
Who was the first president
of the United States?
Washington.
Yeah. Whoo!
Give it a chance
Who authored
the Emancipation Proclamation?
Gotta be Lincoln.
Yes.
Yeah.
It's coming to life Little by little
Sixty three.
Yeah.
Jefferson.
Yeah. The Magna Carta.
Yeah.
But there's work to be done now
Work to be done
You've got to
You've got to put one foot
in front of the other
Put your other foot down Down, down, down
JAMES: You're early.
I can come back later.
Don't be silly.
Good quality in a person.
What are we doing here?
You know the hardest part of what I do?
Doing a job without anyone
knowing you did a job.
Take JFK for instance...
The grassy knoll, book depository.
So many theories, so much confusion about
where the bullet originated.
Perfect hit.
Have a look.
JAMES: What do you see?
A Greek deli, a donut shop,
cell phone store.
I don't know.
What am I looking at?
Confusion.
Do you have the time?
It's 12:00.
Perfect.
Take another look.
Say when.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
Anytime you're ready.
Why is it up to me?
You hired me to do a job.
Yeah, so you do it.
This way, I'm assured no regrets.
So what's it gonna be?
Every time I close my eyes
Something small within me dies
Can't say if it's dark or bright
But it's all I've ever known
And when !I sleep I sleep alone
Do it.
Now?
Now.
(GUNSHOT)
You're ready.
What?
Gonna put you back in the schedule.
Thank you.
Why did you change your mind?
We're alike.
You and I.
I don't know about that.
I was... just bored, too.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Took you long enough.
Where is she?
Well, couple of options here.
You keep taking it until you pass,
or move to West Virginia
and work the coal mines.
If you bring your own helmet,
I hear they hire you on the spot.
They said I tested
on the high end for a sixth-grader.
At least it was on the high end.
You can go now.
Right. Get up.
Pass.
You're coming with me.
Where?
A field trip.
Just 'cause I'm British
doesn't mean I play darts.
Are you sure?
Or cricket or rowing or rugby or...
Oh, oh, of course not because
you don't have any time
'cause you're always out on a fox hunt.
I don't go on fox hunts!
(LAUGHS)
I'm scared of horses.
Are you really?
Yeah.
Ah, I wish I had
a good therapist to give you.
Outrageous. How dare you?
How dare you?
You walked right into it.
Yeah, I know.
(SIGHS)
God, I just, I feel so dumb.
I Know.
I really, really tried.
That's how you know you're not dumb.
That makes no sense at all.
I hoped you were too dumb
to realize that.
(LAUGHS) Shut up!
I mean, I wasted so much time studying.
Yeah, I mean, not that much.
You did fail.
Like, I Know that a logarithm
is an exponent,
and I know the difference
between a trope and a bromide,
and all the republics of Russia.
And for what?
Well, if you can spell
Chechnya, that drink's on me.
I thought it already was.
No stalling.
Okay. It's no problem.
It's, you know, C...
"Ech" N-Y-A.
"Ech" is not a letter
in any language. (LAUGHS)
Well, that's what
autocorrect is for, so...
(BOTH LAUGHING)
I, um...
I proposed to Lila.
Couple of nights ago.
Congrats.
I should go.
It's fine. I got mine.
Couldn't spell it.
DEAN: Hey.
Hey.
Where are the kids?
You know what?
I have no idea.
Dean.
I mean, they're here somewhere, I just...
Hopefully alive.
I've just been in this.
Welcome to Boland Bubbles.
I'm not really in the market.
I'm just browsing.
Oh, well, as you look around,
keep in mind none of this is to scale.
Blue Legos are two-seaters,
red, four-seaters,
and green are eight-seaters.
Let me know if you wanna
try something out.
You're gonna be great.
Hey, Beth.
Thank you.
For what?
Getting me back in the game.
I'm gonna go file
the police report on our kids.
(CHUCKLES)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
It's not her.
I think it's her.
Mmm-mmm.
Been a member of that church
forever, lives in her mother's house.
They got nothing in their bank accounts.
So?
So...
They're making some of the best fake money
I've ever seen.
You don't live a little?
Well, she just bought a car for cash.
Seriously? What kind?
Well, not one she can afford.
Guess where she works.
Ooh, young liars
I said thank you for taking my hands
And burying them deep
in the world's wet womb
Where no one can heed their commands
Except young liars
Young liars