1,290 square feet.
Let's call it 13 with the balcony.
One and a half bathrooms.
That means it's a full bath
and a powder room.
Two bedrooms, 1 1th floor...
one parking spot
with an option for a second.
And at $28,000...
I do believe that was
everything on your list.
It's a little farther east than I wanted.
In fact, it's about
as far east as you could go.
- You can see the highway from the corner.
- You could see the river.
And who needs Central Park...
when you can smell the ocean
and the Hungarian bakeries?
Believe me, when they finish
the Second Avenue subway...
this apartment will quadruple in value.
Oh, that's Barbara.
You let me do the talking.
Sorry I'm late.
It's quite a hike between First and York.
It's got to be longer than a normal block.
I don't think so.
We just got started.
What do you think?
I think no one's gonna catch
that doorman napping.
I left your name.
It's got a doorman.
I was telling Peggy that an offer is
coming in at asking price.
We'd have to beat it.
So it's in your best interest
to be decisive...
and take this property seriously.
Well, okay, but it's not my decision.
Ginny, we are taking this seriously.
- What Abe means is-
- I'm more her trusted adviser.
An interested party.
I see.
I misunderstood.
I'm going to flush that toilet again.
She didn't know I wasn't the buyer?
So all this time she was just being rude.
Forget about her.
Is it too far east?
Dinner!
Bobby, Sally, let's go.
Look at you two. Heading to the track?
- Where are you going?
- D.C., if Jonesy can find a cab.
- Hope you're not in a rush.
- We have a car coming.
6!30? We should have done that.
We're not going to miss the train.
Where are you going?
They said D.C.
I mean, why are you going?
Arnie was invited last minute
to give a keynote address.
Did you have to tell him
it was last minute?
I guess the point is
somebody more important fell out.
It's a very distinguished group.
And you must have been
at least as important.
Either way, it sounds like a good excuse
for a weekend in Washington.
Yes. Come Monday morning,
it'll all be a dream.
We should really go away.
Looks like you're going somewhere fun now.
We are. Megan's up for an award.
Good for you. Maybe tomorrow...
you'll be calling the producers
and asking for a raise.
No, it's for advertising.
The Ad Club of New York.
- Paul Newman's coming.
- My goodness.
You're really good at everything.
I was just a name on the team.
There's the car.
Well, break a leg.
You too.
Oh, and, Don, we're going to D.C.
Hey, Pop, I-
I'm sorry. Am I interrupting something?
We were waiting for you.
Look, miss, whatever he told you
we were interested in, we're not.
See how funny he is?
Now, don't be rude.
This is Beverly Farber.
She is Chaim Farber's daughter.
I'm- Our dads, they play chess together.
Oh-
Well- It's nice to meet you.
And now that you're home
from a busy day on Madison Avenue...
I think you should go out
and have some dinner.
What?
Maybe we should do this another time.
Nonsense.
There's no time like the present.
You both should have some fun.
She's a schoolteacher.
She works all the time.
I need to shave,
change my clothes, prepare.
I mean, look at her. She had a jump on me.
I did.
I was led to believe
that you knew about this.
- Why did you tell her that?
- What's the difference?
Look at her.
I'm obviously doing you a disservice.
At least we're close to the kitchen.
It's not fair that
all the big agencies are up front.
Closer to their trophies.
But at least we're gonna eat before them.
Oh, I see Peggy back there.
We should go say hello.
- I'm gonna wait for the group.
- You can't avoid her forever.
I'm not.
Tell her that no matter what...
her laxative radio spot
is the sentimental favorite.
Hello, stranger.
I was hoping I'd see you.
You know, other than on TV.
- You don't watch.
- My mother and sister do.
Really? Do they hate me?
Oh, just a minute.
Megan, I want you to meet Jim Cutler.
He's the president of CGC.
This is Megan Draper.
She's also a finalist.
You must be Don's wife.
When I started out,
they didn't make copywriters like you.
Good luck.
He's the head of accounts.
He's like Roger with bad breath.
So he knows who you are.
It must be going well.
If I survive tonight.
CGC has no other finalists.
Other-They have none.
I only came because
it seemed important to Don.
I bet it is.
We're the only finalists from SCDP...
and neither of us work there anymore.
My work was for beans,
and they aren't even a client anymore.
I don't want to talk about this.
I want to talk about my apartment.
I made an offer today.
I think we're gonna be neighbors.
- 84th and York.
- You're buying a place?
Well, I paid off my debts
and helped out my mother...
and it turns out I still
have this tax problem.
Don't apologize, Peggy. You deserve it.
Thank you.
I should get back.
I have to walk
all the way down to the front.
You're terrible.
These are the worst seats in the room.
- Don Draper, this is Randall Walsh.
- A pleasure to meet you.
Randy here is in insurance and he wants to
come in for an official visit.
Look, man, it's not like we're not
supposed to talk about business here.
You want a presentation right now?
I don't think we'll interrupt
the proceedings, wherever they are.
- I just thought you two should meet.
- We've already met.
In fact, I'm pretty sure we've had
this meeting already too.
- And it went well.
- So where's our check?
- He's solid.
- Okay, Randy.
Go get back in your cage.
- What was that?
- Don't worry about it.
Have no fear. They're gonna fire off
a cannon when the atrocities begin.
Hello all. You remember my wife Nan.
Hello, everyone. Good luck.
I told you, Nan,
Peggy's the only one competing.
Well, I didn't know what else to say.
So you probably figured out by now
that you didn't win.
Ted.
But it doesn't matter,
because next year you will.
- Ted.
- And the year after.Just a second, honey.
- Hey, man, sorry.
- Oh, I'm in your seat.
Nan, you wanted to see Paul Newman.
Here he is.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we would like to welcome you...
to the Advertising Club of New York's...
Fourth Annual ANDY Awards
for Excellence in Advertising.
So you like kids?
Excuse me?
I was asking because you're a teacher...
but I realize how that could sound
like something else.
I'm a student teacher.
I'm getting my master's at Hunter.
And, yes, I like kids. Some kids.
I just really can't believe
he brought you to the apartment.
Stop saying that.
You don't know where I live.
Well, it's kind of early
to find out, isn't it?
Yes, I suppose it is.
I don't know what you're expecting.
A couple of alter kockers arrange
a little meeting like this-
It sounds very old world,
but it doesn't feel like it.
I mean, you're a sexy girl,
and you smell great.
You don't need to be set up.
And I sure as hell didn't arrange this.
I'm sure my father told you
what a lothario I am, but I'm not.
I'm very anxious about it.
I've never had sex, not even once.
Okay.
What am I doing?
I ordered soup. I just said that.
Michael...
I'm just doing a favor for my parents.
Tonight will not be the night.
And I saw a picture of you...
and, honestly, you're very handsome.
And I'm obviously very shallow.
- I am?
- You must have heard that before.
So...
do you make a lot of money teaching?
No.
Ladies and gentlemen, Paul Newman.
Good evening. I am Paul Newman.
The Advertising Club of New York...
has been kind enough
to let me say a few words here tonight.
And I want to make one thing
clear from the very start.
I need binoculars.
I'm not here because I'm an actor.
We invited him because he's an actor.
I'm here because I've got six kids
and I'm worried about-
That's not an actor. That's a speck.
Gene McCarthy stood up
to Lyndon Johnson...
before Bobby Kennedy.
The others backed into the election
with their fingers to the wind...
thinking of their own career...
when the nation was
in critical need of a hero.
I know Bobby Kennedy...
but I'm supporting Gene McCarthy
for President of the United States.
Mr. Newman, sir!
Do you know, Mr. Newman, sir,
that Martin Luther King is dead?
What have you to say?
No, that can't be.
Who the hell said that?
How awful.
If I could have your attention
for a moment, please.
A moment of your attention.
Not wanting to interrupt the festivities...
we hoped to keep this news
until the end of the event.
As it stands, let's take 10 minutes...
to talk out this terrible event
and then resume the program.
What do you think happened?
- What do you think?
- Come on.
I guess Puerto Rico. But who has time?
Your father says you've even
written some billboards.
That must be exciting.
You'd think so,
but they usually change it so much...
by the time they put it up there, it just
makes you angry every time you walk by.
... in Memphis, Tennessee...
after being shot in the face
by an unknown assailant...
on the balcony in front of
a down town hotel a short while ago.
Associate d Press says Assistant Police
Chief Henry Lux of Memphis...
confirmed Dr. King's death.
Reverend Dr. King,
winner of the Nobel Peace Prize...
Oh, my God.
- was 39 years old.
- They had to do it.
He was in Memphis
to lead demonstrations...
in sympathy with a prolonged strike...
by municipal garbage men,
most of them Negro.
Police at last report
were still looking...
for a young white male
who was seen running...
from the scene of the shooting and
reportedly dropped the weapon in flight.
What are you doing in here?
Thought you'd be by the set.
She won't let us watch.
Because who knows what
they're going to show.
You don't have to go.
Betty, they're gonna burn down the city.
Everything's fine.
I have to go help the mayor.
Please be careful.
- And call me.
- We repeat...
Dr. Martin Luther King,
America's non violent civil rights...
What is taking so long?
There are other people here
who need to make calls.
They shot him in the face in Memphis.
Do they know who?
Come on, they didn't catch him yet,
but you know who.
Listen,Jimmy says they can get me
a photographer if I can get uptown.
No, it's not a good idea.
It's the New York Times.
- And what?
- It's a huge story.
- Don't do anything stupid.
- Peggy, it's too late.
I'm going to Harlem in a tuxedo.
I can't believe this.
Abe just went uptown for work.
I'm sick and I don't even know
how I'm gonna get home.
We'll give you a ride.
I'm tired of waiting for a phone.
I'm going home.
What are we doing?
They're really still having the awards?
What else are we gonna do?
Look, I'm sure it's hard to sleep.
What is that?
What are you doing?
I didn't do it. It peeled off.
Why are you destroying this house?
You can't do this.
I didn't do anything.
I don't want to talk about it now.
Please just go to sleep.
... the Civil Rights Movement has been
shot to death in Memphis, Tennessee.
Police have issued
an all-points bulletin-
It's me.
... seen running from the scene.
How are you?
Not good.
I don't know why I'm so surprised.
It's shameful.
Listen, I-
I don't want you and Tammy to be alone.
I could come out
and sleep there tonight if you want.
No, I-
We'll be fine.
Well, I want to see Tammy.
Is she all right?
She doesn't know what's going on.
No, of course.
I'll see you on Saturday.
No, I'll just tell my parents
you couldn't get out of the city.
Or I'll just cancel it altogether.
- Trudy.
- What?
I don't want you to be worried.
Okay.
In a nation wide television address...
President Johnson
expressed the nation's shock.
Good night, Peter.
Good night.
... of Dr. Martin Luther King.
I ask every citizen
to reject the blind violence...
that has struck Dr. King...
who lived by non violence.
Pop, wake up.
What time is it?
What are you doing home so early?
We cut it short.
Martin Luther King got killed.
... try and cool things down.
In Boston, according to police reports...
a large crowd of Negroes
stoned six police cruisers...
near a Negro housing project
in the Roxbury section.
And there was a clash between
police and young Negroes...
in Raleigh's main
down town streets tonight.
The latest report of trouble
comes from Washington, D. C....
where stores along a six-block area...
were broken into late this evening.
President Johnson went
on nation wide television...
to express his shock
and personal grief at the tragedy.
... looking subdued and grim
at the thought...
of what this act could mean in a country
already taut with racial tension.
He said he applauded
the escalation of decay.
So sick of that Marxist bullshit.
So far it's only looting in Harlem
but a lot of places are on fire.
Well, it's raining.
Do you think your secretary is okay?
Sylvia and Arnold are in D.C.
My father just hides behind his intellect.
He doesn't want to feel any emotions.
Let's watch inside.
Maybe we can fall asleep.
Am I disturbing you?
No. I'm not gonna judge you
if you want a drink.
The man knew how to talk.
I don't know why,
but I thought that would save him.
I thought it would solve the whole thing.
Oh, I don't know if
he just wants to hold hands...
but my insurance friend
from last night, he called.
He wants to come in at 3!00.
I'll have Caroline remind you
since you're on your own.
Could you get the door?
Yes, actually, I'm trying
to reach Dr. Rosen.
No, I'm not a patient.
I just know that he's in Washington and-
Well, I was concerned.
I'm his neighbor.
Oh, well, if you do reach him...
just say-
Actually, no message. I'll try later.
Oh, you're here.
I'm sorry.
There's no reception out there.
No, I just-
I didn't expect you to come in.
I kept calling and no one answered.
We went out to my aunt's in Newark.
- Why would you do that?
- My mother wanted to be with her sister.
Abe said it could have been a lot worse.
I'm so sorry.
I knew it was going to happen.
He knew it was going to happen.
But it's not gonna stop anything.
And these fools running in the streets-
It's exactly what he didn't want.
You should go home.
In fact, none of us should be working.
Thank you.
Is this really what happened?
You didn't tell me anything.
They got it right,
except that it was terrifying.
Walking into that angry, crazy crowd...
and Lindsay smiling like he was going
to a pancake breakfast.
The only lives His Honor seemed worried
about protecting were the photographers'.
- But it worked.
- I'll tell you what worked.
Cutting deals with
all the militants last year.
Well, I'm glad you were there.
Me too. And I got to go back in.
I want you to eat something first.
Clara!
- Have you seen Scarlett?
- Where's my girl?
They must all be watching TV somewhere.
- Not in my office.
- I barely slept last night.
I just thought working
might take my mind off things.
Good luck.
Been on the phone all morning.
They're worried about
last night, obviously...
but they're worried about tonight,
they're worried about the weekend.
- Who?
- The clients.
They won't take make-goods.
They want money back.
- That's disgusting.
- I don't know.
It's enough of this crap already.
All these special broadcasts preempting
the prime-time schedule.
Be witched, Merv, Dean Martin.
You know they might
cancel the Stanley Cup?
How dare you.
This cannot be made good.
It's shameful.
It's a shameful, shameful day!
Don't you scream at me. You don't think
I'm upset about that man being shot?
Only because it's costing you, you pig!
It's costing all of us.
And when's it gonna stop?
No one will be happy...
until they turn the most beautiful city
in the world into a shit hole.
- Gentlemen, stop it. Stop it this minute!
- In a second, Bert.
Did you know we were
in the presence of a bona fide racist?
That's the latest thing, isn't it?
Everybody's a racist.
Gentlemen!
I urge you to shake hands
in the spirit of erasing these remarks.
I'm sorry.
I suppose that my comments
were inappropriate.
I mistook this for a workday.
Don't worry.
I'm sure you can make your money back...
on some Movie of the Week
next fall about the death of a great man.
That is not what I meant.
Let me put this
in terms you'll understand.
That man had a wife and four children.
I'm sorry I'm late. Would you like coffee?
Dawn, I'm just glad you're okay.
Joan was trying to reach you.
The phone was out
for a little bit last night...
and, well, it took some time to get here.
I don't think you should work today.
I couldn't reach you.
I assumed you weren't coming in.
My mother told me I should.
Well, Mr. Cooper just announced
that out of respect...
we're going to close the office early.
That's probably a good idea.
Mr. Sterling still wants
to have the 3!00 meeting.
Are we closed or not?
Stan and Ginsberg will also be joining.
Do you want to cancel it?
- If you're gonna stay, I'll stay.
- No, you go.
I'd really rather be here today.
Okay.
We're all so sorry.
Do you want anything?
No.
- Hello?
- Peggy Olson, please.
This is Peggy.
I was about to send over your offer,
and it occurred to me-
Oh, my offer.
I completely forgot about that.
- You haven't sent it?
- No, I haven't.
Well, no one's going
to want to look at that today.
May I speak?
I thought the same thing,
but then I realized...
there's trouble 10 blocks away.
They're probably on pins and needles.
So am I.
Do I want to live up there?
Get a hold of yourself.
The other buyer never came in.
Why don't we come in
at 5,000 under asking...
and give them 24 hours to respond?
We'll let the TV news do the rest.
- I don't know.
- This is the only apartment for you.
You don't want to be
kicking yourself next week.
And, of course, I'll wait
until tomorrow to present.
Good girl.
Randall Walsh, you remember Don.
This is Stan Rizzo and Michael Ginsberg.
Randall, would you like a drink?
Never. I really don't even want to talk.
I was trying to communicate without words,
but it's not working.
Randy, it never works.
Randall has an idea and
the ad director won't take a chance.
You're in the property insurance business.
I'll bet you're about
to get hit pretty hard.
Forget about that.
This is about a no bullshit approach
to why I got into this business.
People say they care.
I really care.
We're waiting for you, Randall.
All I see when I close my eyes...
is our name and a Molotov cocktail
being lit with a match.
And then a coupon at the bottom.
The ad sales guy didn't like that?
I know what it looks like- fearmongering.
But this is the opposite.
This is a coded message that came to me...
when I was visited by
the spirit of Dr. King last night.
He said that I should question
the whole property thing, man.
It makes you happy, right?
No, I think it was,
is and will always be in poor taste.
'Cause you'd rather not think about it.
But there is a tear, and in that tear
are all the tears in the world...
all the animals crying.
You're right.
I don't want to think about it.
What Don's saying is despite
what we believe to be good intentions...
you're allowing the emotions of the day...
and whatever else you got in your system,
to influence your judgment.
Are you forgetting what Tecumseh said?
Heya howa howa hoya.
- Heya howa howa.
- I had forgotten that.
We'll think about it.
This is an opportunity.
The heavens are telling us to change.
You talked to Dr. King's ghost?
Make sure Randy doesn't get lost.
- I had to wait around for that?
- I don't know.
He was very emotional.
He talked me off a roof once.
I kind of owed him. You want a drink?
I just want to go home.
Someone's gonna do that idea, you know.
Not us.
Three deaths have been reported
in the Washington rioting so far.
There are no details yet
on the circumstances surrounding them.
More than 350 persons
have been treated for injuries.
Among them,
several policemen and firemen.
Firefighting was hampered
if for no other reason...
by the sheer volume of the alarms.
But still, some persons
were injured and-
It's Betty. You're supposed
to pick up the kids!
Oh, shit.
Got it. Hello.
I knew you would forget.
You really want them down here?
I know you don't. You get out of
every opportunity to see them.
You don't even know
how strange they're acting.
The news is very upsetting.
I'm sure it has nothing to do with
the fact that their father forgot about them.
You want me to come up there
and get them...
drive right through everything after dark?
Well, of course, Henry thinks it's fine...
but he's not as concerned
about their safety as you are.
Well, Henry would know.
I guarantee you'd go to Canada
on your knees to pick up your girlfriend.
I don't believe this.
I'm going to get the kids.
... relatively little interference
during the afternoon.
Really?
They called in the troops in Washington...
but Henry says we're fine here.
She's a piece of work.
Looting spread to the down town
shopping section of the city...
and as darkness fell, arrests increased.
You finished with that?
You can walk me to work.
I'm already at work.
Since when are you going in on Saturday?
Since I don't want to be
in front of the TV set.
Good as new.
This?
This is a mess.
You can't sew.
You can't cook. You can't clean.
You don't think there's a reason
you have all these flaws?
You need a girl.
But maybe you don't like 'em.
I like girls, Dad.
If that was true,
you'd be in bed with her right now.
I don't think anybody's in the mood.
It's quite the opposite.
Now's the time when a man and a woman
need to be together the most.
In a catastrophe.
In the flood, the animals went two by two.
You, you're gonna get on the ark
with your father.
I can find my own girls, okay?
Okay.
I'll bring you a sandwich.
I'm glad you finally slept.
What's going on?
We're going to a vigil in the park.
- You're not supposed to be watching TV.
- I'm not.
- You are, and Mom said you can't.
- Sally, stop it.
Troy and Bridget called.
They're gonna meet us there.
- We'll be back in a couple of hours.
- I don't feel well.
You go on ahead. I'll watch him.
Come on.
Look, I just can't sit around
in the apartment anymore.
I feel like I have to do something.
I understand.
I knew you wouldn't go.
You want some aspirin?
Hey. Turn it off.
Tell me exactly what your mother said.
I'm not allowed to watch TV for a week.
Man has no understanding.
He can be taught a few simple tricks,
nothing more.
I'm afraid I must disagree.
According to my experiments-
Dr. Zira, I must caution you.
I guess your stomach's feeling better.
Why are you being punished?
I don't know.
Come on.
Because the wallpaper didn't line up.
... the simian nature
from a study of man is sheer nonsense...
because man is a nuisance.
He eats up his food supplies
in the forest...
You maniacs!
You blew it up!
Oh, damn you!
Goddamn you all to hell!
- The humans blew up New York?
- All of America.
- So he came back to here?
- In the future.
Jesus.
You want to see it again?
Can we?
I need another half hour.
Oh, yeah.Just a minute.
It's for you. It's the real estate agent.
- Hello, Ginny.
- Well, we didn't get it.
Wh-What happened?
Someone came in a little bit higher.
But you know what? It wasn't meant to be.
How much higher?
It was still under asking, Peggy.
It wasn't meant to be.
There's no other way to think about it.
Try, try again.
Someone else got the apartment.
What are you gonna do?
- That's it?
- What do you want me to say?
That you give a damn.
Peggy, this is an emotional story.
Stop being such a martyr.
You're having the time of your life.
- Why are you so mad?
- Because I'm alone in this.
That's not cool.
I don't mean financially.
I mean, don't you care where we live?
Look, I don't feel right expressing an opinion.
Now is your chance.
I don't want to live
on the Upper East Side.
Fine. Why?
I don't know.
I saw us raising our kids in a place
with more different kinds of people.
This photographer
trailing me the other night...
he lives in the West 80s.
- Isn't it dangerous?
- No, it's more run-down.
But that's why it's so cheap.
Get some lumber, a coat of paint-
People are doing it.
I didn't know you felt that way.
About the Upper East Side.
I do.
I'm sorry.
I just felt it wasn't my money.
How much of a say do I have?
You're in my life.
You're a part of my life.
Peggy, I've got to finish this.
- Did you see this movie?
- Not yet.
Do you get to see it for free?
- I do.
- It's really good.
- We're seeing it again.
- You enjoy yourself.
Everybody likes to go to the movies
when they're sad.
I was looking for you.
You left the TV on.
I don't feel right turning it off...
but I don't want to watch it.
He doesn't even want me to come in.
Everything has settled down.
For the time being.
No, I think this is the end of it.
Good.
Betty, I hope you know
you'll never have to worry about money.
Why would you bring that up?
Nothing.
I just keep asking myself,
"What am I doing?"
- About what?
- I keep thinking about walking through Harlem...
Lindsay a few paces ahead,
grinning like he always does...
the rest of us following behind.
- Wasn't that frightening?
- It was exhilarating.
But what was the cost
of avoiding that riot?
Police corruption,
disrespect for authority...
negotiating with hoodlums.
You can't say that to the mayor.
He's never been more popular.
It's just- Betty...
I keep thinking I would do it differently.
I want to do it differently.
And, well, they approached me
like they always do when somebody dies...
and they offered me a seat
in the state senate.
Do you want to run?
Run? It's a Republican seat.
It's basically unopposed.
- You'd have to quit the mayor's office.
- He'll understand.
You think I'm the first guy
sick of being in a flank?
I feel like I've been
asking you to do this since I met you.
Well, I finally heard you.
It's a stepping-stone
to state attorney general.
- And-
- And who knows what else?
Easy, partner.
This is what I've wanted for you.
Us.
I can't wait for people to meet you.
You know? Really meet you.
Everyone's in bed.
Gene finally climbed in with Sally.
I felt better, but now I don't.
- Why?
- Because who knows what you're feeling?
I didn't know what to say to her...
except, "I'd tell you to ask your father,
but he's at the movies."
I should have said, "He's just drunk."
You're better with them.
You don't understand.
I do.
You don't have Marx. You've got a bottle.
Is this what you really want to be to them
when they need you?
No.
I don't think I ever wanted
to be the man who loves children.
But from the moment they're born...
that baby comes out,
and you act proud and excited...
and hand out cigars.
But you don't feel anything.
Especially if you had a difficult childhood.
You want to love them, but you don't.
And the fact that you're...
faking that feeling...
makes you wonder if your own father
had the same problem.
Then one day they get older...
and you see them do something...
and you feel...
that feeling
that you were pretending to have.
And it feels like your heart
is going to explode.
That was faster than I expected.
Are things calmer out there?
Well, then...
have a good night.
Hey.
- You need to go to sleep.
- I can't.
So why can't you sleep?
I'm scared.
Don't make me sorry
for taking you to the movies.
No.
I just keep thinking...
what if somebody shoots Henry?
No one's gonna do that.
- But they could.
- But they won't.
Henry's not that important.
Go to sleep.