ＤＡＲＫＭａＴｔＥｒ
SEASON 01 # EPISODE 08
"JUPITER"
Where's your mom?
Uh, she went to Ryan's.
Why?
Uh, she said Mindy sounded bad
on the phone.
Wanted to check on them.
JASON: Oh, yeah.
[SIGHS]
- Hey, how about a late-night deep dish?
Yeah. Yeah. You speak my language.
Be right back.
[OBJECT RATTLING]
[OBJECT THUDS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[YELPS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
- [KNIFE FLICKS]
[BOTH GRUNTING, PANTING]
[GRUNTING]
- [SCREAMS]
[GRUNTS, SCREAMS]
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
Hey.
- [INHALES SHARPLY, BREATHES SHAKILY]
[GRUNTS]
H-How do I know you?
It's Daniela.
The Honda Civic Daniela?
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah. That's the one.
You burn through brake pads
faster than any other customer I ever had.
[SPITS, BREATHES SHAKILY]
Yeah?
[RYAN SNORTS, PANTS]
- I'm your customer?
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
Loyalty Motors. Logan Square.
- Do you really think you're a mechanic?
I am a mechanic.
[TOILET FLUSHES]
What's the last thing you remember?
Well, I was at my bar.
And...
- Which bar?
[STAMMERS]
Shakers in Logan Square. In, um...
[SNIFFLES, GULPS]
I mean, yeah, I...
I got a little out of hand.
And then this guy
kept buying me shots, so...
Just...
- Who was?
I didn't... [SIGHS]
I'd never seen him before. He was, uh...
He told me his name.
It was, uh, James or...
I don't know.
[SNIFFLES, BREATHES SHAKILY]
This guy?
Yeah.
- This guy was buying you drinks?
Who is he?
[SEND TONE BEEPS]
- I just texted it to you.
[PHONE DINGS]
- Got it. Big Shoulders Mental Health.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Sure I can't drive you?
We'll be okay.
Okay. Let me know how it goes, okay?
Okay. Thank you.
[DOOR OPENS, CREAKS]
Hey.
Hey. Hey!
Hey!
[PANTING]
Hey, Dad.
Hey.
Pizza's here. I got us Pequod's.
Cool. Cool.
Uh, I'll be right inside.
You doing something out here?
Yeah, I was just, uh,
moving some, uh, stuff around.
You need a hand?
What? No. I'm... I'm fine.
I'll see you inside.
Okay.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[HORNS HONKING]
MATT: Jason, you good?
Yeah.
Uh...
I need a... a drink.
That was quick.
What?
- Same?
Uh... yeah.
Here you go, brother.
[CHUCKLING] Fuck me.
BOTH: When did you...
Uh...
tonight.
You?
Yesterday.
So you were kidnapped too?
Yeah.
Daniela was killed right in front of me.
The other Daniela.
Me too.
Were you taken back to Velocity and beaten?
Amanda helped me escape.
Same.
Well, I guess this was inevitable,
that the different versions of us...
would spawn in the box.
But how many?
I know some of them
must have been killed or lost.
Or ran out of ampoules.
But some of them, like you and like me,
made the right choices.
Right choices.
Or got lucky.
Our paths may have been altered
by different doors and different worlds...
but eventually,
they made their way back to this Chicago.
Every choice I made in there
created a different Jason.
And every choice those Jasons made.
And those Jasons.
Fuck.
Where's your Amanda?
She, uh...
I lost her.
Where?
Very dark world.
Yours?
She found a place that she wanted to stay.
That's good.
Do you have any ampoules left?
Me neither.
So here we are.
Here we are.
What now?
You must have thought of Kankakee, right?
I only know about that 1ˢᵗ reserve
because of Charlie.
We only know about it because of Charlie.
Jason Two, that's what I call him,
doesn't know about it.
Right.
Take him for a drive at night.
Take him for a walk down one of the paths
on the north side of the river, and then...
I thought about it today.
I dug the grave today.
We don't have a gun.
You don't have a gun.
Okay.
It's a pretty good plan...
but now there's a whole lot more
to contend with.
We all want the same thing.
We all want our family back.
We all want our life back.
Till a month ago we were exactly
the same person with the same thoughts.
We said exactly the same things.
We had the same fears and the same love.
We think of him as Jason Two...
which means we all think
of ourselves as Jason One.
Can't all be Jason One.
How many do you think made it back?
One of them tried to kill me last night.
One followed me today.
If I get my hands on Jason Two,
he's definitely gonna pay.
Definitely.
Now, I don't wanna hurt you
or anyone like us...
but I'm not gonna let anyone get in the
way of me being with Daniela and Charlie.
These are on me.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Anything else?
Warm you up?
Mmm. Yeah.
No rush, okay?
Thank you.
[SIGHS]
[COUGHS]
You can't do that in here.
You can't do that.
There's nothing like a fine cigar
after a lovely meal.
Or so I've heard.
You can't smoke in here.
Do I need to get my manager?
You are a very rude man.
You can't smoke inside.
You're disturbing the other customers.
Am I disturbing anyone with my cigar?
DINERS: Yes.
DINER#1: Yeah, you are.
- [DINERS CLAMORING]
Hmm.
[DOOR OPENS]
DAWN: Put it out.
Now.
Hey, can I...
can I ask you a personal question?
Can I... [GROANS]
How did you become a detective?
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
Yeah?
[DOOR OPENS]
Morning.
Get up early?
Can you take Charlie to school?
Sure.
I have some pieces to move at the gallery.
Can I take the Civic?
Just take Charlie's.
It's fine. I'll drive the Civic.
I know you hate it.
Nah. Charlie's has more space, and, uh...
I forgot to get gas for the Civic, so...
Well, is it empty?
Honey, just take Charlie's.
Sure.
See you later.
Oh, hey...
how was, uh, Ryan last night?
Not great, actually.
I just can't believe that he relapsed
after all these years.
That's what he said.
Gotta run.
- All right.
I'd let you drive.
The car is just playing up a little.
- It's fine.
It's...
Where are we going?
What do you mean?
I'm... I'm dropping you at school.
What about the University of Chicago?
I thought you were gonna
show me around campus.
Uh, today? I said...
Yeah. [SCOFFS]
W-What...
- You know what?
No. Forget it.
You know what? I said we'd go.
We'll go.
You know I don't have
the grades to go here, right?
It's never too late.
You can turn things around.
So, there's the physics department.
That's where I spent most of my time here.
The house where I met your mom, actually,
is right over there.
The garden party?
Almost didn't go.
Decided last minute.
CHARLIE:
Do you ever think about if you hadn't?
Yeah, I would have regretted
it for the rest of my life.
[CHUCKLES] No, you wouldn't.
Regretting is easy.
[STAMMERS] There's nothing
you can actually do about it.
[GROANS] Maybe you'll understand
when you get older.
Yeah, or maybe
you're too old to understand.
Why are you saying all this?
Your whole life hinged on a moment
that's basically just a freak accident.
I mean, the smallest little choice
to go to a party?
What?
What's up? You... You okay?
- Yeah.
Let's just...
Come on, thought I saw someone.
I wanna show you the library.
Come on.
Okay.
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
Hey, excuse me. Could we get...
Yeah, you need to swipe.
I just wanna take him
for a quick look at the library.
Do you a visitor's pass?
No, I... No, I'm... I'm alumni
and he's on a college tour.
Dad, it's okay. Let's just go.
- Please. Please, I promised.
Get passes for next time, okay?
Thank you.
We'll be... We'll be really quick.
Come on.
CHARLIE: What?
- JASON: Yeah.
[CHARLIE CHUCKLES]
- JASON: See?
Now, this, this is really cool.
- Yeah, come on. Come on.
Did you used to study here?
They built it after I graduated.
JASON: Come here.
- What's up?
Just sit... [STAMMERS] Take a seat.
It's, uh... It's pretty cool, huh?
Is everything okay?
- Hmm? Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
- You sure?
Come on.
So, there's not much down that way.
- What is going on with you?
What?
- You are acting really weird.
All right, just listen.
I forgot I have to do something.
I'm gonna... Listen, take the car.
You're gonna meet me
at the south gate on 57ᵗʰ...
and South University, okay?
Okay, I... I don't even know where that is.
Just get your phone and map it.
Dad, I only have a permit.
Charlie, you're gonna be fine. Come on.
Dad, what the fuck is going on?
Listen, I'm gonna explain everything
to you in the car when we meet.
Where did I say? Tell me.
South University and 57ᵗʰ.
57ᵗʰ. Good. All right, go. Tru... Trust me.
[GROANS]
[PANTING]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[PANTING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[BOTH GROANING, GRUNTING]
Wait, wait, wait!
What... What... What do you need?
[PANTS] What do you need?
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[GROANING]
[PANTING]
[STRAINS]
[GROANS, PANTS]
[KNIFE FLICKS]
- [GASPS]
[GRUNTS, PANTS]
[THUDS]
Fuck.
[SIREN BLARES]
[PANTING]
[GRUNTS]
License and registration.
Yeah.
[WALLET ZIPS OPEN]
Learner's permit, huh?
Officer!
It's, uh... That's... That's my car.
That's my... my son.
He can't park here.
No, we were just leaving.
He was waiting for me.
Uh, we're on a college tour
and I used to be a student here.
He just can't park on an active road.
I'm sorry, Officer.
Yeah. [STAMMERS] It is my fault.
[CLEARS THROAT]
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Thank you. Appreciate it.
Be careful.
Yes, sir.
- JASON: All right.
Nice day.
All right, fuck.
- I... I think you should drive.
Just drive.
Just drive! Drive! Fucking drive.
- [STAMMERS] Okay.
OFFICER: Sign and date.
[DOOR BUZZES]
- Thank you.
Oh, my God.
No. Don't touch me.
Smoking in a restaurant?
I just needed to get you
to a place that we could talk.
Why?
Do you have something honest to say?
Because I'm done with the lies.
Bailed you out. You're welcome.
Whatever happened, it wasn't me.
Okay. No.
- Now listen...
[STAMMERS] The night of Ryan's
celebration at the Village Tap...
that was the last time that I saw you.
What are you even saying?
That man isn't me.
He's another version of me.
He... He built a box. My box.
And he has access to other realities...
and he stole me from my world
so that he could take my life.
Do you know how that sounds?
I can prove it. Call me.
I'm sorry.
[STAMMERS] If it's the last thing
I ever ask you to do. Just call me.
[LINE RINGING]
- [SIGHS]
JASON: Hey, what's up?
[GASPS]
See?
Call him back and say
that you've been thinking about...
how we had such a great time
at the Keys last Christmas...
that you wanna go back.
We didn't go to the Keys last Christmas.
I know that but he doesn't.
[PHONE RINGING]
- [GASPS]
Okay, answer.
Hello?
JASON: Hey.
Uh, I thi... I think we got cut off.
Are you there?
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
I was just thinking.
We, uh, took that trip last year
when went to the Keys for Christmas.
[SNIFFLES] What if we went back?
JASON: Uh, yeah.
Definitely.
Do you remember the house?
The pink and white one by the beach?
JASON:
Yeah. No, I... I... I loved that place.
Me too.
JASON: Well, let's make it happen.
CHARLIE: Hey, Mom.
[JASON CHUCKLES]
We decided to play hooky today.
Listen, honey, I need you to come home.
Why?
JASON:
Just... I'll explain it when you get here.
[LINE DISCONNECTS]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
How is this possible?
It's not just him.
There are other versions of me
here as well.
[GASPS]
I have to get Charlie.
Please let me come.
Where would we meet?
You'll need to pick 'cause
he thinks exactly like me.
The Bean.
And we'll need a safe word
so that you know it's me.
Jupiter.
I'm not saying we'll come.
Be careful.
Please. Be careful.
He's dangerous.
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[LINE RINGING]
Hello?
[OBJECT RATTLING]
[JASON PANTS] Hi.
Where's Charlie?
He's gone down to get a suitcase.
Why?
'Cause we need to get out of here.
We need to leave.
Honey, we're in a little bit of trouble,
okay? I... I... I'll explain.
It's got something to do with
the investment and Leighton...
What happened?
Just grab a suitcase, please.
Get some things together,
we're gonna have to leave.
Now!
[FOOTSTEPS ASCENDING STAIRS]
[JASON BREATHING HEAVILY]
[DANIELA WHISPERS]
Charlie. Listen, we're gonna...
JASON: Hey.
Could you come out here?
Yeah.
[SIGHS]
Look, I'm sorry if I scared you.
Okay? [KISSES]
So, you're getting a suitcase?
I am.
Okay.
[SIGHS]
Yeah.
JASON: What are you doing?
[SEND TONE BEEPS]
- Nothing.
[PHONE DINGS]
Taking the RAV4, not the Civic.
Take that.
Don't forget your phone.
Thank you.
Are you getting a bag?
Yeah.
I was gonna get one from the basement.
Can you help me reach it?
[GRUNTING]
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
Mom?
- Get back in.
Mom, what's going on?
- Get back in the car.
Hey! Come with me! It's not safe!
Just leave it, Charlie.
Quick, get in!
Honey, this is gonna sound crazy...
and you're gonna think that I've
lost my mind, but I haven't, I swear.
CHARLIE: What the fuck is going on?
Now, remember the night
at Ryan's celebration...
at the Village Tap when he won the Pavia?
When I walked out the door that night...
that was the last time
that I saw you until right now.
Mom?
The Jason that you're with,
he... he's an impostor.
He... He built a box,
he has access to other realities.
He stole me from this world
so he could have my fucking life.
Pull over, please.
It's insane, but I can prove it.
Stop the car.
[DISTORTED] Charlie. Charlie, are you okay?
[NORMAL] Yeah.
We need to get out of here.
[JASON GROANS]
JASON#1: Daniela, it's me.
- Mom.
Charlie.
- JASON#2: Daniela.
JASON#1: Charlie.
Daniela! Daniela!
- CHARLIE: What the fuck is happening?
[PANTING]
Hey! Daniela!
Daniela!
Say it.
Jupiter.
[SIGHS]
ＤＡＲＫＭａＴｔＥｒ