- Okay.
Here we are on Madeline Beyer.
Today, we're performing
the revision surgery.
This whole midline structure
has been severed
from the underlying spine.
I just grabbed the ligament
and it's exposing the dura,
which is leaking spinal fluid.
I do see down here more bone.
It looks like putty.
It's just smashed in there.
What did he do to her?
- I reviewed the photo
you faxed over.
- And?
- That is
Dr. Christopher Duntsch.
- Did you know?
- No.
- Did you know what
he was capable of?
- No.
The things he is
reportedly doing there,
I never saw here.
Son of a bitch.
- Here you go.
Thank you.
- One of those for me this year?
- I know better than that.
- Here, trade me.
You doing okay?
Yeah, me too.
I get what they've been
telling me.
Braindead.
I know what they're saying.
And I've been looking at that
face every day for 46 years.
That's what she looks like
when she's asleep.
You want to tell me when
a person stops being a person?
What about the craniotomy?
- What do you mean?
- Duntsch said he could
save her with a craniotomy.
- I don't think so.
- You don't think?
- I know.
- It'd be worth a shot,
wouldn't it?
- No.
- Why no?
- She's beyond that now, Earl.
- You're not her doctor.
- I know that.
- You come in here
asking questions,
asking to look at her files,
and now you're telling me no?
Dorothy and I learned
how to sail together.
We bought a boat.
It was just a 24-foot cruiser
earlier this year.
Docked on Lake Texoma.
- Nice up there?
- Nice.
Quiet.
Especially in winter.
It took us 30 years
to buy that boat.
Why did it take us so long
to buy that boat?
- My son was here
just a few doors up that way.
Nine years ago this week,
he lasted a month.
I thought I was... I thought
I was managing the situation.
I figured someone
had missed something.
I mean, this is what I do
my whole life.
I save people,
and no matter
what anybody told me,
how they tried
to convince me otherwise,
I assumed...
Pretended...
there was a chance,
pretended I didn't know
the statistics,
cited miracle cases,
clung to them like facts.
No matter what...
and there's no way around this...
no matter what you decide to do,
you're going to hate yourself,
and...
more than a little.
She's not asleep, Earl.
- And you want me
to listen to you?
To trust you.
I trusted him too.
- All right?
Watch for the long count.
Stay disciplined.
You guys pointed to that
bullshit from last week.
I swear to God,
whoever you want to fucking
till you'll be puking
out of your assholes.
You understand me?
All right, so.
90% of the time, on first down,
they're running twins
to the wide side.
Do not fall for the play action.
It's a fake hand-off...
- He's gonna roll out.
He's gonna hit the inside
receiver with a quick out.
- Freshman?
- What's that?
- You a freshman?
You got that freshman focus.
- Sophomore.
- Oh, redshirted?
- Walk-on.
I just transferred
from Millsaps, Mississippi.
- Walk-ons aren't easy
to come by.
Must be a bitch.
- Well, I always
go the distance.
Chris.
- I'm Chris.
- Duntsch.
- Beton.
But nobody can pronounce
that shit.
- Call me Betts.
- Next up.
- 86.287.
Right on target, Martinez.
Nice work. Next up!
198.
- Um, Coach?
- Next up.
- But I think
that number is wrong.
It's just,
I'm weighing 220 back home.
- Ahh.
Well, you weigh 198 in here.
You're in your goal range.
No need to stress over
a few pounds, Daisy.
- Next up!
- No, no.
There's just no goddamn way.
- Yes, goddamn way. Get off.
- Coach, I think you need
to recalibrate this fucker.
- We can recalibrate
your position on this team
if you don't get
the fuck off my scale.
243. Two pounds light.
I want you up by next week.
- That was, uh, daring.
- Bullshit.
- Come on. Who gives a fuck?
- I bet you were right
on target.
- By your math, I'm fat.
Whatever, man.
- I need to bulk up.
My brother swears by this shit.
It's like his secret weapon.
Nathan gained, like, 40 pounds.
- Whoa. Hold up.
Nathan?
I have a brother Nathan.
- Get the fuck outta here.
That's not enough fingers.
Nathan is, like, a genius.
He got the brains
of the family for sure.
And then my other brother,
Matthew,
is just unbelievable
with a ball... any ball.
Put it into his hands,
he's unstoppable.
They just don't struggle
with things, you know, like me.
I got to outwork 'em or... you
know, that's what my dad says.
- Oh, fuck that guy.
- What's he do?
- Doctor,
or a physical therapist,
but it's cool,
'cause, you know...
"It really don't matter
if I lose the faith."
"'Cause all I want to do
is go the distance."
- Oh, Italian Stallion!
- Yeah!
Fucking classic.
- You know, I'm actually taking
a couple of cinema classes.
- What, like,
you watch movies for credit?
- I know, right?
- You pick a major?
- Eh, I don't know.
I'm looking into chemistry
or biology
or even giving
vertebrate zoology a look.
- That's not a thing.
That doesn't look right.
- It doesn't matter, anyway.
- I can't take it.
Conflicts with morning practice.
Coach would kill me.
What?
- Oh, come on, man.
I mean, the New Jersey is great
for chicks and parties and shit,
but it's not like
we're going pro.
- Maybe you're not.
All right.
Chicken, broccoli...
God, peanut butter?
Jesus, we're going
to eat all this?
- Yup.
I mean, we gotta
blend it up first, but...
- I got a better way
to put on weight.
Come on. You're gonna love it.
Get in there.
Look alive, handsome.
- Hey, Betts!
- Hey, there he is.
- Oh, hey. Thank you so much.
Drunken bastards. Look at you.
Let's have a drink.
Hey, what are you doing?
Gettin' lucky.
Wear some protection.
Creerie, yeah!
You're a very nice man.
Thank you so much. Oh, hey.
- Yeah.
- See you later, okay?
How are you doing?
Thank you so much. Oh, yes.
Hey ladies, let's just
dance the night away.
Just us girls
dancing the night away.
Hey!
Never graduate!
Solomon!
Duntsch, come on.
- Faithful friend,
and future acquaintance, enter.
Some dope dope, my man.
- I'ma head home.
- Come on.
- School day's tomorrow,
you know?
But you have fun.
- Baylor let Duntsch resign.
- He wasn't fired?
- I asked around here two turns,
and all he had
were temporary privileges.
- Were they revoked?
- I was told
that was confidential.
You like peanuts?
Hate that part.
Sitting with the relatives
like that...
never got used to it.
- There was no getting used
to it.
The only thing you can do
is stay if they want you to,
get out of the way
if they don't.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Well, where the hell
was Duntsch?
Not sitting there offering
apologies or advice to that guy
on when to pull the plug
on his wife.
- Do you have any idea
where he is?
- Farting tornado.
What do you think?
- About?
- A guy from
a top medical program
followed by a top residency
followed by a top fellowship.
He keeps getting
these surgical outcomes because.
A, he's either
doing it on purpose,
or two, he just sucks.
- I can't make sense of it.
- Personally,
I'm leaning towards B.
- The question isn't
why he did it.
It's how he got away with it.
- You and I are mind-melding.
- I have no idea
what that means.
- We're on the same page.
I mean, Baylor Plano
has, what, three, four
of the top neurosurgeons
in the area on staff,
and I'm talking the best.
Well, instead
of these top, top guys
getting the patients,
Duntsch gets them...
the newbie,
just arrived in town,
zero experience,
zero business operating.
Come on, you'd think he was,
you know...
With somebody up the ladder.
- Now we're not even
in the same library.
- I'm just saying... motive.
- Move on.
- Are we gonna eat?
- I'm fucking starving.
- You have to make sure
that Duntsch never operates
at a hospital in Texas
ever again.
- Mm-hmm.
- I have a suggestion.
It's a bit extreme,
but I think
the situation warrants it.
We report Duntsch
to the Texas Medical Board.
What do you think?
- I'm still waiting
for the extreme part.
- I don't need to remind you
of what the stakes are here.
- Ooh, they got a porterhouse
in the menu for two.
- Halvsies?
- If we're not meticulous
in presenting our evidence,
if we don't get this right,
Duntsch will continue
to operate.
We need pure, hard facts,
not cocktail umbrellas.
I've been gathering evidence.
- Evidence.
- Yeah.
Patient files.
- Ooh, hee,
here's your girl, Bobbie.
HIPAA violations.
- Are you done?
- I don't know how you pulled
that one off,
and I don't wanna know how,
but I do wanna know how.
- I actually asked his patients
for their permission.
- Mm.
Boring.
- I have some other questions
I need to get answered.
So you enjoy your meal.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Can't trust a place with a red
wine milkshake on the menu.
- At the end, now I face that
which was alluding me
at the start.
The settling, the trading,
and embrace with disappointment.
The sky cracks open
and is crying out for me.
The ground has no shape.
My feet sink in
and takes me down to the depth.
The far depths.
- Chris.
Chris D.
- One day,
we're here without a why.
We grow and live
and always try.
We seek each day,
the reasons why
and push each day
against the tide.
At first, we seek
to find our dreams,
but dreams are never
what they seem.
Some are fast,
and some fall behind,
and push and pull
inside our minds.
- Keep your head up.
- Keep both feet moving!
- Stay wide.
- Here we go, here we go!
- Bring it in! Let's go!
Hustle up.
All right. Listen up.
Clench will be running
a 43 D next week.
Duntsch, you're up.
You're running the play.
Weak cross, plug zero.
Everyone get the concept?
- Yes, Coach!
- All right, let's go.
- Let's go now. Look sharp.
- Ready.
Ready.
Set, hut!
- Duntsch,
what the fuck is that?
You don't go left.
You blitz right. Hit the A gap.
Get your shit together.
Let's go.
- Ready.
Set, hut!
- If you're gonna suck
this hard,
you might as well
get on your knees, Daisy.
Go right, Duntsch.
Run it again.
On the ball.
- Set, hut.
Set, hut.
On the ball!
Run it again!
- Set, hut.
- You're done.
- No, Coach. Coach, I got this.
- No, you don't got this.
- I got this, Coach. Seriously.
One more try, please. Please.
Weak cross, plug zero,
hit the A gap.
One more try.
- All right, let's go.
- Let's chop some wood!
Let's go! On the ball!
- A gap.
- Yeah, yeah.
Son of a bitch! Duntsch!
What the hell was that?
Red jersey means do not hit.
Are you fucking dyslexic
and color blind?
- Want a ride home?
Ah, come on.
Yeah. Today was shit.
But we got practice
again tomorrow.
Two, as it turns out.
And the next day,
and the next day.
You'll get it eventually.
- Eventually doesn't help.
- I need to get it now.
- Tonight?
- You need to get it tonight?
- I don't understand.
I mean, what am I doing wrong?
Why can't I run this?
- Chris, man. I'm tired.
I got a six-pack, a party,
and a girl named Portia
waiting for me at the house.
- One hour. Tops.
Eye of the tiger, motherfucker.
- Yes!
- You did all these notes
in your playbook?
Dork.
Okay.
So you got your center
in the center, obviously.
And then you got guards,
tackles,
and tight ends
laterally on each side.
Here's you at mid.
Now, on the snap,
you blitz right
and hit the A gap
on the weak side.
X marks the spot.
- That's what I'm doing.
- No.
Weak side.
You're mixing them up,
and you're flattening
our quarterback.
Show me your right hand.
All right.
This gap here, on your right,
this is yours.
You got it?
Booyah.
Great. Let's drink.
- Run it?
- You know where to find me.
Got the sled? Okay, man.
- Come on!
- Hello? Help you?
- Where the hell are you?
- Josh?
- Be right up.
Dr. Henderson.
- Can we ask you
a couple questions?
This is Dr. Kirby.
- May I get you something?
- No, thank you.
- Beer would be great.
- Sure. I think I have a...
- Whoa, whoa, wait.
- Are you gonna say an IPA?
- Yeah.
- Seriously? Forget it.
What happened to beer?
You ask for a Bud,
you get an IPA.
You ask for a Coors,
- Life is hard for you, right?
- Can be.
- What's going on?
- Now, if at any moment
you feel uncomfortable...
- We're going after Duntsch.
- You in?
- You're like
a restless toddler.
We're planning
on reporting Duntsch
to the Texas Medical Board.
But we need more information.
Now, we don't have
to use your name, but if...
- Use my name. It's all yours.
- Madeline Beyer came in
for an elective laminectomy
and spinal fusion.
- Totally straightforward.
- We reviewed the pre-op notes
from last week.
Duntsch's plan
for Mrs. Beyer's procedure
was sound, well-reasoned.
He knew the science.
He knew what
he was supposed to do
heading into the OR.
- If you say so, sir.
To me, it was a disaster
from the start.
He showed up late.
And not surgeon late...
late, late.
And when he finally gets there,
that's when
I noticed his scrubs.
There was a hole in them.
- A hole?
- First saw it a few days before
at Rose Keller's operation.
You saying he was wearing
the same scrubs for days
into surgeries?
- At Mrs. Burke's surgery
on Tuesday, hole.
No underwear,
three surgeries in a row.
- Sorry.
- Where... where was this hole?
- How is that relevant?
- Oh, it's relevant.
- In the back.
- In the back, back?
A hole in the a-hole?
- All through
Mrs. Beyer's surgery,
he was mumbling
about Dorothy Burke.
He was preoccupied.
And then the blood?
A lumbar fusion...
acceptable blood loss
would be what?
200, 250 ccs?
She lost 1,700 ccs of blood.
That much blood loss?
Of course we were worried.
- There's a hemorrhage here.
- You need to fix it.
Do your goddamn job
and get her blood pressure
under control.
I can't see anything.
Get the blood out of my field.
Screw.
- Excuse me, sir.
I believe the screw
is out of place.
- I know where it is.
- It should be a little left.
Patient's left.
- I did a fucking visual, okay?
- I know where it is.
- Doctor, it looks
like the screw
might have missed the pedicle.
It seems to be
in soft tissue here.
- Is this guy on something?
- Am I talking to myself?
Reposition the C-arm
on Mrs. Burke now.
- You mean Mrs. Beyer?
- You know what I mean!
Cage. Give me the cage.
- Looks like the screw
is still outside the bone.
- The X-rays are bullshit.
- Get me the cage.
Mallet.
Craniotomy.
Get Dorothy Burke into pre-op.
- Dorothy Burke?
- We need to finish this, sir.
- I'm aware of that. Thank you.
Get Dorothy Burke
prepped for a craniotomy.
- Sir, this hospital
doesn't have privileges
to perform a craniotomy.
- Schedule it.
- We don't have the equipment.
- I'll do it with whatever
the fuck you do have.
Just get it scheduled. Now.
- I'm sorry, sir,
but I can't schedule it
because we do not perform
craniotomies at this hospital.
Maybe we could transfer
Mrs. Burke
out to an equipped facility.
Baylor Plano has privileges
for that.
- When I tell you
to do something, you do it.
- You're talking about
drilling a hole
into her skull, sir.
- Get the charge nurse in here.
Now.
Rod.
- Dr. Anthony?
There's a slight issue
with our lumbar case.
- Am I supposed to guess
what that issue is?
- Dr. Duntsch.
- Who's that? The new guy.
- Yes. This is his first week.
He's requesting a craniotomy.
- Brain surgery
on a lumbar case?
- No, sir.
- It's for a different patient.
- Dorothy Burke.
- I don't give a shit.
- We don't do craniotomies.
- I've told him that, sir.
I think he'd like
to hear it from you.
- Oh.
- I asked for the charge nurse.
- Yeah, well, you got
the chief of surgery.
- She's my patient.
- Her treatment is my decision.
- Well, today,
this is my hospital.
And when you applied
for privileges here,
you didn't check
the little red box
that said "brain surgeries."
- You are interrupting
an extremely delicate
spinal fusion.
- Oh. Oh, I'm so sorry.
I thought you called
for this interruption.
- Because I presumed
that you were shrewd enough
to simply sign off.
- Well, I'm just a country hick
from the Bronx,
so let me put this in a manner
even I can understand.
We don't do craniotomies
at this hospital,
and you are a guest here
at Dallas Medical.
If one of our staff tells you
we don't have privileges
for a procedure,
it is not an invitation
for debate.
- I have privileges
everywhere across this city.
- Oh, you do, do you?
- I will ensure
that not a single patient
comes through your door.
- Wow, that would be so tragic.
- Get the fuck out of my OR!
- I'm gonna walk you through
what's about to happen.
You will complete your work
on Madeline Beyer.
She's been over far too long.
You will then transfer
Dorothy Burke out of your care.
There will be no more
discussion of craniotomies.
No more arguments.
You will do it.
And then you will get the fuck
out of myOR.
- Anything else?
- What else do you need?
- We want you
to suspend his license
pending a formal investigation.
- Neither of you is in the
operating theater at the time?
That's correct.
- So this is all
secondhand information.
All hearsay.
- Yes.
- Just playing devil's advocate.
From your recitation
of the events that day,
Dr. Duntsch could make a case
that he was distracted.
- Did you not hear about
the hole in his scrubs?
I don't think she heard
about the hole.
- I agree. We all agree
that there were some surgical
misadventures at play...
- Misadventures?
- In. Dr Duntsch surgeries
last week,
but there are other issues.
We have a circulating nurse
demonstrating a measure
of non-compliance,
an X-ray tech
challenging a surgeon,
and then
an administrator barging
into an OR mid-procedure.
- They were doing their part
to stop
an out-of-control surgeon.
I was at Baylor Plano.
I saw what he's capable of...
or no, better put...
incapable of.
What about the craniotomy?
He was demanding a procedure
the hospital didn't have
privileges to perform.
- The doctor who took over
Dorothy Burke's case
stated a craniotomy
might've saved her life.
"I would have grabbed
the local handyman's drill
to perform it."
Dr. Duntsch may not have gone
about it the right way,
but it appears
he may have been right.
We receive hundreds
of these reports every year.
We take each case seriously,
but you both know
that there is context
to every story,
mistakes do happen
to every doctor,
even I'm sure to you both.
You're prepared to file
a formal complaint?
- Absolutely.
- Yes.
- All right.
- You are going
to suspend his license?
I mean, what happens to him
in the meantime?
- We can't do that.
- Why the hell not?
- The attorneys
won't go for that.
We'd be opening ourselves up
to a lawsuit.
- I thought protecting
the public was the priority.
- That's our
number one priority.
- Well, what's to prevent him
from seeking privileges
at any one of the other
400 hospitals in the state?
- Dr. Duntsch has resigned
from Baylor.
- He should have
been shitcanned.
- He no longer has privileges
at Dallas Medical.
He has no privileges anywhere.
Perhaps he's taking
some personal time
getting his head straight
after what was a difficult week.
Difficult week.
You know what?
There was a urologist...
a urologist, you got me...
accused by a patient
of fondling his genitals.
A urologist!
These morons pursued the case.
I mean, this... this feels like
we've got to draw blood
in order to move the needle.
Duntsch was distracted?
Give me a fucking break.
- Well, they're not wrong.
He lost privileges
at two hospitals.
News travels fast.
- Not fast enough.
- We voiced our concern.
- We filed a complaint.
They launched an investigation.
What more would you like to do?
- I want to break
his goddamn hands.
- Dr. Kirby, we have no choice
but to respect the integrity
of this process.
- Did you hear those goobers
in there?
The process is gonna fuck us.
The system is broken.
- And we are a part
of that system.
- Oh, fuck this.
- Hey.
- Been looking all over for you.
- Yeah, I've been looking
for you too, man.
I got some news. Great news.
- Yeah?
- Yep.
I am going home.
I'm going back to Tennessee.
And I had an idea.
I haven't really thought
through all the details yet,
but I think
you should come with me.
- Come with you to Tennessee?
- Yes, man.
If you think football
is big here, you have no idea.
Like, two division one football
players retired in the South?
We would be like gods.
- Hold on. Back up.
Why would you leave now?
You just made walk-on.
- Oh, fuck this team.
- There's no future here.
It's bullshit. I don't need it.
- Then why you still
wearing the jersey?
- Look, this is good for me.
Okay? It's good for me.
So just come with me.
- I am not going to Tennessee.
What are you talking about?
- Your loss.
- Dude, I don't think
you thought this through.
- No, no, no. It is all settled.
Okay? I'm leaving.
I'm going home
'cause I don't need this shit.
I don't need any of it. Fuck it.
- Dude, what's going on
with you?
- I can't stay.
- I can't stay, okay?
I needed a football scholarship.
I didn't get it,
so I can't stay.
I'm going home.
I needed it,
and I didn't get it.
- Shit.
Dude, I had no idea.
- Forget it.
- No.
No!
It's gonna be good.
U fucking T, they're awesome.
Great record, solid coach,
and the way you work,
you'll be starting
within three games.
- My third school, Betts.
- My third transfer.
I can't play anywhere.
I'm not even eligible to sit
on the goddamn sidelines.
- Well, maybe
this is a good thing.
I mean, did you ever
really want it?
- What?
- It's just, I think you have
this idea in your head
of what football means
or what it's supposed to mean.
But does it...
does it mean that to you
or do you just think it should?
- Where were you all those
Monday morning film sessions?
Where were you all those hours
after practice,
the drilling, the weightlifting?
Huh? Where were you?
Partying? Sleeping it off?
And you ask me if I wanted it?
Fuck you, Betts.
- Yeah, and all that work
for what?
So you can act like an asshole
and sit
on the goddamn sidelines?
Fuck you!
Stop, okay?
- Stop.
- Come on.
Come on. Let's go.
No, fuck you...
- Stop!
You can't win.
Stop fucking trying.
- Dumb face!
- Is your grandma
good with this?
- Mee-maw? She's good.
This is a light night. Hey.
I'm sorry about
the whole dumb face thing.
- Old habits.
- Ah, don't worry about it.
- So, my hotshot friend,
word is you're a big-time
football player up in the CO.
- I was, yeah.
- Yeah, starting mid.
You should've seen the girls
I got in that jersey.
But some of the guys
on the practice squad
were kind of busted.
So that slowed me down
every now and then.
Honestly,
I'm kind of over football,
you know?
It just... it just feels
beneath me, you know?
- Hey, man. No love lost here.
My neck's still fucked
from junior year.
- Plus I got bigger things
going on here.
- What do you got brewing?
- Pre-med.
UT. I'm taking the MCAT.
- Oh, man! Like, ah!
I always knew
you were gonna end up
doing some crazy
high-end shit with your life.
You were always, like,
the smartest guy I knew.
- Yo.
- And given
the spaz company you keep,
that's not really saying much.
- Ah!
Dumb face!
So that's it.
You're back?
- I miss the weather.
- And your boy, Jerry.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
My boy don't play.
He's going beyond.
Gonna change the world.
Someone get him a Boone's Farm.
Strawberry Hill, right?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, light and sweet, baby.
I knew it. Hey, yo, yo, yo.
Get my homie some Boone's.
- We don't got any of that.
- Then go get some,
you piece of shit.
Go, go! Get some.
Good to be home.
- I'm going to see you
every day.
- I know.
I know it's not ideal
me moving back home,
but Jerry did mention
that maybe I could live with him
for a little while
just until classes start.
And I really think
that I'm onto something
with this research.
I really think that
there's a future in it.
- What exactly does one do
with research?
- Well, maybe you could go
into the medical field,
like your father.
- Actually, Dad,
I've been looking into that
and giving it a lot of thought.
So not all of my courses
from CSU would transfer,
but the biology credits would,
so I'd only actually
need to do, like,
two additional semesters.
I mean, I thought I'd have to
do, like, two additional years.
Two semesters is nothing.
- Money's not nothing, Chris.
First it was Millsaps College
for football,
and then it was Colorado State
for football.
And now you're back
for research.
- I know, sir,
but I would be a doctor.
A neurosurgeon.
- Oh, I don't know.
I have a medical degree, Chris,
and I know the...
the difficulties that come
with that area of study.
- Well, this is not exactly
something you'd be
familiar with.
- Oh? How so?
- I just mean there's been...
there's been a lot
of advancements,
and there's new studies
and new technologies,
and I'd be an MD.
- You know,
this is what I always used
to tell your brother, Nathan.
He has that kind of mind.
Nathan should have gone
to medical school, you know?
- I think it's a great idea.
- Susan.
- Christopher, you have always
struggled to find something
that challenged you,
like Einstein.
Maybe you should
reach out to John.
- Dr. Davidson.
- Susan...
- He's like an uncle to him,
and maybe he could
help you find something.
- Chris is not going
to ask for favors
he definitely cannot repay,
not from my friends.
- Dad, I really think my stem
cell research has potential.
- Stem cell.
- Yeah, they're the... the
building blocks of the human.
- No, I know what
stem cells are, Christopher.
- Okay, so then you know
that they can develop
into other types of cells,
which is why they have
so much potential.
They're incredibly complex
starting right
from the beginning
of their formation
in the embryo.
- If they're in the embryo,
how does one access them
for research?
- We can isolate them
from immature human embryos
and fetal tissue.
- So you're talking about
spending your time
and my money parading around
masquerading as a doctor
promoting the exploitation
of unborn babies?
That is not medicine, Chris.
It's not science.
- Dad,
science is what
can be done by man.
What is conquerable?
And I plan on conquering this.
Well...
I wouldn't count on it.
- Well...
The MCATs disagree with you.
I got a couple wrong.
- Some things
can be learned, son,
and some things
are just biology.
- Hello?
- He was running on a platform
about reducing
the cost of government.
And his plan was to eliminate
three government agencies,
and he couldn't name them.
Fancy pants.
- That's definitely
his kind of...
- Shrimp!
- Oh, God.
- Ah!
Great party.
I did hear a nasty little rumor
about a lobster tail somewhere
with my name on it.
- Randy Kirby.
- Oh. You're Dr. Kirby.
- Oh, I see my reputation
has exceeded me.
- Indeed.
- Would you excuse us
for a moment, please?
- Merry Christmas, Randy.
- Hey, season's greetings
to you.
- So they just let you in?
- Well, I told security
that we needed
to talk some doctor stuff.
- Doctor stuff.
- But firstly, I want to say,
I know I should have called
months ago.
I haven't been able to sleep
thinking about how we left
things after the Medical Board.
I just want to say I'm sorry.
- That's why you came?
- Partly.
- All is forgiven.
- Thanks.
- What's the other part?
Duntsch is back.