A woman who
jumped from the roof
of a multi-story building
in Camberwell yesterday
has been pronounced dead.
Okay, I found a place.
Five-star, swanky,
the whole thing.
And I've never been
to Spain before, so...
- Portugal.
- Hmm?
Sagres is in Portugal, babe.
Okay, who cares? Look,
it looks so nice.
- And you know all about looking nice.
- Hey, now I've got hat hair.
Yeah, I like it like that.
Here, try this.
- What is it?
- My new creation.
It's focus group today, so...
Oh, sneak preview. Lucky me.
- Mmm. Yeah.
- Mm-hmm?
- Yeah?
- It's great.
- What is it?
- It's miso jam.
Hmm?
- Miso jam.
- You so what?
- Oh, you are such a dick.
- You so pretty.
You so tasty.
And miso want a holiday.
Okay.
People may say that they're not
ready for those textures in biscuits,
but our taste tests have
rated off the charts, so...
- Ah, ah! That's my almond milk.
- I was only gonna have a bit.
- But you can have any milk.
- Well...
- That's the only vegan one.
- Oh my God. You serious?
- Okay.
- Milk fascist. Okay, I'll have some...
Ow!
- Maria, we're ready in here.
- My kidneys!
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Guys, sorry. I'm gonna
have to wrap up on this.
Looking like a
regular Hucklebuck.
Yes, boss. Made
just like you said.
- Oh, no nuts in the nougat, right?
- Nah. Just sugar and egg whites.
Okay, good.
'Cause my EpiPen is way over
there, and I can't be arsed to run.
I think
you've done it again.
It's another of your mental ideas
that, annoyingly, really works.
Okay. Got my guinea pigs
at reception. All set?
Yeah. Wanna try one?
Come on in. Take a
seat around the table, please.
Hi.
Okay.
They're amazing,
but think about...
First thing I'm...
Guys, Captain Jack
Sparrow at the end.
- What?
- That guy. Look at him.
- That's nice.
- Yeah.
Thank you.
- Anyone want a coffee?
- Oh, yeah.
- Can I get a double espresso, please?
- Black for me.
Can I get a latte?
Okay, well, thank you all
so much for being here.
Um, I'm Camille. I'll be
running today's session.
Hi. Sorry, is this the right
room for the tasting thing?
Oh.
Oh, sorry, I don't
think you're in today.
- Is that...
- Oh.
No, it can't be.
Uh, I should be on your
list. Verity Greene.
- Christ, that is her. Verity Greene.
- Hang on.
Oh yes, you are down here.
Um, come on through. We
haven't got going yet.
- Sorry.
- You know her?
- I'll grab my seat...
- Yeah, she went to my school.
- Sorry, so sorry.
- Oh no, no bother.
- Hey.
- Well, that's a makeover she's had.
- Oh yeah?
- Okay.
Guys, time to dig in.
Our head of flavor has dreamt up a
fresh take on our famous Hucklebuck,
and you lucky people
get to try it first.
So have a taste,
and let's talk about
how it makes you feel.
Yeah, do take a moment to sit with
the flavor if you're not sure.
I'm sorry, but that's rank.
Okay.
I mean, I like
the normal Hucklebuck,
but these are just... I mean...
I liked it.
What did you
say the flavor group was?
Uh, miso. It's a sort of umami.
Why? Why would you do that?
- Can I have another one?
- Yeah. Of course.
Take as many as you like.
Sorry.
Maybe it's just me, but it
definitely grows on you.
Okay.
But on the second one, it's,
like, ten times better. Honest.
You should try.
Mm. Actually,
now I've gotten
used to it, it's...
it's not bad.
I like the saltiness.
Okay, saltiness.
It really compliments the
chocolate, like, the contrast.
- Yeah. That's what I thought.
- Great.
- Thank God for Verity, yeah?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- Punchy.
- Mm.
- Well done, boss.
- The colors go...
- Thank you.
That was my design brief.
Maria.
Yeah, it's Maria, isn't it?
Verity Greene. Do you remember
me? Colworth Manor High.
- Oh my God. Yes. Of course.
- Yeah.
- Hi. Wow. It's been...
- God, yeah... like, ten years?
- Crazy.
- Yeah. What are the chances?
- Wow!
- Are you here for the tasting thing?
Oh, no. No, no. No,
I... I work here.
- You work here?
- Yeah, in the R&D division.
- In the R&D? Oh!
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I'm just doing
the focus group thing.
I really enjoyed it.
It was so interesting.
All the new fillings.
- I mean, all the science of it.
- Yeah.
Yeah. I think I'm definitely
gonna apply for the job.
- Right. Sorry, the job?
- Yeah, the, uh, research assistant in R&D.
I don't think there
is a job going.
Oh, the...
It said on the website
there was a vacancy.
I'm quite... I mean, I'd know,
and I, yeah, I don't think
there is a job going right now.
- Oh.
- Sorry.
Yeah, I could have sworn...
Oh. That's a pity.
If you remember anything about
me, you'll know that I love a lab.
Yes.
I was such a geek
at school, wasn't I?
- Well...
- I, like, lived in the computer room.
Yeah, you were...
I'm amazed you remember me at all
because you were definitely popular.
I mean, I don't know...
Oh yeah. No. Especially
compared to me.
Like, what was I?
Um, look, I...
Actually, I have to go.
- Oh God, sorry. Yeah. Sorry.
- Yeah.
Yeah, um...
- It was good to see you.
- Yeah, you too.
Hey, Gabe.
- Hey.
- Oh, nice one on the miso jam Hucklebuck.
- Oh.
Camille said they were
hesitant at first, then...
- Yeah, it's a grower.
- A big grower.
They asked for takeaways.
I just saw we've got an advert
for a research assistant.
- Oh yeah. Yeah, it went up a few days ago.
- It's just that we hired Luisa in March.
Well, expanding the team.
I mean, we're doing
well. You are doing well.
Ditta's really into
your mallow concept.
- Might launch it globally if he likes it.
- Mr. Ditta said that?
Ask him if you don't believe
me. He'll be here Thursday.
- Here?
- Yeah.
Gonna get myself a new shirt.
She's this girl
I went to school with.
I haven't seen her in
years, and then today, bam,
she's in one of the focus groups, and
then she's after a job in our office.
- In your office?
- My office.
- Is there a job going?
- Well, yeah, but not for her.
- She was, like, the school freak.
- Is that her official title or...
She was clever,
like, brainbox clever to the
point where she was sort of "off."
Zero social skills.
She had this mad hair.
She was always scribbling, like,
these weird little diagrams
of, like, computers that
she wanted to build.
She... sounds kind of cool.
No, she definitely was not
cool. Right from the off.
And there was this
rumor about her.
Spicy rumor?
That she wanked off Mr. Kendrick
in the computer room.
What, "Mr. Kendrick"?
What, like a teacher?
Yeah. But it probably
wasn't even true.
- It was...
- That is...
Teenagers love to gossip,
even if it's bullshit.
This is you saying you
gossiped about Verity?
- Everyone gossiped about Verity.
- Okay.
- It was just... She was just...
- An easy target?
Not for me.
This one girl, Natalie Caine,
when she heard about the
Mr. Kendrick stuff, she was ruthless.
She kept calling
Verity "Milkmaid,"
like, over and
over till it stuck,
and then that was just her name.
Like, "Look at Milkmaid's hair."
"Look at Milkmaid sitting on her own."
- Kids can be vicious.
- Mm.
But she was always this big
computer genius at school,
and this says she's been
working at a travel agent.
- Wait. Are you stalking her?
- No.
But to go from that to
food research, I mean, why?
Maybe she's got
the qualifications.
She won't have the
qualifications.
Uh, after that, then I took
molecular biochemistry at Cambridge.
Yeah. I was quite proud
because I got a first.
So I see.
And around the same time, I
just got fascinated by food,
so I enrolled in a catering
course at Oxford Brookes.
You've been scuba diving
since you were 12?
- That's your mate, isn't it?
- Mm.
Oh, who's been at this?
- Don't look at me.
- I'll write my name on it, then.
- Need help with spelling? Begins with "L."
- Yeah. Funny.
Uh, guys? Hello! Everyone.
Um, this is Verity.
She's gonna be joining us as
our new research assistant.
Please make her feel welcome.
Nick, could you
find Verity a desk?
Yeah. Definitely, yeah.
Thank you.
- Hi. Thank you.
- Enjoy.
- Hi.
- Do you want to come this way, m'lady?
- Yeah.
- Uh, great. You're welcome.
- Hi.
Hey, again.
- How about right here?
- Oh.
- Pre-warmed chair.
- Slide you in, which is a plus.
- Gabe? Gabe? Hey.
Um...
- That's quite the fast track.
- Yeah, well, I just thought, why not?
- She's overqualified if anything. I mean...
- Right, and that's... that's all legit?
Well, I haven't rung Cambridge
to ask if she's a fantasist,
if that's what you mean.
I'm just saying 'cause, um,
I went to school with her.
- Yeah, you said. Did you not get on?
- There it is.
No, it wasn't that. It
wasn't that. She was just a bit...
A bit?
You know...
odd.
Well, we're all a bit odd.
I'm just saying maybe
kick the tires a bit more.
I'll... I'll
call around. Better?
Yeah. Look, it's
probably all fine.
Yeah. It probably is.
It's a great
place to work.
We're a really chill
partnership, and, um...
No, internal dating is allowed, but
it's just frowned upon in some areas.
We'll add you to, uh,
the WhatsApp group.
Um, there's a funny WhatsApp group.
We do memes. We do sort of, like...
Hey, babes.
- Gabe's hired her.
- Huh?
Verity fucking Greene.
So she was qualified.
Yeah, on paper.
Qualifications are on paper.
Have you got beef with her?
No.
It sounds like you
got beef with her.
Go back to your... game.
- Doors closing.
- Oh.
- Morning.
- Doors opening.
- Doors closing.
- So I checked Verity out.
- Yeah?
- Clean bill of health.
- They all said super attentive.
- Okay.
- Really smart.
- Plays well with others. Yeah.
- I get it.
- So, um, all okay?
- Floor two.
All okay.
Doors opening.
Great, because I told Verity she can
conduit between you and Yudy today.
- She can conduit? Conduit's not a verb.
- You know, liaise.
- You... you got what I meant.
- Also, we don't need a conduit.
It's just so, you know,
she can watch your process.
- Learn the ropes.
- Right.
- Uh-huh. And maybe even break the ice.
- Sure.
- Have you tasted Verity's flapjacks? Wow.
- Steady on.
- Help yourself.
- Hey. What's going on?
These are so good.
- Mmm. You should work for a food company.
- Yeah, maybe I should.
So this is my new
mallow concept, the Doubloon.
Mmm. I wanna eat it
already!
Always a good sign.
So, for Yudy, the kitchen head, we compile
the full list of ingredients, obviously.
Right, yes. That's
where I come in.
For today, yeah.
- So, for the enrobing chocolate...
- Mm-hmm.
...that is 70% dark
with fine salt crystals.
70% dark choc,
fine salt crystals.
- Yeah.
- Um...
And the, um, marshmallow?
- It's just mallow.
- Yep, right, mallow.
Non-pork gelatine
for the mallow.
Non-pork gelatine.
Actually, you know what? I can't remember
if it's pork Mr. Ditta doesn't eat.
Better to go totally
plant-based. Um, carrageenan.
Uh...
Uh, it's made from... it's
made from a sort of seaweed.
- Oh, seriously, again?
- Carra...
- Who's had me almond milk?
- Carrageenan.
- "Not I," said the little red hen.
- How do I spell that?
Uh, carra...
Uh, carrageenan is...
- C-A-R...
- Uh, no. It's...
- I know it was...
- Honestly, I went for cow's milk.
Um...
Know what? I'm just gonna email
you with the full spelling.
- Yeah, great. That's great.
- Yeah? Great, great.
Seriously, this stuff
costs, like, £4.50 a carton.
I actually lived above
a Greggs in Wandsworth once.
My waistline's still not forgiven me.
I used to be
hooked on their steak bake.
It was like heroin in pastry for
me, but now I've gone vegan, so...
- They do a chicken one?
- Yeah. It has weird sauce.
The only chicken thing I actually
miss is the Morley's burger.
Oh, I love Morley's.
Well, if we're talking fast-food chicken,
the absolute winner for me is Bernie's.
- Bernie's?
- Bernie's Chicken.
Had branches
everywhere. Went bust.
Whoever Bernie was, he
was shit with money.
It was Barnie's.
- Say again.
- Barnie's Chicken, the chicken chain.
It was "Barnie's" with an
"a," not Bernie's with an "e."
Yeah, no, it was
definitely Bernie's.
- B-E-R...
- B-A-R-N-I-E-S.
"Barney" with an I-E at the ending?
That's not how you spell Barney.
No, I think "Barnie" meant, like,
an animal that lives in a barn.
Like a chicken.
They live in coops.
- Honestly, it's Barnie's.
- Yeah.
It was the chain. Bernie's.
They were all over South London.
Yeah, sorry, I've got to say, I think
it was Bernie's. Bernie's Chicken.
- Okay. I know for a fact it's Barnie's.
- She's getting a strop on.
Yeah, Nick, because my boyfriend
used to work at a Barnie's.
He still wears a baseball cap from there,
so I see the logo every single day.
So I know it is Barnie's.
Come on, guys. "Bernie's,"
"Barnie's," does it matter?
- It matters that she's wrong.
- Oh my God! Okay! Okay!
- Let's Google it.
- Yeah, okay. Let's do it.
- Yep.
Barnie's Chicken.
Oh dear.
N... No.
- Oh no. Oh, no, no, no.
- No, look.
- Oh, deary me.
- No.
- No?
- It was not that.
- Oh, is it not? No.
- It wasn't that.
- Is the whole Internet wrong today?
- It...
- That's annoying, isn't it?
- Oh my God.
Troubleshoot that if you can.
Feel the "Bern."
- Nick...
- What?
- Let it go.
- I am.
- Hon...
- Mm-hmm?
Look at this.
- What about it?
- It's changed.
- From what?
- Just read it.
Bernie's.
It used to say "Barnie's."
Why? It's Bernie's Chicken.
- You okay?
- It was Barnie's.
- Babes.
- Don't "babes" me. It was Barnie's.
I was the one who worked at a
Bernie's Chicken for a year, okay?
- It's always been Bernie's.
- I swear to God, it's changed.
Maybe you just think it has,
like the Mandela Effect.
- People misremember things.
- No. I...
Like the Monopoly man wearing
a monocle. That was a big one.
- I made a dick of myself at work.
- 'Cause of Bernie's Chicken?
- No, because of fucking Verity.
- Okay, what's she got to do with that?
She's just getting on my nerves.
Everyone's fawning all
over her, kissing her arse.
- She's allowed to be popular.
- Why are you taking her side?
- What side? She's allowed to be popular.
- I didn't say she wasn't.
It doesn't make her a threat.
- I didn't call her a threat.
- Okay, well...
What? Now I'm threatened by
popular people? Is that it?
No, I'm just saying that
you like to be top dog.
- Oh, fuck off.
- You do.
You love it when everyone's
sucking your dick...
I expect people to suck my dick?
I didn't say "expect."
Oh sorry. I ask them to?
Be a bit difficult since I
don't have a fucking dick.
You can relate to
that, can't you?
Bernie's Chicken!
Oh, just through here, Mr. Ditta.
This is where the magic happens.
Uh, this is Nick in Graphics.
Um, Kitchen Head, Yudy.
And, of course, of Chili
Flake Bête Noire fame,
our chief wizard, Maria.
Oh, technically, a female
wizard is a witch, so...
Either way, I'm impressed
by your conjuring.
Thank you.
Ah, the famous miso
jam Hucklebuck.
I've heard good things.
There is a bit of
a learning curve to it.
Very good.
Uh, this is the Doubloon.
- Mm-hmm.
- It's a new concept.
- It's made from...
- Please, please, no spoilers.
Let me guess.
That's good.
That's great.
Okay, so it's, uh,
dark salted chocolate.
- Yes.
- And, um, kind of a marshmallow.
- Just mallow.
- Mm.
But what's this texture?
It's very interesting.
Uh, well, it's bound with
a plant-based gelatine,
which is derived from seaweed.
- Seaweed?
- Mm.
- Um...
- The things that we can do, hey? May I?
Yeah. Oh, yeah, you're
the boss.
Mmm.
Tight ship you're running,
Gabe. See you in Berlin.
Yes. Of course.
Good. And I think
you should join us.
I...
Yeah. Yes.
- Good.
- Okay, all right.
- What is up with you?
- It's beef gelatine in the mallow.
- Beef?
- Oh, what? Ditta is Hindu.
- You just fed him beef.
- Carrageenan.
- I said "carrageenan."
- Wasn't on the list.
- I was specific.
- It wasn't on Verity's list.
Verity's list.
- Sorry, what did you call it?
- Carrageenan.
- I've never heard that word before.
- You wrote it down.
You even asked how to spell it.
- She just said, "Non-pork gelatine."
- I didn't.
Luisa was complaining about
almond milk. Maybe you were distracted.
- Honestly, non-pork was all she said.
- So it's a verbal instruction.
Maybe some things get misheard.
I wrote it in an email to
her. Listed every ingredient.
Sorry, Maria, but in the email you
sent, it just says non-pork gelatine.
I know what I wrote.
Well... Please stop
shouting at me.
I am not...
- I am not shouting.
- You've been raising your voice.
- What? When?
- I think you need to calm down.
I am calm!
I'm... I...
I am calm.
Gabe, I remember what I
wrote and how I wrote it.
I am saying that
Verity is mistaken.
Let's see that email.
Mm.
- You owe Verity an apology.
- That is not what I wrote.
Just apologize.
I'm sorry.
Can I go now?
- She altered it somehow.
- Whoa!
- I don't know how or why. She must have.
- Maria.
Gabe, please, come on. You
have known me for years.
Will you please
just listen to me?
I am listening. You
sound quite emotional.
I... know what I wrote.
Look, you have some
personal issues with Verity.
I can see that.
But, from my perspective, she's
hardworking, you know, well-liked.
- She's done nothing wrong.
- Yeah, she's doing this.
No one is doing anything.
- Look, is everything all right at home?
- Don't fucking patronize me.
- If you want to take some time off...
- I am fine.
All right. Well, if
that ever changes,
I'm always here to talk.
Oh, uh, Maria.
In the meantime,
get off Verity's back.
Okay?
You're starting to
look vindictive.
What I don't understand is how
she changed the fucking email. How?
Maybe she didn't.
- Kae, I know what I wrote.
- Maybe you sent it to draft by mistake.
I checked the draft
folder. Fucking hell.
Have you... have you listened
to anything I've fucking said?
Every word since you came in.
Okay, Verity has orchestrated
some high-tech conspiracy...
She has always been good with
computers. Like, mad genius level.
- She is doing this.
- I think you're working too hard.
- Oh, don't you fucking start.
- I do. You're sounding...
I think you sound stressed and obsessed.
Sh, Natalie texted back.
Who's Natalie?
Nat from school.
It's not from her.
"Hi, this is Dan,
Nat's husband."
"No easy way to say this, but
Nat passed away a few days ago."
"Sorry it took a while to reply,
but it's been tough, as
I'm sure you understand."
Shit.
Sorry.
Was she a close friend or...
Maybe just send him a
text, you know. Poor guy.
"Sorry for your loss," or...
Don't... Babes, don't call. What you
doing? The man just said he's grieving.
- Hello?
-  Hey! Hi, sorry.
Um, this is... this is Maria, um,
from Nat's school. You just texted me.
Yeah. Your name
was on the thing.
Honey, stop.
Sorry to break it in a text.
It's just been rough, you know?
With the kids and...
It was such a shock.
Oh, I'm sure, I'm
sure, I'm sure.
Um, God, yeah.
How did she...
Was she ill, or...
- Maria.
- Or...
- How did she... die?
- Yeah.
She... she took her own life.
- As in, she killed herself?
- Yeah.
But why? I mean...
I don't know. Some
kind of breakdown.
In the weeks leading up,
she wasn't really rational.
How so?
Like, paranoid. Accusing everyone
of lying about stuff. Stupid things.
Her grip on reality
wasn't, you know, the best.
Sorry, why... why do
you wanna know this?
Had she been in touch
with anyone from school?
What do you mean?
Had she bumped into anyone
from Colworth Manor High?
- What's that have to do with anything?
- Did she mention Verity Greene?
- No. I don't know who that is.
- Fuck's sake. Maria.
- Are you sure?
- Look, I'm sure.
- Verity Greene.
- Listen, I have to go.
- I've got to put my kids to bed.
- Oh, I'm so sorry.
- I'm gonna hang up.
- If you could try to remember...
Don't call this number again.
Morning.
Are you sitting the meeting out?
Sorry?
There was a team meeting this morning.
The rest are still down there.
- I'm early.
- Uh, it was at 8:00.
- No one said.
- I think Gabe sent an email yesterday.
I did not see that.
- I mean, it's probably in your junk.
- Oh, I bet it is.
Do you have a problem with me?
What?
You just seem like you
have a problem with me.
And why might that be?
I don't know.
You can't think of any reason?
I know you didn't think
much of me at school.
I didn't think anything of you at
school, Verity. I hardly noticed you.
You even said yourself you were
always in the computer room.
I'm sorry, but you didn't
really cross my mind very often.
- People said stuff about me.
- I don't know. Did they?
About me and Mr. Kendrick.
I never... I never
believed any of that.
Whole time I was at school, he was,
like, the only one who was nice to me.
He didn't care that I
had mad hair or whatever.
He just, like, told me I was
clever, and he looked out for me.
That computer room,
like, I lived for it,
those lunchtimes, because it was
the only place I wasn't on my own.
So when he was
transferred, I had nothing.
Because everything outside
of that was, like...
You know.
Kids can be fucking awful.
They're just kids.
They're not thinking.
Yeah, I know.
I never had a problem
with you, Verity.
And I am... I'm really sorry
that you had such a hard time.
Thank you.
Mm.
Nick, we gotta change that
slogan by the end of the day.
"Crunchy Surprise" is
not gonna play. Oh.
What's with the
no-show at the meeting?
Hello?
We had an emergency recall. A YouTuber
found a toenail in a Caramel Cove.
Did you not get my email?
Maria, my email?
Uh, I bet it's in my spam.
Oh, you guys
are taking the piss.
Okay, sorry, everyone.
Uh, this keeps happening,
and it's not on, all right?
One of you's been at
my almond milk again.
And it was full this morning,
so... I know it's just happened.
So who was it?
I was in the meeting
with you, so...
Oh my God. It was her.
Okay? It was Verity. She drank
the whole thing in front of me.
- Why are you doing this?
- Because you are a fucking freak.
- Okay, enough.
- I don't know why she's doing this.
- I don't know why you're doing this.
- I didn't want to say.
I find her so intimidating.
But it was Maria
who drank your milk.
Really?
I drank almond milk?
Yeah.
Which I'm allergic to?
I mean, I only know what I saw.
- You lunatic fucking liar.
- I said enough.
We can... we can just
check the camera.
The security camera?
Okay?
Uh-huh.
Yeah. Let's do it.
All right.
Okay.
- Kitchen area.
- Mm-hmm.
- Play it from here?
- Yeah.
Honestly, it wasn't
me. It was her.
Let's just...
watch the tape.
Jesus Christ, Maria.
I didn't do that.
Oh my... That...
That is not even possible.
I've got a nut allergy!
- No such thing as a nut allergy.
- What's "nutallergy"?
- A nut allergy.
- What?
Nut...
"Nutallergy"?
An allergy to nuts.
I am allergic to nuts.
Well...
I have had a serious nut
allergy my whole life.
I've always had to read
ingredients and study labels.
It's how I got into food.
Because of my nut allergy!
"Nutallergy." You keep saying it
like it's supposed to mean something.
- What does it mean?
- Do you know?
No.
Oh, now we're Googling it. Okay.
How are you doing this?
Okay, look,
Maria. Look, just...
- It's that. It's that pendant thing.
- Maria...
Oh my God. She's
changing things...
Okay. Whoa. Hey.
...with that thing
around her neck.
- Get off me!
- You need to calm down.
I am calm. I am calm.
All right. So why
don't we just sit down?
Let's... Maria. Hey! Whoa!
Your actions leave me
with no choice but to let you go.
Maybe you're struggling with
your mental health. I...
Whatever nutallergy
is, I don't know.
But you need to take a
break and focus on yourself.
You need to get well.
This is not coming
from me as a boss
but as a friend, one
human being to another.
Please speak to someone.
- Get some help.
- Oh, shut up, you cunt.
- See you tomorrow, Verity.
- See you tomorrow, Nick.
What the fuck?
Oh shit.
Shit. Ow!
♪ Her legs are long
like a licorice ♪
♪ She's a genie, and
you got one wish ♪
♪ Ya dressed up in
the snake's venom ♪
♪ You wanna touch her And
you just might let 'em ♪
♪ You're rolling
on the esplanade ♪
♪ Her spirit's long
And her spirit's hard ♪
♪ You wanna try her,
and she'll fold ten ♪
♪ Life ain't a bitch It's
a lover or a friend ♪
♪ Star fire, she
fell from the sky ♪
♪ Star fire, do
you wanna ride? ♪
♪ Star fire, she
fell from the sky ♪
♪ Five hundred times a night ♪
♪ She sees the golden
grass And golden towers ♪
♪ Here she comes,
she's star fire ♪
♪ You think you know
The world about loot ♪
♪ She'll take you out On
the back of the boot ♪
♪ Star fire, only
one side of town ♪
♪ Star fire, star fire ♪
♪ Burning holes in
her short hot gown ♪
♪ Star ♪
Come out.
I will call the police.
Yeah, I thought it might be you.
I've got your fucking thing.
Your fucking pendant.
It won't work for you.
It's got finger ID.
This changes things, doesn't it?
You say something,
you fiddle with this,
and then somehow,
reality changes.
How can that little
thing change reality?
It's just a remote.
Connects to the quantum
compiler downstairs.
That's what changes reality.
I'll show you how it works.
- You're not fucking getting this back.
- It really is just a remote.
I've got loads of them.
Technically, it's not
changing anything.
It just retunes our
corporal frequency
to one of the parallel realities where
whatever I've said has always been true.
There's infinite timelines,
so I just pick the one
where you're the only one
who knows what's going on.
- So you feel really...
- How...
...special.
- Where... where did you...
- I built the system.
Computer lab nerdo.
I can change little things, like you chose
a red top this morning instead of yellow.
Make it so you've
always spoken Chinese.
Make it so we're having
this conversation in the office.
Or put it all back.
You total fucking bitch!
It's quite cool,
though, isn't it?
I don't understand.
I don't care if
you understand it.
I'm doing it to hurt you.
That's the main thing.
Why?
- You know why.
- I don't know.
Who started that rumor...
about me and Mr. Kendrick?
- What?
- Who started the lie?
I... I don't know.
And you're still lying.
Natalie Caine told
me it was you.
Just before she jumped.
She said it was you.
Was she lying?
No.
Then why?
I don't know.
Um, maybe I was jealous.
Um, maybe I wanted Natalie
to get off my back.
I... It wasn't my fault.
I just said it as a joke.
She ran with it, and, like...
And everyone else just
went along with it.
Yeah, and then it became a reality, and
weirdo Milkmaid couldn't fight back.
And she was stuck there.
Just like everyone
calling her mad.
Lonely old place, isn't it?
You... you could use that.
You could use that
to do anything.
You can make it so that
none of that matters.
- You could be...
- Empress of the universe?
Yeah.
What, make it so I'm
empress of the universe?
Worshiped by acolytes?
Yeah. Yeah, that was
the first thing I did.
Don't get me wrong.
It was amazing.
For a while.
I've done everything.
I've been everything.
But whatever I do, all
that stuff is just...
It's just still there.
Just aching away.
So here I am, fixing a hole.
Seeking closure.
Took me five weeks
to break Natalie.
You've been what, like,
five days.
How do you think you'll do it?
She was a jumper, but
you're not a jumper.
Maybe you like wrists.
Or, um...
Ow!
Fuck!
- The police are here. Armed police.
- Fuck you!
Your boyfriend called and
said you've gone berserk.
You've broken into my
house with a knife.
Police! Drop it!
Oh, thank God you're here.
Don't let her hurt me.
Drop the knife.
Hands on your head. Now.
Turn around.
Christ!
Drop it!
Get your hands up!
Stop!
The pendant works for me.
The pendant works for me!
Drop it now, now, now!
She shot herself. It wasn't
me. You saw the whole thing.
I know.
Who is she?
Um...
I've never seen her before
in my life. I don't know who she is.
So why did she shoot herself?
What's going on here?
We're gonna need to take you to
the station to ask some questions.
No, you won't.
How so?
You work for me. Both of you.
Yes, guv.
You worship me.
Yes, ma'am.
Because...
...I am...
I am the empress
of... the universe.
Hail Maria.
Hail Maria!
Hail Maria! Hail Maria!
Hail Maria! Hail
Maria! Hail Maria!
♪ Never in a million
fucking years ♪
♪ Did I ever think I'd ever
See your fucking face again ♪
♪ I'll find you on the wall ♪
♪ Find you in reflection ♪
♪ Well, I thought I
was getting better ♪
♪ I must think I’m
fucking Mickey Mouse ♪
♪ This year's been a belter ♪
♪ Shithouse! ♪
♪ Well, I thought I
was getting better ♪
♪ I must think I’m
fucking Cinderella ♪
♪ In the mind there
lives a louse ♪
♪ Shithouse! ♪