My god. Look.
- Wait!
- You have to stop!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Coming over to this
side's a piece of cake.
Heading back the other
way, that's the problem.
Last night my mom told my dad
Arlo said there's a voice in his head.
He told 'em there's something coming.
Something that's gonna kill us.
Assassin-kill-murder. Assassin-kill!
- Where are you going?
- We should go with him.
You have to listen to harbinger.
Harbinger is real, meryl.
And he's telling the truth.
We need to go right now.
- What is this?
- Toxin.
Bad... poison.
So what are we gonna do with it?
We drink it.
Anybody here?
Somebody down there?
Okay. Can you grab this?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Okay.
So, everybody takes a sip of this
and then we walk over
the line? Easy-peasy?
Easy-peasy.
But it's poison.
Yes, it is poison.
So, if we drink too much,
like all these animals...
Dead.
Drink too little?
Walk over the line, and then dead.
Don't drink it at all,
assassin shows up and...
Dead.
Dead, dead, and...
Hey. Let's go.
Come on.
So you're telling us that
everything that has happened,
the electricity, the phones, the engines...
And what about the line and what
happens when someone tries to walk over it?
The effect the line has, the odd
and aggressive behavior of animals,
and as I said, some
people too, yeah... all of it.
It's terrifying and tragic,
but not beyond explanation.
Well, what is the explanation?
We'll get to that, I promise,
but first and foremost,
I am here to get you all
out of this, okay? Safely.
- Obviously, that's good to hear.
- But this is insanity.
One thing at a time, please.
Of... of course.
Now, you said there are nine.
You two, the two men
who went to the neighbors'.
Right, James and Ruben.
One man in the clinic,
injured, a woman with him.
- Donald and Maggie.
- Maggie's a veterinarian.
Medical professional,
that's good to know.
And the three children. No one else?
There was the guy with
the mask holding the signs.
I know all about him. But
no unannounced visitors?
- No one hurt, acting strange, confused?
- No, no. Nobody.
You must be Maggie.
This is lieutenant Olsen.
We're trapped, but we have a way out.
The way out could kill
us, but not if we're careful.
What are you doing?
Your grandma told me that
when things are screwed up...
She says whatever's going
wrong and then says "but"?
There's a bad guy coming,
but he's not here yet.
Hit my forehead. It was
bloody and it hurt a lot, but...
The girl I've been in love
with since the second grade
took care of it and made me feel better.
We need to go home.
Yeah, okay.
What was she even doing up there?
I don't know.
Unfortunately, I do.
This is why I was asking
about unannounced visitors.
What do you mean?
A big part of my job was to locate
and isolate Carmen navarro.
- God. Why?
- Why? What... what happened?
As I understand it,
she had become erratic,
confused, left the
navarro property on foot,
missing since yesterday.
And what was wrong with her?
Was she sick?
Yes, but... it's more than that.
What happened to Carmen has something
to do with that blue line, doesn't it?
It's all connected, yeah.
Now, as far as you know, are
you the only one who saw Carmen?
I mean, Donald was talking about her.
He was in the woods last night.
- Donald's the one in the clinic?
- Yeah.
Do you know if Carmen was
dead when Donald saw her?
I mean, he didn't know it was Carmen.
He... he said "body."
"The body." So yeah, he
thought Carmen was dead.
Well, that's, actually good.
Is it?
If someone had come into contact
with Carmen when she was still alive,
well, we'd have a real problem.
What does that mean, "a real problem"?
Maggie.
Arlo was in the woods
last night before Donald.
And.
I mean, he's definitely been acting...
Well, he hit his head.
I mean, he has a concussion.
Arlo is...
My son.
You know where Arlo is right now?
I think the kids are upstairs.
- Take me to them?
- They're actually in the barn.
- They are?
- Yeah.
Arlo was feeling a lot better
and he wanted to go and, feed the goats.
I thought, you know, it's
a really good distraction
given everything that's happened
so I can take you over there.
Good.
Here.
- What is she doing?
- I don't know.
What did the man write on
the sign? "Don't trust anyone."
Why did you say that?
Why did I say what?
You know what I'm talking about.
Yeah, I do.
So?
Because it's true.
And with everything
that's going on right now,
if I didn't tell you
look.
Arlo!
Harbinger!
I wanna talk to my brother.
Let me talk to Arlo now.
Enough is enough.
You sound just like mom.
Good.
Then you know I'm not kidding around.
I want answers, okay? Real answers.
Nicholas asked you
where harbinger came from,
and you pointed to the sky.
That's right.
So you're saying what? Outer space?
That's where harbinger's from?
Yeah.
And... and assassin's the one
who made that horrible line
in order to trap harbinger?
Yeah.
Why does assassin
want to stop harbinger?
Harbinger's here...
Harbinger's on a secret mission.
What does that mean, secret mission?
It's a car.
Okay, let's go.
So, what are you?
What am I?
You're a-a police officer?
A lieutenant, yes.
With the Birmingham police.
Alabama?
We're nowhere near Birmingham.
I'm part of a task force made
up of police, army, marines.
We're from all over and we travel all over.
So, where is everybody else?
We work alone.
Until a situation becomes untenable.
And this isn't untenable?
I get it, but no, it's not.
Not yet.
You wanna tell me what's
really going on here?
- What do you want to know?
- Everything.
The line. What the hell is it?
The line itself, it's nothing.
It's, just a line.
The man who painted it
is trying to help, I guess,
but he doesn't have all the information.
And he's unstable, so he's
doing more harm than good.
- That's not what I meant.
- I know what you meant.
The way things have
been explained to me is
it's a very strong,
concentrated kind of vibration,
and when complex organisms
come into contact with it,
well, you know what happens.
And what causes it?
Short answer is, we don't know.
We do know that it can
disrupt signals and currents.
It adversely affects animals
and sometimes humans.
So, was there some
kind of a confrontation?
With Carmen?
Yeah.
Something pretty
horrible happened to her.
Obviously there was a very
serious altercation after she left,
but before? No.
And it wasn't with you, right?
I arrived after Carmen went missing.
And not with anyone
from your task force?
I told you, I work alone.
Right, but what happened with Carmen,
you said it was connected.
You think it might be part of
what's happening with Arlo?
Well, it could be your son just
has a concussion, like you said,
but there have been
instances of whatever this is
moving from person to person.
They could be up in
the hayloft, so, you know,
we should...
Your son's not up here.
No, he's not.
Carmen's wrists had marks on them,
like she'd been restrained.
What you said about what
happened to her, it's not true, is it?
Not all of it.
No.
So, is it that you're
not telling us everything,
or is it that you're just lying?
You're smart.
It won't help.
What do you mean? Why not?
Because there is no one else coming.
And there is no way out.
The only way for any
of you to survive this
is if you take me to your son.
No.
No, I'm not gonna do that.
Sure you will.
He's not who he says he is.
And all of this, whatever
it's for, it's not fucking good.
Okay, but if he is police
Carmen had marks on her
wrists, like she'd been tied up.
He has zip ties on his belt.
What does that prove?
Nothing, if it's just about that,
but this guy's been lying
ever since he got here.
- What?
- He
he doesn't look like a liar to me.
Well, that's the thing about liars,
isn't it, Valeria?
They look just like everybody else.
Okay, well...
If he's not here to do good,
then who the hell is he?
I don't know, someone dangerous.
What do we do now?
I have no idea.
You know.
About... James and me.
Do I?
It's over.
It's fine if you hate me.
I don't hate you.
You don't?
What good is that gonna do?
I feel angry, sad.
Betrayed.
I don't hate you, I feel bad for you.
Why is that?
I thought it was because you aren't
the good person that I thought you were.
But then I realized, I feel bad for you
because you aren't the good
person that you thought you were.
And that's gotta hurt.
Knowing that.
Yeah... James was right.
Yeah?
About what?
How cold you can be.
Who the hell are you?
It really doesn't matter.
It absolutely matters.
Just bring your son to me.
We're running out of time.
I'm not gonna do that.
- You need to bring me Arlo...
- Stop!
Before it's too late.
- Just...
- I'm not gonna say it again!
We... we can't just keep hitting him.
If Ellen comes back,
just don't let the kids up here.
Hey... where are you going?
God...
She's got it all wrong.
No, I don't think she does.
Well, then you've got it all wrong too.
Well, I think I'm okay with that for now.
What the hell is that about, right?
It is not the time or the place.
It's fucking ridiculous.
I can't get it out of my head.
It's an earworm.
A what?
An earworm.
It's when you can't get
a song out of your head.
An earworm?
I like that.
I can't help you like this.
And I get it, I do. This is all scary.
And... confusing.
And Maggie's right to
be worried about her son.
But if you don't cut me loose right now,
things are gonna get...
I, I saw Maggie on the way to the clinic.
- So...
- She'll be back. The kids?
They're not in the
house, I can't find them.
Maybe they heard us and got scared.
W-Went to hide in the woods?
You wanna go?
You go.
We have to watch him.
Okay...
Yell, if... I will.
I will.
Shit.
Shit...
Whoa. Hey, hey, hey.
You're up.
Yeah, I don't wanna miss the fun.
Anybody find a way out of this mess?
It's... It's... There's
just somebody... He's...
Sorry... Take... take it easy.
Hey.
It's just... I thought he was...
It's Arlo and the kids and...
Just tell me what's going on.
We need to... I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry...
- It's okay. It's okay.
You don't have to. You
don't have to. It's okay.
It feels like everything all at once, yeah?
Yeah, c-Claire had 'em too.
Claire had 'em too.
It feels uncontrollable... But it's not.
You got this.
Just breathe.
Breathe.
Arlo, come on. Hurry up. Come on.
Stop.
- No.
- What?
No!
Yeah.
No.
Hey, don't. That... that line...
- Let go!
- Stop! Stop! Stop!
- No!
Shit... shit... no.
What... what do we do?
We help him.
It's okay, it's okay. Here.
Here, let me help you.
Man.
Nicholas, give me that.
All right, this is gonna hurt.
I... I'm sorry. I'm really
he's... he's assassin, right?
I know you.
You...
You're...
It's you.
Yes.
You were that woman.
Now I am here.
Now I am Arlo.
And you are mcnab.
I am.
I was trying to help you.
Almost got you to the car.
We were almost safe.
But then you ran.
I lost you.
But god damn it, I found you again.
Yes.
Yes, you did.
What's wrong with your hands?
Nothing, they just shake.
I think you're worried
Maggie might have lost it.
I think I'm worried we
all might have lost it.
Could you...
Could you just come get this blood off?
It's getting in my eye.
It burns.
Please. What am I gonna do?
I can barely move.
Not even barely.
Don't do anything.
I won't.
What are you...
That's better.
Where's mcnab?
Where's Travis? What
happened to Travis?
He's...
Who... Who are you?
What's happening?
Fuck.
There we go.
A conundrum.
That's what this is.
'Cause I don't know if you're here to
help me or finish the job, you know?
What...?
Basically, I'm gonna need you
to give me one really good reason
why I shouldn't finish this cigarette
and shoot you in the fuckin' head.