NARRATOR:
Previously on Prison Break:
This is an overview.
Just the beginning of what’s on here.
You honor your side of the agreement,
I will do the unveiling tomorrow.
-I thought we were with these people.
LINCOLN: So did I.
We almost got our asses handed to us
getting these.
These things are for tomorrow.
I want Scylla today!
Vincent Sandinsky?
-Yes?
-Let's go.
-Uhn!
MICHAEL: What are you gonna do?
-I warned you not to come, Michael.
-It's not over. Not by a long shot.
Christina Rose Scofield.
-That name mean anything to you?
SANDINSKY: No.
Yes?
How badly do you want him, Mom?
Michael, listen to me.
That's not an answer.
I'll be in touch.
I got the ass-kicking of a lifetime
and you come back empty-handed?
-What?
-Linc and Michael's mother.
She's got Scylla here in Miami.
Fuel the jet.
We're going to Miami.
MAHONE: The guy knows something.
-Hey.
I don't know what else I can do
to help you guys.
Please, let me go.
I won't say a word to anyone.
LINCOLN:
Never heard of Christina Scofield?
SANDINSKY:
I told you, no.
-Never?
-Never.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
Yeah?
MICHAEL:
That guy you picked up at the airport.
There's something you should know.
LINCOLN: What do you mean?
-He's not some innocent victim, Linc.
He and Christina have been exchanging
e-mails, phone calls, you name it.
They got some kind of plan.
I just...
-...haven't figured it out yet.
-Thanks.
So, what are you gonna do
with him, Linc?
Leave town, Michael.
Linc?
-Where's Scylla?
-No.
Where's Scylla?
-You ready?
-Almost.
-Is that Sandinsky's phone?
-Yeah.
-Good luck.
-Thanks. I may need it.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
It's Michael again,
on Sandinsky's phone.
-I thought he turned it off.
-Well, now it's on. Track it.
Michael?
Hello, Christina.
I hope you're ready to talk.
Let's start with Vincent Sandinsky.
Vincent Sandinsky, the scientist?
Yeah, he's an old friend of mine.
A bit of a bore, don't you think?
But who cares about him?
I'd rather talk about you.
I'd rather meet you face-to-face.
Unless you're bringing me Scylla,
I'm not interested.
[TYPING]
MICHAEL:
No Scylla, no meeting.
That's all I can offer.
What do you hope to accomplish?
I need your answer in 10 minutes,
and that's the last time I'm calling back.
DOWNEY:
And, found him.
He's in an industrial park in El Portal,
right up the coast.
Good. Let's go.
-Uhn!
-You're lying. You're lying.
-I don't work for the Company.
-Six words that never prove true.
Come on, man!
This is over. Look around.
-What are you doing?
SANDINSKY: I don't know anything.
I don't know. I am here for a conference.
I don't know who told you otherwise.
I do. And Michael's also full of crap.
He's got no reason to lie.
He does. He might be leading us
off the scent so he--
He doesn't want Christina
to have Scylla.
It's not the first time he's lied to us.
Where is it?
[GUN COCKS]
SANDINSKY: No.
-Linc.
Come on, Linc.
He can't talk if he's dead.
You got three seconds.
-No!
KRANTZ: Burrows!
Put the gun down.
Vincent and I need to talk.
Vincent? Yeah.
Yeah.
We had a deal.
New deal.
I'm taking charge.
Vincent and I are old friends.
Where'd you find him?
At an airstrip.
He's got something to do with Scylla.
KRANTZ:
Good.
Then you can help me find it,
can't you, Vincent?
And you can help me find
Christina Scofield.
Dr. Sandinsky's been
a Company operative since--
How long's it been, Vincent?
Twenty-one years.
KRANTZ:
Twenty-one years of service.
Scientist, statistician,
expert field combatant.
What brought you to Miami?
[SCREAMS, GROANS]
Does that help?
She invited me, okay? She invited me.
-Who?
-Christina Scofield.
-I'm working with her.
-That brings you full circle, doesn't it?
But you knew that already.
When were you planning on telling me
that your mother was behind all this?
We just found out.
But bottom line is, you knew.
All of you!
On your knees.
You heard him. Get down.
KRANTZ:
Oh, not you.
I don't need to make deals with men
who can't do their jobs.
If Bagwell is the only one
who's competent here...
LINCOLN: What?
-...he'll do it alone.
Who do you think found this guy?
-Where's Scylla?
-I don't know. I don't.
She doesn't tell me where she keeps it.
But I do know where she's staying.
A place called Edgewater Tower,
room 1099.
You have today.
One day.
KRANTZ:
You're wasting time, Burrows.
One day.
[SIGHS]
You tipped him off.
Wow.
Oh.
KRANTZ:
No, Bagwell.
You stay here.
MAHONE:
Yeah, Theodore.
He needs you.
But you better stay away from us.
[DOOR CLOSES]
MAN: This is where Michael's signal
was coming from.
DOWNEY: Perfect.
CHRISTINA: Be careful.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Stay here.
Check it out.
[EXHALES]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
Let's go. Let's go.
He's leaving.
-Come on, he can't be that far away.
-Let's go.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[COUGHING]
Out.
[TIRES SCREECH]
[COUGHING CONTINUES]
All right, let's go.
[EXHALES]
MICHAEL:
All right.
Where is it?
You don't really expect me
to answer that, do you?
Actually, I do.
Because your life depends on it.
And considering your track record,
I think it's safe to assume...
...that you're always looking out
for number one.
I've waited 25 years for this moment,
Michael.
There's no way I can say
everything I wanna say.
-Why should I let you?
-Because I'm your mother.
That's something you can't change.
Something you can't take away.
It's nice to meet you, Sara.
In some ways,
Michael's done very well for himself.
In other ways, I'm not so sure.
Lincoln's led you down a dark path.
MICHAEL:
I make my own decisions.
You break Lincoln out of prison
and he goes to work for Krantz.
And he has his reasons.
But if you're looking for some kind
of common ground between us...
...maybe that's it.
I don't wanna see Lincoln working
for the Company either.
At least you've stopped making excuses
for him.
I stopped making judgments.
Something I couldn't afford.
But that was a long time ago,
and that's not why we're here.
No.
You're right.
None of us wants to see Scylla
go back to the Company.
So if we can put the past behind us...
...maybe we can work something out.
-Like what?
-Like a deal.
A deal.
All right. You tell me where Scylla is
and we'll work out the details later.
We'll go fifty-fifty.
-A mother-son operation?
-Maybe.
But first, Scylla.
Please, Michael, I know better.
We're very similar.
I know what it's like
to look at the big picture...
...see all the little moving parts.
How much easier it is to think
after the surgery.
I know you.
That's why you'll never be able to
manipulate me like you do the rest.
You're running out of time.
All right, there's no one back here.
They were here. But there's nobody
here now, because that's what happens.
You know, this whole thing...
...it's just....
It's just crap, is just what it is.
We're always one move behind,
every step of the way.
And it's gonna get worse now that
Bagwell is breathing down our back.
How do you make
that kind of mistake?
And let that inbred
get anywhere near us?
No, the first mistake was working
for Krantz. That was the first mistake.
What do you think's gonna happen
now he has his goons calling the shots?
What's gonna happen now?
MAHONE:
I should have known better.
That they'd get anywhere near this.
You know what?
We should go. Let's go.
No, we can't go.
You saw the photos, right?
You saw the photos.
You know what he's gonna do.
We should have known
what he was gonna do with them.
-That's what we should have--
-Hey. Just calm down.
You know what? The deal is over.
You know it. I know it.
Everybody knows it.
We're not getting out.
We're gonna take a walk to the gallows
or somebody else is gonna stab us.
I did that walk and I survived.
Even if we win, do we win?
-You don't believe that.
-I'm gonna do what I gotta do.
If you don't wanna roll with me,
that's fine.
MAHONE: What is that?
-Rental receipt. Silver minivan.
What is this?
[GRUNTING]
KRANTZ:
What do you know about this?
We found a whole box of them
down in Little Cuba. Guns too.
What do you know about this?
She wanted me to speak there.
KRANTZ:
About Scylla.
She said she'd give me a script
beforehand, that's all I know.
She said her interest
was purely scientific.
Her interest was financial.
She came to me about a year ago
with an idea.
Rather than build our organization with
Scylla as the permanent cornerstone...
...she wanted to use the technology
to make a quick profit.
If certain events occurred...
...various nations
might feel the need...
...for a more modern defense system.
And they'd come to us
for the answers.
Solar weaponry.
Water desalinization.
Now, what do you know
about all this?
I told you all I know.
KRANTZ:
Well, I thought it was a crazy idea.
Plan of an amateur.
But I figured she'd be angry.
She wasn't allowed to hold a card.
-Yeah. I had no idea--
-Now, what was that?
I think it's more than that.
Really?
What did she tell you?
I know how the Company operates.
Shell corporations like EcoField,
rampant misuse of funds.
You're literally sitting on a gold mine.
But your leadership only benefits you
and your friends...
...10 generations in the future.
Then you would like to see
the Company implode.
I wanna see something happen.
You think too small.
[CHUCKLES]
Laos? We'll all be dead
before that pays off.
Laos, sir?
Don't trouble yourself.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
-Burrows?
-I got a question for your friend.
What is it?
Ask him what the letters "DMB" mean.
Do the letters "DMB"
mean anything to you?
[GRUNTS]
I'm sorry.
I thought you understood me.
[GRUNTS THEN COUGHS]
She said her place is on the same block
as Dade-Miami Bank.
-Did you hear that?
-Got it. He better be telling the truth.
See what else the doctor knows.
SANDINSKY: No.
MAN: What's Christina's plan?
[PUNCH LANDS,
SANDINSKY GRUNTS]
I don't know.
I don't know. Maybe we should have--
Maybe we should have followed her
or something.
Sit down for me.
Please.
How about I talk to her?
I might have some perspective.
She didn't leave me when I was 6.
Okay.
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
I'm sorry we had to meet this way,
Sara.
I'm sorry we had to meet at all.
Michael's been through a lot.
At some point it's gonna be too much.
Michael can handle it.
He's never known a life without change.
-Well, you say that like you know him.
-Oh, I do.
Better than you.
I don't see how that's possible.
Well, you will when your child's born.
See, I wasn't sure at first,
but you do have that drawn look.
And I see the way you protect yourself
when you sense danger.
You don't even know you're doing it.
It's instinct.
And what is it you know
about maternal instinct?
I've tried to be a mother.
-Even to Lincoln.
-How can you say that?
You left them...
...without so much as an explanation.
-But if Michael would listen--
-You know what? You can stop.
You can’t justify what you did.
Michael doesn't know you're pregnant,
does he?
[DOOR OPENS]
What happened?
Uh.... I got nothing.
SELF: Hello, Joyce.
-Hi.
How are you? My name is Don Self.
Homeland Security.
Don't worry.
There's nothing the matter.
I'm just doing a favor for my friend.
His mother passed away yesterday.
Her last will and testament
is in one of your security boxes.
It's actually Box 6468.
JOYCE:
Is he authorized to access it?
SELF: That's the problem. He's not.
We're willing to fill the paperwork--
Only authorized individuals
are allowed to access safety box--
Listen, I need to get in that box.
Where's your boss?
-Sir. Sir, can I help you?
-I need to get in my mom's deposit box.
-Do you have a court order? DMB policy--
SELF: Here's the policy.
Okay, I need to open Box 6468 now.
Name's Don Self, Homeland Security.
Excuse me, Mr. Frank. Number 6468
was accessed a minute ago.
He just left.
It was the guy with the silver suitcase.
There he is.
Hey, that looks like the guy
from the embassy.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
-Mr. Banerjee, how are you?
-I'm trying to reach Christina Hampton.
She's in a meeting right now.
If I don't talk to her before 5...
...the deal is off.
[CUTS TAPE]
Okay.
This is my final offer.
You're gonna take me to Scylla,
and then you can walk.
No questions.
No one tells the general.
You can live the rest of your life like this
never happened, but Scylla is mine.
Lincoln would never let that happen.
He doesn't have to know.
Even as children you couldn't agree.
You fought about everything.
The two of you
couldn't be more different.
But you know that, don't you,
Michael?
This isn't about Lincoln.
You have blue eyes, he has green.
He played with trucks,
you took apart the television set.
And I don't need to point out
the difference in IQ or temperament.
You know what I'm getting at,
don't you, Michael?
I don't have any idea
what you're talking about.
You've always known it
deep in your heart.
You just had no one to confirm it.
Lincoln...
...isn't your brother.
It's true.
I should have told you before...
...but you always looked up to him...
...and I had no idea
things would happen like this.
You don't know what you're saying.
Have you ever seen
pictures of Lincoln as a baby?
-Yes.
-No.
There aren't any.
Your father didn't adopt him
until he was 3 years old.
His parents worked for the Company.
They were killed in an explosion
in Manila.
Aldo brought him home the next day.
He felt it was his duty.
He didn't ask me how I felt.
I never bonded with him
like mother and son.
He was always so angry.
Understandably so.
He was too young
to remember his mother...
...but he always knew
something was missing.
I can't believe you're playing this card.
I'm sorry, Michael.
But I felt differently about you.
And you could tell.
That's why you always felt guilty.
Why you were always throwing yourself
over the cliff...
...after Lincoln was already dead
at the bottom.
It's why you went to prison
and pissed your life away.
You don't know
why I did the things I did!
You weren't there!
Who knows what
you could have accomplished.
But you always felt like you had
to make less of yourself...
...to make Lincoln look less pathetic
in comparison.
Lincoln was more of a brother to me
than you were ever a mother.
You left.
He stayed.
He fed me.
Kept me off the streets.
Put me through school.
How?
By getting in trouble over and over again,
just like he is right now.
What do you mean, right now?
Where is he?
He's out looking for Scylla,
and he's not going to find it.
Maybe you should call him
and tell him.
Unless there's too much bad blood
between you.
Or no blood.
[LINE RINGING]
[HORN HONKING, TIRES SQUEALING]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
MAHONE:
Watch the guy in our lane.
Is it Michael?
It's gonna be all right. Just relax.
Where is he?
SELF:
All right, keep up with him, come on.
I am, just shut up.
It's not that I don't wanna help you...
...it's just that I hate to see you
go running after him again.
MICHAEL: Come here!
-Michael, stop it!
-Michael. Stop.
-Where is he?
Aah!
Okay, you wanna go
running after him?
Flush your life down the toilet
once and for all? Go ahead.
MICHAEL:
Where is he?
If you don't tell me where he is,
I'll kill you myself.
-I'll kill you myself.
-Michael!
Michael. Michael.
-Come on. Come here.
-Aah!
Where is he? Where is he?
Where is he?
-Where's Lincoln?
-All right. Fine.
There's an energy conference
at the Panda Bay Hotel in about an hour.
He'll be there.
That's the truth.
[PANTING]
[SIGHS]
I'm sorry.
-I don't know what to think.
-Go. Go, go, go. Go find him.
-I got her. Go.
-If she gives you any trouble....
-If she gives you any trouble--
-I know. Just go.
[PANTING]
You have surpassed expectations,
Bagwell.
You're much more than an informant.
I multitask.
Well, if things go
as well as expected here...
...you'll be rewarded accordingly.
As a special liaison to the Company?
Yes.
What exactly does that entail?
Well, that would be up to you.
Most Company operatives
choose their own career path.
Though I can't say
what would suit you.
What do sexual predators
from Alabama typically do?
Aside from the obvious.
Those days are behind me, general.
What I lack in formal education...
...I more than make up for
in natural skills...
...and curiosity.
And as you've seen,
my loyalty knows no bounds.
Then you shouldn't have any difficulty
passing your final exam.
Now, you didn't expect
that a few phone calls on the sly...
...would set you up for life, did you?
No, sir.
I'm ready for anything.
Good. Then prepare for this:
When Burrows bring Scylla
back to us...
...I will fly it safely back
to Los Angeles...
...and you will be the one
to put a bullet in his brain.
CHRISTINA:
Sara?
SARA: What's going on in there?
-Sara.
What do you want?
Oh, please keep that open.
Why?
So you can lob more accusations
and assumptions out at me?
I haven't made any.
Lincoln is adopted.
And you're pregnant.
You don't deny it, do you?
You should tell him.
He'd be happy
even under the circumstances.
-Really isn't any of your business.
-I'm sorry.
Sometimes in-laws overstep
their bounds, but--
When it comes right down to it...
...I am the only mother
any of you will ever have...
...so you shouldn't throw that away
so easily.
The only thing I get from you...
...is a great example of the mother
I don't wanna be.
Sara.
-It doesn't have to be like this.
-Yeah, it does.
And that was your decision
a long time ago.
Sara, can I just give you
one piece of advice?
Stay out of the bars.
-That's good advice.
-I have friends in A.A.
They're only alcoholics.
I can only imagine what it's like for you
trying to stay off the smack.
It's morphine.
Hospital-grade morphine.
Christina Scofield
will not be leaving Miami tonight.
I want eyes at every airport and gas
station between here and Atlanta.
And I want the names of everyone
attending that conference.
I thought you might be asking
that question, so I called the hotel.
Said I was from the newspaper.
Excuse the spelling.
-These are all scientists?
-I told you.
Those are speakers.
Names below are special guests.
Sounded like bigwigs
from all over the world.
Frederich, Carlotto, Linarte...
...Banerjee?
-Naveen Banerjee?
-Who is that?
The son
of Prime Minister Nandu Banerjee.
He has a known interest
in solar weapons technology.
This will all be over
by the end of the day.
Come on, Linc, where are you?
[RINGING]
LINCOLN [ON RECORDING]:
It's Linc. You know what to do.
Linc, it's me. Call me when you can.
We gotta talk.
[TIRES SQUEALING]
Mahone!
This way!
[PANTING]
[THUD]
Christina.
Don't move...
...or I'll kill you both.
Where is he?
Where did he go?
-There. Right there. Right there.
SELF: Where is he?
MAHONE: Linc, stop.
LINCOLN: What?
Wait. Wait.
That's the hotel.
The energy conference.
That's right. It's today.
Silver van. The rental van.
They want us here. Something's up.
What the hell is going on?
[DIALING]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Downey?
It's for a getaway.
Linc, no!
-Where are you?
-Running. Burrows is on my ass.
Are you okay?
I was worried you didn't get away.
This whole thing can go to hell.
I'm fine. I'm right on time.
See you soon.
Down.
Good girl.
He'll never forgive you for this,
and neither will his brother.
CHRISTINA:
Soon this will all be behind us.
[COCKS GUN]
[TAPE RIPS OFF]
Maybe I can meet
my grandson one day.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
[SPEAKS IN HINDI]
My apologies, Naveen.
Where have you been?
I was told that you would call.
I got hung up on a few details
for this evening.
You spoke with Downey?
It did very little to reassure me.
I need to speak to Dr. Sandinsky.
Oh, you haven't heard.
Dr. Sandinsky had a family emergency.
His wife was in a terrible accident.
I spoke with him this morning.
He took a private jet out this afternoon.
It's very late to be making
these decisions now.
Yes, but you've come all this way.
You are prepared to give your speech,
aren't you?
Fine.
But in light of the fact
that I did not speak with the doctor...
...I'll amend my offer.
One million dollars
in exploratory research.
The rest will follow
in the weeks to come.
That's very generous, Naveen.
History will thank you.
Your country will thank you.
See you soon.
May I have your attention, please?
We're about to begin. Thank you.
Welcome to Miami Beach.
And thank you for attending
the first global conference of its kind...
...where great minds will meet
to explore our energy future.
The importance of finding new ways
to power our world...
...should not be underestimated.
MAHONE:
It's running.
Rented this in Linc's name.
Okay, look at this.
-These passports. It's us.
-It's a setup.
-For what?
Okay, thank you.
[FOOTSTEPS]
It's 5:00.
If Burrows doesn't call in five minutes,
you're going downtown.
TV ANNOUNCER: An international
competition awarded the summit...
MAN: General, you should see this.
-...to the city of Miami.
Today, the venue will be
the Panda Bay Hotel...
...where security has been tightened
for the arrival of important guests.
This includes Naveen Banerjee,
son of Prime Minister Nandu Banerjee...
...who is scheduled to be the event's
keynote speaker.
Banerjee's fragile political position...
...may leave him vulnerable
to criticism on the world stage.
He has aggressively sought
to place his ideas--
Christina's plan.
What she needed to profit from Scylla.
An incident that'll domino
into global warfare.
--expanding the search for new forms
of greener energy...
...and how these ideas
can be implemented.
SANDINSKY:
Krantz.
You're out. It's over now.
--new energy contracts.
The pressure of increasing competition
has caused some tension--
No.
Policy makers have resolved
to consider any energy policy...
...that is both proven--
You do it.
Do it!
[GUNSHOT]
[SANDINSKY FALLS]
-Hey! You need a pass!
MAN: At this point in our history...
...solar power accounts
for less than one-tenth of 1 percent...
...of the total power
generated in our world.
And in the next 10 years, that number
should increase to 10 percent.
But it's still not enough.
We must strive to seek
new alternatives...
...so that we can break the cycle
of oil dependence.
We cannot do that without your help.
So that's why we're here today.
To explore our new energy future
and envision a new tomorrow.
Now, our first guest
is an author and an entrepreneur...
...as well as having a notable heritage.
He has spoken to audiences
across the world.
Please welcome Naveen Banerjee.
Thank you. Thank you.
Good evening, my friends.
It is my pleasure
to be here with you today...
...in this beautiful city of sunlight.
Throughout the United States...
...I find there to be great interest...
...in the changing ways
that we all power our world.
Many times I have--
No!
--proposed to reinvent the wheel.
New resources--
[CROWD SCREAMING]
LINCOLN:
No.
Michael!
Linc, we gotta go.
She set the whole thing up.
-Do you have it?
-Right here.
-How'd it go?
-The van was there with the passports.
Got off the phone with our contact
at the bank.
And they've got clean video of Burrows
trying to access the box.
They must have trashed
the hotel room.
His hands were all over the shells.
Did you see Michael?
He was there on my way out.
Lincoln's right back where he started.
It really is too bad about Michael.
I know you--
Shut up and drive.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[AGITATED CHATTERING]
[ENGLISH SDH]