NARRATOR:
Previously on Prison Break:
It was a meeting between
all cardholders.
Now we know
who has the other five cards.
Your nose is bleeding.
-I'm Cole Pfeiffer.
-Welcome to Los Angeles.
MICHAEL:
His name is Theodore Bagwell.
He was with us in Panama.
Now he's here in Los Angeles.
And he has a book
that used to belong to Whistler.
Mahone thinks this book
has a plan for the break-in.
Cole Pfeiffer did not arrive
for our meeting.
You don't have Scylla?
[GRUNTS]
WYATT: It seems your friend Whistler
wasn't the only one looking into Scylla.
-Do you know anything about that?
-No.
I'm looking for the man
who killed my son.
This man is a professional assassin.
He's African-American, 6-foot-4,
about 220 pounds.
MICHAEL: We refined the images
the best we could...
...but we need your specialist to sharpen
the video so we can ID the rest of them.
All right, I'll see what I can do. I've seen
what those tech guys are capable of.
Sometimes it's....
Wait a sec. I know this guy.
This guy works in my building.
That's Griffin Oren.
MICHAEL: You know him?
-He's the head of Treasury's L.A. bureau.
If he's in your building,
you can get close to him.
-I need a reason.
-Make something up.
Something about al Qaeda
using, uh, stolen bearer bonds...
...to finance shady operations.
Whatever.
Making false claims
affecting government?
-That's up to five years in prison.
-Welcome to the club, Agent Self.
MAHONE:
Thanks for meeting me.
I would have come up to see you,
but I can't--
I'm sorry.
But you said that you had some pictures
to show me.
[WHIMPERS]
That's him.
I'll get in touch with you
as soon as....
Soon as I....
You didn't do this.
In your heart,
you are a really good man.
That's why I married you.
That's why I started a family
with you.
[SHUDDERS]
When you used to bring
your files home...
...and I would beg you
to leave that stuff at work.
But when you have a monster
in your sights...
...you can't focus until you get him.
And I used to hate that about you.
Now it's the only thing
that lets me sleep, because I know...
...that you're gonna get him.
DRIVER:
What the hell are you doing?
[HORN HONKING]
MAN:
Move.
[PANTING]
BLAUNER: What are you doing?
BAGWELL: Hey, there, Blauner.
Heh. Just, uh, doing a little research.
-GATE-related?
-Adding a little flourish to my pitch.
Like the caged macaw
who cannot spread her wings--
BLAUNER:
Well, you know, Cole...
...I was thinking maybe you should
spend less time practicing...
...and a little more time
actually pitching.
I mean, number-one salesman
in the world?
We're just waiting with bated breath
to see what you can do around here.
Ouch.
[CLEARS THROAT]
SUCRE:
I just saw him right here.
-Hey.
-You haven't seen Sara, have you?
-No.
Look, you wanna end up
back in Fox River, just go right ahead.
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
Hey, what's going on?
-He wants to look for T-Bag.
-We know he's got the bird book.
The bird book's got the plan
for the break-in.
And we saw that snake
right here today.
It ain't safe
for a member of the Fox River Eight...
...to be looking for another member
of the Fox River Eight.
Yes, but....
Bellick, go with Sucre. Canvas the area.
See if you can get a lead on him.
There are six buildings there.
He could be in any one.
That's why it's called canvassing.
You do realize
this is the Treasury Department, right?
Tell Self to go down a few floors,
walk past the right computers...
-...and we are billionaires.
-Just the card, please.
Don Self, Homeland Security.
-I need to see Mr. Oren.
-Not available.
I need to see him right away. Hundreds
of Americans will be in jeopardy.
-Don Self, Homeland Security.
-Talk to Angela down the hall.
Sorry to barge in, but this is urgent.
I'm sure it is.
Talk to Angela down the hall.
We are hearing chatter
about stolen bearer bonds.
-We have reason to believe al Qaeda--
-Do you have serial numbers?
No, I do not.
-Mind turning around?
-Not at all.
OREN:
I leave for Asia in six hours.
He's got it.
OREN: Until then, I've got meetings
with the bureau chiefs...
...of the FBI, the CIA,
and Homeland Security.
It's gone.
OREN: If what you have
to tell me is important...
...I'll hear about it from your boss.
Until then,
talk to Angela down the hall.
If you set foot in my office again
without my prior consent...
...I'll see to it you spend the rest of your
career running border security in Alaska.
-Did we get it?
MICHAEL: What happened?
What do you mean?
We had it for two seconds
and then it disappeared.
It's in the safe.
He has this safe in his office.
That must be blocking the transmission.
That's where he keeps the card.
-We need to get into that safe.
-Trust me, there's no way.
I'll have the enhanced images of the
other cardholders. We'll go from there.
Now, you can access
the building's blueprints, right?
I can't go back up there.
-We'll take care of that.
-You'll never get past the front door.
Even if they don't recognize you,
you need a security card--
Just get the blueprints
and get back here, all right?
Yeah.
-Sara, what happened?
-I'm fine, but someone was following me.
I lost him a mile back.
I don't think he could have followed me.
-I made sure of that.
-What'd he look like?
-Uh, tall, black, he had a beard.
-Is this the guy?
Yeah.
MICHAEL:
Who's that?
That's the man who killed my son.
Now he's coming to kill us.
MAHONE: Where were you
the first time that you saw him?
-The very first time.
-Walking home.
He didn't just run into you
on the street.
Where were you before that?
-The Towne Lounge.
-Is that a bar?
You have a problem with that?
No. I just wanna know
how long you were there.
Sara, I need to find this guy
and I can't do it without your help.
I don't care why or what you were doing
in the bar. I just wanna know how long--
-Okay, a couple hours.
-Thank you.
So something
must have tipped him off.
-You paid cash, right?
-Of course.
But the credit card
that Bruce gave me is gone.
What credit card?
These are the security checkpoints.
You can't get past one of those
unless you have one of these.
Any way we can forge it?
Sure, if you have two weeks and access
to the building's mainframe, maybe.
It doesn't look there are any security
checkpoints on the 10th floor.
No, just at all the access points
to the 10th floor.
But if you could somehow magically
appear in the hallway, you'd be fine...
...except for all the government officials
who'd arrest you in a heartbeat.
If you get us into the parking structure,
will security check our van?
Sure, transporting known felons.
Why not?
The parking structure.
Then this is our point of entry.
We need the details of the safe.
Okay, the, um--
The safe has an insignia on it...
...that looks something like this.
MAN:
You're gonna need some of this.
I got a positive ID of Sara Tancredi
in Los Angeles.
That means Michael Scofield is here.
That means Lincoln Burrows is here.
Why?
Sara, huh?
She's a slippery little bitch, isn't she?
Time is not on your side, Gretchen.
Maybe you hadn't noticed...
...but since you seem to be somewhat
immune to physical coercion...
...we've decided to move on.
The nose is an evolutionary marvel.
Our brain has been constructed
so that certain aromas...
...coffee beans, blueberries...
...that are helpful to our body,
we perceive as pleasant.
Whereas other smells
that signify death, disease....
[COUGHING]
Initial symptoms include nausea,
dizziness, burning eyes.
All of which
you are experiencing right now.
Prolonged exposure
will lead to faintness...
...rapid degradation
of your mental faculties.
Tell me.
I don't know anything.
You've got one more day.
MICHAEL:
Top of the line.
It's a biometric design,
and only Oren's fingerprint will open it.
So we, uh, lift his prints
off something he touched.
The pad knows
what human skin feels like.
If we trick it, we'll set off the alarm.
And then there's the 12-digit key code.
-What about the hinges?
-Wired to the alarm.
We drill it.
MICHAEL: Through the outer
layer of steel, maybe.
But the bones of this thing are
three-quarter-inch cobalt-alloy hard plate.
Drilling's not gonna work,
not in our time frame.
Basically we have a way
to get you into the garage...
...which in case you forgot,
puts me on the hook for other charges.
But no way
to get you up to the 10th floor.
But let's say you do
get to the 10th floor.
Then we need to get you
into Oren's office for an hour.
Then we need to hope
that not one of Oren's coworkers...
...is gonna hear the loud drill
you're gonna be using...
...to break into a safe that
I'm telling you cannot be broken into.
You understand? There are
Homeland agents whose sole job...
...is to design safety measures
to make this structure impregnable.
Yeah. They had those guys
at Fox River too.
-Whose office is this?
SELF: Sam Middleton...
...Department of Justice.
This wall separates Middleton from Oren.
I'm gonna need some supplies.
The credit card was used at the bar
at 10:32.
-What time did you see him?
-Uh, about 11:00.
And how long were you walking
at that time?
Ten-, 15 minutes.
Let's assume that he was at his place
when he received the call.
That's an 18-minute drive from
the Towne Lounge bar in San Pedro.
Averaging 30 miles an hour
the whole way, that's a--
That's a nine-mile radius.
He's gonna be somewhere
around that circle.
He's gotta be mobile.
Within a half mile of a major freeway.
The 10, the 110, the 405.
SARA: No permanent address,
so we're looking for hotels.
But nowhere you need to valet your car.
Gotta be readily accessible at all times.
Somewhere you don't need a credit card
down for incidentals. Got that?
I'll see what I can do.
Hurry.
Trishanne, I'm gonna need a mug of tea
with lemon.
Uh, I'm sorry, Cole.
I can't leave the desk right now.
Good help is so hard to find.
TRISHANNE: May I help you?
-We're with Upper Valley Insurance.
And this man just came into
a $100,000 inheritance.
We can't track him down, so we're
offering 10 percent finder's fees...
...to anyone who can point us
in his direction.
-Oh, my gosh. What, $10,000?
-Yeah.
Mm.
I'm sorry, I don't recognize him.
Okay, so if you do see him,
would you please give us a call?
Thank you.
-GATE?
-Greatness Achieved Through Excellence.
SELF:
A toy? You wanna try to explain this?
Mix aluminum powder with iron oxide,
add a little heat.
[PHONE RINGING]
Hey.
Yeah, well,
thanks for calling me back, Sam.
[VACUUM RUNNING]
Yeah, I know you have
these trial dates coming up...
...and we just wanna make sure you have
everything to convict these bastards.
Okay. That's terrific.
All right, I'll see you then.
All right. We're gonna have lunch.
I'll keep him out of his office
for as long as I can.
Good luck.
All right.
SUCRE [OVER PHONE]: Hello?
-Hey, any sign of him?
No, we checked about 10 buildings,
but nothing so far.
MICHAEL:
Scrap it. We're going after the next card.
Meet me on the corner of Santa Monica
and Century West.
[VACUUM RUNNING]
SELF: Hey, Charlie.
-Yankees lost again last night.
At least our fans show up
before the fifth inning, right?
-Have a good day, all right, Charlie?
-You too, Mr. Self.
I'm letting you guys know right now,
you get busted, don't mention my name.
We're ready.
MICHAEL:
Now.
One, two, three, up.
TRISHANNE:
So...
...a couple of scruffy guys walk in...
...tell me they're from
the insurance company...
...and they offer me $10,000
if I know where you are.
Something tells me there's a better offer
on the table.
Well, I'll be, Trishanne.
You just caught yourself a leprechaun.
And as the legend goes,
you got yourself one wish.
-Anything in the world.
-Oh, really?
-And I am bound to grant it.
-Yeah?
Well, your commencement check is
sitting on my desk waiting to be signed.
That's a pretty nice pot of gold.
Before you say another word...
...now it's true, leprechauns
cannot refuse their captor's demands.
But if they deem her to be greedy
or covetous...
...whatever she desires will certainly be
accompanied with disastrous tidings.
Or so the legend goes.
Three percent of your commission
from here on out.
Done.
Don Self to see you.
You can go right on in.
-All right, thank you. Have a great day.
-You too.
Hey. Hey, Sam.
-Great to meet you.
-Same here.
Thanks again for squeezing me in
on such short notice.
I figure we had so much to get through
that this would be the best way.
-I thought we were going out for lunch.
-Is there a problem?
Well, actually, I'm a vegetarian.
It's a new diet. But there's a great place
down the street, and it'll be my treat.
-Elise?
ELISE [OVER INTERCOM]: Yes, sir?
I'm heading out for lunch.
Hold it there.
Sorry, I was just coming in to--
There's no more tp in the ladies' room.
-We'll get right on that.
-How about you get it right now?
Best we got in here.
You guys
need to get better organized.
Fifty-three hotels
matched the search criteria.
You know, I read this article
a little while ago, right...
...about the whole, uh, nature
versus nurture thing, and it turns out...
...it's all kind of a mismatch
because DNA trumps everything.
And I believe it, because,
I mean, I grew up in the same house...
...went to the same school as my
brother, who's a math professor.
My sister's a pediatrician...
...and I'm a thief who blows his money
on hookers and coke.
So like the same way Scofield's
hardwired to be a genius...
...and you were always
gonna be a lawman, right?
Whoever this guy is...
...you think he wanted to grow up
to be a murderer? Probably not.
Be very careful choosing the next words
that come out of your mouth.
I-- I'm just saying...
...we are who we are.
SUCRE:
Oh, man.
Jake, I'm gonna need you
in front of Room 1018, now.
-What's going on?
SUCRE: I apologize...
...but we're gonna be in your way
for the next 90 minutes or so.
-Black?
-Yep.
Excuse me, ma'am,
but where can I plug in?
For now, you can go in there.
But when my boss gets back
from lunch, you're gonna--
[VACUUM RUNNING]
MICHAEL: The safe should be
somewhere behind this wall.
[BEEPING]
[VACUUM RUNNING LOUDLY]
As soon as you're through the steel
I'll have the thermite ready.
[SIGHS]
-What is it?
-How long has it been happening?
-It's not a big deal.
-It was a big deal when you were 13.
-Promise me you won't tell Sara.
-Sara can help.
Look, I'm acclimating
to the warmer climate, all right?
Come on, we've got work to do.
Let's go.
ROLAND: I don't know
what this Company is up to...
...but it sure sounds like
there's a whole lot of money involved.
Yeah, I don't know.
Lisa Tabak just hopped a flight to Laos,
didn't she?
-Yeah, I guess.
-Griffin Oren just said...
...he was going somewhere in Asia.
-Down to the cobalt.
-All right.
-What can I get you?
-Just a moment of your time.
I'm a private investigator. I'm working
with a woman named Sara Tancredi.
-And she was recently a patron of yours.
-I don't wanna get involved.
She moved all the way across
the country to get away from this guy.
Help me find him before he finds her.
Last time Sara had a broken jaw.
I was standing by the front door
when he left.
A second later, I saw him
take something out of his car.
-Remember what the car looked like?
-Gray.
A sedan, sort of like one of those
rental cars, you know?
You need something?
Just a small...
...kindness.
That's the easiest 300
you'll ever make.
BELLICK:
Hey, hey, hey.
We're working here.
[VACUUM STOPS]
So am I.
There's a stack of letters
that I need to put in the mail.
The chemicals
don't react so good with leather.
-What are you using, lye?
-Wait, wait, wait.
Listen, we know this is a hassle.
We know we're disrupting your work
and giving you a headache.
We annoy a different person
every day.
But if this gets dirty while it's wet,
it's gonna leave a stain...
...and then we'll be back here
all over again.
Why don't you just tell me where
they are and I'll get them for you.
On the corner of his desk
near his computer.
-How much longer?
-Another couple minutes...
...and we'll be ready to copy.
[VACUUM RUNNING]
KRANTZ: Is Griffin in?
-He's in a meeting right now.
But I can pull him out if you like.
KRANTZ:
If you could.
Just have a seat in his office.
He'll be right with you.
All we need is one more.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Someone's in there.
If I can hear him,
he's gonna hear the drill.
We can do it manually.
-It won't generate enough heat.
-We're like a 16th of an inch away.
-Can I help you?
-I phoned earlier...
...about one of your guests.
-Gray sedan, right?
-Yeah, right.
Is that the guy?
Yeah, that's him.
-What room?
-He was in 130.
He checked out.
Did, uh....
Did he leave any clue
as to where he was going?
Do you mind if I look at the room?
Nineteen dollars an hour,
59 for the night.
Fine, whatever. Give me a key.
[PHONE RINGS]
Yes?
You wanted to know
if anyone came looking for you.
Did they?
[GUN COCKS]
No, I was just calling
to let you know...
...my shift was ending
and nobody showed up.
WYATT [OVER PHONE]:
All right. Thank you.
What do you say you give me that paper
in your hand. How's that sound, huh?
Sorry for keeping you.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
Just making sure you're ready
for your trip.
I better be.
I'm leaving in five minutes.
If we dial it down to the lowest setting,
that might work.
-You sure?
-We don't have a choice.
I'll tell you when.
The finance minister
is anxiously awaiting your arrival.
Well, if you recall, I successfully
negotiated financial policies...
...with the IMF and the World Bank.
Pretty sure I can handle Laos.
Now.
I'm well aware of your résumé, Griffin.
We got it.
LINCOLN [OVER PHONE]: We're in.
-Got it.
WOMAN [ON TV]: The runaway inflation
in Laos has given way to food riots...
...in the capital city of Vientiane, where
the death toll has risen to over 200.
KRANTZ:
Monetary policy is a means to an end.
OREN:
I'm aware of our final objective, general.
This is an important day for us.
I need to make sure
that everyone knows his role.
You could have told me all of this
on the telephone.
Why did you take today of all days
to come down and berate me in person?
Things happened in the past few days
that have made me somewhat uneasy.
Today we got confirmation
that one of our targets is in Los Angeles.
That on top of the fact
that one of Lisa's bodyguards was killed.
I thought that was because
she was married to that Turk.
-That's the official story.
-What is the problem?
Come on. Come on.
-Do you have your card on you, Griffin?
-Of course.
I'd like to see it.
-Where are we?
LINCOLN: Talk to me, Roland.
ROLAND:
Seventy-two percent.
OREN: I put it in my safe this morning.
-I'd like to see it.
Eighty-six. Eighty-seven.
ROLAND:
Ninety-two.
Fifteen years of working together,
you think you'd trust me.
Don't turn this into an opera.
Just hand me the card.
Come on. Come on.
-Happy?
-From now on...
...I'm asking that everyone keep
their card on them at all times.
Anyone makes a move,
anything goes missing, you call me.
-Did we get it?
ROLAND: One hundred.
Yeah.
-I don't know how you eat that crap.
-Yeah.
What was that called, tempeh?
You could barely choke it down.
-Yeah, well, it's an acquired taste.
-Excuse us.
Well, it looks like I should be getting
back to work. This was a pleasure.
SARA: Apparently billions in counterfeit
currency flooded the economy...
...which is what caused it all.
What I don't understand is why.
So far all the cardholders
have been experts in their fields.
In energy, in logistics, in finance.
I mean, it looks like they're just trying
to tear the country up.
So they can profit by rebuilding it.
So the question is, what's next?
I was at a bar earlier.
-Nothing happened, I didn't drink.
-If this is too much for you--
No, no.
-Say the word, we'll scrap the thing.
-It's not gonna happen again.
But it would be a lie
not to tell you...
...and I want you to know
that I'll never lie to you.
I'm sorry.
Somebody's here for you.
For me?
Cole Pfeiffer.
Is your name Xing?
Mr. Xing stayed behind in New York.
Well, have a seat then.
Uh, what can I help you with?
You were supposed to deliver the item
two days ago.
Where is it?
-Where's what?
-I've traveled a long way, Mr. Pfeiffer.
My patience is wearing thin.
Playing games is not going to be good
for either of us.
Scylla. Where is it?
-Mr. Pfeiffer--
-I'm at work.
It's not like I can talk freely.
Just tell me the latest.
The latest? If you deliver it to me
by the end of the day...
...I will pay you the sum
that we agreed upon.
As much as I'd like to tell you
that were possible--
Give it to me by tomorrow and
you will receive 50 percent of your fee.
Two days, 25 percent.
Three days,
I shoot you through the brain.
That is the latest.
No problem.
I thought that urine
might be getting a little stale...
...so I brought you some more.
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
SELF: Hey, the image enhancement
from the video came back.
-Did you get what I sent over?
-We got all three cardholders.
For the first two,
we have names, addresses...
...everything we need to grab them.
Sara.
But for the general, we got nothing.
This guy's a ghost.
You all right?
Look, most of what happened to me
in Panama is a total blank.
When I was being held, I could hear
Gretchen talking on the phone.
And she was taking orders
from the guy in charge...
...and she called him the general.
-In charge of the mission?
-No, I think in charge of the Company.
I told you...
...we should have killed Gretchen
when we had the chance.
She'll come home.
-She always has.
-You'd better be sure about that.
-Excuse me, sir.
KRANTZ: What?
Someone at Homeland Security
did an enhanced image search on you.
-We couldn't tell where the original--
-Who?
The guy who ordered it,
his name is Don Self.
[ENGLISH SDH]