NARRATOR:
Previously on Prison Break:
I'm giving you an opportunity
to avoid 15 years in jail.
-In exchange for?
-Scylla.
These are GPS ankle monitors.
I'm your boss.
And if I ask you to put on a monitor,
you put on the monitor.
MAHONE: Whistler's assignment was to
drop off Scylla to a Company executive.
And his job was to protect it.
When this is all done, you and me,
we're gonna settle up.
I'm looking for Alex.
CAMERON: Mom.
-We're done talking.
[GRUNTING]
OFFICER: Hey, hey. You don't wanna go
in there. You don't wanna go in there.
Where are Michael Scofield
and Lincoln Burrows?
I swear to you,
I have no idea where they are.
-What's wrong?
-Whatever it is, it ain't it.
If Scylla was like a pizza,
all we got is a slice.
So Scylla isn't one card. It's six.
-Hey. What did you pull us into?
SELF: Excuse me?
Figured you'd get us on the hook so we
could find out how screwed this was.
-What the hell are you talking about?
-The card, Agent Self.
-I'm talking about the card. It's useless.
-Wait, hold on. You already got the card?
Yes, but without the other five cards,
it means nothing.
And I can only assume you knew that.
What other five?
Don't.
Roland downloaded the card.
There's no Company data on the card.
So without the other five cards,
it's unreadable.
It's like one-sixth of the puzzle.
That's not my problem
because we had a deal.
-And we gave you what you asked for.
-No, you didn't.
We had a deal for you to get me Scylla
and you haven't.
-You gave me your word.
-I'm giving you my word again.
You will go back to prison if
you can't get me those other five cards.
But if you can't get this done, just let
me know and we'll get your cell ready.
-You understand?
-I'll get it done.
SELF:
There's one more thing.
-What did he say?
MICHAEL: We gotta find the other cards.
BELLICK: Screw that, man.
We got the card.
Let's do the break-in and end this.
MICHAEL: Doesn't work that way.
-It's not fair, we did what he said.
Then call Agent Self,
tell him you wanna go back to Fox River.
Hell, we're all gonna go to prison
if we can't find the other cards.
When the government gets scared,
they tend to cut the cord.
Did Self talk about shutting us down?
Let's just concentrate on finding Scylla,
all right?
Alex.
-Where is he going?
-Who cares?
How we gonna find Scylla?
We don't even know where to start.
-Where's the rest of the stuff you found?
-Still printing it up.
When my device was in Tuxhorn's
house, it must've been next to his PDA.
Sucked up data from it.
I got e-mails and photos.
-You see anything we can use?
-No, and let me be crystal clear.
I point and click.
Other than that, I'm off the clock.
-Shut up.
MICHAEL: Wait. Where's his calendar?
Dr. Feelgood's got it.
Here, take a look at this.
This is today's date.
There's nothing on it but a star.
Every other date has details for his
meetings, who he's with, when, where.
-This is the only thing with nothing.
-Must be a reason he's keeping it secret.
Why are we letting Self call the shots?
We should play hardball.
From now on,
either help out or get out.
If you open your mouth,
I expect you to offer up a solution.
I'm not gonna say it again.
[LINE RINGING]
WOMAN [OVER PHONE]: Hello?
-Do you know who this is?
-Yeah. Where are you being held?
-I'm not in prison.
-Where are you?
- I can't say.
I need you
to get something to me in L.A.
-Alex.
- It's nothing dangerous. Please, I-- I--
I don't know how much more time
I have here.
Look, don't ask me to do something--
You just need to reach out
to the residential agency in Durango.
Alex, no.
MAHONE:
Do you know what they did?
They killed my son.
They killed my boy.
-I don't know what to say.
-Just say that you'll help me.
Please? I just need your help.
I need to find out who did it.
Please.
SARA:
Hey.
I know in Fox River
you had to keep secrets from me.
You don't now. What's going on?
Self said we have until the end of
the day to find the next cardholder...
...or we all go back to prison.
WYATT: I know that you bailed out
Scofield and Burrows.
And I know they aren't in a supermax
in Texas.
But you know where they are,
don't you, Bruce?
You don't want any more trouble
than you're already in.
I'm not the one in trouble.
Let me help you relax.
It's a beautiful day. The sun is shining.
Do you feel that gentle breeze?
It's a great day for a family picnic.
Don't you think so, Bruce?
Six cards?
That's not what you sold me, Don.
-I realize it's more than we anticipated.
-More than you anticipated.
I already have people questioning me
about the supermax line we're selling.
-This whole thing was a mistake.
-No, no, this wasn't a mistake.
Scofield got us a card within 24 hours
of being dropped in Los Angeles.
He knows what he's doing.
I'm willing to take the risk and do my job
here. I don't understand why you aren't.
I've been in Homeland Security
before it had a name.
Since before you
even had a short and curly, so don't--
Then you should know
what's at stake here, director.
But we could stop it, but--
But not if you end this now.
I'm calling Senator Dallow now. I will
see if he wants this thing killed or not.
But he follows my recommendations,
Don.
"Sir, changed your late London arrival.
Now 7-16 at 4 p.m."
Today's the 16th, but there's nothing
about London in his calendar.
Not that we've seen, no.
-Nothing about travel to or from the U.K.?
-No, nothing.
Why would he get an e-mail
about an arrival in London...
...when he has no business
scheduled there?
Probably because the e-mail is a code.
Alex, I'm so glad you joined us.
S-C-Y-L-L-A, Scylla.
The meeting today at 4 is about Scylla.
Tuxhorn did not schedule a meeting
with himself...
...so that is where
we're gonna find our next cardholder.
Okay, so 4 p.m. is our when.
We need a where.
If you're having a secret meeting,
you don't send the information together.
You'd send the where and the when
separately as a precaution.
Were there other e-mails sent to Tuxhorn
at the same time as the London e-mail?
Within a few seconds of the London mail,
two more followed from the same IP.
My device ran out of space. It picked up
the IP address but not the content.
Trace the IP address.
Find out who sent the e-mails.
E-mails get bounced to routers all over
the world before they end in your Inbox.
Wherever the mail's been,
it leaves a shadow file.
Based on the geography, I'd guess these
e-mails squatted at the Anaheim server...
...a nanosecond before reaching Tuxhorn.
That's where you're gonna find your file.
So get it.
Not every geek with a Commodore 64
can hack into NASA.
These servers have more firewalls
than the devil's bedroom.
You want those e-mails? I'm sorry,
it's on a main server in Anaheim.
It is possible to find those e-mails
at that server?
-Technologically possible.
-We're going to Anaheim.
I want you two
to go to Tuxhorn's workplace.
Stake it out.
If you see him, tail him and call us.
You're just gonna walk up to
a main server? There's gonna be security.
We don't have a choice.
We have to find that e-mail message.
We find out where the meeting is,
we find our next cardholder. Got it?
-And we stay out of jail.
-Yeah, good luck, man.
-Actually, you're coming with us.
-Guess again.
Self told me to sit here and make with
the clickety-clack on the keyboard.
I'm not going nowhere.
[GRUNTS]
Oh, yeah, you are.
Hello?
"Instahomes welcomes you home...
...to your furnished apartment."
Why must you go after this man?
Where I come from,
there's something called a blood feud.
You coming back--?
[BAGWELL SCREAMING]
Michael Scofield left me for dead
one too many times.
Good news, Bruce,
your favorite aunt made it to the picnic.
She brought lemonade.
The little cousins are swimming
in the pond.
Brothers and sisters
are playing catch...
...in a lush green field.
Everyone is here.
Well, almost everyone.
Two very important people
are missing.
Where are Michael Scofield
and Lincoln Burrows?
I don't know.
That's okay, Bruce.
I'm sure you'll remember soon.
Just enjoy the picnic.
[CHATTERING]
My name is Stephanie Reed. I'm here for
a job interview with Human Resources.
Okay, then.
Sorry, your name's not in the system.
Um....
-Would you look again under, R-E-E-D.
-Sure.
She should drop a few buttons on that
shirt, the guard will give her the e-mails.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
MICHAEL:
Great.
-Yes?
SELF: You're in Anaheim, Michael?
This is a strange time
to be taking a trip to Disney.
-Listen to me, if you're trying to run--
-I'm trying to get you another card.
-From where, Tomorrowland?
-From an e-mail on a main router.
There's a Scylla meeting
this afternoon at 4:00.
-Where?
-That information will be on the e-mail.
-Michael, we're running out of time.
-Then stop wasting mine.
I gotta go. I gotta go.
Did you talk to Senator Dallow?
Yes, I did. Now I need to talk to you.
I'm shutting it down.
I'm sorry, ma'am. I don't have you down
for any meeting today.
Okay, um.
Yeah, the temp agency
said that they had set the interview.
Again, I'm sorry.
Okay.
It was really hard to get a sitter today,
um.
Would you call Human Resources
and see if they'll see me since I'm here?
Sure.
Hey, it's Tom at the front desk.
Yeah, I've got a Stephanie Reed here.
She said she had a job interview.
Stephanie Reed. R-E-E-D.
She just passed it off to Michael.
The server room could be anywhere.
Network and wiring specifications
require a server that's on the first floor...
...centrally located, like right there.
What are you,
an engineer or something?
-You know how to drive this thing?
-It's gonna take a while.
-I don't wanna get busted.
-Relax. Find those e-mails.
When I steal, I do it from home,
in my boxers, eating Krispity Krunch.
No chance of being seen,
no chance of getting caught.
-Just get it done.
-Okay.
Okay. All right.
LINCOLN:
Come on. Come on. Come on.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Hey, lady. Did you get what I need?
Yeah, I got it.
Thank you.
I know what you're planning, Alex.
If you do track him down, call me. Don't
do something that could get you hurt.
I won't.
So the material will be where you asked
by 5 p.m.
And, Alex, I'm so sorry.
Goodbye, Lang.
Sorry, they can't see you today.
There's nothing more I can do.
Okay. Thank you for your help.
I appreciate it.
Hey.
Uh, what was the name of
the temp agency that sent you?
Maybe we can call them together
and figure this all out?
-I have it in my car.
-Where is my security badge?
It ain't at my station.
It was there when you showed up.
Take your hands off me.
I don't have your badge.
We'll see about that.
Sara's in trouble.
-What's going on?
-She's been made.
LINCOLN [OVER PHONE]:
Sara's been made.
Is she all right?
The guard has her.
You gotta get out of there.
-Roland, I'll be back.
-Where are you going?
Just keep working.
Like I said, I don't have your badge.
Excuse me, I need to leave.
You can tell your story to the cops,
sister.
[FIRE ALARM RINGING]
Don't move.
Hey!
Where are you? Where are you?
Come on. Come on.
-What the hell?
-Roland, talk to me.
-We're almost there. Almost there.
-We gotta go.
-We gotta go now.
-Got it.
What's going on?
Why won't the door open?
[METAL CLANKS AND AIR HISSING]
What the hell is that?
It's a fail-safe device.
Activated when the alarm gets pulled.
-To protect the server from fire damage.
-Then why the hell did you pull it?
This is an old building. It shouldn't
have such an advanced system.
Okay, well, clearly it does.
What's it do?
To kill the fire,
it sucks all the oxygen out of this room.
[SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
Michael, where are you?
It's getting crowded out here.
We're trapped.
We're in the server room.
LINCOLN: What?
MICHAEL: It's sealed.
It's sucking all the oxygen out. We got
two, maybe three, minutes of air left.
Linc? Linc!
I can't breathe. I can't-- I can't breathe.
I can't breathe.
I can't breathe. I can't breathe.
MICHAEL: Just calm down.
-I can't....
Calm down.
When you panic it gets worse.
Come on. Let's go!
You think we're spinning our wheels?
We got no choice.
Better wait and see if he shows up.
I'm not talking about finding Tuxhorn.
I'm talking about finding the cards.
About finding six cards.
About whether we have a snowball's
chance in Haiti of actually doing this deed.
Better than no chance.
I'm just saying,
we're a couple hours from Mexico...
...wouldn't mind having someone with me
who could speak the native tongue.
Just do your job, Brad.
You feeling good, Bruce?
You look great.
Your father, Josh, is so happy
you made it to the family reunion picnic.
He's missed you very much.
My father's dead.
That's right.
He is.
You see that, Bruce?
You just told me the truth
in response to something I said.
Because lying is so hard right now.
But telling the truth is so easy.
So tell me the truth.
Tell me what everyone at the picnic
wants to know.
Tell me where are Michael Scofield
and Lincoln Burrows?
I don't-- I don't know. I....
Bruce, a bad storm is coming.
A real bad storm.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Don Self.
Good.
So the senator did get my message?
No, no, I'm sorry,
tomorrow's too late. Okay?
I need to speak to him now.
Thank you. Thank you.
Agent Self, it's time to go.
[SINGING TO MUSIC
PLAYING OVER RADIO]
MAN [OVER PHONE]:
Papa Paul's Pizza Palace.
I'd like a large with extra pepperoni
and extra cheese.
The Nobbit.
Add Mama to the Train.
Amateur Screen Test Number Nine.
And we have a winner.
[MAN MOANING ON TV]
WOMAN [OVER PHONE]: Thank you for
calling GATE, how may I help you?
The first e-mail's an ad for Discretia.
An e-mail for pecker pills?
-You want the number?
-That's great.
Definitely worth
almost losing my life for.
MICHAEL: Second e-mail's an invitation
to join some kind of Stargazers Club.
You know, constellations can be used
to track points on Earth.
There's a website that lets you enter
the coordinates of star patterns.
And depending on the date, it'll pick
a corresponding location on Earth.
And you know this because?
Because my son...
...and my ex and I
used to go on this site.
He would look up at the sky
and know where I was.
That's not it.
That constellation's over Antarctica.
He's not gonna get there today,
by 4 p.m., not from L.A.
So I almost died for nothing.
That's good to know.
-A lot of people have died.
-That's their problem, boss.
Because anyone who gives up their life
for this crap is a sucker...
...because you guys can't win.
[YELLING]
MAHONE:
Say it.
Say it about the people who died.
-Say it. Say it.
LINCOLN: Alex.
Alex.
[ROLAND GRUNTING]
Get up. Get back to your nerd box
and do your job.
BELLICK: We could get a little place
by the water.
You'd be better off
not being on the run by yourself.
I vouched for you, Bellick. I told Michael,
"Brad helped me get to Chicago.
He's a good guy, trust him."
Are you crazy? You just wanna run when
we have a chance to clear our names?
Odds of that don't look so good.
Tanks full, gas pedal's on the right. I say
we get the hell out of dodge right now.
Worry about the ankle bracelets
once we get over the border.
You listen to me.
There's only one thing
I'm thinking about.
She weighed 7 pounds,
has her mother's eyes...
...and my heart
in the palm of her tiny hand.
So if I gotta find one card, or six cards,
or 6 million cards...
...I'm gonna do whatever it takes.
Because I only got to hold my baby
for 10 seconds...
...and that wasn't nearly long enough.
[CAR ENGINES REVS]
-What are you doing?
-This guy ain't showing up.
Get your hands where I can see them!
-Get your hands up!
SUCRE: Oh, my God, this ain't good.
MAN: Put your hands up.
-I got them up.
Put your hands up, Sucre. Come on.
Who you calling? They're gonna shoot.
-Come on, put your hands up.
-Okay. Okay. Don't shoot.
-Don't shoot.
MAN: Get your hands up.
Computer's frozen.
-What do you mean, it's frozen?
-I don't know. It's not responding to me.
-I rebooted twice. Still not letting me on.
-Try again.
I've tried a back-door entry. You were
in prison, you're familiar with that.
-You wanna stop breathing?
-What happened?
They locked me out.
MAHONE:
They're shutting us down.
[CELLPHONE RINGING]
-We gotta go. They're coming after us.
ROLAND: Where you--? Whoa.
MICHAEL: Let's go. Come on.
-Wait a minute. We run, they shoot us.
Then stay.
-Sara?
SARA: Yeah.
LINCOLN:
Let's get out of here.
You said
we'd have until the end of today.
No, this goes way over my head.
This project's been terminated.
-Now pull over and end this.
-But we can finish the job.
There is no more job, okay?
If you make this takedown public...
...going back to prison
is gonna be the least of your worries.
Lose him.
[CAR HORNS HONKING]
Stay on them. Stay on them.
[TRUCK HORN HONKING]
MICHAEL: Come on. Let's get out!
LINCOLN: Go!
Let's go. Let's go.
Go! Go! Go!
WOMAN [OVER PHONE]: Thank you for
calling GATE, how may I help you?
Yes, hi. My name is Cole Pfeiffer. I'm
calling about my commencement bonus.
-I haven't received it yet, and--
-Oh, of course. Mr. Pfeiffer, um.
Mr. White is out right now...
...but he's gonna be so upset
he missed your call.
-Here, let me try to track him down.
-No, no. Don't bother.
Maybe you just could forward
the check to me.
Mr. White has to sign off on any checks.
I know he really wants to talk to you...
...so can I have him reach you
on the number that came up on my ID?
Looking forward to it.
LINCOLN:
This way. Come on.
Why did you tell Self
that we could get a cardholder by today?
He set the terms. I didn't have a choice.
Now none of us have a choice.
And I am not going back to prison.
-And I still have things that I need to--
-Then go ahead! Go ahead, run!
Guys! Cut it out.
We ain't running anywhere
with these things on our ankles, all right.
It's over here. It's this way.
[BEEPING]
Wait a minute. Wait a second.
The signal-- The signal's gone.
The signal is gone.
Where are they?
Okay, we gotta go get the signal.
Let's get the signal.
MAHONE: We cannot stay here forever.
They will eventually figure this out.
I don't care if this place
blocks the signal.
LINCOLN: What are you doing, man?
We don't have time for this.
The answers are here. If I can
find them, we might have a chance.
It's an ad. The words don't make sense.
It's gibberish.
Exactly, that's what makes them ideal
for hiding data.
Forget about the damn cardholder.
Self's pulled the plug on us.
[GRUNTING]
SARA:
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
We're gonna figure this out.
We're getting good
at pulling off the impossible.
Hell, I came back from the dead, right?
What is it?
What do you see?
They go over each other.
"Power, plant, new, beach."
There's a power plant in Newport Beach.
That's your meeting.
We ain't got a long until 4:00. How
the hell are we gonna get out of here?
How fast can you run?
-Got a signal?
-Yeah.
They're heading west, four blocks.
Go!
LINCOLN: Out of the cab.
DRIVER: What? What?
LINCOLN: Get out of the cab.
DRIVER: What do you think you doing?
LINCOLN: Move it!
DRIVER: Hey!
Hey!
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello?
Cole Pfeiffer. Gregory White here.
Oh, sorry to disturb you sir. I was just
calling about the, uh, bonus stipend.
Bother me? What are you talking about?
I'm thrilled to finally be able
to put a voice to the e-mails.
And better yet, I'm gonna be able
to put a face to the voice.
-Right, because, we haven't met yet.
-Yes, and that is a crime, my friend.
There are a lot of people over at GATE
who are very excited about meeting you.
I'm going on to San Francisco tomorrow
with my wife...
...and I'd love to see you before I go.
Come to GATE first thing in the morning.
We can all learn something
from the number one salesman...
...in the entire Northeast region.
Well, it's what GATE teaches.
"You can unshackle others
with the keys of knowledge."
It's what I'm here to share. It's what
I know. It's what I wanna give back.
I started this company so people
can avoid the captivity of negativity.
-Amen to that. Amen.
- I gotta go. I've got a lunch.
But I'll see you at GATE tomorrow.
We'll set your office up.
Get you in the payroll system.
And I will personally hand you
your bonus check.
Well, I'll see you
at GATE tomorrow then.
Grab a bat, Cole Pfeiffer,
coach just put you in the game.
Strange place for a meeting.
A little cloak and dagger, don't you think?
Belts and suspenders, Stuart.
Belts and suspenders.
Why Laos?
A doctor doesn't perform his
first dissection on a human cadaver.
First he learns on a frog, then a pig.
Then one day a human.
Laos is our frog,
perhaps Denmark or Chad will be our pig.
After that,
anything we want could be our cadaver.
Let's check on the other side
of the complex.
They could be meeting there.
Whoa.
SELF: Don't you move!
MAN 1: Stay down! Stay down!
SELF: Don't move! Do not move!
MAN 2: Agent Mahone! Stop!
SARA: Go!
MICHAEL: You sure about this?
SARA: Yeah. Go.
Freeze. Don't move. Hands up.
Keep you hands where I can see them.
Come on.
MAN 1:
Freeze!
MAN 2: Stop!
MAN 1: Hold it!
MAN 2: Hands up!
MAN 1: Hold it! Don't move.
Get him cuffed.
-Scofield ran.
-It won't take long to find him.
[GRUNTING]
-You're delaying the inevitable.
-It wasn't, it's a meeting with Scylla.
SELF:
Shut up. Get him in the car.
They got a meeting
on the other side of that building.
SELF: It's over! It's over Lincoln!
-It's not over!
I know you wanted this to work out,
but it's beyond me now.
-Okay? It's done. I have orders. It's over!
-It's not.
It's finished!
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
So when exactly does
the op order commence, general?
It already has.
No, I mean,
when do we see ramifications?
I'll tell you what Stuart, you worry about
the gigahertz and the offshore drilling...
...and let me worry about
the op orders.
[GATE CLANKING]
Oh.
There they come.
What about her?
Let her go.
Real group of winners you hooked me
up with. Thanks. I appreciate it.
We both have worn the badge in our day,
I can't survive anymore time in lockup.
-Can we please work something out?
-You can work your ass into this van.
-Congratulations, the Company wins.
MAN: Go on. Get in.
What? Get in.
You gotta be kidding me.
BELLICK:
It's Michael.
SELF:
Easy.
I gave you a good enough head start.
You should have took advantage of it.
Yeah, but then I wouldn't be able
to give you this. Press the video function.
It wasn't a meeting between
two Scylla cardholders, Agent Self.
It was a meeting
between all six cardholders.
So now we know
who has the other five cards.
And that should mean something.
Even to someone
who's word means nothing.
I'm gonna call Senator Dallow now.
He follows my recommendations, Don.
The next time you run from me, I'm not
gonna be chasing you down in a car.
It's gonna be with a bullet in your back.
Let them go.
-All of them.
MAN: Agent, come on.
Let them go.
Put them in the warehouse.
All of them.
Bring them out.
Yeah, it's Don Self.
I need to talk to him, right now.
Right now.
MICHAEL:
Some day soon...
...we're gonna drop that boat of yours
in the water and disappear forever.
I promise.
Hey, where's Mr. Personality going?
They check his bracelet, he's bust--
Let him be.
STANTON:
Insubordination's tiring, huh?
Where do you get off
calling Senator Dallow directly?
You don't move into my city,
my regional office, and go over my head.
What do you want from me?
You know how it works, Herb.
You think when the Company's
breathing down your neck...
...Senator Dallow's
gonna bring in the cavalry?
He'll pretend
he's never even heard of you.
You're on your own from now on.
You're an island.
If I'm an island,
what are you doing in here?
Just get out of my office
and let me finish what I started.
When you do get buried...
...I'll be the first one there
with a shovel.
Great. I'll see you then.
Sara Tancredi's somewhere safe,
isn't she, Bruce?
You would have made sure of that,
wouldn't you?
So tell me where is Sara?
Help me get your family to Sara,
where it's safe.
Safe.
Los Angeles?
Where in Los Angeles?
I don't know.
I believe you.
Good job.
Picnic's over, Bruce.
[GUN CLICKS]
MICHAEL:
What's up with Mahone?
They murdered his son.
The Company killed his son
like they tried to kill L.J.
Alex, I, uh....
I know what happened.
I'm sorry.
They did this...
...to get to me.
To flush me out.
And then they'll let my ex-wife
stay alive.
Just so she could tell me
that she was next...
...if I didn't turn myself in.
But now she's in protective custody...
...and I'm living in a warehouse trying to
find the son of a bitch who killed my kid.
LINCOLN:
We're all here for somebody.
All of us are here for someone.
You need to stay focused
until this is done.
I can do my job.
I promise.
I promise I'll do whatever it takes to help
you find the person that killed your son.
And the people behind the hit.
We're gonna get these guys, Alex.
I'm gonna help you.
[CRYING]
[ENGLISH SDH]