The man in my head...
He says we're trapped.
God dammit!
What the fuck is happening?
It's coming.
And it kills everything that gets in its way.
- Let me... go!
- No!
Claire...
Hey.
I need you to look after
Arlo when he wakes up.
Okay.
- Nicholas still in there?
- Yeah.
He used to be such a goofball.
He still is, but
now he's also kind of...
Yeah. Yeah, I guess he kind of is.
Cuddle with me for a minute.
Mrs. Kelly.
Claire.
She died?
She did.
What happened, mom?
I would tell you if I knew.
I would love to keep hanging out
with you and Arlo here all day, but
there are things that I need to do.
Yeah, I know.
I really need you to...
Be an adult for a little while.
Can you do that?
Yeah.
Yeah, I can do that.
Should have gone to
the navarros' last night.
No, no. Not in the dark.
Not with whoever's out there.
And certainly not with
whatever this line is.
"Don't trust anyone." Sure it
goes all the way around us?
Any other day, I'd say
he was a whack job, but...
Not today?
Not today.
I'll just cut through the
woods by the back pasture.
It's pretty much a
straight shot to Carmen's.
Well, whatever you do, you should
probably take Ruben with you.
Yeah, but that'd be leaving
you guys without somebody too.
Between Ellen and Valeria and I,
I think we're fine. So please, take Ruben.
Maggie, I don't know.
We have absolutely no idea
who or what is out there, so...
Well, that's... that's what I'm saying.
That's not what you're saying.
Okay, so what am I saying?
You're saying you
don't wanna go with the
husband of the woman
that you've been fucking.
How'd you find out?
Does it matter?
No, it doesn't matter
because I told you it's over.
Does Ruben know?
- Maggie, we can still try...
- try to what?
I don't know. Get through
whatever the hell this is,
and then, I don't know...
Okay. Can we try not
to feel betrayed too?
Or humiliated?
Or sick about the fact
that Valeria is sleeping
in our fucking living room?
Could we try that?
Just go.
Maggie, I'm sorry.
Who cares if you're sorry?
I mean, who cares about any of that?
Obviously you do.
No, I don't, because I can't.
Because I have to be better than that.
And that's what I'm gonna be.
For meryl and for Arlo and for me.
I need to go check on
Donald. Change his bandages.
Maggie, I'm sorry. I really am.
And I do love you.
Wouldn't hurt so much
if you didn't, James.
Ma?
Yeah?
Can I come in?
Hey.
Hi.
I'm gonna walk down the driveway.
Maybe somebody will come by?
Yeah, well, it's Sunday.
Mail isn't coming, but...
And I was thinking we might wanna cook
some of the stuff that's in the fridge.
No electricity, frozen
stuff's not gonna last.
I mean, sure. Can't hurt. Freezer
in the barn has stuff in it too,
if... you know, if you want.
What was that?
You heard?
Just the tone.
It doesn't matter right now.
Well, when it does matter, do you think
yeah.
Yeah.
There you go. You okay?
Well, I'm not... not okay.
I don't know. There's
some cramps, and...
These tremors.
Right.
Nothing I can't handle.
I woke up this morning thinking
maybe it's all just a bad dream.
Yeah, afraid it still is.
I'll be back with help.
Everything is gonna be okay in the end.
And if it's not okay... it's not the end.
What is that, John Lennon?
- Or Noel coward.
- Sure.
I don't know. Either way, desperate times
call for reassuring quotes from mom.
- I'll be back.
- Okay.
Love you.
Hey.
You get any sleep?
I'll sleep when this is over.
Okay, well...
Are you all right?
No idea how to answer that.
Okay, well, I was supposed to drop
Nicholas off at the ever sons' today,
so maybe when we don't
show up or answer our phones...
Even if somebody came by our
place to check on us, it won't matter.
Why not?
Because nobody knows we're here.
- Where are you going?
- I don't know, to do something.
Well, don't do anything stupid.
Or brave.
Keep it cowardly.
Got it.
Scout looks good.
Yeah. Yeah, he does.
But you're gonna tell
me he needs to stay put.
I am.
You got two other horses in that barn.
You, wanna go with James?
The only thing dumber than
him going alone is us letting him.
Know how to use one of these?
They make me a little nervous, but yeah.
The thing to remember is take your time.
Even if there is no time.
Slow is smooth.
Smooth is fast.
Got it.
Hey, Ruben?
Yeah?
Thanks.
We'll get through this.
Both of us.
Hey, Donald?
I just came down to
get my jacket and just...
All right, why don't you come with me.
Come on.
Here.
Okay.
Come on goats, enough.
Still okay with me borrowing
one of your horses?
Yeah, of course. Why wouldn't I be?
The goats are still spooked.
Definitely less than yesterday.
The guy in the mask...
According to his drawing,
the line makes kind of a circle.
He also said don't trust anyone, so.
Say it is a circle.
I'm hoping Edward and
Carmen's is outside of it,
but close enough for us to talk to them.
Otherwise...
Otherwise what?
The navarros are just
as fucked as we are.
Okay.
This is gonna hurt a little bit.
What is it?
It's, something that's
really not made for people,
but it will help you with the pain.
I don't think I've ever
been this fucking tired.
Okay. Why don't you lie down? Here.
Who's this for?
Sometimes there's a horse
that I need to look after overnight.
Your boy?
He's, sleeping.
I'd love to have a son.
A real family, you know?
We wanted kids, Claire and me.
We thought we were gonna.
Not now. I'm.
I'm talking ten years back.
Claire.
She was... she was so excited.
You know? But then...
It didn't happen.
I'm so sorry, Donald.
She said we were gonna try again, but...
- God.
- No, you... you need to rest.
- The body...
- We will take care of Claire, I promise.
No, no, no, not Claire.
There's a body in the woods.
Whoa, whoa. Whoa.
Jesus.
Man, how'd he know where to paint it?
Well, maybe he's the one
behind whatever the hell this is.
Yeah, I don't know. He was
acting like he did it to help us.
Sometimes people act like one thing,
even though they're something else.
Nobody'd know.
Nobody'd know what?
What happened if one of
us ended up over the line
out here in the middle of nowhere.
Just saying.
Be careful.
That don't look good.
Yeah.
Could be they're after
something that crossed the line.
Died that way. A coyote
or deer, maybe. You know?
Or maybe some new nightmare.
Either way...
Yeah, either way.
Let's go.
I think he's, like, learning words.
- What?
- Watch.
Hey.
Who are you?
Warning-alert.
Prem... prem... premonition.
Harbinger.
So, "harbinger." That's... that's you?
So, where's Arlo?
Arlo... sleep-rest.
Sleep-safe.
Quiet-unscathed.
Got it. So that's a relief.
Is it?
Arlo?
Last night, my mom told my dad
Arlo said there's a voice in his head
telling him things.
That's super scary.
But it's not the scariest part.
He said the voice,
it told him there's something coming.
Something that's gonna kill us. All of us.
What is it you said we
need to do, harbinger?
- Hide or die?
- Trapped.
Hide-or-die.
- Assassin?
- Assassin-kill-murder.
- Assassin-kill. Assassin-kill-murder.
- Arlo...
- Assassin-kill. Kill!
- Arlo.
- Stop. Let go!
- Kill!
- Arlo, stop, you're hurting me.
- Trapped. Hide-or-die!
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'm okay.
Trap?
- Arlo?
- Not-no.
Not... trapped.
Not-trapped.
Arlo, where are you going?
We should go with him.
- I told my mom I'd watch him.
- We can watch him and go.
- No, we're supposed to stay.
- Hey, meryl?
You have to listen to harbinger.
Arlo...
Are you all right?
I am. It's weird. Really weird.
But it's not bad.
He's not bad. He's good.
And he's scared, so
he's hiding in my head.
There is no "he," Arlo, okay? It's just you.
Harbinger is real, meryl. He is.
And he's telling the truth.
We need to go right now.
- Go where?
- He says...
He says it's not far.
Arlo, this is crazy,
okay? It's crazy, isn't it?
Any crazier than that blue line
and what happened to Mrs. Kelly?
It is crazy, but assassin is coming, meryl.
And assassin won't stop.
You're always saying to trust you.
You're my sister, and you know things.
- That's different.
- It's not different.
I need you to listen.
I'm your brother, and right now,
I'm the one who knows things.
So I need you to trust me.
Please.
Maybe we should find your
mom, or my dad, or somebody.
No.
Arlo says there's no
time, so there's no time.
James told me about
your... yeah. My ms?
- Do they happen often?
- The tremors?
Only if always is often.
- Wow.
- It does take some Patience.
My husband, William,
he used to say, "Patience is a virtue."
It used to make me nuts.
- Why?
- Because virtue is a virtue.
Patience is just tolerating
bullshit and not being annoyed.
Yeah, I like that.
That man was a pain in my ass,
but I sure did love my life with him.
It kept me sane, you know?
Kept me grounded.
A good marriage will
do that, don't you think?
James told you.
Well, nobody had to tell me.
When Ruben and I first
got married, moved here.
I thought...
Farming seemed like such a
storybook kind of life, you know?
But it's just not.
It's non-stop, and it is all of this...
Just all this nothing.
My god. Look.
My god. The line.
Wait! Don't cross the line.
- Stop! Stop!
- Wait, stop! Stop!
Stop! You have to stop!
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Wait!
Coming over to this
side's a piece of cake.
Heading back the other way...
Well, that's the problem.
But I guess you know that already.
We don't know anything.
All-all we know is... We're terrified.
I hate to say it, but...
Terrified's a pretty good place to start.
It's not far, is it, Arlo?
I don't think he's Arlo.
Harbinger?
It's close.
- What's that?
- What's what?
That.
You know, with all the animals
acting so weird, I thought...
You know, to protect us.
What, it's not... it's not cool?
No, it's cool.
It's really cool.
Arlo? Harbinger!
Arlo?
I guess this is where
all the animals went.
What is this?
Mine.
It's mine.
What does that mean?
This is mine.
Did you come from...?
Arlo? Hey, don't.
Whoa.
Arlo, what is that?
Toxin... bad... poison.
That's poison?
Poison.
So, what are we gonna do with it?
We drink it.
- Hey, Edward!
- Anybody here?
Carmen! Brian!
I'll go this way. You check the barn.
- Meet at the house?
- Yeah.
Go. Go on. Get!
Hello?
Edward!
Ruben!
Fuck.
Carmen?
Hello?
Carmen...
What happened to you?
Hello!
Hello?
Is somebody down there?