♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Did you ever want it? ♪
♪ Did you want it bad? ♪
♪ Oh, my ♪
♪ It tears me apart ♪
♪ We can try to hide it ♪
♪ It's all the same ♪
♪ I've been losing you ♪
♪ One day at a time ♪
♪ And I know
In my heart, in this cold heart ♪
♪ [can live or I can die ♪
♪ I believe if I just try ♪
♪ You believe in you and I ♪
♪ Inyouandl? ♪
Celeste, Celeste.
Oh, my God.
I just...
- I was having a nightmare.
- Shouldn't they be awake?
Oh, my God.
Oh.
Yeah. Josh, Max, up we go. We overslept.
Come on, come on.
- Let's go. We're in a rush. Quick.
- Come on, soldiers.
- Good morning, Grandma.
- Protein-bar breakfast in the car.
Your favorite.
I have to go to town.
I can drop you off.
Oh...
thanks, Mary Louise.
What was it about?
Your nightmare.
Oh, it was stupid.
Nothing, really.
You said "rape."
What?
Something about a rape.
Hmm.
Can I have some water, please?
♪ Never said I wanted
To improve my station ♪
♪ An' I'm only doin' good
When I'm havin' fun ♪
♪ An'l don't have to please no one ♪
♪ An'l don't give a damn
‘Bout my bad reputation ♪
♪ Oh, nod
I'm putting this in your
small pocket, okay?
Yep.
First day of school!
- Stop. Hey, Max, you idiot!
- Hey, hey, boys come on.
Keep it down, would you?
I can't hear myself think.
Then just don't think, Mom.
- Give it back, you idiot!
- Hey.
- Stop.
- Give it back.
Hey. Quiet!
Fine young men
don't suddenly become fine young men
all of a sudden
in a whoosh, you know.
It starts with being fine young boys.
And part of being a fine young boy
is listening and respecting your mother.
She works so hard for you.
That's why the sun shines on her so.
Thank you, Mary Louise.
I have two showings,
I have Abigail's college advisor,
not to mention all this scrutiny.
- It's just gonna be a day.
- What scrutiny?
Ed, this is the first day of school.
We have to earn our good mom badges
all over again.
"Has she gotten fatter over the summer?"
"Does she look older?"
These questions get asked, Ed,
and we all get judged all over again.
It's a double standard.
If a dad shows up, they're like:
"Wow, there's a dad here. He's involved."
But with the moms, ugh.
It just makes me wanna blow.
Boom!
Oh, my God, Chloe. Goddamn it.
Just right there. I need to get right
there. Could you please turn it down?
Let second grade begin.
♪ This is our fork in the road ♪
♪ Love's last episode ♪
♪ There's nowhere to go, oh, no ♪
♪ You made your choice I
♪ Now it's up to me ♪
♪ To bow out gracefully F
♪ Though you hold the key, but, baby ♪
♪ Whenever you call me, I'll be there I
♪ Whenever you want me, I'll be there ♪
♪ Whenever you need me, I'll be there ♪
Welcome back to our wonderful,
wonderful Otter Bay.
Gosh, I always so love the sound of that.
Let's all say that together, shall we?
Wonderful, wonderful Otter Bay.
Here we go. Now, gang, since we ask
our children to sing this every year,
I think it's time we sing it with them,
So everybody let out their inner otter,
and sing along.
♪ Otter Bay, Otter Bay
It's the best place of them all ♪
Very impressive.
We're in the key of F, Madeline.
♪ To start our day
When we rise up with a snort ♪
♪ With dance and song and sport ♪
♪ Oh, to be a little otter in the bay ♪
Yes!
Oh, you got my otter heart going.
Thank you.
Warren.
Really pushing the school spirit
this year, aren't you?
Well, it's my otter blood, Madeline.
- Hi, Madeline Martha Mackenzie.
- Lisa Coolidge.
Anyway, it was a beautiful service, Warren.
Well, thank you, Madeline,
I like to think of it more as an assembly.
A service is for when someone dies,
you know, like a school fundraiser.
You're not seriously gonna go there,
are you?
My hope is you don't go there.
Now, let's remember a lot of last year's
mishigas were lovingly stirred up by you.
Anybody want a red velvet?
- Melissa.
- Cupcake?
- I'll take one for each thigh.
- Absolutely.
I don't even like to chew.
I just shove them down.
Maybe you can give one to Warren
so he can shove it too.
Ah.
And we're off.
- It's a classy crop of moms, these ones.
- Bonnie.
Those gluten-free?
Tahoe was good?
Uh, yeah, it was good.
Nathan caught a lot of fish.
- Wow.
- And I hear you're selling houses like crazy.
That's very cool.
Oh, my gosh, in Monterey,
it is like printing money.
I should've done this years ago.
- I'm gonna go find Skye.
- Okay.
Okay. Are you two fighting?
No. Actually, I almost wish we were.
No, she's...
She's been acting like that
for a while now.
Acting like what?
Shut down. Like, withdrawn.
Oh, you mean you're not having sex.
Don't forget
Abigail has her college counselor meeting
- at 2 p.m.
- Yeah, I got your e-mails.
Six of them this morning.
- It's good. Thank you.
- This is her future, Nathan.
Nice to be back.
I'm told that my daughter, Amabella,
is gonna be in your class. So exciting.
Yes, very nice to meet you.
Um, she has an 1Q of 152. Genius level,
right? That's a very high number.
Life's about give and take.
I expect you to take care of my daughter.
Pay special attention.
And, again, welcome.
Um, oh, oh, oh.
And my Amabella was bullied last year.
I mean, in, like, biting and choking.
So we're gonna make sure
that doesn't happen again.
Oh.
Sorry.
Here's my problem
with the whole meditation thing.
Like you shut out the world,
but you also shut out your friends,
which is a bit weird.
And also, does she look funny?
Something's not right.
- You're talking about Bonnie?
- Mm-hm.
Like, she's off.
But she was off before she went to Tahoe.
Unplugged is one thing,
but unhinged is a total other thing.
Hey! Asshole! Hey!
- Oh, hon.
- Why are you cutting me off?
- Honey. The horn. The horn.
- Dick! I just think we... Oh, yeah, sorry.
- Once I lean in, you know how I am.
- Indeed.
And I think we need to talk to her
and see where her head is at.
- Do you?
- Do you wanna get a coffee?
By the way, did you see Renata
getting up that new teacher's ass?
I thought she was gonna have to pull out
her snorkel.
Easy.
I'm gonna go to the ladies' room.
Can you get me an Americano?
Will do.
- Hey, Bruna.
- Hey, Madeline.
Do you sell weed?
Smells like weed over here.
- Keep the change.
- Thank you so much.
Can I get an Americano
and a bran muffin?
- That's a thing?
- Mary Louise?
- Hi. I'm Madeline.
- Hi.
- Madeline. So nice to see you again.
- Yes. I'm Celeste's friend. Yes.
- How have you been?
- Good, good. The kids are good.
- How are you?
- I can't complain.
Actually, I can.
My son is dead.
But Celeste tells me
that you continue to be so helpful
with her and the boys and...
She should just get
a proper housekeeper.
- You're very short.
- Excuse me?
- I don't mean it in a negative way.
- Oh.
Maybe I do.
I find little people to be untrustworthy.
My apologies. It's just that I'm...
I pride myself on being
a very good judge of character,
but you have always presented
such a difficult read.
You know, you seem like a nice person.
Loving.
But, also, you strike me as a "wanter."
- A wanter?
- Mm.
You know, there are people in life
who content themselves
with what they have,
and then there are others who just...
Just want.
I'm not a wanter.
Oh, you don't have to take it personally.
Anyway, I'm a wanter myself.
You know what I want?
I want Perry back.
I wanna know what happened that night.
And I'm very tempted to ask you,
but I doubt I would get the, uh, truth,
would 1?
Your son lost his balance and he fell.
Yes, that seems to be the company line.
Depending on whose company you keep.
Mary Louise.
Madeline and I were just... talking.
What the hell was that?
That was a very strong position.
And I didn't like it.
Welcome to my life.
Sorry.
Whoa.
- Hi.
- Tori.
Sorry, I didn't recognize you at first.
Yeah. I, uh, had my breasts done.
- Oh.
- Yeah, it's fabulous.
I always felt a little self-conscious,
you know.
About your breasts?
- My nose.
- Ah.
Now nobody notices it so much.
Everybody notices these, though.
And that pisses Joseph off.
So, uh...
Well, I'll see you around.
Hmm.
How long does she plan to stay?
Well, she comes and goes.
It's a short hop from San Francisco.
She's been a really big help.
Mm-hm.
I mean, I'd be lost without her.
So, what brings you?
It's been a while.
I've had some nightmares
starting up of late that, um...
I mean, may be triggered
by the beginning of the school year.
I think I still associate
that place with...
How could you not?
Last night was...
It was a beauty.
Perry and I
were in the in-vitro facility, and...
it was all so sweet, and...
And suddenly, I...
I turned into a monster.
I was strangling him.
I was lifting him up, and I...
It was beyond disturbing, and I...
A little exhilarating.
Hmm.
Is that...?
Do you see yourself as a monster?
I guess I still feel...
responsible.
For?
For the accident.
I mean, if I'd left him when I should have.
We should never have been together
that night,
and he might still be alive.
That I chose that night, of all nights,
to leave him and to tell him and...
Even in death, his message lives on.
- What message?
- That you're to blame.
That you're always to blame.
You're not.
Are you getting out?
- Are you seeing anyone?
- No.
That part of me is still dead, I suppose.
First things first,
get the boys' lives back on track.
That's the priority.
Seeing their mom happy
could help there.
So you're saying
for my life to go on successfully,
- I need to be with a man?
- No.
But the freedom to be with one, maybe.
You're still married, Celeste,
and the husband is dead.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Where have you been?
I told you I was running.
That was like two hours ago,
I've been calling you.
Sorry.
Bonnie. I just thought it might be
that you hated Tahoe,
but since we've been back...
Come on.
I need some space, Nathan. I told you.
Just let it be.
He's my favorite in the whole
aquarium. It's a red octopus, and watch.
The closer he gets to the kelp,
he'll change his color
so that he camouflages
with his environment.
- Cool.
- Look. You see him right now?
- Yeah.
- He's changing color.
You guys wanna know a fun fact
about octopus?
- Yeah!
- It's kind of weird.
- You can handle it?
- Yeah.
Okay. Females contain deadly venom.
And sometimes they'll kill
and they'll eat the males
after they mate with them.
Ew!
- I know.
- Interesting.
Why is it the prettier something is,
the more dangerous?
Like with snakes and spiders.
That's a great question.
I wish I knew the answer to that.
- One second.
- You're so observant.
Sometimes, pretty colors
are to give a fair warning
so other animals know
they need to keep a safe distance.
Oh...
There you go.
How you doing?
Good. You?
Not really, no. Bonnie.
I mean, she's gone missing
in mental action.
The whole summer, truth be told.
Hey, man, could I...?
Could I ask you a big favor?
Could you maybe take her out to lunch?
You've always been better
at talking to women than I have,
and you certainly got Madeline
in a way that I never could.
I mean, I think you might be able
to get her to open up.
You know, you have your little way.
All I'm getting is pushback at every turn.
I swear to God, if I signed up for
this bullshit, I'd still be with Maddie.
I mean... I don't mean...
Oh, no, no. Um...
Look, Nathan,
I'm no expert on marriage or anything.
I mean, something tells me
if you're seeking out the husband
of your ex-wife
to, like, lead the communication charge
with your new one...
- Why do you always have to be so snide?
- I don't mean to be.
You don't mean to be, it just comes
natural. Like you're a snide fuck.
That's what you are. A snide fuck.
You know, Nathan,
maybe instead of just talking to Bonnie,
you should embrace
some of her interests.
- Her interests?
- Yeah.
She won't even let me embrace her.
- Okay.
- Yeah, you're snide.
- You're a snide fuck.
- What?
- Whatever.
- Come on.
Snide fuck.
♪ As I walk this land of broken dreams ♪
Hello.
- Mrs. Klein?
- Juliette.
Hey, honey. I'm pulling in.
Can you...? Can...?
Wait. Hold on one second. Hold on...
- Hello?
- This is my talk about being nice.
- Hey. I can't...
- People don't take my word...
But what do you think?
I love the view.
Oh, sorry, I'm on the phone.
Yeah, I thought Tahoe was supposed
to be about decompression too,
but she seems like she's on Mars.
Maybe she's using.
- Excuse me.
- Yeah, just a second.
And I am beating myself up
that I told Jane I liked her bangs.
- Can you get off the phone, please?
- Hmm?
Oh, let me call you back.
Yeah, what can I do for you?
I can't deny it.
- ♪ It's my house and I live here ♪
- Good, right there.
♪ It's my house and I live here ♪
Beautiful. Come on down. Good.
- Eyes up this way. Gorgeous.
- I'm so tired of those shots of women.
I mean, they're in power, right?
They own banks,
and they're all, like, demure. Bullshit.
Back to the ocean.
What's all this?
Hey. The photo shoot. Women in power.
- I thought they wanted just, uh, office shots.
- No, they're doing house and office.
You look nice.
- ♪ It's my house and I live here ♪
- Here we go. Look at me.
So she has a 3.8 GPA,
and she has done charity work
with human trafficking.
- She also has an internship coming up...
- Okay.
Stanford has an admit rate of under 10.
Princeton and Williams the same. Since
she doesn't have legacy going for her...
Any of these schools would be lucky
to have her.
She's an excellent candidate...
- Candidate is, I think, the wrong...
- Honey.
What? Don't "honey" me.
She has a 3.8 GPA.
She has a 1350 on her SATS,
but we're gonna get that number up
because she has private tutoring
coming up, so I feel...
I don't even wanna go to college.
Okay. She's just... She's just nervous.
She doesn't mean that.
I do mean it. I don't wanna go to college.
It feels so good to say that out loud.
Okay, Abigail, honey.
You're going to college.
The planet is dying, Mom,
but God forbid I don't study Lysistrata?
It's bullshit.
Do you know what kids do at college?
They drink, they fuck.
They mull over a sex change.
- I'm not going. I'm not going to college.
- You're going to college.
If you wanna go, you go.
You should go to college.
Hey, no,
I know how to make any situation about me.
This is not that.
This is about you and your future, Abigail.
Abby.
- I'm not going.
- I'm so sorry.
-Where did she go?
I...
- Did you know about this?
- No, I swear.
You were with her all summer,
and you knew nothing about this?
- I didn't know.
- What about Bonnie?
Did she know
about this "fuck college" plan?
Bonnie's left the building.
Unbelievable. You know if she doesn't
go to college, she won't have a life.
She'll just be serving Big Macs
and French fries, and that'll be her life.
- Is that what you want for her, Nathan?
- Stop. Stop yelling at me.
- You know you bear some responsibility.
- I do?
-You're her father. This is
her senior year, -Oh, okay.
She's on the cusp of her life,
and you let it go all to shit in Tahoe!
- You just hit me. You just hit me.
- Because you deserve it.
But honestly, Ed,
if she doesn't go to college,
what's she gonna do?
Go into retail?
Let me call you right back.
- Mary Louise?
- Hey, Maddie.
Madeline. Hello.
What's going on?
Well, I thought I might look
for a small flat here in town,
so that I can help out with the boys
but not quite be so underfoot.
- Oh, I see.
- Do you work here?
- Yes.
- Do you handle rentals?
- I do, actually. Oren and I both do, yes.
- Oh.
I see you're wearing heels.
Yes.
Um, Oren, do you mind if I just
have a minute with Mrs. Wright?
Of course not.
You're in wonderful hands.
Thank you.
Mary Louise,
I realize that you're still grieving,
and that you've been through
a tremendous amount of heartbreak,
but I don't care
for the way you spoke to me before.
It was rude, and I didn't deserve it.
No, you didn't.
Um, I apologize.
Well, thank you.
The truth is it had nothing to do
with you.
When I was in boarding school,
I had a best friend,
or so I thought,
who, uh, revealed herself
to be quite treacherous
and, uh, caused me a lot of pain.
So...
She was just an itty-bitty little thing
with a big, bubbly personality
that, um, was designed to hide
that she was utterly vapid inside.
You remind me so much of her
that I suppose I punish you for that.
That's wrong of me, and I apologize.
- Oren.
- Yes. Sorry.
I'm sure Oren will address
all of your concerns.
Okay.
Where did we leave it?
♪ Oh, to see without my eyes ♪
♪ The first time that you kissed me ♪
♪ Boundless by the time I cried ♪
♪ I built your walls around me ♪
♪ White noise, what an awful sound ♪
♪ Fumbling by Rogue River ♪
♪ Feel my feet above the ground ♪
♪ Hand of God, deliver me ♪
Oh.
- That probably looked weird.
- Yeah.
Are you on the spectrum?
Are you?
Uh... I'm...
Yeah, most likely.
- Well, I don't think I am, but...
- A little advice.
You probably don't wanna
act weird and shit in public.
We do a lot of kids' events
at the aquarium.
Parents have a thing
about entrusting their kids to psychos.
Noted. Got it. Thank you.
The way people talk in this town,
I don't need to tell you.
You don't need to tell me?
What does that mean?
You're one of the Monterey Five, right?
Monterey Five?
You were there the night the guy fell.
- Where did you hear that?
- Someone at work.
- I'll see you around.
- Yeah.
- It was just the way he said it.
- How exactly was that?
Like we all have scarlet letters
on our backs.
- Oh, please.
- We're kidding ourselves
- if we think people have stopped talking.
- Yeah, but people talk. It's...
I think we're all being a
little bit paranoid, you guys.
I think people have moved on.
The police definitely moved on.
- We don't know for sure.
- Yeah... No, I talked to Susie Burke.
- Do you know Susie from IBM?
- Yeah.
She's a good friend of Detective Quinlan.
- Oh.
- Mm.
I mean, like, really good friend.
Gossip for another day, but she told me
that she heard Quinlan say,
like, the case isn't "closed" closed,
but they've got nothing.
- Mm-hm.
- Good.
Good.
- We're good.
- Okay.
Yeah.
Where were you?
We were waiting for you at the beach.
Oh, yeah. Um, something came up.
Yeah?
What?
Are you all right?
Do you care?
Do I care?
What's going on?
I killed someone.
- Remember?
- Yes.
- I...
- It's heavy.
Are you...? I mean, are you angry at me
for some reason?
I'm angry with myself.
If I had just told the truth,
I would have gotten off,
but you said he slipped,
and everyone else joined
in the fucking chorus.
- That was to protect you.
- Yeah, thanks a lot.
You know, I can't talk to my husband.
Or my kid.
I have to just swallow it all.
You can talk to us.
We're here for you. All of us.
Well, it hasn't really felt like that.
Well, I'm sorry, but you've been in Tahoe.
It's not like you can put that shit on
Gmail. Like, what am I supposed to...?
Hey.
Bye, Maddie.
- Little Miss Sunshine, right?
- Listen, I'm sorry I pushed you.
There you go, I said it.
Okay, um, I need to talk to Abby.
Is she here?
Abby!
♪ Scented and tall ♪
♪ Hesitating once more ♪
♪ And as I take...
So...
what was that all about?
I just don't think college is for everyone,
that's all.
Okay.
So why is it not for you?
Well, starting with the cost.
It's really expensive.
So I'm assuming that if you're gonna
abandon that plan to go to college,
- you have another plan...
- I do.
What is it?
- It's to work for a startup.
- Oh, my God.
Specifically, one that builds
for-profit housing for the homeless.
- Excuse me?
- Yeah.
And unlike, you know, the privatized shams
like banks and credit card companies,
ours will make money
while actually helping people.
This is something real?
I've been offered a position
to start in June.
- You cannot be serious.
- I'm gonna take it.
You cannot mortgage your future
over some sort of short-term plan.
- I'm not doing that.
- Well, then, what are you doing?
There are four million homeless people
in America,
the average age being 9 years old.
- And I...
- I don't give a fuck!
I don't care
about fucking homeless people.
- What?
- That is not what I meant.
I do care about homeless people.
I just think you can give money
to some charity
while you actually attend college.
- I'm not going to college.
- Yes, you are.
- Give me one good reason why I should.
- It's non-negotiable. You're going to college
because I said so,
and because you're not thinking straight...
- Because you said so?
- Yes, because I said so.
What do you know?
You didn't go to college.
That's exactly why you're going.
Exactly.
Because you will have no life!
Can't you just tell her it's time to go?
The boys love her. I mean, they love her.
And she's...
She's a big help. She really is.
So, what's up?
I'm guessing you don't need my help
on how to handle a mother-in-law.
Why are you not cashing the checks?
- I don't know.
- Come on, Jane. Why?
It's rape money. You know I can't do that.
Ziggy's entitled to it.
He's part of Perry's estate.
Do you ever hate me? Just a little bit?
How could I hate you?
Because I slept with your husband.
I mean, I didn't...
You know what I mean.
He raped you.
But I knew he was married.
I mean, I didn't know he was
married to you, but somebody.
No.
I don't blame you for anything.
I think I would if I were in your shoes.
Celeste, for a man to commit adultery,
he... There has to be another woman,
and, you know what, more times than not,
she's complicit. I was complicit.
Not in the end,
but definitely in the beginning.
Are you glad that he's dead?
It's complicated.
♪ Come a little bit closer
♪ Hear what I have to say ♪
♪ Just like children sleepin' ♪
♪ We could dream this night away ♪
♪ But there's a full moon risin' ♪
♪ Let's go dancin' in the light ♪
Come on, everybody.
Put it away, Max.
Come.
This looks so delicious.
Thank you, Mary Louise.
I thought we were having KFC.
Well, one cannot survive
on fast food every night.
We don't have it every night.
You know that they ban
these insidious fast food institutions
from some parts of San Francisco.
Do you remember when we walked
across the Golden Gate Bridge?
It's red.
Yeah, you're right, it is red.
Oh, and Dad said
he was gonna swim to Alcatraz.
Oh, yeah.
Sharks would have eaten him, stupid.
No, they wouldn't, idiot.
Hey! Hey! You could hurt him.
What's wrong with you?
- I barely touched him.
- You stuck him with a fork, Josh.
That is unacceptable.
For God's sake.
I miss Dad.
I know, baby.
I know you do.
We all do.
- We still have some recovery ahead of us.
- Well, they're grieving, Celeste.
Their father's death is not...
something to be recovered from,
like a cold.
You know,
your daddy was the most amazing man,
and you were so lucky to have him.
And it's very unfair
and wrong that he died.
And you still feel angry about it,
don't you?
I mean, you feel angry that the other kids
have their dads. You don't.
You know, the other day,
I was with some friends,
and, um, their sons were not a patch
on your dad.
Not a patch.
Just... I felt so angry.
Angry!
You know, that their mediocre,
spindly, pudgy, balding,
middle-management sons, still alive.
And my Perry...
My Perry...
I just felt just... I wanted to scream.
So you know what I did?
- What?
- I did scream.
You wanna hear?
Okay.
Mary Louise! Mary Louise!
Mary Louise, please.
What, my grief is too loud for you?
- Oh, Celeste.
- No, just... Just...
- I should be more discreet.
- The boys.
We should scream. We should scream
and beat our breasts and tear our hair.
Don't you feel angry?
You don't?
I'm sorry.
I feel so, so alone, you know.
♪ In the sun I feel as one ♪
♪ In the sun ♪
♪ I'm married
♪ Buried ♪
We were like animals.
We had to save her.
We... It was like every instinct
inside of me told me that she was...
He was gonna kill her
if we didn't help her.
And, um...
I thought he was gonna crush her
or kick her ribs in or...
I didn't know what he was gonna do.
And then he, um...
Renata or me, we grabbed him, and then...
Then he grabbed Jane by the neck.
Yeah. Um...
I'm sorry.
In your own time.
Take a good look.
No!
Fucking kill you!
Are you all right? Celeste?
You all right?
You all right, dear?
- Yeah.
- Another nightmare?
Yes?
It's all right.
I'm sorry.
So...
who are we planning to kill?
♪ It's everywhere I look ♪
♪ From Las Vegas to right here ♪
♪ Under your dresser ♪
♪ Right by your ear ♪
♪ It's creeping in sweetly ♪
♪ It's definitely here I
♪ There's nothing more deadly
Than slow-growing fear ♪
♪ Life was full and fruitful
And you could a take a real bite ♪
♪ The juice pouring well over
Your skin's delight ♪
♪ But the shadow, it grows
And take the depth away ♪
♪ Leaving broken down pieces
To this priceless ballet ;
♪ The shallower it grows ♪
♪ The fainter we go
Into the fade out line ♪
♪ The shallower it grows
The shallower it grows ♪
♪ The fainter we go
Into the fade out line ♪
♪ Did we build all those bridges
To watch them thin down to dust? ♪
♪ Or blow them voluntarily
Out of constant trust ♪
♪ The clock is ticking
Its last couple of tocks ♪
♪ And there won't be a party
With weathering frocks ♪
♪ The shallower it grows ♪
♪ The fainter we go
Into the fade out line ♪
♪ The shallower it grows ♪
♪ The fainter we go
Into the fade out line ♪
♪ Heading deep down ♪
♪ We're sliding without noticing
Our own decline ♪
♪ Heading deep down
We're hanging onto ♪
♪ Sweet nothings left behind ♪
♪ Deeper down ♪
♪ We're all going down I
♪ Down, deeper down, yeah I
♪ We are all plunging straight towards
Our own decline ♪
♪ Without noticing we slide down ♪
♪ Deeper down ♪
♪ The shadow grows
Without ever slowing down ♪
♪ We are heading straight
Into the fade out line ♪
♪ The shallower it grows ♪
♪ The fainter we go
Into the fade out line ♪
♪ The shallower it grows ♪
♪ The fainter we go
Into the fade out line ♪
♪ The shallower it grows ♪
♪ The fainter we go
Into the fade out line ♪
♪ The shallower it grows ♪
♪ The fainter we go
Into the fade out line ♪
♪ The shallower it grows ♪
♪ The fainter we go
Into the fade out line ♪
♪ The shallower it grows ♪
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::