♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Did you ever want it? ♪
♪ Did you want it bad? ♪
♪ Oh, my ♪
♪ It tears me apart ♪
♪ We can try to hide it ♪
♪ It's all the same ♪
♪ I've been losing you ♪
♪ One day at a time ♪
♪ And I know
In my heart, in this cold heart ♪
♪ [can live or I can die ♪
♪ I believe if I just try ♪
♪ You believe in you and I ♪
♪ Inyouandl? ♪
I pushed him.
It was my fault. My fault.
- We have to.
- No, no, Maddie!
You didn't push him.
And you didn't.
Nobody did this.
Help! Call an ambulance! Help!
Help!
Get help!
- You want me to kiss her?
- Yeah.
How do you kiss?
- Let me teach you.
- Like this?
Mm-hm.
This is so...
Oh, I kind of like this.
- Ew, you guys are disgusting.
- Gross.
Let's get a family photo of this.
♪ Happy birthday... ♪
♪ -To...
- ..youJd
How we feeling?
Are we pumped? Are we excited?
- Yeah.
- First day of school.
- I'm excited.
- Looking good.
High intensity.
It's the new workout craze.
Are they gonna get divorced?
No.
He seems mad.
Well, that must mean
that he loves her a lot, right?
But you like him.
Yeah, I do.
Do you love him, though?
I think you do.
I don't really...
know him well enough to love him.
Love is a really big word, you know?
But he makes you happy.
You're like a whole other person.
Your whole face and stuff
has been different.
Well, I know that the three of us
can be friends for a long time.
I want you to be with him.
Ziggy...
And I think you wanna be with him too.
Last one to the bottom is a rotten egg!
Double Americano.
All right. Double Americano. Would you
like me to leave room for milk?
- Americanos don't have milk.
- Some like milk in their Americanos.
It's espresso and hot water.
Do I need to come back there
and make it myself?
No, no. It's fine.
- Renata?
- Thank you.
Oh.
How are we today?
How are we?
- We...
- Hi.
Are wrought, Mary Louise.
-We are worried about a wonderful mother
-Hm.
Who's being put through an onerous,
if not despicably cruel, court procedure
to, what?
Get to be with her own kids?
We're wrought.
You're a good friend to her.
And Celeste is very, very lucky
to have such a strong support system.
And I sometimes think
that if she hadn't tried
to take on so much alone,
you know,
she wouldn't have unraveled so.
She hasn't unraveled.
She's a single mom and a widow
with two kids.
She's done a damn good job.
So I encouraged a housekeeper.
Or a nanny.
She thinks nannies are too much trouble.
More trouble than they're worth sometimes.
- What did you just say?
- Just a mint tea.
- A mint tea.
This is exactly what you did
the last time you were at my house.
Stay-at-home moms who make me feel
like I should be locked up?
- No, you shouldn't.
- What, for neglect?
Because I have a fucking career?
I have spent every day of my goddamn life
putting my family and my child first.
So don't go there.
- Don't go there, judgy judger.
- I'm...
Keep your eyes
on your own fucking paper, Mary Louise.
Put it in a bag.
I'll take it to her.
Because we're going to the same...
With you questioning her,
she can come at you directly.
She can bait you, provoke you...
I've questioned witnesses before.
- With the stakes this high...
- I'm fine. I'm fine.
- It could backfire.
- I know her.
And she knows that I know her.
So I have a better chance
of getting to her than you do.
- Celeste...
- It's my turn, Katie.
It's my turn.
It's a very smart play on her part.
Because she might be up there
in her capacity as a lawyer,
but she'll be presenting herself again
as a person, as a mother.
And this time without being subject
to cross-examination.
And all the questions she's asking you,
what she'll really be doing
is showing the judge:
"Look at how stable I am,
look at how reasonable, how smart."
I even expect her to go gently,
you know?
Putting her compassion on full display.
- If you see her doing that...
- Sleeping Beauty.
That's how Perry would describe her
to me.
Sleeping Beauty.
He was her prince.
- And she killed him.
- Mary Louise...
only answer the questions
that are asked.
Oh, uh, yeah.
No problem.
Okay. Let's go.
And she kept repeating...
over and over again.
Look what you made me do.
Look what you made me do!
All rise.
Case number CV-04111,
the matter of Joshua and Maxwell Wright.
This court is now in session,
the Honorable Judge Marylin Cipriani
presiding.
Be seated.
Mrs. Wright, please take the stand.
Mrs. Wright?
Please raise your right hand.
Do you swear to tell the truth,
the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth,
so help you God?
- I do.
- Be seated.
Okay. You're up.
Mary Louise.
Celeste.
Your attorney made me out
to be quite the bad mother.
He was just asking questions.
You answered them.
Is it your observation
that I am a bad mother?
As I...
As you heard me tell Judge Cipriani
when we were in chambers,
I consider you
to be a wonderfully committed parent.
That's not the impression...
As to my observations, yes.
I have observed you
being violent with the boys.
I witnessed you throwing Max to the ground
and shaking him.
I saw you drive off,
wearing nothing but your jammies,
under the influence of who-knows-what.
You say Ambien.
And you crashed the car, in fact.
So you're not okay.
That's my observation.
Which we can all accept,
after all you have been through.
But I cannot accept
these children being placed
in such imminent peril.
Did you ever report to Child Services
that you believed
my children to be in danger?
I probably should have.
So the answer is no.
Yeah, it's no.
Did you ever report to any other agency
that you believed
my boys to be in imminent peril?
No.
You suggested
that I got violent with my sons.
Is it your testimony
that I am routinely violent with them?
- No. Not routinely, but...
- Is it your testimony
that I am often violent with them?
No.
But who knows what I haven't seen?
So now you're basing your opinions
on what you haven't seen?
I'm not a trained lawyer,
so the semantics...
Please, would you direct your responses
to me?
I'm asking the questions.
Okay.
Now, the truth of it is, you saw me
lose my temper with my son once.
Where I overreacted,
I pushed him to the ground once.
All it takes is once.
Well, you would know that
better than anyone, wouldn't you?
As a young mother,
did you ever lose your temper
with your boys?
Well, this isn't simply about temper
or temperament...
Did you ever lose your temper
while you were driving an automobile
and cause the car to crash?
Would you like me
to repeat the question?
No, I heard the question.
It was obscene.
Your son Raymond died, in part,
because you lost your temper.
Isn't that true?
Objection.
This witness has testified
that I put my sons in peril.
It is relevant to this proceeding
as to whether or not
she has ever killed a child in her care.
Mrs. Wright, please sit.
Please.
Why are you doing this?
I am simply trying
to protect my children.
Now, the idea of you driving with
my children in the backseat of your car
while you lose your temper,
that is terrifying to me.
Your Honor, this is indecent.
Are you suggesting this cross-examination
should be limited to decency, Mr. Farber?
Mrs. Wright, you don't get to go at him.
Indecent or not,
this case is about mothering,
which puts your parenting strategies
in issue.
Now, I cannot imagine the trauma of
losing your child in an automobile crash.
It must have been unspeakably devastating
for both you and for Perry.
It was.
How old was Perry at the time?
Oh, he was 5.
He was 5.
- Five years old.
- Mm-hm.
To witness his brother die,
his only brother.
Did you put him into therapy?
To deal with the trauma?
In those days, we were less inclined
to outsource our children's pain.
So you assumed that role, did you?
Attending to Perry's trauma?
Yes, I did.
And you talked to him?
You consoled him?
Yes.
Held him?
All of the above. Yes.
Mm-hm.
Blamed him?
Did you ever blame him
for causing the car to crash?
I most certainly did not.
Did you ever accuse him
of distracting you?
Did you ever say to him,
"Look what you made me do"?
No.
No? So if Perry were to have told me
that you blamed him
- for his brother's death...
- Objection, hearsay.
Overruled.
If Perry were to have told me
that you punished him,
that you even emotionally battered him...
I never, ever battered him.
If he told me that you said to him:
"This is your fault.
It is your fault
that your brother was killed."
- Stop it.
- Did you ever...?
- No, stop it.
- Objection, Your Honor.
- Did you ever, ever hit him?
- No.
- Did you ever kick Perry?
- I never...
- Mrs. Wright.
- It's a lie. It's a lie.
Mrs. Wright, we do seem to be drifting
beyond the scope of the inquiry here.
My husband physically and emotionally
abused me.
Your Honor well knows
that abusers don't just happen.
They are more than likely
to be victims of abuse themselves.
Whether or not this witness is an abuser
is certainly, certainly not
beyond the scope of this inquiry.
You're a liar.
And the fact that violence
may have been a part
of your sexual relationship...
He was not an abuser.
Not for one second.
And is Jane Chapman a liar?
Is this woman sitting here lying
when she says that your son raped her?
- She's mistaken.
- She is "mistaken."
Is that something
a woman is likely to get wrong?
Whether or not she's being raped?
Well, he perhaps got too vi...
Physical with her...
as a result of thinking
that women sometimes like that,
the way you enjoyed it.
And now you're trying
to cover over your sickness
with these disgusting fabrications.
Max and Josh need to believe
in their dad.
How do they get to do that
with you walking around
calling him a rapist and an abuser?
The way you assassinate him,
his memory.
He's not here.
He's not here to defend himself.
He's the victim here.
- Oh, my God.
- Not you.
I can't, Perry. You're hurting my arm.
You don't wanna do this, okay?
I'm talking to you!
Get off!
You little shit.
Will you stop?
Fuck you!
Oh, my...
Are you gonna ask more questions?
Come on.
Get up, get up.
Stop it, stop it, stop it.
- Please.
- You're bleeding.
- No!
- Okay. Okay.
My sons took that video.
Your concerns that I am making up stories
about their father are unfounded.
Mary Louise, look at me.
This was your son.
You were so incredible.
I'm just sorry that...
I didn't know he was doing that to you.
That he was hurting you like that.
It's because I didn't tell you.
No, I should've known, Celeste.
I'm your best friend.
I should have felt something.
- You're gonna win, right?
- No, not necessarily.
That just spoke to Perry's evil,
but it didn't...
It didn't go so much
to my fitness as a mother.
I mean, how could I let them live
in that house?
How could I let them see those things?
And they saw so much more
than I ever knew.
Maybe I'm not a good mother.
Maybe I'm not fit.
Don't ever say that.
Don't even think that.
You are an incredible mother.
Are you perfect?
No. Am I perfect? No.
There's no such thing.
But you...
Celeste, look how far you've come.
And look at how strong you are.
You can't falter here.
Do you hear me?
Those boys belong with you.
Okay?
How's it going?
Not great.
I'm sorry.
I don't want you to think
that I don't like you.
It's not fair to put all this on you.
You know, you should be out there
having fun,
not dealing with me.
What is fun?
Is that getting drunk
and going to some bar,
ending up with a girl
I have no connection to?
This is fun.
Okay, first, nothing is perfect.
Nothing's even best.
But if you can find better, nice...
Even good is good.
Secondly,
no matter how good something is,
you can ruin it by overthinking it.
Just your two cents.
- What?
- Kill it.
Ten more minutes.
- Stop it.
- And then all the killing stops.
- I got it, I got it.
- Okay, there you go.
- Hey.
- Come on.
Did court go good?
Yeah. I think it did.
Were you a superhero?
Oh, I was like Wonder Woman
and the Incredible Hulk.
Combined.
Did you beat her up?
What?
No.
Nobody beat anybody up.
Oh, my God...
- Why did you lie?
- I didn't lie.
You said that I hit him, that I kicked him.
Perry told me what you did.
- That never happened.
- So you're saying Perry's a liar?
No, I... I brought him up to be good.
A good boy. A good man.
That person that we saw on the videotape,
I don't know who that is...
I hope that you don't live
to bury your children, Celeste,
because you would not even
be standing.
You lost your boys.
You don't get to take mine.
But... Don't...
Don't lie.
Don't lie about me.
Don't lie about me. It's not fair.
It's not fair.
My turn, Dad.
You can go.
You go.
If you don't mind,
I'd like to stay by myself.
I've been really enjoying this time
with her, you know?
She's, um... She's a good listener now.
Okay.
Bye.
So you wanna go, huh?
I forgot to tell you something.
Or maybe I said it.
I don't remember, but...
it looks like now's the time.
I love you, Momma.
It took me my whole life to say that.
I've been thinking a lot
about something you said a while back.
About the lie.
And that it was...
It had a shelf life.
I think you're right.
And I've been feeling really, really bad
that I started it.
- You didn't start it...
- Yes, I did.
And you didn't have to follow suit,
but you did, but I started it.
And...
I can just see the damage that it's done,
and it's eroding all of us.
Every single one of us.
Including me.
It's unraveling all of our friendships.
Madeline, you and I have a friendship,
and Jane.
That... That's...
the Monterey Five,
whatever we call ourselves...
The lie is the friendship.
- Hi, baby.
- Hi, Momma.
Hi, Grandma.
My God.
What's happened?
She woke up saying she was hungry.
Are you hungry, baby?
Will you run out and get a bottle of wine?
- Yeah. Okay.
- Thank you.
Do we really have to wear ties?
Yes.
I think it's a good idea.
You're so handsome.
Your daddy always looked so good in ties.
If he was here,
he wouldn't let Grandma do this.
No.
Now, I don't think it's likely,
but if the judge asks you any questions,
you just answer honestly and you be polite,
- all right?
- Tell her that we wanna stay with you?
Yeah. If that's what you want.
Yeah. You tell her that.
Are you scared?
A little bit.
Are you?
Mm. Kind of, yeah.
- Mm-hm.
- Me too.
We're in it together, okay?
Hey. What'd I say about sugar?
What doesn't kill you...?
No. Where did you even get that stuff?
I have connections.
Uh, you should pack up
your things, though. We have to go.
So is that me?
That punching bag?
It's not you.
I need to know what you're thinking.
I honestly don't know
if we are apart or together,
or getting better, or we're getting worse.
I just need to know what's in your head
before my own fucking head explodes.
Okay, come on.
Sit down.
Chloe, please.
You know, I've been thinking
about our wedding day.
Maybe because you were, like,
prancing around in your veil.
- Do you remember that day, Madeline?
- Yeah.
I remember it was really joyous.
Yeah, it was joyous for me too.
But delusional.
I mean, we did not know
what we were getting into.
I mean, you were married before,
maybe you had a better idea,
but most weddings
are just like this blind leap of faith.
All the vows we take, I mean,
we can't even know
what the fuck that means.
- L really don't like where this is going.
- Look, you are not who you were then.
And neither am I. People change.
We need to renew our vows.
What?
This time, committing to live up to them.
- Do you think you can do that?
- With all my heart.
Fully informed
as to what we're getting into.
Truly, truly, yes.
Committing to better or worse...
No, no. Your worst is off the table.
- Okay, yeah.
- Okay?
- Got it. Absolutely.
- All right.
Do you really mean it?
Look...
This is not some, like:
"Put a tidy ribbon on it,
bygones be bygones" ending.
Okay? This is a shot at a new beginning.
Which, like, if you really feel
that you're up to it...
I am. I am.
Well, then so am I.
- I love you.
- L love you too.
- This is gonna be really good.
- Yeah.
Oh, my God. We can do it on the beach.
We can have a tent, and a big party,
- and then we can do like a seafood...
- No, no, no. No party.
Just you, me, Abigail, Chloe.
Family.
That sounds perfect.
Okay.
It's gonna be okay.
- What's going on?
- There's been a setback.
- What kind of setback?
- Another stroke, most likely.
We're taking her into radiology now
to see what we're dealing with.
Momma...
- Has she been sedated?
- No, she's just unconscious.
- Jesus.
- Will she wake up?
We have to look at the pictures
to know what's going on.
She's too young.
This doesn't make any sense.
We'll get her back as soon as we can.
All rise.
Case number CV-04111,
the matter of Joshua and Maxwell Wright.
This court is now in session,
the Honorable Judge Marylin Cipriani
presiding.
Be seated.
This is a difficult decision,
one made more so by the cumulative wash
of the child psychiatrists' reports.
These reports, which conclude...
If I may be heard, Your Honor.
All right.
What I saw on that video...
I simply had no idea.
I'm so sorry. I...
I don't know what to say
to make you forgive me.
I had no idea.
If I had...
But...
this is not about forgiveness or blame.
This, today, is about the well-being
of these two splendid young men,
Josh and Max.
Your Honor, I told you from the outset,
I bear no contempt for my daughter-in-law.
In fact, I... I love her.
How could I not?
She made my son so happy.
And the boys.
But, Celeste, you are ill.
What we saw on that video
was repugnant.
It was grotesque.
I'm so ashamed of my son.
But you were a part of it.
You were complicit in it.
You have admitted to me,
to yourself, to this court,
that you were a part of this sickness
that you exposed your children to,
that they may have been infected by,
that they recorded on their smartphone
to stick in their memory book.
It's a sickness that,
given your most recent...
social adventures with strangers,
it seems that you are unable to resist.
So...
Your Honor, I have no doubt
that she will get herself well.
But in the meantime, right now,
we just need to safeguard the boys.
She wants what's best
for her grandchildren,
as she did for her son, Perry.
That man that you saw on that tape,
that was because of your parenting,
your caregiving.
It's one thing to be asked
to turn your children over.
It's quite another
to be asked to give them to you.
These are my babies.
I am their mother.
And I have protected them
against the most formidable of odds.
I kept them alive. I kept myself alive.
And on this, I agree with you,
Mary Louise, you had no...
No idea.
And that is the problem.
My sons are...
They're good boys.
And I will raise them to be good men.
They will be good men.
I have a list of conditions
and compliances,
which will be entered
together with my judgment.
They are self-evident
and they are to be followed.
As for the judgment itself,
as it's been noted by all,
these boys have been through
an unimaginable ordeal.
They face great challenges ahead
with their healing, their development.
It won't be easy.
I'm not going to make it any harder
by taking them away from their mother.
The petition to appoint guardianship
is denied.
Full custody shall reside
with Celeste Wright.
- We're adjourned.
- Oh, my God.
I'm sorry.
I need you to do something for me.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
- Here.
- Thanks.
I'm so sorry, honey.
Nathan.
You're a good man
and a wonderful father.
Skye adores you, and she should.
And I know you love me.
But you've been right to think
that something's been going on with me.
So I'm gonna be truthful.
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you this sooner.
I'm not in love with you.
I know this isn't the best
time to tell you, but I...
I don't think I've ever been.
I just can't lie anymore.
I'm sorry.
What the fuck is this?
Well, hi.
Why is this still here?
Funny you should ask.
I sold it all today to Ted Farrell.
The guy gave me a check for 410
for the whole kit and caboodle.
- Nice. Well, Celeste...
- And the best part is, we get to keep it all.
What do you mean,
we get to keep it all?
Ted's just a collector,
only cares whether it appreciates or not.
And he knows there's no better steward
for it than me, so we get to keep it all.
So basically, you're saying
you get to keep your toys?
Ah. Perfect, huh?
No.
No, it's not perfect.
- It's far from fucking perfect.
- Oh, God.
- All my stuff is gone.
- Look. Come on. Please.
We got money for this, all right?
Calm the fuck down.
- Calm down?
- Yes, calm down, all right?
You lost all our money.
- Oh, my God, here we go.
- You have plunged us into bankruptcy.
- Yeah.
- We are selling our home.
Our daughter's home.
And all the while,
you've been fucking the nanny?
Well, now she's gone,
I need something to play with, don't 1?
Oh, my God.
That was too much. I'm so... Hey!
What the fuck are you doing?
We don't own any of this!
Goddamn it!
- Renata! Fucking hell!
- Fuck youl!
- Come on now... No.
- Fuck you! Fuck! Fuck!
Fuck it!
- Not that. No, come on, don't...
- Is that your favorite fucking baby?
No! Hey, hey.
No!
Oh, my God.
Maybe you should've shown a woman
a little respect!
I'm done.
No more bullshit.
No more lies.
Do you, Ed,
take Madeline to be your wife?
To love her, comfort her,
honor and protect her,
as long as you both shall live?
I do.
Do you, Mom, take Ed
to be your husband,
to love and comfort him,
honor and protect him,
as long as you both shall live?
I do.
Okay, I therefore proclaim
that you are husband and wife.
You may now kiss the bride.
♪ Someone told me long ago ♪
♪ There's a calm before the storm ♪
♪ I know ♪
♪ It's been comin' for some time ♪
♪ When it's over so they'll say ♪
♪ It'll rain a sunny day
♪ I know ♪
♪ Shinin' down like water ♪
♪ I want to know ♪
♪ Have you ever seen the rain ♪
♪ Comin' down on a sunny day? ♪
It's gonna be okay.
♪ Yesterday and days before I
♪ Sun is cold and rain is hard
♪ And I know ♪
♪ It's been that way for all my time ♪
I wanna go with you.
Just let me drive you.
♪ 'Til forever, on it goes ♪
♪ Through the circle, fast and slow ♪
♪ I know ♪
♪ It can't stop, I wonder ♪
♪ I want to know ♪
♪ Have you ever seen the rain ♪
♪ Comin' down on a sunny day? ♪
♪ I want to know ♪
♪ Have you ever seen the rain ♪
♪ Comin' down on a sunny day? ♪
♪ Didn't I make you feel ♪
♪ Like you were the only man?
♪ Yeah, and didn't I give you nearly
everything That a woman possibly can? ♪
♪ Honey, you know I did ♪
♪ And each time I tell myself that I
Think I had enough ♪
♪ Well, I wanna show you, baby
That a woman can be tough ♪
♪ Won't you just come on, come on ♪
♪ Come on, come on and take it ♪
♪ Take another little piece
of my heart now, baby ♪
- ♪ Oh, oh, break it ♪
- ♪ Break another little bit of my heart, darling, yeah ♪
- ♪ Oh, oh, have a ♪
- ♪ Have another little bit of my heart now, baby ♪
♪ Aw, yeah ♪
♪ You know you got it, child
If it makes you feel good ♪
♪ You're out on the street lookin' good ♪
♪ Baby deep down in your heart
I guess you know that it ain't right ♪
♪ Never, never, never, never
Hear me when I cry at, at night ♪
♪ Honey, I'm cryin' all the time ♪
♪ But each time I tell myself that I
Can't stand the pain ♪
♪ When you hold me in your arms
I'm singin' once again ♪
♪ Won't you just come on, come on ♪
♪ Come on, come on and take it ♪
♪ Take another little piece
of my heart now, baby ♪
- ♪ Oh, oh, break it ♪
- ♪ Break another little bit of my heart, darling, yeah ♪
- ♪ Oh, oh, have a ♪
- ♪ Have another little bit of my heart now, baby ♪
♪ Aw, yeah ♪
♪ You know you got it, child
If it makes you feel good ♪
♪ Feel good 7
♪ I need you to come on, come on ♪
♪ Come on, come on and take it ♪
♪ Take another little piece
of my heart now, baby ♪
- ♪ Oh, oh, break it ♪
- ♪ Break another little bit of my heart, darling, yeah ♪
- ♪ Oh, oh, have a ♪
- ♪ Have another little bit of my heart now, baby ♪
♪ You know you got it ♪
- ♪ Waah, yeah, take it ♪
- ♪ Take it ♪
♪ Take another little piece
of my heart now, baby ♪
- ♪ Oh, oh, break it ♪
- ♪ Break another little bit of my heart, darling, yeah ♪
- ♪ Oh, oh, have a ♪
- ♪ Have another little bit of my heart now, baby ♪
♪ You know you got it, child
If it makes you feel good ♪
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::