Use it on me.
This is all I got here.
Please, please.
It feels so good when you do it.
Douse it.
Hurry.
My father was right.
The devil is in all of us.
My father preaches on weekends
around the county.
He never met a person he didn't believe
had a sinner inside them.
Oh, it must have been
great fun growing up with that.
Guilty before you're even tried.
If he could see me here with you...
Men like that would rather be proven right
than anything else on Earth.
You know, my father
is as devout as they come.
He prays, quotes scripture,
never misses a Sunday.
He's also a drunkard.
A mean, violent son of a bitch.
After the war, he slaughtered Indians
in the Colorado territory for a living.
He believes the former forgives the latter.
I believe the latter's all that matters.
That's the devil your father
should be speaking of.
Sex, pleasure,
immodesty,
us here now,
this is no sin.
Will you be there on Judgment Day
to make my case, then?
God's not watching.
He's too busy not saving sick children
and letting people starve.
But if He does exist, He's the one
that should be doing the atoning, not you.
Don't say things like that.
You're here with me now.
Do you want to be or not?
I do.
Good.
Good morning, Nurse Elkins.
Good morning.
There's a new exhibit
at the Metropolitan Museum
that I think you might like.
I didn't know if you had
any plans for this weekend,
but I've really enjoyed our time together.
And I promise there'll be none
of these lurid, naked
French Polynesian women...
Nurse Elkins. Dr. Chickering.
- Good morning, Doctor.
- Doctor.
There'll be none of these lurid,
naked French Polynesian women
that they showed last year.
Strictly lily ponds and seascapes and the like.
I think the curators have
duly learned their lessons.
Why is there no cocaine?
Because of the war in the Philippines.
The guerillas have started
attacking our cargo ships.
Some have been sunk,
many have been not able to pass.
There are shortages of all sorts
from chestnuts from Malay,
teakwood from Siam,
-coca leaves from Java.
-I'm not interested in chestnuts
or Siamese teakwood.
We're a hospital. We need cocaine to exist.
Well, then our existence is in doubt
because we used the last of it yesterday.
-Good morning.
-Good morning, Doctor.
Dr. Thackery, a few final questions
about our hernia paper presentation.
Fine, just bring it to my office
after the board meeting.
Excuse me.
That’s unacceptable.
How can they refuse to pay?
They’re our insurer.
Don't they know
how this will affect us financially?
Our insurance is for
flood damage and fire protection.
The riots would have had to
fall into one of those categories
or be an act of God.
And an act
of godless doesn't qualify.
Then what are we paying
$35 a year in insurance premiums for?
Had there been a flood or a fire...
Seems we'd have been better
off putting a torch to the place ourselves.
It certainly would make it easier to walk away
from this wretched building.
I say we explore it.
Burn down the hospital?
Is that legal?
I was referring
to a move uptown
to a more hospitable location, Monsignor.
The riots were unfortunate, but...
They were a damned disgrace.
Attacked by the very people to whom
we practically give our services away for free.
Is there any more proof needed
that it's time to abandon this place?
Perhaps if we better understood
our losses, Mr. Barrow.
Yes...
I have compiled a partial list
of what was damaged by the hooligans.
Nineteen windows, $3 each.
Seven lab kits, $4 each.
One upright cabinet, $2.10.
One long cabinet, $5.40.
One medium-length cabinet, $2.20...
And the list goes on and on.
What about the drugs?
Drugs.
We're out of cocaine.
We're aware, Doctor.
It's a vital anesthetic. Our patients need it.
Barrow?
Short of launching a ship
and stopping the attacks,
there's little we can do.
There must be some supplies of it in the city.
I mean, it's your product.
You're only too happy to sell it to us.
Now we can't even get a lick of it.
There's just none to be had.
Someone must have some.
We supply all the hospitals, so I assure you,
they're all out or critically low.
We can't make the drug without the leaves,
and we don't have the leaves.
We haven't made or shipped a bottle in weeks.
So there are no stores of it?
-No supplies of any kind?
-Whatever there was has been exhausted.
Nothing for the beverage makers,
the elixir chemists,
physicians or pharmacists.
For the foreseeable future, all institutions
are going to have to work without cocaine.
What is it?
That cow Mallon petitioned a judge
to get herself removed from quarantine.
-He's gonna hear it.
-Why?
The tests proved
she was a carrier for typhoid.
She needs to be kept away.
Well, she got herself a lawyer to claim
that she's been imprisoned
without due process.
Hearing's on Tuesday.
Maybe we can get her
to make some peach melba for the judge.
See what happens.
Yes?
I found them for you.
I have three, but I wanted
to save one for us to share.
Come in.
Ah. Good. Dr. Edwards.
Thanks for your help, Nurse Elkins.
Greatly appreciated.
Most of the changes I made
are to the postoperative care section.
It's a good paper.
I only wish I were allowed in to hear it.
-Are you all right?
-Fine.
What time is the conference?
-At 3:00.
-Great.
I'll let you know how it goes.
She's beautiful.
And very healthy.
That combination can only mean
she's of Irish stock.
And you think she's about six months?
Give or take.
We named her Elisha.
And we've been going
by her middle name, Grace.
But you and Eleanor
should make her your own.
I'm sure you have ones in mind.
No, Grace is perfect.
Let's hope Eleanor falls for her
as quickly as I have.
Gentlemen,
welcome to the 83rd meeting
of the Metropolitan Surgical Society.
In past years, we have been privileged to learn
of so many new, groundbreaking discoveries,
and I'm certain that this quarter's gathering
will be no exception.
I want to remind you all
that nominations for the Thessler honoree
for breakthroughs in nephrology
are due by the end of this month.
Our treasurer tells me that
we have a surplus of $22.07
in the general fund,
most of which will be put toward
our much-needed chimney repair.
A reminder. We will be sitting
for the annual photograph
directly following today's reception.
My coauthor Dr. Edwards and I
rebuild the canal's posterior wall
using a three-layer repair
approximating the medial tissues.
The transversalis fascia,
the transversus abdominis muscle,
and the internal oblique muscle
to the edge of the inguinal ligament.
Once the wall is created,
we suture the external oblique aponeurosis,
thus recreating the canal
and the external inguinal ring.
Now, failure rates for previous procedures
ranged from 30 to 50%.
In our admittedly small sample,
the Thackery-Edwards method
has a re-herniation rate of only 2%,
and that is due to a patient not following
proper postoperative instructions.
Our full paper will be available to you all,
and we believe you'll have
great success with this new procedure,
as it is probably the biggest advance
in inguinal hernia surgery
in the last 100 years.
Thank you, Dr. Thackery.
Once again, you've come and impressed.
Would you be willing to take any questions?
No.
Very well.
Our next presenter has recently arrived
with great fanfare from
the University of Chicago,
lured here by none other than the esteemed
Jacob Schiff of Kuhn & Loeb,
to continue his groundbreaking surgical work
at Mount Sinai Jews' Hospital,
Dr. Levi Zinberg.
I'm always nervous when it's mentioned
that I was persuaded to come
to New York by a banker.
Even my 10-year-old son
asked if I was brought here
to surgically remove people's
wallets from their pockets.
Cutting people open is what we surgeons do.
But often we haven't any idea
if the site of the incision
is even remotely correct.
The stone we are seeking
may be nowhere near our first cut.
We might believe there is esophageal trouble,
but until we lay the patient open
and invade him,
well, we have no idea if we are correct.
The pain and suffering
caused by our indiscriminate scalpels
is great indeed.
And I have endeavored to change that,
With this.
This
is the Illuminating Intrascope.
Now, you may wonder
why I didn't name my invention
after myself, as so many other surgeons do.
But the reality is that
anything named after a Zinberg
will always be at the end of the book.
With this device,
I can make a small incision,
place the Intrascope into the wound,
turn on its built-in light source,
and actually see inside the human body.
If the patient is
sufficiently relaxed with opium,
the Intrascope can be placed
down a patient's throat
to observe the esophagus or larynx.
Through an incision,
it could be placed near a broken bone
or in the urinary tract.
Or even to probe the intestines.
Gentlemen,
we are healers.
And the fewer incisions we make,
the better our patients will heal.
With my Intrascope,
we can stop being butchers
and start truly being surgeons.
Dr. Thackery.
I'm sorry I wasn't able to introduce myself
before the proceedings began.
Oh, I think you introduced yourself
quite well during them.
Thank you. Levi Zinberg.
And you must either be
Gallinger or Chickering.
By the age, I'd say Gallinger.
-Yes, Everett Gallinger.
-Dr. Chickering Jr.
You've been doing your homework
on the competition.
Nonsense. We're all in this together.
Your team is well-known throughout the city.
I'm eager to read your hernia paper
and put that discovery into practice.
And I'm eager to own
one of your magic scopes,
as I'm sure everyone here is.
Yes, well, it'll be a while
before we reach that point.
But now that people know of its existence,
I hope others will quickly surpass me.
I've never hoped that in my life.
I am presenting my new previa procedure
at the next meeting.
I see you're also on the list of speakers.
May I ask what it is you'll be presenting?
I'd rather not say.
It was nice meeting you all.
He'd rather not say.
-Can he do that?
-He just did.
I suppose we're not as
"all in this together" as he claims.
The arrogance is astonishing.
Rest assured that this will be the last time
you were ever outshined by a Jew.
I must be going.
Sister Harriet is meeting me
to bring home a little surprise to Eleanor.
We will drink a toast to your new family.
Cheers. I'm starving.
-Is there no food again?
-Through there.
-Oh, good.
-Scotch.
Thank you.
Dr. Thackery.
Dr. Chickering.
I was hoping for a word.
But by the looks of you,
an examination might be more in order.
Are you unwell? Your color is terrible.
Just a bit too much work.
You wanted to speak about Bertie, I presume.
About Bertram Jr. Yes.
You wish to commend me for
my excellent mentorship of the young man
and to show your gratitude
for the influence I've had on him.
You have to let him go.
The boy is in your thrall. It's no good for him.
-You need to send him off.
-To what?
There's nothing out there that compares
to what I'm giving him.
It's what you're taking from him
that is at issue.
He's free to go anytime he wishes.
I hold no special power over him.
You hold enormous power. He worships you.
-And that carnival you run.
-Circus.
Where his former surgical chief
put a gun in his mouth and pulled the trigger.
It was his temple, actually.
It was over a procedure
that your son helped me conquer.
A procedure that will save thousands of lives.
There are
good surgeons everywhere.
Let him learn from one of them.
Good is not enough.
Good does not change the world.
But it can change his life.
He can get married, have a family
and an excellent, lucrative practice
away from the tumult of The Knick.
If the goal is money or ease,
then, yes, I agree with you.
But I assumed our job was to heal
and to save lives.
You are aware how false
any sanctimony is coming from you, correct?
Of course.
Perhaps with a word from both of us,
we could place Bertram
with someone like Dr. Zinberg.
I knew you disliked me,
but until now, I had no idea how much.
You would prefer your son to work
at the Jewish hospital instead of with me?
I would take him working
for the Tsar over you.
Dr. Chickering, your son is very talented.
I've invested a lot of time and energy into him,
and I am telling you,
he possesses real greatness.
Whatever you have invested in the boy,
I can assure you, I have infinitely more.
Good afternoon.
Good evening, dear.
I didn't know
you were bringing a guest.
I would have tidied up.
That's quite all right.
I won't be staying long.
This is Grace.
She's a healthy six-month-old baby
abandoned at The Knick.
Oh, the poor thing.
Are you out for a walk with her?
No, dear.
Sister Harriet is bringing Grace to us.
- To us?
- Mmm.
Grace will be our daughter.
Oh, no. I can't.
This could be exactly what we need.
I won't do that to Lillian.
Lillian is gone.
And we can't bring her back.
We must begin to look forward.
Isn't that right, Sister?
God has placed this child here for a reason.
No, God has cursed us.
We have proven we are incapable
of caring for a child.
And I won't be responsible
for the death of another.
Please, take the baby out of here
before we infect it.
-Eleanor.
-Go!
Now!
Of course. I'm sorry, Mrs. Gallinger.
Harriet.
- Give it to me.
- What are you doing?
Give it to me. Give it to me.
Come here. Come here.
-Look at her.
-Get it away.
-Look at her!
-I can't.
She needs a mother.
Stop, Everett. Please.
Thank you, Jesse, but I'm gonna stay
and work for seven more hours.
Of course. I'll be here waiting, then.
No, don't be silly. It might be late.
You should go home
and I'll find my own way back.
Find your own way, ma'am?
I'll be fine here. You take your time.
No, please. I insist.
-You can head back.
-Yes, ma'am.
I'll see you at the house.
Diggs Hotel, 26th and 6th Avenue.
I'm not sure a woman like you
should have any business in a place like that.
And I'm quite sure
you have no business questioning me.
Now, please.
I said, you know,
"You're gonna have to pay that rent for us."
You know where she is?
You seem to be working late a lot
these past few weeks.
When I'm not out of the house for evenings
at the opera, the ballet, and, apparently,
even a symposium at the
Natural History Museum on dinosaur bones,
which I'm sure would have been fascinating.
It's impossible to keep you at home
at night at all anymore.
I just can't help myself.
I yearn for culture
and thirst for entertainment.
You seem very passionate about it.
lam.
I hope I can continue to keep
your curiosities satisfied.
Based on experience,
I have no doubt you will.
Aren't you scared of what we're doing?
I'm only scared we won't be able to stop.
Could you pass that vial, please?
Are we gonna do it again?
So soon?
No, I have some work to do downstairs.
You're shaking.
Let me do it.
Thank you.
May I come in?
I couldn't sleep.
Would you like me to make you a cup of tea?
-John?
-What?
I just thought you might like a cup of tea.
No, thank you.
Will you please put that back?
I think I'll go home.
Fine.
You're in early this morning.
I couldn't sleep.
I'm sorry to hear that.
What kept you up?
Maybe I can help.
It's nothing you need to worry about.
You're right, I don't need to worry about it,
but that doesn't prevent me
from worrying about it, however.
Bertie, could you come
and see me in my office?
Of course.
-Morning, Nurse Elkins.
-Good morning, Doctor.
I'll write you a
prescription for a large, hot cup of coffee.
You're very sweet.
You look worse this morning
than you did at the conference.
I might have a touch of something.
I've reworked our previa papers.
I thought you were happy with it.
I was until I saw what Zinberg presented.
We can't be outdone by him.
We are at the forefront
of discovery and technique.
Everything we do.
Everything, even the words we put on paper
must be above and beyond expectation.
This is gonna make you, Bertie.
Now, your father
will have a hard time arguing with that.
Yes, he will.
Is this the final draft before we print?
Well, I don't see how
we can make that any better.
I'm due back on the ward.
Just take your time.
Now, the Roosevelts’ hospital’s
got their hands on some of the drug.
But the Hospital for the Ruptured
and Crippled does, too,
thanks to Mr. Frick.
I wanted to give you the opportunity
to do the same for us.
It seems I've had more
than my fair share of opportunities recently.
The electrification, the new x-ray machine,
covering the cost of cleaning up
after the recent riots.
For which we are eternally grateful.
It's not writing a check that irks me.
It's the unceasing assumption
that I always will.
I have done more than my fair share recently,
and you have come back to the well
one too many times,
Mr. Barrow.
If I seem presumptuous,
it is only because I have never met a man
who's shown greater generosity
than you have toward us.
And I will again, but today is not that day.
Those ships that are going down,
those are my ships.
That's my cargo.
Those are my customers who are demanding
I pay them for their losses.
Two ships at the bottom of the sea already,
another limping to the dock in Saipan.
I am supposed to be making money
on this war, not losing it.
And I understand that the well is dry...
The well is far from dry.
It's simply you're the man with the bucket
about whom I am least concerned right now.
It is only a few thousand dollars.
Then you should have no trouble
finding it elsewhere.
Mr. Tuttle, age 52.
No alcoholism or syphilis.
Swelling in his right jaw
began approximately five weeks ago.
And just prior to that,
Mr. Tuttle had two teeth extracted.
And you believe they're linked.
It would appear so.
Swelling in the jaw has increased slowly
and if you feel the location,
the edges are quite hard.
Conclusion?
Actinomycosis.
Not uncommon in the wake of dental surgery.
- Treatment so far?
- Iodide of potassium.
Ninety grains three times a day for two weeks.
I think it's time
we go in and remove the mass.
Will someone please shut that man up?
You were saying?
I believe
it's too soon to operate.
I'd agree
if there had been any improvements.
But quite to the contrary,
Mr. Tuttle's mass seems to have grown larger.
Well, let's prepare him for surgery.
Both of you assisting.
- Are you feeling all right?
- I'm fine!
Now if everyone would
just stop asking me that
and just take care of the people here
who are actually ill.
I'm sorry about that, Mr. Tuttle,
and promise we will take
excellent care of you.
He's brusque,
but he's a fine surgeon.
As long as it isn't you doing it,
he can yell all he wants.
You do such a wonderful job
aiding Sister Harriet
with her work for the children
of this blighted city.
But you can understand
that the rest of our hospital
is in need of the Lord's help as well.
Of course, Mr. Barrow.
Our concern is always for everyone in need.
We treat so many of your people.
Italians.
Spanish. Polacks.
And the Irish.
Regardless of the cost,
we would never turn them away.
It's a godly thing you're doing.
I feel it every day, Archbishop.
But now,
we need supplies in a hurry
and we just don't have the funds.
Well, with a half-million wretched immigrants
coming into this city each year,
the pinch is on everywhere.
It's a bind we understand completely.
I knew you would.
We fund so many
Catholic hospitals of our own,
do work in the poor neighborhoods
with the immigrants,
that the drain is enormous.
So much so that we really
have nothing left to give.
I'm sorry, Mr. Barrow,
the Church can't spare another penny.
More tea?
No.
Thank you.
Surely Dr. Thackery or Dr. Gallinger
could have come to the hearing in your place.
I did many of the tests
involved with Miss Mallon,
so Thack thought... Well, Dr. Thackery
thought I should be the one
to represent the hospital.
He's giving me more and more responsibility.
How is the previa paper coming?
Still being worked on.
Bertram, I'd like you to reconsider my offer.
You can join my practice
and I can guarantee you
an excellent starting salary.
Father, I don't want to be disrespectful...
Well, if not me, then what about Dr. Zinberg?
He said he'd meet with you.
He's a fine man at a very good hospital.
Well, I already have all of that at The Knick.
And there's something else there
that would make for a very rewarding life.
I'm in love with a girl there.
Really?
-Nurse Lucy Elkins.
-A nurse.
Yes, we've been out several times.
She understands the life of a physician
better than anyone.
In love.
Bertram, that is wonderful to hear.
I look forward to meeting the girl.
But if you wed,
she won't be a nurse much longer,
so you won't be able to use her as an excuse
to keep you tethered to The Knick.
My offer will be difficult to refuse.
I should head inside now.
Miss Mallon
has committed no crime.
She's been tried in no court
and has had no due process under the law.
On the word of a few crusaders,
she's been shut up in quarantine
in a tiny cabin
on North Brother Island against her will
with the sick and the dying and the diseased,
of which she's none of those things.
She wants her freedom.
And I'm here to make certain that she gets it.
Miss Mallon,
would you take the stand, please?
Place your hand here, please.
Do you swear to tell the truth, the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth, so help you God?
-I do.
-I'd toss out that Bible if I were you.
-Your Honor.
-Inspector Speight, please.
Miss Mallon, can you tell me
how you came to be at this hearing today?
I was kidnapped.
Not for ransom, but I was attacked.
Taken from me job
and shut away by these awful people
who think I'm some sort of monster.
A devil. Those people.
Maligning me in the papers.
Calling me Typhoid Mary.
I didn't get no one sick
'cause I was never sick me-self.
Me lawyer, Mr. Bakerman,
told me all about that habeas corpus
you got in the law.
Produce a body, that says.
Well, here's me body.
And it's not got any disease.
I've never felt better.
Look at me. I'm in the pink.
No cough, no cold, no fever.
Sick people get sick.
Do I look sick to you?
Not a bit, Miss Mallon.
Hey, excuse me. Hey.
Two of you are fired.
Well, Which two?
You for insubordination.
So don't expect to be paid for the week.
We run a respectable business.
Thank you very much.
Your Honor, simply because Miss Mallon
isn't showing signs of the disease,
it doesn't mean that she doesn't have it
or that she can't give it to other people.
Her presence in
all of the homes and businesses
where the health inspector
found out that she had worked
produced at least 18 cases of typhoid fever
and several verified deaths.
- That's hogwash.
- Miss Mallon.
Dr. Chickering,
how many other documented cases
like Miss Mallon's with no symptoms?
Admittedly, Miss Mallon is
the first asymptomatic case
of a disease we've ever found.
We were previously unaware
that something like this could exist.
But, Your Honor, you must understand
that even though Miss Mallon feels fine,
she still carries the disease
for others to catch.
Her bowel movements
contained a pure culture of bacillus typhi.
She has the disease.
How many tests were done?
She has had one a week
for the last four months,
so that's 16 in total.
You should ask him
how many of those tests
didn't have the disease in them.
Miss Mallon, please.
How many, Dr. Chickering?
There were five instances where the disease
was not found in a sample.
Well, it makes one
wonder if it is your test
that might be ill and not Miss Mallon.
Though the fact that she has been
on North Brother Island
in close contact with so many
other patients with typhoid fever
and her health hasn't changed is more proof
for the fact that she has the disease,
but is impervious to its symptoms.
Perhaps it's proof of the opposite.
Perhaps Miss Mallon is
as healthy as a horse and simply immune.
And perhaps if you had gone to
medical school instead of law school,
you would have some idea
of what you were talking about.
You can step down now, Doctor.
It's times like this I wish I drank.
I'm sorry I lost my composure.
-It's not why we lost.
-The man is a fool.
It took 5,000 years for people to understand
that germs can make a body sick.
It's gonna take some time
for them to figure out
that they can exist and not.
Mmm. Sweet freedom!
-Go fuck yourselves.
-Go wash yourself.
At least your fucking hand
and your fetid ass when you take a shit,
so you don't kill someone
with your shit-filled cooking!
My apologies, Miss Robertson.
Oh! Don't apologize to me.
She's the filthy gash.
The gallery should take note that the abscess
is located
near the mental foramen.
I am going to curette the area
and possibly
remove some bone from the jaw.
There's quite
a bit of pus in there.
This tissue is hard as gristle.
Perhaps it makes more sense
to cut posteriorly...
No, this is fine.
It is critical not to puncture the mass
during the removal.
If the...
If the... What is it?
- It's the ray fungus.
- The ray fungus
is allowed to escape...
Thack, you all right?
Do you need assistance?
I have a bit of a headache.
Would you excuse me?
Where are you going?
Dowels, needle, and silk.
Nurse Elkins.
Nurse Elkins, dowels, needle,
and silk, please.
Quickly, thank you.
Hello?
Eleanor?
-What are you doing?
-It's cold.
I'm knitting a hat for Lillian.
Grace hasn't been changed all day.
Who hasn't?
Do you have references?
Oh, I certainly do, yes.
Is this your married name
on your application?
Yes, it's right there. Corinne La Mere.
Well, as long as it's not "La Mary,"
you should be fine.
I don't understand, ma'am.
Oh, I'm sorry.
There was an outbreak, a woman named Mary.
-It was in all the papers.
-Oh, I don't read the papers, ma'am.
Do you think you'll be able
to place me somewhere soon?
I miss the kitchen, and I could use a wage.
I'm sure I'll have no problem
finding you something good.
I Will add this to your bill.
If I'd have known you were gonna charge me,
I would have gone back to sleep
and let you choke.
I would not have died.
Nothing can kill me.
Of course not.
You're healing nicely.
I will not forget what you did for me.
You will always have a friend in Wu.
-I pack you a bowl, honey?
-Three.
Price is a lot now.
Wu making everyone pay first now,
even you.
Or no more opium from China.
-Lots of problems.
-But you have it?
Yes, still have.
-I lie with you, too?
-No.
I want to go out and stay out.
If I wake up,
you shove this pipe in my mouth
and you fire it up again and again and again.
You do want to wake up sometime,
right, Johnny?