-[beeping]
-[door opens]
[Cooper] We'll be safe here for the night.
[scoffs] Holy shit, Coop.
How did you afford this?
Thought I'd splurge.
[chuckles]
[smacks lips]
You wanna take a shower?
I'll watch the door.
Yeah. Yeah, thanks.
[sirens wailing in distance]
Mmm.
God, I fucking love room service.
-Who doesn't?
-Mmm.
[chuckles]
Should have married you
when I had the chance.
Look, I got this, okay?
Captain Coop has it all figured out.
[chuckling] Captain Coop?
Captain Coop.
Right. Well, I'm not some kind of
distressed damsel, all right?
Understood.
Okay, I'm gonna go take a lie-down.
All this espionage stuff's
kind of exhausting.
[sucks teeth]
Um…
Do you want me to…
Oh, take the bigger one.
Thank you, by the way.
It's… It's a lot of crazy,
and I don't really know what I'd be doing
if you weren't here, so…
Of course.
I love you.
[inhales shakily]
There, I said it.
But I do. I… I love you, Cooper.
[rhythmic beeping]
[Meyer whispering] Hail Mary,
full of grace, the Lord is with thee.
Blessed art thou amongst women
and blessed is the fruit
of thy womb, Jesus.
Holy Mary, Mother of God,
pray for us sinners,
now and at the hour of our death.
Hail Mary, full of grace,
the Lord is with thee.
-Blessed art thou amongst women…
-[loud beeping]
-[steady beep]
-[gasps]
Let go.
Joey, Joey, it's okay. Daddy's here.
It's gonna be okay. Just let go.
[nurse] Excuse me, sir.
You need to step back.
-[nurses clamor]
-It's okay.
[sobbing] It's okay. It's okay.
[gasping] What the fuck? I stepped out
for, like, two minutes…
Stop. Stop the compressions.
You're gonna break her ribs again.
-Juliana, it's okay.
-Just let go of me. Where were you?
You didn't wake up? Were you asleep?
-Get… [breathes heavily]
-[beeping]
[doctor] The patient's stabilized.
[breathing heavily] Oh.
Oh, thank God.
[breathes shakily] Thank God. Thank God.
There you are. There you are.
-Yeah, it's good. [sobbing]
-[rhythmic beeping]
-I knew you would.
-[wheezes]
[whispering] You're okay.
You're okay. You're okay.
-[Meyer] "Goodnight stars, goodnight air."
-[sighs]
"Goodnight noises everywhere."
The end. This one never gets old.
[rhythmic beeping]
-Dad?
-Hmm?
Can I… make an observation?
Okay.
My room, it looks like a baby lives here.
You'll always be my baby.
But I'm a teenager now, right?
I mean, can I have a room
that doesn't look like a baby lives here?
Maybe some Charli XCX posters.
Uh…
Sure. Okay. That can be arranged.
You got it.
[beeping continues]
[♪ jazz playing]
[Juliana] I'll take the midnight to 4:00.
You take the 4:00 to 8:00, okay?
I have to work tomorrow.
This is the work, Meyer.
This is our life's work.
I need to sleep in the morning.
I'm exhausted.
-I did two double shifts this week.
-Okay.
Okay. Okay. I'll take care of it.
-Sit.
-I'm gonna go check on her.
Sit. We need to talk.
Okay.
The next time
Joey goes into cardiac arrest…
Don't say it.
Meyer, this is not gonna go good for you.
…I want to institute
a do not resuscitate order.
My God. Are you fucking kidding me?
[whispering] She is our daughter.
-There is no cure for progeria.
-[laughs]
She may be 15,
but she has the heart of a 90-year-old.
-No, no, no.
-I have a say in this!
This is no way to live for her.
Or for us.
I never should have fucked you
-or married you.
-[sighs]
-You did this.
-[chuckles] I gave her the disease?
Is that what you're fucking saying,
Juliana?
-How many pills have you had?
-Oh, go fuck yourself.
Your sperm was too old. You were 45,
-degraded, rotten, old.
-My age has nothing to do with this.
-This is a genetic disease, you know that.
-Old, fucking used up, corrupt,
ancient and flawed sperm.
And I was beautiful.
I was 30. I could have had anyone.
But you fell in love with me.
Yeah, my mistake.
I'm not gonna give up.
I'm gonna stay with her till the end.
Naturally, on God's terms.
I'm not gonna pull the plug.
Maybe you were the carrier.
What did you say to me?
-Nothing.
-What did you say?
[grunts]
[laughing]
[crying]
[children clamoring in distance]
[doorbell rings]
Ah, Mr. Williams.
Hi, Byron Forst. Pleasure.
I know, you're confused.
I do not look like I did
on the cover of Time magazine.
We'll get to that.
Right now, I just ask for a moment
of your time and your patience. May I?
We're good.
Lookit, there she is. There she is.
Mrs. Williams.
Byron Forst. Look at you. Wow.
[huffs]
[sighs]
Child's hospital bed
in the living area playroom.
[sighs] That's… That's hard.
I'm heavily involved with
the Make-A-Wish Foundation.
Behind the scenes.
John Cena claims he's fulfilled
the most wishes, but I call bullshit.
[chuckles] It's this guy right here.
Mr. Williams, you are one lucky man.
I mean, all those years in fashion
have really refined
your sense of style and taste.
-[Juliana chuckles]
-You were the features editor
for Elle magazine, am I right?
-Yes.
-Ah, that's right.
Look at this.
The lawman and the fashionista.
It's like a classic American
love story. Let's sit.
What the fuck is this? Who are you?
Oh, someone who's been following
your daughter's case very closely.
Through Make-A-Wish?
Remember? We applied there.
Um, Joey wanted to cook a meal
with the cast of The Bear,
but they couldn't make that happen.
Guys,
I am incredibly inspired by your family.
[Meyer chuckles]
Excuse me?
The life expectancy of such a severe case
of progeria is well under 15 years.
Lonafarnib can be harsh,
but her tolerance
has been nothing short of remarkable.
But ultimately, it's not good.
Our baby is a fighter.
And how many laws did you break
accessing this information?
Mr. and Mrs. Williams,
I am here because I chose your family
for a reason.
I've developed a breakthrough new biotech,
and I believe that your daughter
is the perfect candidate.
We've chased every clinical trial
we can find.
But there just isn't that much out there.
There's no more runway
for Benjamina Button here.
Sir, I'd like you
to leave right now, please.
The Progeria Research Foundation
has spent a measly nine million dollars
since 1999.
That doesn't get you very far.
This kind of mutation
in the LMNA gene can be a fickle beast.
And what I'm offering you
-is not a treatment or a cure.
-[zipper opens]
It's so much more than that.
This young man,
aggressive type 2 spinal muscular atrophy.
This level of severity…
He wouldn't have made it
to his 25th birthday.
-[boy speaking indistinctly]
-[Juliana stammers]
You're seriously suggesting
that's the same person?
The proof of concept is…
staring you right in the face.
Now do you believe you might be
talking to the Byron Forst?
I know. Look, I know. I know.
This all seems crazy.
Like some Dr. Oz special
where some obscure fruit seed
solves all your problems.
-Seems a lot crazier than that.
-Yeah.
Look, if you want me to leave,
I will go right now.
But I'd rather help you and little Joey.
[Juliana breathes heavily]
Let me present you…
[clicks]
…The Beauty.
I believe your family
has earned an early taste
of something that the whole world
is gonna be wanting very soon.
[Juliana breathing heavily] My God.
I don't care what it costs.
We'll sell the house.
Please put us on your list.
Whatever it takes.
Mrs. Williams, I'm almost offended
that you think I would charge you a dime.
I think I've heard enough.
I think, uh…
A drink is in order.
A whiskey man, Mr. Forst?
That's my flavor.
[chuckles]
Not the kind of stuff
you're used to, I'm sure.
-[The Corporation whispering] We got her.
-[Juliana chuckles]
-And you're gonna get her back.
-[Juliana] Right.
She's gonna be all right. I promise.
There you are.
Jesus Christ.
Meyer, what the hell are you doing?
[Meyer] You got a lot of nerve
walking in here.
Using our daughter's name, her affliction.
I have to say, this is so boring.
Your lawman response.
There's been a sudden spike of deaths
of mysterious beautiful people
-all over the world.
-[groans]
My agents are being chased all over.
You wouldn't know anything about that,
would you, Mr. Forst?
-This stuff is killing people.
-That's not true.
I cannot control
the underbelly of humanity.
Look, people misbehave,
they take good things
and they do terrible things with them.
But you need something.
Squash your investigation.
The files, the paper trail.
Call off your agents, your assets.
Get them to shut up
and tell them the case has gone cold.
There's one, in particular,
I would like to deal with personally.
Cooper Madsen. Give him to me.
No questions asked. No search party.
-[scoffs] Come on.
-You have the right to remain silent.
But the request is so simple.
I have eyes on him all the time, 24-7.
They've tried to scare him.
Some juvenile tactics and whatnot.
You know, he's a trenched-in company man.
So, plan B, shit the bed. We could do
some KGB fun, like, poisoning and stuff.
I do love a game of darts.
I have to admit.
But I cannot stomach, nor can I afford,
a public mess or some fake news hysteria.
Not with someone
who I know was gonna fight back.
Not when I'm this close,
and I can taste success
and solidify my legacy.
Help me. Give him to me.
Put him in a secure location.
My people will be there, stealth.
And you'll what? Suddenly, peacefully,
quietly kill him somewhere?
Your beautiful agent
that you lost in Venice, she's back
and infected, and your boy
has her locked up like Rapunzel.
He's trying to pull one over on you.
Hide the truth. Hide the evidence.
This guy's just like everyone else.
He's out for himself.
Are any of these fucking people
more important to you than your daughter?
You make my problems go away right now,
and I'll make your family
whole again, Agent.
But you turn me in,
or you kill me, and poof.
That dream's gone for you.
Don't you wanna look better, Juliana?
Like, feel better?
You're still looking a little wan
after that breast cancer scare last year.
And those pesky problems,
they have a tendency to come back,
but they won't
with my exciting new product.
[breathes shakily]
Ten million dollars a year for life.
A house at a tropical island
with a maid service.
It's all yours.
I've got the accounts right here.
Doses of The Beauty for all of you.
Ten fingers, ten toes.
That was the moment for me,
when my kids were born,
and I felt a sense of relief.
They're here, they're safe,
they're healthy.
And I can't imagine…
how horrifying it must have felt
to have that rug just slowly
pulled out from underneath you
when you look at her for the first time
and you realize that something…
isn't quite right.
And then you're too scared
-to even try again.
-[sobbing]
It isn't fucking fair, is it?
Heroes, Agent Williams…
they do not stand over
their daughter's graves.
They save them.
[cries]
-[announcer speaking indistinctly on TV]
-[Antonio] You got a team?
Fuck football.
I mean, look, old Jeremy,
he would have been a hell of a lineman.
Got feet like a dancing bear. [chuckles]
You sound like my dad.
Your old man wanted you to play?
Begged. [chuckling] Begged.
The shit is, I actually wanted to play.
It's just…
He was such a prick about it and…
-I don't know, I just couldn't do it.
-[sighs]
And you're too soft anyway.
I was. I was overweight. I was sad.
-[TV continues, indistinct]
-[Antonio] Ooh.
Look, that's… You see, look at that hit.
Bro, how could you not love this game?
Dudes pounding each other to dust?
The pearl clutching is all baloney.
To be violent is to be human.
-Is that what you tell yourself?
-Nah, it's what the world tells me.
-[fans cheering on TV]
-Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's go. Let's go, run. Yeah! Yeah, baby!
Look, you like that? I'm telling you,
it's about to be an ass whooping.
I'm about to win that parlay.
No, you know what's crazy?
-What?
-I have not for once thought about no gym.
I ain't think about no workout,
no ab crunch.
The only thing I'm crunching on
is these fries. It's like…
I can eat whatever I want. It's like…
Just don't seem to matter much.
Yeah. I mean,
'cause it doesn't matter.
Metabolism runs high and efficient.
Everything is refreshed
and regulated, like, hourly.
Sounds like a lot of work.
Time for you right now,
it's kind of stopped.
Can we, like, die?
The balcony is over there in the bedroom.
Leap. See what happens.
Splat. That's what.
Big shit. All will kill the new you,
same as the old one.
I swear this shit, like, rewired my brain.
It's got me tripping.
[Antonio] Yeah, well. Clearly not enough.
After watching you fumbling around
with that clit… [chuckles]
…we got some work to do.
Can't have my sidekick being a soft,
clumsy fuck. You know what I'm saying?
[TV continues, indistinct]
What? What? What?
What the fuck? You gonna cry?
No,
sometimes you just sound like those dudes,
like, I used to talk to in the chat room.
All that incel shit is isolating, man,
and lonely, all right?
And I… I wanna be different.
Yo, J.
You're not alone.
I haven't had many friends
in this life either,
and I'd call you one.
Antonio.
Nice to meet you, Antonio.
[whispering] I'm Jeremy.
[normal voice] Now, how the fuck
did you become the one-eyed killer?
Don't get greedy.
Now it's your time to talk.
Hey, it's your time to talk.
You keep asking me shit.
Always asking me shit,
always asking me to trust you.
I ain't no punk. I ain't no sucker.
Nobody made a bigger fool out of me
than my pops.
And I loved the shit out of that man,
hoping it would make him stay.
Motherfucker still left.
You said I reminded you of your son.
This how you treat him?
-[bottle thuds]
-[breathes heavily]
Look,
I knew early on that I wasn't made for
conference rooms and cubicles.
I joined the military at 18.
I worked my way up to Delta Force Captain.
I applied for a spot in Secret Service,
but got denied.
Psych eval spooked them.
Then I wanted to make money.
Sketchy jobs with sketchy people
in sketchy places.
What changed?
[breathing heavily]
Everything.
-Look who's up?
-[baby coos]
[Antonio] Travel the world like I did,
you see some bad bitches.
Audrey, she was the baddest.
Super sperm slipped one past the goalie,
and Nicholas came into the world.
[Nicholas cooing]
[Antonio] And I was naive, I thought maybe
I could balance both worlds.
But being a killer
and a father don't exactly mix.
[tap running]
And I was getting old.
You miss one step in this game,
you get killed.
It's like an athlete, right?
You gotta know when to step away.
I tried to go legit. I made a few calls.
I got into the billionaire flow.
And with my resume, that wasn't difficult.
[Jeremy] Who were you guarding?
Mark Zuckerberg?
I signed a lifelong NDA. I can't say.
I know it was Zuckerberg.
Life was boring.
It was good.
[Jeremy whispering] Zuckerberg.
[sighs] Then came the fucking Furies.
Who?
[Antonio] Socialist, eco terrorist fucks
who don't understand
how the real world works.
[camera shutters click]
And they've been up
every billionaire's ass for years.
A lot of talk and empty threats.
Until one day…
it wasn't.
Mother Earth screams in pain!
Poison, plunder and pillage!
[all clamor]
[distorted voice]
Feel the wrath of the Furies.
[grunting]
[camera shutters click]
[screaming]
It burned over 80% of my body.
It's a miracle I survived.
[rhythmic beeping]
I was looking at a lifetime of surgery
and skin grafts
and just generally being fucked up.
And that asshole billionaire who hired me,
he just cut me a small check,
and he called it a day.
Wasn't enough to sustain my family.
You've been loyal to one
that didn't appreciate you.
I can fix the hellscape that is your face.
But it will come at a cost, my friend.
I need you to stop
those that are hurting me.
-[breathes heavily]
-There, there.
There, there.
[Antonio] He offered me a dose,
a second chance
to live and provide for my family.
Glimpses of the pain remain…
but I was grateful…
to my savior who saved my family.
In exchange, I had to accept
what he called a promotion.
[The Corporation] Wow. Impressive, killer.
This is much better than
the last time I saw you.
[sighs]
But still imperfect.
There are some things that
The Beauty can cure
and other things
that are left up to chance.
How the DNA moves under the instruction
of the new RNA, blah, blah, blah.
We need to iron out some bugs,
and we will.
I'm sorry about the fucked up eye.
But I did make you this really awesome
eye patch thingy.
[Antonio] I had long accepted that
the one thing I was good at was killing.
And it filled me with dark shame,
but this was a no turning back
kind of moment.
OMG. It's so cool.
Better than a real eye socket even.
Mmm.
We're going to do
some great things together.
[Antonio] I knew that given who I was
and who I needed to be to do this job,
it required me
finally letting go of ever being normal.
And being a father
was one of those things.
I killed off that part of me forever.
And my son…
I couldn't let him see what I'd become.
He's the only good thing I ever did.
Do you miss him?
You miss your father?
As fucked up as he was…
yeah.
I do.
I miss him. I wish he were here right now.
Maybe he could…
Maybe he could tell me
how to be a good person.
[sobbing]
Not a perfect person, but a good person.
You know, maybe he could…
[inhales sharply]
…just tell me how I got so lost.
If he hadn't left…
[sniffles]
Can never forget
that this new version of us,
it's all superficial.
-Hey.
-[sniffles]
There's not a thing in this world
that could change a soul.
You can't see 'em yet, but there are
long strings attached to us both.
One of these days,
you're gonna feel a tug.
[phone buzzes]
Story time's over.
It's time to head to NIH
to take care of those pesky agents.
[vehicles passing]
[Cooper] We got one-hour full access
thanks to Meyer.
[Jordan] Why did he ask you
to bring Agent Stone with you?
[Cooper]
Because I might need some assistance.
-Agent Stone.
-[scanner beeps]
NIH has been throwing
everything they have at Manny.
Extensive proprietary testing.
Due to the national security nature
of this virus,
most of the lab data is kept digitally
in a secure room
on an encrypted private server
disconnected from the Internet.
I'll sweep Manny's room and his chart,
and get a fresh tissue sample
while you retrieve the data
off the servers.
Then we can try to understand
what this virus is
and how to stop it before it progresses.
[beeps]
[shutter clicking]
[shutter clicks]
[person knocks on door]
Morning.
[beeping]
[breathing heavily] Come on. Come on.
Any developments? How's he holding up?
If you ask me, it ain't looking too good
for old Manny here.
Why do you say that?
Well, you know,
I've been doing this a long time, so…
I got, like,
a sense of when death is imminent.
You know, chill in the air,
Grim Reaper breezing past.
What else?
The hospital's fucking grim as shit.
[chuckles]
Can't you feel it?
Not really.
-What's with the shades?
-Fucking cataracts. [chuckles]
At my age. Man, can you believe that shit?
But the doctor says
it's barely noticeable.
What do you think, hmm?
[Manny gasps]
[gasping, choking]
-What's up, Jordan?
-[gasps]
That's right. I know exactly who you are
and why you so predictably came here.
Oh, yeah? [breathes heavily] Why is that?
To find out how you were made.
You're comin' with me.
[grunts]
[both grunting]
-[Jeremy grunts]
-[Jordan pants]
Don't fucking move.
[panting]
Where we goin'? Where we goin'?
-[screams]
-Hey, yeah.
[grunts]
-[groaning]
-Got to be more careful.
[choking, straining]
I am kinda lukewarm on these though,
freebies off my buddy Nate. Pfft.
Well, you know him, right?
I mean, I think you do.
I… I left him in your bed.
No, don't do that. Don't do that.
[Manny choking]
I guess my dose was a little low.
The poor fucker is going through it.
-Oh, shit. Yep, there he goes.
-[loud beeping]
Oh, Cooper,
why didn't you just heed my warning?
Picking at a scab
and now we have a goddamn infection.
[beeping continues]
You don't have to do this, you know.
I can help you.
Shut the fuck up.
-Walk. Get in there.
-[grunts]
Sit the fuck down.
Sit the fuck… down.
Do not play with me right now.
[Jordan] You're infected, aren't you?
You have no idea
how much danger you're in.
You wanna start a ruckus in here?
You got all kinds of badges
asking all kinds of questions.
Look, I don't want this headache either,
so let's just be cool, yeah?
Come on.
My man. All right.
I'm gonna fuck you up.
[chuckles]
Quietly.
[both grunting]
[Antonio breathing heavily]
[grunts]
[groans]
[shushes]
[both grunting]
[straining]
[groans]
[grunts]
[both grunting]
[Antonio groaning, straining]
Yeah.
Keep going and she's dead.
[panting] You think I came alone,
dumbass? [chuckles]
-I know you sure as shit didn't.
-Bullshit.
Bet her life on it?
She's down in the server room, right?
My sidekick,
he lacks my theatrical nature,
so he probably hasn't taken her apart
joint by joint,
but if you don't believe me,
let's go see her.
One bruise, one scratch,
I will fucking kill you.
Yeah. [chuckles]
You had us in my apartment. Why wait?
Kill three birds with one stone.
You, your girlfriend, my man Manny.
Worked out perfectly. Keep walking.
That's it.
Nice ass.
J, crack the gate.
Ta-da.
-Hi.
Let's go. Move your ass.
[grunts]
I love you too.
[chuckles]
Sweet. It's cute.
[bangs]
[Juliana] Oh. [sucks teeth]
How is everyone today?
Nervous.
But excited, hopeful.
Great. Well, I'll have you know
-that Joey's procedure has already begun.
-[sighs]
And she's in wonderful hands,
supervised
by pediatric doctors and nurses.
Everything is going well. As expected.
Shall we?
You're lucky.
Because like all great things,
with time and practice comes refinement.
This batch
was just synthesized this morning.
It is our best, most potent series yet.
[Meyer] Hmm.
Who'd like the first poke?
-I'll go.
-Oh, okay.
Great.
Room B.
Any bad reaction, you keep it
away from her, you hear me?
Rest assured we are tested and perfected.
There are no side effects to speak of.
Please.
Hmm.
In about an hour, you'll be
a whole new happy family together again.
I love you.
I love our family.
[breathes shakily]
[Juliana grunts, screams]
[bones cracking]
[gasping]
[screams]
-[Meyer grunts]
-[Juliana pants]
[bones cracking]
[Juliana grunting]
[grunts, screams]
[Juliana screams]
-[new Juliana] Babe?
-Juliana?
[chuckling] Oh, my God.
-What the fuck? [chuckles]
-What the…
-Oh, my God. Look at you.
-Hmm.
-Honey?
-Hmm? Yes?
-We need to go.
-Oh.
Yeah.
[both chuckle]
Wow. Um…
I'd fuck you both. [chuckles]
Shall we?
Mom, Dad, you made it.
-Joey.
-You made it.
-[Juliana] You look so good.
[new Juliana, new Meyer sob]
Happy endings. They get me every time.
[all sobbing]