FLINT: We're fighting
a war to protect Nassau
in which our most
effective weapon
is the fear that we can
instill in our enemies.
Everything is
dependent upon that gold,
and right now it is sitting in a
fort with no guns and full of holes.
You couldn't figure out
how to repair the fort,
so you lured me into capturing
a ship full of slaves to do the job.
TEACH: I wonder if you can help
me locate an old friend of mine.
His name is Charles Vane.
ROGERS: I am to set
sail for the West Indies,
the one element I lack
is someone who
understands Nassau.
If you agree to be that person,
your sentence will be commuted
and the charges
against you released.
Crew of the Walrus, surrender,
and I am authorized
to offer you full,
unqualified pardons.
We're not fighting and
we're not surrendering,
so what are we doing?
We're going that way.
That's a ship killer.
♪
[WIND WHOOSHING]
[NO AUDIO]
[SIGHS]
[WOOD CREAKING]
[DISTANT HISSING]
[ANIMAL GRUNTS SOFTLY]
[WHOOSHING, EXPLOSIONS]
BILLY: Captain.
He's closed the gap.
All hands to quarters.
MAN: Come on, lads.
Rouse yourselves.
Quickly!
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
I've got starboard watch below,
caulking the gunports.
The pumps are keeping
up with the water-line,
but given what's ahead of us,
I don't imagine
that'll last long.
[MEN SHOUTING]
MAN: Heave, lads!
♪
He'll be withdrawing soon.
He'll drive us into the storm,
but he'll want no part of it himself.
Captain, perhaps we could
take the topgallants in now.
If we enter that
storm under full sail,
it may become impossible
to take the canvas in.
If we take at least
some of them now...
If he sees us slow,
if we show him the
least sign of weakness,
it'll only encourage him to
press on and finish the job.
[SAILS FLUTTERING]
But we'll get men into the tops.
Soon as he turns, we'll
shorten sail immediately.
Aye, Captain.
I want crew aloft!
Quick as you can!
Taking and stowing all
that sail will be a challenge.
You'll see to leading
the men in the rig
when the time comes, yes?
Yeah.
I'll pull all hands from below.
We'll need all the
strength we can muster.
[MEN SHOUTING]
[THUNDER CRASHING]
We should have
taken the pardons.
Sign our name, swear to whomever
or whatever the fuck one
swears to on the occasion,
accept the pardons,
then go straight
back to the account.
What the fuck could they do to
us they weren't gonna do anyway?
I don't imagine
Hornigold's offer still stands,
if that's what you're asking.
No, I don't imagine
it does either,
but a few hours ago
when the offer did stand,
perhaps that should
have been a conversation...
Accept the pardons with
full intent not to honor it
rather than face
what we now face.
The men, I understand.
[SOFTLY] Flint had them exactly where he
needed them... Angry, resentful, afraid.
I understand why they would
rather do battle with that storm
than even consider
surrendering to Hornigold.
But he had me there too.
He had me there.
And that is not
supposed to happen.
[EXPLOSIONS]
May I help you?
The governor requests your
presence on the quarterdeck.
You should dress.
You'll have to pardon me.
I've never had a proper
chambermaid before.
Is that how they address
all their employers?
Governor Rogers is my employer.
You are a convict in need of
someone to keep your things clean,
your movement restricted,
and your door shut.
As such, you're the
first daughter of privilege
I have been able to serve
while speaking my mind openly.
I would have thought my
story is well told by now,
but I come from no privilege.
Don't you?
My understanding is that your
father built a criminal enterprise
and you inherited it.
The only difference between you and
the ladies I have served in the past is...
their families had
better lawyers.
Let's not keep the
governor waiting.
ROGERS: The HMS Milford.
150 soldiers, 60 guns.
My lead naval escort.
Uh, behind her, the
HMS Rose. 48 guns.
The HMS Shark, 30 guns,
the Willing Mind. 20 guns.
She's carrying two thirds
of the farming implements
and most of our foodstuffs.
The Buck. 18 guns.
The amount of energy it took
to persuade my
investors to fund this,
it's hard to properly convey.
This fleet, every ship at sea,
every man contracted,
every penny lent.
I am personally
answerable for all of it.
I'm impressed.
Though somehow I don't imagine
that that's what this exercise
is intended to accomplish.
The Gloucestershire.
I wasn't entirely
sure I needed her,
but seeing as it was someone
else's money, I figured it couldn't hurt.
She's the one I can do without.
The moment I believe you are no
longer necessary to this endeavor,
you go on that ship,
that ship turns back for London,
and soon thereafter,
you swing over Wapping.
Except that you can't
actually do any of those things.
No? Why?
'Cause you don't know that Samuel
Wayne has never once paid for a drink.
Because you don't know that the Boyd
brothers can't be in the presence of anyone
from Captain Moulton's crew.
'Cause you don't
know which of the street
merchants is in the pocket
of the brothel madam.
You don't know.
You don't know...
you don't know.
But I do.
To slay Nassau,
you must know her.
And amidst all those ships
and all these men
and all that money,
I am the only one
who can introduce you.
Provided you tell me the truth.
So let us assume those are
now the rules of the game.
I need to know everything
you know of Nassau.
If you withhold,
if you manipulate,
if you lie... you die.
Shall we begin?
- 500 pieces.
- Yes.
You want to withdraw 500
pieces of eight from your share.
That's correct.
You were just here two days ago.
Yes.
To withdraw 500 pieces. It
was dispersed, was it not?
Yes.
- But you're back for more.
- Yes.
What in God's name did you spend
500 pieces on in two days' time?
Oh, I lost it.
Lost it? As in through a wager?
No. "Lost it" as in I had it
in a sack and I put it down,
and when I came
back to pick it up,
it weren't where I put it.
Lost.
- Would you like me to...
- Thank you.
FEATHERSTONE: The crew
has entrusted the captain and I
to watch over the prize
gold and to protect it
in all our interests, yeah?
Now, as your quartermaster
and as your friend,
I feel duty bound to suggest
that you reconsider
withdrawing sums this large
without a better
plan for keeping it
once it's withdrawn, yeah?
Yes.
Good.
Now, is there a lesser amount
you might want to
begin with for today?
Well, 500 pieces.
500 pieces. Why not?
- I need a new sack as well.
- Obviously.
- Yeah.
- [KNOCK AT DOOR]
Yes?
Mr. Featherstone,
may we have the room
for a moment, please?
[WHISTLES]
These are identical.
350 pieces on both sides,
yet one I can fit in
the palm of my hand,
and the other is
currently occupying
the entirety of the
vault beneath your fort.
Which of the two would you
rather have in your possession
the day Spain or England arrives
and sets its eyes on
conquering that fort?
Yeah. I have that.
So I suppose what we ought to do
is ensure that the
fort is not conquerable,
which, as good
fortune would have it,
is what I'm doing.
You cannot truly
believe that is possible.
You know as well as I do
that so long as
that gold is sitting
in the belly of that fort,
we are doubly exposed.
Losing the fort guarantees
the loss of the gold.
Excuse me. What
are you suggesting?
That we exchange it.
As much of it as possible.
Find partners and trade coin
for commodities far easier
to move and to protect.
If Nassau falls, we will
have something to set aside
to ensure our futures.
"Our"? Who?
Mine. And Anne's.
Lovely. Good old Jack gets
buried beneath a pile of rubble
while you two begin a
well-funded life of leisure.
I didn't say that.
It's bad enough the
only time I get to see her
is when she comes here to relay
something that you're displeased with.
Now we're just accepting
that if forced to choose
between a long future with
you and a short one with me...
there's no chance she'll
even consider the latter.
Of course she will choose you.
The fort is going to fall.
Tomorrow. Next week. Someday.
And I do not
believe for a moment
that you are stupid enough
to let yourself be
buried beneath it
when it does.
It will pain her to
leave me behind...
What we have shared
these past few months,
it will be very hard.
But you...
without you, there is no her.
I am here in part to
secure my own future.
I will not apologize for that.
But that is not why I'm asking
you to cooperate with me.
I am asking because though I
know we have our differences,
I know there is
one thing we share.
We both love her.
Let us make sure her
future at least is secure.
[MEN SHOUTING]
MAN: Heave!
- [EXPLOSION]
- [WATER SPLASHES]
♪
Stand ready!
[GRUNTING]
[MEN SHOUTING]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[GRUNTING]
[SHIP GROANING]
[GRUNTS]
[YELLING]
Ah! [GROANS]
You don't need to be doing this.
I can finish it.
I'm useless to 'em up top.
Gotta do my part somehow.
You shouldn't talk
that way, you know.
We got our share of
useless fucks on this crew.
You ain't one.
This is the second time
in the last few months
I'm facing certain death.
And you are again
offering moral support.
Does that mean we're married?
[SOFT LAUGH]
[GROANS]
Don't.
Fuckin' hell.
What part of "let us take care
of you" did you not understand?
If it wasn't for you,
we'd all be planted at the
bottom of the Charles Town bay.
We got a debt for that.
It ain't right not
to let us pay it.
All the shit we been
through the last few months,
do you wanna know what
the most terrifying part
of all of it's been?
"We'll take care of you."
I get it.
Do you?
'Course I do. Look at me.
I know what it's
like to be afraid
of being the one ain't
strong enough to stick.
But it don't work
that way, yeah?
And even if it did,
it wouldn't work
like that for you.
Captain!
We're standing by!
The rig won't hold!
We must break the sails
before we lose the mast!
Take down the course
and the topgallants now!
Now!
Now! Now!
Billy! Get those topgallants up!
Rogelio, is the
halyard running free?!
It's stuck!
It's bound up by the
mast! It's not coming down!
- [WIND WHISTLING]
- [SHIP GROANING]
At first, when my father
left, I only watched.
My guardian, a slave belonging to
my father, ran the operation in his stead.
Eventually, I felt it
was time I stepped in.
How old were you at this point?
I was 17.
How does one persuade an island
full of thieves and murderers
to respect the authority
of a 17-year-old girl?
I identified the one
they were most afraid of
and I threw him off the island.
What was his name?
His name was Edward Teach.
You're getting all of this, yes?
Um...
please. Continue.
He sailed at the
head of a pirate fleet
with a man named
Benjamin Hornigold.
I conspired with Hornigold,
offered him control
of Fort Nassau
to turn against Teach.
Eventually, I isolated him
from all of his former allies
until it was just
him and his protégé,
a young captain he had
groomed in his image,
trained as a peerless fighter.
Had they stayed together,
they might have resisted me.
But the protégé turned?
Yes. And once
he'd sided with me,
Teach had no choice
but to withdraw.
After that, my credibility
with crews on the beach
was in good order.
And the protégé,
what was his name?
His name was Charles Vane.
Leave us, please.
Now.
I need very specific answers
to the following questions.
Ask me what you want to ask me.
Charles Vane sided with you?
Yes.
Betrayed his mentor,
betrayed Edward Teach for you?
Yes.
You were...
I was fucking him.
Where are you going?
To inform the captain
of the Gloucestershire
he's about to head home.
Plus one passenger.
You never asked me.
- I needed to ask?
- I never lied.
I was fully prepared to set foot
on that island and say his name,
say that the universal pardon
had an exception,
put my credibility at risk
based solely on your counsel,
and it was all to
settle a personal feud
with a former lover?
Why did you bring me here?
You know these men's names,
you know the things
they have done.
But I know them.
I know Flint is dangerous,
but he can be reasoned with.
I know Rackham is devious,
but all he cares
about is his legacy.
And because I have
history with Charles Vane,
I know him most of all.
I'm all too aware what
he is capable of destroying
when he sets his mind on it.
I underestimated him
and I lost my father.
The Lord Governor
Ashe underestimated him,
and Charles Town burned.
What is it you would like
to have him take from you?
Why, in God's name,
would I trust you?
Nassau is my father's house.
It is my birthright,
and I am obligated
to see it set right, to see
its monsters driven out.
You don't have to trust me
because we have
mutual self-interest.
And that makes
for better partners.
[GRUNTING]
Captain.
I understand why you are here,
and I understand
why this troubles you.
But they do not understand.
In the interest of getting this
done as quickly as possible,
perhaps it would be better
if all our roles were
more clearly defined.
To avoid unnecessary and
uncomfortable confusion.
TEACH: A man puts a
dead thing in the ground,
he expects it to stay there.
Sometimes it comes back.
I harbored such resentment
in that moment
all those years ago
when you turned
your back on me...
though I sailed countless
leagues with you,
fought countless
battles with you,
taught countless
lessons to you...
and you did it all for a girl.
♪
Good to see you, old friend.
[CHATTER]
For years, I've laid
my head down at night,
and no matter where I was,
there was an odor
would arrive at my nose...
Brine and hides
and pitch and shit.
The perfume of this place.
Across eight years and
as many wives and...
so many distractions.
Oh, then I meet
wife number nine.
And to my surprise, I
stop thinking about Nassau.
The smell goes away.
For almost three weeks.
And then news
comes across my door
that there are no more
Guthries in Nassau.
One dead, the other in chains.
It seemed a sign it
was time I returned.
They're both dead.
Really?
I heard that the spectacle
of Eleanor Guthrie's trial
could go on for months.
They are both dead.
Mm.
What happened between she and I,
our role in forcing
you out of this place,
it's in the past.
So if you returned
looking to gloat
about how it turned out
or looking for some
sort of apology from me,
then you can go fuck yourself.
Forced me out?
Is that the story you've been
telling yourself all this time?
That's how I remember it.
All I remember... A
young man's poor judgment
which forced me to
choose between killing him
and walking away
and letting him live.
Not quite the same thing.
If you think I've been sitting around,
waiting for an apology all this time,
I don't know what to tell you.
Then why are you here?
Whose is that?
What?
Man-of-war out there.
I assume that's the ship Flint
used to sack Charles Town.
It's here and he isn't.
I'm just asking whose it is.
Ours.
So don't get any fuckin' ideas.
Who's "ours"?
I have partners.
In a compact toward the
common defense of this place.
Provide a stipend to
the crews on the beach,
in exchange for their agreement
to follow our lead in battle,
should the need arise
to defend the island.
Mm.
Smells differently
than I remember.
Maybe it's changed, or maybe I've
just been misremembering it all this time.
Let's go. Where?
I'd like to meet these
partners of yours.
- [WIND WHISTLING]
- [MEN SHOUTING]
Get up there! Slack
off the truss lashing!
Get it moving!
Cut it loose if you have to!
[GRUNTING]
[CREAKING]
♪
[RAIN PATTERING]
Keep her steady!
Hold fast, men.
[WIND WHISTLING]
Knockdown!
[SCREAMING]
Whoa! [SCREAMS]
Bub!
[SCREAMS]
[THUNDER CRASHING]
[MEN SCREAMING]
Captain! Captain!
With that topgallant loose,
it'll drive us into the sea!
We must reduce the
windage, or we'll sink.
Give me another block!
[GRUNTS]
Look out!
Gah!
Aah! Aah!
Oh, my fucking leg!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Pull 'em out!
[GRUNTING] Get out!
Come on. Here,
here, take my hand.
[GRUNTING]
[MEN SCREAMING]
[SCREAMING]
Help! Help!
[WIND WHISTLING]
[GROANS]
Hey! Help!
Help!
Help! Help!
[SCREAMS]
[MAN SCREAMS]
[SHIP GROANING]
SILVER: Help! God...!
They say the worst
of it don't last long.
What the water does
to you once it's got you.
It makes you cold,
makes you scared.
It shows you things. Bad things.
But then it warms you.
It settles you.
[GRUNTS] It shows you
the places you've been.
Like the people you've loved.
They're all there
waiting for you.
It doesn't sound so bad.
Fuck.
Come on.
[GRUNTING, BREATHING HEAVILY]
Fuck... [GASPING]
[GRUNTING] Oh, fuck.
Hey! Wait!
Take my... God... God, come on!
[GRUNTING]
Come on, come on, please!
[MUFFLED YELLING]
- Ah, God!
- [SPLASHING]
No. [PANTING]
Fuck!
Aah!
[SOBBING]
Fuck! Fuck!
[BELL RINGS]
- [MUSIC PLAYING]
- [CHATTER]
Found that. At
the inn by the bar.
Oh, I know. Mr. Warren
misplaced it yesterday.
No, that one we found
in the privy yesterday.
This is the new one
he was dispersed today.
Are you certain?
[SIGHS]
Just how fucking stupid,
exactly, are your men?
It's hard to say.
Ah, to a momentous return.
A man of your
ability and experience
will be a most welcome addition
to our ranks.
Jack.
Rackham.
That's my name.
You were the scrawny one...
who was trying so desperately
to join Charles' first crew.
Flint I can understand,
but this is your third partner?
VANE: Jack took the
Urca de Lima prize.
Transported it, secured it.
He's been employing it to
provide for Nassau's defense.
Nassau, as I'm sure you recall,
lacks the will to
form an identity.
It is and always has been
fragments of an idea,
and without identity...
An organized defense?
Near impossible. The stipends...
create an obligation
to follow one command
in the event of a
threat to the island.
Captain Flint, as the island's
most able naval tactician,
would command our
forces on the water,
and Charles would captain
the militia to defend the land.
Why?
Beg your pardon?
Why are you so determined
to defend Nassau?
Because Henry Avery
set his camp here
and said, "This is a
place for free men."
And because you sailed from
here and made this place feared.
Because Henry Jennings
and Benjamin Hornigold
and Sam Bellamy
gave Nassau life.
And you think your
name belongs on that list.
Yes, I understand.
MAN: Captain Teach?
We hear you're
taking on new men.
We'd like to join you.
If you please.
[SCOFFS]
When I was a young
man in this place,
it was a settled notion that in
order to join a crew of any repute,
one had to prove his worth.
Two men, evenly
matched, bare fists,
the only measure of
difference between them
being the measure of their will.
Now all a man need
do is say "please."
You want us to fight
each other for this?
I had such hopes for this place
when I heard the
Guthries had gone.
Thought it had a chance to return to
what it once was, return to that state.
But now I see there's
no hope of that anymore.
You have taken away
the one thing that made
Nassau what it was.
You have given her prosperity.
Strife is good.
Strife makes a man strong.
For if a man is capable
of confronting death daily,
functioning in the face of it,
there's no telling what
else that man can do,
and a man whose
limits cannot be known
is a very hard man
to defeat in battle.
Now I look around me and
I see crews filled with men
who've only ever won a
prize through surrender.
I see captains who ought to
have been deposed months ago
keep their office because
their men are comfortable.
I see decay everywhere.
Now, I returned to go on
the account as I know it.
I returned because in this place
I believed I could find the
men necessary to do so
and, in particular, one
man that I thought worthy
of standing alongside me
at the head of a terrible fleet.
I wonder if he's still here.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [MUSIC PLAYING]
- [CHATTER]
Now, listen.
I am committed to
defending the gold,
the fort, this place,
to preserving it for an age.
I owe that to my partners.
I owe it to myself.
I cannot imagine failure.
But I cannot deny the
potential for it either.
You will organize
the exchanges...
Gold for things of equal value,
yet small and light.
Mr. Featherstone and I
will facilitate moving the gold
from the treasury in secret
to the site of each location.
You will keep it quiet.
Only as many men as it takes
to secure the transactions.
I don't like how
any of this looks,
our scurrying about, stashing
things away in dark places
like fucking rodents
preparing for the winter.
And most critically,
I do not want my partners,
Captains Flint or
Vane, to hear about it.
If either of them
catches wind of this,
shit, I don't know.
Just keep your
mouth shut about it.
What did you say to him?
Tell me the truth.
What did you say to
make him change his mind?
You and I spoke of
what will likely happen
the day England
returns to this place.
We spoke of how I must stay.
Must find a way to
enter into their world,
and I believe you would
want to enter it with me.
I believe that in this moment
you cannot fathom leaving me.
But if we are honest
with each other,
I think we both know...
Stop.
Sooner or later, the
day is going to come
when, no matter our feelings,
the world will demand
that you and I...
[MEN SHOUTING]
We'll be heading into the wind!
Things'll get rougher!
Captain!
There's nothing more to be done.
We should heave
to, ride it out below.
Hornigold knows
our last position.
They'll be patrolling downwind.
The storm'll blow
us right to him.
Head up now... Close as you can.
Captain, this is mad!
Billy, make it so.
You two, man the
starboard braces.
MAN: You heard, man the braces!
[HATCH OPENS]
Hold it. Hold it.
[MEN GRUNTING]
BILLY: Got to close the hatch.
MAN: Close the hatch!
[WIND WHISTLING]
Where's the captain?
[WIND WHISTLING LOUDLY]
- [MEAN CHATTERING]
- [WATER SPLASHING GENTLY]
Not that I anticipate it will
alter your behavior in any way,
but you should know I
do not approve of this.
I know what I'm doing.
Like most of London,
I read your memoir.
Marveled at your
privateering exploits.
It was quite a story.
But I hear things.
Certain details of
your grand voyage,
rash decisions and the
terrible injuries that followed,
the scars of which are...
left out of the pages
of your account.
[SOFT LAUGH]
But perhaps harder
to erase elsewhere.
Were you so confident
then as you are now?
[BELL RINGS]
Captain Hornigold.
Welcome aboard.
Mr. Dufresne.
I have news to relay, sir,
but first, I'm sorry,
I must address a rumor I've
heard since my arrival here,
a rumor most troubling
about a fugitive
that you've made a
part of your endeavor.
Jesus.
I would introduce you,
but, uh, from what I understand,
you're quite familiar
with one another.
Respectfully, that
woman is not to be trusted.
I know,
but perhaps I don't
need to trust her.
And, by way of context,
I don't much trust you either.
Let's assume you'll each
be a check on the other,
and I'll count myself fortunate.
What news, Captain?
I engaged Captain
Flint as promised.
When he and his crew
declined my offer of pardons,
I pressed my advantage
and drove him,
already battered,
into a tempest.
When it subsided, I
patrolled the area extensively
and recovered several
pieces of fresh debris.
Debris? What kind of debris?
The definitive kind.
Captain Flint is dead.
[WOOD CREAKING]
[NO AUDIO]
♪
[GASPS]
[MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
We're not moving.
Where are we?
The storm drove us east
into the Sargasso Sea.
We are becalmed.
Stores?
Most of the fresh water
was lost in the
flooding in the storm.
The food that could be salvaged,
we have a few days.
Maybe a week.
How far to the nearest coast?
At our current speed?
About three times that.
SILVER: Unless the
wind returns soon...
we won't survive this.