How lovely. Thank you, Joy.
Sorry.
It will... calm you.
No, thank you.
David?
Why did you do it?!
Why did you have to kill him?!
Nail file. Scent bottle.
Lip brush. Sixpence in copper.
Powder compact.
One .38 revolver and six empty
cases, already in custody.
We've just seen the
body of David Blakely
at Hampstead Mortuary.
I understand you know
something about it.
Tell us about how
Blakely ended up dead.
I am guilty.
I'm rather confused.
Hold still!
I've got lippy on, Vicki.
Well, not enough for Morrie.
Perfect. Drinks
on you tonight?
If I get the job.
Knock him dead.
You're a good hostess, Ruthie,
but it's a big step from
hostessing to management.
Not many girls of your...
background make it.
I know, sir, but I will.
A peer of the realm, an actor,
and a travelling salesman
all want a table.
You've got one
left. Who gets it?
Well...
the poshos get a kick out
of being treated like scum.
So you send Lord
Snootybollocks packing.
He'll tell all his mates
and come back for more.
The actor just wants free booze.
So you set him up at the bar,
let everyone get an eyeful,
got yourself a gossip piece
in "The Mirror" the next day.
Now the salesman...
he may look shabby,
but he's got pockets
full of cash.
A few years ago he was
a hero, fighting Nazis.
Now he's flogging
dusters door to door.
You make him feel
like somebody again,
he'll spend everything he's got.
He gets the table.
How's it going
with the new bloke?
He sent me every bouquet from
The Dorchester's florist.
- How'd you meet him, anyway?
- Stephen, obviously.
Of course, that
bone-crunching perv.
He's been good to me.
Could introduce
you to Lord Astor.
He's just got divorced.
- No, thanks.
What you need is a nice, rich
husband, big, posh house.
All you'd have to do is
spank him once a week.
Thank you.
Do you mind?
This is a private conversation.
Shush, I know him
from Carroll's.
Oh.
Erm, er, sorry. I wasn't,
erm, eavesdropping.
It's Miss Ellis?
Yes. Hello.
Er, Desmond Cussen.
This is Vicki Martin. My
children, Andre and Georgina.
Hm.
"The Beano."
I'm more of a
"Magnet" man myself.
Well, I was thinking
that I might
go to Carroll's Club tonight.
Actually, I'm not
working there any more.
Got a new job.
...Er, congratulations.
...Thank you.
It's at the Little Club.
Er, good... Er, goodbye then.
Stephen Ward may be a perv,
but at least he's amusing.
It's, erm... very funny today.
Desmond?
Since I'm celebrating,
you can buy me a drink
later if you like.
That would be lovely.
Shall we?
- Evening, Reggie.
- Evening.
Evening.
The club's reopening
next week, redecorated.
I'll be London's
youngest club manager.
Quite an achievement.
I've been working
since I was 14...
Cinema Cafe, Lyon's
Corner House.
Most of the money went
to my mother. Still does.
It's all I've ever wanted
to do, really... work.
I-I thought, erm, girls
mostly wanted to get married.
Tried that. No, thank you.
And the, erm, the... the
children's, erm... their father?
I'm separated from Georgina's,
and Andre's was
killed in the war.
Hm.
So, you've done all
that on your own.
I've done nothing with my life,
except turn my father's
successful business
into a middling one.
You, on the other hand...
well, you're quite something.
Can I get you another drink?
I'm buying.
Oh! Sorry.
I suppose you're the hostess?
I'll have another gin and tonic.
As a matter of fact,
I'm an old has-been.
Two vermouths, please, and
who is that pompous arse?
Some racing driver.
You set out from home tonight
with a gun in your bag,
and you shot David Blakely.
That is correct.
Blakely was your lover.
Why did you want to kill him?
He hadn't picked me up
when he said he would.
He was drinking
with some friends,
and there was...
some other woman there.
I became very furious.
Where did you get the gun from?
It was given to me as
security in a club.
By whom?
A man. I don't
remember his name.
When was this?
About three years ago.
Mrs. Ellis, when you
put the gun in your bag,
did you intend to
kill Blakely with it?
Yes.
I left Andre at home,
I took the gun, and I got
in a taxi to Hampstead.
Andre... who's that?
My son.
Where's Andre now, Ruth?
Yes? Can I help you?
Detective Inspector Peter Gill.
Andre, the son of Mrs.
Ruth Ellis... where is he?
Here. It's room number five.
Mum?
It's alright, Andre.
Go back to sleep.
Hello?
I can't afford to pay
solicitor's fees, Mr. Bickford.
That's all in hand.
Mrs. Ellis, you have
signed a written statement
admitting your guilt
without any legal advice.
Well, I am guilty.
I've already agreed
to tell the court
I fully intended
to shoot David...
Stop there. Do you
feel quite well?
Have the police
treated you well?
Perfectly.
Ever been in any trouble
with them before?
Certainly not.
Why did you decide...
to do what you did
earlier tonight?
I was in a rage...
at the way David and his
friends were treating me...
laughing at me...
hanging up when I tried to
call, like I was nothing.
You killed him because he
wouldn't answer the phone?
When did you decide you
were going to do this?
Yesterday morning. I
hadn't been able to sleep.
I hadn't been able
to find David.
I suddenly had an overwhelming
and peculiar desire to kill him.
You thought he was
with another woman?
What, you lost control?
No, I saw things clearly
for the first time.
Has a doctor ever
treated you for...
mental instability?
I'm not cuckoo, if
that's what you mean.
No, no, no. Of
course, but it...
it's important that we explore
every possible line of defence.
You don't understand,
Mr. Bickford.
I'm not interested
in any defence.
You have admitted
to a capital crime.
Without mitigation,
without a defence,
any judge would be forced to...
To hang me. Yes.
I chose to do what I
did. I don't regret it.
I don't ask you or anyone
else to plead for my life.
An eye for an eye.
I took David's life.
I don't ask you to save mine.
Just over there
by the piano, Sam.
Lovely.
What do you think? Too much?
I think it's perfect.
Thanks, Jackie.
Almost.
Good evening. Welcome.
Ruth, you look wonderful.
Thank you.
Vicki...
What do you think?
Bloody gorgeous!
- Hello, Cooch.
- Hi.
- Champagne?
- Oh, please.
Champagne each for
the Vicki and Cooch.
I've seen you before.
You look...
different.
I was probably
rather rude to you.
I probably deserved it.
Can I buy you a drink?
I run this place, Mr. Blakely.
Let me get you one.
Well remembered.
I'm very good at my job.
Hm.
It's a little too much tonic.
Perhaps you should
go back to Carroll's.
Most nights I'm at the
Steering Wheel Club, actually.
I'm a...
- Racing driver, I know.
I expect you're waiting
for me to ask you about it.
I travel all over Europe. I
meet a lot of famous people.
You think I should go weak at
the knees for your little hobby.
I was once engaged to a
Canadian Airforce pilot.
Now, flying... that's something.
Not just racing toy cars.
Oh, believe me,
they're not toys.
Who's he? Your boyfriend?
Do you care?
Not particularly.
I think you do.
I think you came here for me.
I'm not taken by this little...
international playboy act.
I think you're a spoiled
brat spending Daddy's money,
and you are too used to
getting your own way.
I do always get my own way.
- This one's on me.
- Thank you.
Ruthie looking
after you alright?
Always.
You need some extra special
looking after, you let her know.
Oh, th-that's not, erm...
Have lunch with me tomorrow.
Gosh, I'm so busy
with the place, I...
You could bring
Andre and Georgina,
and we could do
whatever you want.
Andre has been going
on about the zoo.
The zoo it is.
Erm, I could, er,
pick you up at 10:00?
I haven't been able to
get you out of my mind.
I know.
You've been thinking
about me, too?
About what an arrogant
bastard you are.
It's all an act.
But you know that, don't you?
Because you are, too.
Mr. Bickford! Just in
time for Peter's round.
Have you dusted the
gun for fingerprints?
Whose prints would
we be looking for?
Half a dozen witnesses
saw her shoot Blakely.
Question is, who
gave her the gun?
She claims it was security
for a loan at the Little Club,
that she kept it in a
drawer for three years.
- And?
- We both know that can't possibly be true.
That gun hasn't been
sitting in a drawer.
It's in perfect working
condition. It's oiled.
You're a two-bob brief,
not an arms expert.
I prosecuted war
crimes in Austria.
Believe me, I know guns.
Does anything about this crime
make any sense to you at all?
A young woman with
no previous record,
never even fired a gun.
20 years of policing
have taught me
anyone is capable
of almost anything.
Have you conducted even the
most cursory investigation
into where she
obtained that gun?
What I am investigating is the
murder of an innocent young man.
And what interests me
are the four bullets
that that gun and your
client put into him.
Hey!
You know David went down
after the first shot?
He was on the ground when
she fired the next three.
Point-blank range.
Tell your client to
do the decent thing.
Spare his family a trial.
Ruth Ellis, you
have been charged
with the murder
of David Blakely.
You will appear in this court to
enter a plea in 10 days' time.
Until then, you will
be remanded in custody
at Holloway Women's Prison.
Where did the gun
come from, Ruth?
I told you, security for a loan.
If I'm to defend you, I need
you to be honest with me.
Honest, Mr. Bickford?
My parents had a visit from
a journalist at "The Mirror,"
says his newspaper are paying
my legal fees, your fees.
That's why you turned up
the night I was arrested...
because a tabloid
wants an exclusive.
Someone's put you up to this.
Someone gave you the gun,
and you're protecting them.
This way, Miss.
Look how long your
eyelashes are.
Are you wearing mascara?
I once threw a girl
in Frensham Ponds
for asking me that.
Naughty boy.
You don't know the half of it.
I heard you once drove a
Bentley around the Albert Hall
at 60 miles per hour.
Mm-hmm.
Didn't get caught, though.
I'm late.
Late for what?
Race meeting in Surrey.
Well, you can show me what
all the fuss is about then
with your toy cars.
Hmm?
I'll pack a champagne picnic.
Thank you.
Now, mind your fingers.
Alright, you all in?
Whoo!
It's a twin-cam version
of the 1500 Singer HRC.
Give me that.
Look, we call it "The Emperor."
This car is gonna make my name.
You don't believe me.
Hm.
- The Emperor has arrived.
- Ah, David.
...David, darling.
...Well, how's she running?
Like silk, old boy, like silk.
It's a beautiful day for it, eh?
- Good to see you, David.
- Hi.
Er, this is Clive Gunnell and Anthony Findlater.
- Hello.
Ant's been working
on the car with me.
Well, he's the money,
and I'm the brains.
- Hello.
And this is Carole Findlater.
Carole, Ruth Ellis. Ruth
works at the Little Club.
- Does she now?
- Manages it, actually.
We brought champagne.
- Ah.
- Let's crack it open, shall we?
- Good choice.
So, what did you
think of The Emperor?
Don't tell David, but I
thought it was thrilling.
You're very sweet.
- David! Stop that! Stop! David!
- Watch out.
Are they always like that?
Ant's never entirely
trusted him,
ever since...
Since what?
It's no secret. David
and I had a tendresse.
Oh, an affair, darling...
all very much in the past,
we laugh about it now,
but, well, I'm afraid
Ant never finds it very funny.
Carole, darling, we're off.
You know, I do hope
we see you again.
One never knows with David,
but I'm keeping my fingers
firmly crossed for you.
Coming!
David's being naughty.
I'm so sorry to put
you all through this.
You have to plead insanity.
I was sane when I did it.
I meant to do it. I won't lie.
What about Andre?
It'll be alright,
Mum. It's alright.
He's going to be taken care of.
It's all arranged.
Arranged with
who? Who? Ruthie!
She swears she was
sane when she did it.
And I know my daughter.
Stubborn as a mule
when she wants to be.
What's going to happen to her?
I need something...
to mount some sort of defence.
She won't tell me
where she got the gun.
And her reasons for
wanting Blakely dead
make precious little sense.
You know he knocked her about?
David was violent towards her?
She does pick 'em, our Ruth.
She has a history of
violent relationships?
Her ex-husband, George Ellis...
handy with his fists, too.
I don't know what went wrong.
She was such a...
happy little girl.
Ray of sunshine.
Are you alright, love?
Just get some water.
Muriel?
Is there anything
you can tell me
that might help your sister?
Muriel?
Ruth...
she lost a baby recently.
It was David's.
Stop! Terrible!
Jackie?
Jackie, will you
help Mr. Cussen?
- Come on.
- Yes, of course.
Not good for business...
favouring some punters,
neglecting others.
Go home to your wife, Morris.
Ah, lover boy doesn't
know, does he?
Her rate's 10 quid a night.
Worth every penny.
She asked you to leave.
Piss off, little
Lord Fauntleroy.
You know, I don't think I will.
I think I'll be staying
tonight and tomorrow night.
In fact, I'm moving in,
so there'll be no
more late-night calls
from you or any other
sweaty, old bastards,
unless you want my stepfather
to speak to his good friend,
the commissioner
at Scotland Yard,
and tell him you're
running a brothel.
Clean up the bar downstairs.
It's a bloody state!
Did you mean it?
I want to live with you.
So how many have
you had up here?
How many?
Men.
It's gonna have
to stop, you know?
'Cause I'm not gonna
be able to stand it.
I'm awfully afraid I'm
falling in love with you.
He beat you, didn't he?
"Body covered in large bruises
with the skin broken in places.
Temporary deafness in one ear.
Strangulation bruises on neck.
Recent pregnancy loss,
likely due to blows
to the abdomen."
This is what your
doctor recorded.
Why didn't you tell the police?
They never asked.
You lost a baby
because David beat you.
There are four
defences to murder...
self-defence, insanity,
proof you didn't do it.
But we can't use any of those.
The fourth is provocation.
If David did something
so terrible to you,
it caused you to
temporarily lose control,
that could be a defence.
Get back into bed now!
I didn't lose control.
If you could be honest
about what you've suffered,
if you can gain their sympathy,
then the jury could
recommend mercy.
I won't stand in a
courtroom and beg.
And I didn't kill David
because he beat me.
Why did you kill him?
You wouldn't understand.
You think I'm just a drab,
little man in a suit.
Perhaps I am.
But men like me... we've seen
things you can't imagine...
inconceivable acts of cruelty,
inconceivable suffering,
and always the impulse is
never to speak of it again,
because to speak of
it makes it real.
I know you're lying
about the murder.
You said it was a black cab
dropped you at the Magdala Pub,
but not one cabbie
has come forward.
I've met a lot of
London cabbies,
and they remember who's
in the back of their cars,
especially when they're
blondes all over the papers,
accused of murder.
Right.
That's all, Mr. Bickford.
Mr. Bickford? These
came for Mrs. Ellis.
She's sent these every day.
Mrs. Ellis has been
remanded in Holloway Prison,
charged with murder.
I have been instructed
to act as her solicitor.
I believe you're
a friend of hers.
More than a friend.
Well, I wouldn't say that.
Someone must have helped her.
Someone must have
given her a gun.
Was it you?
I have only her
interests in mind.
It was Desmond Cussen
gave you the gun,
drove you to the Magdala.
He confessed to me.
Wouldn't say much.
He's lying.
- I have to tell the police.
- No.
I'd be struck off. I
could be prosecuted.
I'll plead Not Guilty. That's
what you want, isn't it?
I will let you fight
my case in court.
But his name stays out of it.
I'd be committing a crime,
withholding Cussen's
confession from the police.
I-I could be seen
as an accessory
to murder after the fact.
You'd be committing perjury.
These are my terms.
Well, I can't accept them.
Fine. I never wanted a
lawyer, Mr. Bickford.
I want to plead Guilty.
But you are the one who is so
concerned with saving my life,
though I haven't
quite worked out why.
These terrible things you saw...
...I suppose they
happened in the war?
Was it you who did them?
So, this is all what?
Penance?
I'm sorry I wasn't able
to help you, Mrs. Ellis.
Mr. Bickford, I'll do it.
I'll do the trial your way.
You can use
provocation as defence.
You can go for manslaughter.
If we do this...
you must do everything I ask...
give evidence in
your own defence.
And his name stays out of it.
Knightsbridge 044.
- Jackie, it's Ruth.
- Ruth!
I need to know he's being
taken care of properly.
Who?
David.
What's your real voice?
What?
Your accent.
I know it's not this fake
telephone voice you put on.
Where did you grow up?
We moved around...
Manchester, Basingstoke.
I was born in Rhyl.
Mm-hmm.
I've never met anyone from Rhyl.
Hmm.
Well, we're a very exotic breed.
You're different to
the girls I know.
Carole?
That's all over.
It's you I want...
...and only you.
He won't give you what
you deserve, you know.
He'll never marry you.
Oh, for Christ's sake, who
said anything about marriage?
You could have everything you
want, everything the children want.
You could... You could
be set for life with me.
Desmond, how much have
you had to drink? Come on.
Who you are, what you do...
it doesn't matter to me.
But it does to him.
You don't know that.
I do.
He's engaged.
What is this?
Bugger off home
to bed, old chap.
No, you should leave.
You know you're a joke to her.
I flew Lancasters in the war.
I dropped bombs on
German children.
And for what?
To defend entitled
boys like you,
who take everything
that they want,
and they never give
a second's thought
to the people that they destroy.
Well, sooner or later,
the bill will come in.
Is it true?
It isn't real. It's...
It's for my mother.
For your mother?
Should have known that's
what you were doing here...
hiding from Mummy.
Stop it.
I was right about you...
playing with your toy cars.
Playing at being a man.
'Cause you're not, are you?
You're just a
frightened little boy.
"The Emperor"?
It's you that's the joke.
"Dear Mrs. Blakely.
No doubt these last few days
have been a shock to you."
"The two people I blame for
your son's death and my own
are his so-called
friends, the Findlaters."
"You will not
understand this yet,
but perhaps before
I hang, you will."
I'm so sorry.
"I implore you to forgive
David for living with me,
but we were very much in
love with one another.
Unfortunately, David
was not satisfied
with one woman in his life."
"I shall die loving your son."
"And you should feel content
that his death has been repaid."
It's alright.
"Goodbye.
Ruth Ellis."
It was Desmond Cussen
gave you the gun.
I have to tell the police.
No.
I'd be struck off. I
could be prosecuted.
I will let you fight
my case in court.
But his name stays out of it.
These are my terms.
Ruth Ellis...
you are charged with the
murder of David Blakely.
How do you plead?
Not Guilty.
They've called Desmond Cussen
as a witness for
the prosecution.
The prosecution? What do
they know about Desmond?
I don't know, but when
this goes to trial,
Desmond will be
speaking against you.
Everything he's seen you
suffer, we can't use it,
but it's not too late
to go to the police
and tell them about it.
There is nothing to tell.
There's something you
need to understand, Ruth.
You represent
everything they fear,
and they're going to
try to destroy you.
- "They"?
- The police, newspapers,
even the courts.
An ambitious woman, no
respect for class boundaries,
no respect for
sexual boundaries.
A mother who has, as they see
it, abandoned her children.
You have used everything
to try to advance yourself
at the expense of
everything they value,
and they won't
forgive you for it.
You're going to be on trial
for far more than murder.
And we will need to
use everything we have.
I won't betray anyone.
Well, then I hope to God
we can say the same of him.
It will all come
out at the trial...
what you put her through,
what you made her suffer.
Hey. Why put his family
through a pointless trial?
'Cause I believe she's
not guilty of murder.
You've seen the press here.
You know this'll be the biggest
case of both of our careers.
And I promise you,
I will see her hang.
Why has the Crown called
Desmond Cussen as a witness?
What's he given them?
See you in court.
I chose to do what I
did. I don't regret it.
David.
You are not trying
her for immorality...
but for murder.
He was... violent
on occasions.
Why did nobody
ask about the gun?
It is quite obvious when I shot
him, I intended to kill him.
I know she lied
about how she got it.
I will make him see
who and what you are.
Then you will have my
blood on your hands.
I know you think
you can save me.
Sleep with him again, and I
swear, I'll kill both of you.
She didn't carry out
this crime alone.
My job, my daughter,
my unborn child are all
gone because of him.
He does not get to
walk away. He doesn't!
You've perjured yourself
in the witness box.
You've condemned yourself.
People are on your side,
Ruth. They're getting angry.
What people?
Ellis! Evans! Bentley! Ellis!
You really think you can
take them all on and win?
You never really believed
you could save me, did you?
No matter what anyone
says or does now...
Call the bloody police.
If she isn't hanged
tomorrow, she never will be.
If we make enough
noise, we can stop this.
I don't want to die.