[Ellia coughs]
[Ellia] I don't care
if you've lost your mind,
it's still your job to get me to the lake.
I have not lost my mind,
we are in my mind.
‐I think.
‐[Ellia coughs]
This is the C pill.
It's confrontation.
- Annia, I'm concerned this madness is...
- I am not mad.
We are in a globular cluster.
Okay?
So, you're telling me
you believe that
this is not the real world.
That some other world, your world,
is the true world,
and that I'm confused who I am
as is every other elf, human,
orc, dwarf,
- hobgoblin, wraithling...
- Oh, my fucking God. Don't list them.
The entire world's mad, but you're not.
Is that what you think?
Yes.
The other way around's more likely,
isn't it, Annia?
This is the place that's real.
Someone has cast a spell on you.
And it will wear off soon.
And if it doesn't,
then maybe the Lake of the Clouds
can heal you too.
[birdsong]
[distant voices]
♪ Aww, yup-a-dee, yup-a-dee, dum, ho-ho ♪
♪ What a lovely day ♪
♪ Yup-a-dee, yup-a-dee, dum, ho-ho ♪
♪ The grubs are here to stay ♪
♪ It feels so good to be a grub ♪
♪ So come on in and join the club ♪
- ♪ Yup-a-dee, yup-a-dee ♪
- [lone voice] ♪ What a lovely day... ♪
‐[grub 1] Together! ♪ Yup-a-dee... ♪
‐[grub 2] Shh! Shh!
‐ It's her again.
‐ [grub 1] Oh.
[grub 3] Ah! Right when
I was about to do my solo.
- [grub 2] Don't move. She won't see us.
- [grub 1] Wow.
‐[Annia] I have to get out of here.
‐I don't want to be eaten, guys.
- Go look at someone else!
- Wake up.
- You can't have our delicious protein!
- Come on. Wake me up, wake me up.
Come on, wake up!
[grunts] Wake up!
What?
[Olivia] I lost you there for a second.
What were you thinkin' about?
I ain't slept in a week.
When's this test?
You've gotta stop it
with the all-nighters, Owen.
[thunder rumbling]
Have you ever heard of the Gnostics?
Is that when you're not sure
if God exists, like not quite an atheist?
No.
Jesus' disciples,
they all wrote gospels, right?
But they didn't all
make it into the Bible.
The church only wanted the ones
that told the story
they were trying to tell.
I didn't know that.
Well, same goes for all history.
Same goes for your brain.
What do you mean?
Our brains are just...
computers that make
our life stories make sense.
You know what, Owen? You...
are the perfect example
of never judging a book by its cover.
Why is that?
You know, the tattoos.
You look like a tough guy.
But you think about the world.
What, tough guys don't think?
Not usually.
My last boyfriend, he was...
into, you know...
criminal enterprises.
Kind of made him go crazy.
He lost his shit
and he started getting all paranoid
that I was workin' for the FBI,
and informin' on him
and recording our conversations.
I wasn't doin' any of that.
Sounds like
he was under a lot of pressure.
And then he really flipped out on me.
He started screamin' at my face,
throwin' things...
dumpin' out my purse, doing...
horrible stuff to me, it was terrifying.
[thunder rumbling]
Did he ever apologize?
No.
Actually, that's the last time
I ever heard from him.
Maybe he wanted to apologize but...
he felt too ashamed to do it.
Maybe it was easier for him just to...
pretend like it didn't even happen.
People can go their whole lives
pretending things didn't happen.
Otherwise, they'd have to admit
they're to blame
for everything wrong in their lives.
I think sometimes there's too much guilt
for one person to bear.
Why are you in school?
You already know about
Gnostics and Magellan.
'Cause I want somethin' different.
We got that in common.
So what do you want, then?
People are always askin' me
to model, right?
So, do that then.
With my chronic hypothermia,
my family says I shouldn't.
I'm more useful to them at home,
especially in the winter. [chuckles]
For people who are supposed
to love unconditionally...
families seem to have a lot of conditions.
One day I wanna make
a family with no conditions.
Maybe that's all I really want.
Talking to you is really easy, Olivia.
You too, Owen.
You see, she was telling the truth.
If there was no lake,
why would we have found the tree?
No, it's just part of the con.
Someone must have told fur lady
how I do it.
I bring them here,
I wow them with the Burning Tree,
and I tell them to look
for the invisible moon, but...
they can't see it
because there isn't one and so...
magic!
[gasps] I can see it.
Have a look.
There obviously isn't...
the moon.
Can you see it, too?
Yeah.
I don't usually even
bring people that way.
[Ellia] Come along.
God.
[Porter] Hey, Ron, make sure you put
those tennis shoes in the furnace.
Let's roll out that periwinkle cuff.
- It's kind of calm.
- How'd those new pills work?
- You sleep any better?
- No.
No? Try the red ones next time.
Talk to me if you need somethin' else.
Well, I found the rat.
Your own brother.
Can you fuckin' believe it?
Aah, I'm slippin'.
No way Rick was the rat.
What the fuck were you doin'?
Oh, by the way, I've got this new system.
Okay?
When you're finished,
you put it directly into the charger,
and then when you need a new one,
you take it out, you put it in the drill.
That way, you never...
You have no idea what's goin' on, do you?
You never had
a fuckin' sixth-sense superpower.
Have you ever considered that,
despite all your problems here...
it's likely that you are currently trapped
inside a malfunctioning
and extremely dangerous simulation,
which is, in itself, directed
by a suicidally depressed
consciousness?
Why?
Ceci n'est pas une fucking drill.
So...
What are you gonna do
about protecting the family?
I ain't crazy,
and I ain't gonna say that I am.
You are failing the big test.
[Ellia] I did have a sister.
[Annia] What was she like?
[Ellia] I hated to...
get clean when I was little.
There was the day...
in the river.
We built a dam with wolf pups.
The Derglassian brothers,
from the farm two miles up the road.
And by the end, we were...
covered in mud and...
and clay, and...
[chuckling] And dog hair.
And Mother was there.
And she just looked at the both of us...
and said...
"I'm the mother of two filthy...
roaches.
I will...
drown you both...
before you set foot in this house."
She was in that sundress.
Havin' a day.
Then you ran away.
Did I ever tell you
what she said to me after?
No.
She asked me
why hadn't I run away as well?
And I said it was out of respect.
Even though, really, it was
because I was more afraid than you.
She swiped her finger across my forehead
and asked what she'd done
to deserve a daughter like me.
And I asked her what she meant.
And she said, "Utterly and predictably...
normal."
Well, it's better than being hit.
[Adelaide] If we move now,
you can promise me another body?
[Owen] How about an apron with four
different motherfuckers' blood on it?
Murder's not enough.
It's gotta be.
You can't push him anymore.
[dialling]
Roosevelt, 088.
- [woman] Password?
- Wendy.
- Green light.
- [Adelaide] Utangátta.
Hey. What... what does that mean?
What is that word?
‐None of your damn business.
‐You think, uh...
your dad knew something?
- What?
- [Adelaide] I mean your brother, Rick.
That's who your dad thought it was, right?
- I'm the rat.
- Yeah, but there could be others.
You never know about Interpol.
Shouldn't you know?
Why don't you fuckin' know?
[Carl] Calm down, Owen. You're just
a little square in this jigsaw puzzle.
Hey, jigsaw pieces are not squares,
you dumb motherfucker.
- Easy, white boy.
- Okay. Owen, take a breath.
[sighs]
It's gonna be okay.
- It's gonna be okay.
- [Carl] Don't coddle him.
[knocking on door]
- [man] Turn down service.
‐ Okay, that's him.
All right, let's get this done.
- Hi.
- Hey.
‐Baby, what are you doing here? It's not...
‐I'm sorry.
[gunshots]
[man] What the fuck?
‐Hi.
‐[Owen] Hey.
[closes door]
Get on the bed.
You don't see it, do you?
I'm your brother.
Hello! Jed!
Grimsson!
The fifth Milgrim boy.
Shunned, abandoned,
black sheep, prodigal son.
Lying fucking eyes. Huh.
Dad never told you.
He said he got rid of you
'cause you were an un-loyal baby.
That's why Dad's a genius.
It wasn't because of that.
It's because he...
he needed a cop with the bloodline.
[chuckles] Do you wanna know why, Owen?
Because nothing trumps blood.
At least‐‐
Yeah, at least, I thought so...
I've watched you my whole life.
I wanna be you.
[chuckles]
I love you.
Owen, the prince.
It ain't that great being me, dude.
What? You... you sad about her?
[clears throat]
Yeah, it's 'cause she's attractive.
I was gonna marry her.
Why the fuck you shoot her, then?
Blood trumps cock, right?
Oh! Fuck.
Need to stretch more...
What are you doing he... Fuck!
Brilliantly played, Owen.
Thanks for the breadcrumbs.
Is she dead?
- Yeah.
- Shame.
There's some spare shirts in the car.
[Owen] This whole time, you've just been
a motherfuckin' fed, dude.
[Frank] I've been undercover
for 36 years now.
‐[honks]
‐Are you fucking kidding me?
Fucking moron!
[Frank] So we're gonna need you
to testify.
We'll put in you into witness relocation.
[Owen] I wanna bring someone with me
when I go into witness relocation.
Luigi, there wasn't
supposed to be bacon on that.
Also, there's a hair in this.
Is this table number nine?
- Hey.
- Owen.
- I'm leaving.
- Leaving? I didn't know you were here.
Why is there blood on your face?
You need to do somethin' different, right?
Yeah.
You wanna see the world, do stuff, right?
So, come with me.
Where?
They'll give us both brand-new identities.
‐Who? Who will?
‐[knocking]
The FBI.
- No, I can't... I can't go with you.
- Is this her?
‐ I'm not done yet.
- You comin', hon, or what?
‐ Who is this guy?
- I'm Frank. Who the fuck are you?
Hey, don't fuckin' talk to her like that,
you understand?
There are so many reasons to say no.
You asked me what I wanted.
And I said something different.
Marry me.
Hey, I wan't you to marry me, Olivia.
I fuckin' love you.
No conditions?
No conditions.
Okay.
- Okay?
- Yeah, okay.
- Hey, she fuckin' said yes!
- Mazel tov!
My motherfuckin' superpower is love!
[Olivia] Asia, stop it!
- [children yelling]
- Antarctica, just grab this.
Africa, enough with the glue!
We don't have to scream like that.
Australia. Australia, stop it, please.
Stop it.
- That's ridiculous.
- I asked him whether or not...
Don't, Africa. I see you, okay?
Stop it!
Australia, enough. Enough with the drum!
Utangátta!
We had a pretty good life, you know.
[baby cries] But I realized last night...
none of it matters.
I ain't supposed to be here with y'all.
I can't be the person
I'm supposed to be here.
Goodbye, everybody.
What?
I'm sorry.
- [child] What does he mean by...
- Owen. What...
- Dad? Dad, no!
- [children screaming]
[Annie] ...look out for each other,
remember?
You made a promise to me.
And you made a promise to yourself.
We promised we'd look out for each other,
remember?
You made a promise to me.
And you made a promise to yourself.
We promised we'd look out for each other,
remember?
[Olivia] Don't you think
you're being a little dramatic?
[Annie] You made a promise to me.
You're really gonna leave me here
with seven children?
[Annie] We promised
we'd look out for each other, remember?
I know where I'm supposed to be now.
[Annie] You made a promise to me.
And you made a promise to yourself.
We promised we'd look out for each other,
remember?
[whirring sound]
[screeching]
[Owen] Annie, I'm coming for you!
This place goes on forever!
Annie, where are you?
[screeches]
[screeching echoes]
Annie, I'm a hawk!
[wind whistling]
[Ellia] This is it.
This is the place.
Where I died.
I don't want to see.
You have to look.
This is how you move on.
[whispers] And it's time to say goodbye.
- I can't say goodbye to you.
- You have to.
- I can't.
[static crackling]
[Greta] It doesn't matter what they want.
I'm here with you now, and right now,
it's all about what you want.
Which is to say, what I want.
What I really need is a friend.
And I think you could use one too.
[chuckles]
I...
fell in love.
And‐‐ and then I lost...
Robert, and...
and I don't‐‐
I don't know how, I don't know how I can...
how I can‐‐
Oh! [laughs]
Oh! So many new emotions.
One minute, I feel like I'm gonna cry,
and the next minute
I feel like I wanna help everybody,
and then the next, I wanna do
as much damage as possible.
[chuckles]
Well, that's a little over the top,
don't you think, all in all?
This is all your hysteria, Greta.
It's all you.
So...
So, what, thi... thi...
this woman with the legs
thinks she can slap a few toddler emotions
into a Speak &amp; Spell
and create a mind, my mind?
You describe your feelings
as toddler emotions?
You're a machine, a computer.
How much of me can actually be in there?
I'm detecting
a great deal of anger from you, Greta.
James? James.
James, let me out!
- [screams] Jamie!
- [gasps]
James. James. James, James, James!
James, James! Oh! Oh! Oh!
What's a McMurphy?
Uh...
[Owen] What is this place?
Beautiful!
Annie, I'm coming!
[hawk screeches]
[screeching echoes]
The Queen.
It's her.
- You have to say goodbye right now.
- No.
- You have to.
- No!
You shouldn't ever have to say goodbye.
I have a deal for you, Annie,
if you're interested.
What if I said you never had
to return to your drab, gray life?
All that obsession with knowing
who you are, knowing yourself...
True bliss is not knowing who you are.
True bliss is staying here.
That's what I have to offer.
[hawk calls]
[Owen] Annie, it's me, Owen, as a hawk!
I haven't forgotten,
we'll protect each...
[screeches]
She's lying. Don't make a deal with...
We'll just send him back
to the Globular Cluster.
[hawk screeches]
[Owen screams]
[splash]
What if I said
you could stay here with us?
Forever and ever.
Stay with your sister.
Don't do this again.
You wanna move on. Just say goodbye.
No. No.
[engine starts]
Wait. Wait, what about Ellie?
Ellie!
No! No!
Wait! Wait!
Ellie!
No, please wait!
[banging on door]
No! Ellie! Ellie!
Ellie! Ellie!
[Queen] I'm sorry, you misunderstood.
This is an exclusive deal.
We'll be together forever.