Previously
on "Better Call Saul"...
Four for unlock, five for lock.
I gotta tell ya,
it does not sound like
the Howard Hamlin that I know.
You're going to forget you ever
heard the name Howard Hamlin.
Lalo is dead.
The DA's office put it together
that Lalo was calling himself
"de Guzman."
What do you think we should do?
Do you want to be a friend
of the cartel
or do you want to be a rat?
- What did you learn?
- Lalo Salamanca lives.
Oh, no.
Really?
I thought it'd be just the trim.
Of all the colors,
why would you pick that?
Use adobe red, if you want red.
What do you even call that?
Fire engine red?
Tomato red.
Their poor neighbors.
Mmh. Mmh.
Ugh. What an eyesore.
There's no way
the Homeowners' Association
approved that color.
Barb's gonna have a cow.
Whew.
Maybe I could put a bug
in her ear...
What can Barb do?
That place isn't even
in Mountain View.
It's Enchantment Hills
over there.
Enchantment Hills starts
at Pinon Lane.
Remember when the Westlakes
planted those Quaking Aspens?
That whole mess?
I thought the Westlakes proved
their lot was in
Enchantment Hills.
They paid for a land survey.
Really?
Where'd you hear that?
Robbie Davis, maybe.
I'll double-check the map
after I shower.
Want some?
Nah. I'm good.
Is that iced tea?
Mrs. Would you like some?
Love some. Thank you, Ma'am.
How's it going?
Eh. Status quo.
You know, hummin' along.
We did land a pretty big client
last week, though.
Insurance outfit in Santa Fe.
They cover most of the high-end
real estate up there.
Great.
But, Howard,
I'm not a shareholder.
I'm... I'm just
getting warmed up.
Although I still think you would
make one hell of litigator.
Ah. Appreciate that,
but I'll pass.
At home, things are
more or less the same.
It's not any worse...
I guess I should be grateful
for that.
It's like we're...
deadlocked.
Cheryl still won't talk about
anything... important.
You tried what we
discussed? Yes.
Yes, Idid, but...
I didhave a dream.
So I look over
the old man's ticket,
and it's clearly
an international flight,
so we search for
his gate number...
But all the signs are
in a language I can't read.
Kim!
Any traffic?
Nope. Straight shot down 25.
This is us.
Thanks for meeting me.
I imagine you're swamped
when you're in town.
Today's not too bad.
In fact, I have a meeting
at your old stomping ground,
with Schweikart.
Oh. Tell Rich I said hi.
Of course. How's Jimmy?
He's great. Thanks for asking.
How about Alice? She's doing well.
She's taking up baking,
and, uh, no complaints here.
Well, lucky you. Don't I know it.
I hear this place makes
a killer latte. Yeah.
They give Java Joe's a run
for their money, if you ask me.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Come on!
Had a customer.
Okay, okay, but it's time to go.
C'mon! We gotta get moving!
Wait. What are ya doing?
No, no, no, no, no.
Hey. Come on.
We gotta move. We gotta move.
I'm getting a root beer.
No, no. We have a schedule.
Remember? We discussed it.
I put two quarters in.
I will buy you an entire case
when we're done.
Here we go. Right in. Whew.
All the way.
Everything okay?
Sure.
Do we need to go over it again?
Nah.
Well, just remember...
Keep your feet out of the way
'cause I'm gonna have to leave
in a hurry.
What?
I really like your hair.
It's not... Thank you.
Thanks.
What if there was
a different way?
What if there was an
independent team of lawyers...
Maybe four or five of them...
Who were dedicated to taking on
the difficult cases?
I'm not saying a few lawyers
can solve
a massive, systemic problem,
but they could make it better.
And why come to me with this?
Well, if I wanted
to shine you on,
I'd tell you it's because
you're known for
your social conscience.
But the truth is
it's because of your connections
in state government.
You can make things happen.
Fair enough.
Kim, the firm has
a service committee.
I should tell you to go to them
and get in line with
all the other worthy causes.
But you're putting your money
where your mouth is.
I'm sure you've heard something
about my son's drug problem.
Gregory's struggle
gave me a more, let's say,
personal view
of the legal system.
Kim, I think
you've got something here.
You can't skimp
on the support staff.
They're the beating heart
of the operation.
I know that's true
in our office...
No, no! No! No!
Jesus.
You son of a bitch!
You twisted deadbeat
piece of shit!
Wasn't that... Howard?
God damn it!
You owe me!
Ma'am, are you okay?
You owe me! Ma'am...
I mean... Nobody does that to me!
I don't know.
It happened so fast.
Damn it! He owes me!
What a rip-off!
Damn you!
No. No!
They moved the cone?!
What kinda asshole
moves a cone?!
Ohh. Crap.
Nngh!
Hey, listen. Um...
Be careful, okay?
Okay.
What?
Five-O.
That kills business
for the rest of the day.
Always hassling me.
Undercover cops?
Yep.
Well, listen, if you ever have
any legal problems,
give me a call, anytime.
No charge.
Thanks.
So I pulled the Jag
into the loading zone
and I start scrapping
with this hunk of metal.
Oh, my God. It was in deep.
Like down-a-well deep.
So I just... wrestled it!
Nngh! Like a freakin' bear!
And I... nngh!... Jam it in
the dirt in front of the Jag.
Boom!
Barely made it out of there
by the skin of my teeth.
Who moves cones?!
Who does that? Narcissists.
You're damn right.
So you think
Cliff really bought it, huh?
One hundred percent.
You should have seen his face.
It landed, trust me.
God, it was beautiful.
Oh. And that is not all.
Spill.
So, I'm doing the stall,
I'm telling Cliff
what I'm doing,
what I wanna be doing.
All I'm thinking about is
I gotta stretch this out
until you get there.
But then, I don't know,
I kind of got caught up in it.
And then...
Cliff went for it.
I mean, like,
really went for it.
What does that mean? Like money?
I-I don't think
he'll write a check himself.
But he knows people.
And I think he'll deliver.
You're kidding.
I know! How great is that?
This is unbelievable.
Are we on a roll
or are we on a roll?
Geez.
You ever feel like
you're being followed?
When I dropped Wendy off
at the motel,
she thought she was being
watched by some undercover cops.
But then, when I drove away,
that same car was behind me.
Right after I spotted them,
they disappeared.
Well, you know what they say.
"The wicked flee
when no man pursueth."
You think we're wicked?
No. What?
It's just a turn of phrase.
I think you're wicked hawt.
Alright.
Listen to the voice
of experience, okay?
You know why
you're feeling like this?
Because we got away with it.
It seems too good to be true.
But trust me,
nobody is following you.
No one knows what we're doing
except for us.
Okay?
Okay.
I get it.
Under the circumstances,
I wouldn't want to be anywhere
near a police station
if I were you either.
I'll tell you what.
Um, the mahogany
in my conference room
is currently getting buffed out,
so I'm using my satellite office
at Juan Tabo and Skyline.
I'm letting a nail salon,
you know, use the lobby,
so my office is in the back.
Meet me there at00.
Great! Thanks.
How's it hanging, Steve-O?
Shoes. Belt. Jacket.
I'm sorry. What?
Seriously? Since when?
It's procedure, sir.
"Sir"?
Why'd Ihit the jackpot?
Never can tell.
Hey. How you doing
on this beautiful day?
Did you, uh, catch
that cookie bouquet
that I sent
for Carlos' birthday?
'Cause I put a few extra
white chocolate macadamias
in there, just for you.
What do you need?
Me? Uh - Nothing. Nothing!
But I have a "friend"
who could use a...
A preliminary hearing
rescheduled.
Uh, Gonzalez v. New Mexico.
My "friend" is looking for
a Friday around nine a.m...
You know, before the judge's
fourth cup of coffee
because, uh, caffeine jitters...
They're brutal
on the defense, so...
What "friend"?
I don't believe
you two have met.
What is this?
A hearing change request form.
Hey, come on. It's me...
Look, Mommy. I just graduated.
I... I can't use a pen.
I have no opposable thumbs.
Hey! Hannah Banana!
Hey, yourself.
Come on, Bill.
That's no way to treat a lady.
You got to make love to it,
Bill.
You know, be gentle...
That's the way to do it.
Think Barry White,
think seduction.
Voilà.
What the hell is going on?
How come everyone's treating me
like I'm covered
in oozing pus sores?
I liked you better
when you were just
a regular bottom feeder.
But this...
"This"? What is "this"?
I understand
advocating for your client.
Deep in my heart, I get it.
But you scammed the court,
you scammed the judge.
And for what?
To get a murdering
cartel psychopath
back out on the street?
It's just...
wrong.
That's a lotta big talk, Bill.
Prove it.
Prove it, Bill!
There's proving,
and then there's knowing.
Abe, you don't want to go back
to county, do you?
Nuh-uh.
Okay. So the meetings?
I'll go.
Great.
Then I'll see you Tuesday,
nine a.m. sharp.
You want this?
I do.
Take your time.
Enjoy.
Yeah, you can sit
anywhere you want. That's fine.
Abe, would you mind
watching my stuff?
Hey. Hello.
Nice day.
Are you following me?
I'm sorry?
What are you, APD?
Know what?
Ithink you're following me,
and if you're not gonna
identify yourselves,
then I'm calling in your plates
because I feel threatened.
Sorry if we've disturbed you.
You have a nice day, ma'am.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, please.
Saul Goodman,
speedy justice for you.
Uh, no, there's no charge
for the initial consultation.
Today?
Yeah, um...
I have an opening around30.
Oh, I'm working
out of my satellite office.
It's at Juan Tabo and Skyline.
I'm letting a nail salon
use the lobby,
so office is in back.
Great. Uh, your name?
Dante.
See you then.
Saul Goodman,
speedy justice for you.
Yeah. Uh, yeah.
I do have an opening today...
Oh, hold on.
I'm getting another call.
Saul Goodman,
speedy justice for you.
Um, hold, please.
My apologies.
I'm having
a bit of a rush here today.
You get these people out
right now.
What? These guys?
Are they bothering you?
Not them. Inside!
Who's here to see Saul Goodman?
You're him? You're Saul?
Yeah.
Then you're the guy, right?
What guy's that?
Salamanca's guy.
Yeah.
That's me.
Everybody who has
an appointment already...
Uh, oh, you know...
You know what?
Um...
Uh, Mr. "Spooge"?
It's just "Spooge."
Just Spooge.
Duly noted. Alright.
Um, Gael Morengo?
Okay. Uh, let's see.
Is there a Dante? Mm-hmm.
And Rocco Kubler. Okay.
Everybody else, um,
kindly wait outside, alright?
Unless... Unless you desire
spa services while you wait.
Uh, that's a separate charge,
but it... it's highly recommended.
The... The best pedicures
in Albuquerque,
right here.
Six.
Lucky number seven.
Oh, you're with him?
And eight.
Nice leathers.
Uh, okay, together.
And nine.
Wow.
Um, thank you all
for your patience.
And... justice for all!
Cucumber water
for paying customers only.
Oh, believe me,
they're gonna be paying.
"Spooge"!
Oh, Spooge and friend.
Okay. Good. This way.
Hi, ma'am.
Yeah, hang... hang a left
at the washing machine.
There you go.
I'll see you next week, Rosa.
And it was nice meeting you,
Pilar.
Don't forget to bring as many
family members as you can.
We will. Thank you, Ms. Wexler.
Take care.
All done for today?
Yeah. Here you go.
Just keep it, Shelby.
Thanks, Kim. See you tomorrow?
You bet.
They're gone.
I'm sorry?
The two men
that were following you.
They're gone.
Do I know you?
Would you mind
sitting for a moment?
And I will answer
any questions I can.
I have men watching you
and your husband.
I'm not with the police,
and as far as I know,
they're not investigating
either of you.
I doknow that you've been
up to a few things
that you probably
would rather keep private.
I don't care.
That's not what this is about.
I'm trying to solve
a problem of my own.
What problem?
Lalo Salamanca.
Lalo Salamanca's dead.
He...
isn't.
We're watching anyone
he might contact.
That includes you
and your husband.
Most likely,
he'll never reach out.
He's got bigger fish to fry.
But in the thousand-to-one
chance that he does...
And who do you work for?
I said I would answer
anything I can.
You're the guy from the desert.
The one who was out there
with Jimmy.
Why are you telling methis
and not him?
Because I think you're made
of sterner stuff.
Alright.
Now here's what's best
for everyone.
You spot my guys again,
which I'm hoping you won't,
let them go about
their business.
Just pretend they're not there.
And pretty soon they won't be.
You and your husband
just...
go on living your lives.
I doknow you.
You worked in the parking booth
at the courthouse.
You're the attendant.
I was.
Hi...
The markets will continue
to be in a state of flux
until the Fed
tightens interest rates.
Some days we'll feel
pretty good about the rate
of economic recovery,
other days not so much.
Because of these macro issues.
The deficit, interest rates,
oil prices, what have you...
Mrs. I think I saw
that somewhere. Here!
Mrs. Nope.
How's youredge coming along?
I'm still missing two...
Mr. You found
all your edge pieces.
I thought I did.
Maybe we lost a few.
These trees are killing me.
The pieces all look
exactly the same.
Then work on the cabin. I could.
There was a green Ford van.
It was behind me
for almost three blocks.
A '98 Econoline.
We ran the plate.
Guy's a freelance plumber.
He's legit.
The man you placed
in my kitchen.
Roy.
You told me
that he had experience
as a short-order cook.
Two years at McDonald's
in college.
He's not there
just to make French fries.
I need guys in close.
He's not up to Pollos standards.
I'll find a replacement.
We're stretched thin.
I've got guys working
18-hour days all over town.
Two weeks.
We haven't had a tickle.
And?
All due respect,
the rest of the world thinks
the guy is dead.
Lalo Salamanca is alive.
Then where is he?
Hey.
How was your day?
Uh, what are we doing here?
Take a look. What do you think?
About what?
My new office. Potentially.
Come on.
Huh.
Mrs. Nguyen kicked me
to the curb.
What? Why?
It's a long story, but upshot is
she wants me outta there
with extreme prejudice.
Wow.
Bad day, huh?
No. It was a great day.
With actual paying clients.
The word is out!
People are throwing
cash retainers at me...
Just to say
Saul Goodman is their lawyer.
Because of who you represented.
Well, I mean, that's part of it.
But, um, the bottom line is
I need a new place
to do business... pronto.
Now, this place is a shithole,
but the price is right
and I think I can talk the
landlord into a month-to-month.
So it's temporary, you know,
'til I find something better.
Hey.
What do you think?
It's small.
It's... dirty.
And this whole place
smells funny.
But the courthouse
is five blocks away.
You can't get to MDC
without driving past.
Parking is good,
bail bond row isn't far,
and, uh...
Taco Cabeza is just around
the corner.
Might be a diamond in the rough.
Just promise me...
...you won't move the toilet.
There it is. Alright.
Um, speaking of
the Taco Cabeza...
I'm starving. Let's do it.
On the next episode
of "Better Call Saul..."
Thank God he's dead.
I can put more guys on the place
if that's what you're thinking.
Open for business.
What you're doing to help the
little guy, it's incredible.
I'm just getting started.
I just need you
to know that I know.
It wasn't me, Cliff.
Sounds like money. Okay. Great.
Who is this Saul Goodman? You?
You got it.