Flint: Somewhere under there is our thief.
Where's the page?
Your schedule is up here.
You want to kill Hamund? Then
you have to kill them all.
- Ah!
- Rackham: When you and Miss Guthrie
were plotting this little coup,
the two of you come up with some idea
how to deal with the
captain when he returns?
Bonny: You don't know
where he's gone, do you?
Eleanor: You could be strong again.
You could take this whole island from me.
You know exactly what it is you need to do,
where it is you need to go to do it.
I certainly didn't expect
to find you down in the hold,
not after you betrayed Miss
Guthrie on behalf of her father.
Found in Bryson's cabin.
It's from the Barlow woman.
She wants a pardon for Flint in Boston.
She says we're going to kill him
when we learn of his betrayal.
Gates: The Scarborough!
Flint: Man overboard!
- It's Billy! He fell!
- We can't turn back.
(theme music playing)
- (wind blowing)
- (Birds calling)
Lambrick: Easter is upon us...
an opportunity for renewal and rebirth...
both in spirit and the flesh.
And yet we may also ask ourselves,
"When the spirit is renewed
and the body resurrected,
what becomes of the sin?"
Will not a trace of it linger
to mock and torment us,
to remind us of the roiling pit of despair
that awaits the unrepentant
beyond this life?
And yet does it not often feel
as if life itself is the pit?
Yah!
Ma'am!
Captain Flint's returned.
Eleanor: Captain.
Captain.
Captain!
Sorry, you were asking
about the Scarborough?
I was, specifically how the
hell did she find you out there?
A trap laid by your father,
for which he will be answering
as soon as I'm finished here.
He won't be the only one, I assume.
Your friend Mrs. Barlow
understood she was responsible
for keeping him under lock and key.
You trusted her.
We trusted her and she betrayed us.
Perhaps he managed to secrete
a message past her men.
That hardly rises to the level of betrayal.
(scoffs)
Captain, yesterday morning,
my father walked into town,
stood out on the steps of the warehouse
and proclaimed to the world
that the Guthries' business
is finished here in Nassau.
What was the reaction?
The men elected representatives,
we agreed upon an agenda,
and we spoke about the merits
of mutual cooperation over tea.
So it was bad?
Bad? It was fucking chaos.
- Yeah.
- Eleanor: For about an hour,
I thought they had
burned down all of Nassau.
But it's been handled.
As of last night, I've
instituted a new trading system
and the street has embraced it.
A consortium with myself at its head,
Captains Naft and Lawrence
as a means of shipping,
and Mr. Frasier as its corporate seal.
Hmm.
All this since yesterday?
I will address the situation
with Mrs. Barlow immediately.
You have my word.
(clears throat)
Captain, one more thing.
The consortium wasn't founded easily.
It required the assistance
of a few other parties.
Among them indispensably was Mr. Silver.
Is that so?
Eleanor: I tell you this because I imagine
you might still hold
some resentment toward him.
And I've given him my word
in exchange for his assistance
that I'll stand between
him and your resentment.
In other words,
if Mr. Silver doesn't return from the Urca,
you and I may find ourselves
with problems of our own.
What a day I missed.
Come on.
(panting)
The fuck, Jack?
It's gone limp again.
Really? I hadn't noticed.
Well, do you want something up your ass?
No.
No, thank you.
(grunts)
What the fuck is your problem?
I'm terribly sorry if
I've ruined your morning,
but at the moment I happen to
have quite a lot on my mind.
Ship purloined, captain
and crew a distant memory,
no prospects at all,
except for this shithole of a brothel,
which by some miracle of economics
seems incapable of turning a profit.
How can you run a brothel
here and not make money?
I have no fucking idea!
Ain't you always the one telling
everyone how fucking clever you are?
Figure it out.
Don't you dare leave me here.
- Don't you...
- (Door slams)
(distant donkey braying)
Alice made you her porridge.
Thicker than snot, but it'll
help you get your strength back.
A couple of us are wondering
what you plan to do now.
Why would anyone care what I do?
Darling, you're all anyone's
talking about out there.
All of us wondering what
kind of voodoo you used
to get eight of Vane's crew to just...
up and disappear.
Haven't you heard?
They left for Port Royal.
Hmm, and I'm Henry fuckin' Avery.
If you've got any thought
of working here again,
- I wouldn't wait too long.
- What do you mean?
Mr. Rackham's got no idea
how to run this place.
We've all got a hand in his pocket.
Mapleton would tell him,
but she's too busy stealing for herself.
Mapleton: Idelle! Downstairs. Customer.
All I'm saying is get in
while the getting's good.
(door closes)
(grunts)
Jesus! The fuck did they do to you?
Postelection initiation, I'm told.
All done in good fun.
At least... (chuckles)
I think it was all done in good fun.
- Congratulations, Mr. Quartermaster.
- Thank you.
Unfortunate, to say the least,
that we find ourselves in the need of one.
Yes, very.
But I'm humbled by the crew's faith in me.
Well, if Billy were here,
I'm sure he would agree with me
when I say that the crew chose well.
Well, much to do.
Mr. Dufresne, quartermaster.
Who would've seen that coming?
- I think he's up to it.
- I'm sure he is.
I just wouldn't have thought the crew
capable of coming to that conclusion.
Well, chew a man's throat out,
it tends to make an impression.
(both chuckle)
You'll be heading to see her now, then?
Mrs. Barlow.
You said you'd be holding her to account.
I assumed you'd not want to wait.
I'll be back before dark.
We'll continue preparations
for our departure then.
Gates: Just one more thing, Captain,
before you leave to see Mrs. Barlow.
I think you and I need to discuss
the letter that Billy found...
and why exactly it is that she believes
you're gonna betray your crew.
- (grunts)
- Hey, get back.
Jesus, Randall.
(panting)
De Groot: Mate.
Randall would like a word with you.
- Council just voted. He's out.
- Out?
De Groot: I suppose it's my fault.
I raised the concern about the fire hazard
a one-legged man in the
galley might present.
And like most things before the council,
it spun out of control.
What's that got to do with me?
He's got a raw deal, Mr. Silver.
The least we can do is
let him say his piece.
(Silver sighs)
Randall.
It's not fair. I can cook.
Yes, I think you might have mentioned that.
You know, it's been my experience
setbacks such as these,
they often go hand in hand
with new and unexpected opportunities.
He's a thief.
What are you talking about, Randall?
He thought I was asleep
at Miss Guthrie's tavern.
I heard him talking.
Wasn't Singleton stole
the page, it was him.
I don't know what he's talking about.
Randall, are you being truthful?
He said he has the schedule in his head,
that he learned it to stop
Flint from murdering him.
All due respect, but he
spent the last two days
beneath a rather heavy cloud of opiates.
- He doesn't know what he heard.
- Get the quartermaster in here.
Right now.
Bear with me.
One minute, please.
Uh, apologies.
(snaps fingers) Give me it.
Ah! Here it is.
It is with great pleasure
that we shall now commence
our inaugural meeting of the Guthrie
Frasier Naft Lawrence Consortium
for the Purposes of Shipping and Trade
in the West Indies, Excelsior.
Reginald, add to the agenda
discussion of a shorter name.
Jesus.
First item of business...
our maiden voyage.
Captain Lawrence,
the status of the Black Hind, please.
(clears throat)
We've begun alterations
to expand our holds.
- But as I predicted...
- O'Malley: Ma'am.
A good number of the crew have defected
upon learning of their new vocation.
Any suggestions for a new source of
labor would certainly be welcomed.
What happened to you?
I told him to get the fuck
out, but he wouldn't go.
He who?
Eleanor: Quite the story I heard out there
from the Walrus' men.
They say you rallied the slaves
in the Andromache's hold,
single-handedly turned
the tides against Bryson.
Imagine what they'd say if
they knew that you're the reason
that they had to chase that
ship in the first place.
- I would like the chance to explain myself.
- I'm listening.
What I did, I did out of love.
(scoffs)
And with every intention of staying
here with you to help you find a safer,
more settled life, a life you deserve.
It was not a betrayal.
It was...
It was not your decision to make.
My life is my own.
It's not Benjamin Hornigold's,
it's not Charles Vane's,
it's not my father's and it's not yours.
Do you understand?
You're right. I'm sorry.
And what?
Now you think you can
just waltz back in here
and pick up from where we
left off like nothing happened?
Where else would I go?
I belong to you.
Chattel property of the Guthrie estate.
You... you know I've
never seen you that way.
Eleanor, I must ask a favor of you.
(bird screeching)
(distant chopping)
He's waiting.
Sit.
You wish to do business?
There's a place...
there's a place not far from here.
A place fueled by plunder.
A place of great wealth
run by its crews and flying no flag.
I know of Nassau.
What of it?
She's weak,
so she's ripe for the taking.
A man with enough strength
could get his hands
wrapped around her throat
in a matter of hours,
control the flow of trade, get rich.
My men are rich.
Wood sells well and we don't
rely on the mercy of the sea.
No man is rich who could
have a lot more by doing less.
(flies buzzing)
When you sailed as captain of these men,
they sacked Campeche for you.
They sacked Cartagena for you.
Give me a dozen of them
and I will bring Nassau in line.
What's your name?
Charles Vane.
I know that name.
These are my men.
Why would I let any of
them call you captain?
Each man gets a share,
plus one share to you in
tribute for every six men.
That's a sizeable piece
of a fucking fortune.
And all you need do is
give them your leave.
How did you know to seek me out?
Is my name spoken as far as Nassau?
Is there someone there that connects us?
Or is it something else?
The fuck do you care?
Do we have a deal or don't we?
Three men.
My tribute... a share for every three men.
Four shares in all.
Yes or no?
You're not answering the question.
I'm trying to answer the question.
So you're saying she's lying?
That the letter is just a fiction?
I'm saying that my relationship
with her is a complex one...
that it's hard for me
to understand at times.
But what is clear is that she
desperately wants to leave this place
and will say anything in
order to make me go with her.
Oh, for fuck's sake, enough.
This is what we do.
You orate and you dissemble,
and I look the other way,
convince myself that supporting you
is in everybody's interests.
But not today.
Not after what happened last night.
After what happened last night?
What happened to Billy, Captain?
He fell.
Why? What are you saying happened?
He thought you saw us all as expendable.
- Expendable?
- Pawns to be used for your own ends.
I have fought and bled alongside my men.
I have sacrificed more than you
could possibly know for their futures.
I know what happened on the Maria Aleyne.
You told me the man you killed
was reaching for a weapon.
You told me it was self-defense,
but there were no weapons in that cabin.
I went and I looked.
And I still kept my mouth shut.
I don't know why,
but I know you used the crew
to assassinate those people.
Men died that day.
Our men.
And I suspect there's been other times
when we've been expendable to you.
And if yesterday was one of those days,
then you and I have a problem,
because Billy wasn't expendable
to me.
He was a son to me.
Then perhaps you should have acted
like a better father towards him.
What the fuck did you just say?
You let his suspicions run rampant.
You let his paranoia
fester to the point at which
when he should have been focused
on the Scarborough's guns,
he was focused on hurling
unfounded accusations at me.
So I'm to blame for what happened to Billy?
Perhaps if you had intervened
when he first came to
you with these fantasies,
perhaps if you helped him understand
the world in which he lived...
he'd still be here right now.
Where are you going?
I'm tired of this.
I'm tired of the energy
it takes to believe you.
To believe in you.
I'm taking this to the crew.
You're their problem now.
I'm taking it.
After the Urca has been secured
and the money warehoused
before distribution...
I intend to sequester a portion of it.
- Sequester?
- A portion of it.
Every man on that crew will still be richer
than their wildest dreams.
But you know as well as I do
that no matter how much
money they're given,
they will drink, whore and piss it away.
Now, they have a chance at
something better than that,
but it isn't gonna happen
unless somebody makes it happen.
You're lying to them.
And if I don't, who will?
Everyone's lied to for their own good...
every mother who tells their child
that everything will be all right,
every soldier who's told by his commander
that courage will see them through,
every subject who's told by...
His king?
Is that what you are to us now?
A sovereign levying a tax?
If no one knows, everyone wins.
- Don't play games with me.
- I'm quite serious.
Who loses?
Absent their worst instincts,
their pride, their greed, their suspicion,
in the light of pure reason,
who says no to this?
They'll be rich men in a safe place
rather than dead thieves on a long rope.
I'm gonna deliver them, Hal.
I'm gonna deliver them
into something better.
I will sail with you
tomorrow to take this prize.
I'll follow your lead in battle.
And I'll take your orders as consort.
But when it's done,
you and I will quietly
go our separate ways.
And I'll thank you not to protest.
No one else knows about this?
Look, as far as I can tell,
it's just the three of us.
Then again, this is
Randall we're talking about.
If he had told anyone
else, we'd have heard.
Does it make any sense to you?
Well, Flint finding that page on Singleton
does seem awfully convenient in hindsight.
Jesus.
A fine mess here, Randall.
Randall: You're a thief.
(sighs) Quite sure you're wrong.
But the good news is it's not
too late to repair the damage.
I know what I heard.
Randall, you were doped.
You have no idea what you heard.
Say you're successful in
convincing our friends out there
to believe your story.
I'm not sure you've given proper
consideration to what happens next.
Do you think they'd just haul
me up in front of the crew,
air your story, and that's the end of it?
No, Randall.
I think you've forgotten
one very important detail.
The money.
That has to be considered, does it not?
If we go tell the crew now,
there's a very good chance
they simply hang the cook
right along with the captain.
If Randall's right,
that would be the end of the Urca hunt.
Are you suggesting we keep this secret?
Lie to the crew? Right along with Flint?
He's suggesting that acting hastily
could come with a very hefty price.
Even if I was convinced, there's
still Randall to contend with.
Are you suggesting there's some
way to guarantee his silence?
I can think of one way.
- They wouldn't.
- Wouldn't they?
A one-legged halfwit versus
a chance at a fortune?
The odds are decidedly not in your favor.
Well, you were confused or delirious.
Take your pick, but tell them now.
Then even if they wanted to go to the crew,
they'd have lost their chief witness.
And no one has to die.
- You're a thief.
- I'm a thief. Right.
Well, good luck, Randall.
It was nice knowing you.
Albinus: For as long as you sail with him,
his orders are my orders.
And when your work is done,
this place will have you back.
They'll serve you well.
Is something wrong?
You were one of ours.
You were just a boy yourself.
Could not have been easy coming back here.
Must have taken great strength.
Go on.
Take these men.
Make me rich.
You don't know me, but you once did...
when I was the lowest among you.
Now I've returned.
And I offer you a chance
to be free of this place.
I'm Charles Vane.
And you were a strong crew once,
proper pirates.
Feared, as you should have been,
before he dragged you away from the sea,
before he convinced you
to live here like animals.
Because it suits his weaknesses.
There is a place not far from here
where strong men live lives
of pleasure, not labor,
a place where you
could be feared and respected once again.
Follow me, and I will
show you what life is.
(panting)
Are you done? Are you done?
Oh!
(grunts)
(groans)
I'm proud of you.
Randall.
I need a word with Mr. Silver alone.
- (laughs)
- What's so funny?
Just that I warned Randall
something like this was coming.
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
Mr. De Groot's inclined to
hand you over to the crew.
He's given me exactly five minutes,
at which point he intends to call
council so Randall can share his story,
after which our hands are clean
and you are most likely, well, dead.
What's that?
A page from one of Dr. Howell's manuals
and your last chance at living
to see the sun rise again.
You have exactly five minutes
to commit it to memory,
after which you will reproduce this
page to the best of your ability.
If you can do so to Mr.
De Groot's satisfaction,
then maybe... just
maybe he can be convinced
to keep your secret for
the sake of the Urca haul.
- It's a test?
- Exactly.
- It's a terrible test.
- Believe me, I'm aware.
If I was the thief, which
I am by no means admitting,
I could have read that
schedule a hundred times over
before I was forced to destroy it.
Whether or not I can memorize this page
in five minutes proves nothing.
Mr. De Groot doesn't
believe that he can trust
the information inside your head,
certainly not enough to risk his own life,
not to mention committing
poor Randall to an early grave.
He says if he's to go down
that road, he needs certainty.
It's the best I could do.
Four minutes.
(sighs)
(rooster crows)
Wait.
Compliments of the new consortium.
A dead cargo is a worthless cargo.
Eme: Did you ask her?
I implored Miss Guthrie
to facilitate your release.
I told her she would not have her guns
without yours and the others' help.
What did she say?
She said she would take
it under advisement.
(sighs)
I warned you this place
would not be any different.
But do not give up hope.
I'll need to know your secret.
To putting up with her.
My decision whether or not
to partake in this consortium
was predicated on her agreement
to lift the ban on Charles Vane's crew.
I understand she did.
Begrudgingly.
And shortly after, all eight disappeared.
Left for Port Royal, I am told.
And you think Eleanor had
something to do with this?
It doesn't matter either way.
Short of my retrieving eight
corpses from her armoire,
nothing would dissuade the other captains
from the course that she's set now.
Which I'd wager she knew would be the case.
I'd wager you're right.
I asked you once to get her under control.
The truth is there is no
controlling her, is there?
You forced her hand in front of men
whose respect she demands
in order to run this business.
Really, Captain,
what choice did you give her?
(hoofbeats approaching)
- (dog barking)
- (Horse neighs)
Miranda: Mr. Guthrie isn't here.
He's taken sanctuary on
Mr. Underhill's estate.
Do you know what you've done?
What madness possessed
you to write that letter?
I tried to tell you.
Billy found it.
If he'd have shown anyone
before I discovered him,
but for dumb luck,
I'd be dead.
I'm sorry.
You know I would never intentionally
put you in any kind of danger.
What was your intent?
What was it?
To destroy everything we've tried
to build here for the past 10 years?
Or was it just to embarrass me?
To show you a way out
of all this, to free you.
A way out?
Have you no memory of how we got here?
What they took from us?
What does it matter now?
What does it matter?
What does it matter what happened then
if we have no life now?
Because there is no life here.
There is no joy here.
There is no love here.
- There's no love here.
- What are you talking about?!
What do you think I'm
out there fighting for
if not to make all those
things possible here?
You'll fight a war so we can make a life?
You don't get one without
the other, my sweet.
No. You're wrong.
I sent that letter to
show you that you're wrong.
There is a life in Boston.
There is joy there and music
and peace.
The door is open.
I've opened it for you.
And it requires no war and
no blood and no sacrifice.
It requires an intolerable sacrifice.
To accept a pardon?
To apologize.
Apologize? Who will you be apologizing to?
To England!
They took everything from us.
And then they called me a monster.
The moment I sign that pardon,
the moment I ask for one,
I proclaim to the world
that they were right.
This ends
when I grant them my forgiveness...
not the other way around.
This path you're on...
it doesn't lead where you think it does.
If he were here, he'd agree with me.
Three days with the Urca's schedule,
three minutes with
whatever the fuck this is.
I'll remind them.
Before you go, just one question.
Harebrained as this test was,
you had to be quite certain
I was the thief to even think of it.
And I don't believe you
have near that kind of faith
in our friend Randall here.
Who told you about me?
Billy?
Randall, we need to talk.
- You're a thief.
- Randall, pay attention.
Right now at this moment,
it is just as likely
you're the one that dies as I am.
What if there was a way
neither of us had to die today?
I go to the crew and I
offer to be your caretaker.
I'll promise to look
after you day and night
and give my personal guarantee
should anything happen,
it comes out of my share.
I think I could persuade
the crew to accept that.
And then you're back on the ship.
All you have to do is change your story.
You're a thief.
Are you fucking kidding me?!
(sighs) All right.
Yes, I'm a thief.
I took the page and I shouldn't have.
I should have counted my blessings
to be let off that merchant ship.
But what can I say, Randall?
I'm not a joiner. I never have been.
But I'm willing to do it now.
So pull your head from your ass
and let's both live to fight another day.
Dufresne: Sorry, Mr. Silver.
- You're a thief.
- Yes, we understand.
Randall?
You're a thief.
Randall, what's gotten into you?
What the hell is going on here?
It would appear Mr. Randall
has reconsidered his position.
If you intend to accuse
Mr. Silver before the crew,
you do so without a witness.
(knocks)
(door opens)
Give us the room, please.
As you can imagine,
money is tight right now.
The Walrus crew are unwilling
to manumit a hold full of slaves,
nor do I have the funds to
purchase their release outright.
So here's what I've done.
The able-bodied males will be taken
onto the Black Hind under Captain Lawrence
to fill a recent rash of desertions.
The consortium has reached an agreement
with Mr. Dufresne of the Walrus
to trade future subsidies
and credits to cover the cost.
Six women remain thereafter,
for whom I was able to scrounge together
enough money to cover their cost.
They'll be offered a wage in my employ.
Thank you.
- As for us...
- Eleanor, I...
I know how much you worry about me.
But I hope the events of the last few days
prove that I can handle myself.
It does.
I'm not blind to Flint.
I know he keeps things from me.
But there's no reason
for you to feel threatened
by my partnership with him.
If you're to stay with me, I
need to know that I can trust you.
Eleanor, Captain Hornigold has extended me
an offer to join his crew.
And you've accepted?
If you need me, I will be here for you.
But as long as you insist on pursuing
this course with Captain Flint,
I will always be tempted to interfere.
Please get out.
(moaning)
I'm sorry, but the income you've
reported for the past two days
is simply too low to be believed.
I'm going to have to ask you to vacate
your room, make way for someone else.
Oh, yes, yes.
Here it comes.
(crying)
Ugh.
I'll have you know I have slit
men's throats while they have wept,
begging my forbearance, and
slept soundly that very night.
If you were hoping to manipulate me,
you are barking up the wrong tree.
(crying continues)
The wrong tree.
Jesus Christ.
- Alice: Mr. Rackham.
- What?
- Five pieces.
- (Coins clink)
Oh, look who's up and about.
Who did you just service?
What's that?
Who paid you those coins?
It was Captain Hallindale I saw
leaving your room, was it not?
A man whose sole desire
is to be swaddled in canvas
while he sucks on a fat, milkless breast
like a nursing child.
And the price we have
always charged for mothering
is 20 pieces, not five.
Who the fuck do you think you're accusing?
A handjob pays five.
All Captain Hallindale had
time for today was a tug.
Will your story hold when
I ask him to confirm it?
Or will you confess your crime now
and pray that our new
patron is more forgiving
than Mr. Noonan would have been?
I swear on the body and
blood of our Lord Jesus Christ
this will never happen again.
For your sake, it had better not.
In my experience, if you
do not discipline a whore,
she will always take advantage.
Get your fucking house in order.
Hmm?
I thought you were going to report back
once you returned from Mrs. Barlow's.
Do you really think it's wise to get pissed
in full view of any of your
men that may stumble in here
just before they're about to embark
on the most dangerous
journey of their lives?
Wise?
Probably not.
But then there was 36 hours before castoff,
so I thought
why not live dangerously?
36 hours is plenty of time
for them to find reason to doubt you.
Perhaps a little doubt in me is called for.
What happened out there?
Tell me
we're not crazy, you and I.
Crazy?
To put ourselves through all this
when the outcome's so uncertain.
The outcome is only uncertain
for those who disbelieve.
I believe in this place.
And I believe if there's anyone
who can do what's necessary
to make it something better,
it's you.
(men shouting)
(grunting)
(chickens clucking)
Oi, where are you going?
Eyes on Randall at all times...
wasn't that the deal?
(chuckles)
Randall, you are a fucking puzzle.
Part of me thinks you must be the
luckiest halfwit in the colonies,
the way this all played out.
But part of me suspects there's
something else going on here.
I'm forced to wonder if you didn't
orchestrate this whole little drama
knowing it would corner me into
securing your return to the crew.
I'm forced to consider the possibility
there is a lot more of the old Randall
in that head of yours
than you'd like to let on.
That you're no halfwit at all,
but a very shrewd operator
who's managed to gain the benefits
of sailing with these men
while avoiding all the risk.
That perhaps,
just perhaps,
you're a goddamn genius.
(farts)
(men shouting)
(chatter and laughter)
Mr. Gates.
Mr. Quartermaster.
The crew seem in good spirit.
All things considered.
What about our friend the cook?
It appears to be resolved for now.
Though I must tell you,
he discerned that I knew
about the missing page beforehand.
He assumed Billy told me.
I can see how he might think that.
I did nothing to dispel that notion,
though it may not take
him a long time to realize
who it was that actually
brought me into this.
Well, we'll have to deal with our situation
as it develops,
won't we?
Aye.
There's something else.
It's Messrs. Howell and De Groot.
Give them a couple of days.
Once we're at sea, the work will
take their focus off Randall.
Actually, it's not Randall
that's troubling them.
It's you.
Having had some time to think about it,
they're not certain that you're
up to doing what's necessary.
The lying we could forgive.
Singleton we could forgive.
We could forgive all of it.
But not Billy.
That requires an answer.
When the time comes, we need to know
that you won't stand in the way.
I understand he's your friend.
But once we have the money,
Flint dies.
No argument.
Not from me.
(rustling)
- Eleanor's voice: You could be strong again.
- (Gasps)
You could resist me.
You could take this whole
fucking island from me
if only you weren't so goddamned afraid.
(chatter and laughter)
- (squelches)
- (Groans)
(chatter stops)
(grunts)