You took one of me best
whores for your private use.
Every day she's not under
my roof costs me money.
(grunts)
Wait, listen to me!
(gagging)
Good men will die for some hidden agenda,
the Barlow woman's agenda.
Things will get better here.
I promise you they will.
We'll need some additional items.
New guns, 12-pounders.
You'll have it.
You want the guns from my
ship to hand over to a pirate?
That is correct.
Richard: Help me, Mr. Scott.
Please, help me save her.
Why don't I take over?
Eleanor: The Andromache, it can't be.
Captain Bryson hasn't had time to unload.
He didn't. She's riding low.
Those guns are still on board.
- Eleanor: What are we going to do?
- Get them back.
(theme music playing)
(wind blowing)
Billy: Captain?
We're steady at six
knots, north by northeast.
You don't trust me, do you?
With any luck, we'll
sight the Andromache soon.
The battle will begin.
You and I will have our roles to play.
We have the chance for a
few minutes' honesty first.
Honesty?
Men died yesterday
careening our ship faster than was safe.
Men are going to die today
attacking that merchant ship out there,
and they'll die not knowing
it was all based on a lie.
A lie?
We don't even know if the
Urca's schedule is accurate.
We're completely relying on the cook.
How can you just pretend you
have no doubts about any of this?
Years of practice.
There's always doubt, Billy.
No sane man would deny that.
No good captain would acknowledge it.
Take our present route, for instance.
We tacked north by northeast,
along Andromache's best point of sail.
If you're Bryson, that's the smart course.
Yeah...
Well, he knows that I know that.
So wouldn't he have at least
considered heading northwest
to follow the coast, lose us in the dark?
Or due east on the chance that
we might sail right past him?
There must be at least one chance in three
that that horizon will remain bare
and we'll never see the Andromache again.
That's the truth.
But what good would that knowledge do
for any man on this crew trying
to focus on doing his job?
This crew needs certainty,
and I need their support to achieve an end
which is in all our best interests.
So we dance the dance.
Never was there a Caesar
that couldn't sing the tune.
Who's Mrs. Barlow?
Ah.
You've heard the stories, haven't you?
She's a witch who pledged
my soul to the devil,
and anoints me with the blood of infants
to keep me safe in battle.
- Come on, I'm not stupid.
- No, you're not.
So you can probably
guess it isn't as much fun
to tell stories about how
your captain makes a home,
with a nice Puritan woman
who shares his love of books.
Is that the truth?
Man: Sails!
Man your posts!
Man 2: Posts!
Man 3: Have a look.
Man: It's the Andromache!
(crew shouting)
(bird trilling)
(dogs barking)
Well, this is a stupid fucking idea.
Given the straits we're in, I would
suggest there is no such thing.
If we don't find a way to
earn an income and soon,
we will lose what little
we have left of a crew.
Or worse yet, we will be eaten
by what little we have left of a crew.
Wish me luck.
You gave him permission, dear.
We must stand by our word.
But I said he could put one
finger in my bum, not three.
Then next time, charge him by the digit.
Mrs. Mapleton, a word, please.
What the fuck are you doing here?
Mr. Noonan expressly
forbade it, did he not?
It turns out Mr. Noonan
has had a change of heart.
A transfer? What is this?
It means, madam, that the dispute
over the whore with Mr.
Noonan has been settled
through an agreement to
purchase this establishment
from him... by us.
- Noonan sold you the inn?
- Yes, ma'am.
And where is he now?
From the tone in his voice,
it sounded as if Mr. Noonan
couldn't wait to be rid of this place
and of its screeching pig of a bawd.
His words, not mine.
The last I saw him, he was
seeking passage to Port Royal,
and then to who knows where.
You're telling me that Mr. Noonan,
who just a few hours ago had the intent
of seeing your captain beaten to a pulp,
that Mr. Noonan decided instead
to sell you his life's work?
Yes.
And you expect me to accept it
based on a piece of paper and your word?
And to keep my mouth shut about it
when any half-wit can see
that there's foul play at hand?
Yes.
I want a raise.
- What did you make before?
- Three percent of gross.
I'll give you 40.
Welcome aboard, sonny.
We are the proud new owners of a brothel.
Let's hope no one notices.
No one has seen or heard
from Scott all morning.
He must have left with Bryson.
You're certain he said nothing
to you about why he would do this?
Nothing, ma'am.
- Before I knew what was happening...
- Get my horse ready.
I'm going to see my father. I want
to know what the fuck's going on here.
(sighs)
Hello.
What the fuck are you doing in my office?
Flint stashed me here.
Presumably to stop what's in my head
from spilling onto the
deck of the Andromache.
Oh, that's Randall.
Why is Randall lying on my sofa?
(chuckles)
Well, he's not exactly going
to be leading the charge
after the day he had yesterday.
Why are you chained to him?
So I don't try to run.
Thank you.
Sorry, have I done something to you?
Excuse me?
Well, you seem to harbor quite
a bit of anger towards me,
and considering we hardly
even know each other,
I'm wondering if there's
something I'm missing.
Flint and his crew offer you a
life of freedom and prosperity
for which you repay them
by stealing the product
of months of their labor and sacrifice.
But you're not finished. Then you
lure Max into your selfish scheme.
Hold on.
I specifically tried to talk her out
of getting wrapped up in my selfish scheme.
I know all I need to know
about the kind of man you are.
Ma'am, you should come outside right away.
Richard: For years, we've
all profited in this place,
trading on the stability
of my family's name.
But unfortunately, our
circumstances have changed.
A fortnight ago, His Majesty's Navy
attempted to place me under arrest.
(crowd murmuring)
I am, since that day, a fugitive
marked for execution by the Crown.
(crowd groaning)
Unbeknownst to me, my family in Boston
learned of this and ordered Captain Bryson
to liquidate our holdings here.
- (crowd yelling)
- Man: What about our goods?
I convinced him to leave behind
the contents of our warehouse,
but that is all.
To those of you owed credit
or for whom we held goods on consignment,
I leave it to my daughter to see
you made whole as best we can.
But once that is settled,
our business with you
must be considered complete.
(crowd groaning, yelling)
I'm very sorry. Godspeed to you all.
Man 2: I want my money back!
- (grunting)
- (Water splashing)
We aren't closing on her!
I said to raise all the canvas!
- What's our speed?
- Sails are all raised!
No, they're not.
Where are my t'gallants
on the main and mizzen?
De Groot: Captain, we're fully loaded.
If we raise the t'gallants,
the mast won't hold.
Man: Stand by to stretch that starboard!
Time.
Present speed: six knots.
We need at least another knot
if we're to catch up by dark.
- Raise the t'gallants.
- Captain...
Shift aft the back stays if
you're worried about the masts.
Shift 'em to the stern if you have to.
Even if the back stays
hold at such an angle,
and I wager they won't,
the load on the sails
will exceed capacity and
she'll dig in hard at the bow.
She'll hold.
Hard enough to shake
loose the rigging entirely.
Captain, Mr. De Groot makes a good point.
The speed we'll pick up will
come with dire risks for the ship.
But I think she can take it.
Mr. De Groot, quickly, please.
- Raise the t'gallants!
- Man: Raise the t'gallants!
Man 2: Out of the way!
Brace up another five degrees!
- Five degrees!
Bring her up into it.
(wind gusting)
(grunting)
More!
Brace up a little more!
That's well!
- That's well.
- Man 2: Hold on!
(yells, grunts)
Now bring her up into it.
More, damn it. (grunts)
Like this!
(yelling)
Aye, Captain!
There.
Hold it there. Hold her tight.
Speed! Again, please!
Time!
Seven and a half knots!
(crew cheering)
All right, ladies, get some rest.
In a few hours, things are
gonna get awfully interesting.
Good morning, dear.
"Orders from Boston,
unbeknownst to me."
You sent Bryson away.
Yes.
You lied to my face, you shit.
And what choice did you leave me?
You let Flint seduce you
into his madness about the Spanish galleon
all in furtherance of the fantasy
that you can resist English rule,
that your authority in this place
is yours to do with as you please.
I am more to this place than you ever were.
You are a child.
I'm fully aware that Captain Flint
left in pursuit of the
Andromache last night.
But you should know
Captain Bryson sailed the Velasco route
for 10 years and was never boarded.
Not once.
Flint will be returning either
empty-handed or not at all.
This treasure galleon business is over.
As for our future here,
I am working on a deal
that'll make a safe place
for us among the farmers in the interior.
- (scoffs)
- When the pirates are gone,
the landowners will drive commerce here.
They'll be indispensable to
the lords and to Whitehall,
and so we will make allies of them.
We will adapt and we will survive.
I won't ask you to walk
out with me right now.
I know your pride would never permit it.
The Barlow cunt who was
supposed to watch over you,
that's Flint's problem.
But Scott...
what the fuck did you
have to threaten him with
to get him to betray me?
We talked like men and he saw reason.
Fuck you.
I been sayin' it. You ain't been listening.
And now it's come to pass.
The day that gentleman and his daughter
tell you that the money they took
ain't never coming back.
(crowd yelling)
Lilywhite: Yeah, that
were just fucking theft!
Right now, that little girl
is sitting in there counting your money
and laughing her scrawny ass off
on how much she has
lifted out of your pockets.
This is fucking nuts!
- We're not working!
- Good riddance, yeah!
(gasps)
I thought my men could help
keep tempers from boiling over,
for a while at least.
But for those owed money out there,
it's only a matter of
time before their tempers
can no longer be held in check.
Now, if I may, I suggest an
announcement of payments to settle debts.
The longer it takes them to hear it,
the more fuel Lilywhite
can throw on the fire.
I can't pay them all.
You're short?
How short?
Well, get out your books, then.
Certain crews may defer
their debts if I ask them.
Any leads you have on future
scores would soften the blow.
Troublemakers we need
to pay off first...
No.
I'm not winding things up here.
My business continues.
Captain Naft of the Intrepid.
Mr. Walker, her quartermaster.
Captain Lawrence of the
Black Hind and Mr. Harrison.
And our friend Mr. Frasier.
Get them all here now.
Miss Guthrie?
I'm not sure you recognize
the gravity of this situation.
Have a drink. Relax.
Everything's under control.
(crowd yelling)
Hamund: She's fucking done!
That Guthrie cunt is done.
Have you not heard?
We've heard.
Well, then what the fuck
are we doing in here?
At the moment, I'm
remembering what it feels like
to have food in my belly.
- Care to join us?
- Jesus, Jack.
We're free of her. Free to hunt again.
So get off your ass and find us a ship.
To assume that we've seen
the last of Eleanor Guthrie
is, well, not to know her.
The fact that she appears to have Captain
Hornigold and his men propping her up
only adds to my conviction.
Right now, we'd do well
to keep our mouths shut,
be thankful we have some
income from this place,
for the moment, and bide our time.
Fuck that.
She's got no ships. She's got no business.
That means she's out.
And I'm going over there
to make sure she knows it.
Captain?
I'll be upstairs.
Well, then, fuck you both.
Who's with me?
Nothing can ever be simple.
(scoffs) I can make it simple.
Darling, this is a lovely stopgap,
but if we are to ever hunt
as a proper crew again,
we will need, well, a crew.
Right now, those men are all we have.
It's unfortunate, perhaps,
but no less a reality.
Why don't we take advantage of
Mr. Hamund's momentary distraction
and have Mrs. Mapleton tend
to the whore on the beach?
(drops fork)
(scoffs)
- Man: Two six!
- Heave!
- Two six!
Stand by! Stand by!
(knock on door)
Ahem.
Yes, Mr. Hayes?
Hayes: The Walrus will be
upon us in roughly four hours,
present speed.
I assume preparations have been made.
Yes, sir.
And the shipment of china plate?
I beg your pardon?
We have 70 plates of Chinese
porcelain in the hold,
which I have undertaken to
deliver to Boston unharmed.
May I suggest more straw in the chest?
Yes, sir.
He's certain this is all we have?
We emptied the girl before we careened her.
This is the best I could
do before we set sail.
Same for food and water, I assume?
Food, water, powder, all of it.
Right. Take it all up top.
No reserves on this one.
Either we take Bryson's ship or we're...
I believe the word you're
looking for is "fucked."
- Yeah, thank you.
- Yeah.
Dufresne?
You can't be serious.
Andromache's manned like a warship.
60 men at least, and they're fighters.
So we'll need every body we can
muster on this one, yours included.
Come on.
(birds screeching)
(dogs barking)
(goats bleating)
Come on, everything's at sixes and sevens
back at the house
and I have to come and tend to this.
All right. Come on, love.
Here we go.
Open your legs.
- (water squirts)
- (Winces)
Oh, hush, unless you want to find yourself
carrying one of those fools' brats.
- (water squirts)
- Ow!
Get out.
(whimpers)
She wasn't using enough lotion.
- (water squirting softly)
- (Whimpering)
You could've left.
(water squirting softly)
When that cunt beat Hamund
off of you, you could've left.
You didn't.
Thought you could
sweet-talk them all, did ya?
What do you care?
Once, one of them came and put his balls
on my shoulder whilst I was asleep.
Thought it was funny.
Last time he put them anywhere.
If you take it, they'll give it.
Why do you say these things?
You were the one who threw
me to them in the first place.
I only thought they'd kill you.
Lilywhite: Do you feel that
soreness between your haunches?
Yeah, well, that's what you get
when you let some cunt
who's never raised a sail,
set foot on a deck tell you your business!
(crowd shouting)
Next thing you know,
she'll have her boot on your throat
and her hand in your fucking pocket.
I think he's talking about you.
Lilywhite: That's what you get when
you're letting a wench tell you...
If you're pretending to remain unconcerned
for my peace of mind, please don't.
It amuses me that you think
I would even give a shit
- about your peace of mind.
- Silver: Of course.
Still, I don't think you're giving that
problem out there its due attention.
(door opens)
Naft and Walker just
arrived. That's everyone.
You've never seen a mob turn, have you?
Funny thing.
The people most surprised when it happens,
usually the ones that gave
rise to it in the first place.
Can you join me, please, Captain?
I want you to hear this, too.
Hamund: Is the cunt still here?
- Out on the street, friend.
- Where is she?
It's a rough world out there, isn't it?
Someone opens their mouth,
you can lose everything.
Tell me, lass...
how's it feel?
Out now.
Well, if we're not welcome in here,
I suppose we can go spend more time
with our friend on the beach.
(pirate chuckles)
Oh, wonderful lass she is.
So, um...
resilient.
(pirates laugh)
So appreciative of what she's given.
We'll send her your love.
(laughs)
- Come on, boys.
- (Pirate laughs)
(speaks African dialect)
Billy: Gentlemen...
I think we all know what
we're up against today,
so let's just get to it.
As we close the distance to the Andromache,
the captain believes
Bryson will attack port
and set himself for a
clean broadside volley.
He'll loose his guns, pay off downwind,
and continue running.
Now, ordinarily,
we would either match him and return fire
or slip into his wake and
make a run at his stern.
Unfortunately, we're too
outgunned for the former,
and Bryson is too skilled
a captain for the latter.
He'll just keep shooting and delaying
and shooting and delaying until nightfall,
at which point he'll just slip away.
So...
So, if we can't shoot at her
and we can't get close to her,
how the hell do we board her?
(murmuring)
We go straight at her.
Without the bow chasers, we'll
be sitting ducks for her guns.
She'll rake us bow to stern.
Logan: Not to mention we'd
be boarding bow to midship.
For all you virgins in the room,
that's also known as fucking suicide.
Billy: Of course we'd need
to board alongside her.
We just need Captain Bryson to cooperate
and bring the Andromache
about for us to do so.
And how the hell do we get him to do that?
Mr. Beauclerc is going to convince him.
(blows)
You're a natural, son.
When this is all over, I'll
be lucky to still have a job.
(laughs)
- What...
- I keep accounts.
That's what I'm good at.
Do you see this number here?
That's how much I've saved
this crew this last year alone.
Can you say of any other man here
that they've earned as much?
Every man on this crew had a first time.
You're overdue.
But I've never even shot a pistol.
Well, that's all right.
Half the time they don't even fire.
I'm sorry.
Time has come for us to tell those who aim
- to make us slaves.
- (Knock on door)
Woman: Mr. Rackham asked me to tend to you.
Lilywhite: Yeah, well, that's what you get.
He said I wasn't to take no for an answer.
They're saying she may be finished.
She's finally got her due.
All I meant is that...
that it should please
you after what she did.
You hate her. I hate her.
They all hate her.
Look what's good it's done us.
No captain on this island's
ever known that kind of power.
Power that doesn't care how
many votes you can tally,
who loves you, who hates you,
who fears you.
Power that just is.
Truth is,
none of us have any
right to hate her for it.
She's strong and we're weak.
That's the reality of things here.
And no one down there is strong
enough to change anything.
Not you?
You're not strong enough?
I don't know.
But I think it's time I probably found out.
(creaking)
What if he's wrong?
There's a chance Bryson just
keeps running, isn't there?
- That's it, steady.
- Right?
Bryson could still gain speed.
I mean, there has to be a chance
this fight will never materialize.
Come on.
Come on, you bitch.
There she goes!
(crew shouting)
Why isn't he attacking?
Because he knows he'll
never board us if he does.
I will say this for him. He's no coward.
200 yards, you may fire at will.
(shouting)
I don't think I can do this.
Yes, you can.
Listen. Listen to me.
You will make it through this.
No one eats it their
first time over the side.
I'm telling you, it's never
happened. Not on this crew.
Don't ask me why, it just is.
Men die all the time. It can't be true.
No, not first-timers.
Name one.
You're gonna be all right.
Come on.
Damn it.
I hope you know what you're doing.
So do I.
Mr. Beauclerc? Range?
Almost there!
50 more yards, Captain!
Fire!
- Let her go.
- Fire!
- Incoming!
- (Men scream)
Fire!
(yelling)
(groaning)
Get 'em back into the cookroom!
- Get 'em back!
- (Yelling)
We can't take much more of this.
Aye. Mr. Beauclerc!
- Two six!
- Heave!
Hayes, another volley right away!
Right cannon round!
Mr. Burnett, prepare to bear
away and bring us into the wind.
Man the braces!
Fire!
(man screams)
- (yells)
- Beauclerc, do it!
Stay where you are!
Bring us to starboard
before we lose the wind!
- Mr. Harris, take the helm!
- Aye, sir!
Fire.
Man: We've lost the wind, Captain.
Prepare to repel boarders!
Bring us around to the port side!
On the rails!
(shouting)
- (guns firing)
- (Gasping)
Now!
20 yards! At the ready.
Get across the gap, choose your targets!
Pistols at zero range.
Don't waste a shot.
Nets in!
(crew shouting)
Nets up, nets up, nets up!
Get it!
10 yards! Go, go, go!
Over! Get it over!
Hold, get down! Hold, hold!
- (gunfire continues)
- Hold!
(all grunt)
(exhales)
Go, go, go!
(all shouting)
(grunting)
(yells)
(panting)
(muffled yelling)
(gasps)
(yelling)
(buzzing)
Dufresne?
Jesus.
Come on.
(cheering)
No fucking longer!
Gentlemen, you all heard
my father this morning,
that the Guthrie trading
operation here in Nassau is dead.
To that, I just
have this to add...
fuck him and fuck that.
Mr. Frasier, you hold a charter from the
Massachusetts Bay Provincial Authority
to ship rare items abroad, is that correct?
That's correct, yes.
And, theoretically, that
charter should pass muster
at any customshouse in the colonies, yes?
Well, I suppose so, but...
Gentlemen, by my count,
the Black Hind and the Intrepid
have accumulated prizes
totaling approximately
1,600 pieces of eight since the new year.
That's gross. That's both ships.
That barely exceeds your
operating costs over the same time.
If you brought us
here to insult us...
It's not an insult, it's a fact.
You command the two least
profitable ships on the island
as a function of basic arithmetic.
But they are ships, and large ones at that.
At this table, we have a legitimate front.
We have ships and crews
that can ferry heavy cargo.
We have relationships with
the merchants and customs men
that kept my father's trade moving.
Your father said he'll take
no part in any further...
They're my relationships now.
We're going to recreate
my father's system here...
without my father.
A consortium, with all of
you sharing in the profits.
- You're mad.
- How so?
My men aren't merchant sailors.
They're hunters.
Yes, but they're bad at it, Geoffrey.
What good is that doing anyone?
I put this to them, they'll vote me out
before I stop to take a breath.
I'm amazed they haven't
voted you out already,
given the shit prizes you've been chasing.
Your men will earn three times
as much in half the time...
- (scoffs)
- Not facing a single sword or pistol in the process.
You're telling me that you can't sell that?
I can sell that.
(sighs)
And you're supporting this?
I don't know. Am I?
None of this matters
unless we can get people
to agree to sell through us.
We need a respected captain
to stand up and bless it.
And we need a strong captain to
ensure that no one dares fuck with us.
You're both.
You know that I want nothing more
than to make this place strong and stable.
I think you want the same things.
Bless this endeavor and we can have them.
I'll do that...
the moment you lift
the ban on Captain Vane.
- Excuse me?
- Listen to that mob outside.
They're tired of your
edicts, your rule by fear.
They believe you to be
a tyrant in a petticoat.
Your action against Captain Vane
is, to them, the most egregious case.
You want me to lift the ban on Charles Vane
to appease a handful of
malcontents on the street?
Those malcontents will be a
problem to anyone in this room
who stands behind you today.
Provocation, even sabotage.
And then you'll ask my men to assume
the responsibility of
defending all of you from it.
Charles Vane is an animal, as
are the men that remain with him.
Because they saw fit to
punish a thieving whore.
I'm not about to say otherwise for
the benefit of Captain Lilywhite
or any of the other idiots
out there listening to him.
I'm listening to him.
Your commitment to this place is admirable,
but you're young and you're rash.
Show everyone your motive
here is for the common good.
Show them that you can be trusted
to keep petty animosity
separate from business.
Rescind the ban on Captain
Vane and show me that.
Do it and I'll back you as
your father's successor here,
the boss behind all trade.
Until then, I'm sorry. I can't help you.
I won't do it.
You have until dark to come to your senses.
At that point, I will withdraw my men
and the business of the street
becomes your business alone.
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
Ah!
- Man: Oh, no! Get down!
- (Explosion)
(men yell)
Man: Take this.
Checked all the dead and injured.
None of them are Bryson.
He only left three men to
defend the quarterdeck bunker.
How does that make sense?
Gates: The vanguard are on their
way to clear the cargo hold.
Maybe Bryson is hiding down there.
Something's not right.
Captain, the rudder's not responding.
Someone must've cut the
mechanism below decks.
Call back the vanguard.
- (gunfire)
- (All yell)
- (labored breathing)
- (Metal squeaking)
Three men dead on their end, Captain.
Perhaps it's time we sent them our terms.
I do apologize for this.
Mr. Guthrie's orders were explicit.
No matter what, I was to make
sure that you were on this ship.
This was not the deal.
(chuckles)
Assist the Andromache to depart unmolested
and you can remain with the girl
and pick up the pieces
and explain yourself.
Mr. Scott, you sided with
his daughter against him.
You forgot your duty.
You must have known there
would be consequences.
But we men of duty must often
put our feelings aside...
as you're about to witness.
(speaks West African Pidgin English)
Do it.
(groans)
- And this one?
- (Speaks West African Pidgin English)
(door opens)
(crowd chanting)
At the risk of overstepping my bounds,
I think you should agree to
Captain Hornigold's terms.
Lift the ban. What
do you care about...
They're beating her.
She chose it.
(scoffs) "She chose it"?
"She chose it."
I've been repeating those words to myself
for well over a week now
and I find them wanting.
Now he asks me to back off Charles,
to proclaim to the world that
what happened to Max is acceptable,
to apologize to those animals
for having ever said otherwise,
and smile while they lord it over me.
To make a dangerous situation
a lot less dangerous.
Then convince me.
Convince me that I should
betray her a second time...
because that's what it
feels like I would be doing.
Max chose.
Why? I don't know.
Maybe it was spite, maybe it was strength,
maybe it was who the fuck knows what.
To be perfectly honest, I don't care
because the moment I start making choices
based on her decisions,
I've given her a hell of a
lot more power over my life
than I am quite comfortable
ceding to a perfect stranger.
Guilt is natural.
It also goes away if you let it.
Losing your life's work...
that doesn't go away.
- Lilywhite: No fucking longer!
- (Cheering)
Captain?
Charles?
Do I understand correctly
that you've requested a skiff?
I suppose that's none of my business,
but you do realize that we
may be able to hunt again soon.
What I'm hearing is all
second and thirdhand,
but something is happening in that tavern.
Our problem isn't in there.
Never was.
What the hell are you talking about?
Chaz?
Where are you going?
Where is he?
Gates: He's in a reinforced hold
directly beneath us here.
Forward end of the lower gundeck.
Doors as thick as the
outer hull, as is the roof.
Impossible to breach from here.
He's also sitting right in
front of a powder magazine,
so if we try to blow our way through,
this whole ship is going down fast.
Unless we can find a way in,
there's no way to get
the guns off the boat.
Anybody we send down there is
just gonna get cut to shreds.
And we cannot sail.
It doesn't make sense.
If Bryson wants to force us to withdraw,
what's to stop me from
burning the ship once we leave?
We're missing something.
- (wood creaking)
- (Lamps creaking)
There you are.
Been looking all over for you.
Thought I'd get a head start
going through Bryson's papers.
Jameson.
Beg your pardon?
You said no man ever died
his first time over the side,
but you forgot about Tom Jameson,
boatswain's mate, about two years back.
That's right.
Also Christian Thoms,
Will Robbins, Jean DuBois,
that Portuguese
guy with the lisp...
what was his name?
- That is funny.
- (Chuckles)
Thank you...
for doing that.
It helped.
(pats back)
Miranda Barlow?
Man: Away from the hatch!
Everyone!
(guns cock)
Captain Flint.
(speaks African dialect)
He says, "I'm secure in the hold below."
(man speaking African dialect)
"With 20 of my men. I
can wait, but you cannot."
(speaking African dialect)
"Before departing,"
I sent a message to the
captain of the Scarborough.
I told him where I was headed,
"and I told him where he would find you."
Man: Sail to the east!
Good God.
The Scarborough!
- (yells)
- Man 2: Look out!
(gunshot)
(grunts)
(panting)
(music playing)