♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Did you ever want it? ♪
♪ Did you want it bad? ♪
♪ Oh, my ♪
♪ It tears me apart ♪
♪ We can try to hide it ♪
♪ It's all the same ♪
♪ I've been losing you ♪
♪ One day at a time ♪
♪ And I know
In my heart, in this cold heart ♪
♪ [can live or I can die ♪
♪ I believe if I just try ♪
♪ You believe in you and I ♪
♪ Inyouandl? l
No! No!
I pushed him.
Listen to me! Listen to me! I pushed him.
Nobody did this.
Nobody.
Help! Somebody help me!
Fuck.
Hey, Ed. Ed.
Hold on, man. Hey.
Hey. Listen, man.
I'm sorry for the whole party thing.
Yeah, I overreacted.
You know what? I don't believe you.
- What?
- That you're sorry.
- Why do you have to be such a fuck?
- Well, I don't have to be. I choose to be.
See, not everybody gets along, Nathan.
I mean, can't we just be comfortable
not liking each other?
Doesn't have to be a reason.
This whole fucking world's lost its mind.
This whole fucking planet
is inhabited by nutfucks!
Hey, nutfuck!
Basically, this is child custody.
We will set a hearing.
I will appoint a psychiatric investigator.
He or she will interview the parties, the
children, your associates, your friends,
anybody and everybody
he or she deems necessary
to making a recommendation
to the court.
In the end, it will come down
to my judgment
whether there's been behavior
detrimental to the children.
- Any questions so far?
- May I be heard, Your Honor?
Very well.
I do not consider Celeste Wright
to be a bad person.
- Good to know.
- A wonderful mother.
- Mary Louise.
- And I don't have any reason to doubt
- her ongoing commitment to them.
- Okay.
- So, what are we doing here?
- That said, she's not well.
- All right.
- It's true.
- This isn't the time, Mrs. Wright.
- Well, that you understand.
This is not a case of angry mother-in-law
on the loose or something.
- So unfair.
- Rather, it's as you suggest,
we have to do
what is best for the children.
We will take this up
at another time. This is inappropriate.
- Yeah, we're good.
- Thank you.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
We will see you at the hearing.
- How do we not respond to that?
- Because we don't.
- You're a lawyer.
- But we should have.
She gets to make a sympathetic first
impression, and what, I just sit there silent?
Which, in the face of an accusation, can be
deemed an admission of fucking guilt.
The judge won't see it that way.
She's after my kids.
That's exactly the type of flare-up
they'll be looking to provoke. Okay?
God.
She gets to make an opening statement,
and you did nothing.
I didn't hire you to do nothing.
Please.
Because nothing
was exactly the right response, Celeste.
We have a very smart judge in there.
One who will be able to see through
your mother-in-law's performance
and see it for what it was.
Just a performance.
I told you, I am not about putting up that
kind of performance. I'm about credibility.
So when I speak, judges listen.
- And now I need you to listen.
- Okay.
They don't win here
unless they establish you as unhinged.
So you should expect everything
and anything they do say
to be precisely designed
to get you to react.
We will not give them that.
Mom.
Hi.
- What a nice surprise.
- Hi.
- Where's Dad?
- Outside with Grandpa.
Is she getting better?
A little.
Still can't talk, though.
- Today's gym, right?
- Mm-hm.
- Got all your stuff?
- Yep.
Oh, I miss you.
There's a surprise for you at home.
- Shh. Hey. What?
- Oh, yeah?
- Okay.
- All right. Time to go, big girl.
- Pit stop's over.
- Okay.
Bye, Grandma.
Love you, baby. Thanks for stopping by.
Bye. I love you. Bye, Grandpa.
Bye.
The most important thing
is that you remain open-minded.
You know, really, open to new theories...
This isn't gonna be like
wife-swapping, is it?
No. This is a healing institute.
Not a swingers' convention.
Please have an open mind. Please?
I'm in the car.
We're warriors, you and me. You know?
♪ Before the day I met you ♪
- J& Life was so unkind ♪
- ♪ Life was so unkind ♪
♪ But your love was the key
To my peace of mind ♪
♪ Peace of mind ♪
- ♪ You make me feel ♪
Really?
I couldn't believe it.
I sat there and I didn't say anything.
Katie seems to think that's the right thing
to do, I'm not thinking straight.
- Yeah, I know.
- I'm just not.
This is disgusting. I mean, honestly,
I wanna sit down with Mary Louise.
Well, I don't think that that would help.
I don't know, Celeste.
Listen, don't get me wrong,
but, um, you're an attorney yourself,
and we gotta just say it:
lawyers fuck things up often.
And that's why
I wanted to ask you about Katie.
- Well, what about her?
- Well, I mean, is she...
- Is she as good as people say?
- She's good because of this.
It's a very different kind of skill set,
and judges in family court
don't like bulldogs.
And so I think given that, she's good.
I mean, I think the straightest line
to get this resolved
- is just to have Mary Louise call it off. Mm...
- No. She's not gonna do that. She's not.
She might.
I need to take a crack at her.
- Okay? This is what I do.
- Renata.
- Yeah? We're in a meeting.
- Renata. I'm so sorry.
I just got a call from Suzie Jenkins,
San Francisco Magazine,
and please don't shoot the messenger.
They are not going to include you
in the "Women in Power" piece.
I'm sorry?
- Did she say why?
- Um...
The bankruptcy thing.
- Listen, I can step out.
- No, no, my God, no. No.
No. Stay right there.
They said it's not the story
that they're telling.
She just said the focus is women on top.
- I'm so sorry. I...
- No, I mean, my God, it's not your fault.
- I know, I just feel terrible...
- I said it's not your fault!
Can you excuse us?
I can make you some
Africa Zimbabwe tea.
If you just stop talking.
Okay, I'm gonna go away.
That would be best.
Are you okay?
I am not okay, Celeste.
Well, I mean, it's just a magazine article.
It's not just a magazine.
It's Women in Power!
I mean, we're supposed to be
on each other's side,
and they're backstabbing sluts.
"Ziggy." That's a dumb ass name.
My brother knows about you.
He said you have a hot mom.
Is that true?
You know you're a mistake, right?
Come on, pussy boy.
Say something.
What's going on?
Beat it. I'm talking to someone.
Leave my brother alone.
He's your brother?
That means your dad's a rapist.
- Get the hell out of here!
- Make me.
His name is Brian McPherson.
He is a bit difficult,
and he has bullied others.
But he's the one sitting in the hospital
getting his lip stitched up.
Oh, my God.
- I'm suspending all four boys.
- What?
It's just three days.
While we investigate...
Investigate? Why didn't you do that first?
It was three against one.
The boy got hurt.
My hands are tied.
You need to tell me
what he said to you.
Hey. Uh-uh. Look at me.
What did he say?
- I told you. I can't remember.
- Ziggy.
He said my father's a rapist.
Answer me!
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
I'll take over.
Okay.
- I'll see you later.
- See you.
Be open-minded, okay?
- Look at the view.
- It is pretty.
And they have a fireplace.
So you're gonna wander the space.
We're not moving in a circle.
We're exploring the space,
and when you come face-to-face
with someone you'd like to hug,
give them a hug for about the length
of a nice inhale, exhale. Okay?
Good.
Thank you.
Oh, my God.
That was awful. I'm so sorry.
Thank you for at least agreeing to try.
You're a really good man.
Good husband, good father.
I was a sound choice.
What are you saying?
- What? What are you trying to say?
- I've said it many times, Madeline.
Saying it one more time
is not gonna kill you, is it?
Nathan broke your world,
which at its core is family.
- You've said it many times.
- I know. I've said it many, many times.
- Is it a fucking crime?
- I didn't say it was a fucking crime.
Okay, then,
what are you trying to say to me?
Please just tell me. I have no idea.
On our first dates,
it was like you were interviewing me.
Not so much for the soulmate position
or lover.
But rather, father.
The stable provider.
Abigail was ripped apart
and you were determined to fix that.
To not make the mistake
of going down the lust path again.
You had a certain criteria,
and I checked all the boxes.
So you made the sound, practical choice.
It's not something
I couldn't make peace with. I did.
But then you got unsound.
You decided to make impractical choices,
one being to fuck Joseph Bachman,
which left me
with the most difficult choice of all:
to walk out with my dignity or to stay
with a woman who I simply cannot trust.
You can trust me to love you.
More deeply
than I've ever loved anybody.
Can you trust me
not to fuck things up again?
Maybe not.
I don't know
if I can trust myself with that.
I didn't trust my parents' marriage,
and the one I had with Nathan
was not to be believed.
And I don't know what itis, I don't...
Maybe it's some unconscious,
preemptive thing
where I wanna be the destroyer,
not the destroyee.
I don't understand,
and I racked my brain about it, but I...
Because all I really want
is to be married to you.
Just happily married to you.
But I must have low self-esteem
or I fucking hate myself or something
because look what I've done.
If I fuck up again,
it will not be with infidelity.
I give you my word.
All my future mistakes
will be brand-new ones.
They said it was ultimately a smear on the
entire publication if I was in this article.
I'm sorry. That sucks.
You know,
it might actually be for the best.
What?
L... The article would have put a target
right on your back.
I've spent my entire life
with a bull's-eye on my back.
This is one I wanted.
That's for me.
Coming!
- Oh, Mary Louise.
- Hello.
- Hi. Thank you so much for coming.
- Thank you.
Pleasure's mine. I don't often
get invited for tea in this neck.
Well, please. Please. Um...
What kind of tea would you like?
Again, I just... I wanna say I really
appreciate you coming because, um...
I know there's a lot going on, and,
uh, it must be so unbearably difficult.
It is. Thank you for...
For understanding that.
Of course. My God.
And listen, just between you and me,
I did want us...
I was hoping
this would just be about tea.
But people don't do that anymore.
Do they?
Uh...
Do what?
Just enjoy each other's company.
Just no agenda.
It would be so nice
if people could just be together, you know.
But maybe somebody will invent an app
for that.
Well, um, can I...
talk to you?
Just mother to mother.
I would like that.
Great. And thinking about
everything that's going on...
What happened to your furniture?
I mean, it's such a big house, you would
think there would be a lot of furniture.
Well, we're going through
a little bankruptcy thing right now,
which is almost resolved.
- But, um...
- Oh, that sounds awful.
- Well...
- But you work, don't you, Renata?
- I do. Yes.
- Yeah.
That must be especially devastating
for a working mom
to lose her house, her belongings,
because just to think about the sacrifice...
You know, all the missed dinners with kids,
and the not being able to host
the after-school play dates,
there's just so many,
many moments lost.
And for what? A screening room.
Maybe a boat.
Sorry.
You were saying... Oh. Mother to mother?
Are you placing judgment
on my life choices?
I don't know your life choices.
I don't know you,
other than you're a friend of Celeste,
and you seem like a very nice person
who lives in a big house with no furniture.
This is a serious situation and the boy
needed stitches, so I need to know.
Who instigated the fight?
Was it you, Max?
- Was it?
- He was saying stuff about Dad.
And he was picking on Ziggy.
So, what?
So the three of you attacked him?
You ganged up on him?
You can't do that.
Violence is not the answer.
Look at me. You think it is?
What?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Stop being such a bitch.
Don't talk to me like that!
You do not talk to me like that!
Come here. Stop it.
You can't talk to your mother like that.
You can't talk to me like that.
Do you understand me?
It's not right.
I have an appointment tonight.
Kelly's gonna be here in a minute to sit.
What kind of appointment?
Oh, um...
With a lawyer.
Your grandmother thinks it would be better
if you lived with her for a little while,
and I disagree, and it's...
Why does she think that?
Because I... I don't know.
- We're not gonna live here anymore?
- No, you're gonna live here.
We have to have a judge decide, and
that's what I have to go and do tonight.
I don't wanna live with Grandma.
I don't want you to live with Grandma
and you're not going to.
You will be living here.
All right?
You will absolutely be living here.
♪ I know change is gonna come ♪
Hey, honey.
It's okay.
You okay? All right.
All right.
Yummy.
Sink into the floor.
♪ A love like ours is
love that's hard to find ♪
- Keep it going. Keep it going.
- ♪ How could we let it slip away? ♪
- ♪ We've come too far to leave it all behind ♪
- Let me hear you.
Is Mom okay?
What the hell is that?
Singing for sleep apnea.
Stanford Sleep Clinic.
They diagnose everyone.
The class is a cash cow. What's up?
Well, um...
Not your mother.
I think we need to get her out
of this hospital.
Aren't they moving her to rehab?
Which means
they're throwing their hands up.
- They don't think she'll get better?
- We need to do something.
Look at you, getting involved.
Wow.
I gotta go.
- Dad.
- You don't think I got involved?
That I didn't protect you?
- No, Dad, I don't.
- If you only goddamn knew.
I do goddamn know. I was there.
Did you diffuse things? Sure.
Did you stop shit from getting worse?
Sometimes. But did you protect me?
♪ We've come too far
to leave it all behind ♪
Well, thank you for agreeing to meet.
I'll get right to the point.
There are only losers
in procedures like these,
and the biggest ones, invariably,
being the children.
So my suggestion is that we agree
to joint custody, one where...
- No. No. No.
- Just hear me out, please. Hear me out.
One where weekdays with you...
- Are you kidding me? No.
- Hear me out. No, just hear me out.
Weekdays with you. Weekends
with my client, Saturdays and Sundays.
- What?
- You would seek treatment
for drug and alcohol dependency,
as well as anger management.
- Once you... Well, there you go.
- Fuck you.
Now, these things will come up,
Mrs. Wright.
Is that a threat?
That's a fact.
You... You're not getting my boys.
Not for a Saturday, not for a Sunday,
not for a fucking minute.
Did you really expect me to accept this?
How are the boys doing?
You know,
we don't want this to go to court.
There will be no joint custody.
I see silence continues
to be your weapon of choice.
- Exactly what am I paying you for?
- It was actually a decent offer.
- No.
- There are so many possibilities
should this go to court, Celeste.
A lot of them bad.
- You said we should win.
- We should.
But we could also lose. The offer
we just got is a win in my opinion.
Oh, God.
There's also...
What?
- What?
- Your husband's death.
It will come up.
Shit.
There's gonna be a guardianship hearing.
I'm gonna have to testify, and that means
that I'm fair game on everything.
- Fuck, you're right.
- And Katie is pretty much convinced
- that Farber is getting help from the police.
- She is?
- What?
- Christ.
So, basically, he's an agent for them,
and I suppose they can ask me anything.
- Under oath.
- Yeah.
- Oh, my God.
- And if I get caught in, like, a lie
or something, then they have a case.
- Can you just plead the Fifth?
- No, I'll lose my kids, Madeline.
That's true.
And they have this witness list with you.
You were all on the list.
But why would they call us?
We're on your side.
Madeline, please.
It's a fucking perjury trap.
That's what they would do. They'd call us to
the stand to testify to Celeste's fitness.
- Yeah.
- Then under oath, they say, "Oh, by the way,
- how did Perry Wright fall down the stairs?"
- No.
- Yes.
- Can they do that?
- Okay, but then we just stick with our story.
That's perjury, babe.
Okay, but they'd have to prove
we were lying.
They probably can't.
What if they can?
I'm just telling you this
because we have to be prepared.
Look, we have to stick together.
That's the only way we've gotten this far.
If we stick together, we'll be fine.
We're gonna be fine.
Thank you again. He really likes you.
You're welcome.
Any time. He's a pleasure.
Still up?
And on your iPad, I see,
which you're not supposed to have at night.
Can I please have that?
Thank you.
Listen, um,
me and you are gonna have breakfast
with Max and Josh in the morning.
I have to work for a few hours,
but I'm gonna get off early
and I'll meet you guys at Whaler's Cove,
I don't know, sometime in the afternoon.
And then you, me, Celeste, and the boys
are gonna go kayaking.
- Cool.
- It's not a reward for bad behavior.
I just figured since you're suspended,
I mean, we might as well get some exercise.
You like Corey, right?
Mm-hm.
Yeah, I do.
Me too.
That's good.
Am I gonna grow up to be like him?
- Like Corey?
- No.
Like my father.
No. God, no, baby.
And you are gonna grow up
to be the sweetest, kindest,
most handsome, funniest, loveliest,
adorablest man.
I promise you that.
Thanks, Mom.
I love you.
Baby?
He's at the hospital, sitting vigilantly.
He wanted us to take a break.
Sweet.
I was protecting you.
Or so I thought.
Best way I could, by keeping the peace.
It's okay, Dad.
I know how weak I must seem to you.
But I was just trying to do whatever I
could to make the rage go away. For you.
And for me.
- Okay.
- And for her.
She started to talk this afternoon.
To mumble.
I had no idea what she was trying to say.
Uh...
She tried and she tried,
and finally, I got it.
What did she say?
She said you're drowning.
Sometimes the things she feels and sees
turn out to be right, and now I'm worried.
Dad.
- What's going on?
- I'm just gonna go check on Skye.
Why is Grandma doing this?
Because I think she's worried
that I'm still sad over missing your daddy,
and she...
She thinks that my sadness
isn't always good for you two.
So she thinks it would be better
if you lived with her.
For a while, while I get over my sadness.
Do you think that?
No.
Mm-mm. I do not think that.
So I don't know what kind of questions
this doctor is gonna ask,
but if she asks you,
who you would prefer to live with,
then it's really important
that you say you wanna live here.
Because she might tell the judge?
Exactly.
She might tell the judge.
Well, shall we say
we don't like Grandma?
No, don't say that.
We can protect you.
Yeah.
We can say whatever you want us to say.
Listen to me.
You do not need to protect me.
All right?
You just have to tell the truth
that you wanna live here.
Okay.
I love you.
Get good sleep.
Big day tomorrow.
Good night, Mom.
- Good night.
Hey, Sweet Pea.
How come I'm not at school?
Sweetie, I told you.
Ziggy and Max and Josh are having
their special day with their moms,
and I thought, "Well, wait a minute.
Let's us have a mother-daughter day."
This is because we're broke, isn't it?
And we have to move.
No, Amabella, it's because I wanted
to spend the day with you.
Sweetie, everything isn't about money.
Well, it is, but it isn't.
What matters is this.
Your family, your friends...
Now, when you're ready, I will
race you to that pool, we will dive in,
and we will have so much fun.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Don't worry.
Do you and Ed have another plan?
No, not yet.
You know what I was thinking?
He loves to golf, so I'll learn to golf,
- something we can do together.
- Why would you wanna golf? You hate golf.
True.
But I took a vow. For better or worse.
- All right, all over your face.
- No, it's not. It's fine.
- Mary Louise.
- Madeline.
- Hi.
- Hello.
This is my daughter, Abigail.
This is Mary Louise Wright.
- Hi.
- You must be the one who's off to college.
- Mm...
- Can I say something?
Of course.
What you're doing is indecent.
Trying to take those boys away
from their mother.
- Very nice to meet you, Abigail.
- What's wrong with you?
Huh?
She's psycho.
♪ LamJd
♪ The only one ♪
♪ Can ride that horse ♪
♪ Th'yonder ♪
♪ I'm full of bees ♪
♪ Who died at sea ♪
Please, just go. Just touch me.
Corey, please.
Are you sure?
♪ It's a wonderful life ♪
- Whoa!
- Oh, my God.
Whoa!
You're upside down.
How did you get over there?
Well, you suffered a trauma.
It's gonna take some time.
I just think it's amazing
that you were still able to enjoy sex
all that time.
You know, despite everything.
Yep, it's pretty fucked up.
Come on.
- Me too, me too, me too.
- Yeah, okay.
- My boys miss this.
- Oh, my God.
- My turn again.
- Should I go save him?
All right, boys, let's go.
You ready?
Aw. They miss this so much.
I want you to stop worrying about me
and start thinking about you.
Skye made this for you.
You are right, though,
I'm going through a rough moment.
But you know me...
I'll figure it out.
What, Mama?
Kill me.
Oh, my God.
God, you're so good.
All right.
Hey. Two Brooklyns, please.
- Tori.
- Hi.
- Mommy.
- Hello, ocean!
Hello.
♪ Ooh, baby ♪
-♪ Ooh, baby
-♪ When we're out in the moonlight ♪
-♪ Lookin' up on the stars above ♪
-♪ Ooh, baby
-♪ Feels so good when I'm near you ♪
-♪ Holdin' hands and makin' love ♪
-♪ Ooh, baby
- ♪ Yes, oh, baby ♪
- ♪ Ooh, baby
-♪ Ooh, baby
-♪ Sandy beach and was makin' love
-♪ As a tide moves in on us ♪
-♪ Ooh, baby
-♪ Feels so good walking side by side ♪
-♪ Wanna be with you all my life ♪
- ♪ Ooh, ooh, baby ♪
- ♪ Ooh, baby
- ♪ Yes, oh, baby ♪
-♪ Ooh, baby
-♪ Dreams of you all the time ♪
-♪ Ooh, baby -♪ Feels so
good when we're together, love ♪
-♪ Ooh, baby
-♪ Just can't wait until tomorrow night ♪
-♪ Hey, baby, let's shake it ♪
-♪ Oh, hey, baby I
-♪ Ooh, baby
- ♪ Hey, hey, baby ♪
- ♪ Ooh, baby
- ♪ Yes, oh, baby ♪
-♪ Ooh, baby
-♪ When we're out in the moonlight ♪
-♪ Looking up on the stars above ♪
-♪ Ooh, baby
-♪ Feels so good when I'm near you ♪
-♪ Holding hands and making love I
- ♪ Oh, oh, baby ♪
- ♪ Ooh, baby
- ♪ Yes, oh, baby ♪
♪ Ooh, baby ♪
-♪ Ooh, baby
♪ Sandy beach and I was making love ♪
-♪ As a tide moves in on us ♪
-♪ Ooh, baby
-♪ Feels so good walking side by side ♪
-♪ Wanna be with you all my life ♪
- ♪ Oh, oh, baby ♪
- ♪ Ooh, baby
- ♪ Yes, oh, baby ♪
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::