♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Did you ever want it? ♪
♪ Did you want it bad? ♪
♪ Oh, my ♪
♪ It tears me apart ♪
♪ We can try to hide it ♪
♪ It's all the same ♪
♪ I've been losing you ♪
♪ One day at a time ♪
♪ And I know
In my heart, in this cold heart ♪
♪ [can live or I can die ♪
♪ I believe if I just try ♪
♪ You believe in you and I ♪
♪ Inyouandl? l
♪ There is no reason for you to hide ♪
I must have taken my eyes off the road
and then...
And then I don't...
You don't remember?
I was driving and...
Ma'am, have you had anything to drink?
No, I haven't.
I couldn't sleep last night,
so I took a pill at 2 a.m.
- You don't remember getting in the car?
- No.
But you passed the Breathalyzer?
I did.
Babe, you gotta be careful with Ambien.
Hey.
Hey, Bonnie.
- What are you doing?
- Walking.
In the middle of nowhere?
This isn't the middle of nowhere.
You're on the side of the highway.
I was hiking.
Okay...
What are you doing?
Do you need a ride?
Why would I want a ride if I'm on a hike,
Madeline?
- Are you on drugs?
- Am I on drugs? What are you...?
- I'm sorry...
- I'm just walking. Can I walk?
- That just came out... I'm sorry.
My God.
Do you see what I'm saying?
I have to get Abigail out of her house.
That woman's not well.
- Thank you. Here.
- No, it was eight women.
- Uh-oh. What?
- You are a fucking incredible publicist.
- Thank you. Goodbye.
- What?
Guess who's going to be on the cover
next month
of the number one women's magazine
in the U.S. of fucking A?
- I have no idea.
- Oh, I think you know.
I think you know
because you're fucking married to her.
Oh, baby.
-My cover girl. I've always known
-Gordon Klein.
- You were a cover girl.
- Special Agent Michael Nelson with the FBI.
- Hands on the hood of the car.
- Sorry...
- What's going on?
- Hands on the hood now, sir.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- What the fuck?
- Title 18 of U.S. Code, section 371.
- Hold on! There's confusion, sir.
- That's security fraud...
- That's my husband, Gordon Klein.
Ma'am, please.
- Securities fraud, title 15 of U.S...
- Call Walker.
What the fuck is going on here?
What are you doing?
You can't just assault somebody.
You have the right
to remain silent.
You have the right to have an attorney
present during any questioning.
Call Walker now!
- Let's go.
- You can't...
We need you to stop, ma'am.
You need to relax.
You're taking my husband in handcuffs.
We understand.
We will get you the information.
You had me worried sick.
You know, it's my fault.
I had a bit of an emergency this morning,
and Celeste came to my rescue.
Where's your car?
It broke down.
Are the boys okay?
Uh, yes, they're getting ready for school.
You went out like that?
- Well, I had to.
- It was an emergency.
What kind of an emergency?
The kind short people have?
You don't like me, do you, Madeline?
I'm sure you mean well.
You know, when I was very young,
my family just moved, and we...
I was going to a brand-new school,
so I was especially scared,
and my father gave me the best advice.
He said,
"Mary Louise, you just seek out the bully,
make friends with her."
Am I the bully in this scenario?
On your awesome days,
I suspect you are a godsend.
But on your bad days, decidedly less so.
Fucking weirdo.
What?
So did you think
about our practice date?
- Our practice date?
- It's like a trial run.
We could shower, we'd put on clothes,
we go to a restaurant,
we eat, talk, and if it's not a total
disaster, then we could do it for real.
Yeah.
Um...
I don't want to offend you, but you are...
I do think you're a very genuine person,
but you're a very...
You're very strange.
You know, one of the last
socially acceptable bigotries
is the one against weirdos.
For what it's worth,
I'm emotionally intuitive.
I get a feeling about people sometimes.
- Mm. You have one about me?
- To be honest, no.
But you're really tolerant
and you're friendly,
and you're really pretty.
You look good in waders.
How could I least not make room
for the possibility?
Are you and Dad going to get divorced?
What? Honey.
No, of course not.
What makes you say this?
Dad never makes you laugh.
And you seem mad at him.
Well, I am not mad at him. Okay?
Who are you mad at?
Nobody.
Hey.
Huh?
♪ And I have saved it all for you ♪
♪ Oh, but I'm gonna demand a little favor ♪
♪ Honey, let your loving be true
♪ You have the whole world
Wrapped up in your hands ♪
♪ All in one... ♪
Who was that?
I still miss him.
I don't think it's ever gonna stop.
When you talked to me about dating again,
it felt like an affront.
Like, preposterous, even.
I only want him.
I'd like to try something.
Think back to one of the times
he was abusing you.
The time in the closet
after his office Christmas party.
I want you to close your eyes
to replay that incident.
- Please, don't ask me...
- It's important. Can you try?
I want you to close your eyes.
To replay the incident.
Mm.
Now I want you to put a close friend
in your place.
Let's make it Madeline.
Put Madeline there instead of you.
- Excuse me, I can't...
- Let's make it Madeline.
Stop it.
No!
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Did Madeline deserve that?
Should Madeline stay
in that relationship?
Just...
Jacket.
Thank you.
Not today.
All right.
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- Step over here please, ma'am.
Arms like an airplane.
Oh, my God.
Gordon. What the fuck?
What the fuck?
I'll be out on bond, so...
Oh...
- Talk to me.
- I, uh...
I made a big bet to short some stock
with, um, Saul Hoffman's company.
Phederol, I think I told you about them,
it's the anticoagulant.
The anticoagulant.
I thought that was a bust.
It was. Oh, my...
Um, which I knew, but, uh...
no one else did.
- Uh...
- Oh.
- Fuck.
- So then the test results completely tanked,
so I started shorting bigtime.
Do you have to do time for that?
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
- Okay...
Listen.
That's not the worst of it.
What?
I kind of bet the ranch.
Our ranch. There's gonna be civil lawsuits
to follow that.
- No.
- Um...
We stand to be broke
by the end of the year,
- and it might even be sooner.
- Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. I don't...
Listen, listen, listen.
Amabella's gonna be okay.
They can't touch her trust.
- It's irrevocable.
- But I didn't sign anything.
-No, no, I know. I know you didn't,
-I didn't do anything. So my money is safe.
But it's community property.
Amabella's trust is...
Fuck. Goddamn it.
Gordon...
I'm not gonna not be rich.
- I'm not gonna have you...
- This could be like a positive thing.
That... Like, there are chapters of life...
I will not not be rich.
♪ Oh, I'm asking ♪
He's really smart.
I don't think there's
much faking it to him.
He's very...
Think "what you see is what you get."
He's weird, though.
He's like maybe "Aspergery" or something.
Like, there's just something...
I don't know.
I've never really met anyone like him.
They fake that sometimes, you know.
- What? Having Asperger's?
- Yeah.
- Get away with saying dumb shit.
- Bonnie.
- Mom.
- Hey, baby.
- Hi. What are you doing here?
- Surprise.
- Your husband called me.
- What?
You had no right.
It's not about being right.
It's about being scared.
- Scared of what?
- Of losing you.
Nathan, if you're scared of losing me,
why don't you try talking to me?
I fucking tried, and you know it.
I've tried. You know that.
You know what, it fucked me up some
when my marriage to Madeline ended.
Divorce creates trauma.
Think something is gonna go on forever
and it doesn't.
Then you're on the other side of it... You
don't trust the ground underneath your feet.
I've never lost sight of the fact
that marriage is fragile.
That it can all go away.
And you...
I don't know where you've gone,
but you're not here.
He's in prison,
and he might stay in fucking prison,
and he's lost all our money.
- Maybe he gets out, what, for days?
- What?
- Until they fucking... Yes.
He's lost fucking everything.
My money too. His money.
- Okay. Here, here. Come here, come here.
- What?
No, we can't go in there.
We're not going in there.
Babe, this is a disaster.
Oh, my God.
This fucker put me back in the hole.
This is my fucking childhood.
This is everything I've worked
to get out of.
-Quinlan was there. I am telling you,
-What?
I think she's been watching,
and she tipped somebody off.
- What? I thought it was the FBI.
- But then who the fuck is tipping them off?
And why is the FBI
taking my fucking computer?
They went to my office.
They took my iPad.
- What?
- I just... Okay.
I need to call an estate lawyer.
Okay, and I need to do a list of assets.
- You're right.
- Do you need a Xanax or...?
When we swallow our feelings,
especially the bad ones,
sometimes they can turn
into really ugly monsters,
which is not a good thing.
I want you to know that it's perfectly okay
to come and talk to me, okay?
You can talk to me about anything,
whether it was over a put-down,
something that happened here,
something that happened on the news,
anything you need to talk about,
I'm here.
Anyone?
What about a dead father?
He said it quite simply,
without any sense of trauma, so...
Whether that's better or worse...
- Are they still getting counseling?
- Um, yeah.
I'm really sorry about this.
- Did I do something wrong?
- No.
It's good to talk about what we feel.
I just...
I just think it's best if you talk to me,
you know, rather than at school.
- But you don't like to talk about it.
- That's not true.
You like to pretend everything's okay.
Well, I shouldn't do that.
We're a family, and...
And a family is meant to be open
and honest with each other, so...
I don't think we're that kind of family.
What? Yeah, we are.
Of course we are, Max.
Of course we are.
- Grandma.
- Put it on the counter, please.
Hi.
What happen...?
Something came up at school.
It's like you said the other night...
They're still grieving.
It's all just so hard, you know?
Hmm...
I do. I do know.
Right after the accident,
after we lost Raymond,
I was sure I would not be able to go on.
I was never sure
about anything in my whole life,
that I wouldn't go on, but I did.
Because of Perry.
And so will you, because of the boys.
What happened this morning?
I don't know. I just...
I took an Ambien when I couldn't sleep,
and before I knew it, I was driving a car.
- Has that ever happened before?
- No.
I've decided to rent an apartment locally,
so that I can, um, be nearby,
but not, you know...
I wanna be here when you need me, Celeste,
and not when you don't.
I'm so grateful to you
for everything you've done,
but a little space might be good.
Madeline told me
that you and she had words.
I don't like her.
Well, you have to try.
Well, I have tried, but she's not
a likable person.
She's been a lifeline to me.
She really has.
- She's a wonderful person.
- Mm.
Well, you're mistaken.
Did I ever tell you
that she once saved Max from drowning?
- Really?
- Mm-hm.
Huh.
Where were you?
- What?
- I feel like you always look at me
with such... suspicion.
No, I don't mean to.
I do look at you as, uh... an enigma.
That's how Perry first described you
to me.
Did you know that?
Stop it! Hey!
- Stop, you idiot!
- Hey!
Stop!
- Stop!
- That's enough.
- Stop it.
- Stop it. I said stop it.
- Stop it! Stop!
That is enough! Stop it!
That is enough.
- Fuck off!
- What did you say?
No!
You will not be like him!
You...
Max, I'm sorry.
Maxie? Maxie, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Mom.
Oh, my God.
Josh, come here.
Are you all right? Huh?
Are you okay?
You smell that?
Clears your sinuses right out.
We have all this newfangled stuff
to improve ourselves.
Self-help apps all over our phones.
Sometimes all we need to do
is just stand still and breathe.
To just breathe in the air
that's all around us.
Is that for me, Mama?
You want me to breathe better?
- Tell me what's going on, Bonnie.
- Nothing, Nathan's just tripping.
Nathan is a complete dolt.
When it comes to emotional,
social intelligence,
oh, Bonnie, he's as dumb as a rock.
But I often wonder
if that's why you married him.
You are out here surrounded by people
who don't even get you.
They don't look like you.
I haven't seen one other black person
since l've been out here.
Is that why you're here?
I mean, because we all know
how fond you are of your walls.
You are out of control.
Something's in the air, Bonnie.
And I don't like it.
You know, I decided to run.
For office?
I swear to fucking God, man.
No, I decided to take up running
because Bonnie likes running.
She's obsessed with it.
- I'm trying to embrace her interests.
- So I'm off the hook for lunch, then?
You remember what you said to me
last year about "give me a reason"?
Should we just get this
out of our system, man?
Okay, so you've asked me
to have lunch with your wife,
and now you challenge me to a fistfight.
I mean, do you have a preference
if I can't squeeze in both?
Really?
- So that's a no, huh?
- Okay.
- Don't, buddy. Don't.
Warning.
Case 6273.
United States v. Gordon Klein.
James Taylor on behalf
of the United States, Your Honor.
Steve Gardner on behalf
of Mr. Klein, Your Honor. Plead not guilty.
Mr. Klein.
You're being charged with security fraud,
mail fraud and wire fraud,
violating Section 17A
of the Securities Act of 1933
and Rule 105
of Regulation M of the Exchange Act.
Question of bail?
No priors, judge.
I ask that the defendant post bail
in excess of $1 million
in light of the severity of the charge.
One million sounds excessive.
One million bond.
Five hundred thousand dollars cash...
Stop!
We'll conference on Tuesday
to set a schedule.
- Thank you, Your Honor.
- Thank you.
I swear someone's gonna do a start-up,
and they're gonna make,
like, the perfect French fry.
It's gonna be, like, nutritional
and healthy and no cal.
It's gonna be a gold mine.
Remember when you used to call them
pomp freaks?
Mm-hm.
French fries.
When she was little,
I told her they were called pommes frites,
and then she started calling them
pomp freaks.
I never even noticed you
eating a French fry.
I eat French fries.
Yeah, you're right.
You just didn't notice, did you?
That's your thing, isn't it?
- Wait, what?
- Don't get all sensitive with yourself.
I'm not. I'm not being sensitive.
- I'm just... What do you mean?
- Honey?
No, I notice things.
I mean...
Like, I noticed shit,
and then I asked you to come.
- So...
- Well, I'm here...
because you're ill-equipped
to connect with your wife.
- Mom, you're drinking again.
- No.
I mean, it's just one glass. Occasionally.
One glass is fine.
One hundred, not so much.
Those days are over.
- Your problem is you're oblivious.
- Will you stop?
You call me and you say
that something's wrong with Bonnie.
"Bonnie's not herself."
"Been going on six months
to a year or so."
Can you narrow that down
a little bit further for me, Nathan?
I mean, can you pinpoint a specific date?
Instance. Anything?
Because I can.
It was after that event.
You all went to that student gala.
Where the man died.
And Bonnie was there.
Your wife watched a man
fall down the steps
and bust his goddamn head open
and splatter all over the place and die.
I don't know, from then to now,
she's probably been dealing
with post-traumatic stress.
I'm fine.
- We're in a restaurant, honey.
- What does that mean?
What, we should just glaze over it?
Act like everything is okay?
Things are not okay.
Your daughter is not okay.
And this mope-a-dope shit,
it clearly is not working for your husband.
And I doubt very much
that it's working for your child.
And from what I see,
it is not working for you.
Mom.
I'm really happy you're here.
Can we just have a dinner
like a normal family?
We are having dinner
like a normal family.
Getting in each other's business, that's
what families do. That's why he called.
So you don't have any siblings?
I had a brother.
Oh.
He passed away when I was 5.
Oh...
Sorry about that.
What about you?
I'm an only child.
- L mean, as far as I know.
- Oh, yeah?
Yeah, I'm not very close to my dad, so...
Right?
You never know.
So your mom passed away,
and you don't have any siblings,
as far as you know,
and you don't talk much to your dad.
Mm.
Now, I don't mean to be presumptuous,
but...
if this works out...
I would have you all to myself.
- Boys are tucked in.
- Thank you, Mary Louise.
They must have been exhausted.
Max is asleep already.
They tell me they have a brother.
Evidently, Perry had a son.
- What?
- With another woman.
And the boy's in their class.
Seems I have another grandchild.
Might you have the decency to tell me...
his name?
- No.
- Then how could they know?
I don't know.
You know what, we did tell that detective.
- That bitch. She probably let it slip...
- Mom.
I'm sorry. You know what, Celeste,
just find out what the boys know exactly
and then call me right back, okay? Bye.
What now?
Celeste, just stuff with the twins, and...
Did they find out Ziggy's their brother?
Who told you that?
I heard you talking on the phone once.
Did you tell Max and Josh?
Only that they have a brother
in the second grade.
- Chloe, good God.
- I didn't say who.
- Did you tell Ziggy this?
- Mm-hm.
Wait, Perry Wright is Ziggy's father?
- You know what, go to your room.
- I'm sorry.
Give me your phone.
I'll deal with you later.
I'm so sorry. She's grounded.
- I gotta go.
- Okay, I...
Oh, fuck.
Hey. Talk for a sec?
- What did I do?
- You didn't do anything. Um...
Did Chloe Mackenzie say anything
to you about...
About who your father is?
She said it was Max and Josh's dad.
Is it?
Mm-hm.
How long have you known for?
Since August.
Ziggy, you've known since August
and you haven't said anything to me?
Figured you'd just lie.
I didn't know.
All of those years
of you asking me where he was
or who he was, I...
I didn't know who he was.
I didn't know until Trivia Night.
- And...
- But why didn't you tell me?
Because I didn't know how.
I just thought that I would wait.
- Till when?
- Till you got older, I guess.
Did Chloe tell you anything else?
She said something about Mr. Wright
giving you salt.
That's how I happened.
He salted you.
No.
Then what did she mean?
Can I sit down next to you?
I think what Chloe overheard
was the word "assault."
What does that mean?
- Look, I wanted to tell you.
- Yeah, but you didn't.
Well, I was trying to protect
Jane and Celeste's privacy.
- But I'm your husband. Okay?
- Okay, but can you understand
and maybe contemplate for a minute
the fundamental violation
of a woman's privacy
when you're talking about rape?
How about the fundamental violation
of our family, of our marriage.
I mean, I'm your husband.
I am supposed to help you with this stuff.
I mean, of course she's gonna hear you
whispering on the fucking phone, Madeline.
I mean, look what our daughter did.
What are we, people who keep secrets
from each other? Is that our thing now?
Come on.
Jesus.
Mom?
I'm really sorry again.
I know you are, honey. I know.
You can't tell your friends private things
that you've overheard us say on the phone.
Okay?
No more eavesdropping, young lady.
Is Daddy mad at me?
Daddy's mad.
But that's the thing about families,
is that you can be mad and you can fight,
but you get over it,
and you always come back together.
That's what families do.
- So we're gonna be okay.
- Okay.
Can I have my phone back?
So this thing
was supposed to have happened when?
Like nine years ago?
When you two were trying so hard
to have a baby? Please.
When did you find out
about this alleged affair?
It wasn't an affair. It was a rape. Rape.
- When did you find out?
- The night he died.
Then how can you...?
This woman, she could have had
multiple partners, you know.
She could have been drugged.
She... You don't know her.
She could have been...
What if she got it wrong?
Aren't you desperate
- She didn't.
- For her to be wrong?
Aren't you desperate to know
that he wasn't unfaithful?
To believe that he... He wasn't capable
of doing the things that she said.
He wasn't.
I'll never believe that.
Your son wasn't an innocent man.
He beat me up.
- I don't believe you.
- Many times. He...
Why wouldn't you go to the police?
- I probably should have.
- But you didn't.
- No, because it wasn't simple.
- I don't believe you.
I don't understand why you're so willing
to believe her.
I don't know why you are willing
to assassinate his character, his memory,
who he was.
- What...? I...
- It's so hard.
I'm telling you what it was.
I'm not saying I was blameless.
I'm just telling you
we were violent with each other,
and sometimes...
Sometimes it would lead to sex.
I don't... I...
We loved each other.
- We were...
- But he beat you up.
We had a sickness.
And you didn't go to the police?
I just...
I'll go to the police.
What?
To get some answers.
You left some things out, didn't you?
The fact that he fathered another child.
You left that out.
That you planned to move,
that you rented an apartment.
You left that out.
That you were planning to leave him
the very night he died.
You left that out.
And that you...
You learned of his infidelity
just 10 seconds before he...
went falling down a flight of stairs
to his death.
Oh, you left that out too.
How's Ziggy?
He's, uh...
I don't know.
And you?
Um, I gotta tell you something. I...
I told Ziggy about the circumstances.
The violence of it?
Mm-hm.
- What?
- Just a little bit, but he knows
that he cannot share it with Max and Josh.
That it's just for him.
- But we had an agreement.
- I know. I know.
- We were gonna wait.
- I know, but I can't lie to him anymore.
- I can't...
- No, I...
-His entire life has just been built
-Jane.
On a foundation of lies.
I can't just... I can't continue.
And I know
that you have to protect your boys,
but I have to protect mine.
I have to be honest with him.
Ugh. God, this is so fucked up.
Have you told your boys about Ziggy?
Not yet, no. I just...
I will. I mean...
Bonnie.
- Hey.
- Could you talk for a second?
- Sure.
Um...
This is in no way meant to blame you
or Nathan at all, for that matter,
but that said, I just feel strongly
that Abigail come stay with me.
Yeah,
she needs more than I can give her.
What's going on?
Are you okay?
No, I'm not okay. I told you I wasn't okay.
I'm having a hard time with the whole thing.
Sometimes I wake up at night in a sweat
with this feeling.
It's gonna get us. It's gonna get us all.
Who are you talking about?
The lie.
I gotta go.
♪ As I walk this land of broken dreams ♪
♪ I have visions of many things ♪
You used to like that song.
I used to like to sit on your face too.
You think that'll happen again?
I mean, give me one fucking reason.
I wanted a Gulfstream.
- Ow! What the fuck?
- Fucking pitiful.
We're creatures of want. Jesus.
You know, we are. Me, you...
God, especially you.
- What?
- What the fuck are you doing?
- What the fuck?
- What are you doing?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Did I ever explain to you
that I wanted more?
- Is that what I said to you?
- Maybe I wanted more!
- Just get the fuck out. Please.
- Oh, please.
- Just stop being dramatic and drive.
- You're gonna blame me?
- Did I say I was blaming you?
- Blame me while you lost my money?
- I didn't say...
- Get out of my car!
- Nothing happens in a vacuum.
- This is my car.
- Come on... Oh, my fucking...
- Out of the fucking car!
Oh, my God.
Oh my...
Will somebody give a woman a moment?
Goddamn it.
I'm not resisting the idea
of coming back here.
Well, that's a relief.
As long as the main goal isn't
trying to convince me to go to college.
The endgame is to move you
into a stable environment
where your executive
decision-making skills are nurtured.
That's a good one.
Can I just say one thing, though?
I think you're being rash, honey.
Life is a series of building blocks
that you stand on and you grow on,
and I feel like you are kicking
the most fundamental building block,
which is education,
right out from under you.
You used to claim that family
was your most fundamental building block.
Well, of course. It's very important.
What, you just, like, kicked that one
to the side?
What do you mean?
You were fucking the theater director
last year, so...
- That's inappropriate. This is not about me.
- You're being really hypocritical.
- This is about you and your future.
- Using the res...
Ed.
Hey.
What's going on?
We were just talking about college.
Is that it?
♪ The distance was too much to bear ♪
What's this about fucking
a theater director?
No, I...
- You misheard that.
- Ah.
♪ I must leave the one I love ♪
Where are you going?
Uh, to get my ears checked.
♪ We could've tried a bit harder
Goddamn it!
You said he wasn't home.
- But we already know him.
- No, but now you'll be meeting him as...
I mean, as brothers. That's...
We're already friends.
What difference does it make?
I don't know.
This is what I do know.
He's part of your family now.
And, I mean,
family isn't always everything, but...
sometimes it is.
- Was Daddy a bad person?
- No.
No, no, no.
Your daddy was a wonderful person.
A beautiful person.
He could be weak...
like we all can.
And he could make mistakes, but your...
Your daddy was a beautiful,
wonderful man.
Okay. Uh...
Thank you for coming back.
[, um...
At best as I fathom,
and I cannot fathom what I've done, I...
This was about me, and I...
I'm so sorry. I... This was not about you.
- Maybe about us as a couple.
- Mm-hm.
And I think we should get therapy.
Okay.
But I need you to know
that this has nothing to do with you.
This happened so long ago.
And it has nothing to do
with how much I love you
because I love you so much, and...
And I just need to know
what you're thinking.
That you would keep the secret
that you kept about Perry and Ziggy.
That you would be unfaithful.
Um...
That you would tell Abigail about it.
I know. That is...
That happened in a moment of weakness.
When?
Last year.
So she's known a year?
My daughter,
and yes, I do think of her as a daughter,
has known this for a year?
Yes, I'm sorry, I fucked up. I, um...
But I'm gonna do anything I can to fix it.
- Does Chloe know?
- No.
No, of course not.
- How can you be so sure?
- No, Ed, I promise you, she doesn't know.
I'm so sorry, she...
Look, this just isn't about you.
It's about me. This is about us.
When you say "us," what...
I mean, what does that even mean?
Because it can't mean honesty.
Right? It can't mean truth or trust.
I mean, it can't mean you and me
confiding in each other,
so what's "us"?
You asked me what I'm thinking.
I'll tell you.
I think we're done.
I do appreciate you coming, Mama.
I do.
Meaning...
"Enough."
I do not want any of that
in my family's life.
We're not having that conversation again.
I have been having visions lately, Bonnie.
- And I know you've had some too.
- Mom.
- They are strong, baby.
- Don't. Don't.
- Somebody's drowning.
- Stop.
I see lots of water,
and somebody's drowning.
I see you drowning right now in a way.
Who's gonna protect you, baby?
I do not need you to protect me.
Not from evil spirits, or your visions...
From what, then?
Tell me.
What have you done this time?
Hmm?
I do want you to go.
I love you too, honey.
Okay, you invited her, you get rid of her.
Get rid of her?
Like, maybe with rat poison?
Or a weekend with Maddie?
Seriously, though,
can you tell her to go?
Can you tell me what's going on?
Be patient, baby.
Patient.
♪ When everything I do is wrong ♪
♪ You give me hope and consolation ♪
♪ You give me strength to carry on ♪
♪ And you're always there to lend a hand ♪
♪ In everything I do ♪
♪ That's the wonder ♪
♪ The wonder of you I
♪ And when you smile
The world is brighter ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ You touch my hand and I'm a king
♪ Your kiss to me is worth a fortune ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Your love for me is everything ♪
♪ I guess I'll never know the reason why ♪
♪ You love me as you do ♪
♪ That's the wonder ♪
♪ The wonder of you I
♪ Ah ♪
♪ And I guess I'll never know ♪
♪ The reason why ♪
♪ You love me as you do ♪
♪ That's the wonder ♪
♪ The wonder of you I
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::