♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Did you ever want it? ♪
♪ Did you want it bad? ♪
♪ Oh, my ♪
♪ It tears me apart ♪
♪ We can try to hide it ♪
♪ It's all the same ♪
♪ I've been losing you ♪
♪ One day at a time ♪
♪ And I know
In my heart, in this cold heart ♪
♪ [can live or I can die ♪
♪ I believe if I just try ♪
♪ You believe in you and I ♪
♪ Inyouandl? l
Oh, my God.
I pushed him.
You didn't push him.
And you didn't push him. Nobody did.
Ew.
It even scared me, Josh.
- It's gross!
- Aren't they supposed to be scary?
It's the whole point.
- They're supposed to be monsters.
- Mine's done.
- It got stabbed.
- That's disgusting.
No, you can't leave it like that.
Some gang member could steal it
and use it to stab a person in the heart.
Chloe, there are no gangs in Monterey.
I have this.
Come on,
draw a face or something.
It's gonna be total disco themed.
It's gonna be amazing.
It's gonna blow Frozen out of the water.
What are you doing?
- I'm smoking. I hate smoking.
- Nobody smokes anymore.
I'm just trying to manage my stress.
We're talking about Amabella's
birthday party. It'll be amazing.
How you doing?
How's everything with Ed? Is he here?
Um... Whether or not we're still married,
it's undetermined.
- Oh. Babe.
- Sorry.
I don't know. It's not just Ed.
I just feel like
everything right now is so fucked.
Yeah, it's a lot.
Everything's weird.
- What time is her party?
- Two,
because I have to go
to bankruptcy court that morning.
- What?
- On a Saturday?
Well, we worked it out.
It's better that we don't have to sit
around those penniless losers,
as though that's not us.
Jesus, I don't know
how you're still with him.
I know he's your husband, but...
- Fuck.
- I don't know.
We stay.
You don't have to.
But we do.
They betray us and we stay, you know.
They lie, they cheat on us, and we s...
- You know you said that out loud?
- I did. I said it out loud. Shit.
I just... We stay.
We work it out, is my point.
I'm coming!
Tell me to stop talking, please.
Just all the time.
-Oh, hi,
-Mary Louise?
The boys told me
you were having a pumpkin-carving party.
It sounded like so much fun.
And I... I can, um...
I can be gone in a flash
if it's an imposition.
Oh, no, no, no. Please come in.
- L brought a...
- Kids!
Surprise.
- Grandma!
Oh, there's my little soldiers.
Aw. I see two handsome grandsons.
Somehow, I thought for sure
there'd be three.
Where did I get that idea?
- Oh, Ziggy. He's right there.
- Ziggy's over there.
There he is.
That's an intriguing jack-o'-lantern.
He's shocked.
I think we're all a little shocked.
Have you met Bonnie, Mary Louise?
Hi.
Uh...
I don't believe I have.
I would certainly remember.
So beautiful.
Jane, hi.
Guess what?
I got a unit in your building.
- My building?
- Yes, it's perfect.
I'm just getting settled, so...
I can take the boys sometimes
for some stayover nights.
Yeah!
Yeah, you know,
SO you can have some time to have a life.
- Can I come too?
- Of course, all my grandchildren.
Mary Louise. Mary Louise,
can I have a word with you, please?
Yeah, sure. Of course.
I'm cleaning my pumpkin.
If you tap on it, all...
You really think that this is a good idea?
- What?
- Moving into Jane's building?
- Why wouldn't it be?
- Because there are boundaries,
Mary Louise.
Where would you have me go? Canada?
This is all beginning to feel
a little perverse.
- I beg your pardon?
- Moving in with your son's rape victim.
- For God's sake, it's not right.
- I'm not moving in with her.
We're in the same building complex.
- No. This...
- And by the way, I'm not as convinced
as you are, perhaps,
that she was a rape victim.
Oh, my God. I can't...
You know, there are many, many questions
that I still have.
For instance,
why was he even with her that night?
What was he looking for?
Perhaps seeking refuge from?
What's that supposed to mean?
How many other women did he go to?
If there's one...
there are others.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, I'm sorry.
- No, no, no.
- I shouldn't have done that. I...
What shall we call that?
Foreplay?
Grandma.
Oh, dear.
- What's all this?
- Pumpkin-carving project.
The school decided
to celebrate Halloween this week.
God forbid they wait
till the end of the month.
I swear everyone in this town is obsessed
with first and better and most.
Speaking of which, it's Amabella's
birthday disco party tomorrow.
It's not even her fucking birthday.
I mean, is it too much to ask people
to check people's calendars
and then get back to them accordingly?
We all have calendar apps
on our phone, for God's sake.
What? Why are you staring at me?
Um...
There's never any middle ground with you.
Like, when you're upset, it's charge.
Full speed ahead.
If there's a problem, charge.
If there was a problem with us,
where was the charge?
Why couldn't you come straight at me
like you go at everyone else?
There wasn't a problem with us, Ed.
There's a problem with me.
Okay.
Oh, and it is a disco party, so...
And costumes may
or may not be required.
So the opportunity
for embarrassment is huge?
- Yeah.
- Ready?
Okay. Come on.
Got you.
- Hi.
- Do you wanna start or should 1?
- Yeah, I'll start.
I'm worried about the boys.
- Because?
- Because. Because...
you seem unwell.
Erratic.
I'm fine.
You hit me.
And I apologized for that.
I've...
You snapped.
It's meant to be shared, you know.
Grief.
It's...
insurmountable.
Too difficult a battle to be waged alone.
Which is what you had to do.
You were alone after the accident.
Your husband left.
Perry told me.
Yes, he blamed me.
And he left.
And I deserved the blame.
To be left.
You know, Ray...
made a new life.
He got a new family.
He became a devoted father, so I'm told.
It's... It's good.
People can move on after tragedy,
just not together sometimes.
What do you think
about going to Big Sur?
Just the two of us.
There's a couples' thing.
It's a... It's a workshop.
A couples' workshop.
I know, I know, that sounds awful,
but it's gotta be better than that lady,
and it's supposed to be amazing.
"Madeline, I would love
to go with you into the woods
and talk about my feelings
and make love to you."
No?
Mom, can you look over my project?
Yeah.
This is opposites.
And next, we're gonna do synonyms.
Okay. Opposites.
- That's a door.
- Yeah.
- And that is...
- That's you.
Me. Of course.
Uh...
I don't... I don't understand.
The door's hinged.
I see. Is that supposed to be funny?
Well, my teacher wants imagery.
Not words like "hot" and "cold."
Uh-huh.
I'll change it.
Ah.
So is this the party line around here?
That I'm unhinged?
- That's the book on me?
- Pretty much.
Great.
I don't understand
why the attorney can't handle this.
Because they can't.
All right? He had to pluck a zillion
strings to get this through on a Saturday
with nobody else around.
It's not like a scarlet letter.
People file for bankruptcy all the time.
Some even go on to become president.
Let's just keep this thing moving along.
I've got a party to throw.
Absolutely no mention of that whatsoever
to the trustee. All right? Am I clear?
So this represents your assets
in their entirety?
- Yes, sir.
- Condo in Aspen.
Four-bedroom vacation home
in Palm Beach,
including a 58-foot Red Sea Yacht.
The Amabella.
Any other recreational
or vacation home?
No, sir.
Estimated liability is $33 million?
Yes, but most of that
is pending civil lawsuits,
and we expect to be able to settle
within that range.
You really don't get to settle anything
anymore, Mr. Klein. That all falls on me.
Your residence has been listed for sale?
- Uh, yes. We expect it to go for north of 20.
- At least.
Again, my decision, not yours.
Any other legal actions pending?
Uh, right to sue?
- Any punitive judgments in your favor?
- No, sir.
Any expectation of inheritance
in the next 18 months?
No, sir.
Parents in good health?
- Are you serious?
- Uh...
Yes, they're in good health.
Do you stand to inherit?
I'm self-made.
I see a charge for $4200
to Morris-Simmons Lab.
Can anybody tell me what that's for?
Medical.
- Did you submit to insurance?
- No.
Why not?
Because it's...
It wouldn't be declared as insurance.
Well, what is it?
It's medical.
Like I said the first time.
I don't think you follow here, Mrs. Klein.
See, this is a bankruptcy hearing.
And I can deny your petition.
Renata...
From dealing with men like you
all my life. Okay?
Mm-hm.
Going forward, disallow.
I have here a listing of your jewelry,
which doesn't include
that Rolex watch you're wearing.
I'll take it.
- You mean mine?
- Are you kidding?
- John, come on.
- It doesn't include that either.
- That's my wedding ring.
- It's not listed.
I'm... I'm not...
- giving my...
- I will handle this later.
We done here?
- How did you get here today?
- We drove.
Personal car?
Tesla, 2017.
- At least we got your ring back.
- Shut up.
There will come a day
that you will pay for this, Gordon.
But today is not that day.
Today is Amabella's day,
and it will be filled with laughter
and magic
and pure, unmitigated joy.
- Hi!
- Welcome to Club Amabellal
- You look incredible. You look...
- Oh, thank you.
- This is my mom, Elizabeth. This is Renata.
- Elizabeth! Renata.
- We have never met.
- No, we have not.
It's such a pleasure,
and thank you so much for inviting me.
Of course.
I mean, The Trammps?
And they're headlining.
- So amazing.
- Come in. Get champagne.
Hi.
Have a wonderful time.
Ziggy Stardust, ladies and gentlemen.
- This is Corey Brockfield.
- I've heard so much about you.
It's so great to meet you, Corey.
Welcome to my home.
- No, hi. Bonnie.
- Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
- Gordon. Get him some champagne.
I can't. He's so cute,
I can't even take it.
- I can't. I can't. I can't.
- Just don't tell him.
- Get on that.
- He's so cute.
You guys have to be cool.
- I made the biggest mistake bringing him.
- I'm never cool.
But I will try my best. For you.
For you, I'm about to be cool
for the first time in my life.
Are we gonna dance again? That's right.
We always need a dance party, don't we?
Hi, how are you?
Uh, this is a list of all
of the best family law attorneys
in the Bay Area,
as well as the peninsula.
I would like you to call each one of them.
But I have you. Wha...?
Why do I need to call them?
Well, you won't,
but your daughter-in-law will,
and if you call them first,
you know, she can't have them.
They'll be conflicted out.
It's... You know, it's an ugly process.
Are you really sure
you wanna proceed with this?
He agreed to go to a sauna center.
It's like a healing institute
for mature couples.
- Yeah, right.
- Maybe it used to be a...
Celeste, what exactly
does your mother-in-law know?
She gave me a very strange look yesterday.
If anything, she's suspicious of me.
Does that bother you, all that suspicion?
It does bother me. It does.
And if I could do it again, I wouldn't lie.
I wouldn't go along with the lie.
Exactly.
Hold on a second.
What are you trying to say?
You were the one that said
that he slipped, that he fell, and...
I mean, we went along with it.
- Are you blaming me?
- I blame myself, all right?
It seemed like a good idea at the time,
but I was numb.
I wasn't thinking straight,
and let's face it,
this fucking lie has
had quite a shelf life.
- Yeah, I agree.
- Wow.
You're talking about me
behind my back?
- You're blaming me.
- No. No.
- No, that's rich. That's really rich.
- We're not blaming you behind your back.
We're right here. It's to your face.
♪ I feel you touch me in the pouring rain ♪
♪ And the moment that you wander
Far from me ♪
♪ I want to feel you in my arms... ♪
How adorable is that?
♪ And you come to me
On a summer breeze... ♪
I suppose we'll never be giving her
anything like this again. Ever.
♪ And it's me you need to show ♪
Okay, look. I know I will never be able
to make up for what I've done.
But, I mean, do you think
there's any chance
that you'll be able
to forgive me eventually?
It's not about you, Gordon.
It's not?
Since I was old enough to dream
of having my own family,
I've been, in my head,
planning my child's life.
What it would entail,
what she would have,
the opportunities I could give her.
So I'm having a difficult time reconciling
that all my dreams have gone to shit.
All my hopes and plans for Amabella
have gone to shit.
I married a man...
who would take my life
and all my accomplishments
and just turn them to shit.
That... That's on me. Right?
My choices. My stupidity.
It's my picker that's broken.
- My fucking bad.
- Renata!
- Hello.
- Hi.
Such a pleasure.
♪ We belong to you and me ♪
♪ Na, na-na, na, na ♪
♪ Na-na-na, na, na-na, na, na, ha ♪
♪ Na-na-na, na-na,
na-na, na, na, na, na, ha ♪
♪ Na, na, na-na-na, na, na, na ♪
♪ And you come to me
On a summer breeze ♪
♪ Keep me warm in your love
Then you softly leave ♪
♪ And it's me you need to show ♪
♪ How deep is your love ♪
I saw you.
With your friends earlier.
Something's wrong.
I don't like the energy in this house.
I mean, not the party. This is great.
Something deeper.
And I don't like the energy around you.
This is just your weird imagination.
Oh...
I don't think so.
♪ Scared and lonely
Going out for the night ♪
No.
♪ Shakin' all over
And wishing I'd never come here I
♪ He pulled up in a cloud of smoke ♪
♪ So much was said
But nobody spoke a word ♪
You wanna dance?
Uh...
No.
♪ I knew he wouldn't beg
So I gave in without... ♪
Wanna think about it?
I mean, I would love to dance
with you, Madeline.
But maybe sometime when we're not
doing a dog and pony show
in front of all of Monterey.
- I'm sick of all the pretending.
- What do you mean, pretending?
What do I mean, pretending?
Are you kidding me?
Are you looking at this room?
This is pretending.
You, me, us, the... Everything.
Just...
- Got it.
- Okay.
Yeah. Got it.
♪ You'll go for a ride ♪
You okay?
♪ For aride ♪
Yeah.
I've been there, man.
Oh, my God.
- No, I mean... I...
- Jesus Christ, just shut up.
Just fucking...
- Don't say that. Don't talk to me like...
- Stop it.
- I don't like that.
- Please...
Don't.
Hey. Hey. What the hell?
- He started it.
- I do not care who started it.
- Just go.
- Hey, we were playing.
We are meant to be happy here.
This is about happiness.
My God. Babies!
Uh... You don't need to read that all here.
You can just give it a good proof tonight
to make sure there are no inaccuracies.
- Oh. Okay.
- Yeah.
So you do realize that once we file,
you can count on being, uh, alienated
from the boys.
I mean,
you might get custody, but affection...
This isn't about me needing to be liked.
Okay, everyone needs to be liked.
I find that's especially true
with grandmothers.
How old are you?
-Eight.
“Eight?
Tell you what. Today is your birthday,
we're gonna dedicate this show to you.
Woop, woop!
Are y'all ready? Say, "Burn."
♪ Burn, baby, burn ♪
I can't hear you. What we say?
That's it. A little louder.
♪ Burn, baby, burn ♪
That's right.
Now somebody scream!
♪ To my surprise ♪
- ♪ One hundred stories high ♪
- ♪ Hundred stories high
♪ People getting loose, y'all ♪
♪ Getting down on the roof ♪
- Let me hear you.
- Say what?
Found you.
You wanna sit?
I know I told you a little bit
about what happened.
We don't have to talk about it.
I would like to.
I've...
I was raped pretty violently
by a man who I thought
was sensitive and...
kind.
Yeah. That's how I got Ziggy so...
Really?
Yeah.
Amabella's so happy you came.
- Thank you.
- Good to see you.
- Even better than Frozen.
- Do you promise?
- Oh, my gosh. Amazing.
- You better not be lying to me.
I'm not lying, I also wanna borrow
your dress. Is that weird?
Uh, no. You own it.
- Oh, my God.
- That was insane.
- Disco was genius.
- Really?
- Yeah, it was great.
- It was. It was so great.
- Oh, thank you so much. Thank you.
- For you. We've got one for you.
I know someone had a great time.
- I had a ball.
- That... Oh, no.
You on that dance floor.
It was amazing.
It was a ball.
- All right. Thank you.
- I'm so happy you were here.
Mama.
You okay?
- Mom?
- Elizabeth?
- What's wrong with her?
Oh, my God. Mom.
- Oh, my God. Mom! Mom! Mom!
- Watch her head. Watch her head.
- Oh, my God! Somebody call 911!
- What is happening to her?
So, what happened?
She had a stroke,
which most likely caused the seizure.
We're gonna take her into surgery now
and clean out a carotid artery in her neck.
It's good that you got her here so quickly.
As soon as we know more,
I'll let you know.
She just dropped like a stone.
I seriously thought she was gonna die.
It really makes you take stock of things.
You okay?
No.
I'm far from okay.
Look, if you're gonna leave me,
can you just do it?
Can you just get it over with?
Wh... I mean, I'm still here, aren't I?
Is that what you think, Ed?
You're far from here.
You're not even fucking close.
I had a really weird thing happened earlier
when I was dancing with Corey. Um...
Everything was going fine, it was great,
and then he moved his hand,
and my mind froze, and my body recoiled
and kind of had this spasm.
It's really frustrating
because I'm doing so well,
and then something like that happens.
And it's like,
am I ever gonna be able to be sexual again?
Can you relate to that?
Did he ever...
Did Perry ever rape you?
How we doing?
Another round?
No, I'm good. Thank you, actually.
It'll happen.
- So he didn't?
- No.
No, he didn't.
I'm gonna swing by the hospital on my way
and just check up on Bonnie.
Would you tell her that my boys
are with Mary Louise tonight, so if she...
If she wants anything, I'm here.
Ugh. Okay.
- Bye.
- Love you.
Love you.
So, what's it gonna be?
- Oh, what the hell, I'll have another one.
- Good choice.
Looking for Elizabeth Howard.
- She's right through there.
- Dad.
- Hi.
- She okay?
- I think.
What'd the surgeon say?
Her brain scans showed some bleeding,
but, um, it's minimal,
so we won't know anything else
till she wakes up.
Did you say something to her?
Before the incident,
did you say something?
- You mean, did I cause this?
- I didn't mean that.
Yeah, you did.
It's just that you know
how easily upset she gets.
I didn't cause her fucking stroke.
Calm down.
What if she can hear you?
Okay.
I'm gonna let you sit with her for a while.
Okay?
I'm here, baby.
It's the best pizza in the world!
That's what your dad used to say.
When he was your age. You know that?
- He said that with us too.
- He did?
Did he teach you
how to stretch the cheese?
- Yeah.
- Stretch the cheese.
Mm-hm.
Nothing better in the world.
If Dad was here,
he would eat a whole pizza to himself.
He is. He is here, in a way.
You know, people are never really gone.
Because they live on in the hearts
of those they leave behind.
We just have to keep your dad here.
In your hearts.
Right?
It's the best pizza in the world.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
- Seriously?
- Excuse me?
- What the fuck?
- Bonnie. Hey.
Sorry.
She chooses now?
No, no, she's here for some DUI fatality
or something.
I ran into her downstairs.
It's something else.
- She's just a daughter of a patient.
- I know who she is.
I so wanted to bring the boys
to church, but Max was adamantly opposed.
He thinks that God is a douchebag.
His language, not mine.
- Hi, Mommy.
- Hi.
- You all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
- Just didn't sleep very well, you know?
- Yeah.
We had pulled pizza.
- Did you?
- Yeah.
Yeah. We stretched the cheese
like Daddy used to do.
Well, that sounds really fun.
And we saw Ziggy this morning.
He lives in Grandma's building.
Mm.
- Great.
- What's the matter?
Celeste, what's wrong?
I just... I don't know,
I feel like I'm coming down with something.
- Hmm?
- I just feel like very zonked.
You look funny.
Mm.
No fever.
What a mess.
- Good Lord.
- Hey.
How we all doing?
I gotta...
Hey, buddy.
And who do we have with us today?
I'm... I'm Joe.
- Hi.
Sorry.
So...
Shall we...
Let's get clean, shall we?
Wait, did you take Ambien again?
And you didn't even remember
he was in the house?
I couldn't... I didn't even realize where I
was when they came running in, I just...
Look, you're entitled
to have a private life.
She said she was taking the boys
for a sleepover.
I know, she comes in at a...
It must have been like...
Yeah, she should have called you first
or texted you.
You can't barge in on people like that.
I dropped the boys off at Jane's,
if that's all right.
So that we could have a conversation.
Is that your hint for me to leave?
Okay.
- It's all right. Mm-hm.
- Okay, I'll call you later.
Celeste...
I do think you need to take some...
Some real time to heal,
and that while you do that,
I think Max and Josh should reside with me.
No.
- That won't be necessary.
- No, I...
I think it is ne... It is necessary.
- Look, last night was a misunderstanding...
- No, no, this is not about last night.
It's about a whole totality of events.
You're a mess, Celeste.
And until you're better,
we just have to think about
protecting the well-being of our boys.
We should at least
be able to agree on that. Hmm?
My boys will not be going
to live with you.
But they're at risk here.
They're at risk in your care.
And I'm their grandmother,
and I will not forsake them,
and I will not forsake what I know
Perry would want me to do for them.
I need you to get out of here.
- Right now.
- We can calmly...
No, no.
- Celeste...
- Get the fuck out of here!
Okay, I'm going to give you this
as a courtesy.
- What?
- It's a...
- What is it?
- A petition
- No.
- For assignment
- of the guardian of the person. Persons.
- What?
- It's plural in this case.
It'll be filed in the Monterey County
Superior Court tomorrow morning.
We need to do what's best for the boys.
- She could really lose her kids?
- Maybe.
It's California law, and it's very tricky.
- You got her a good lawyer.
- Good. She's good.
But I would have had her hire Ira Farber,
and now I hear Mary Louise got him,
- and that's why he was unavailable.
- Oh, my God.
It's just everything feels like
it's unraveling, and Bonnie,
- I don't know how she's keeping it together.
- I heard her mother is stable.
- Hey, Madeline.
- Oh.
- Hello.
Renata.
It's nice to see you both. You well?
- Yeah.
- Great.
- You?
Hey, I heard you gave a great talk
the other night at Otter Bay Assembly.
Wish I'd seen that.
People pull out their iPhones
at these things.
I'm sure it's posted somewhere
on Instagram or something.
I'll look for it.
Have a good day.
What the fuck was that?
- Hi, Jane.
- Hi.
- What a surpri...
- Can we have a conversation, please?
Of course, come in.
- Can I get you a cup of tea?
- No, I'm fine.
I'm just a little bit curious as to what you're
doing and if you plan to take my kid next.
What? What would make you think
that I would seek custody of Ziggy?
- You're a wonderful, wonderful mother.
- So is Celeste.
No. No, no.
I have concerns about Celeste.
Her mental and emotional health...
I know you're her friend, Jane.
But truly, do you not also worry?
No. No, I don't.
Well, put yourself in my shoes.
If you became convinced
that the boys were at risk...
- They're not at risk.
- Physically at risk.
I've seen her as a mom.
She's a great parent.
You have seen the outward appearance,
but I've seen the drawer, with, uh, Ambien
and Vicodin and Xanax,
something with a tramma... I don't know.
All these different medications,
and she's driving on these roads.
Let me ask you,
do you ever put Ziggy in the car with her?
Does he sit in the front next to her
when the twins are strapped in the back?
Are you okay with that?
- I'm not gonna testify against you.
- But they might force you.
They might be able to, I don't know,
get a court order.
Celeste, first of all, you can trust me.
I trusted her,
so don't talk to me about trust right now.
I let her into my life.
I let her into my house.
I tried to help her.
Whatever you say to me
is doctor-patient privileged.
- You know that.
- I don't feel strong enough to handle this.
They're gonna wanna interview the kids,
and they've been through enough.
We've all been through enough,
for God's sake.
Maybe you can settle?
Don't tell me to fucking settle.
I'm not settling anything with that woman.
God. These are my kids.
And she wants them.
She wants my boys.
If she's seeking custody on the grounds
of parental unfitness or neglect...
Whose side are you on, for God's sake?
I've seen the way these things play out.
Nobody wins.
I will win. I'll fucking win.
God.
Mama.
Hi.
What, Mama?
Mama...
♪ Tell me why, tell me why ♪
♪ Ooh, why can't we live together I
♪ Everybody wants to live together ♪
♪ Why can't we be together? ♪
♪ No more war, no more war, no more war ♪
♪ Ooh, just a little peace in this world F
♪ No more war, no more war ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ All we want is some peace in this world ♪
♪ Everybody wants to live together ♪
♪ Why can't we be together? ♪
♪ Gotta live, Gotta live ♪
♪ Gotta live together ♪
♪ Gotta live, gotta live ♪
♪ No matter, no matter what color ♪
♪ Ooh, you are still my brother ♪
♪ Everybody wants to live together ♪
♪ Why can't we be together? ♪
♪ Gotta live, gotta live ♪
♪ Gotta live together ♪
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::