1
00:00:02,651 --> 00:00:04,429
Previously on Prison Break...

2
00:00:04,432 --> 00:00:07,476
Losing a brother, the massive
hole that leaves in your life.

3
00:00:07,479 --> 00:00:08,844
Like the same massive hole

4
00:00:08,846 --> 00:00:10,164
losing a husband makes.

5
00:00:10,167 --> 00:00:12,614
- Your brother's dead, Lincoln.
- How do you explain that?

6
00:00:12,617 --> 00:00:14,586
- Lincoln Burrows.
- Jacob.

7
00:00:14,589 --> 00:00:16,489
- Uncle Lincoln!
- Hey!

8
00:00:16,491 --> 00:00:18,792
911. I have an armed
intruder in my house.

9
00:00:18,795 --> 00:00:20,729
We've awoken something...

10
00:00:20,732 --> 00:00:22,807
Something people are trying
to hide about Michael.

11
00:00:22,810 --> 00:00:25,651
- I don't know who we're fighting.
- Let's go to Yemen and find out.

12
00:00:25,654 --> 00:00:27,113
You don't know a damn thing about Yemen.

13
00:00:27,115 --> 00:00:28,601
I'll find someone who does.

14
00:00:28,603 --> 00:00:30,637
The country's falling apart.
Everyone wants out.

15
00:00:31,990 --> 00:00:33,422
Welcome to the civil war.

16
00:00:33,425 --> 00:00:35,726
Come quickly, or we'll all be dead!

17
00:00:35,729 --> 00:00:37,878
- Who's that contact again?
- A woman named Sheba.

18
00:00:37,880 --> 00:00:39,734
Michael's caught in the
middle of something big.

19
00:00:39,736 --> 00:00:40,736
Kaniel Outis is

20
00:00:40,739 --> 00:00:42,348
- a big-time terrorist.
- We've arranged

21
00:00:42,350 --> 00:00:44,039
a visit to Ogygia Prison.

22
00:00:44,042 --> 00:00:45,476
That mean Michael's in there?

23
00:00:45,478 --> 00:00:46,407
Michael?

24
00:00:46,410 --> 00:00:49,255
My name isn't Michael, and
I don't know who you are.

25
00:00:49,257 --> 00:00:51,090
_

26
00:00:51,092 --> 00:00:53,226
Michael, what are you doing, damn it?!

27
00:00:53,687 --> 00:00:56,388
The fighting in Yemen intensified today

28
00:00:56,391 --> 00:00:58,831
as ISIL forces get ever
nearer to the capitol.

29
00:00:58,833 --> 00:01:01,367
The rebels, who have the
stated intent of taking over

30
00:01:01,369 --> 00:01:03,836
the country and establishing
a radical caliphate,

31
00:01:03,838 --> 00:01:05,772
are also bent on freeing their leader,

32
00:01:05,774 --> 00:01:09,309
Abu Ramal, who was captured by
the government five years ago.

33
00:01:09,311 --> 00:01:12,578
Ramal is known for his
extreme views and practices,

34
00:01:12,581 --> 00:01:14,847
from using young girls as sex slaves,

35
00:01:14,849 --> 00:01:17,850
to a medieval brand of justice
that includes public beheadings

36
00:01:17,852 --> 00:01:19,485
and executions in the street.

37
00:01:19,487 --> 00:01:21,421
Ramal is currently being held in Yemen's

38
00:01:21,423 --> 00:01:24,206
most notorious
penitentiary, Ogygia Prison.

39
00:01:24,207 --> 00:01:27,002
_

40
00:01:52,191 --> 00:01:53,624
Psst.

41
00:01:56,360 --> 00:01:58,360
This is it.

42
00:02:01,062 --> 00:02:03,396
Whip, get up here.

43
00:02:03,398 --> 00:02:05,698
Is it happening?

44
00:02:05,700 --> 00:02:08,701
You are not going to leave us, are you?

45
00:02:08,703 --> 00:02:11,671
- If the rebels take the city, we're dead.
- You've told us that

46
00:02:11,673 --> 00:02:14,507
a thousand times, Sid. You're
a broken record. Is it clear?

47
00:02:15,910 --> 00:02:17,744
Okay, it's clear.

48
00:02:17,746 --> 00:02:20,446
Whip. Come on.

49
00:02:21,650 --> 00:02:24,651
Lights go out... you follow.

50
00:02:24,653 --> 00:02:26,019
Come on.

51
00:02:30,615 --> 00:02:32,448
Would have made it so much easier

52
00:02:32,451 --> 00:02:35,853
if it was just you and me like
it was on all the other ones.

53
00:02:35,856 --> 00:02:38,264
Nothing is easy on this one.

54
00:02:38,266 --> 00:02:41,200
Yeah, tell me about it.

55
00:02:47,342 --> 00:02:49,776
One minute.

56
00:03:26,414 --> 00:03:28,081
Board spans the gap.

57
00:03:28,083 --> 00:03:30,383
Okay.

58
00:03:32,287 --> 00:03:33,619
Blanket covers the wire.

59
00:03:37,279 --> 00:03:38,956
Now it's about those lights going out.

60
00:03:40,395 --> 00:03:42,361
He didn't flash it 24 hours before.

61
00:03:42,363 --> 00:03:44,630
- That's supposed to be the signal.
- Have faith.

62
00:03:44,632 --> 00:03:46,432
Seven straight nights?

63
00:03:46,434 --> 00:03:48,601
No signal, no lights getting turned out?

64
00:03:52,407 --> 00:03:54,974
Those strikes are getting closer, too.

65
00:03:57,345 --> 00:03:59,512
Those lights aren't going out.

66
00:03:59,514 --> 00:04:01,881
- Lights aren't going out.
- Got to go back.

67
00:04:01,883 --> 00:04:03,265
Maybe make a run for it.

68
00:04:03,268 --> 00:04:04,851
Too much ground to cover.
They'll shoot us down

69
00:04:04,853 --> 00:04:05,993
before we make the gap.

70
00:04:05,994 --> 00:04:07,920
What's the plan then? Give up and die?

71
00:04:07,922 --> 00:04:09,522
I can't wait another four years.

72
00:04:09,524 --> 00:04:11,390
It was supposed to be one week.

73
00:04:11,392 --> 00:04:13,826
- Poseidon has left us here to die.
- We still got

74
00:04:13,828 --> 00:04:15,628
one card left to play.

75
00:04:15,630 --> 00:04:17,930
I didn't want to play it,
but it's already in motion.

76
00:04:17,932 --> 00:04:19,999
Let's go.

77
00:04:23,777 --> 00:04:26,004
Apparently, Kaniel Outis
was thrown into Ogygia

78
00:04:26,006 --> 00:04:27,672
for crimes against the government.

79
00:04:27,674 --> 00:04:29,874
Shortly after, he was captured

80
00:04:29,876 --> 00:04:32,911
trying to escape, and
thrown into solitary.

81
00:04:32,913 --> 00:04:35,113
They just released him
into gen pop recently.

82
00:04:35,115 --> 00:04:36,681
Call him Michael, will you?

83
00:04:36,683 --> 00:04:38,750
But why didn't he acknowledge us

84
00:04:38,752 --> 00:04:41,419
when he saw us?

85
00:04:50,130 --> 00:04:51,796
Stop!

86
00:04:53,533 --> 00:04:54,959
Get back here!

87
00:05:22,228 --> 00:05:24,562
- Kid was spying on us.
- Yeah.

88
00:05:24,564 --> 00:05:26,991
And he left something under the doormat.

89
00:05:42,500 --> 00:05:45,336
_

90
00:06:21,333 --> 00:06:24,012
This is Michael's handwriting.
Swan was his calling card.

91
00:06:24,015 --> 00:06:25,308
He's reaching out to us.

92
00:06:25,311 --> 00:06:27,390
But why is he being so mysterious?

93
00:06:29,048 --> 00:06:31,749
Back in the day, he never
talked to you straight, as in

94
00:06:31,751 --> 00:06:33,113
- not in code?
- He's worried about

95
00:06:33,116 --> 00:06:34,651
someone intercepting his message.

96
00:06:34,653 --> 00:06:36,389
Yeah, but what does it mean?

97
00:06:36,392 --> 00:06:38,489
I don't know, but
we're supposed to know.

98
00:06:38,491 --> 00:06:40,791
"Sheik of Light." Sheik of Light.

99
00:06:40,793 --> 00:06:43,327
That sounds like a
guy on a mountain peak

100
00:06:43,329 --> 00:06:44,962
communing with God.

101
00:06:44,964 --> 00:06:47,097
Yeah, we got to get help.

102
00:06:47,099 --> 00:06:49,366
- We're out of help.
- Sheba.

103
00:06:49,368 --> 00:06:51,433
She's thinks I'm abetting a terrorist.

104
00:06:51,436 --> 00:06:54,972
Well, then you have to
convince her that you're not.

105
00:06:54,974 --> 00:06:57,174
You have got to leave, Papa.

106
00:06:57,176 --> 00:07:00,444
- I will not run away.
- The government is being targeted.

107
00:07:00,446 --> 00:07:03,080
You are being targeted.

108
00:07:03,082 --> 00:07:05,582
- I'm a no one.
- You are government to them.

109
00:07:05,584 --> 00:07:09,186
You don't understand being a Yemeni.

110
00:07:11,123 --> 00:07:14,258
You would run away when
she needs you the most?

111
00:07:14,260 --> 00:07:18,262
I understand that we are no
good to this country dead.

112
00:07:18,264 --> 00:07:21,198
Papa, there will come
a time. We go abroad,

113
00:07:21,200 --> 00:07:23,200
regroup with an exile government.

114
00:07:23,202 --> 00:07:25,736
With what money, girl?

115
00:07:25,738 --> 00:07:28,207
It would cost two years' salary.

116
00:07:31,691 --> 00:07:35,879
I'd rather die with my face
to the enemy than to run away.

117
00:07:35,881 --> 00:07:38,482
Papa...

118
00:07:45,224 --> 00:07:47,291
- Hey.
- I suggest you leave

119
00:07:47,294 --> 00:07:50,861
this country as quickly as you can.

120
00:07:50,863 --> 00:07:52,710
What's he doing here?

121
00:07:52,713 --> 00:07:54,145
My friend needs your help.

122
00:07:54,148 --> 00:07:55,117
I gave him my help.

123
00:07:55,120 --> 00:07:57,300
You didn't tell me he was
working with the enemy.

124
00:07:57,303 --> 00:07:59,192
This man you claim is your brother,

125
00:07:59,195 --> 00:08:01,705
Kaniel Outis, worked with the rebels.

126
00:08:01,707 --> 00:08:03,340
- His name's Michael Scofield.
- I don't care!

127
00:08:03,342 --> 00:08:05,108
Not Kaniel Outis!

128
00:08:05,110 --> 00:08:07,442
There's nothing you
can say to me that will

129
00:08:07,445 --> 00:08:09,888
make me help you, okay?

130
00:08:09,891 --> 00:08:12,485
Is that right?

131
00:08:12,488 --> 00:08:15,422
This enough to get your
family out of the country?

132
00:08:20,690 --> 00:08:22,947
Deliver me this first.

133
00:08:27,081 --> 00:08:30,091
_

134
00:08:31,124 --> 00:08:33,257
Ready, love?

135
00:08:38,911 --> 00:08:41,716
_

136
00:08:50,606 --> 00:08:52,520
- What's that?
- It's, uh... it's

137
00:08:52,523 --> 00:08:54,934
something your Uncle Lincoln sent.

138
00:08:54,937 --> 00:08:56,682
- Here.
- I don't want to go.

139
00:08:56,685 --> 00:08:57,948
I want to stay with you.

140
00:08:57,950 --> 00:09:00,384
You got to go to school.

141
00:09:00,386 --> 00:09:02,286
And I'm gonna be right
here when the bell rings.

142
00:09:02,288 --> 00:09:04,889
Okay? You walk down those steps,

143
00:09:04,891 --> 00:09:06,957
you hop straight into the car. Yeah?

144
00:09:09,923 --> 00:09:12,579
I love you.

145
00:09:12,582 --> 00:09:14,065
Make it a great day.

146
00:09:27,265 --> 00:09:29,013
I got the note.

147
00:09:30,283 --> 00:09:32,917
I got the note, Michael.

148
00:09:40,960 --> 00:09:42,727
We're going to get you out of here.

149
00:09:42,729 --> 00:09:45,096
Look, my name isn't Michael,

150
00:09:45,098 --> 00:09:48,265
and I don't know who you are.

151
00:09:48,267 --> 00:09:50,067
I'm sorry.

152
00:09:58,065 --> 00:09:59,443
Hey.

153
00:09:59,445 --> 00:10:01,212
You know I'm a noted economist?

154
00:10:01,214 --> 00:10:02,880
I mean, that's what
it says in the paper.

155
00:10:02,882 --> 00:10:06,717
"Noted Economist Attacked in Home."

156
00:10:06,719 --> 00:10:08,986
I didn't even know
economists made the news.

157
00:10:08,988 --> 00:10:11,389
That's the first and
last time, hopefully.

158
00:10:11,391 --> 00:10:15,960
I've been trying to piece
this thing together.

159
00:10:15,962 --> 00:10:18,429
You remember those government guys,

160
00:10:18,431 --> 00:10:20,346
those think tank guys,

161
00:10:20,349 --> 00:10:22,583
trying to pick my
brain about game theory,

162
00:10:22,586 --> 00:10:24,786
how they could use
it for foreign policy?

163
00:10:24,789 --> 00:10:26,950
Yeah, you bored the
hell out of 'em, right?

164
00:10:26,953 --> 00:10:30,074
Yeah, okay, but I mean,
did I hear something

165
00:10:30,076 --> 00:10:32,443
- I shouldn't have?
- I don't know. Did you?

166
00:10:32,445 --> 00:10:33,944
Like who shot JFK?

167
00:10:33,946 --> 00:10:36,280
I am trying to be serious here.

168
00:10:36,282 --> 00:10:37,848
No, you're doped up on painkillers

169
00:10:37,850 --> 00:10:39,974
and you're thinking too much.

170
00:10:39,977 --> 00:10:42,432
I promise this has
nothing to do with you.

171
00:10:42,435 --> 00:10:46,457
You rest. I'm going to, um...

172
00:10:46,459 --> 00:10:48,292
I'm gonna run some errands,

173
00:10:48,294 --> 00:10:50,327
and then I'm gonna come visit you, okay?

174
00:10:50,329 --> 00:10:52,763
Okay. Love you.

175
00:10:53,900 --> 00:10:55,833
Love you, too.

176
00:11:07,213 --> 00:11:08,946
Okay, no problem. Thanks.

177
00:11:08,948 --> 00:11:11,949
Hi. I, uh, I called earlier
about a missing U.S. citizen

178
00:11:11,951 --> 00:11:14,251
- in the Middle East.
- Yes. I'm Henry Kishida.

179
00:11:14,253 --> 00:11:16,687
Let me walk you to
the director's office.

180
00:11:17,361 --> 00:11:19,194
It's an unusual situation,

181
00:11:19,197 --> 00:11:20,825
which you can appreciate,

182
00:11:20,827 --> 00:11:23,045
since your husband is
declared legally dead,

183
00:11:23,048 --> 00:11:24,359
and the person that you're referring to

184
00:11:24,361 --> 00:11:26,063
goes by another name.

185
00:11:26,065 --> 00:11:28,365
I'll take it from here, Henry.

186
00:11:30,670 --> 00:11:32,236
How are you, Sara?

187
00:11:32,238 --> 00:11:33,838
Kellerman?

188
00:11:40,465 --> 00:11:43,114
I'll leave you two be. Let me
know if you need anything, sir.

189
00:11:43,117 --> 00:11:45,463
- Mm-hmm.
- Sorry, how did I

190
00:11:45,465 --> 00:11:46,664
end up with you again?

191
00:11:46,666 --> 00:11:48,632
You asked for the
State Department's help.

192
00:11:48,634 --> 00:11:50,267
I wanted the State Department, not you.

193
00:11:50,269 --> 00:11:51,936
Yeah, you've lived

194
00:11:51,938 --> 00:11:53,904
so many lives, I don't know who you are.

195
00:11:53,906 --> 00:11:55,881
That'd be a consistent theme
for you, wouldn't it, given that

196
00:11:55,883 --> 00:11:57,775
you were married to a
man who never existed?

197
00:11:57,777 --> 00:11:59,810
What is that supposed to mean?

198
00:11:59,812 --> 00:12:02,246
It means you should come
in and let me enlighten you

199
00:12:02,248 --> 00:12:04,382
to all things Michael Scofield...

200
00:12:04,384 --> 00:12:06,617
Or should I say Kaniel Outis?

201
00:12:12,479 --> 00:12:14,046
You shouldn't drink

202
00:12:14,049 --> 00:12:16,246
bottled water... the
dioxins, the BPAs in there...

203
00:12:16,249 --> 00:12:17,648
I'm touched by your concern.

204
00:12:17,651 --> 00:12:18,729
Have a seat.

205
00:12:18,732 --> 00:12:20,031
Good, thank you.

206
00:12:21,940 --> 00:12:23,801
You know, Sara...

207
00:12:23,803 --> 00:12:26,437
you and I have... a checkered past.

208
00:12:27,666 --> 00:12:30,343
But I am evermore a
boring guy now, and...

209
00:12:30,346 --> 00:12:32,221
mellowed by life, trust me.

210
00:12:32,224 --> 00:12:33,857
If you have something
you want to tell me

211
00:12:33,860 --> 00:12:35,593
about Michael, I'd sure love to hear it.

212
00:12:35,596 --> 00:12:39,216
Okay. When your call came in
and Kishida processed it...

213
00:12:39,218 --> 00:12:41,519
well, let's just say
there are certain keywords

214
00:12:41,521 --> 00:12:43,751
that get our system
buzzing pretty quickly.

215
00:12:43,754 --> 00:12:45,387
Kaniel Outis...

216
00:12:45,389 --> 00:12:47,416
Actually, can't stand it

217
00:12:47,419 --> 00:12:49,185
watching you drink out of that.

218
00:12:49,188 --> 00:12:50,838
Hey, Kishida?

219
00:12:50,841 --> 00:12:54,275
Could you bring Sara a
glass for her water, please?

220
00:12:54,277 --> 00:12:55,310
Thank you.

221
00:12:55,312 --> 00:12:56,711
Kaniel Outis...

222
00:12:56,713 --> 00:12:57,879
is a known terrorist,

223
00:12:57,881 --> 00:12:59,748
ties to ISIL, wanted in the killing

224
00:12:59,750 --> 00:13:00,949
of a senior CIA official.

225
00:13:00,951 --> 00:13:02,398
- Michael's no killer.
- You see,

226
00:13:02,401 --> 00:13:04,052
that's the problem.

227
00:13:04,055 --> 00:13:05,630
Because Kaniel Outis is.

228
00:13:05,633 --> 00:13:07,006
Thank you.

229
00:13:07,009 --> 00:13:08,108
You're welcome.

230
00:13:08,111 --> 00:13:09,510
And...

231
00:13:09,513 --> 00:13:11,793
this is Kaniel Outis.

232
00:13:11,795 --> 00:13:13,361
That's ridiculous.

233
00:13:13,363 --> 00:13:15,296
The record here at State says

234
00:13:15,298 --> 00:13:18,166
- that... that's Kaniel Outis's face.
- Okay,

235
00:13:18,168 --> 00:13:20,402
but you and I both know
who Michael Scofield was.

236
00:13:20,404 --> 00:13:22,604
No, that's just a memory.

237
00:13:22,606 --> 00:13:25,111
The official record... history...

238
00:13:25,114 --> 00:13:26,680
It says otherwise now.

239
00:13:26,683 --> 00:13:30,005
Now, that's scary, to think
who could be behind that.

240
00:13:30,008 --> 00:13:33,076
Because only somebody very formidable

241
00:13:33,079 --> 00:13:34,274
would be capable

242
00:13:34,277 --> 00:13:36,183
of officially turning
one man into another.

243
00:13:36,186 --> 00:13:39,287
It would take a genius... like Michael.

244
00:13:41,625 --> 00:13:43,391
You're insinuating that he did this?

245
00:13:43,393 --> 00:13:45,226
He disappeared,

246
00:13:45,228 --> 00:13:46,814
just quit on his life?

247
00:13:46,817 --> 00:13:48,417
I want answers just like you do.

248
00:13:48,420 --> 00:13:49,998
Who's capable of this?

249
00:13:50,000 --> 00:13:53,034
Only a handful of people in the world.

250
00:13:53,036 --> 00:13:55,637
Sara? Sara!

251
00:13:58,308 --> 00:14:01,509
I figure we got a day, maybe two,

252
00:14:01,511 --> 00:14:03,278
tops, to get out of this hole.

253
00:14:07,546 --> 00:14:08,616
At that point,

254
00:14:08,618 --> 00:14:11,129
either the shelling gets us...

255
00:14:11,132 --> 00:14:13,065
or ISIL does.

256
00:14:15,776 --> 00:14:17,509
Does any of this phase you at all?

257
00:14:17,512 --> 00:14:18,896
The fact that we're gonna die in here?

258
00:14:18,898 --> 00:14:21,596
We're not gonna die.
We're still getting out.

259
00:14:21,598 --> 00:14:22,964
All of us.

260
00:14:24,147 --> 00:14:26,247
How's that? The roof?

261
00:14:26,249 --> 00:14:28,416
- The roof ain't happening.
- The roof is happening.

262
00:14:28,418 --> 00:14:30,418
We don't have time to come
up with another escape plan.

263
00:14:30,420 --> 00:14:32,620
So you are nervous.

264
00:14:36,059 --> 00:14:39,360
Great, now I know I'm in deep crap.

265
00:14:40,496 --> 00:14:42,897
I'm only doing this for the money.

266
00:14:42,899 --> 00:14:45,967
Don't think you and I are suddenly good.

267
00:14:45,969 --> 00:14:48,436
You just deliver me the sheik.

268
00:14:48,438 --> 00:14:51,138
The sheiks are well away from here.

269
00:14:51,140 --> 00:14:52,840
High desert.

270
00:14:52,842 --> 00:14:54,059
And I've never heard of one

271
00:14:54,062 --> 00:14:56,077
being referred to as Sheik of Light.

272
00:14:56,079 --> 00:14:58,679
Which means it's probably a code.

273
00:14:58,681 --> 00:15:01,549
She knows your brother.

274
00:15:02,752 --> 00:15:03,985
This tape...

275
00:15:03,987 --> 00:15:06,821
It's the only thing that doesn't belong.

276
00:15:07,824 --> 00:15:09,590
Your brother speaks in riddles,

277
00:15:09,592 --> 00:15:12,163
- does he?
- Maybe it's Braille

278
00:15:12,166 --> 00:15:14,762
or, uh, Morse.

279
00:15:14,764 --> 00:15:17,098
Or just numbers.

280
00:15:22,286 --> 00:15:24,387
I think it's a phone number.

281
00:15:34,450 --> 00:15:36,550
Voice mail.

282
00:15:36,552 --> 00:15:38,686
Mohammad El-Tunis.

283
00:15:39,956 --> 00:15:42,757
Director of Electrical Works in Sana'a.

284
00:15:42,759 --> 00:15:44,358
Director of Electrical Works.

285
00:15:44,360 --> 00:15:46,327
"Sheik of Light."

286
00:15:52,741 --> 00:15:54,100
_

287
00:15:54,103 --> 00:15:56,170
Thanks for taking the time to see us.

288
00:15:56,172 --> 00:15:57,972
Where is everybody?

289
00:15:57,974 --> 00:16:00,174
They are fleeing ahead of the advance.

290
00:16:00,176 --> 00:16:01,876
We have been trying to reach him.

291
00:16:01,878 --> 00:16:04,251
All we know is that
he went to the suburbs

292
00:16:04,254 --> 00:16:05,946
to try to find his daughter.

293
00:16:05,948 --> 00:16:07,248
Do you have an address for her?

294
00:16:07,250 --> 00:16:09,717
We tried calling her, but no answer.

295
00:16:09,719 --> 00:16:13,888
Address is here.

296
00:16:13,890 --> 00:16:16,123
You are not going to
try to find him, are you?

297
00:16:19,887 --> 00:16:21,544
God be with you, then.

298
00:16:25,068 --> 00:16:27,268
Circled the address.

299
00:16:27,270 --> 00:16:28,502
Good luck.

300
00:16:28,504 --> 00:16:30,137
You're coming with us.

301
00:16:30,139 --> 00:16:32,319
If you think I'm going into the suburbs,

302
00:16:32,322 --> 00:16:33,040
you're crazy.

303
00:16:33,042 --> 00:16:34,575
What's wrong with the suburbs?

304
00:16:34,577 --> 00:16:37,011
The suburbs are out there.

305
00:16:37,013 --> 00:16:38,713
The front line of the war.

306
00:16:38,715 --> 00:16:40,881
Nice knowing you, Benjamin.

307
00:16:40,883 --> 00:16:41,859
I hope next time

308
00:16:41,862 --> 00:16:43,718
it's under better circumstances.

309
00:16:43,720 --> 00:16:46,082
- Pay up.
- You have to get us past the checkpoint.

310
00:16:46,085 --> 00:16:48,456
Two Americans... we'll
never make it without you.

311
00:16:48,458 --> 00:16:49,824
I am not getting myself killed.

312
00:16:49,826 --> 00:16:50,991
Pay up.

313
00:16:50,993 --> 00:16:52,693
Deliver the sheik.

314
00:16:52,695 --> 00:16:54,562
Then you get your money.

315
00:17:02,071 --> 00:17:03,370
Get in.

316
00:17:26,062 --> 00:17:27,595
Yes?

317
00:17:27,597 --> 00:17:30,664
You should check your e-mail, Sara.

318
00:17:33,002 --> 00:17:34,468
What am I looking at?

319
00:17:34,470 --> 00:17:37,505
Footage captured by a
hunter four years ago.

320
00:17:37,507 --> 00:17:40,975
One of those motion sensor
devices you hang on trees,

321
00:17:40,977 --> 00:17:43,010
takes intermittent photos of prey.

322
00:17:43,012 --> 00:17:45,960
Hunter comes out one
morning, finds these images.

323
00:17:56,826 --> 00:17:58,692
This is the killing I
was telling you about.

324
00:17:58,694 --> 00:18:03,497
The victim's Harlan Gaines,
Deputy Chief of the CIA.

325
00:18:03,499 --> 00:18:05,232
And the killer...

326
00:18:05,234 --> 00:18:06,600
well, you can see,

327
00:18:06,602 --> 00:18:08,569
it's who we call Michael Scofield,

328
00:18:08,571 --> 00:18:11,739
- or Kaniel Outis, or...
- This is exactly what they did to Lincoln.

329
00:18:11,741 --> 00:18:13,941
And then there's the blood
evidence the next day.

330
00:18:13,943 --> 00:18:16,377
Kaniel or Michael or whatever
gets on a flight to Yemen.

331
00:18:16,379 --> 00:18:18,314
We all most nail him when he lands.

332
00:18:18,317 --> 00:18:19,814
He gets away.

333
00:18:19,816 --> 00:18:21,282
His luggage doesn't

334
00:18:21,284 --> 00:18:24,685
and Gaines' blood is all
over the clothes inside.

335
00:18:24,687 --> 00:18:27,174
The evidence is overwhelming.

336
00:18:27,177 --> 00:18:30,005
Whatever name you want to call him,

337
00:18:30,008 --> 00:18:31,877
Michael's a murderer, Sara.

338
00:18:40,927 --> 00:18:42,293
Hey.

339
00:18:45,874 --> 00:18:47,140
Are you all right?

340
00:18:47,142 --> 00:18:49,242
You all right?

341
00:18:49,244 --> 00:18:50,777
Oh, this old thing?

342
00:18:50,779 --> 00:18:52,578
Yeah, I'm doing fine.

343
00:18:52,580 --> 00:18:55,214
What's going on?

344
00:18:55,216 --> 00:18:57,050
I need your advice.

345
00:18:57,052 --> 00:18:58,751
It's probably something you're not gonna

346
00:18:58,753 --> 00:19:01,087
want to talk about.

347
00:19:01,089 --> 00:19:03,434
I could really use
your clarity right now.

348
00:19:04,459 --> 00:19:06,259
It's about Michael.

349
00:19:25,366 --> 00:19:27,647
Still want to know how
he got that in here.

350
00:19:27,649 --> 00:19:29,782
Hugging naked with the guards.

351
00:19:29,784 --> 00:19:31,350
Got to be, right?

352
00:19:34,022 --> 00:19:36,923
What the hell is that?

353
00:19:36,925 --> 00:19:38,891
"We are the Champions."

354
00:19:40,872 --> 00:19:44,297
You get stuck in a Porta-Potty
like this, you go Queen?

355
00:19:44,299 --> 00:19:45,431
I mean, where are the girls

356
00:19:45,433 --> 00:19:47,400
riding the washing machines, right?

357
00:19:47,402 --> 00:19:50,164
Look at my screen again,
this goes in your eye.

358
00:19:53,047 --> 00:19:55,108
You know, the world
never ceases to amaze.

359
00:19:55,110 --> 00:19:56,509
You get stuck in a
Middle Eastern prison,

360
00:19:56,511 --> 00:19:58,978
the biggest S.O.B. is a Korean.

361
00:19:58,980 --> 00:20:00,980
He's in withdrawal.

362
00:20:09,789 --> 00:20:11,724
You know, he's
the biggest collector

363
00:20:11,727 --> 00:20:13,960
of Queen paraphernalia in the world.

364
00:20:13,962 --> 00:20:16,838
They say his house in Seoul
is a shrine to Freddy Mercury.

365
00:20:16,841 --> 00:20:18,331
And he got in here how?

366
00:20:18,333 --> 00:20:20,099
Identity theft.

367
00:20:20,101 --> 00:20:21,936
Apparently he used to sit on his couch,

368
00:20:21,939 --> 00:20:24,475
hack high net worth
accounts all over the world.

369
00:20:24,478 --> 00:20:27,240
Turned it into a collection
of Hummers, helicopters

370
00:20:27,242 --> 00:20:29,342
and, apparently, Freddy Mercury's ashes.

371
00:20:29,344 --> 00:20:32,178
Wait, you mean like his burnt-up body?

372
00:20:32,180 --> 00:20:35,047
The story is Freddy's cremated,
but his ashes go missing.

373
00:20:35,049 --> 00:20:37,416
To this day no one knows where they are.

374
00:20:37,418 --> 00:20:40,653
Ja admitted to me once when
he was high he bought them.

375
00:20:40,655 --> 00:20:42,388
Two million bucks.

376
00:20:42,390 --> 00:20:44,524
He's got Queen's lead
singer in his family room.

377
00:20:44,526 --> 00:20:46,392
How exactly do you know all this?

378
00:20:46,394 --> 00:20:47,635
I asked him.

379
00:20:47,638 --> 00:20:49,938
He's a real mensch when
he's not in withdrawal.

380
00:20:49,941 --> 00:20:52,999
I didn't know you talked to him.

381
00:20:53,001 --> 00:20:54,500
Amazing.

382
00:20:54,502 --> 00:20:56,636
Just when I think I
know your game, I don't.

383
00:20:56,638 --> 00:20:58,171
You know my game, Whip.

384
00:20:58,173 --> 00:20:59,605
See, right there, "Whip."

385
00:20:59,607 --> 00:21:01,274
I don't even know why you call me that.

386
00:21:01,276 --> 00:21:02,875
Because you're my whip hand.

387
00:21:02,877 --> 00:21:04,544
My ace in the hole.

388
00:21:04,546 --> 00:21:07,246
Yeah, sure, okay.

389
00:21:08,701 --> 00:21:12,285
See, in game theory,
it serves you to be two-faced.

390
00:21:12,287 --> 00:21:17,245
Be everyone's friend till
the moment you're not.

391
00:21:17,248 --> 00:21:19,979
You make them love you so much
that when they're up against it,

392
00:21:19,982 --> 00:21:21,527
their loyalty will make them act

393
00:21:21,529 --> 00:21:23,329
against their own best interests.

394
00:21:23,331 --> 00:21:25,698
That's game theory.

395
00:21:25,700 --> 00:21:29,869
A cold, rational focus on winning.

396
00:21:29,871 --> 00:21:32,572
Even if it's at everyone else's expense.

397
00:21:32,574 --> 00:21:35,731
What I'm trying to understand
is what he stands to gain.

398
00:21:35,734 --> 00:21:40,154
Leaving his family,
and-and the new identity.

399
00:21:40,157 --> 00:21:42,315
According to the little you've
told me, he was different.

400
00:21:42,317 --> 00:21:43,583
Always an agenda, right?

401
00:21:43,585 --> 00:21:45,857
Yeah.

402
00:21:45,860 --> 00:21:47,820
I mean, he apparently loved you.

403
00:21:47,822 --> 00:21:49,288
Of course he loved you.

404
00:21:49,290 --> 00:21:51,757
How could he not?

405
00:21:51,759 --> 00:21:54,760
But he also wanted you to open that door

406
00:21:54,762 --> 00:21:57,701
in the prison for him.

407
00:21:57,704 --> 00:21:59,865
I mean, true game theory,

408
00:21:59,867 --> 00:22:02,868
everything, everyone

409
00:22:02,870 --> 00:22:06,572
is a contingency.

410
00:22:06,574 --> 00:22:09,242
You meet people, you
bring them into your life

411
00:22:09,244 --> 00:22:12,645
and you keep them
percolating until the moment

412
00:22:12,647 --> 00:22:15,915
you need to manipulate the
relationship to your advantage.

413
00:22:17,986 --> 00:22:20,920
I'm not judging, you
know? That's not my thing.

414
00:22:20,922 --> 00:22:22,888
- I know.
- You know me. But...

415
00:22:24,926 --> 00:22:26,959
schema as deep

416
00:22:26,961 --> 00:22:29,962
and as calculating as
that can, in the end,

417
00:22:29,964 --> 00:22:32,331
spin a man off into madness.

418
00:22:32,333 --> 00:22:34,667
He might initially think
smaller evils are okay

419
00:22:34,669 --> 00:22:36,435
in the service of a greater good.

420
00:22:36,437 --> 00:22:39,071
Like breaking Lincoln out of prison.

421
00:22:39,073 --> 00:22:42,041
But the dance of good and
evil could become jumbled,

422
00:22:42,043 --> 00:22:44,143
and the manipulation itself becomes

423
00:22:44,145 --> 00:22:45,945
the most important thing.

424
00:22:45,947 --> 00:22:47,780
Becomes about winning

425
00:22:47,782 --> 00:22:50,816
rather than whether the
game should be won at all.

426
00:22:58,485 --> 00:23:01,926
I don't think I've seen
you this scared before.

427
00:23:07,302 --> 00:23:10,303
They say, for Ramadan, as an act

428
00:23:10,305 --> 00:23:12,672
of forgiveness, they're going to release

429
00:23:12,674 --> 00:23:14,607
all prisoners from solitary over there

430
00:23:14,609 --> 00:23:17,610
back into general population.

431
00:23:17,612 --> 00:23:19,464
Worst of the worst.

432
00:23:19,467 --> 00:23:21,585
ISIL fanatics.

433
00:23:21,588 --> 00:23:24,250
Abu Ramal.

434
00:23:24,252 --> 00:23:26,759
They're going to kill me, you know.

435
00:23:26,762 --> 00:23:30,856
Government gave me 20 years

436
00:23:30,858 --> 00:23:34,427
for homosexuality.

437
00:23:34,429 --> 00:23:36,195
But the monsters in there,

438
00:23:36,197 --> 00:23:38,564
Ramal and his men,

439
00:23:38,566 --> 00:23:41,267
won't let me live 20 minutes.

440
00:23:42,236 --> 00:23:44,570
Please tell me

441
00:23:44,572 --> 00:23:47,073
you still plan on
getting us out of here.

442
00:23:47,075 --> 00:23:49,241
You were responsible
for killing the lights,

443
00:23:49,243 --> 00:23:51,344
and then your Sheik
of Light went missing

444
00:23:51,346 --> 00:23:53,679
at exactly the wrong time.

445
00:23:53,681 --> 00:23:57,350
I don't know what happened to him.

446
00:23:57,352 --> 00:24:00,786
Maybe I can find another way.

447
00:24:00,788 --> 00:24:02,722
There is something you could do.

448
00:24:02,724 --> 00:24:04,390
Give me a piece of that gum.

449
00:24:04,392 --> 00:24:08,094
Piece of gum is going
to get us out of prison?

450
00:24:08,096 --> 00:24:10,719
It'll start the process.

451
00:24:10,722 --> 00:24:13,232
Sometimes, my friend, I
can't tell which is bigger,

452
00:24:13,234 --> 00:24:15,634
your plans or your lies.

453
00:24:15,636 --> 00:24:18,771
I take that personally,
you calling me a liar.

454
00:24:18,773 --> 00:24:21,807
And I'm gonna show you, just
like the butterfly's wings,

455
00:24:21,809 --> 00:24:24,543
this piece of gum is gonna
start a sequence of events

456
00:24:24,545 --> 00:24:27,046
that will finish on the
other side of the world.

457
00:24:42,689 --> 00:24:45,457
Battery, please.

458
00:25:04,311 --> 00:25:07,612
Prison lighter.

459
00:25:14,342 --> 00:25:16,558
Whip, I need your socks.

460
00:25:21,995 --> 00:25:24,462
Sid, water can.

461
00:25:30,370 --> 00:25:32,370
How we doing out there?

462
00:25:32,372 --> 00:25:34,773
We're all good. Quick though.

463
00:25:36,817 --> 00:25:38,950
Okay.

464
00:25:43,283 --> 00:25:44,683
Hey.

465
00:25:44,685 --> 00:25:46,384
You sure about this?

466
00:25:46,386 --> 00:25:47,485
There's no time left.

467
00:25:47,487 --> 00:25:49,087
The city's about to collapse.

468
00:25:49,089 --> 00:25:52,590
Desperate times call
for desperate measures.

469
00:25:59,900 --> 00:26:01,032
Ah! Got it.

470
00:26:01,034 --> 00:26:02,832
Come on, come on, come on.

471
00:26:04,304 --> 00:26:05,570
Go, go, go.

472
00:26:06,840 --> 00:26:08,973
Guards!

473
00:26:08,975 --> 00:26:11,342
We got a sick one in here.

474
00:26:13,810 --> 00:26:15,576
What is this?

475
00:26:15,579 --> 00:26:17,682
He's burning up, he needs the infirmary.

476
00:26:17,684 --> 00:26:19,367
Please.

477
00:26:24,524 --> 00:26:26,713
This is it.

478
00:26:26,716 --> 00:26:29,294
Limit of government control.

479
00:26:29,296 --> 00:26:32,497
Anything after this is ISIL territory.

480
00:26:32,499 --> 00:26:34,599
Stop.

481
00:26:37,838 --> 00:26:40,538
Let me do the talking.

482
00:26:53,653 --> 00:26:56,321
He's says us being
Westerners, a woman...

483
00:26:56,323 --> 00:26:59,090
we go inside, we are not coming back.

484
00:26:59,092 --> 00:27:01,993
They're not letting us through.

485
00:27:01,995 --> 00:27:05,764
Tell him I bet $500 bucks
we'll make it back in one piece.

486
00:27:05,766 --> 00:27:08,266
He doesn't have $500 to bet.

487
00:27:08,268 --> 00:27:09,567
It doesn't matter.

488
00:27:09,569 --> 00:27:12,537
We don't make it back, he keeps it.

489
00:27:28,088 --> 00:27:30,288
He says we have a death wish.

490
00:27:30,290 --> 00:27:31,823
Fine.

491
00:27:42,894 --> 00:27:47,771
The city used to be beautiful, alive.

492
00:27:47,774 --> 00:27:50,275
Look what they've done to it.

493
00:27:56,082 --> 00:27:59,017
They're putting up
portraits of Abu Ramal.

494
00:27:59,019 --> 00:28:01,252
He's only gotten more powerful

495
00:28:01,254 --> 00:28:04,088
since he got locked up in Ogygia.

496
00:28:04,090 --> 00:28:06,124
God help us if he gets out.

497
00:28:26,713 --> 00:28:28,646
ISIL.

498
00:28:28,648 --> 00:28:30,281
We're gonna get stopped. Get down.

499
00:28:30,283 --> 00:28:31,816
Down now.

500
00:28:31,819 --> 00:28:33,920
Cover up.

501
00:28:37,991 --> 00:28:39,624
Can't believe this.

502
00:28:39,626 --> 00:28:41,125
I know him.

503
00:28:44,054 --> 00:28:45,496
_

504
00:28:47,599 --> 00:28:48,839
_

505
00:28:50,437 --> 00:28:51,669
Reza.

506
00:28:51,671 --> 00:28:54,138
It's Abu Amir now.

507
00:28:54,140 --> 00:28:57,342
What are you doing
in the suburbs, Sheba?

508
00:28:58,266 --> 00:29:00,466
Took a wrong turn.

509
00:29:01,414 --> 00:29:03,348
You got your hair covered up.

510
00:29:03,350 --> 00:29:06,384
That's good.

511
00:29:06,386 --> 00:29:08,887
Finally find God?

512
00:29:08,889 --> 00:29:11,089
Not your God.

513
00:29:11,091 --> 00:29:13,191
There is only one God.

514
00:29:14,146 --> 00:29:16,279
We're gonna take the city, you know.

515
00:29:18,498 --> 00:29:20,965
You be nice...

516
00:29:20,967 --> 00:29:24,335
maybe I'll make a good woman of you.

517
00:29:24,337 --> 00:29:26,471
Forgive the devil in you.

518
00:29:26,473 --> 00:29:30,775
Why don't I just turn around now?

519
00:29:30,777 --> 00:29:32,810
We forgive each other.

520
00:29:32,812 --> 00:29:35,546
Forget each other ever existed.

521
00:29:35,548 --> 00:29:38,950
Beauty is not so easily forgotten.

522
00:29:38,952 --> 00:29:40,752
Lover boy!

523
00:29:40,754 --> 00:29:42,186
We have to go.

524
00:29:42,188 --> 00:29:43,955
Government's moving in at Aksa Park.

525
00:29:46,426 --> 00:29:48,259
Cut her loose.

526
00:29:51,480 --> 00:29:53,513
Get the hell off our territory.

527
00:30:04,577 --> 00:30:06,711
They are gone.

528
00:30:09,783 --> 00:30:11,720
We have to hurry.

529
00:30:11,723 --> 00:30:14,619
We're lucky he didn't
kill me right then.

530
00:30:14,621 --> 00:30:16,087
Why?

531
00:30:17,390 --> 00:30:20,058
Maybe I'll tell you one day.

532
00:30:24,331 --> 00:30:26,331
They're destroying our city.

533
00:30:26,333 --> 00:30:30,635
Your ISIL friends are
destroying our city.

534
00:30:30,637 --> 00:30:32,157
And you come in here

535
00:30:32,160 --> 00:30:34,272
wanting help.

536
00:30:34,274 --> 00:30:36,629
Just give me a little something.

537
00:30:36,632 --> 00:30:38,943
Is there a doctor here?

538
00:30:38,945 --> 00:30:40,611
I'm burning up.

539
00:30:40,613 --> 00:30:42,714
You should have thought about that

540
00:30:42,716 --> 00:30:45,807
when you supplied guns to them,

541
00:30:45,810 --> 00:30:47,585
assassinated good men.

542
00:30:47,587 --> 00:30:49,520
Those charges were a misunderstanding.

543
00:30:49,522 --> 00:30:51,923
Oh, Allah. Kaniel Outis says

544
00:30:51,925 --> 00:30:54,092
it was a misunderstanding.

545
00:30:54,094 --> 00:30:56,147
Was it also a misunderstanding

546
00:30:56,150 --> 00:30:58,062
when you tried to escape the moment

547
00:30:58,064 --> 00:31:00,465
you got into this prison? Hmm?

548
00:31:03,372 --> 00:31:06,537
An honest man doesn't try to escape.

549
00:31:06,539 --> 00:31:09,707
He asks for a lawyer. But you,

550
00:31:09,709 --> 00:31:12,226
you tried to escape the very first week.

551
00:31:17,982 --> 00:31:21,419
I'd have left you in solitary
forever if it was up to me.

552
00:32:16,752 --> 00:32:19,335
The address at the end of the block.

553
00:32:20,413 --> 00:32:21,612
Rebels...

554
00:32:21,614 --> 00:32:23,081
right in front of the house.

555
00:32:23,083 --> 00:32:24,582
Son of a bitch.

556
00:32:24,584 --> 00:32:26,417
Anything easy in this country?

557
00:32:26,419 --> 00:32:28,786
The question is: is
the sheik even inside?

558
00:32:28,789 --> 00:32:30,976
Only one way to find out.

559
00:32:37,230 --> 00:32:38,863
They find us up here,

560
00:32:38,865 --> 00:32:40,865
there's no explaining ourselves.

561
00:32:40,867 --> 00:32:42,900
We're all dead.

562
00:33:02,789 --> 00:33:04,822
Shh, shh, shh.

563
00:33:04,824 --> 00:33:06,591
Quiet.

564
00:33:06,593 --> 00:33:08,459
You... You are not ISIL?

565
00:33:08,461 --> 00:33:11,929
No. But you're Mohammad
El-Tunis, I take it?

566
00:33:13,740 --> 00:33:15,899
_

567
00:33:15,902 --> 00:33:18,903
We are from the city center.
We are here to get you out.

568
00:33:18,905 --> 00:33:20,304
Not without my daughter.

569
00:33:20,306 --> 00:33:22,540
We can bring her. Where is she?

570
00:33:22,542 --> 00:33:24,342
- She's out there.
- Where?

571
00:33:25,812 --> 00:33:27,912
In the basement of the
schoolyard, across the street.

572
00:33:29,314 --> 00:33:31,233
Pinned since ISIL arrived.

573
00:33:31,236 --> 00:33:32,998
I came to get her out.

574
00:33:33,001 --> 00:33:35,170
And I got pinned, too.

575
00:33:35,173 --> 00:33:37,655
I hate to say it, Linc,
but I think we might've

576
00:33:37,657 --> 00:33:39,157
just got pinned as well.

577
00:34:10,301 --> 00:34:12,034
You okay?

578
00:34:19,444 --> 00:34:21,844
You look like you could
use a few sharp edges

579
00:34:21,846 --> 00:34:24,046
knocked off your world.

580
00:34:24,048 --> 00:34:27,116
You don't look so good yourself.

581
00:34:32,490 --> 00:34:35,124
Say what you want about Yemen,

582
00:34:35,126 --> 00:34:37,317
they're not shy about prescriptions.

583
00:34:37,320 --> 00:34:39,687
It's the good stuff.
Morphine derivative.

584
00:34:42,667 --> 00:34:46,268
I need access to your cell
phone and a credit card number.

585
00:34:46,270 --> 00:34:48,571
Why?

586
00:34:48,573 --> 00:34:52,675
I want to order a pizza.

587
00:34:58,383 --> 00:34:59,882
There's a back door,

588
00:34:59,884 --> 00:35:01,681
toward the schoolhouse. Come on.

589
00:35:06,424 --> 00:35:07,857
Too late.

590
00:35:07,859 --> 00:35:09,725
Go to the rooftops.

591
00:35:09,727 --> 00:35:11,026
They're all over the Rover.

592
00:35:11,028 --> 00:35:12,952
- We'll never get to it.
- I can get in that pickup,

593
00:35:12,954 --> 00:35:14,230
make a ruckus on my way out.

594
00:35:14,232 --> 00:35:16,007
Any luck, they'll be all over me.

595
00:35:16,010 --> 00:35:17,533
Then you got a clean shot to the Rover.

596
00:35:19,624 --> 00:35:20,819
Go. Go!

597
00:35:20,822 --> 00:35:21,660
I'm not leaving

598
00:35:21,663 --> 00:35:22,729
without my daughter.

599
00:35:22,732 --> 00:35:24,457
You don't know what ISIL will do to her

600
00:35:24,460 --> 00:35:26,041
for educating those girls.

601
00:35:26,043 --> 00:35:28,043
I'll get her out, I promise.

602
00:35:30,588 --> 00:35:33,489
- Go!
- Okay! Okay.

603
00:35:49,381 --> 00:35:51,311
Your father sent me. I'm
getting you out of here.

604
00:35:51,314 --> 00:35:53,169
Come on! Come on!

605
00:36:08,219 --> 00:36:10,386
Get down! Stay down!

606
00:36:23,355 --> 00:36:24,762
He's got to make it.

607
00:36:24,765 --> 00:36:26,464
You know you got to make it. Come on.

608
00:36:28,043 --> 00:36:30,234
There he is! There he is!

609
00:36:32,004 --> 00:36:33,309
Yeah, baby!

610
00:36:39,923 --> 00:36:41,617
Oh, no. This isn't good.

611
00:36:42,820 --> 00:36:44,286
This isn't good.

612
00:37:00,471 --> 00:37:02,371
This government checkpoint.

613
00:37:02,373 --> 00:37:04,507
They'll think we're suicide
bombers. We have to stop.

614
00:37:04,509 --> 00:37:06,008
Are you out of your mind?

615
00:37:07,277 --> 00:37:08,983
Don't shoot at us!

616
00:37:08,986 --> 00:37:10,880
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!

617
00:37:15,418 --> 00:37:16,984
Stay down!

618
00:37:57,962 --> 00:38:00,129
I'm so happy, too.

619
00:38:15,880 --> 00:38:18,113
Forgive me, uh...

620
00:38:18,115 --> 00:38:20,583
Their parents have been killed.

621
00:38:20,585 --> 00:38:22,649
I'm trying to figure
out how I can help them.

622
00:38:22,652 --> 00:38:24,620
They can stay here for now.

623
00:38:24,622 --> 00:38:27,130
As long as you tell me
who you know in Ogygia,

624
00:38:27,133 --> 00:38:28,857
and why they want you so bad.

625
00:38:28,859 --> 00:38:31,727
I'm a man with, uh...

626
00:38:31,729 --> 00:38:34,129
troublesome children.

627
00:38:35,466 --> 00:38:38,734
They're beautiful.

628
00:38:38,736 --> 00:38:41,755
But perhaps too modern for this country.

629
00:38:41,758 --> 00:38:45,516
My daughter tries to educate girls.

630
00:38:45,519 --> 00:38:47,343
And my son,

631
00:38:47,345 --> 00:38:49,912
he falls in love with another man.

632
00:38:49,914 --> 00:38:53,849
They gave him 20 years in Ogygia Prison.

633
00:38:54,739 --> 00:38:56,985
I went to visit him a few weeks ago.

634
00:38:56,988 --> 00:38:59,888
He said, maybe there is a way out.

635
00:38:59,890 --> 00:39:02,124
A way I could help.

636
00:39:02,126 --> 00:39:03,626
A man is not a man

637
00:39:03,628 --> 00:39:05,508
if he would let his family die.

638
00:39:07,698 --> 00:39:09,365
You agreed to help him.

639
00:39:09,367 --> 00:39:10,666
How?

640
00:39:10,668 --> 00:39:13,102
He said if I could arrange a blackout,

641
00:39:13,104 --> 00:39:15,804
he... he knew someone
who could get him out.

642
00:39:15,806 --> 00:39:16,939
An American?

643
00:39:16,941 --> 00:39:18,641
I don't know.

644
00:39:18,643 --> 00:39:21,043
I-I was supposed to do this a week ago,

645
00:39:21,045 --> 00:39:24,647
but then this happened with my daughter.

646
00:39:24,649 --> 00:39:25,981
Thank God you found us.

647
00:39:25,983 --> 00:39:28,384
There's still time to do it.

648
00:39:28,386 --> 00:39:30,452
They're waiting for you in there.

649
00:39:30,454 --> 00:39:31,820
Then I have to go now.

650
00:39:31,822 --> 00:39:33,922
He said I was to give a signal

651
00:39:33,924 --> 00:39:36,291
exactly 24 hours before the blackout.

652
00:39:36,293 --> 00:39:38,460
I will pulse the power grid twice.

653
00:39:38,462 --> 00:39:41,043
This city may not have 24 hours in it.

654
00:39:52,410 --> 00:39:53,475
Bye, guys.

655
00:39:53,477 --> 00:39:54,515
Bye.

656
00:39:57,948 --> 00:39:59,915
God knows I'm no perfect
judge of character,

657
00:39:59,917 --> 00:40:02,885
but Michael?

658
00:40:02,887 --> 00:40:05,521
If any of what they're saying is true...

659
00:40:05,523 --> 00:40:07,656
So there's more to find out, Sara.

660
00:40:07,658 --> 00:40:11,226
I mean, the important thing is
that you are gonna survive this,

661
00:40:11,228 --> 00:40:13,204
however it turns out.

662
00:40:13,207 --> 00:40:14,204
Mm-hmm.

663
00:40:14,207 --> 00:40:17,433
And we're here for you. Okay?

664
00:40:17,435 --> 00:40:18,834
- Let's go.
- Thank you.

665
00:40:18,836 --> 00:40:19,835
Call me, okay?

666
00:40:19,837 --> 00:40:21,437
Yeah.

667
00:40:23,910 --> 00:40:25,843
Hey, can I just scoop Mike real quick?

668
00:40:25,846 --> 00:40:28,277
All the kids have been released.

669
00:40:28,279 --> 00:40:30,879
You don't have him?

670
00:40:30,881 --> 00:40:32,181
Mike?

671
00:40:33,451 --> 00:40:34,983
- I'll go this way.
- Okay, yeah.

672
00:40:36,120 --> 00:40:37,820
Mike?

673
00:40:37,822 --> 00:40:41,390
Hey, hey, have you seen Mike?

674
00:40:41,392 --> 00:40:42,691
Mike!

675
00:40:44,361 --> 00:40:46,428
Mike!

676
00:40:46,430 --> 00:40:48,997
Mike!

677
00:40:48,999 --> 00:40:51,900
There...

678
00:40:51,902 --> 00:40:53,569
What are you doing? You scared me.

679
00:40:53,571 --> 00:40:55,066
I was looking for where the man went.

680
00:40:55,069 --> 00:40:56,202
What man, baby?

681
00:40:56,205 --> 00:40:57,940
The man that gave me this.

682
00:40:57,942 --> 00:41:00,576
The pizza man.

683
00:41:00,578 --> 00:41:02,478
The pizza man?

684
00:41:08,243 --> 00:41:11,219
_

685
00:41:11,222 --> 00:41:13,122
Michael.

686
00:41:13,124 --> 00:41:14,929
What are you into?

687
00:41:21,265 --> 00:41:24,199
ISIL is getting closer by the hour.

688
00:41:24,201 --> 00:41:26,602
And the rebels in here know it.

689
00:41:26,604 --> 00:41:28,871
When they take over,
they'll kill all of us.

690
00:41:30,141 --> 00:41:34,176
Infidels, the sinners, the foreigners.

691
00:41:44,728 --> 00:41:45,998
Praise Allah.

692
00:41:46,001 --> 00:41:48,201
Someone found my father.

693
00:41:48,204 --> 00:41:49,964
Means the escape is on.

694
00:41:53,635 --> 00:41:55,235
24 hours from now.

695
00:41:56,874 --> 00:41:58,700
But this may be too late.

696
00:41:58,702 --> 00:42:01,537
Ramadan has begun.

697
00:42:01,539 --> 00:42:03,772
The guards are releasing the prisoners.

698
00:42:05,903 --> 00:42:07,676
Abu Ramal and his men,

699
00:42:07,678 --> 00:42:09,444
they'll kill me.

700
00:42:09,446 --> 00:42:10,817
And you.

701
00:42:47,765 --> 00:42:50,054
_

702
00:42:50,057 --> 00:42:52,086
_

703
00:42:53,500 --> 00:42:56,750
_

704
00:43:00,710 --> 00:43:02,312
_

