1
00:00:02,242 --> 00:00:05,406
- Previously on Prison Break...
- We're gonna get you out of here.

2
00:00:05,445 --> 00:00:07,882
- The escape is on.
- Go, go, go!

3
00:00:07,929 --> 00:00:09,398
Who the hell is the guy?

4
00:00:09,437 --> 00:00:10,984
He's my brother.

5
00:00:11,022 --> 00:00:12,966
Can't die on me now, Michael,
you know, you're gonna tell me

6
00:00:12,968 --> 00:00:15,088
- why I'm your whip hand.
- We found Michael.

7
00:00:15,090 --> 00:00:16,815
- He's been busted up real bad.
- I got to go.

8
00:00:16,817 --> 00:00:18,350
You don't know what
you'd be walking into.

9
00:00:18,352 --> 00:00:19,418
It's not safe.

10
00:00:19,447 --> 00:00:21,273
I can't look my son in the eye

11
00:00:21,314 --> 00:00:23,162
and tell him that I let his father die,

12
00:00:23,198 --> 00:00:25,231
a father he's never met.

13
00:00:25,266 --> 00:00:27,333
Never thought I'd see this face again.

14
00:00:27,369 --> 00:00:30,280
You weren't supposed to.

15
00:00:31,740 --> 00:00:33,172
Lincoln Burrows.

16
00:00:33,208 --> 00:00:35,241
How about you step out

17
00:00:35,268 --> 00:00:36,973
and pay us the 100 grand you owe us.

18
00:00:37,020 --> 00:00:39,918
- There is nobility in you, Lincoln.
- You should rest up.

19
00:00:39,957 --> 00:00:42,382
- We're gonna need you.
- Didn't know you worried.

20
00:00:42,417 --> 00:00:43,716
About the right things.

21
00:00:43,752 --> 00:00:45,351
What's wrong?

22
00:00:45,382 --> 00:00:47,253
It's him. Your husband.

23
00:00:48,223 --> 00:00:49,452
Jacob

24
00:00:49,491 --> 00:00:51,824
is Poseidon.

25
00:00:51,860 --> 00:00:53,226
He's a CIA operative,

26
00:00:53,229 --> 00:00:55,496
deep cover. He runs a splinter cell

27
00:00:55,528 --> 00:00:56,396
called 21-Void.

28
00:00:56,431 --> 00:00:58,731
He targeted me for my skills.

29
00:00:58,767 --> 00:01:01,134
Michael, he's with our son right now.

30
00:01:01,169 --> 00:01:02,793
I'll get to the States as soon as I can.

31
00:01:02,796 --> 00:01:04,509
Did my husband, Jacob Ness,

32
00:01:04,512 --> 00:01:05,972
ask you to work on my cell phone?

33
00:01:06,007 --> 00:01:06,806
He said he was looking to find

34
00:01:06,808 --> 00:01:08,040
the people who were stalking

35
00:01:08,076 --> 00:01:11,310
his wife, so I did a data dive.

36
00:01:11,346 --> 00:01:12,979
Where's my son?

37
00:01:13,022 --> 00:01:14,146
I have him.

38
00:01:14,185 --> 00:01:15,851
And whether or not I
have to threaten him

39
00:01:15,880 --> 00:01:19,294
is entirely contingent upon
you putting the gun down.

40
00:01:24,125 --> 00:01:25,324
Kaniel Outis

41
00:01:25,360 --> 00:01:27,393
has been located on a cargo ship

42
00:01:27,429 --> 00:01:28,861
in the Mediterranean.

43
00:01:28,897 --> 00:01:29,962
They made you.

44
00:01:29,998 --> 00:01:31,230
Run!

45
00:01:41,523 --> 00:01:43,942
_

46
00:01:43,945 --> 00:01:46,546
Hey!

47
00:01:49,268 --> 00:01:50,667
Hey!

48
00:01:53,087 --> 00:01:55,655
Hey!

49
00:02:04,466 --> 00:02:06,432
Hey, yo,

50
00:02:06,468 --> 00:02:08,267
where we headed?

51
00:02:08,303 --> 00:02:09,569
Marseille.

52
00:02:09,604 --> 00:02:13,506
- Marseilles.
- Marseilles.

53
00:02:19,294 --> 00:02:21,280
I own you, Scofield.

54
00:02:21,316 --> 00:02:23,449
I know everything about you.

55
00:02:23,485 --> 00:02:26,886
Even your most mundane
actions, like the zoo.

56
00:02:26,921 --> 00:02:28,792
What's with you and the zoo?

57
00:02:28,824 --> 00:02:30,090
I go there to think.

58
00:02:30,128 --> 00:02:32,391
18 times in the past month?

59
00:02:32,427 --> 00:02:34,594
- A lot of thinking.
- I was figuring out how to get

60
00:02:34,629 --> 00:02:36,562
- your guy out of Barranquilla.
- Hmm.

61
00:02:36,598 --> 00:02:38,498
Turns out he's not
just a rebel leader...

62
00:02:38,533 --> 00:02:40,366
He's a murderous sociopath.

63
00:02:40,392 --> 00:02:42,085
That's the only way to make omelets.

64
00:02:42,096 --> 00:02:44,063
I need to know more about our targets.

65
00:02:44,105 --> 00:02:47,106
If I'm facilitating escapes,
we can't have surprises.

66
00:02:47,141 --> 00:02:49,509
Be proud. You and me,

67
00:02:49,544 --> 00:02:52,478
- we're changing the world.
- Doesn't make it right.

68
00:02:52,514 --> 00:02:55,915
Don't act like you're suddenly
a fan of the status quo, okay?

69
00:02:55,950 --> 00:02:59,585
The system, it's slow,
stupid, and doomed to fail.

70
00:02:59,621 --> 00:03:02,855
That's why you had to bust your
brother out in the first place.

71
00:03:02,891 --> 00:03:05,791
New ink since the last time I saw you.

72
00:03:05,827 --> 00:03:08,874
- Working on a new plan?
- No. No new plan.

73
00:03:08,877 --> 00:03:11,244
Just get tired of looking at empty skin.

74
00:03:11,294 --> 00:03:12,493
Uh-huh.

75
00:03:12,552 --> 00:03:14,901
You know, it was those tats at Fox River

76
00:03:14,936 --> 00:03:16,807
that caught my eye in the first place.

77
00:03:16,810 --> 00:03:18,371
I had to know everything about the man

78
00:03:18,406 --> 00:03:20,518
who wore his plans on his skin.

79
00:03:20,521 --> 00:03:25,257
In plain sight yet so mysterious.

80
00:03:25,292 --> 00:03:28,127
The key to real power is to disappear.

81
00:03:28,162 --> 00:03:30,729
- Hi, Professor Ness.
- Hello, Claudia.

82
00:03:30,765 --> 00:03:33,132
Yeah, the secret to real power

83
00:03:33,167 --> 00:03:35,501
is to never betray your intentions,

84
00:03:35,536 --> 00:03:38,670
to wear nothing on your sleeve.

85
00:03:38,706 --> 00:03:40,605
And to never let anyone

86
00:03:40,628 --> 00:03:42,841
see your face.

87
00:04:02,897 --> 00:04:05,497
Come on in.

88
00:04:10,638 --> 00:04:13,238
Next time I'm sitting in solitary,

89
00:04:13,274 --> 00:04:15,374
I'll think of you in
here, running the world

90
00:04:15,409 --> 00:04:17,142
in air-conditioned comfort.

91
00:04:17,178 --> 00:04:19,326
I've spent my time in the field.

92
00:04:19,365 --> 00:04:21,580
You all set for Myanmar?

93
00:04:21,615 --> 00:04:23,048
It's only a few weeks off.

94
00:04:23,083 --> 00:04:24,249
That's why I'm here.

95
00:04:24,285 --> 00:04:26,018
I want to bring someone on board.

96
00:04:26,053 --> 00:04:27,363
- Oh, really?
- The prison camp

97
00:04:27,366 --> 00:04:28,722
at Sittwe is a two-man job.

98
00:04:28,756 --> 00:04:31,023
I've been watching this
guy. He'll be useful.

99
00:04:31,058 --> 00:04:32,658
Watching him? You in charge

100
00:04:32,693 --> 00:04:34,893
- of recruiting now?
- Trust me.

101
00:04:34,929 --> 00:04:37,296
The last thing I want to do is
suck someone else into this.

102
00:04:37,331 --> 00:04:40,032
He'll have my back and
he'll speed things up,

103
00:04:40,067 --> 00:04:43,068
increase our odds.

104
00:04:45,439 --> 00:04:48,233
Not exactly a distinguished career.

105
00:04:48,272 --> 00:04:50,816
He's held up well in prison.
He's got a mean streak.

106
00:04:50,845 --> 00:04:52,826
And he grew up without a family.

107
00:04:52,850 --> 00:04:54,320
It means he can be manipulated.

108
00:04:54,348 --> 00:04:56,315
If you're planning something,

109
00:04:56,350 --> 00:04:59,117
I'll always be a step ahead of you.

110
00:04:59,153 --> 00:05:01,420
You know that.

111
00:05:01,455 --> 00:05:03,488
I can see everything in your eyes.

112
00:05:03,524 --> 00:05:06,391
It's what's behind the eyes that counts,

113
00:05:06,427 --> 00:05:07,659
Professor.

114
00:05:07,695 --> 00:05:08,927
Hmm.

115
00:05:08,963 --> 00:05:10,229
So you're gonna wait a year

116
00:05:10,264 --> 00:05:12,231
for me to find my way out of Sittwe?

117
00:05:12,266 --> 00:05:13,899
Or are you gonna get me a partner,

118
00:05:13,934 --> 00:05:16,014
so we get on with the
business of changing the world?

119
00:05:26,501 --> 00:05:27,868
Done.

120
00:05:35,625 --> 00:05:40,296
_

121
00:05:40,794 --> 00:05:42,527
I need some food.

122
00:05:42,563 --> 00:05:43,996
I'm with you.

123
00:05:44,031 --> 00:05:47,466
Linc, it's Sara.

124
00:05:47,501 --> 00:05:50,168
She's back in New York.

125
00:05:51,686 --> 00:05:53,438
Are she and Mike okay?

126
00:05:53,474 --> 00:05:55,116
That's what I'm trying to find out.

127
00:06:02,870 --> 00:06:05,904
_

128
00:06:07,558 --> 00:06:10,199
_

129
00:06:12,826 --> 00:06:14,693
What is it, Michael?

130
00:06:14,728 --> 00:06:16,828
Something's wrong.

131
00:06:25,539 --> 00:06:28,640
Yes, you will.

132
00:07:11,627 --> 00:07:14,682
- I got to get back to the States.
- Slow down.

133
00:07:14,711 --> 00:07:16,177
You're Kaniel Outis, remember?

134
00:07:16,212 --> 00:07:17,912
You're on every no-fly
list in the world.

135
00:07:17,947 --> 00:07:19,914
Jacob's done something
to Sara. Maybe Mike, too.

136
00:07:19,949 --> 00:07:21,582
- How do you know?
- That text.

137
00:07:21,617 --> 00:07:23,584
She referred to our son as Junior.

138
00:07:23,619 --> 00:07:25,353
We agreed we'd never call him that.

139
00:07:25,388 --> 00:07:27,421
He's baiting you, Michael.

140
00:07:27,457 --> 00:07:29,757
It worked.

141
00:07:32,411 --> 00:07:34,077
_

142
00:07:38,735 --> 00:07:40,935
Hey, buddy.

143
00:07:40,970 --> 00:07:42,370
Where's Mom?

144
00:07:42,405 --> 00:07:44,438
Oh. I, uh, dropped her off at work

145
00:07:44,474 --> 00:07:46,474
while you were at school.

146
00:07:46,509 --> 00:07:49,143
That is quite a pirate ship.

147
00:07:49,178 --> 00:07:52,446
Although it would be a little hard

148
00:07:52,482 --> 00:07:54,448
to sail with the mast that far forward.

149
00:07:54,484 --> 00:07:56,751
- Your ship might tip over.
- The mast has

150
00:07:56,786 --> 00:07:58,619
to be there. It's not just a ship...

151
00:07:58,654 --> 00:07:59,754
It's a treasure map.

152
00:07:59,789 --> 00:08:01,981
What do you mean?

153
00:08:02,005 --> 00:08:04,392
It's for Jimmy. We hide
Legos for each other.

154
00:08:04,427 --> 00:08:06,060
I always find his.

155
00:08:06,095 --> 00:08:08,129
He doesn't always find mine.

156
00:08:09,278 --> 00:08:11,198
Wait a second,

157
00:08:11,234 --> 00:08:14,835
how is this drawing a map?

158
00:08:17,206 --> 00:08:19,940
This is the park.

159
00:08:19,976 --> 00:08:22,443
That's the playground.

160
00:08:22,478 --> 00:08:24,945
And this is the sidewalk.

161
00:08:26,033 --> 00:08:27,882
Impressive.

162
00:08:27,917 --> 00:08:30,451
You put a code in the drawing.

163
00:08:30,486 --> 00:08:33,421
So, okay, where did you hide the Legos?

164
00:08:33,456 --> 00:08:36,123
These cannons are pools at the park.

165
00:08:36,159 --> 00:08:38,859
But there's an extra one, in the sand.

166
00:08:38,895 --> 00:08:41,997
That's where I buried the Legos.

167
00:08:42,045 --> 00:08:45,301
Well done, Mike.

168
00:08:45,334 --> 00:08:47,357
Well done.

169
00:08:50,927 --> 00:08:53,474
I've tried everyone. I'm out
of resources in the States.

170
00:08:53,476 --> 00:08:55,743
All my contacts. People who
can go and check on them,

171
00:08:55,778 --> 00:08:57,144
make sure they're okay.

172
00:08:57,180 --> 00:08:58,746
Linc, I got to get home.

173
00:08:58,781 --> 00:09:01,148
I can't spend another
two weeks on a cargo ship.

174
00:09:01,184 --> 00:09:02,616
He's got my wife and kid.

175
00:09:02,652 --> 00:09:04,185
There may be another way.

176
00:09:04,220 --> 00:09:07,121
You told me about the last
seven years of your life.

177
00:09:08,825 --> 00:09:10,858
Haven't told you about mine.

178
00:09:13,029 --> 00:09:15,863
After Sara got exonerated,
she left Panama.

179
00:09:15,898 --> 00:09:18,899
Me and Sofia stayed behind
and opened a dive shop.

180
00:09:18,935 --> 00:09:21,969
We broke up, and
everything went to hell.

181
00:09:22,004 --> 00:09:24,438
You weren't there to stop
me, so before I knew it,

182
00:09:24,474 --> 00:09:26,440
I was in the old hood, doing odd jobs.

183
00:09:26,476 --> 00:09:27,808
Odd jobs meaning what?

184
00:09:27,844 --> 00:09:31,479
Moving things from point A to point B.

185
00:09:31,514 --> 00:09:34,081
For Luca Abruzzi.

186
00:09:34,116 --> 00:09:35,649
John Abruzzi's son.

187
00:09:35,685 --> 00:09:37,218
Yeah.

188
00:09:37,253 --> 00:09:40,855
I just wanted some quick
cash to kick-start my life.

189
00:09:40,890 --> 00:09:43,524
They told me not to look in the boxes.

190
00:09:44,427 --> 00:09:46,527
But I looked in the boxes.

191
00:09:46,562 --> 00:09:49,330
The amount of fentanyl they're
smuggling out of Europe...

192
00:09:49,365 --> 00:09:51,699
Tens of thousands of
pills in every box...

193
00:09:51,730 --> 00:09:53,567
It's just killing people.

194
00:09:53,603 --> 00:09:55,269
So I dumped a box in a Dumpster,

195
00:09:55,304 --> 00:09:56,704
100 grand's worth.

196
00:09:56,739 --> 00:09:58,839
Now you're in hock to Abruzzi's son.

197
00:09:58,875 --> 00:10:01,108
Yeah. He wants to kill me.

198
00:10:02,845 --> 00:10:05,713
But maybe it's a way to get
back to the States real fast.

199
00:10:08,523 --> 00:10:09,982
_

200
00:10:09,985 --> 00:10:11,852
You got balls, Burrows.

201
00:10:11,888 --> 00:10:14,146
You actually think I want to help you?

202
00:10:14,185 --> 00:10:15,856
What if I can get you the $100K?

203
00:10:15,858 --> 00:10:17,691
$100K?

204
00:10:17,727 --> 00:10:19,660
How are you gonna come up with that

205
00:10:19,695 --> 00:10:21,629
crawling around the
back alleys of Chicago?

206
00:10:21,664 --> 00:10:23,464
I'm not in Chicago. I'm in Marseilles.

207
00:10:23,499 --> 00:10:25,866
- Marseilles?
- Yeah.

208
00:10:25,902 --> 00:10:28,335
I've been working on a
couple deals. I got $100K

209
00:10:28,371 --> 00:10:31,222
in my hand. But I want off the hook.

210
00:10:31,261 --> 00:10:33,974
Sure you do. How about you get
over here and hand it to me?

211
00:10:34,010 --> 00:10:35,676
That's why I'm calling.

212
00:10:35,711 --> 00:10:38,379
I need to sneak into the States
invisible, like your pills.

213
00:10:38,414 --> 00:10:40,814
Those flights you got
coming out of Europe...

214
00:10:40,850 --> 00:10:44,418
The fentanyl flights...
I need a few seats.

215
00:10:48,491 --> 00:10:50,925
I'll tell you what.

216
00:10:50,960 --> 00:10:52,626
I'll make a few calls.

217
00:10:52,662 --> 00:10:53,928
'Cause either I'm gonna see you

218
00:10:53,963 --> 00:10:55,896
and get that money,
or I'm gonna see you,

219
00:10:55,932 --> 00:10:58,098
and you're gonna get
something a whole lot worse.

220
00:11:00,202 --> 00:11:02,169
I can't believe I'm doing
this to myself again.

221
00:11:02,204 --> 00:11:06,240
Difference is this
time, you're not alone.

222
00:11:13,950 --> 00:11:16,250
God, these things are disgusting.

223
00:11:16,285 --> 00:11:18,819
What they call 'em again?

224
00:11:18,854 --> 00:11:21,188
Boudin noir.

225
00:11:21,223 --> 00:11:23,257
Not sure what's in them.

226
00:11:23,292 --> 00:11:26,193
I don't think your French is
as good as you think it is.

227
00:11:26,235 --> 00:11:29,704
Yo, be happy you're not eating snails.

228
00:11:32,335 --> 00:11:33,801
Hey.

229
00:11:40,588 --> 00:11:42,509
Do you think they noticed?

230
00:11:42,545 --> 00:11:45,112
Let's not take any chances.

231
00:11:51,020 --> 00:11:53,153
Guys.

232
00:11:53,203 --> 00:11:54,562
Your faces were on the news.

233
00:11:54,592 --> 00:11:56,391
Somebody sees you, this thing is over.

234
00:11:56,421 --> 00:11:58,325
- We got to move, papi.
- We got to go.

235
00:12:00,465 --> 00:12:01,998
Hold. Luca.

236
00:12:02,036 --> 00:12:03,831
If you can get to Lyon by midnight,

237
00:12:03,866 --> 00:12:05,699
I can get you on a flight.

238
00:12:05,735 --> 00:12:08,025
I got a warehouse in New
York. You're coming to me?

239
00:12:08,028 --> 00:12:09,069
We'll be there.

240
00:12:09,105 --> 00:12:10,671
Can't decide whether I want you

241
00:12:10,706 --> 00:12:12,606
to have that money or not, Burrows.

242
00:12:12,642 --> 00:12:16,577
Killing you might be
a lot more satisfying.

243
00:12:16,612 --> 00:12:19,546
Now we know they survived the
strike in the Mediterranean.

244
00:12:19,582 --> 00:12:22,049
We can be pretty sure
he's coming back to Ithaca.

245
00:12:24,253 --> 00:12:26,520
I need some clarification.

246
00:12:27,757 --> 00:12:30,057
Why would he come back here...

247
00:12:30,092 --> 00:12:31,892
to the States

248
00:12:31,927 --> 00:12:33,761
when he's more wanted here

249
00:12:33,796 --> 00:12:35,763
than anywhere else in the world?

250
00:12:37,366 --> 00:12:39,233
Of course.

251
00:12:42,405 --> 00:12:44,938
Because of them.

252
00:12:46,342 --> 00:12:48,481
He had a life before he worked for me,

253
00:12:48,520 --> 00:12:51,278
a name... Michael Scofield.

254
00:12:51,313 --> 00:12:53,180
A family.

255
00:12:54,158 --> 00:12:57,072
And when he went away, I
ended up looking after them.

256
00:12:57,119 --> 00:12:59,987
Ended up... falling for them.

257
00:13:00,022 --> 00:13:01,855
Well...

258
00:13:02,925 --> 00:13:04,725
He wants to kill me.

259
00:13:04,760 --> 00:13:07,671
He thinks I stole his life,
ruined him, which speaks

260
00:13:07,697 --> 00:13:09,496
to his dissociative mind.

261
00:13:09,523 --> 00:13:12,249
I mean, he's a murderer,
a turncoat, a terrorist.

262
00:13:13,595 --> 00:13:15,696
But we'll use it.

263
00:13:15,731 --> 00:13:17,731
I'll be the bait if I have to.

264
00:13:17,766 --> 00:13:21,335
So we can go about taking
him down once and for all.

265
00:13:21,370 --> 00:13:23,103
He's not just gonna stroll in here.

266
00:13:23,138 --> 00:13:26,273
He's too clever for that.

267
00:13:26,308 --> 00:13:29,343
That's why we got
someone even more clever.

268
00:13:30,779 --> 00:13:32,112
Thoreau?

269
00:13:32,147 --> 00:13:33,780
Guy's a pencil neck.

270
00:13:33,816 --> 00:13:36,116
A pencil neck with insight
into Scofield's plan.

271
00:13:36,151 --> 00:13:38,719
So you, in turn, can be the hammer.

272
00:13:43,151 --> 00:13:45,092
Screen-grab of the Skype transmission

273
00:13:45,094 --> 00:13:46,460
he sent from the desert.

274
00:13:46,495 --> 00:13:47,928
He routed the image through a server

275
00:13:47,930 --> 00:13:50,197
to this BlueHawaii guy,
but it could have been

276
00:13:50,232 --> 00:13:51,898
secretly subrouted to another, yet

277
00:13:51,934 --> 00:13:55,305
unknown, recipient to use
the information encoded in it.

278
00:13:55,308 --> 00:13:56,703
Information?

279
00:13:56,739 --> 00:13:59,539
It's actually incredible.

280
00:13:59,575 --> 00:14:03,176
Encrypted in the Arabic, the
images are all sorts of stuff.

281
00:14:03,212 --> 00:14:05,245
Apparently, mundane as hell.

282
00:14:05,280 --> 00:14:07,981
Visiting hours for zoos,
links to defunct message boards

283
00:14:07,983 --> 00:14:09,049
on the Internet.

284
00:14:09,084 --> 00:14:10,584
What message boards?

285
00:14:10,619 --> 00:14:14,421
Truesnuff.com, Hunterspycamporn.com,

286
00:14:14,456 --> 00:14:16,890
both of which carry... this.

287
00:14:16,925 --> 00:14:20,293
Images of the Harlan Gaines murder.

288
00:14:20,329 --> 00:14:23,104
What's the bastard doing
rubbing that in our faces?

289
00:14:23,151 --> 00:14:25,966
Of all the things to encrypt, why that?

290
00:14:26,001 --> 00:14:27,534
What's that get you?

291
00:14:27,569 --> 00:14:29,169
Steganographically, a lot.

292
00:14:29,204 --> 00:14:31,849
Steganography is the practice
of concealing information

293
00:14:31,852 --> 00:14:34,174
in the code that makes up digital files.

294
00:14:34,209 --> 00:14:36,610
Russians do it, Chinese, everybody.

295
00:14:36,645 --> 00:14:38,445
He's probably thinking
if anyone sees this,

296
00:14:38,480 --> 00:14:40,313
this'll be as far as they'll look.

297
00:14:40,349 --> 00:14:43,250
But I'm already going inside
the image, breaking down the data

298
00:14:43,285 --> 00:14:45,685
- that comprises it.
- This is making my head spin.

299
00:14:45,721 --> 00:14:48,188
Point is we put big data, AI on this,

300
00:14:48,223 --> 00:14:51,057
we can crunch any codes
hidden in there pretty quickly.

301
00:14:51,093 --> 00:14:52,139
And that's what I'm doing.

302
00:14:52,142 --> 00:14:55,529
Nice work, but the truth
is if I've done my job,

303
00:14:55,564 --> 00:14:59,366
he may reveal his
intentions to us first.

304
00:15:17,352 --> 00:15:20,454
Because I've got him
so far off his game now,

305
00:15:20,489 --> 00:15:23,523
he'll start to play
his cards too early...

306
00:15:25,627 --> 00:15:28,829
Teddy.

307
00:15:30,365 --> 00:15:32,699
"But in return, you must take a life."

308
00:15:32,734 --> 00:15:35,387
Show us what the tattoos mean

309
00:15:35,434 --> 00:15:37,973
even before the computers
will, and all the people

310
00:15:38,019 --> 00:15:39,585
he'll be enlisting for the fight.

311
00:15:39,613 --> 00:15:41,446
You have to call this pay phone

312
00:15:41,489 --> 00:15:44,344
in France.

313
00:15:48,383 --> 00:15:51,551
Wait. Chicago? I thought
I was going with you.

314
00:15:51,587 --> 00:15:55,255
Not until you find out
why you're my whip-hand.

315
00:15:56,425 --> 00:15:59,092
I have to go to Chicago
to find that out?

316
00:15:59,127 --> 00:16:01,461
Safe travels.

317
00:16:01,497 --> 00:16:03,563
In the grandiosity of his plan,

318
00:16:03,599 --> 00:16:05,398
he'll lose sight of
the simplest details.

319
00:16:05,434 --> 00:16:07,267
The phone he texted me with

320
00:16:07,302 --> 00:16:10,170
was located in Lyon, France last night.

321
00:16:10,205 --> 00:16:14,207
It was turned off in an
airport terminal at 11:51 p.m...

322
00:16:20,414 --> 00:16:24,451
20 minutes before a direct
flight to New York where

323
00:16:24,486 --> 00:16:25,819
you'll be waiting for him

324
00:16:25,854 --> 00:16:28,778
to put this game to bed for good.

325
00:16:30,571 --> 00:16:33,073
_

326
00:16:33,262 --> 00:16:35,495
Flight 290 to Miami, Florida

327
00:16:35,531 --> 00:16:37,597
will now depart from gate B24.

328
00:16:37,633 --> 00:16:39,132
He just powered back up.

329
00:16:40,836 --> 00:16:43,370
We got him.

330
00:16:44,006 --> 00:16:45,772
Look out!

331
00:16:45,807 --> 00:16:47,173
Back of the plane.

332
00:16:47,209 --> 00:16:49,242
Uh, excuse me! Excuse me.

333
00:16:49,278 --> 00:16:50,911
You're not allowed...

334
00:17:02,489 --> 00:17:04,790
Looks like the game's still going.

335
00:17:22,039 --> 00:17:24,923
_

336
00:17:29,373 --> 00:17:31,173
It's impressive how you get these drugs

337
00:17:31,208 --> 00:17:32,941
in the country just
by bribing small-time

338
00:17:32,976 --> 00:17:34,276
airport officials.

339
00:17:34,311 --> 00:17:35,877
I'm guessing you got about

340
00:17:35,913 --> 00:17:38,513
five million bucks worth
of fentanyl in here.

341
00:17:38,541 --> 00:17:39,769
So what?

342
00:17:39,772 --> 00:17:41,801
You and your brother
here are gonna lecture me?

343
00:17:41,819 --> 00:17:43,051
We were actually debating on whether

344
00:17:43,053 --> 00:17:44,841
I should give you the 100K or not.

345
00:17:44,844 --> 00:17:48,023
He says it's blood money.

346
00:17:48,058 --> 00:17:51,993
- I agree.
- How about you just shut up and pay me, Burrows?

347
00:17:52,029 --> 00:17:54,463
I don't have it.

348
00:17:58,415 --> 00:18:00,681
Grab his guys, bring 'em
to the back and shoot 'em.

349
00:18:00,684 --> 00:18:03,377
I don't think you want to add
murder to your arrest warrant.

350
00:18:03,380 --> 00:18:05,173
Wait.

351
00:18:06,276 --> 00:18:07,476
Arrest warrant?

352
00:18:07,511 --> 00:18:09,044
That guy out there

353
00:18:09,079 --> 00:18:10,797
is a DEA informant.

354
00:18:10,800 --> 00:18:12,700
We have him in our pocket.

355
00:18:12,750 --> 00:18:14,883
He owes us. He's got three vans

356
00:18:14,918 --> 00:18:17,419
full of agents that are
waiting for his call.

357
00:18:17,454 --> 00:18:19,955
They're gonna rain down
on you and your pills.

358
00:18:19,990 --> 00:18:23,125
Unless you forgive my brother's debt.

359
00:18:23,160 --> 00:18:25,427
Then our informant won't make the call.

360
00:18:25,462 --> 00:18:27,395
Have your brother fighting
your battles, do you?

361
00:18:27,431 --> 00:18:29,698
No.

362
00:18:29,733 --> 00:18:31,766
Why don't you tell your
guys to drop the guns,

363
00:18:31,802 --> 00:18:33,335
and you and I can have it out?

364
00:18:33,370 --> 00:18:36,104
What do you say, Luca?

365
00:18:37,441 --> 00:18:39,107
Scare that guy off.

366
00:18:39,143 --> 00:18:41,209
Bring these guys to the back.

367
00:18:41,245 --> 00:18:42,911
They make a move, he makes a call.

368
00:18:42,946 --> 00:18:45,847
Yeah? I think you're bluffing.

369
00:18:47,151 --> 00:18:49,784
I warned you.

370
00:18:53,457 --> 00:18:55,090
We got company.

371
00:18:59,229 --> 00:19:01,897
You shoot us, there's
dozens of witnesses now.

372
00:19:03,800 --> 00:19:05,267
Let's go.

373
00:19:22,629 --> 00:19:24,920
All they had to see
were DEA hats and SUVs,

374
00:19:24,955 --> 00:19:26,488
and they were gone.

375
00:19:26,523 --> 00:19:28,990
Famous Michael Scofield.

376
00:19:29,026 --> 00:19:33,314
Sheba. Thank you for everything.

377
00:19:33,337 --> 00:19:37,699
You have no idea how happy
I am to see you back home.

378
00:19:37,734 --> 00:19:39,634
We're not home yet.

379
00:19:39,670 --> 00:19:41,736
All right, so what's next?

380
00:19:41,772 --> 00:19:44,039
How do we get this son of a bitch?

381
00:19:44,074 --> 00:19:45,574
We don't do anything.

382
00:19:45,609 --> 00:19:47,242
Your part is over.

383
00:19:49,713 --> 00:19:51,012
No, no, no, no, no, no.

384
00:19:51,048 --> 00:19:52,847
Tricking Abruzzi's kid is one thing.

385
00:19:52,883 --> 00:19:54,783
Poseidon... he knows your face.

386
00:19:54,818 --> 00:19:57,786
Been tracking you
since you went to Yemen.

387
00:19:57,821 --> 00:19:59,354
You've been a warrior,

388
00:19:59,389 --> 00:20:01,056
and I owe you.

389
00:20:01,091 --> 00:20:04,025
But your face is a liability
now to you and your family.

390
00:20:04,061 --> 00:20:06,661
I don't want you to risk that.

391
00:20:08,799 --> 00:20:11,633
They may know his face,
but they don't know mine.

392
00:20:14,471 --> 00:20:17,172
It's the punch you don't see
coming that knocks you out.

393
00:20:17,207 --> 00:20:19,808
That's my Sheba.

394
00:20:19,843 --> 00:20:22,844
You take care of her, all right?

395
00:20:22,879 --> 00:20:25,013
I take care of him, you mean.

396
00:20:26,683 --> 00:20:30,051
- I love you, brother.
- Love you, too.

397
00:20:32,397 --> 00:20:34,330
Be safe,

398
00:20:34,358 --> 00:20:35,857
- okay?
- You, too.

399
00:20:35,892 --> 00:20:38,593
- Bye.
- All right.

400
00:20:38,629 --> 00:20:40,528
Well...

401
00:20:40,564 --> 00:20:42,297
when you need me again,

402
00:20:42,332 --> 00:20:45,133
you know where to find me.

403
00:20:53,543 --> 00:20:55,243
We'll transport her at 1600 hours.

404
00:20:55,279 --> 00:20:57,879
Lay low until then. Thank you.

405
00:21:07,891 --> 00:21:09,891
Hey?

406
00:21:09,926 --> 00:21:12,527
That doesn't bother you...
What you just saw in there?

407
00:21:12,562 --> 00:21:14,696
Down in the basement

408
00:21:14,731 --> 00:21:16,865
with his wife, the woman
he says he fell for?

409
00:21:16,900 --> 00:21:18,566
Stop.

410
00:21:19,836 --> 00:21:23,071
I'm done with 21-Void after this.

411
00:21:25,909 --> 00:21:28,643
After we get Scofield... Outis...

412
00:21:28,679 --> 00:21:30,812
Whatever his name is...

413
00:21:30,847 --> 00:21:32,814
I'm done.

414
00:21:32,849 --> 00:21:35,750
That's all I ever wanted,
to get Gaines' killer, but

415
00:21:35,786 --> 00:21:37,719
what he's got going in there...

416
00:21:37,754 --> 00:21:40,121
That's not normal.

417
00:21:40,157 --> 00:21:41,556
It's personal.

418
00:21:41,591 --> 00:21:43,385
Something sicker.

419
00:21:43,416 --> 00:21:46,728
There's no leaving
21-Void, Van. You know that.

420
00:21:47,964 --> 00:21:51,733
He hired us because we are the best.

421
00:21:51,768 --> 00:21:54,669
We can do whatever we want.

422
00:21:54,705 --> 00:21:58,206
And if we want to
disappear after this...

423
00:21:58,248 --> 00:22:00,482
we can disappear.

424
00:22:02,012 --> 00:22:03,712
There's no getting out.

425
00:22:03,747 --> 00:22:07,048
If you think that way...

426
00:22:07,084 --> 00:22:09,584
then you're a prisoner, too.

427
00:22:23,107 --> 00:22:26,108
The guy at the gate
said the vehicles split

428
00:22:26,136 --> 00:22:27,669
five minutes after they got here.

429
00:22:27,732 --> 00:22:29,789
Five minutes?

430
00:22:32,309 --> 00:22:33,608
Something ain't right.

431
00:22:33,643 --> 00:22:35,143
The product is still here.

432
00:22:36,213 --> 00:22:37,445
Come on.

433
00:22:37,481 --> 00:22:40,181
It was all staged.

434
00:22:40,217 --> 00:22:42,014
Clever.

435
00:22:42,017 --> 00:22:43,512
But Burrows is gonna die for it.

436
00:22:43,515 --> 00:22:45,286
I don't know how we're gonna find him.

437
00:22:45,288 --> 00:22:46,488
He's in the wind.

438
00:22:46,523 --> 00:22:48,123
Maybe not.

439
00:22:48,158 --> 00:22:49,990
EZ Pass transponders.

440
00:22:51,161 --> 00:22:53,194
Santora's got a guy
at transit authority.

441
00:22:53,230 --> 00:22:56,131
I bet you he can us what roads
they've been taking and when.

442
00:22:56,166 --> 00:22:59,534
Then it's up to us to
comb the neighborhoods,

443
00:22:59,569 --> 00:23:01,269
find the vehicles,

444
00:23:01,304 --> 00:23:04,439
and put a bullet in that son
of a bitch once and for all.

445
00:23:10,220 --> 00:23:13,557
_

446
00:23:13,762 --> 00:23:17,363
Please keep your baggage
with you at all times.

447
00:23:17,399 --> 00:23:20,033
Unattended baggage is a
security risk and may result...

448
00:23:20,068 --> 00:23:22,502
I got a weird request.

449
00:23:22,537 --> 00:23:25,538
If I give you some coordinates,
can you take me to 'em?

450
00:23:25,574 --> 00:23:28,041
See what I can do.

451
00:23:32,655 --> 00:23:34,288
No.

452
00:23:34,316 --> 00:23:35,949
Unless this cab's got pontoons,

453
00:23:35,984 --> 00:23:37,684
ain't gonna happen.

454
00:23:37,719 --> 00:23:40,587
These coordinates are in
the middle of Lake Michigan.

455
00:23:56,738 --> 00:23:58,938
This is it.

456
00:23:58,974 --> 00:24:01,262
No lights.

457
00:24:01,293 --> 00:24:03,376
I don't think they're here, Michael.

458
00:24:03,411 --> 00:24:05,712
Unless that's what he wants us to think.

459
00:24:05,747 --> 00:24:07,347
Come on.

460
00:24:09,760 --> 00:24:12,694
Get ready to get us out
of here as fast as you can.

461
00:24:14,155 --> 00:24:15,355
Linc.

462
00:24:19,895 --> 00:24:22,095
Be careful.

463
00:24:22,130 --> 00:24:23,593
Thanks.

464
00:24:33,220 --> 00:24:34,786
What's wrong?

465
00:24:46,659 --> 00:24:49,113
That's why Sara never responded.

466
00:24:56,087 --> 00:24:58,387
I wasn't allowed to contact anyone,

467
00:24:58,400 --> 00:25:00,233
but she was my wife.

468
00:25:01,303 --> 00:25:03,236
I reached out to her in a way

469
00:25:03,271 --> 00:25:04,804
I thought only she would know.

470
00:25:07,275 --> 00:25:09,534
But he knew my ways, too.

471
00:27:08,663 --> 00:27:10,797
Nothing.

472
00:27:13,463 --> 00:27:15,300
_

473
00:27:15,303 --> 00:27:17,437
What are you doing?

474
00:27:19,040 --> 00:27:20,239
That's not Sara, Michael.

475
00:27:20,257 --> 00:27:22,791
He doesn't know I know that.

476
00:27:22,931 --> 00:27:25,759
_

477
00:27:28,436 --> 00:27:30,814
_

478
00:27:34,025 --> 00:27:36,444
_

479
00:27:38,575 --> 00:27:40,041
- _
- That's the right answer.

480
00:27:40,064 --> 00:27:41,694
She's alive.

481
00:27:41,729 --> 00:27:43,963
He must be right there with her.

482
00:27:43,998 --> 00:27:46,165
I'm gonna set a meeting.

483
00:27:46,201 --> 00:27:48,361
And what, you're just gonna
show up and show your face?

484
00:27:48,369 --> 00:27:50,036
Yes.

485
00:27:50,071 --> 00:27:52,672
That means Poseidon has
to show his face, too.

486
00:27:52,707 --> 00:27:55,741
And the endgame begins.

487
00:28:09,691 --> 00:28:11,257
It's high noon, boss.

488
00:28:11,292 --> 00:28:13,459
I'm not seeing him.

489
00:28:13,495 --> 00:28:15,328
And you shouldn't. He's waiting for us

490
00:28:15,363 --> 00:28:17,597
to push the first piece
out onto the board.

491
00:28:17,632 --> 00:28:18,965
Which would be me?

492
00:28:21,669 --> 00:28:23,302
Maybe not.

493
00:28:23,338 --> 00:28:25,338
Black SUV.

494
00:28:28,243 --> 00:28:30,243
Something I can help you with?

495
00:28:30,278 --> 00:28:33,463
Car service. I'm here to
pick up a lady and child.

496
00:28:33,502 --> 00:28:35,181
They got another ride. Hit the road.

497
00:28:36,384 --> 00:28:37,617
Are you sure?

498
00:28:37,652 --> 00:28:39,285
Hit the road.

499
00:28:42,824 --> 00:28:44,457
Mark the black SUV.

500
00:28:44,492 --> 00:28:46,692
No need. They were just here
to make you show your face.

501
00:28:46,728 --> 00:28:48,361
Walk away, please. Now.

502
00:28:49,964 --> 00:28:52,131
Okay, act the tiniest bit flustered.

503
00:28:52,167 --> 00:28:54,800
Now repeat these words back
to me loud enough to be heard:

504
00:28:54,836 --> 00:28:56,135
"They didn't show.

505
00:28:56,171 --> 00:28:57,837
I'm coming back to you now."

506
00:28:57,872 --> 00:28:59,672
They didn't show.

507
00:28:59,707 --> 00:29:01,807
I'm coming back to you now.

508
00:29:07,549 --> 00:29:09,148
Now we have a game.

509
00:29:09,184 --> 00:29:11,083
He's already revealed

510
00:29:11,119 --> 00:29:13,019
his brother, his biggest piece.

511
00:29:13,054 --> 00:29:15,988
Soon he'll have to
show his face. Trailer,

512
00:29:16,024 --> 00:29:18,191
please take him down.

513
00:29:34,576 --> 00:29:36,042
What the...?

514
00:29:48,756 --> 00:29:50,756
I lost him.

515
00:29:50,792 --> 00:29:52,124
Hey.

516
00:29:52,160 --> 00:29:53,893
Can you hear me?

517
00:29:57,265 --> 00:29:59,031
Damn it.

518
00:29:59,067 --> 00:30:01,701
No signal.

519
00:30:06,841 --> 00:30:08,174
What are you doing here?

520
00:30:08,209 --> 00:30:09,508
I lost reception in the garage.

521
00:30:09,544 --> 00:30:11,150
Damn it, you fell right into it.

522
00:30:11,153 --> 00:30:12,686
Now they've got a mark on us.

523
00:30:24,692 --> 00:30:26,125
Black sedan.

524
00:30:28,696 --> 00:30:29,929
He's heading west.

525
00:30:55,380 --> 00:30:56,656
Please!

526
00:30:56,691 --> 00:30:58,124
Please, don't shoot.

527
00:31:04,966 --> 00:31:06,499
You okay?

528
00:31:08,034 --> 00:31:10,336
So that's what the dog
who's destroying my country

529
00:31:10,371 --> 00:31:11,937
looks like.

530
00:31:15,343 --> 00:31:16,776
Talk to me.

531
00:31:16,811 --> 00:31:18,711
Michael, we found the car.

532
00:31:18,746 --> 00:31:21,047
We're on the corner of Third
and Washington by an alley.

533
00:31:21,082 --> 00:31:22,481
Get here now.

534
00:31:22,517 --> 00:31:24,884
He had Sara with him

535
00:31:24,919 --> 00:31:26,886
- but we couldn't see her.
- What do you mean you couldn't see her?

536
00:31:26,888 --> 00:31:28,616
There's no way we could have.

537
00:31:34,387 --> 00:31:37,288
Oh, my God. Sara.

538
00:31:44,061 --> 00:31:46,161
There was no one

539
00:31:46,196 --> 00:31:47,796
- in the backseat?
- No, the windows

540
00:31:47,831 --> 00:31:49,898
were blacked out... We couldn't see.

541
00:31:53,170 --> 00:31:54,536
What's that?

542
00:31:54,570 --> 00:31:56,631
My son did this.

543
00:31:56,670 --> 00:31:58,840
He's good.

544
00:31:58,875 --> 00:32:01,376
There might be something here.

545
00:32:01,411 --> 00:32:02,904
It's a ship.

546
00:32:02,936 --> 00:32:04,879
A pirate ship with three pirates...

547
00:32:04,915 --> 00:32:06,381
Man, woman and a boy.

548
00:32:06,416 --> 00:32:08,116
That's me, Sara and... Mike.

549
00:32:08,151 --> 00:32:10,175
What do you think that is?

550
00:32:10,191 --> 00:32:12,487
It's a... it's a many-headed hydra

551
00:32:12,522 --> 00:32:14,322
reaching up to attack.

552
00:32:14,358 --> 00:32:15,949
Think it's Jacob?

553
00:32:15,981 --> 00:32:17,580
Must be.

554
00:32:17,613 --> 00:32:19,394
- This is a message.
- You're telling me

555
00:32:19,429 --> 00:32:21,463
Mikey's left something encoded in that?

556
00:32:21,498 --> 00:32:23,932
Yeah. Yeah, it's encoded in him.

557
00:32:23,967 --> 00:32:25,533
He's got my DNA.

558
00:32:25,569 --> 00:32:27,168
He didn't even know you were coming.

559
00:32:27,204 --> 00:32:29,404
Sara must have told him. I don't know.

560
00:32:29,439 --> 00:32:31,539
She must have told him I was coming.

561
00:32:31,575 --> 00:32:34,542
There's definitely
something here. Definitely.

562
00:32:44,154 --> 00:32:45,954
What is it?

563
00:32:45,989 --> 00:32:49,048
It's one of Luca's guys.

564
00:32:49,103 --> 00:32:51,025
What?

565
00:32:51,061 --> 00:32:53,094
How the hell did he track us here?

566
00:32:53,130 --> 00:32:55,501
I don't know. All I
know is all the chickens

567
00:32:55,504 --> 00:32:57,744
are coming home to roost
at the worst possible time.

568
00:32:57,747 --> 00:32:59,768
We got to go.

569
00:33:00,971 --> 00:33:02,904
Linc?

570
00:33:04,110 --> 00:33:05,643
I got it.

571
00:33:05,678 --> 00:33:07,912
This ship, this galleon.

572
00:33:07,947 --> 00:33:11,315
The body of water it's
on. I looked at the map.

573
00:33:11,350 --> 00:33:14,202
There's a lake, a lake
shaped exactly like it,

574
00:33:14,205 --> 00:33:15,753
up in the Finger Lakes district.

575
00:33:15,755 --> 00:33:17,191
"Long lake."

576
00:33:17,194 --> 00:33:18,189
This X

577
00:33:18,224 --> 00:33:20,724
would be on the east shore of that lake.

578
00:33:22,975 --> 00:33:24,573
He's telling us where he is.

579
00:33:24,576 --> 00:33:26,797
I'm trying to figure out if
you lost your mind or not.

580
00:33:26,799 --> 00:33:29,867
There's only one way to find out.

581
00:33:29,902 --> 00:33:31,268
- Uh-uh.
- What?

582
00:33:31,304 --> 00:33:33,137
- You're going back to Buffalo.
- What?!

583
00:33:33,172 --> 00:33:35,492
I want you to be with your
family, look after the refugees.

584
00:33:35,508 --> 00:33:37,908
Linc, I'm a part of this fight, too...

585
00:33:44,584 --> 00:33:45,983
What was that?

586
00:33:46,018 --> 00:33:47,685
It's good-bye.

587
00:33:48,801 --> 00:33:51,021
I could never forgive myself

588
00:33:51,057 --> 00:33:54,291
if something happened to you.

589
00:34:03,665 --> 00:34:06,945
_

590
00:34:11,844 --> 00:34:13,377
Can I help you?

591
00:34:13,412 --> 00:34:14,912
Yeah.

592
00:34:14,947 --> 00:34:17,314
Can I rent a boat?

593
00:34:17,350 --> 00:34:19,950
I want to take one out on the lake.

594
00:34:44,710 --> 00:34:47,278
Been thinkin'.

595
00:34:49,382 --> 00:34:50,914
God...

596
00:34:50,950 --> 00:34:53,917
I been thinking.

597
00:34:53,953 --> 00:34:56,987
'Cause a hard bargain's
been presented to me,

598
00:34:57,023 --> 00:34:59,790
and I'm considering something

599
00:34:59,825 --> 00:35:01,959
that's-that's gonna seem like

600
00:35:01,994 --> 00:35:04,128
the old Theodore Bagwell.

601
00:35:05,865 --> 00:35:07,998
T-Bag.

602
00:35:11,168 --> 00:35:13,270
And if that's indeed what's coming...

603
00:35:15,975 --> 00:35:18,208
it won't be the work

604
00:35:18,244 --> 00:35:21,111
of a cold-blooded man.

605
00:35:22,948 --> 00:35:25,549
And it won't be for sin...

606
00:35:27,853 --> 00:35:30,287
or for hate.

607
00:35:34,217 --> 00:35:36,026
If there's blood on my hands,

608
00:35:36,062 --> 00:35:38,128
know this, world...

609
00:35:40,599 --> 00:35:43,033
it'll be for love.

610
00:36:09,228 --> 00:36:10,928
How you doing, buddy?

611
00:36:10,963 --> 00:36:12,229
I'm sick of the lake house.

612
00:36:12,264 --> 00:36:13,897
I want to go home.

613
00:36:13,933 --> 00:36:16,133
I know. I know.

614
00:36:16,168 --> 00:36:18,702
We'll go home soon.

615
00:36:18,738 --> 00:36:19,937
Don't worry.

616
00:36:19,972 --> 00:36:22,115
Is Mom okay?

617
00:36:22,130 --> 00:36:23,440
She's, uh...

618
00:36:23,476 --> 00:36:24,942
she's a little under the weather.

619
00:36:24,977 --> 00:36:26,176
She's just resting.

620
00:36:28,080 --> 00:36:30,848
Everything will be fine, kiddo.

621
00:36:30,883 --> 00:36:34,585
Everything will be back to
normal soon enough, okay?

622
00:37:28,855 --> 00:37:31,323
Michael, go get him. And I'll be ready.

623
00:37:38,561 --> 00:37:40,571
- Thanks, man, that was fun.
- Yeah, anytime.

624
00:37:40,606 --> 00:37:42,573
Yeah, great. Thank you.

625
00:37:43,542 --> 00:37:46,710
What kind of honorific is Whip?

626
00:37:48,180 --> 00:37:50,681
Who's asking?

627
00:37:50,716 --> 00:37:54,351
A man drawn into this by destiny.

628
00:37:54,387 --> 00:37:57,021
Okay. How about you take off?

629
00:37:57,056 --> 00:37:59,256
I don't exactly cotton to
strange men coming up to me

630
00:37:59,291 --> 00:38:00,924
in the middle of the night, you know?

631
00:38:00,960 --> 00:38:03,560
Only one person calls
me Whip... you ain't him.

632
00:38:03,596 --> 00:38:06,230
Nobody calls you that.

633
00:38:07,942 --> 00:38:10,776
Man who gave me this hand. Nobody.

634
00:38:13,001 --> 00:38:14,567
Kaniel Outis.

635
00:38:14,640 --> 00:38:17,241
Or for those of us who know him,

636
00:38:17,276 --> 00:38:19,610
Michael Scofield.

637
00:38:22,948 --> 00:38:25,182
Who are you?

638
00:38:25,217 --> 00:38:27,951
We all got handles, don't we?

639
00:38:29,422 --> 00:38:32,790
Outis. T-Bag. Whip.

640
00:38:32,825 --> 00:38:35,793
But you're Dave Martin, aren't you?

641
00:38:38,931 --> 00:38:40,531
How'd you know that?

642
00:38:40,566 --> 00:38:41,899
Huh?

643
00:38:41,934 --> 00:38:44,268
You better start talking, old man.

644
00:38:44,303 --> 00:38:46,503
You don't want to tangle with this.

645
00:38:46,539 --> 00:38:47,571
Neither do you.

646
00:38:48,741 --> 00:38:52,609
All your answers are
right in here, all right?

647
00:38:53,512 --> 00:38:55,345
West Virginia honky-tonk,

648
00:38:55,381 --> 00:38:57,314
1991, pretty waitress,

649
00:38:57,349 --> 00:38:59,990
bunch of personal business
between us after closing,

650
00:38:59,993 --> 00:39:02,753
and then I git, 'cause Johnny
Law's breathing down my neck.

651
00:39:02,788 --> 00:39:04,688
Lacking a forwarding address,

652
00:39:04,716 --> 00:39:08,284
I never heard from her again.

653
00:39:08,327 --> 00:39:10,828
What are you trying to tell me?

654
00:39:12,331 --> 00:39:15,332
Scofield was looking for
a partner, combing prisons,

655
00:39:15,367 --> 00:39:18,335
looking for someone who
could handle himself.

656
00:39:19,672 --> 00:39:22,506
And with your innate ability to thrive,

657
00:39:22,541 --> 00:39:25,008
rising to the top in
even the worst of cages,

658
00:39:25,044 --> 00:39:28,145
you reminded him of a certain someone.

659
00:39:28,180 --> 00:39:30,581
And so he did a little research.

660
00:39:30,616 --> 00:39:33,617
Wanted to know what we all want to know.

661
00:39:33,652 --> 00:39:36,086
Did you learn it...

662
00:39:36,122 --> 00:39:38,555
or was it ingrained in you?

663
00:39:40,826 --> 00:39:43,961
It was ingrained in you, son.

664
00:39:45,564 --> 00:39:48,432
You got it from me.

665
00:40:10,022 --> 00:40:12,356
Linc, he's here.

666
00:40:12,391 --> 00:40:14,558
- My son.
- Thank God.

667
00:40:14,593 --> 00:40:16,693
Hold on.

668
00:40:19,031 --> 00:40:20,731
Hold up.

669
00:40:20,766 --> 00:40:22,633
I think Jacob's coming back.

670
00:40:25,003 --> 00:40:26,970
I can't believe I'm seeing my son.

671
00:40:31,343 --> 00:40:33,043
Something's wrong.

672
00:40:33,078 --> 00:40:35,078
Sara's here, but...

673
00:40:35,114 --> 00:40:37,915
- something's wrong.
- Don't do anything. He's coming back.

674
00:40:47,526 --> 00:40:48,859
I'm going in.

675
00:40:53,385 --> 00:40:54,717
It's not Jacob.

676
00:40:54,752 --> 00:40:55,918
You're clear.

677
00:40:55,955 --> 00:40:57,901
Get your family. Get your son.

678
00:41:05,578 --> 00:41:07,344
Burrows!

679
00:41:32,305 --> 00:41:34,305
Hi, Mike.

680
00:41:35,510 --> 00:41:37,510
You know who I am?

681
00:41:46,886 --> 00:41:48,585
I got your map.

682
00:41:48,621 --> 00:41:51,555
I'm gonna get you and
your mother out of here.

683
00:41:51,590 --> 00:41:54,640
I... I didn't draw a map.

684
00:42:03,402 --> 00:42:06,036
- Is someone in there with your mother?
- It's not...

685
00:42:06,071 --> 00:42:08,472
We need to run.

