1
00:00:02,312 --> 00:00:05,460
- Previously on Prison Break...
- We found Michael.

2
00:00:05,462 --> 00:00:07,329
Never thought I'd see this face again.

3
00:00:07,364 --> 00:00:08,843
You weren't supposed to.

4
00:00:08,867 --> 00:00:10,999
I own you, Scofield. If
you're planning something,

5
00:00:11,034 --> 00:00:13,268
I'll always be a step ahead of you.

6
00:00:13,303 --> 00:00:14,770
Your husband.

7
00:00:14,805 --> 00:00:16,104
Jacob is Poseidon.

8
00:00:16,139 --> 00:00:17,764
He's a CIA operative,

9
00:00:17,799 --> 00:00:19,088
deep cover.

10
00:00:19,112 --> 00:00:21,076
He runs a splinter cell called 21-Void.

11
00:00:21,111 --> 00:00:23,278
He targeted me for my skills.

12
00:00:23,313 --> 00:00:26,615
Four years ago, he betrayed
me so he could have you.

13
00:00:26,650 --> 00:00:28,533
- How did he betray you?
- We were meeting a man

14
00:00:28,535 --> 00:00:29,634
named Harlan Gaines,

15
00:00:29,662 --> 00:00:31,586
a deputy director of the CIA.

16
00:00:31,617 --> 00:00:33,950
Poseidon shot and
killed Gaines that night.

17
00:00:33,985 --> 00:00:35,691
I knew I was being set up.

18
00:00:35,726 --> 00:00:37,552
Michael, he's with our son right now.

19
00:00:37,587 --> 00:00:40,429
Scofield was looking for
a partner, combing prisons,

20
00:00:40,464 --> 00:00:42,864
looking for someone who
could handle himself.

21
00:00:42,899 --> 00:00:44,433
What are you trying to tell me?

22
00:00:44,468 --> 00:00:47,620
It was ingrained in you,
son. You got it from me.

23
00:00:47,652 --> 00:00:50,038
Screen grab of the Skype
transmission he sent from the desert.

24
00:00:50,040 --> 00:00:51,829
Of all things to encrypt, why that?

25
00:00:51,860 --> 00:00:53,665
I'm done with 21-Void after this.

26
00:00:53,680 --> 00:00:56,036
There's no leaving 21-Void, Van.

27
00:00:56,071 --> 00:00:58,213
How about you just shut
up and pay me, Burrows?

28
00:00:58,248 --> 00:00:59,381
I don't have it.

29
00:01:02,110 --> 00:01:03,952
You know who I am?

30
00:01:03,987 --> 00:01:05,887
I'm gonna get you and
your mother out of here.

31
00:01:05,922 --> 00:01:07,535
We need to run.

32
00:01:14,656 --> 00:01:21,267
_

33
00:01:34,918 --> 00:01:37,219
Do you know that you're a psychopath?

34
00:01:37,254 --> 00:01:40,255
I assure you, I'm not the
first CIA man to hide his life

35
00:01:40,290 --> 00:01:41,590
from his family.

36
00:01:41,625 --> 00:01:43,124
You hid it from the CIA.

37
00:01:43,144 --> 00:01:45,130
Look, you want to screw something up?

38
00:01:45,165 --> 00:01:47,228
Put a thousand people on it.
You want to get it done right?

39
00:01:47,230 --> 00:01:49,110
Put it in the hands of
a few. What we were doing

40
00:01:49,132 --> 00:01:50,532
was advancing this country's cause.

41
00:01:50,534 --> 00:01:52,597
How does freeing a man like Abu Ramal

42
00:01:52,628 --> 00:01:54,002
advance this country's cause?

43
00:01:54,037 --> 00:01:57,539
Well, it doesn't.

44
00:01:57,574 --> 00:02:00,075
The missions before,

45
00:02:00,110 --> 00:02:02,811
they were for the good
of the country, but...

46
00:02:02,846 --> 00:02:06,415
No, this one wasn't about country.

47
00:02:06,450 --> 00:02:08,583
It was about you.

48
00:02:08,618 --> 00:02:12,596
Nobody wants to die to
their old life, Sara.

49
00:02:12,627 --> 00:02:14,756
And Michael didn't.

50
00:02:16,426 --> 00:02:20,862
He wanted to hold on
to it so desperately.

51
00:02:20,897 --> 00:02:22,664
In that moment, I wanted him

52
00:02:22,699 --> 00:02:23,843
to go away,

53
00:02:23,875 --> 00:02:26,301
the whole agreement,

54
00:02:26,336 --> 00:02:27,402
and just have you.

55
00:02:27,437 --> 00:02:29,337
You sent him to Yemen to die.

56
00:02:29,372 --> 00:02:33,492
Kept telling myself this
was gonna be my last lie.

57
00:02:33,523 --> 00:02:38,080
That it would fade with
time as we had anniversaries,

58
00:02:38,115 --> 00:02:39,981
raised that beautiful child.

59
00:02:40,016 --> 00:02:41,650
That is not your child.

60
00:02:41,685 --> 00:02:43,218
I raised him.

61
00:02:43,253 --> 00:02:44,419
That love is real.

62
00:02:44,454 --> 00:02:45,554
It's not a lie.

63
00:02:45,589 --> 00:02:48,087
You are using him as bait.

64
00:02:48,122 --> 00:02:49,424
You son of a bitch.

65
00:02:49,459 --> 00:02:50,926
She knows not to hurt him.

66
00:02:50,961 --> 00:02:52,093
You were so obsessed with Michael

67
00:02:52,095 --> 00:02:53,261
that you would risk my son!

68
00:02:53,296 --> 00:02:55,263
Michael? You mean you.

69
00:02:55,298 --> 00:02:58,266
You don't love me. Your ego's too big.

70
00:02:58,301 --> 00:03:00,602
You're too busy trying to be
the smartest man in the room.

71
00:03:00,637 --> 00:03:02,904
And then you met my husband,

72
00:03:02,939 --> 00:03:04,339
and you realized

73
00:03:04,374 --> 00:03:05,640
he's smarter than you.

74
00:03:06,877 --> 00:03:08,310
I don't think so.

75
00:03:08,345 --> 00:03:09,203
You sure?

76
00:03:09,218 --> 00:03:12,114
I'm positive.

77
00:03:12,149 --> 00:03:14,149
Our love was real, Sara.

78
00:03:14,184 --> 00:03:15,260
Past tense.

79
00:03:15,295 --> 00:03:18,620
I still love you.

80
00:03:21,487 --> 00:03:22,850
Everything's set, boss.

81
00:03:22,883 --> 00:03:24,249
Good.

82
00:03:29,166 --> 00:03:30,766
Got to give you credit.

83
00:03:30,801 --> 00:03:32,847
You'll go the whole nine
yards to help one man

84
00:03:32,869 --> 00:03:34,102
steal another man's wife.

85
00:03:34,137 --> 00:03:35,337
No, no, no. Don't talk to him.

86
00:03:35,372 --> 00:03:37,072
Or what? He'll do something

87
00:03:37,107 --> 00:03:39,175
you're not already gonna
do? You're going to kill me.

88
00:03:39,177 --> 00:03:41,751
No matter how many times you
tell me you love me first.

89
00:03:41,774 --> 00:03:42,563
Shut up!

90
00:03:42,594 --> 00:03:44,679
Michael didn't kill Harlan
Gaines. He had no motive.

91
00:03:44,681 --> 00:03:46,381
- Shut up.
- He's the one with the motive.

92
00:03:46,416 --> 00:03:48,250
Harlan Gaines was your CIA director

93
00:03:48,285 --> 00:03:49,851
and he was looking into Jacob.

94
00:03:49,886 --> 00:03:51,986
He was gonna put him in prison.

95
00:03:55,492 --> 00:03:57,225
Damn it!

96
00:04:00,096 --> 00:04:02,063
Tape her mouth shut, please.

97
00:04:02,098 --> 00:04:03,810
Tape it shut.

98
00:04:04,901 --> 00:04:06,868
If you do, an innocent man dies,

99
00:04:06,903 --> 00:04:09,433
and the real killer walks.

100
00:04:09,459 --> 00:04:10,956
Don't you understand?

101
00:04:10,987 --> 00:04:13,088
Jacob killed Harlan Gaines.

102
00:04:13,123 --> 00:04:14,894
Just shut it.

103
00:04:20,116 --> 00:04:21,850
Is there a problem?

104
00:04:24,616 --> 00:04:27,316
Here he comes. It's time to do this.

105
00:04:31,194 --> 00:04:34,062
This place is gonna
burn down in ten minutes.

106
00:04:34,097 --> 00:04:37,699
There will be two bodies in it.

107
00:04:37,734 --> 00:04:40,068
And if it's any solace,

108
00:04:40,103 --> 00:04:42,704
our son won't be one of them.

109
00:05:13,203 --> 00:05:17,872
While the cat's away,
the mice will play.

110
00:05:22,312 --> 00:05:23,878
Something's wrong.

111
00:05:41,398 --> 00:05:42,998
I got your map.

112
00:05:43,033 --> 00:05:45,133
I'm gonna get you and
your mother out of here.

113
00:05:45,168 --> 00:05:47,283
I didn't draw a map.

114
00:05:54,344 --> 00:05:55,443
We need to run.

115
00:05:58,548 --> 00:06:00,315
Wait.

116
00:06:00,350 --> 00:06:02,050
What are you doing up here, Van?

117
00:06:02,085 --> 00:06:05,153
I just want to make sure that
we're getting the right guy.

118
00:06:05,188 --> 00:06:06,755
Ask him some questions.

119
00:06:09,726 --> 00:06:11,293
Let my son go.

120
00:06:11,328 --> 00:06:13,461
Do whatever you want with me.

121
00:06:13,496 --> 00:06:15,063
Just let my son go.

122
00:06:18,603 --> 00:06:21,503
Orders weren't to ask questions.

123
00:06:21,538 --> 00:06:22,937
It was to shoot on sight.

124
00:06:27,210 --> 00:06:29,778
Maybe we should ask questions, damn it.

125
00:06:29,813 --> 00:06:31,880
If Scofield killed Harlan Gaines,

126
00:06:31,915 --> 00:06:33,815
we take him to the
police, if we have to.

127
00:06:33,850 --> 00:06:36,017
We get this done the right way.

128
00:06:36,052 --> 00:06:37,652
Poseidon would never let us live.

129
00:06:37,687 --> 00:06:39,087
He won't find us.

130
00:06:42,292 --> 00:06:44,693
I told you. We want to
disappear, we disappear.

131
00:06:44,728 --> 00:06:46,728
I can make that happen.

132
00:06:46,763 --> 00:06:48,530
We turn him in,

133
00:06:48,565 --> 00:06:49,764
and we're gone.

134
00:06:49,799 --> 00:06:51,533
Don't make me choose like this.

135
00:06:51,568 --> 00:06:52,734
Emily.

136
00:06:52,769 --> 00:06:54,636
Is it really even a choice?

137
00:06:54,671 --> 00:06:56,437
No.

138
00:06:59,151 --> 00:07:01,809
'Cause there's no leaving 21-Void.

139
00:07:09,919 --> 00:07:11,353
Go.

140
00:07:11,388 --> 00:07:12,989
Your uncle's at the end of the driveway.

141
00:07:12,992 --> 00:07:14,581
Don't turn around. Run! Go!

142
00:07:21,156 --> 00:07:22,697
Sara.

143
00:07:22,732 --> 00:07:24,265
Where's our boy?

144
00:07:25,769 --> 00:07:27,739
Uncle Lincoln, Uncle Lincoln!

145
00:07:27,763 --> 00:07:30,330
No, no, no, it's me. What's going on?

146
00:07:30,365 --> 00:07:32,332
They're shooting. I'm scared.

147
00:07:32,367 --> 00:07:33,989
- Okay. They've come for you.
- Who?

148
00:07:34,020 --> 00:07:35,576
I am not gonna let them hurt you,

149
00:07:35,578 --> 00:07:37,170
you understand? Get in the car.

150
00:07:37,205 --> 00:07:38,971
No, we've got to go now,
Mike. We've got to go.

151
00:07:38,973 --> 00:07:39,939
What about my mom?

152
00:07:39,974 --> 00:07:41,007
Go, go, go.

153
00:07:42,410 --> 00:07:46,246
Mike! No!

154
00:07:46,281 --> 00:07:48,281
No!

155
00:07:48,316 --> 00:07:49,249
No!

156
00:07:49,284 --> 00:07:50,417
Mike!

157
00:07:50,452 --> 00:07:51,351
He took him.

158
00:07:51,386 --> 00:07:52,986
- Sara...
- He took our son.

159
00:07:53,021 --> 00:07:55,121
Come back to me. Come
back to me, sweetheart.

160
00:07:55,156 --> 00:07:56,389
Come back to me.

161
00:07:56,424 --> 00:07:57,903
We got to stay focused, all right?

162
00:07:57,906 --> 00:07:59,793
This is not over. Not by a long shot.

163
00:07:59,828 --> 00:08:01,194
- Where's Linc?
- What?

164
00:08:01,229 --> 00:08:02,295
We got to find Linc, okay?

165
00:08:02,330 --> 00:08:03,663
We're gonna find Linc.

166
00:08:07,302 --> 00:08:09,302
Linc.

167
00:08:09,337 --> 00:08:11,337
Oh my God.

168
00:08:12,273 --> 00:08:14,540
Linc. Linc.

169
00:08:50,909 --> 00:08:52,508
I let you down, Michael.

170
00:08:52,543 --> 00:08:55,469
I should have taken care of
Luca when I had the chance.

171
00:08:55,492 --> 00:08:57,847
You didn't let me down.
You couldn't have known.

172
00:08:57,882 --> 00:09:00,516
We're so close because of you, Linc.

173
00:09:00,551 --> 00:09:01,918
You got me home.

174
00:09:01,953 --> 00:09:03,352
You got me home.

175
00:09:04,522 --> 00:09:05,889
They've stabilized him, Michael.

176
00:09:05,924 --> 00:09:07,323
There's nothing we can do.

177
00:09:07,358 --> 00:09:09,525
We've got to get you
out of here right now.

178
00:09:26,144 --> 00:09:28,745
Okay, you got to give me
some direction here, you know?

179
00:09:28,780 --> 00:09:30,446
Some, um...

180
00:09:30,481 --> 00:09:32,982
fatherly advice

181
00:09:33,017 --> 00:09:38,788
on how to deal with having
a father that's, um...

182
00:09:38,823 --> 00:09:41,090
you.

183
00:09:45,865 --> 00:09:47,863
Well, you know, uh...

184
00:09:51,336 --> 00:09:54,270
Is this blood freaking you
out like it's freaking me out?

185
00:09:54,305 --> 00:09:55,838
Yeah, yeah. Let me, uh...

186
00:09:55,873 --> 00:10:00,209
Scofield said that it would
deliver me. Both of us.

187
00:10:00,244 --> 00:10:02,378
All I have to do

188
00:10:02,413 --> 00:10:04,213
is just get it to him.

189
00:10:04,248 --> 00:10:06,882
I understand why.

190
00:10:09,382 --> 00:10:11,165
So I can finally understand this.

191
00:10:14,425 --> 00:10:16,292
He give you this?

192
00:10:16,327 --> 00:10:18,761
"By your hand, you shall know

193
00:10:18,796 --> 00:10:20,263
the glories of your progeny..."

194
00:10:20,298 --> 00:10:21,664
I-It's, it's...

195
00:10:21,699 --> 00:10:24,300
It's "progeny," dear boy.

196
00:10:25,436 --> 00:10:27,568
"Progeny.

197
00:10:27,602 --> 00:10:29,969
And our world will be
made right forevermore."

198
00:10:29,975 --> 00:10:31,621
Originally, I thought
it was a religious thing.

199
00:10:31,623 --> 00:10:33,240
You know, son of God, and all that.

200
00:10:33,243 --> 00:10:34,978
But now I know it's...

201
00:10:35,013 --> 00:10:39,115
it's my own progeny.

202
00:10:40,218 --> 00:10:41,550
You.

203
00:10:47,965 --> 00:10:51,294
It's a glorious thing indeed.

204
00:10:51,329 --> 00:10:54,663
Even if I don't have a damn
clue how to deal with it.

205
00:10:56,667 --> 00:10:59,101
You and me both.

206
00:11:03,991 --> 00:11:05,423
I've got a way to get

207
00:11:05,446 --> 00:11:07,377
our son back, Sara.

208
00:11:07,412 --> 00:11:09,278
I've been planning to bring Jacob down

209
00:11:09,313 --> 00:11:14,183
ever since he forced me to
turn my back on you and Mike.

210
00:11:14,218 --> 00:11:15,451
A plan I had to put on hold

211
00:11:15,486 --> 00:11:17,954
while I was in that Yemeni prison.

212
00:11:17,989 --> 00:11:21,157
I had to wait till I got out.

213
00:11:24,095 --> 00:11:25,628
Till everything aligned.

214
00:11:29,233 --> 00:11:31,801
Till now.

215
00:11:45,883 --> 00:11:47,603
Tell me you got something.

216
00:11:47,618 --> 00:11:50,153
It's eluding me.

217
00:11:50,188 --> 00:11:54,323
There's an even bigger code
encrypted into the eyes.

218
00:11:54,358 --> 00:11:55,892
And what's it say?

219
00:11:55,927 --> 00:11:57,894
I don't know yet.

220
00:11:57,929 --> 00:12:00,215
But with the amount of
processing power I throw at it,

221
00:12:00,218 --> 00:12:02,171
we're gonna find out real soon.

222
00:12:15,713 --> 00:12:17,313
What's wrong?

223
00:12:19,250 --> 00:12:22,018
I-I don't know how to say it, so, um...

224
00:12:22,053 --> 00:12:24,220
That man was a police detective,

225
00:12:24,255 --> 00:12:27,023
and he told me your moth...

226
00:12:27,058 --> 00:12:28,691
your mother's dead.

227
00:12:29,794 --> 00:12:31,094
What?

228
00:12:31,129 --> 00:12:33,029
I know. I know.

229
00:12:33,064 --> 00:12:35,398
But I'm gonna take you somewhere safe,

230
00:12:35,433 --> 00:12:37,667
where those people that
are trying to hurt you

231
00:12:37,702 --> 00:12:39,135
can't reach you.

232
00:12:39,170 --> 00:12:40,436
Why would they try and hurt me?

233
00:12:40,471 --> 00:12:42,472
It's because I love you.

234
00:12:42,507 --> 00:12:44,132
And they're trying to hurt me...

235
00:12:44,164 --> 00:12:46,627
Take the one thing
that I truly love away.

236
00:12:46,662 --> 00:12:48,820
Why would they try and hurt you?

237
00:12:53,351 --> 00:12:54,717
Because there are some things

238
00:12:54,752 --> 00:12:56,852
I haven't told you about me.

239
00:12:59,179 --> 00:13:01,457
I sent that letter to you for a reason.

240
00:13:01,492 --> 00:13:03,493
Poseidon was monitoring
my communications

241
00:13:03,528 --> 00:13:05,655
with everyone who could
possibly be a resource

242
00:13:05,671 --> 00:13:07,263
or an ally, but not with people

243
00:13:07,298 --> 00:13:10,366
I despised.

244
00:13:10,401 --> 00:13:13,402
Give it to me straight...
How you really feel about me?

245
00:13:14,590 --> 00:13:16,313
I figured if I showed grace to a man

246
00:13:16,324 --> 00:13:17,934
who'd never seen it before in his life,

247
00:13:17,937 --> 00:13:19,207
maybe he'd be grateful,

248
00:13:19,210 --> 00:13:20,810
do something for us.

249
00:13:20,845 --> 00:13:22,706
All of us,

250
00:13:22,721 --> 00:13:24,814
himself included.

251
00:13:24,849 --> 00:13:28,354
"And our lives shall be
made right forevermore."

252
00:13:28,361 --> 00:13:30,581
I'm talking about normal, everyday life.

253
00:13:30,584 --> 00:13:34,375
The kind of freedom none of us
has known in a long, long time.

254
00:13:35,130 --> 00:13:37,064
But Poseidon's not just gonna let us go.

255
00:13:37,094 --> 00:13:39,281
He's got me and your son

256
00:13:39,309 --> 00:13:40,726
in an iron grip.

257
00:13:40,746 --> 00:13:43,680
Someone has to make him let go.

258
00:13:43,711 --> 00:13:46,636
Do you understand?

259
00:13:46,671 --> 00:13:48,538
I'm tracking where you're going.

260
00:13:50,975 --> 00:13:52,875
Only way we're gonna get

261
00:13:52,910 --> 00:13:54,777
that beautiful, mundane life

262
00:13:54,812 --> 00:13:57,180
you're talking... Any of us...

263
00:13:57,215 --> 00:13:59,648
Is if I take his.

264
00:14:14,244 --> 00:14:16,461
We'll be safe here for now.

265
00:14:16,489 --> 00:14:18,122
Hey, listen,

266
00:14:18,148 --> 00:14:20,649
I promised I'd explain.

267
00:14:20,684 --> 00:14:22,518
The reason those people are after me...

268
00:14:22,553 --> 00:14:24,620
I know this is gonna be hard to believe,

269
00:14:24,655 --> 00:14:28,890
but I'm basically a secret agent.

270
00:14:41,872 --> 00:14:43,572
Come on in.

271
00:14:45,409 --> 00:14:49,044
You know that fort you've
got in the backyard?

272
00:14:49,079 --> 00:14:52,314
It feels good to go
somewhere like that, right?

273
00:14:52,349 --> 00:14:56,952
A place no one knows about,
where no one can get to you.

274
00:14:56,987 --> 00:14:59,955
Well, that's what this place is for me.

275
00:15:02,593 --> 00:15:04,493
It's okay.

276
00:15:04,528 --> 00:15:05,728
It's okay.

277
00:15:05,763 --> 00:15:06,795
Would you please show him

278
00:15:06,830 --> 00:15:08,030
your credentials, Agent Blake?

279
00:15:08,065 --> 00:15:11,600
Agent Emily Blake, CIA.

280
00:15:11,635 --> 00:15:12,801
I'm sorry that had to happen

281
00:15:12,836 --> 00:15:14,837
in front of you at the house.

282
00:15:14,872 --> 00:15:17,606
She was stationed at the
house to protect you...

283
00:15:17,641 --> 00:15:20,109
from exactly the man
who ended up coming,

284
00:15:20,144 --> 00:15:21,420
the man who said

285
00:15:21,444 --> 00:15:22,811
he was your dad.

286
00:15:22,846 --> 00:15:24,389
Really?

287
00:15:35,826 --> 00:15:38,894
I've made enemies defending
America over the years.

288
00:15:38,929 --> 00:15:40,462
Worst part is that this

289
00:15:40,497 --> 00:15:43,165
particular one dredged up
the memory of your father.

290
00:15:45,068 --> 00:15:46,969
The truth is, Mikey,

291
00:15:47,004 --> 00:15:50,243
despite what you may want
to believe, your father died

292
00:15:50,274 --> 00:15:51,907
seven years ago.

293
00:15:55,379 --> 00:15:57,012
Yeah.

294
00:15:57,047 --> 00:15:59,314
This is Michael Scofield.

295
00:16:02,653 --> 00:16:04,853
We were just talking about you.

296
00:16:04,888 --> 00:16:07,489
I'm giving you one last
chance to save your life.

297
00:16:07,524 --> 00:16:10,359
Hand the boy over or I
can't be held responsible

298
00:16:10,394 --> 00:16:11,726
for what happens next.

299
00:16:11,761 --> 00:16:13,144
Are you threatening my life?

300
00:16:13,175 --> 00:16:14,930
Only if you don't hand him over.

301
00:16:14,965 --> 00:16:17,499
I'd never hand over my son.

302
00:16:17,534 --> 00:16:20,269
He's not your son and never was.

303
00:16:20,304 --> 00:16:22,204
Stay away from my dad,

304
00:16:22,239 --> 00:16:23,839
you hear?

305
00:16:23,874 --> 00:16:25,874
Stay away!

306
00:16:29,112 --> 00:16:31,079
Good boy.

307
00:16:39,185 --> 00:16:41,390
He called him Dad.

308
00:16:41,425 --> 00:16:43,025
Jacob.

309
00:16:43,060 --> 00:16:46,208
No, he's-he's brainwashing
him, that's all.

310
00:16:46,239 --> 00:16:48,597
Man like that, you're right.

311
00:16:50,133 --> 00:16:53,335
He deserves to die.

312
00:16:53,370 --> 00:16:55,505
Where is he?

313
00:16:55,537 --> 00:16:57,606
Where is Poseidon?

314
00:16:57,641 --> 00:16:58,874
He'll be dealt with.

315
00:16:58,909 --> 00:17:00,876
Wait, hang on, hang on, hang on, man.

316
00:17:00,911 --> 00:17:02,619
If you get caught...

317
00:17:02,654 --> 00:17:04,813
If he gets caught, he's
going back to the pen.

318
00:17:04,848 --> 00:17:06,181
- Come on, come on.
- I'm not...

319
00:17:06,183 --> 00:17:07,583
And if I don't do it?

320
00:17:07,618 --> 00:17:09,485
Criminy, I want you free and clear,

321
00:17:09,520 --> 00:17:10,886
and if that's the only way to do it,

322
00:17:10,888 --> 00:17:12,053
then I got to be the one that does it.

323
00:17:12,055 --> 00:17:13,188
Scofield ain't gonna do it.

324
00:17:13,223 --> 00:17:14,456
He don't got the killing gene.

325
00:17:14,491 --> 00:17:15,824
No one is getting caught.

326
00:17:15,859 --> 00:17:17,631
There's a very specific order to this.

327
00:17:19,696 --> 00:17:22,498
Sara, I want you to make sure

328
00:17:22,533 --> 00:17:25,534
Linc's safe and out of harm's way.

329
00:17:25,569 --> 00:17:28,403
Whip, T-Bag, you're gonna
collect a wild card for us.

330
00:17:28,438 --> 00:17:31,206
One that Jacob doesn't
know is out there.

331
00:17:31,241 --> 00:17:34,324
I'm gonna go to the nest,
where this all started,

332
00:17:34,347 --> 00:17:37,513
where the secrets lay hidden,

333
00:17:37,548 --> 00:17:40,916
and where blood will finally be
spilled in its rightful place.

334
00:17:44,086 --> 00:17:45,916
The call I just got from Scofield...

335
00:17:45,938 --> 00:17:47,823
I want to know where it came from.

336
00:17:47,858 --> 00:17:49,424
Location data

337
00:17:49,459 --> 00:17:51,960
coming to you right now.

338
00:17:51,995 --> 00:17:53,762
Middle of nowhere.

339
00:17:53,797 --> 00:17:56,965
Started moving northeast
and the phone was shut off.

340
00:17:57,000 --> 00:17:59,100
Maybe tossed.

341
00:18:06,043 --> 00:18:07,843
You and your damn zoo, Scofield.

342
00:18:07,878 --> 00:18:10,495
I'm gonna find out once and for all

343
00:18:10,513 --> 00:18:12,346
what you were really doing there.

344
00:18:12,378 --> 00:18:14,116
What you were really planning.

345
00:18:14,151 --> 00:18:16,261
And then I'm gonna kill you.

346
00:18:27,030 --> 00:18:29,264
I know everything about you.

347
00:18:29,299 --> 00:18:31,300
Even your most mundane actions.

348
00:18:31,335 --> 00:18:34,836
Like the zoo. What's
with you and the zoo?

349
00:18:51,054 --> 00:18:52,588
I had to know everything about the man

350
00:18:52,623 --> 00:18:54,723
who wore his plans on his skin.

351
00:18:54,758 --> 00:18:56,051
In plain sight, yet

352
00:18:56,059 --> 00:18:57,903
so mysterious.

353
00:19:24,388 --> 00:19:27,022
The secret to real power

354
00:19:27,057 --> 00:19:29,224
is to never betray your intentions.

355
00:19:29,259 --> 00:19:31,526
To wear nothing on your sleeve,

356
00:19:31,561 --> 00:19:34,863
and to never let anyone see your face.

357
00:19:37,598 --> 00:19:39,302
_

358
00:19:39,337 --> 00:19:43,305
I'll always be a step ahead of you.

359
00:19:43,340 --> 00:19:45,440
I can see everything in your eyes.

360
00:19:49,846 --> 00:19:51,446
What?

361
00:19:51,481 --> 00:19:53,115
I decrypted the code from the eyes.

362
00:19:53,150 --> 00:19:56,084
It's a quote from Napoleon.

363
00:19:56,116 --> 00:19:57,552
What quote?

364
00:19:57,587 --> 00:19:59,121
"Never interrupt your enemy

365
00:19:59,156 --> 00:20:01,289
when he's making a mistake."

366
00:20:11,201 --> 00:20:14,235
It's what's behind the eyes that counts.

367
00:20:37,432 --> 00:20:38,765
Yeah.

368
00:20:38,800 --> 00:20:42,135
Thought you should know I'm looking
at your closed servers right now.

369
00:20:42,170 --> 00:20:44,604
I'm holding your hard drives in my hand.

370
00:20:44,639 --> 00:20:46,639
All your secret communications.

371
00:20:46,674 --> 00:20:49,442
Enough to send you away forever.

372
00:20:49,477 --> 00:20:50,977
Bravo, Michael.

373
00:20:51,012 --> 00:20:52,512
However you got in there, bravo.

374
00:20:52,547 --> 00:20:54,747
You sent me to the zoo
so you could get into

375
00:20:54,782 --> 00:20:57,317
my office. But you and I both
know your threat's a hollow one,

376
00:20:57,352 --> 00:20:58,918
because you know I've got something

377
00:20:58,953 --> 00:21:01,421
that's even more
valuable to you: your son.

378
00:21:01,456 --> 00:21:03,189
So we're back to game theory.

379
00:21:03,224 --> 00:21:04,958
Do we work together, make a trade

380
00:21:04,993 --> 00:21:06,392
so we both get what we want?

381
00:21:06,427 --> 00:21:07,960
Or are you gonna try
something underhanded?

382
00:21:07,962 --> 00:21:09,195
You know I will.

383
00:21:09,230 --> 00:21:10,964
As will I. So why don't we

384
00:21:10,999 --> 00:21:12,432
cut past that and make a deal?

385
00:21:12,458 --> 00:21:14,119
Sure, Michael. Yeah,

386
00:21:14,144 --> 00:21:15,076
let's do that.

387
00:21:15,087 --> 00:21:16,269
Old shipyard.

388
00:21:16,304 --> 00:21:17,570
Warehouse A.

389
00:21:17,605 --> 00:21:18,938
5:00 p.m. tomorrow.

390
00:21:18,973 --> 00:21:20,439
Fine.

391
00:21:26,194 --> 00:21:28,381
Uh, excuse me?

392
00:21:28,416 --> 00:21:30,917
My brother-in-law...
did-did Lincoln Burrows,

393
00:21:30,952 --> 00:21:32,218
did he get moved?

394
00:21:32,253 --> 00:21:33,720
No, ma'am. He checked himself out.

395
00:21:33,755 --> 00:21:35,855
- He was down a lot of blood.
- I know.

396
00:21:35,890 --> 00:21:37,790
We tried to stop him,
but if a patient insists,

397
00:21:37,825 --> 00:21:40,026
if it's within their power,
we have to let 'em go.

398
00:21:40,061 --> 00:21:41,327
Uh, this is Dr. Ballard.

399
00:21:41,362 --> 00:21:42,793
- He did the surgery.
- Hi,

400
00:21:42,796 --> 00:21:44,931
Sara Scofield, I'm an internist,
actually, up at Ithaca.

401
00:21:44,933 --> 00:21:47,670
Do you have any idea where my
brother-in-law might have gone?

402
00:21:47,673 --> 00:21:49,402
- No idea.
- Right.

403
00:21:49,437 --> 00:21:50,988
What happened up in Finger Lakes,

404
00:21:50,991 --> 00:21:52,491
do you know? Another gunshot victim

405
00:21:52,526 --> 00:21:54,393
came in from the same area

406
00:21:54,423 --> 00:21:55,641
at the same time.

407
00:21:56,876 --> 00:21:59,178
My brother-in-law was alone.
It must be a coincidence.

408
00:21:59,180 --> 00:22:00,847
But thank you.

409
00:22:00,882 --> 00:22:02,602
Well, I'm heading out.
I've done what I can.

410
00:22:02,617 --> 00:22:04,484
He's on life support up on three,

411
00:22:04,519 --> 00:22:07,119
but candidly, I don't think
he's making it till morning.

412
00:22:31,245 --> 00:22:32,378
Luca.

413
00:22:36,150 --> 00:22:38,051
You had me running there for a bit,

414
00:22:38,054 --> 00:22:39,660
thinking I'd done something wrong.

415
00:22:39,695 --> 00:22:43,089
You did. You stiffed me $100 grand.

416
00:22:43,124 --> 00:22:44,958
Nah. It's blood money.

417
00:22:44,993 --> 00:22:46,826
No debts with blood money.

418
00:22:47,929 --> 00:22:50,062
Say we're clear.

419
00:22:52,233 --> 00:22:53,232
Eat me, Burrows.

420
00:22:58,239 --> 00:22:59,942
Say we're clear.

421
00:22:59,974 --> 00:23:02,642
I'm gonna get more guys.

422
00:23:02,677 --> 00:23:04,911
And you're gonna be running again.

423
00:23:06,214 --> 00:23:07,480
Not this time.

424
00:23:08,734 --> 00:23:10,491
Are those your fake friends again?

425
00:23:10,510 --> 00:23:11,985
You son of a bitch.

426
00:23:12,020 --> 00:23:13,486
No. This time,

427
00:23:13,521 --> 00:23:15,288
they're real.

428
00:23:17,458 --> 00:23:18,691
Federal agents!

429
00:23:18,726 --> 00:23:20,393
Hands where I can see 'em!

430
00:23:20,428 --> 00:23:21,694
- Hands up!
- Burrows!

431
00:23:21,729 --> 00:23:22,862
Do it now!

432
00:23:22,897 --> 00:23:24,563
Burrows!

433
00:23:36,411 --> 00:23:38,678
I need your help.

434
00:23:38,713 --> 00:23:41,180
I need to find my boy.

435
00:23:52,292 --> 00:23:54,625
Here.

436
00:24:08,276 --> 00:24:10,943
He's an evil man and he's got my son.

437
00:24:10,978 --> 00:24:12,586
You've got to know someone.

438
00:24:12,626 --> 00:24:13,826
Something.

439
00:24:13,845 --> 00:24:16,912
Some way I can get my boy back.

440
00:24:21,556 --> 00:24:22,655
Please.

441
00:24:40,608 --> 00:24:42,842
You sure this is where my son is?

442
00:24:42,877 --> 00:24:44,243
Uh-huh.

443
00:24:48,254 --> 00:24:50,287
Thank you.

444
00:25:08,736 --> 00:25:10,970
It's all right.

445
00:25:13,441 --> 00:25:14,774
Killing ain't right.

446
00:25:14,809 --> 00:25:16,008
Yeah, I read the Bible.

447
00:25:16,043 --> 00:25:17,076
You did?

448
00:25:17,111 --> 00:25:18,945
You know, I scanned it
once in a hotel room.

449
00:25:18,980 --> 00:25:20,513
Well, what you gonna do?

450
00:25:20,548 --> 00:25:22,181
Don't kill anybody unless
they really deserve it.

451
00:25:22,183 --> 00:25:23,415
Yeah, you must've read
the Old Testament part.

452
00:25:23,417 --> 00:25:24,977
An eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth.

453
00:25:24,986 --> 00:25:26,018
Sure, whatever.

454
00:25:26,053 --> 00:25:27,320
Yeah, I'm just saying,

455
00:25:27,355 --> 00:25:29,989
sometimes, certain...
Certain sons of bitches,

456
00:25:30,024 --> 00:25:31,858
they just need to be
plain old eradicated.

457
00:25:31,893 --> 00:25:33,626
- Mm-hmm.
- World's just better minus them.

458
00:25:33,661 --> 00:25:35,528
Like Abu Ramal.

459
00:25:35,563 --> 00:25:37,897
But for the most part, you
know, killing's just bad.

460
00:25:37,932 --> 00:25:39,499
Yeah, absolutely.

461
00:25:39,534 --> 00:25:41,834
Except Poseidon.

462
00:25:41,869 --> 00:25:43,469
- Yeah, he's got to go, too.
- Got to go.

463
00:25:43,504 --> 00:25:44,870
I just don't want you
to get the wrong idea

464
00:25:44,872 --> 00:25:46,139
- about me, okay?
- Okay.

465
00:25:46,174 --> 00:25:48,241
You got to see it like the yogis, okay?

466
00:25:48,276 --> 00:25:51,410
Destroying the negative
to create the positive.

467
00:25:51,445 --> 00:25:54,413
The dance of the Shivas and all that.

468
00:25:54,448 --> 00:25:56,982
Murder the dark, so the...
The light can be born.

469
00:25:58,553 --> 00:26:00,253
You're out of your
damn tree, aren't you?

470
00:26:00,288 --> 00:26:02,454
- Now you know where you got it from.
- Great.

471
00:26:03,858 --> 00:26:05,525
Is there a BlueHawaii in there?

472
00:26:05,560 --> 00:26:07,993
Yeah, don't just dillydally, come on in.

473
00:26:09,530 --> 00:26:13,232
I assume you two desperados
are Scofield's guys.

474
00:26:13,267 --> 00:26:15,167
Yeah.

475
00:26:16,588 --> 00:26:18,155
He get you out of prison, too?

476
00:26:18,158 --> 00:26:19,288
No.

477
00:26:19,291 --> 00:26:21,507
But I do owe him.

478
00:26:21,542 --> 00:26:23,176
Where'd he break you out of?

479
00:26:23,211 --> 00:26:25,478
Barranquilla, South America.

480
00:26:25,513 --> 00:26:27,547
They were gonna eat my lunch down there,

481
00:26:27,582 --> 00:26:29,549
pretty boy like me.

482
00:26:29,584 --> 00:26:32,685
Scofield took pity.

483
00:26:32,720 --> 00:26:35,187
Saw a talent in me, I guess. Got me out.

484
00:26:36,791 --> 00:26:39,025
Said he might call on those
talents some day in return,

485
00:26:39,060 --> 00:26:40,632
and now here we are.

486
00:26:41,562 --> 00:26:44,030
Soon as I put the touches on this,

487
00:26:44,065 --> 00:26:45,798
I'm yours. Got bored waiting.

488
00:26:45,833 --> 00:26:47,433
It's incredible.

489
00:26:47,468 --> 00:26:50,102
Rebuild of Dealey Plaza,

490
00:26:50,137 --> 00:26:52,738
where JFK was shot.

491
00:26:52,773 --> 00:26:54,607
This here

492
00:26:54,642 --> 00:26:57,033
is a book depository.

493
00:26:57,036 --> 00:26:58,811
Attention to detail like that,

494
00:26:58,846 --> 00:26:59,946
drive a man crazy.

495
00:26:59,981 --> 00:27:02,849
Look at me. I'm a crap house loon.

496
00:27:02,884 --> 00:27:04,283
Excessive need to bring the past

497
00:27:04,318 --> 00:27:06,786
back to life.

498
00:27:06,821 --> 00:27:08,654
Make it real.

499
00:27:11,456 --> 00:27:13,957
But enough of that.

500
00:27:15,796 --> 00:27:18,264
Time for the real dance
to begin, am I right?

501
00:27:23,414 --> 00:27:25,111
We're going to get him back, okay?

502
00:27:25,139 --> 00:27:27,546
We got your wild card ready to go.

503
00:27:30,611 --> 00:27:32,378
Thank you.

504
00:27:33,547 --> 00:27:34,947
Me that should be thanking you.

505
00:27:34,982 --> 00:27:36,349
You brought me all this way.

506
00:27:36,384 --> 00:27:37,617
We did it together.

507
00:27:37,652 --> 00:27:39,451
We'll be doing this together.

508
00:27:41,489 --> 00:27:43,856
You gave me family.

509
00:27:43,891 --> 00:27:45,357
Seriously, thank you.

510
00:27:47,288 --> 00:27:48,621
Speaking of family...

511
00:27:53,134 --> 00:27:54,967
Let's go.

512
00:27:56,824 --> 00:27:59,527
_

513
00:28:00,708 --> 00:28:03,409
Don't touch that, please.

514
00:28:03,444 --> 00:28:06,178
It's not an option right now.

515
00:28:27,935 --> 00:28:30,002
Now where is my son?

516
00:28:30,037 --> 00:28:32,872
You ask questions you know
there isn't a chance in hell

517
00:28:32,907 --> 00:28:34,240
I'm gonna answer.

518
00:28:34,275 --> 00:28:36,042
So we're back to the game.

519
00:28:36,077 --> 00:28:38,678
The truth is, we never left.

520
00:28:38,713 --> 00:28:40,246
You're not holding the cards.

521
00:28:40,281 --> 00:28:42,315
- I am.
- Are you?

522
00:28:42,350 --> 00:28:45,184
Every law agency in the
world is looking for you.

523
00:28:45,219 --> 00:28:47,486
Doesn't sound like a
position of power to me.

524
00:28:47,521 --> 00:28:50,122
If I get arrested, those
servers will be released,

525
00:28:50,157 --> 00:28:52,291
and everything you've
done will be exposed.

526
00:28:52,326 --> 00:28:54,720
I'll find them. I'll destroy them.

527
00:28:54,752 --> 00:28:56,729
Like I said,

528
00:28:56,764 --> 00:28:58,864
I'm holding the cards.

529
00:28:58,899 --> 00:29:01,133
Whoa!

530
00:29:01,168 --> 00:29:02,868
Didn't expect that.

531
00:29:02,903 --> 00:29:04,754
It's beneath you, Michael.

532
00:29:04,757 --> 00:29:06,939
Let him go!

533
00:29:12,249 --> 00:29:15,681
Now that, I expected.

534
00:29:15,716 --> 00:29:17,883
Thank you.

535
00:29:19,421 --> 00:29:21,654
How about we drop it, lady?

536
00:29:21,689 --> 00:29:23,923
You don't think I expected this?

537
00:29:23,958 --> 00:29:25,858
We could do this all day.

538
00:29:25,893 --> 00:29:27,995
Play contingency after contingency.

539
00:29:28,018 --> 00:29:29,551
But do you really want to do that?

540
00:29:29,581 --> 00:29:30,596
Ah!

541
00:29:30,631 --> 00:29:32,365
No! David. Dammit!

542
00:29:32,400 --> 00:29:34,734
Back off, or I kill him right now.

543
00:29:34,769 --> 00:29:37,159
And that must be

544
00:29:37,190 --> 00:29:39,305
the last of your contingencies.

545
00:29:39,340 --> 00:29:41,374
Thank you so much for
showing me, Michael.

546
00:29:43,444 --> 00:29:44,877
Oh, yeah.

547
00:29:44,912 --> 00:29:47,179
You should also know I called the FBI.

548
00:29:47,214 --> 00:29:49,682
An anonymous tip saying

549
00:29:49,717 --> 00:29:52,151
that Kaniel Outis would
be at this warehouse.

550
00:30:13,774 --> 00:30:15,841
Keep clear. Moving to second position.

551
00:30:15,876 --> 00:30:17,243
Okay,

552
00:30:17,278 --> 00:30:19,278
they're in the building.
There's no more time.

553
00:30:19,313 --> 00:30:20,980
The hard drives, or we'll start shooting

554
00:30:21,015 --> 00:30:22,281
- your pieces.
- Hand over

555
00:30:22,316 --> 00:30:23,282
the damn boy!

556
00:30:23,317 --> 00:30:25,251
Shut up.

557
00:30:25,286 --> 00:30:27,486
Lady, put the gun down, walk away,

558
00:30:27,521 --> 00:30:29,488
as I cannot be held accountable
for what's about to happen.

559
00:30:29,490 --> 00:30:31,057
- He moves, shoot him!
- I killed a guy

560
00:30:31,092 --> 00:30:32,758
in a bar fight once. He
was taking yang to my girl.

561
00:30:32,760 --> 00:30:35,361
- Took me one second to do it.
- Don't do it!

562
00:30:35,396 --> 00:30:37,096
Should listen to him. He's a very smart man.

563
00:30:37,131 --> 00:30:38,297
I'm talking to you, Whip.

564
00:30:39,934 --> 00:30:42,160
It's not worth dying
for. This is my fight!

565
00:30:42,179 --> 00:30:44,432
This is our fight. We've
come too far to let this

566
00:30:44,435 --> 00:30:45,336
son of a bitch win.

567
00:30:45,339 --> 00:30:46,639
This wasn't the plan!

568
00:30:46,674 --> 00:30:47,540
Don't do it!

569
00:30:47,575 --> 00:30:48,807
Some sons of bitches just got to go!

570
00:30:48,809 --> 00:30:50,109
We're the only ones who could do it.

571
00:30:50,111 --> 00:30:51,518
- Ain't that right, Pa?
- David!

572
00:30:51,521 --> 00:30:52,687
Try me.

573
00:30:59,087 --> 00:31:00,486
Whip!

574
00:31:03,757 --> 00:31:05,324
No!

575
00:31:08,129 --> 00:31:10,362
- Whip. Whip.
- No.

576
00:31:10,397 --> 00:31:12,465
Come on. Whip.

577
00:31:12,500 --> 00:31:14,166
This wasn't the plan.

578
00:31:14,201 --> 00:31:16,001
David, stay with me.

579
00:31:16,036 --> 00:31:17,436
Stay with me, boy. Stay with me.

580
00:31:17,471 --> 00:31:20,176
The hard drives. Now.

581
00:31:24,278 --> 00:31:26,512
I got him. It's okay, I got him.

582
00:31:28,362 --> 00:31:29,728
All right.

583
00:31:31,485 --> 00:31:32,818
Okay, okay...

584
00:31:37,291 --> 00:31:38,790
It's that way.

585
00:31:41,792 --> 00:31:43,626
Keep it calm, boy.

586
00:31:46,122 --> 00:31:48,322
- Stay calm.
- If he tries to play hero, too,

587
00:31:48,325 --> 00:31:51,370
execute him.

588
00:31:54,542 --> 00:31:55,774
David...

589
00:31:57,211 --> 00:31:59,745
You shot him, you bitch.

590
00:31:59,780 --> 00:32:01,247
He shouldn't have tried me.

591
00:32:01,282 --> 00:32:03,182
- David...
- Hands up! Freeze!

592
00:32:03,217 --> 00:32:05,017
Do it now! Federal agents!

593
00:32:14,461 --> 00:32:15,961
Federal agents!

594
00:32:15,996 --> 00:32:18,564
Hands where I can see them!

595
00:32:21,368 --> 00:32:22,635
I'm...

596
00:32:22,670 --> 00:32:24,603
I'm good. I got to s...

597
00:32:24,638 --> 00:32:26,738
see your face.

598
00:32:28,008 --> 00:32:30,609
Freeze! Get your hands up!

599
00:32:32,246 --> 00:32:34,027
Go easy, son.

600
00:33:07,129 --> 00:33:08,729
How we doing?

601
00:33:08,764 --> 00:33:10,631
Hey.

602
00:33:10,666 --> 00:33:12,299
Better than you.

603
00:33:16,320 --> 00:33:18,187
Oh, thank God.

604
00:33:18,222 --> 00:33:20,089
You okay?

605
00:33:20,124 --> 00:33:22,457
Oh.

606
00:33:26,063 --> 00:33:29,264
Up ahead, in the next bay.

607
00:33:32,865 --> 00:33:34,798
I'll take that call.

608
00:33:36,561 --> 00:33:39,274
We got him, Michael. We got our boy.

609
00:33:44,214 --> 00:33:46,749
Good news for you.

610
00:33:46,784 --> 00:33:49,852
But now you've got no reason
to give me what I want.

611
00:33:49,887 --> 00:33:52,821
Which kind of makes it bad news for you.

612
00:33:54,892 --> 00:33:56,158
Federal agents!

613
00:34:22,519 --> 00:34:24,152
You son of a bitch.

614
00:34:34,298 --> 00:34:35,697
The cabin.

615
00:34:43,440 --> 00:34:45,336
Gaines' jacket.

616
00:34:47,284 --> 00:34:49,451
Camera, taking my picture.

617
00:34:54,751 --> 00:34:56,117
Blanks.

618
00:34:57,622 --> 00:35:00,388
You wanted me to take the
gun from you back there.

619
00:35:01,840 --> 00:35:03,273
You're better than I thought.

620
00:35:03,295 --> 00:35:06,527
Re-framing me for the
murder I actually committed.

621
00:35:06,530 --> 00:35:08,730
The one you framed me for.

622
00:35:08,765 --> 00:35:11,099
Michael, pick up the body,

623
00:35:11,134 --> 00:35:12,601
make it look like it never happened.

624
00:35:12,636 --> 00:35:14,636
Genius, really.

625
00:35:14,671 --> 00:35:16,429
But no one will ever go for it.

626
00:35:16,452 --> 00:35:18,960
The truth is whatever
you tell people it is.

627
00:35:21,345 --> 00:35:22,911
You taught me that.

628
00:35:22,946 --> 00:35:25,147
Oh. Too bad the feds'll be here

629
00:35:25,182 --> 00:35:26,682
in two minutes, see your little

630
00:35:26,717 --> 00:35:28,817
diorama here, and know it's all bull.

631
00:35:28,852 --> 00:35:30,986
Except none of this will be here.

632
00:35:31,021 --> 00:35:32,754
And neither will I.

633
00:35:37,845 --> 00:35:39,461
Bastard!

634
00:36:17,067 --> 00:36:18,934
Aah!

635
00:36:30,058 --> 00:36:32,514
This is for the last seven years.

636
00:36:36,653 --> 00:36:39,121
Freeze! Get your hands up!

637
00:36:39,156 --> 00:36:40,489
Put 'em up!

638
00:36:40,524 --> 00:36:44,359
It's him! It's Kaniel Outis!

639
00:36:44,394 --> 00:36:46,295
Thank God you're here.

640
00:36:46,330 --> 00:36:47,996
Thank God!

641
00:36:48,031 --> 00:36:50,165
Thank God.

642
00:36:50,200 --> 00:36:51,803
Thank God.

643
00:36:51,832 --> 00:36:53,164
Hands up!

644
00:37:04,514 --> 00:37:06,548
Thank God you guys
got here when you did,

645
00:37:06,583 --> 00:37:08,011
that's all I can say.

646
00:37:08,027 --> 00:37:09,785
I mean, he would have...

647
00:37:09,820 --> 00:37:11,653
I'd be dead right now.

648
00:37:11,688 --> 00:37:14,222
Look, if it's okay with you
guys, I'd like to go home,

649
00:37:14,257 --> 00:37:16,825
clean myself up a bit.
As you can imagine,

650
00:37:16,860 --> 00:37:18,427
it's been a long day.

651
00:37:18,462 --> 00:37:19,695
That's okay.

652
00:37:19,730 --> 00:37:21,229
Thank you.

653
00:37:22,966 --> 00:37:25,046
Jacob Anton Ness?

654
00:37:25,062 --> 00:37:26,367
Can I help you?

655
00:37:26,367 --> 00:37:28,837
You're under arrest for the
participation in the murder

656
00:37:28,839 --> 00:37:30,839
- of Harlan Gaines.
- If you're talking about that nonsense

657
00:37:30,841 --> 00:37:31,940
- in there...
- We're talking about blood evidence

658
00:37:31,942 --> 00:37:33,211
found in your office

659
00:37:33,214 --> 00:37:35,177
at the university. An office

660
00:37:35,212 --> 00:37:36,745
only you have access to.

661
00:37:36,780 --> 00:37:38,380
Harlan Gaines' blood.

662
00:37:38,415 --> 00:37:39,748
And blood will finally

663
00:37:39,783 --> 00:37:42,717
be spilled in its rightful place.

664
00:37:46,223 --> 00:37:48,256
What? How...

665
00:37:57,598 --> 00:38:00,345
These are the missing frames
from the night of the killing.

666
00:38:00,348 --> 00:38:02,013
The ones Poseidon edited out.

667
00:38:02,048 --> 00:38:04,248
Yes, I was there. I've never denied it.

668
00:38:04,283 --> 00:38:06,284
He forced me to...

669
00:38:06,319 --> 00:38:09,153
so he could frame me.

670
00:38:09,188 --> 00:38:11,589
So the blood evidence
found in your belongings

671
00:38:11,624 --> 00:38:14,632
was because he tasked you
with disposing of the body.

672
00:38:14,663 --> 00:38:17,061
Correct.

673
00:38:17,096 --> 00:38:19,697
And with the revelation of
the additional blood evidence

674
00:38:19,732 --> 00:38:22,033
found in his office at the university,

675
00:38:22,068 --> 00:38:25,336
it neatly supports
your theory, doesn't it?

676
00:38:25,371 --> 00:38:27,505
That he was there.

677
00:38:27,540 --> 00:38:29,273
That he was the gunman.

678
00:38:29,308 --> 00:38:33,177
I guess I would have
one question for you.

679
00:38:36,549 --> 00:38:38,483
I'm director of the CIA.

680
00:38:38,518 --> 00:38:40,818
I'm aware of that. That's
why I sent you the e-mail

681
00:38:40,853 --> 00:38:42,320
with the evidence directly.

682
00:38:42,355 --> 00:38:44,655
My question is...

683
00:38:44,690 --> 00:38:46,557
would you be manipulating me, too?

684
00:38:46,592 --> 00:38:48,025
How would I do that?

685
00:38:48,060 --> 00:38:51,162
Well...

686
00:38:51,197 --> 00:38:53,331
you look too closely at this evidence...

687
00:38:53,366 --> 00:38:56,567
Metadata in the pictures,
degraded blood evidence...

688
00:38:56,602 --> 00:38:58,002
You might find some problems.

689
00:38:58,037 --> 00:39:00,338
Depends how motivated
you are to look closely.

690
00:39:00,373 --> 00:39:02,340
Poseidon killed your deputy director.

691
00:39:02,375 --> 00:39:05,376
He was a cancer inside
your agency for years.

692
00:39:05,411 --> 00:39:07,145
I've shown you his face!

693
00:39:07,180 --> 00:39:09,914
Now, calm down.

694
00:39:09,949 --> 00:39:12,717
You should know that we
have Mr. Ness' accomplice,

695
00:39:12,752 --> 00:39:16,119
Andrew Nelson, in custody,

696
00:39:16,122 --> 00:39:18,589
thanks to your brother,

697
00:39:18,624 --> 00:39:20,091
Once we saw your e-mail,

698
00:39:20,126 --> 00:39:21,759
we interrogated him.

699
00:39:21,794 --> 00:39:24,562
He's fully disclosed 21-Void's

700
00:39:24,597 --> 00:39:27,598
conspiracy to frame you for
the murder of Harlan Gaines

701
00:39:27,633 --> 00:39:31,269
and bury your identity
by giving you a new one:

702
00:39:31,304 --> 00:39:33,237
Kaniel Outis.

703
00:39:33,272 --> 00:39:34,539
What does that mean?

704
00:39:34,574 --> 00:39:36,307
It means...

705
00:39:38,045 --> 00:39:40,144
you're free to go, Mr. Scofield.

706
00:39:50,189 --> 00:39:51,689
You don't know how long I've waited

707
00:39:51,724 --> 00:39:53,457
to hear someone call me that.

708
00:40:04,036 --> 00:40:05,570
One other thing.

709
00:40:05,612 --> 00:40:07,959
The level of ingenuity

710
00:40:07,998 --> 00:40:10,041
that you displayed with all of this...

711
00:40:10,076 --> 00:40:12,577
We could use a person like that.

712
00:40:12,612 --> 00:40:14,373
I am not looking for a job.

713
00:40:14,428 --> 00:40:15,513
Right.

714
00:40:23,016 --> 00:40:25,456
There is one thing you can do for me.

715
00:40:31,163 --> 00:40:32,263
You liking it here?

716
00:40:32,298 --> 00:40:34,632
It's strange.

717
00:40:34,667 --> 00:40:36,634
Being alive again.

718
00:40:36,669 --> 00:40:38,769
Not running.

719
00:40:41,340 --> 00:40:43,307
Yeah.

720
00:40:43,342 --> 00:40:45,476
I've been running, too.

721
00:40:46,579 --> 00:40:48,412
I know.

722
00:40:51,684 --> 00:40:54,585
Why'd you call her?

723
00:40:54,620 --> 00:40:56,687
Because I knew you wouldn't.

724
00:41:03,262 --> 00:41:05,196
What's really strange is...

725
00:41:05,231 --> 00:41:07,932
things actually working out.

726
00:41:10,369 --> 00:41:12,469
Yeah.

727
00:41:17,176 --> 00:41:18,609
I love you.

728
00:41:19,745 --> 00:41:21,779
I love you, too.

729
00:41:23,382 --> 00:41:25,049
He's better at getting himself into...

730
00:41:28,733 --> 00:41:31,122
He's stubborn.

731
00:41:31,157 --> 00:41:32,356
Hey.

732
00:41:32,391 --> 00:41:34,725
Hey, babe.

733
00:41:34,760 --> 00:41:36,160
Hmm.

734
00:41:43,749 --> 00:41:46,777
_

735
00:41:50,443 --> 00:41:52,777
Not used to guys
smiling, coming in here.

736
00:41:52,812 --> 00:41:54,929
Yeah, just not planning
on sticking around long,

737
00:41:54,932 --> 00:41:55,846
that's all.

738
00:41:55,881 --> 00:41:58,048
Yeah, right.

739
00:42:02,823 --> 00:42:04,455
Have a good one.

740
00:42:23,376 --> 00:42:25,610
No. No, no, no, no, no, no,

741
00:42:25,645 --> 00:42:27,278
no! No! No!

742
00:42:27,313 --> 00:42:29,413
Guard! Guard!

