[BABA VOSS] The festival's
a few days' walk.
Kofun. We're going to see the world.
- [PRIEST] Behold!
- [SCREAMING]
We have brought witches to burn.
The Witchfinder has missed us,
but his message has traveled.
[MAGHRA] Where's Kofun?
Help! Haniwa!
[HANIWA] Kofun has written a message.
How do you know those words?
[HANIWA] It's knowledge
from the box, Mama.
We opened it. We have
learned to read and write.
And we read all the
books he left behind.
[SCREAMS]
Your boy!
[BOTH SCREAM]
[GETHER] A message.
It will flow downstream through
a dozen different valleys.
[COURTIER] News from the
Sun Grave, Your Majesty.
[QUEEN KANE] It's not over.
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
[BIRDS TWEETING]
[BIRD SQUAWKS]
[SOFT METALLIC CHIMING]
[BIRDS TWEETING]
[RIVER RIPPLES]
[BIRDS SCREECHING]
[BABY BURBLING]
[RIVER RIPPLES]
[ROPE BRIDGE CREAKS]
[MAN] Chet-chet!
[BIRDS SQUAWKING]
- [WINGS FLUTTER]
- [HORSE NICKERS]
[MAN CHANTS IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
[CROWD] Chet-chet-chet!
[RHYTHMIC CHANTING]
[SNARLS]
[SILENCE]
[DOGS BARKING, SNARLING]
[BARKING]
[TRIBESPEOPLE CHATTERING]
[SOUTER] They have come
for the witches at last!
[GETHER] Before we came here,
we had a chance to give the witches up,
but they enchanted you all.
Now is your moment to repent.
[SOUTER] Let us rid ourselves of them!
They are the ones to blame for
the danger we are facing today,
and they must answer for it!
[GETHER] Everyone knows
that you have been our
true enemy this whole time!
Hold them! Don't let them go!
Do not let them leave!
We will use them as a
bargain for our lives.
I have him! I have him!
Stand back! The witch
has me by the throat!
We have to leave now.
Get them to the river. To the river.
- [GETHER] Let the devils pass!
- Arca!
[GETHER] We'll be rid
of them soon enough!
[BABA VOSS] Matal!
Go.
Go with them. Live. [SOBS]
I love you.
[SNAPS FINGERS] Matal.
[HANIWA] What is she doing?
[KOFUN] Bow?
[BOW LION] I'm coming with you.
Come with me! Follow!
Kofun.
You have no use for me.
Let me go.
He deserves to die.
No.
If I were a devil for real,
I would take great pleasure.
[EXHALES] But we're
not that kind of tribe.
Ha-ha.
[DOGS BARKING]
I am Tamacti Jun.
Witchfinder General for Queen Kane
and the Holy Guardians of the Payan.
At last, Witchfinder,
you have come to save us.
On your knees.
What?
All of you.
For your lives...
give up the children of Jerlamarel.
We Alkenny are good people.
Quiet people.
Please...
Witchfinder, please.
The witches are gone.
[GRUNTS, GURGLES]
Until proven otherwise...
you're all witches.
- [METALLIC CHIMING]
- [GETHER] Holy Guardian!
This is Gether Bax!
The witches, they've run!
Follow me!
[RIVER RUSHING]
Wait. It's a dead end.
No, my boy. This is where we descend.
Look.
[KOFUN] Dad.
You did this? Alone?
Anything Jerlamarel can
do, I can do, only bigger.
What is it? What's below us?
Freedom, Mama.
[HANIWA LAUGHS]
Dad built a boat.
Son.
[KOFUN] When did you do this?
When I could.
You'd be surprised how
much you can accomplish
before your eyes even
get open in the morning.
Why?
Like you, I hoped this
day would never come.
But you prepared for it?
Yes, I did. And because of it,
we will live to see tomorrow.
[DOGS BARKING IN DISTANCE]
[DOGS BARKING]
[DOGS PANTING, SNARLING]
[BARKING CONTINUES]
[GETHER] Huh.
The ones that fled...
was one of them a builder?
Yes. Yes, a very skilled one.
[DOG BARKING]
Cross.
[BARKING CONTINUES]
[BARKING CONTINUES IN DISTANCE]
- [WHISPERS] Dad.
- [QUIETLY] Shh. I know. I can hear them.
Give me my sword.
They are ahead. Both sides.
We travel silently.
[SOLDIER WHISTLES]
[BOAT CREAKING SOFTLY]
[CREAKING CONTINUES]
[BOAT CREAKING]
I have been looking for you...
for a lifetime.
I was there when you were born.
I heard your first cries.
And ever since, I have devoted
my life to finding you again.
[ROPE WHISTLES]
[TAMACTI JUN] I have laid waste
to so many lives to reach you.
And now...
what next?
Nearby, there's a village
filled with your kinsmen
all on their knees
begging for my forgiveness.
Perhaps you can purchase it for them.
Speak.
Let me hear the sound of your voices
for the first time since
they were newborn wails.
Announce yourselves.
And let me escort you
to meet your queen.
Do it...
and the village lives.
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
No?
Ah.
[TAPS STAFF TWICE]
[WHISPERS, INAUDIBLE]
[GURGLES]
[RAGGED BREATHING]
[SCREAMS]
[MATAL] Help!
[SCREAMING]
[YELLS]
[KOFUN] No!
[SOLDIER GRUNTS]
[GRUNTS]
- [MAGHRA YELPS] Baba!
- Maghra.
[GRUNTS]
- [KNIFE DINGS]
- [GRUNTS]
[GRUNTS]
[KOFUN] Wait, Mama.
[GRUNTING]
[SHOUTING]
No!
[MAGHRA YELLS]
[KOFUN] Mom!
[GRUNTS]
[SCREAMS]
[ARCA, SOLDIERS GRUNTING]
Go!
[ARCA YELLS]
Arca!
[DOGS BARKING]
- [GETHER BAX GRUNTS]
- [TAMACTI JUN] What lies downriver?
Can we pursue?
I've been run through.
What lies ahead?
Perhaps you can be saved.
Open waters, deep water.
They'll move quickly.
You will not be able to catch them.
Help me.
[GRUNTS]
There. That should save you some time.
Return to the village. Kill them all.
Herald.
Message for Queen Kane.
The witches have escaped.
[METAL SCRAPING]
[CHANTING] Ah...
[ROYAL CABINET CHANTING] Ah...
Tamacti Jun sends news.
[LORD DUNE] Did he locate the witches?
Yes. But, for the moment,
they escaped him.
They escaped him again?
- How?
- He doesn't say.
Ah. So we must guess,
or invent for ourselves.
[QUEEN KANE] Lady An,
when the God Flame burns our skin,
do you blame God or yourself?
Neither one, my queen.
I blame my maid for not shading me.
Gods are not blamed.
No one is blaming you.
But perhaps this news means
Tamacti Jun should return home.
[QUEEN KANE] No. No, no, no.
But to undertake such a journey,
Tamacti Jun will need more soldiers.
Majesty, please...
Send more. Send all of them.
These are fathers and mothers,
husbands and wives,
daughters and sons.
Their families have
suffered their absences.
They are tired of
this... fruitless crusade.
It's beyond their understanding.
The holy machines are
groaning too, Your Majesty.
The gods themselves
do not understand this.
Oh! But you understand
what the gods are saying?
Yes! They are saying "enough!" Enough!
[METALLIC RATTLING]
Oh, ohh...
There...
in our ancient constitution.
"And the monarch shall
rule the parliament,
and the monarch shall rule until death".
I'm not feeling unwell.
[LORD DUNE] Majesty, here is
what the people of Payan say.
[QUEEN KANE] As you fuck
them like prayer mats.
[LORD DUNE] Plainly, simply,
you have chased the
witches for a generation.
Yet none has been found.
You have sacrificed our army,
emptied our treasure houses.
Still there is no proof of evil power.
Just...
a man you once loved
who ran away from you.
They say we are a nation
governed by a broken heart.
A message from Jerlamarel.
A message to present to the children
once they were ready to leave us behind.
It is a message for eyes.
[MAGHRA] More surprises from Jerlamarel?
I gave him my word.
I would present it no sooner
than when they were ready for it.
It's the last of my messages from him.
Last of my promises to him.
Are we sure?
Yes, we are.
Go ahead.
"My dear children...
the river is the beginning.
The first step of your
long journey back to me.
Follow the river to the lavender.
The great lavender road".
[HANIWA] The lavender road is real.
"Then follow the lavender road
to the House of Enlightenment.
There, I will build a new kingdom.
A bright shining light
in a world of darkness.
And one day, you will come
to me and know what I know.
And carry this knowledge forward
to the darkest corners of the earth".
- "Those with eyes to see must follow me".
- "... see must follow me".
So, what? We just follow
the river? For how long?
He'll leave us signs.
- We'll make it.
- Will we?
What other choice do we have?
[MAGHRA] We have a choice.
Listen to me.
Look at me.
The longer the journey,
the more profound its challenges,
the more it changes all who endure it.
A journey like this one...
Those of us who could survive it,
I fear, would emerge
on the other end of it
unrecognizable to each other.
What kind of answers will the
House of Enlightenment provide
to any of us if we no
longer recognize ourselves?
I will abide to whatever
our vote decides,
but you must hear this.
We have a choice to live as we are.
We can gain some distance
on the Witchfinder,
who most certainly continues
his pursuit as we speak.
And we can move far away from
anywhere he might track us...
and live our lives simply, and quietly,
and together.
Mama, I don't know that I
can ever know who I really am
until I know where I came from.
And I can't know that
until I know Jerlamarel.
And you?
I don't think I'm meant to be
someone who hides from the world.
I don't think I want to be
someone who ignores the truth
because I'm afraid
of what it might mean.
I see.
Shall we take the vote?
All those in favor of leaving
the river and finding shelter.
Chet-chet.
All those in favor of following
the trail of Jerlamarel.
- Chet-chet.
Chet-chet.
There's still one vote left to be cast.
- No.
- We are one tribe, Haniwa.
We are one tribe.
We.
The ones who have been in this
together from the beginning.
[BABA VOSS] I agree with Paris.
Right now we are all that
remain of the Alkenny,
and Bow Lion shares that connection.
The Alkenny were willing to
hand us over to the Witchfinder
in order to save themselves.
They did what they did.
But they also taught you, they fed you,
they loved you, and befriended you.
They uprooted their lives to save yours.
And the very first chance
they got, they betrayed us all.
There are six of us on this boat,
and everyone will be heard.
No.
She has absolutely
nothing to do with this.
Haniwa.
[BOW LION] I vote to follow the river.
I vote with Haniwa and Kofun.
Arca, Matal, my mother...
We've sacrificed too much to stop now.
Then we have decided.
[MAN YELLS, GRUNTS]
[MAN 2] General!
Report.
Good news, General.
We believe the terrain ahead is
treacherous but may be passable.
The column needn't be camped
for more than a half day
while we scout it out.
No one's stopping until
either we're all dead
or we find the children
of Jerlamarel. Understood?
- [MAN 2] Understood.
- Good.
So move!
Then it must be done to kill the queen.
A God?
Who here still believes that?
What we believe is not important.
Many of the people of the
lower walls still believe it.
- [LORD UNOA] If we deposed...
- [LADY AN] Deposed their god,
they would rise up.
- [LORD UNOA] We have soldiers.
- [LADY AN] So few.
Then we must not be
the ones to depose her.
[LADY AN] If even we fear to
do it, who else possibly would?
To kill a God, one must enlist a God.
Her death must involve no
struggle, no blood, no weapon.
No evidence of human hand whatsoever.
And then the people from the lower wall
will hear that their queen was
struck down by divine intervention.
And they will say, "This is justice".
[OPERATIC MUSIC PLAYS]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACH]
[METALLIC CREAKING]
[CREAKING CONTINUES]
I'm too merciful.
We could pray.
I pray only for the truth.
What do you hear?
There are new whispers about you.
Who whispers? Lady An? Lord Dune?
Yes, and others.
Give me names.
All of them, my queen.
- Why did you do that?
- Do what?
You have no reason to
go where we're going.
If you voted against
us, you wouldn't have to.
They're gone.
Everyone's gone.
Where else am I gonna go?
Still. Still you chose the harder path.
The more dangerous one. But why?
I don't know you and
your sister very well.
Not like I knew the
others in the village.
Because we were the only
ones you couldn't spy on.
I know you're a shadow.
I may not know all your secrets...
but your sister's anger has
never been a secret to anyone.
I voted that way because...
I don't know what difference it makes,
and I'm done fighting for today.
She-She isn't angry.
I mean, she isn't angry with you.
Look, this is just a lot for
her, and she's trying her best.
And sometimes that comes out as anger.
Isn't it hard for you too?
Thank you for trying to speak to me.
I'd like to be alone now.
Hey, do you need help?
Yes. I made these.
- To give to Bow.
- Okay.
For you and Haniwa.
[PARIS] We need to stop for the night.
She needs to rest by a fire.
Yes.
Are you all right?
She's never spoken
to me that way before.
Argued with me, yes.
Defied me many times, but...
this was just something so different.
If the vote had been a tie and
I'd broken that tie against her,
I honestly don't know
what she would have done.
[PARIS] We told them to hide
who they were their whole lives.
Told them it wasn't
safe for anyone to know.
We never really knew who
they were supposed to be.
How could they?
Maybe the further up this river we go...
the freer they'll be to find out.
Hmm?
[LIGHT CHATTER]
Your Majesty? Your handmaiden
delivered my invitation?
Indeed, she did, Lady
An. Indeed, she did.
Your Majesty, welcome.
[QUEEN KANE] Ah.
Ah. [INHALES DEEPLY]
The smell of sex and
the sound of songbirds.
The divine combination.
And as I told you in my invitation,
I have a special
pleasure in store for you.
Everyone not invited, leave now.
A new song. A new bird.
You will be the first to hear
it inside the palace walls.
And who will stay to share my delight?
It is I, Your Majesty.
With your permission.
Oh, of course, Lord Dune.
I know it'd be you.
[RATTLES RING]
We think the strange new bird
has been blown off course by a storm.
My net man heard it
singing in the apple trees
and managed to trap it.
Well, then that man will be rewarded.
As will you, Lady An. And you,
Lord Dune, for thinking of me.
And here is our new guest.
I don't hear a song.
I'm told this particular bird
only sings when you
take it in your hand.
Yours will be the first hand to hold it.
Well...
then open the door of
the cage, Lord Dune.
Birds usually tremble among
people. I don't hear it tremble.
Perhaps it's not afraid.
Huh.
[SNAPS]
And I am not afraid.
You see, my whole entire
parliament agreeing to my death,
this whole rotten
city wanting me to die.
I've decided I won't die for this city.
- This city will die for me.
- [LADY AN GRUNTS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [BLOOD SPLATTERS]
You can go first.
[FIRE CRACKLING]
Okay.
[GRUNTS]
[BABA VOSS] We've
traveled a good distance.
As long as we keep moving by
daybreak, we should be fine.
One of us should stay
awake through the night
to keep watch and tend the fire.
[MAGHRA] Sit with me.
Mama...
Tell me. What do you
imagine it will be like?
What will what be like?
"There, I'll build my kingdom", he says.
We're all gonna risk life
and limb to get to this place.
So, tell me.
What do you imagine this
kingdom will be like?
Well...
I imagine...
it will be... a place
where we'll remember things.
About what things were like for us once.
About who we used to be.
About...
how to use that knowledge
to make things better now.
I imagine...
it will be a place where...
I won't be the strange
one anymore. [LAUGHS]
Where I can help to build
something important...
and do it without
having to hide who I am.
If your father builds himself a
kingdom, you would be its princess.
It's not like that.
I would do whatever he asked
me to do. However I could help.
And who would I be in this kingdom?
You'd be its queen.
I don't think so.
A king with vision...
a prince and princess with vision.
I'd be the one without.
I'll be the strange one.
The one they say is weak.
I would never let anyone say that.
I know you wouldn't.
It is important for
me to reach this place.
But it's not about me.
It's about all of us.
We'll all be better off there.
I really believe that.
We should all rest awhile.
Okay.
[STICK CLATTERS]
[BABA VOSS] Kofun, my sword is missing.
[HANIWA] My bow's gone, too.
- [PARIS] Maghra.
- [BABA VOSS] Bow, check the boat.
- [BOW LION] Chet-chet.
- [PARIS] Maghra.
- I thought one of you was awake all night.
- [PARIS] Come.
- [KOFUN] We were.
- Come.
[BABA VOSS] Then how did this happen?
Someone walked all through
our camp, woke none of us,
- and was seen by neither of you?
- [KOFUN] I don't know.
[BABA VOSS] It's all gone now, isn't it?
- Help me. We need to go.
- [KOFUN] Okay. Now walk.
We can't leave.
We must.
All that was taken was weapons.
It's nothing irreplaceable.
- I'm missing something.
- Come.
What are you missing?
It's a small pouch. It's
soft. Size of a fist.
What is in the pouch?
Something very important to me.
It's the only thing I have
left of my father.
- My only connection to him. It's...
- Okay.
It's irreplaceable! We have
to find out where it went.
We have to get it back.
- But, Mom, what is it?
- It's important.
Maghra, listen...
Please can you just...
Don't ask me to say anything
more. Just help me find it.
My love, we are unarmed.
Whoever came last night may return.
And the Witchfinder
lurks out there somewhere.
If we remain too long, he will find us.
Then we must hurry.
My father, my relationship
with him is not something
I know how to talk about.
It's complicated.
And, of all people, I would
think you would understand.
Whatever secrets I have kept
from you has been to protect us.
Whatever secrets you have kept from me
has always been to protect us.
Please help me understand this.
Help me justify putting our
children in danger right now
because I cannot.
I know.
What could possibly be so important
and still you'll not say it?
- [HANIWA] I'll do it.
- [KOFUN] No.
Haniwa.
[HANIWA] She already knows
everything you're asking.
I'll find it for you.
If it were river bandits,
they're half a day away.
If it was the Opayol, there
could be hundreds of them.
A hundred of them won't see me coming.
Do you know how fortunate we
were to escape the Witchfinder?
Very fortunate.
Another fight and now without arms?
I'm not suggesting we
get into a fight, Papa.
Whoever took it...
how can they fight me if they
don't even know that I'm there?
And besides, we don't know who they are.
- We should at least try to figure out...
- I think I know.
- What?
- I think I know who took our things.
- What are you talking about?
- Look, please.
What is it? What do you see?
Tell me. What is it?
Tell me.
[SINGS]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACH]
[METAL CREAKING]
[NYRIE] It is time, my queen.
News of Lady An's parlor has spread.
Demonstrations in protest of you
having killed several beloved lords
have begun about the lower wall.
The palace guard keeps them at
bay, but for how long I do not know.
My queen?
What happens next?
The remaining lords are convening.
If they gain the trust of the mob,
there's no telling what they may do.
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
Ah.
[MACHINERY CLANKS, HUMS]
[EXHALES]
Father, whose power we
feel but cannot touch...
I accept my fate.
I thank you that I
could choose its hour.
[MACHINERY WHINES DOWN]
[GRUNTS]
[RUMBLING, METAL CREAKS]
[CHUCKLES]
Jerlamarel, you did not
come for me, my love.
So I am coming to you.
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -