[TAMACTI JUN] Tell me what
you know about Jerlamarel.
Tell me about his children.
There is a small cave. There you
will find a box for my children.
Bury the books. And for 12 summers,
we will not speak a word of this.
[PARIS] Twelve years, you have kept
a secret. Could you keep another?
They are books from your true father.
You opened the box.
Maghra will burn the books.
[PARIS] So do not tell her. The
books will give them knowledge.
It was Baba Voss who
condemned my mother,
your own sister, to the bonfire.
I'm gonna send news
of a witch. A message.
Who knows who will find it?
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
[BIRDS TWEETING]
[BIRD SQUAWKS]
[SOFT METALLIC CHIMING]
[BIRDS TWEETING]
[RIVER RIPPLES]
[BIRDS SCREECHING]
[BABY BURBLING]
[RIVER RIPPLES]
[ROPE BRIDGE CREAKS]
[MAN] Chet-chet!
[BIRDS SQUAWKING]
- [WINGS FLUTTER]
- [HORSE NICKERS]
[MAN CHANTS IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
[CROWD] Chet-chet-chet!
[RHYTHMIC CHANTING]
[SNARLS]
[SILENCE]
[DOG BARKS]
[WHISTLING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[METAL SQUEAKING]
Still recognize your melody...
the way your right is
heavier than your left.
But now you shift
uneasily from foot to foot.
You never used to. You were solid.
Life, experience...
they rock me from side to side.
Welcome home, Tamacti Jun.
Majesty.
My tour of duty is done.
My commission was for 20 summers.
And those summers have turned to winter.
You brought taxes and tribute?
Yes.
[MUSIC BOX CHIMES]
The axles groaned through the mountains.
A hundred carts, God bone, grain,
diamond for axes, axes for wood, slaves.
You're a fine tax collector.
But you're not a finder of witches.
In every village, I interrogated,
presagers would say, "Jerlamarel.
No, no, sir. I don't know that name".
I burned all who lied to me.
You spread his name.
[TAMACTI JUN] In order to find him.
You were a prophet for him?
Gathering people, telling
them about his power,
giving them his name,
scattering his seeds?
As your Witchfinder general,
I have come to report that
I have failed my queen...
and I accept the natural consequence.
But I ask only this:
instead of execution on the altar...
you allow me to take my own life...
in the manner of a warrior.
[LORD DUNE] Your Majesty,
the people are rejoicing.
The elders are dividing the spoils.
The warehouses are being filled.
A market for the slaves
is put into ropes.
Ah.
Our most exalted general has returned.
Tamacti Jun?
Yes. It is I, Tamacti Jun...
who have returned with a hundred carts
when it should've been
a hundred and one.
[LORD DUNE] Your Majesty, his
failure to find one man, one heretic,
must be balanced against this
sound of hundreds calling his name.
Lord Dune, go to the high altar.
Tell the people to
gather. I'll speak to them.
I, too, will rejoice.
Tamacti Jun.
[METAL CLINKING]
Yes.
In recognition of 20
years' loyal service...
you have my permission...
to take your own life.
Farewell.
[METAL CREAKING IN DISTANCE]
Lord Dune, why are you still here?
You could have ordered him to live.
Tamacti Jun understands the nature
of his failure better than you.
Outside, they're
celebrating their own doom.
One man lost.
No!
Our power lost!
Jerlamarel's a god striding
across the world, making more gods,
who will make more gods!
Tamacti Jun knows what is lost.
Go.
[CROWD CHANTING]
Tamacti Jun! Tamacti Jun!
Come, come. He's over
there, under the tree.
- Who's where, under what tree?
- Shh.
[TURKEY GOBBLING]
Turkeys.
So, you go around and
drive them towards me.
Ready?
- [ULULATES]
- Hush, Daddy.
Feel.
I made something.
From the books, for hunting.
Listen.
And learn.
- [BABA VOSS] Ooh.
- [TURKEY SQUEALS]
- I got it. Come.
- What?
I read in one of the books from the box
something very interesting
about the people who
used to live in America.
What is America?
This is just the beginning,
Daddy. I've read so much.
With the right machines
and enough power,
we could make weapons much more
powerful than what I just used,
to kill a hundred in one hour.
Or they had these bombs...
Things called "bombs" that
could blow up whole cities.
Half your words are
book words to me, love,
and they mean nothing to me.
Well, what about this turkey?
Turkey means dinner.
Every day I could go out.
I could get deer, even.
Just like Jerlamarel.
You say deer.
Mm-hmm.
And how exactly would I
explain that to your mother?
That is exactly what Kofun says.
Everything we learn, he wants to hide.
You know I enjoy a tasty deer.
- I don't even like turkey.
- [LAUGHS]
- Makes me sleepy.
- I know, Papa.
[FAINT CHATTERING]
[WOMAN LAUGHS]
What are you doing?
I could kill any one
of them at any time...
and they wouldn't even know what it was.
They'd say it is the
God Flame's vengeance.
Even though we know
the God Flame is a bunch of
gas 93 million miles away...
- burning in outer...
- Stop!
He didn't leave us books
so that we can make weapons.
How do you know? Why did he leave
us books? What was his reason?
Explain, Professor.
Stop.
Do you think about it?
Think about what?
What it'll be like when we meet him.
If we meet him.
This will guide us. It's
a picture of the world.
Look, I've already
worked out where we are.
See, our river flows to this
bigger river called Mississippi.
And then...
this... this was once
a city called Pittsburgh.
- Pittsburgh.
- I think it was...
Industrial town known for the
production of steel manufactured goods.
Goddens' History of America.
Our father left us with the knowledge
and wisdom from all ages of humanity,
and yet, somehow, Kofun,
you make it boring.
"Boring" is bows and arrows.
"Boring" is reading and not doing.
[HORN BLARES]
- Chet-chet!
- [ALL] Chet-chet-chet!
Last night, a baby was born...
[SOUTER BAX SOBS]
to Souter Bax.
[DREAMER] But the baby was not whole.
The baby was not formed human.
Because you witches cursed me! [YELPS]
[SOBS]
You should burn them...
not follow them.
What came from her was...
a devil.
And it's their fault.
The baby was not born that
way because of any curse.
God Flame, welcome her.
It was born that way
for want of fresh blood.
When so few are together for so long,
the blood of the tribe thickens.
We have known through the
generations that without new blood,
the monsters would come.
- Simple genetics. DNA clusters...
- Hush, Haniwa.
This baby is a warning to us.
And we should heed that warning.
We need to share
ourselves and be shared.
No.
We must go out again
and join the festival,
dance away the monsters.
We have avoided the
festivals for a reason.
Out in the world, we are hunted.
Here, we are safe.
Perhaps here, we might be a little
smarter about choosing partners.
The need is deep, Baba Voss.
New blood is needed here,
and has for a long time.
[BABA VOSS] I said, no.
These people have been
held here for so long.
Held here? Held here?
They have been protected here.
The one does not out-rule the other,
especially since so many of them dispute
whether we are here to protect
them from the Witchfinder,
or to protect your children from them.
They have done without
medicine while sick.
trade while wanting.
They have done without.
And if you forbid them from travel...
they will start leaving on their own.
[BABA VOSS GROANS]
Our people wandering the
countryside on their own.
They'll lead the
Witchfinder to us in no time.
Then maybe it's better we have
some control over where they wander
and who they come in contact with.
What do you propose, my love?
I know the way to a festival.
They have some medicine,
goods, and new blood.
The only way to protect Haniwa and Kofun
is to make sure that
this place is secure.
And if that means we have to
control where the Alkenny goes...
then that's what we'll do.
[MUSIC BOX CHIMES]
[METAL SQUEAKING]
[MUSIC BOX CHIMING CONTINUES]
I'll be told when it's done?
Yes, Your Majesty.
[MUSIC BOX CHIMING CONTINUES]
It is done?
[MAN] News from the
Sun Grave, Your Majesty.
[MUSIC BOX CHIMING STOPS]
News?
[METALLIC RATTLING]
[SNAPPING]
[SCREAMS]
Great God Flame,
accept my spark into your flame
and let it rise to meet you.
[METALLIC RATTLES]
It's not over.
[QUEEN KANE SOBS]
We'll be gone for a week. The
festival's a few days' walk.
Antia is going, and
she's younger than us.
Haniwa, I am not risking anyone
finding out about your gift.
We've kept our secret
safe here for 17 summers.
Well, not without suspicion.
We're better at keeping
secrets than you know, Mama.
Meaning what?
You are not old enough to
share or spread your seeds.
We don't want to share disgusting seeds.
Well, then you should be happy to stay.
Why would someone like me
want the seed of a blind man?
Come here.
I said, come here.
Why would you speak this way?
I don't know. I'm sorry.
Because I love you all...
and you all love me,
I ignore certain voices in my head...
because I know you would not lie to me.
[SNAPS]
By accident of birth, you
were given the ability to see.
Do not think you are superior
because others cannot.
And keep your book words to yourself,
because sometimes
those words are wicked.
Mama, these flowers will
rot before I even get there.
These flowers are for you,
to smell along the way,
to find the feeling to
enter into the dance.
Who says I'll dance?
It's long past time, Bow.
Your father and I danced.
[BABA VOSS] Form up.
- Baba?
- Love.
Remember, Alkenny, let us be known
as "the people of the waterfall".
Let us not speak of the past.
[ARCA] Travel well.
[MAGHRA HUMS]
[HUMMING]
Hey.
Haniwa.
Slow down!
We're upwind. They can't hear us.
I'd like to keep it that way.
Happy?
Kofun.
We're going to see the world.
[HUMMING CONTINUES]
[HUMMING STOPS]
[HANIWA] What is that?
[KOFUN] Maybe this
is one of those places
where the spaceship took
off and went to the moon.
[HANIWA] Look. Look at that wheel.
I don't remember reading
about cars that size.
Huh.
Come on, before it gets too dark.
[CHATTERING]
[MAN] Fresh wool. Fine, like silk.
[MAN 2] Mesh to mend your clothes.
[MAN SHOUTS IN DISTANCE]
[METAL SQUEAKS]
[SHEEP BLEATS]
[CHATTERING CONTINUES]
[MAN 3] I am the
priest of the God Flame,
brother of the fire, who
shapes me like God bone.
Executor of God's will.
We have built this temple of flame.
We have brought witches to burn.
All have been convicted of
having the power of light.
A Witchfinder is here.
[PRIEST] Behold...
No. This is something different.
... as we turn the witches
of light into heat.
[SOBBING]
Please.
They can't even see.
Look... Look at their eyes.
They're being burned for nothing.
- [ACCUSED WITCH] Stop!
- [ACCUSED WITCH 2] Please.
[MAN SCREAMS]
[ACCUSED WITCHES SCREAMING]
- You're wrong! They can't even...
- Shh!
[SCREAMING CONTINUES]
The Witchfinder has missed us,
but his message has traveled.
Made disciples.
[PEOPLE SHOUTING]
The children will never be safe.
The children will be safe at home.
Everyone thinks home is safe...
until it isn't.
[VOMITS]
[FROGS, INSECTS CHIRPING]
[PANTING]
[FLAMES CRACKLING]
[FROGS, INSECTS CHIRPING]
[CRACKING]
I'll...
Help!
Haniwa!
Strong. [GRUNTS]
Young.
[KOFUN GAGS]
Healthy...
For once, these sheep are
not held behind their fences.
[WOMAN] Fethin?
[MOANS SOFTLY]
[WOMAN] Fethin!
Fethin!
Slavers! Slavers!
[MAN] What is it?
[WOMAN] There's Slavers!
They... They took my Fethin!
They took my little girl!
Fethin! [SOBS]
Fethin!
They were Slavers!
Mama. Mama, Papa, wake up. It's me.
What are you doing here?
Mama, I think something bad has...
Where's Kofun?
I think he's...
I think he's been taken.
[BABA VOSS] By whom?
I think he's been taken by Slavers.
[CHAINS RATTLING]
[RATTLING CONTINUES]
[GRUNTING SOFTLY]
What do you think you're doing?
Why have we stopped?
The boy thought he'd take a break.
- Something's wrong with him.
- I'll find out.
No.
I will.
You scream, I will gut you.
Can't you hear her? She... She's hurt.
She keeps tripping, so I'm tripping.
So, don't trip.
No, please! She's bleeding.
How do you know?
I'm a Scentier.
I can smell the blood.
And she's limping.
It is not her foot my
customers are interested in.
Huh.
A bit of spirit.
[GAGS]
This one will get a good price.
Move!
There! I see smoke. They
follow the Sage Road.
They will stray from it.
For you, but not for me.
They will leave a trail. I will see it.
- I will gather warriors. We pursue!
- There's no time.
Few men will come. I need them back.
Haniwa, lead the way.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
Hemlock. It's theirs.
You certain?
Absolutely.
Mama? Papa?
There's a message here.
Kofun left a message.
What message?
How could he leave a message?
You're just going to have to trust me.
Trust you? What message?
Kofun has written a
message, and I can read it.
No. How do you know those words?
How do you know "written" and "read"?
It's knowledge from the box, Mama.
We opened it.
We have learned to read and write.
And we read all the
books he left behind.
Who opened it?
I did.
What does the message say?
- Mama, I...
- My son is missing!
I want him back! So, what does it say?
[CHAINS RATTLING]
Guards!
[COUGHS]
Sit!
[FETHIN PANTING]
[KOFUN BREATHES HEAVILY]
What's your name?
Ko... Kofun.
My name is Fethin.
I mean, did you really think
telling the Slavers I was hurt
would make them help me?
Ok... Okay, you're welcome.
No, I d... I didn't mean it like that.
Thank you.
[METAL CLANKING IN DISTANCE]
[METAL SCRAPING IN DISTANCE]
[HANIWA] Careful.
Many rocks. Many rocks.
Mama.
I'm good.
Yes.
I see ahead, smoke coming
from inside a structure.
- Are the towers made of God bone?
- Yes.
It's where they hold the
slaves before they sell them.
If I don't get to him now,
he'll be sold to the market.
How do you know, Papa?
I know this place...
because my father was a Slaver...
and his father before him.
And for a time, so was I.
[PARIS] It's not as you think,
Haniwa. Your father was different.
[BABA VOSS] Do not tell
her that. It isn't true.
I was raised to chain and whip
and beat and sell innocent people.
He taught me how to torture.
But I've buried that
part of me, that man...
deep down in a hole.
But now I must do something
I swore I would never do.
What?
Wake him up.
- Papa, I can go with you. I have my bow.
- No.
No, my love.
You must not see what I'll become.
I will get Kofun back.
No.
[METAL CLANKING IN DISTANCE]
[GRUNTS]
[FETHIN PANTING]
[SIGHS] I will get
mighty God bone for you.
- [PANTING]
- Mighty God bone.
[COUGHS]
Chet-chet!
What was that?
[GRUNTS]
[KOFUN GRUNTS]
Ch-ch!
[METAL SCRAPING]
Close your eyes.
[BABA VOSS SHOUTS]
[GAGGING]
[AIR WHIPPING]
[MAN SCREAMS]
[MAN SHOUTS]
[GRUNTING]
Wech.
[METAL SCRAPES]
[WECH CHUCKLES]
The great Baba Voss.
The great coward.
The great...
deserter.
Finally, my day has come.
And I will have your head.
Upokokohua.
Haere Mai!
[GRUNTS]
[WECH SCREAMS]
Pick it up.
[METAL JINGLES]
Papa, watch out!
[GRUNTING]
Your boy!
[BOTH SCREAM]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[GAGGING]
No...
[HANIWA] Papa.
[HUMS, TAPS STICK]
It's me.
Mama, it's me.
Mama, it's all right.
- Kofun?
- It's all right.
Kofun.
Mama, it's all right.
It's all right.
Haniwa. Haniwa.
I'm here, Mama. We're all here.
[KOFUN] I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
- I'm sorry about the box.
- It's okay.
I'm sorry.
Mama?
[SCREAMS]
- Mag...
- No.
[HANIWA] Mama!
No.
[CHIMES JANGLE]
Mama?
All we have learned from our books,
and all we have learned
from the festival...
all we have learned in 17 summers...
None of it makes me wanna leave here.
And Haniwa?
What of you?
A man is dead.
A bad man...
but still, he's... he's dead.
I killed him
because I knew I had the power
to kill him and not be caught.
All that I've learned...
all that I've read...
all of it...
all of it makes me want to leave here.
But, Mama...
I'm scared of...
what I am and what I can do.
And I just want you to
know that I love you, Mama.
And I love you, Papa.
And one day, my big
mouth might get me burned.
No.
I already know.
I know.
I know you.
My babies...
Because I knew him.
And it's time I told you about him.
Jerlamarel.
It's time for the truth...
for all of us.
He was a good man.
But sometimes power
can consume goodness.
I'll tell you about him.
Baba, go and get Paris.
She should hear this too.
[DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE]
[BARKING]
[BARKING CONTINUES]
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -