Oh, for God's sake.
Planking is a very stupid
and dangerous trend.
Basically you lie like
a plank in weird places.
That's it.
Sometimes you get run over.
Welcome to the Internet.
Planking is one of
those things where,
hey, you either
get it or you don't.
And I don't. But I am so
excited to be a part of it.
After you,
my good sir.
No, I insist.
The search
committee finally decided,
after a lot of deliberation,
on Robert California
for the manager position.
Who took one look
around and left.
He drove down to Florida and
convinced Jo to make him C.E.O.
C.E.O. Her own job.
He talked her
out of her own job
and I don't really know
how someone does that,
but anyway, then the
position was his to fill,
and he chose...
It's unbelievable.
True. I may have
been the second choice,
but I was the first
choice's first choice.
And about Dwight,
I sense that he might have some
resentment about not getting the job,
so I sat him down
and we had a talk.
And I told him, "I need a
really strong number two.
"I want you to
be my enforcer."
Smart, right?
Very smart.
This has got to stop.
I can't get down.
Hey! Kevin!
Yeah, at first I was
really disappointed.
But I've got a great daily
routine going right now.
I've upped my karate
to eight times a week.
I've added boxing art
lunches and on weekends,
I do kick-boxing three times a
week, Krav Maga four times a week,
an hour of meditation
every morning at sunrise,
and again at sunset.
So yeah.
I'm doing great.
I'm going to need
some help. Pam?
I don't think I should.
Oh, yeah. Pregnant.
Right here.
Little Michael Scott.
Nope. I told you I
don't like that joke.
It is a boy.
We found out early.
Much different
the second time around.
And I have to say
it is nice not being
the only pregnant
woman in the office.
Look, it's "little
pregs" and "big pregs."
Wait, when did we
start calling each other...
Isn't it amazing the
difference in our sizes?
Well, I am a few
months ahead of you.
I'm having a child with
my husband, the senator.
And Pam is having a child
with Jim. The great salesman.
Hoist him aloft!
Come on, Darryl, lift.
Lift, Darryl.
Come on, man.
Yeah, I wanted the manager job,
but I got something much better.
This soda.
This is mine.
It might be easier if you take a
deep breath, lift from the knees,
and shove it
up your butt.
I came up with
a new thing this summer.
I act like I'm telling someone
how to do something.
I go on with a long
description and then I say...
And shove it up your butt.
It's stupid,
but it's my thing now.
No one should be
planking at all.
Thank you. Yes.
Dwight, my enforcer, my number
two, can you take care of this?
Say no more.
Kids, don't try planking,
it's dangerous.
Especially with me around.
Are you watching
that commercial again?
Why do you keep watching it if you
know it's just going to make you cry?
Because everything makes
me cry, so what's the difference?
This dog, he just wants
to protect his bone.
He's got a bank vault.
That's a start.
Not enough, though.
All right.
The new C.E.O. works out of the
conference room about half the time,
but whenever he takes a break, he
does these weird walks around the office.
And you never know who
he's going to Zero in on
for these really
intense small talks.
You just hope
it's not you.
And yet you hope it
is you, too. It's strange.
Here we go.
Hello.
Robert California.
Let's have a conversation.
Describe your day so far.
Well, I woke up and...
When you recount your
day, never say you woke up.
It's a waste of your time.
That's how every day has begun
for everyone since the dawn of man.
Very smart.
Suddenly, I was awake
and ...
Hey, Robert. We have that 9:30
A.M. casual chit chat scheduled.
I emailed you about it last night
to confirm. And again this morning.
First item on the agenda,
can I get everyone
an extra long
Columbus Day weekend?
Item number two,
connect with the guy.
Robert California,
what does he think of me?
Don't know.
Super care.
Number three, time permitting,
we lost our biggest client.
Pam. Pam. Psst! Pam.
Jim.
Can I call you right back?
Thank you very much.
Okay.
What is this?
The Friday before
Columbus Day, thoughts?
What are your thoughts?
Just making chit-chat.
Kind of a medium year
for women's soccer, no?
What are you looking at?
It's nothing.
It can't be nothing.
Yeah, it can't be nothing.
It's just a list of our names
split into two columns.
What?
Okay, just wait one
second, all right? I will copy it.
Do you have a pen?
No.
Okay. Um, I'll take
a photo of it.
Dwight, can you
throw me my phone?
Nice catch.
If he comes out,
distract him.
We need a warning signal.
We don't need
a warning signal, Kevin.
We can see him right
there. - We do.
I promise you we
don't need a...
Warning! Warning!
Warning! Warning! Warning!
Phyllis!
You okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
One, two, three.
Thanks, guys.
Okay. Which side
of the list am I on?
Yes!
Left.
Why are you...
How do you know?
Really great
list of names, guys.
Thank you so much.
Good work.
No, actually, that was
in Robert's notebook.
He left it at reception
and we photocopied it.
Oh!
Okay. I don't want
any part of this.
Maybe it's the list of people
he's going to fire.
Okay.
It's not that, Pam.
You know, I was
thinking it reminds me
of those lists
Dwight used to make.
This is if we were all
on a cruise ship
and had to divide
into life boats.
And this is if we
were on a cruise ship
and had to divide
into life rafts.
Here's something. "Who would
eat who in an Alive situation?"
No. That can't be it.
I gotta say,
it kind of seems like the
left side is the side to be on.
Me, Jim, Dwight, Darryl,
no offense, Pam.
I don't think...
Excuse me?
Shh. Pam, come on.
Don't be such a right-sider.
Did you guys figure it
out? We couldn't crack it.
Go in there, just ask
the man what it means.
He'll know that we looked
at his private notebook.
Come on. Just say you
saw the list by accident.
I'm already working on this
Columbus Day thing for you guys.
And it's starting
to stack up.
It feels like a lot.
One thing at a time.
Yeah, that's all you had to do
today is ask about Columbus Day?
Yes. For God's sake,
Andy, yes. Come in.
What's up?
Weird thing.
Totally awkward.
But you left your notebook
on the reception desk.
Great. Thank you.
And it was open,
and people saw this,
and they're just kind
of going nuts and, like...
What is this?
...wondering what it is.
It's a photocopy
from your notebook.
You read my notebook? And
photocopied it and distributed it?
No. They did. And they
asked me to ask you about it.
Please.
Oh.
Here's what it is,
it's a doodle.
What?
Some people doodle at work
when they let their mind run.
They draw houses, penises,
funny how the houses
are always colonials
and the penises are
always circumcised.
Don't you think?
Well, I doodle too but I'm not
an artist so I draw words and lists.
That is fascinating.
And by the way,
I am so glad I asked.
People were just sort of...
Did you just move my name?
Might as well have
been sketching a cube.
Okay, Robert's in the annex,
everybody think quick.
What do these
groups have in common?
Maybe we're supposed to
do it with people in our group.
That's not it.
People in
the other group.
Mmm. Still wrong.
Stanley, you do puzzles
all day. What do we got?
Well, you take the first
letter from each name,
assign it a number,
add them all up,
and shove it up your butt.
Thank you, a little
much needed comic relief.
But we really need to
figure this out, guys.
I know.
It's alphabetical.
No, it's not.
Here's how we find out.
Let's line up and
compare the lines,
see if we learn
anything, okay?
Left-siders over here,
right-siders line up over here,
face each other.
Match up by height
and relative weight.
Let's just size
each other up here.
And left side of the list,
attack!
Wait, wait, wait, stop, stop!
Will you stop?
Dwight!
Don't do it!
What are you doing?
Stop!
Warning! Warning! Warning!
I'd like to invite the following
people to join me for lunch.
Jim, Dwight,
Angela, Darryl,
Kevin, Toby,
Phyllis, Oscar.
That's great.
Let's do this, guys.
All right. Well,
I will see you in a bit.
I love you so much.
Hey, it's nothing,
all right?
I'll text you
when we get there.
I'll let you know
what's going on. Okay.
No. No dog video.
Okay.
See you, guys.
Well, we should all
be really excited about
our very own pizza party.
Pizza party! Pizza
party. Pizza party.
Jim, your daughter Cecelia,
what does she think of the Street?
The street?
Sesame Street.
Oh. I didn't know
anybody called it...
She likes it a lot.
She loves Elmo.
Elmo, God save us, the Elmo era.
Right?
Sesame Street was
created to reflect
the environment of
the children watching it.
Complete self
absorption of Elmo
is brilliantly
reflective of our time.
Ours is a cultural ghetto.
Wouldn't you agree?
Yeah. She does like Elmo.
Cultural ghetto?
Totally agree.
Completely.
Apt. Apt analysis, Robert.
The thing that I like
about Elmo is the tickling.
I should not be here. I don't
know. I was in the wrong...
I'm... I'm sorry.
Just picture me back
there. I was never here.
Great group.
Pizza party.
How is this a pizza party?
Well, why don't you
ask me again
when the five pizzas
get here?
Yeah, well,
that's just pizza.
You need at least one other
element for it to be a party.
Okay. Have you guys
ever had margherita pizza?
What's that?
Fresh tomato with a dollop
of mozzarella cheese.
That's pizza.
That's regular pizza.
You know, I feel comfortable
enough now to ask you this question,
what made you
pick this group?
I just think
you guys are winners
and I wanted to
have lunch with you.
Okay.
Aw.
What about the other guys?
Losers? Come on.
Oh, I don't know.
Come on. Come on.
I guess I think
they're losers.
I knew it.
Yes!
Probably shouldn't
have said that.
Whoo-hoo!
Ah-ha! Their interpretation
of margherita pizza.
Fans of classic pizza
will be psyched.
A text from Jim.
"This is getting very weird.
Will explain later."
Text from Kevin.
"Suck it, losers."
Okay, not to point
out the glaringly obvious,
but doesn't the fact
that I'm in this group
make anyone feel just
a little bit better?
Oh, this crust is sharp!
I used to be young and cute
and sort of funny
and I could do those
cute little cartoons
and everyone who came
through here was like,
"Who's that receptionist?
I like her."
Now I'm just a fat mom.
Yeah, and you take one look at
me and you're like, "Oh, loser."
Come here, Pam.
Chins up, okay?
Bad joke.
Look around this room.
Does this look like a
group of losers? Seriously.
Oh, God.
Oh, hey, guys,
we had so much fun.
We had margherita pizza.
We all hung out and got
to know each other better.
How was your lunch?
It was excellent.
Good times.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Oh, we did.
It was the best time.
And you know what? Now it's
over, back to work, everyone.
You too, Andy.
I knew it.
I just knew my whole life that
everyone was wrong about me.
My parents, my teachers, my
friends, the doctors, everyone.
Well, that was
certainly an odd lunch.
Is everything all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Just take the
casserole out of the...
Loser.
Take it out of the
refrigerator, put it in the oven.
It'll be fine. Just leave
it in for 20 minutes.
Loser.
When I was a salesman,
I could just be like,
"Not my job, not my prob. I'm going
to the warehouse to polish my knob."
Metaphorically, of course.
But now,
it is my job and my prob.
Hi, Robert.
Can you come out here,
please? It's really important.
I just wanted to
clarify something.
Some people here
are under the misconception
that some people
may be considered,
let's say top tier,
and others would
be second tier.
I never said that.
Thank you. Great.
I said winners and losers. Is
that what you're talking about?
Oh, that might... That actually
might be what I'm thinking of.
Can you clarify that?
Let me tell you some
things I find productive.
Positive reinforcement,
negative reinforcement.
Honesty.
I'll tell you some things
I find unproductive.
Constantly worrying
about where you stand
based on
inscrutable social clues,
and then inevitably reframing
it all in a reassuring way
so that you can get
to sleep at night.
No, I do not
believe in that at all.
If I invited you to lunch,
I think you're a winner.
If I didn't, I don't.
But I just met you all.
Life is long,
opinions change.
Winners, prove me right.
Losers, prove me wrong.
Well, I guess
that's that.
No.
No. No.
Andy, don't go in there.
I'm going in there.
I know that every time I talk to
you things just seem to get worse.
But you don't know
these people, and I do.
And if I let you work
with faulty information,
well, then I'm not doing
my job as regional manager.
So, please take this pen
and change your list.
I'm not going to
change my list, Andy.
And I don't use
ballpoint pens.
Well, then I will
make a new list for you.
Stanley, you may think
he's a lazy grump,
but did you know that he has the
most consistently high sales numbers
of anyone in this office?
And you may think
he's hard to love,
but did you know
that he's in not one,
but two long-term
romantic relationships?
I did not know
about the sales figures.
Meredith Palmer,
supplier relations.
The word "no,"
not even in her vocabulary.
And just to show you
that I'm being fair,
you had Gabe in
the loser column,
I think that is astute.
Good call.
Pam,
easily the most creative and kind
person I have ever worked with.
Jim, shut the door.
This is just gross.
Shh.
Erin Hannon, the receptionist,
and my closest confidant.
A winner if
there ever was one.
I like my new group.
I liked my old group.
Are we done?
Yes.
No.
The Friday
before Columbus Day,
we're going to
take a half-day.
So that everyone can get a
jump on the long weekend.
You want a three-and-a-half
day weekend for Columbus Day?
Yes, I do.
And you are aware that
Columbus and his legions
committed genocide against an
entire civilization of Native Americans?
I don't care.
Hey, guys,
so Columbus Day, we
got that half-day on Friday.
We get that every year.
Well, you got it
this year, too.
Good night, Andy.
Good night.
Bye.
Good night, Andy.
Good night.
Night.
All right, I'm going
to go warm up the car.
Okay.
You dropped something. Jim?
Okay, I know I've been
crying easily today, but...
I mean, that's just
pretty killer, right?
I mean,
maybe it's stupid.
No.
It's wonderful.
I'm going to frame it.
I can always un-frame it.