No, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no,
No!
Okay, fine.
Ryan, is something the matter?
Yeah.
Smokey's dead.
Smokey the Bear?
Smokey Robinson, Pam.
He died like
an hour ago.
I guess I'm the
first to know.
Wow, that's terrible.
I really liked him.
Oh, you liked him?
That's nice.
Did you like when he changed the course of
American music, like, two or three times?
Did you like that
Tracks of My Tears
is maybe the last true
love song ever written?
I'm glad you
like him, Jim.
I am completely
devastated right now.
Well, I second
that emotion. Huh?
I know a few of his songs,
but what were his big ones?
Oh, God, Nellie.
What wasn't his?
I mean,
Tracks of My Tears.
Yeah.
God, so many, Nellie.
No, no, no.
Tracks of My Tears
and what else?
What are some more?
What's one more?
Okay, I'm not I'm not playing
this game, Pam. Not today.
I don't think you love
Smokey Robinson.
I think you're just doing all of this to
prove how deep you are about music.
Okay, I'm sorry that I'm not a
fan of Jason Mraz or the Beatles.
You don't like
the Beatles?
That's not the point.
Eleanor Rigby?
Paperback Writer?
You always think you have time to
see these legends before they go.
What was I so
busy doing?
It says here the Smokey
Robinson dead thing is a hoax.
It's on CNN as of
two minutes ago.
Okay, well.
That's a relief.
Wow, look at that.
Says he's actually
playing State College.
That's only three
hours away.
Oh, my God, Ryan,
that's perfect.
You have to go.
Tickets are
250 bucks.
$250 is nothing to the world's
biggest Smokey Robinson fan.
Yeah.
Who's opening?
Paul Anka.
Paul Anka?
How can they make the Smoke
Man play with someone like that?
I don't think
I can see this.
Okay, you could just
show up late, though.
How much is parking,
like, 30 bucks?
That's not what Smokey
would have wanted.
Does want.
Tears of a Clown. Don't
call me a clown, Pam.
You're better than that.
Looking good, RC.
I hate ties.
I feel like I'm
being strangled,
like I'm at some erotic
asphyxiation sex club over on 1-84.
The Red Room, say,
or Dominick's.
Robert, the Senator was
going to wear dark brown tonight.
I'm sure it'll be fine.
My husband is sponsoring a
fundraiser tonight for local dog shelters.
Robert California bought
two tables for everyone here.
These people were
lucky to get seats
because it is going to be a who's
who of the northern 22nd district.
I don't want to alarm people,
but there is a distinct chance
that we're all about to be killed.
Well, as long as you
don't want to alarm people.
What's going on? There's
a disgruntled ex-employee
sitting in his car
in the parking lot.
Oh, that's Andy.
He's just hanging out.
That's how workplace
tragedies always begin.
A middle-aged white
male "hanging out."
Call the cops.
Dwight, I don't think he's
going to hurt anybody.
How do you know? I mean,
why do you think he's there?
I don't even know
what kind of weapon he has.
Could be a knife,
could be a gun.
Could be a series of guns,
all lined up to shoot parallel.
I'm going up
to the roof.
I'm going to bring my
gym bag just in case.
I knew this would happen.
Everybody told me if I moved
to America, I'd be murdered.
Hey.
Just wanted to say hi and hear
you say everything's normal.
Maybe videotape you saying that
so that everyone upstairs can see?
We think you
might kill Robert.
What?
Because he fired you, which means
apparently you're living in your car now.
Guys, everything
is fine.
I'm just here to pick up Erin.
We're going to the fundraiser.
Great. That
sounds good.
Wait, what?
You're going to the
fundraiser tonight?
That's going to be weird.
Why would
that be weird?
It's going to be
super weird.
He just fired
you last week.
Andy's just coming
as my date.
Hey, I hear you.
I hope you're right.
It just seems like it's going
to be really, really weird.
Come in.
You really redid
Andy's office, huh?
Yes, cut out
the clutter.
Very simple,
very minimal.
I need you to sign these.
We got a shipment going out.
How are things in
the warehouse?
You could go downstairs
and ask them.
The warehouse
isn't downstairs.
Is it?
Who knew, right?
I...
Tonight could be the
night that Darryl and I
go from casual work
friends to actual good friends.
The only thing standing in our way is
the contempt he seems to feel for me.
Robert, the Senator and
I wanted to stop by.
Hello. Robert.
Robert, how are you?
- And say hello.
- Hello.
Did anyone order a blast from
the past with a side order of sexy?
Hi, Andy.
Oh, man, this is weird.
Andrew.
Want to shake
my hand, huh?
Because I want to
shake your body.
I had you, I had you.
Where...
Where do I look?
It's been so long since I
did one of these things.
Okay, all right.
What's the question?
How am I doing? Umm...
Great.
So, how's the talent?
Grey suit over there
is sending a signal.
Downstairs is receiving.
Is that Gabe?
Ladies.
How come you look so
decent all of a sudden?
Yeah, normally you
look so stricken.
Well, I'm embarrassed.
I had to give up
my hair gel
because it was giving me
this angry rash on my scalp.
And I just gave up
on this low-protein diet
that I was doing
for eight years, so...
Ladies seem to like it, plus I'm getting,
like, half as many bladder infections.
Wow.
Yeah.
Wow. You ladies
look very pretty as well.
Thanks.
Why is it that things are
their most beautiful
in the autumn of their lives?
You had to say that.
Sorry. Sorry.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Creed, I just bid $20
on six jujitsu lessons.
No one's
raping this guy.
Well, I don't
want to get raped.
22.
No, it was my idea to
not be raped. Oh, well.
Wait, you think that
jujitsu classes cost $22?
If you're going to
play guess the price,
you might as well try
and be halfway accurate.
$180.
Whoa.
Dwight, I don't think
you understand.
You guess the price,
you win the prize.
Have you never been
to a Quaker fair before?
God.
So, Dwight doesn't
understand silent auctions.
I guess he's the stupid
guy in the office. Huh?
Because up until now
we didn't have one.
What haven't I been doing?
Gosh, just today I was working
on this rock opera that I'm writing,
although it feels more like
I'm receiving it than writing it.
Wow, that's
exciting.
But until you firm up the idea, you
might want to keep it between us.
The hero lives in
this dystopian future
and he flies around in a spaceship
that's shaped like a treble clef.
And he has to sing his
heart out to destroy all evil.
Sounds like you're
doing all right.
A little better than
all right, actually.
Really good.
Have you thought about
getting into photography?
Are you kidding me?
"Cause I'm way into it.
What are you
taking pictures of?
Children?
Yes.
Homeless people?
"Cause in a way,
they're more real...
...than the rest of us!
The rest of us!
This guy's
having a breakdown.
You know, Oscar, I really had no idea
that you were so passionate about animals.
My dog, Gerald,
is my life, Really?
Well, if you want to
get involved, call me.
This is my cell.
I'm more likely to
pick up at night, say,
after 9:00.
Excuse me.
This confirms three things.
I'm right about the Senator,
I still got it, and poor Angela.
I wonder where they
got the flowers.
That piece is
so predictable.
Daffodils in spring,
I wonder what's next,
mistletoe at Christmas?
Yeah.
Oh! It says, "You're
welcome to take this home."
Oh.
Sweetie, you don't want that.
Even in your house, it's a little much.
Have you ever been
to our house?
Not exactly,
but I know the Flats.
I'm going to say what
everyone is afraid to say.
Phyllis is a bully.
A big, beautiful bully.
And she is not
getting that centerpiece.
Step in right
away and start...
Bobby, Bobbo.
You're a rock
opera guy, right?
You like rock operas.
Well...
You've got to check out
this thing I'm working on.
It's really cool.
There's this character,
Thomas Oregon,
and he wants to destroy
all the guitars in the world
because he realizes that music
is the one thing he can't control.
So, Thomas Oregon
is an evil figure.
Evil.
Although he's
humanized at the end
because he weeps uncontrollably
and pees in his pants.
And the hero,
who is that based on?
Me, I guess.
We're flying so
high we're cracking the sky
Going to fly out of this
dome My girlfriend and I
Hey, jabroni,
show some class.
She's right, Andy.
You're being a jabroni.
You're being a
Thomas Oregon.
Andrew,
I think this may have
been a bad idea.
Why don't you let me
pay for you and Erin
to go out to a great,
romantic dinner tonight?
Don't need you to pay for me.
I'm doing just fine, thank you.
Why don't you quit
harshing our mellow?
Andy, you should leave.
Now.
Excuse me,
I would like to purchase two
seats at another table, please.
I'm sorry. The tables are
sold as complete units.
Then I'll take a table.
Okay.
And a high five.
Let's do that again.
Well, I just give a
dollar to every charity.
That way, you get all
the mail, all the calendars.
You can't believe how
much you get just for a buck.
It's also nice to know
you're making a difference.
Jim and I give
to the Red Cross.
Are you sure you
ought to be giving?
I mean, with your
financial situation...
Excuse me?
You ladies are as tangy as the
salad dressing over there. I love it.
Oh, yes indeed.
When.
Whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Forgot a few salads.
When.
I stumbled into a
very dramatic situation.
Here, let me move this
SO you can see him.
Pam.
Yeah.
Angela's husband
just hit on me.
Oh, my God.
I know.
Wait, what? Come on.
We were talking
about animals.
He gives me his
cell phone number.
He was just dying
for me to have it.
Okay, Oscar, I'm not saying
you're not dreamy, because you are,
but isn't it possible that he
was just schmoozing a voter?
Well, if you would have
seen the look he gave me.
He wanted to rock
more than just my vote.
Okay.
What was this look?
Whoa!
What happened?
Did he do it? Are you...
Twice. For real?
Okay, guys. Not every glance
means something, all right?
Life isn't Downton Abbey.
Life is Downton Abbey.
Here's what
I'm going to do.
I'm going to go over there,
I'm going to talk to him.
And I guarantee you he gives
out his cell phone to everybody.
How much do you guys charge
for one full-year gym membership?
Thank you.
It's $475.
Like candy from a baby.
That's the third time you've
asked me about my strategy.
It's called "Guess the Price,"
strategy's in the name.
Simplest game since
"Touch the Rock."
Three-time champion.
Almost four, but
I touched the wood.
Hey.
David Wallace?
Andy Bernard?
Hey, how are you?
How you doing? I'm great.
How are you doing? Are
you still with Dunder Mifflin?
No, got canned last week.
Oh. I'm sorry
to hear that.
No, best thing that
ever happened to me.
That's the attitude
to have.
You know what? When I
got canned, I was lost, right?
I poured myself into this ridiculous
vacuum for toys called Suck It.
Yikes.
Yeah, exactly, right?
Then suddenly
out of nowhere,
the US Military bought the
patent from me for $20 million.
Point is,
forget those guys.
Okay? Move on.
Good to see you, Andy.
Call me a lay man, but I wish
there was some real food here.
You know,
like hamburgers
or Oreos,
or a pizza pie, or...
What's another food
that we like? Tacos.
What I wouldn't give
for a big mess of tacos.
Tacos.
Right now.
I can go get us
some tacos.
Brilliant.
If you loan me
some money.
Yes, I can do that.
For two tacos we
probably need about,
what, $207?
Or $25720...
$30.
Yes, yes.
I've never eaten a taco.
I'm not entirely sure
what they are.
As long as they're not slimy, and
please, God, don't let them have eyes.
So”?
Boom.
This is interesting.
Mm-hmm.
What is interesting?
I just proved that he gives
his cell out to everybody.
Or you proved that
he thinks you're gay.
He doesn't think
Jim is gay.
A gay man would not leave
the house wearing those shoes.
A gay man wouldn't leave
the store wearing those shoes.
Hey, you bought me
these shoes.
Wait a second,
where's the centerpiece?
I knew it was bothering you,
so I threw it in the garbage.
Really, Phyllis? You
didn't just put it in your car?
Nope.
Which garbage?
It's not there anymore.
A man emptied the garbage
into a bigger garbage
and then I heard someone say
they were locking the garbage.
You are out
of control, Phyllis.
Come on, sweetie. We both
knew how this was gonna end.
Before we bring out
our guest of honor tonight,
we are very proud to introduce a
great philanthropist, and a great guy,
Robert California.
Thank you.
Why do we love dogs?
Want me to tell you why?
There is no answer.
Our love for them
confounds reason.
Do you believe this guy?
The State Senator Robert
Lipton loves dogs.
He asked me if I loved dogs.
You know what I said?
Yes.
Not a joke. That,
that was not even a joke.
Bella here was a
therapy dog for 10 years.
When her owner passed away, she
came to this organization for placement.
But people don't often
adopt older dogs.
So Bella and 11
heroes like her
are being cared for by
our generous volunteers
because, frankly,
nobody else will.
I will.
I will take all
of those dogs.
Andy, that's very
kind, but...
No, no, no. This guy can
talk and talk all he wants,
but it's not that
complicated.
Andy, why don't we discuss
this... No, no, no. It's about
being there for someone after it's
become inconvenient for them to be around.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Andy Bernard
and I am going to take
that bitch home.
That is a female
dog reference.
This bitch
understands loyalty.
Sassy human reference.
Thank you.
I will take Bella.
Aw!
And every single
one of her friends.
Oh, God.
This way.
Hope you all learned
something. Okay.
Huey's going to need his
medication once every 90 minutes.
You can administer it orally,
but he's going to puke it up.
So other end's best.
Don't split up Daisy and Mojo,
because Daisy will start to...
I was going to say bark,
but it's more of a scream.
I'm so ready to love
all of these animals.
This one's even bonding
with me already.
I know. Kenny's
a therapy dog.
He apparently thinks you're in
some kind of emotional crisis.
Stupid dog.
If you would like to talk about this
some more, my door is always open.
So here's my office number
and my cell number.
Thank you.
Okay.
Well, it looks like he
really did just want
to talk about the issues.
I'm sorry, Oscar.
No, sorry about what? There's
nothing to be sorry about here.
No, I'm certainly not disappointed that
Angela's husband wasn't hitting on me.
I'd have to be a
monster to root for that.
A lonely, aging monster.
Tacos were on sale.
Eight for $3.
Oh, great.
Okay.
Oh. Oh. Oh...
These tacos.
Mm-hmm. Mmm...
Uh...
Mmm.
Mmm. Oh!
Huh.
Mmm.
Well, that's hit the spot.
Um...
Very savory.
What do you do with
the crispy holder?
Here, let's try this again.
Here, don't put
your finger in...
Yeah, just hold it like
that. Hold it to the side.
Right.
Hold it to the side.
Lean it to the side.
Look at me, like this.
She's trying.
The winner of the three-day
trip to the Skytop Lodge
is Dwight Schrute!
Yes!
The year-long membership to
Scranton Bikram Yoga is...
Dwight Schrute!
Oh, yes!
Yeah!
A one hour appointment with the
"Kissing Magician” goes to Dwight Schrute.
Oh, yeah!
Well I think I can save
us all some time.
Dwight Schrute has
won every single item here.
Thank you very much!
All I had to do was look up
the prices, idiots. Suck it!
Well, Dwight, yes, you
certainly are a record breaker.
Your donation is the largest
we've ever received
at over $34,000.
Speech!
Come on. Speech, speech!
Thank you.
Wow, I can't tell you
what an honor it is
to support this
thing.
And obviously that amount of
money is no concern to me whatsoever.
But I want to ask
you something.
When did it become
all about the money?
When did it become about
the flower arrangements?
And the white
wine spritzers?
Hmm?
And all the dinner rolls?
You people should be
ashamed of yourselves.
How many courses did
we have tonight?
Two? Three, maybe?
If you chose the pudding.
I mean, what waste. These tables
tarted up like Victorian whores.
Let's remember we are all here
for the dog society.
He's what's important,
whatever his name is.
Not any of this.
So that is going to be
my donation to you.
Thank you and good night.
Whoa!
Uh...
Oscar. Nice to
see you again.
It was lovely.
And don't forget to call. Okay.
Thanks so
much for coming.
Why does this always
happen to me? Ahh!
I just feel so
bad for Angela.
Apparently, there were some
silly rumors going around tonight.
We are very much in love.
Very much in love.
So it just goes on under
here like this?
That's right.
Oh, God. Yeah, you
never get used to that.
Hey, just wanted to check in
to see how you're doing.
I am so great.
He's great.
We're all great.
Twelve dogs.
This is my life now.
I'm a dog nurse.
Look at that one,
though. He's smiling.
Yeah, he should be. It's
his first day without a muzzle.
This is the greatest thing
that has ever happened to me.
Absolutely, it's...
Yes.
Awesome.
I'm sorry.
Are you guys nuts?
He's not doing great.
He was fired.
This is terrible.
This is literally the worst thing
that has ever happened to you.
Not the best.
You're right.
He's right. I am a mess.
This whole night I've been trying
to convince you guys that I'm fine.
I guess I thought that if I could
convince you that I'm fine, maybe...
Maybe you would
think it, too.
I'm sorry,
it's just, I...
I don't get to be in a lot of
human conversations, so...
Okay. Well, Andy, listen, it's
okay if you don't feel totally settled.
This is all very fresh.
Yeah, I mean, admitting that
you need help is the first step.
Yes, and also focusing
on the positive.
Like, I got a lot of good
things going on.
Yeah, like that
rock opera.
You could always
do that, right?
Yeah, I do. I have that.
Yeah.
You're going
to be all right.
No. No, he's not.
Yes, I am.
Thank you, Kev.
You're welcome.
Sometimes I feel like
everyone I work with is an idiot.
And by sometimes,
I mean all times.
All the times.
Every of the time.
So, some of us ended up
adopting those elderly dogs.
It's been great.
Pepper's been getting me
out of the house. Going on runs.
My dog Ruby
doesn't do anything.
She just lays
there all day.
She's so chill.
What do you
feed her?
Well, I put out Pro Bow Wow,
but she barely touches it.
She's so dainty.
Is she sick?
How are her poops?
Doesn't really poop.
It's perfect.
Nothing to pick up.
She just kind of lies there
all day like a good girl.
I put on the TV for her,
but I have to prop her eyes
open SO she can see it.
Does she smell?
She smells horrible.
It's unbelievable.
But I don't want to
put her in the bath.
"Cause I'm afraid
that she'll drown.
People seem awful
interested in you, Ruby.
Guess they're
just jealous, right?
Yeah, that a girl.
That a girl.
Man, that stinks.