Oops. A little help.
Wow, your hair
is really thinning.
Standing is proven to be
healthier, increases productivity
and just looks cooler.
Picture someone
doing something heroic.
Now, was he sitting
or standing?
Not counting FDR.
Every second you sit there
is an hour off your life.
Look at all of you.
I feel like you're
in a suicide cult.
No, no, no. You're
way off on that one.
Are you really
comfortable standing there?
I tried one of those, and I just
couldn't find the sweet spot.
Hey, guys, let's just all admit
it, okay? Dwight's better than us.
He had the guts
to stop sitting,
and he's never, ever
gonna go back on it, right?
That's right, Jim.
Hey, man.
Taking a
load off, huh?
No. Putting a
load on, more like.
Good luck with that.
Last thing I need is luck.
Thank you so much.
What are you up to?
Oh, look out.
Just... What are you doing?
Think fast. Ha ha!
Give that back. Come on. Prank!
That's real creative.
You know what, you're
right. It's not my best.
"Cause you could
easily just bend over
and pick that up,
right?
I could. I just don't
feel like it, loser.
Because you're sitting?
Standing.
Okay.
Don't!
Because you're sitting?
Standing.
You know
I have to do this.
I know.
Whoa!
Andrew Baines Bernard.
I think you could
just do Andy Bernard.
Andrew Baines Bernard.
I love filling
these out 'cause it's like,
Oh, I'm taking a test,
but I know the answers.
In four seconds, my wife is going
to be coming through that door.
I told her she
could work here.
Under no circumstances
can that be allowed to happen.
There you are, honey.
How on earth did
you miss the elevator?
What was that?
I don't know.
He wasn't talking to me.
But if I were you,
I wouldn't hire his wife.
That's why my foundation,
the Dream For
A Wish Foundation,
is gonna put them
out of business.
They're not gonna know what
hit them.
Everyone, I'd like
to introduce my wife,
Mrs. Robert California.
Mrs. California,
this is everyone.
Hello.
Hi.
Welcome.
Call me Susan, please.
Last night at dinner,
Susan and I were talking
about her returning
to work.
So she's here today
to see if there's a good fit.
Something tells me it
just might work out.
This is Andy Bernard,
the regional manager.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
Hey there.
It's a pleasure. Welcome.
Thank you.
Andy, would you
be so kind
as to show Susan
around the office,
introduce her to
various departments,
find a place
where she'll shine?
I would love to,
but I have to be
completely honest
with you guys.
We're 100% staffed up.
Andy, let's see if there's a
good fit first, then we'll talk.
All right.
Knock, knock, knock
You don't have to say
it if you're doing it.
Remember how you said
that you were looking
for a place in the office
to do calisthenics
and aerobics?
Ah, weightlifting, yeah.
Well, today's
your lucky day.
I have opened,
in this very office building,
Dwight Schrute's
Gym for Muscles.
Want to take a look?
I'll take a look.
Your path from
obesity begins right here.
I've been meaning to
join a gym. For my health.
I used to say I wanted to live long
enough to see a black president.
I didn't realize how
easy that would be.
So now I want to
live long enough
to see a really,
really gay president
or a supermodel president.
I want to see all the
different kinds of presidents.
Obese people in my office
building are a drain on resources.
Chairs wear out faster.
It takes more freon
to keep them cool.
They flush the
toilets more often.
Plus, their massive BMs
bust the rivets on my pipes.
But a gym turns
fat into cash.
All right, the DM
Express is pulling out.
All right, well, it was really
nice to meet you, Brian.
Ah, it's actually Ryan.
Oh, Ryan.
Yeah.
Bitch.
We will start
here at Erinville.
Hi.
Reception.
Your classic
one-man operation.
Although, I was
watching a movie,
and Meryl Streep
had two secretaries.
I was watching a movie, and a
bunch of apes took over San Francisco.
Just saying.
Two secretaries could convey
a sense of importance
and success to our clients.
Certainly worth exploring.
Wouldn't you agree, Andy?
I'll explore exploring
it. - Good.
Seems like you have
this under control,
so I'll just duck out and
run the company for a while.
Okay.
Okay, next stop
on the tour, sales.
Here we go. Station
stop, Jim Halpert.
Oh, boy, our resident
truth teller. Uh...
All right, have at it.
Let her rip.
What do you hate
about this place?
Well, it's sales,
SO you have to be able
to live in the
world of rejection.
Maybe you do.
Hi, I'm Dwight.
Sales is really not so
hard, okay. It's paper.
We have it,
and they want it so bad
they are willing
to pay for it.
Jim?
Well, it's not that easy.
It's kind of
sometimes difficult.
It's the second-easiest
job in the world.
Being a mom.
I love shopping.
And sales is just
the other side of that.
That's true.
You know, if you joined
our sales department,
you would be working
very closely with our
department head,
Mr. Dwight Schrute.
That's me.
Dwight, why don't you tell
Susan about some of your hobbies.
Oh... Mmm-hmm. Survival skills.
Ranking of animals.
Maybe over a beer
after she's closed her first
sale.
Well, make that a red wine and
I'll tell you my animal rankings.
How am I
supposed to pull this off?
The entire office is being nicer to
her than they've ever been to me.
What I wouldn't give
for one of Phyllis'
classic room-clearing
farts right now.
Ready?
What do you think?
Huh?
Umm, no.
No. This is not a gym.
This is like a
scene out of Saw V.
You haven't even
looked around yet.
Look.
Gravel bucket squat yoke.
Right?
Hmm.
Dedicated phone
book ripping station.
You ever cut tin before? No.
Five yards in and your
forearms will be on fire.
Plus, I will buy
the tin back from you
that you cut for
two cents a yard.
Now, let's go
over membership.
I'm gonna need
the first month's
and the last month's
up front for $49 a month.
But every third
month is $59 a month.
But the fourth month is a
discount month at $19 per month.
Obviously, you know
how a gym works.
So you know I'm not
gonna pay money for this.
You want people to
come to your gym?
Make a real gym.
Darryl.
I was thinking accounting
might be a good fit
because I really
clicked with Oscar,
and I do have some
experience with bookkeeping.
But we already have a
surplus of accountants as it is.
I would work in customer
service, um, HR, even.
Those are fully
staffed as well.
Are you telling me that there's
no one in this entire office
that could use
an extra pair of hands?
Yes.
I am the CEO, and I am telling
an employee of mine what to do.
Let me beat around
the bush for a second.
Our chairman of the board has
some very strong feelings...
Robert, it's all right.
This is very uncomfortable.
Obviously, there's no place for
me here, so thank you for trying.
Why don't we
just let it go?
No.
Absolutely not.
Andrew, there must be
something you can do.
There must be. Think.
Well, there are
a lot of considerations.
I would be eternally grateful.
It's not a bad thing
to have the CEO owe you one.
All right!
Well, then, welcome aboard.
So what happens next?
We get you over to HR and then
get you set up with accounting.
Hang on.
- Hello?
- Say "hello, grandma.”
Hi, gam-gam.
Hold one finger up
to Susan. You'll just be a second.
You numbskull!
You were given
a very simple task.
I could not have been
more clear with you.
Now say, "Are you
taking your medicine?"
Are you taking your med-meds?
Why can you not say
exactly what I tell you?
Undo this. Undo it.
You didn't say good-bye
to your grandmother.
We promised we'd
never say good-bye.
Attention! I am
now accepting memberships
for the Dwight Schrute
Gym for Muscles.
First 20 members
can take advantage
of our "pay what
you weigh" promotion.
All I need
is another gym.
As if I don't
have enough drama.
We have a gym at home.
It's called the bedroom.
Who's spotting who?
"Don't use the bike
in the corner,
"that's Bruce's.
Jeremy says..."
Enough. Oscar, enough.
Kelly?
I have these sneakers,
which are basically just
like a gym for your feet, so...
That's okay. I know
how to build a business.
You gotta bet the
black people to do it
to get the white
people to do it.
Then you gotta get the
black people to stop doing it.
One step at a time.
Did you bring your
passport with you?
Who walks around
with their passport?
Well, I do.
Always ready
for adventure.
Have you had any?
No.
Hey, guys.
So Robert doesn't want
his wife working here.
So now that she is,
we have to drive her away.
Andy, if he didn't want her working
here, then why did you hire her?
Oscar, it was a mistake.
But one that can be fixed
by all of us being mean to her.
How can we do that?
She's simply wonderful.
This is all pathetic.
I am not asking,
I am ordering.
How mean are
we talking about?
It would be great if
she were gone by lunch.
Erin, you're up. Find her a place
to work, but not too comfortable.
Got it. I know exactly
which stapler to give her.
Here you go.
Um, do you think it
would be possible
to move to that
desk over there?
Because this seems a bit cramped,
and I don't have a computer.
Well, that's a sales desk.
Yeah. You need to be over
here with us accountants.
Just sit here
and be quiet.
And if you have a question,
just raise your hand.
But I'm gonna save you some time,
sweetie, and give you the answer now.
I don't know.
No, I don't think
we should be trying
to make this
place seem unpleasant.
I think we should
let this place
just crush her
spirit by itself.
I mean, it knows
what it's doing.
That's Gerald.
Oh, wow. So cute.
Oh, that is so cute.
Oh, he's so tiny.
Is he in a ladle?
Yeah, he's in a ladle.
That's adorable. How on
earth did you get him in a ladle?
He did it himself.
Is that ladle
stainless or...
Oh, stainless.
Williams Sonoma.
Excuse me, waiter,
there's a dog in my soup.
It's
not that kind of ladle.
Very cute.
Let me see.
Just the battery
on these things.
I'm sorry,
I've gotta recharge this.
I get it.
Last time I had a job,
I remember I hated
the boss' wife.
Of course, she was
married to Robert.
Your employees don't
seem to be taking to me.
Andy!
Andy, could you
step in here, please?
We'll fix this.
What is going on?
Please.
Ah, Andrew, my wife
has brought up an issue
that requires your attention.
So, if you'll excuse me,
I should step out,
get to the ATM before that homeless
man sets up camp for the night.
Okey-dokey, artichokey.
You hate it, don't you?
Do you not want me here?
Why would you say that?
It's okay.
I understand. I'm not
sure how I would feel
about having the boss'
wife work for me either.
It's not that exactly.
But it is something.
Let's just say that if you
don't want to work here,
I am totally
prepared to respect that.
Why would you not
want me working here?
I don't know.
I think I understand
what you're going through.
My husband can be a very
difficult man to read, can't he?
Yes!
The dude is an enigma.
So he is mixed up
in this, isn't he?
Got it.
What do you
think you're doing?
Getting my sweat on.
I build you this
temple to the human body,
and you're lifting
what, five pounds?
I just did, like,
35 minutes on the treadmill.
I was watching you. You want
to know how long it really was?
Eight minutes!
No.
Dude, I'm gonna be
here all week, right?
Five days a week.
I figure I'll start slow.
Is that the same philosophy
you apply to buffalo wings?
I want you to bring that same
buffalo wing passion to this gym!
I'm gonna make you
look like Lebron James!
It's Lejon Brames.
That's what I said.
Yeah.
Get it right.
I know.
Cameras...
Still here. Terrific.
Andy and I had
a great conversation.
And I just want
to let you know
that I am not going
to be working here.
Well, that's a shame.
It just was one of
those things... Is it?
Because we
talked about it,
and it seems like that
might be what you want.
Which is fine.
Where did this come from?
Did Andy say that?
No, he did not.
But I could tell
he was struggling
to understand what
was expected of him.
What's the struggle? He made
a great call, hired a great person.
You sure about that?
Absolutely.
No games?
No games.
Because Andy seemed to
think there was some information
he was not able
to share with me.
Enough of this. I
mean, real... Enough.
It's gotten way out of hand.
Andrew, this is my wife.
Whatever privacy you were trying
to protect between us, I thank you for.
But it is not
welcome right now.
Just be honest.
Andy...
Yes.
Why do you keep
looking at my husband?
Andy, just answer
the question.
No games?
No games.
Okay.
I mean, it was kind
of funny, actually.
Robert storms in,
and he says,
"In four seconds,
my wife's gonna be in here.
"I told her she
could work here.
"Under no circumstances
can that be allowed to happen."
You lying son of a bitch!
Tell my wife you're lying.
I am lying.
I am a compulsive liar.
That's not true, is it?
No, it's not.
I tell the truth
most of the time,
and I was just telling the
truth about your husband.
Jim knows. He was there.
This is preposterous.
Robert...
Let's get Jim in here.
Where's Jim?
He just rolled out
and crawled out.
Can you call security, tell
them to keep an eye out for him?
Time to settle this.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hold on, hold on.
I just need to get through.
Just real quick.
Real quick, open... Okay.
That's weird.
Well, he's gotta be
around here somewhere.
Ow! Ow!
Ow!
Creed, I was
never here, all right?
Okay. What about
your friend?
Oh, boy.
This is my gym, my rules. You do
exactly as I say, no questions asked.
Yeah, I'm gonna
ask questions,
and I might not
do what you say.
First thing, we're gonna
stretch the pelvic bowl.
Ready? Get down on the floor.
Okay, I'm not doing that.
Really?
Too embarrassing
for you? Huh?
You wish that every exercise was
strutting around the gym like the Fonz?
Well, how do you think
the Fonz got so cool?
He stretched
his pelvic bowl.
I didn't know
Darryl joined.
Looks that way.
Nice pelvic bowl. Deep.
Hello, Jim.
No, no. No, no, no!
Don't. Damn it, Tuna!
So, I think you know
what we want to know.
Do 1?
Yes.
I know. I do.
Jim, I've had enough
of your unhelpfulness.
I really wish I could help.
I'm not really sure how I can.
For God's sake,
did Robert tell you
that he didn't
want me working here?
That's the thing.
See, I didn't want to get in
the middle of this. Still don't.
But here's something.
I feel that maybe,
if we take a step back,
this is a simple case of
anxiety to work with a spouse.
I think we've
got ourselves an answer.
That makes
complete sense, right? No...
Thank you all for a
wonderful day. Perfect!
Yes? Jim...
Answer the question,
please.
I don't know what you
want me to tell you.
To be really honest,
my wife works here.
And I love it.
She literally
makes me work harder.
She makes me smarter. She
makes me remember why I'm here.
And between us, she's on
maternity leave right now,
and I would love to leave
this room and see her face.
I would love it.
I don't know how this helps,
but it's just
what I'm thinking.
All right. Thanks.
Yes. All right.
Uh...
Yeah.
Thank you.
Andy.
Hey, Mrs. California.
Hey. I'm sorry about the
position you were put in today.
You know, honestly, we
all wanted you to work there.
Except for him.
Especially me.
Yes, I thought we
really hit it off.
Yeah.
Well, different circumstances.
Who knows?
Maybe after all
this settles down...
Totally.
It's a date.
Hmm?
You're nothing!
You're so weak!
You call yourself
a man? Huh?
This doesn't help me. I don't
respond to that kind of strategy.
Okay, fine.
Finish your set on your own, and
never come back to my gym again!
Dwight, come back and spot me.
All right, I'll help you.
But first, you gotta
tell me what your goal is.
What do you want?
To push this bar up.
No! Because if that was the
case, the bar would be up by now.
What is your goal?
Help me!
What do you want?
To look good for Val!
Val Kilmer?
I don't buy it,
that doesn't make any sense.
Wow.
I figured out your goal.
I am gonna make you the buffest
dude Val Kilmer has ever seen.