Today is the test launch
day for the inaugural Sabre store.
And I, Dwight Schrute, am in
charge of the entire operation.
If I can prove myself today and
the store is a hit with the media,
and Nellie sees this,
the vice presidency is mine.
Hey, are you
holding this chair?
Because I feel like
I'm going to fall off.
Yeah. Yes. Yes. I'm not
wearing the right shoes for this.
We went
over this, okay?
Your tiny fingers
make the best knots.
Hey, strangers. I'm so stoked
for the Sabre store opening.
Hey, my name's Tabitha. I'm
camped out in front of the Sabre store
so I can be first in line
for the new Pyramid.
Psst!
It's me, Erin. Dwight had
me pretend to be a hipster
to create hype
and it's working.
There's already people
camped out behind me.
Test launch day, people.
Now, I would like to fill you
in on a little secret about me.
To inspire you today.
Now I know you probably all
think I'm this patrician goddess.
But here's the truth.
I was born in the little
working-class town of Basildon,
and until the age of 32,
I talked like this.
Which was
bloody horrendous, innit?
I came from dirt.
No, lower than...
What's lower than dirt?
Loam. Magma. Mantle.
Outer core. Inner core.
Yeah, thank you. Loam.
Bloody loam I came from.
I hit rock bottom when I
auditioned for the Spice Girls.
I didn't even
get a callback.
Which Spice Girl?
The black one.
I never stood a chance.
Okay.
Now think about my
journey here today
and let it inspire
your journey.
Okay. Nellie, thank
you. Thank you so much.
Yep. Yep.
Today is press day, and press is
going to make or break this store.
And for a tech company, press
can only mean one thing, bloggers.
Dossier on bloggers.
Bloggers are gross. Bloggers
are obese. Bloggers have halitosis.
You're going to love them.
Ryan is going to be
the main event today.
He is the pitchman
who is going to give
the feisty yet
profound speech
worthy of a world's fair.
Ryan, you ready to do this?
When people see
this presentation,
they're going to
in their pants.
- Come on, man.
- Come on.
Okay.
Seriously disgusting.
Cathy, you will be the hot
girl who talks to bloggers.
Ugh! Kill me.
It was my idea.
Packer, you will be the sexual
predator who has come to prey
on the trendy teenage girls who
are obsessed with the Pyramid.
Ah...
That is excellent.
I don't see what
that gets us,
but I'm a team player.
Perfect casting, right?
Schrute's out to get me,
but I'm playing the long game.
As soon as he messes up, I
swoop in like a sexual predator.
I want to create a sense
of wonder and enthusiasm,
as if at the end of E.T., candy
poured out of the screen.
Do you understand?
I want to get
goose pimples.
Speaking of pimples,
let's release the bloggers!
Morning, everyone.
Oh, Andy, guess what
happened to me this morning.
Don't care. Tell me
later. Listen, it's important.
You've got to hear this.
What do you got?
Oh, my God.
Do you have a black eye?
Yes, I do, Phyllis.
I woke up at 4:00 a.m.
by accident,
in time for
the paper to be delivered.
Guess what?
It's not a kid on a bike.
It's a man in a car.
Andy, who punched you?
Hey, I was on the can. What's
this about a black guy in the office?
Black eye, Meredith.
Will someone please explain
what's going on here?
Since the interesting thing happened
until now, so much time has passed.
It's like my
life is buffering.
Here's what happened. Pam
and I were arriving for the day
and there was a gang in the
parking lot, on bikes, on motorcycles.
And they just
were hassling Pam.
That's true.
They had weapons.
Weapons.
I just stepped in lo talk
some sense into them.
But these were not the kind
of people who use their words.
Punches were going,
and I ducked a few,
landed a couple, and
I was fighting them off.
It was a totally,
like, senseless crime.
Thank goodness he was
there. - Good job, Andy.
I didn't do anything any
of you wouldn't have done.
Open the gates!
There's plenty for
everyone. No need to panic.
everyone. There's plenty...
Don't stampede.
No need to stampede, sir.
Okay, okay! Hey, hey! It's going
to be fine! It's going to be fine!
There's plenty of Pyramids!
Come on,
I was in line before you.
So you're
a blogger, right?
Yeah.
Blogger.
God, stay away.
Oh, I always get in
trouble around bloggers.
I'm trying to be
a good girl for once.
Uh, yeah, I already bought my
Pyramid, but I don't want to leave yet.
I haven't had so much fun
since seeing Zooey Deschanel
at the Coachella
music festival. So fun.
How can we feel safe knowing
that there are gangs here?
We should call the police
right now! - Yes!
No, no, no, no, no, no! We
don't need to call the police.
They'll just ask
everybody questions,
get up In everyone's
business, right, Pam?
Police are a hassle. We
settled this on the street.
And my eye will heal.
But if the police come,
then we will forever stain our
neighborhood as a troubled area.
Why would you care what the
police think of our neighborhood?
Because I have
neighborhood pride. 18505!
Guys, guys,
that's so vague.
You got to do
the zip plus four.
18505-7427.
Look, I don't feel safe. I
think we should call the police.
Yes. Exactly,
we need to feel safe,
which is why Toby is
teaching us self-defense.
Me?
Toby, will you
teach us self-defense?
Yeah. I can't believe
you remembered.
I do self-defense.
I'll go put on my cup.
Great.
- Yes!
- Okay.
I wasn't sure which
one of you was Chuck.
Yeah, no, it seems
to be going great.
Andy got beat up by
a fifth grade girl?
Look at that guy, he's
got a Sabre phone on him,
he's not even using it.
This is a perfect photo
for my daily fail blog.
Uh, I got to go.
Okay.
Dwight, what is a fail?
That sounds bad.
No, no, no, it's good.
It's really...
On the Internet, that's a
really good, good thing.
Are you trying to
sabotage this entire event?
I'm very sorry.
We gave you an Arrowhead
for free for the day.
How hard would it have
been to do this? Hmm?
Hello. Hi, sweetie, it's Jim. I'm
calling you from my new Arrowhead,
which is why my
voice is crystal clear
and my hand
won't ever get tired
because of
the ergonomic shape.
I'm really sorry. Is there anything I
can do? Maybe pretend to be Chuck?
You could have
pretended to be Chuck.
I begged you to
pretend to be Chuck.
But you chose to be yourself
and you can no longer be Chuck.
Surrender the tri-pack.
You know what
you have to do.
Point it towards
the store, idiot.
You know what I mean?
Pick one of these
buttons and just...
Damn it. Take over.
Oh, hey, hey, hey, you guys.
You must be lost.
Listen.
Excuse me, sir.
The fountain where you can feed
the pigeons is out behind the bank.
Tell your great-grandson
to bring his kid by.
Okay, so long.
Here we go.
Erin! Psst! Come on.
The elderly suck the life out of
the young. Get them out of here.
We are closed.
Come on.
Self-defense is not some
fun boxing match, okay?
This is about
escaping with your life.
So strike,
scream and run.
All right,
let's try it.
That may have
been my fault.
What the hell, Toby?
Okay, look, in a
real crisis situation,
you're not going to
have time to think.
Okay?
So just remember IAATG.
"It's All About The Groin."
What if you're being
attacked by a smallish man
who happens to
not have a groin?
I don't think
that's very common.
But what if
you're being attacked
by a 4'11" man
who's penis-less.
Why are you fixated on this
hypothetical transgendered attacker?
Why don't we
start with the basics?
Show us how to defend
ourself against a baby
and then like
a fifth-grade girl
and then, you know, if we
have time, on up to a scary man.
The most common scenario is a
larger man attacking a smaller female.
So in that scenario,
what if the victim
sucker punches
the attacker in the face?
What can the attacker then
do to better protect himself?
It's interesting
that you're drawn
to the point of
view of the attacker.
You would like
The Turn of the Table.
Okay? The latest
Chad Flenderman novel.
From the point of view of
his nemesis, Dr. Lucifer Woo.
Can I please leave?
I have a rape flute.
All right, well, let's try one
simple technique together.
Okay, why doesn't
everyone stand?
Okay, so,
you're being attacked,
you've got your hands up,
simple palm strike to the chin.
Up to the chin.
One, two.
Cathy, I would like to introduce
you to Fatty Gruesome.
He is a freelancer
for Wired magazine.
Patty Grossman.
I'm a woman.
But you still work
for Wired, right?
Yes.
Good.
Okay. Flirt away.
Sabre. It's time
to come home.
Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, I think... It seemed
like you were a little nervous.
Yeah, no Sherlock.
Can somebody please tell
me something encouraging
about this presentation
before I go out there in front
of a million people and do it?
Okay. I know!
I know, champ.
Just calm down
because, listen,
when you are out in
front of all those people...
Yeah, what?
...you just
need to realize
so much rides on this.
You have no idea.
Dwight.
I'm trying to make
him feel important.
I wish Kelly were here.
She always knew what to say.
Um...
Oh, Ryan, you're so smart.
You're smarter
than Mark Zuckerberg
and those Google guys
all combined.
You're so ignorant. You barely
know what you're talking about.
It's so ridiculous.
You really need to
read a couple of books.
What's a book?
Oh, my God.
You're so embarrassing.
My mom would say
the best stuff though.
You can...
You can do it, Ryan.
And you know that
I'm capable of this?
You're the only one
who can do it, sweetie.
What did you think
of the presentation?
I thought
it was great, sweetie.
I would just
fix that one...
"Fix" means you hate it!
I knew it!
I need something
to drink!
Jim, get him a water.
No, not a water,
a sports drink!
I hate everything
in that fridge.
Not red! Get me
something yellow or green
from a nearby store.
Not red!
Why are you just
standing there?
Go to a nearby store and get
him a yellow or green sports drink.
Now if your attacker is
willing to defile a corpse,
you better stop
playing dead right away
and just make it known that you're
alive.
Forgive me
for interrupting.
I believe my daughter had an
altercation with somebody here,
some fancy gentleman
with a squeaky voice?
I think you
guys might have the wrong office.
That's him.
The guy I hit.
What?
You've
got to be kidding me.
Poor Andy.
First you got beat up by a
gang and now she kicks your ass.
No, Kevin.
What about the lady
you hit with a pinecone?
There.
That chubby one.
I just had a baby.
Yesterday?
Wow.
Apologize.
Sorry I kicked your ass in
front of your "thin" girlfriend.
How about we wait until next
year after you have your kid?
You know what?
Tiffany's going to college.
Listen, I don't know what
you guys are talking about,
but I guess I'll just accept your
apology so we can get on with our day.
God bless. A friend of
mine uses your paper.
You do good work.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
So, Toby, I think we should do
a different self-defense seminar,
how to protect ourselves
against tiny little girls.
There's no shame in
getting beaten up by a girl.
My ex-wife used
to demolish me.
No, there is
shame in it, okay?
We have to draw
the line somewhere.
Oh, my God, I think I see
the imprint of a Ring Pop.
Oh...
Have you seen Erin?
I'm on break.
Oh, my God.
No, hey, bloggers, where
do you think you're going?
No, you got to stay
for the big presentation.
We got this
young whiz kid, Ryan.
He's like an even
more handsome Bill Gates.
When's the presentation?
It's moments away!
Just stay here.
Hey, Uncle Lucas,
it's your nephew, Ryan.
Honestly, I could use a
prescription for Ritalin right now.
Well, I know you did
one for Aunt Carol.
So it's different
because it's your wife?
Well, that doesn't
make any sense to me.
How are you doing?
Don't talk to me right now.
I'm sorry.
I know you're my boss,
but seriously,
you need to get
the hell out of my face.
Your little man is
unraveling. Now go and fix it.
Sorry about
kicking you out.
It's just we don't want our
brand associated with death.
It's okay. I'll go to the Costco
and search for handsome men.
You're not married yet?
Oh, I was. My husband
was my best friend.
He passed away.
My best friend
was my boss, Andy.
We dated for a while,
but since then,
he rejected me and
we're not really friends.
Someone rejected you? With
that body and those bazongas?
Forget him.
Yeah. Forget him! And you
should forget your husband.
Well...
How long has he
been in the bathroom?
Like 10 minutes.
Geez, what's he
doing in there?
Oh, that's my phone.
Am I allowed to answer it
or are you going to freak out?
Are there bloggers around?
It's Ryan.
“I'm sorry. I lied.
I'm not in the bathroom.
"I can't do it.
I need to see my mom.
“I'm going home."
What is the delay here?
Where is Ryan?
Why is he not here?
I had to send him home.
As brilliant and
creative as he is,
he is nothing
compared to this guy!
Uh...
What?
That's right. Will you
just give us a second?
You are going to bloody ruin
it. You're going to bloody ruin it
because you're a no-good,
half-assed, cockeyed numpty!
Okay. Okay.
Jim. I'm not doing
the presentation.
Look at me. Look at me.
Look at this face.
This is not
the face of a performer.
This is the face of a scary
apparition you see before you die.
I'm telling you, if you don't
do this, I don't stand a chance.
Please, Jim.
Okay, I'll do it.
Oh, my God. Okay!
Go get into Ryan's costume
and check out his notes.
A costume?
Of course
there's a costume.
Oh, this is going
to be great.
There's nothing like
some last minute changes
to really energize
a presentation. Huh?
Did you pass out in there?
What is taking so long?
I've been in here
for 20 seconds.
Hurry up! Let me in! I want
to watch you get dressed.
Did you find
the eyeliner?
I'm not wearing eyeliner.
You are wearing
eyeliner, Jim.
Time, space, gender.
There
are no rules anymore.
All boundaries
are breaking down
in the wake of
the infinite future.
The only thing that... The
only thing that remains...
The only thing
that remains
are the things that have
stood the test of time.
Love, values, and of
course, the Pyramids.
The strongest shape
ever constructed.
A shape that fits all
other shapes inside of it.
No, that's...
Mmm. It's true.
This is the future
because this is the past.
I've been through a
lot of issues in my life.
I've seen drug addiction,
unemployment.
I've been in a relationship
that tore my heart apart
without ever being able to
accept that love drove the pain.
Yep.
When I was 10 years old, my
parents took me to Disneyworld.
I cried the whole time.
I was not able to comprehend
the beauty that was before me.
I just wanted to go home.
This is what the
Pyramid will do for you.
It is the bridge
to the world.
It has the USB port.
Wireless will be
available in 2013.
You can play anything
from Chuck to Cars 2.
With the Pyramid, you have
the connection to everything.
In time and space.
Psst!
Oh.
Sabre. It's time
to come home.
All right.
Thank you so much. Wow!
Wow!
And good night!
Yeah!
Okay, this isn't over.
Let's stay focused, okay?
We made fun of Andy earlier
for getting beat up by a little girl,
but little things
can be dangerous.
Whether it's a gremlin
or Chucky the doll,
the key is to
throw it in something,
like a fireplace or
a tub of electricity.
Okay, good point. Um...
Good point? What
is a tub of electricity?
I don't know.
With all due respect,
we know what we're
defending against.
It's a 12-year-old
female bully.
I was a 12-year-old bully.
Great! I think Kelly
should attack Toby.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's not
a bad idea actually
because I have had
a lot of pent-up aggression.
- Thanks.
- Good! Go!
I don't know whether
this is gonna help.
All right, Kelly!
We should stay to maybe
some more traditional models.
You think
you're so pretty?
You're not going to be
so pretty come prom-time!
Okay, this is what's
called... Take that!
...pre-violent posture.
Take that!
Not so pre-violent
anymore!
I'm in what's called
the decision point.
Hey, hey, hey.
Kelly! Kelly!
Ow!
My good eye!
Oh, boy.
Oh, no, I'm not
laughing at you.
I'm laughing at
something that Cece did
on the playground earlier,
yesterday, this morning.
You know why I
got hit by girls?
Because I stood up
for others.
Pam and Toby.
I stepped in and I didn't care
that I was standing up to girls.
You may want to ask yourselves,
where were you when the girls came?
Tough day, yes.
But I feel good.
I put the office
in their place,
took a bunch of painkillers, drank
half a bottle of wine, took my pants off.
I just feel good.
Okay, okay, I will be
the first to admit it.
We could have integrated
more Chuck into the presentation.
Dwight, you're
the vice president.
Yeah!
Okay! Come on!
Right on!
Bam, bam, barn, bam, barn!
Boom!