Hey, so this isn't
matching up with this,
and I'm not sure
which one is right.
Can you just hunt down
the original for me?
Yes, me do.
All right.
Hey, Kev, what were you saying
before about the paperwork?
Me do it now.
Go. Stop worry.
Kevin, do you feel okay?
Me feel good. Body strong.
Sleep big last night.
Yeah, I think we should
get him to the hospital.
Yeah, all right, Kev,
why don't you come with us?
No, he's fine. OSCAR:
No, no, guys. He's fine.
He's always
been like that.
No, he hasn't.
I mean, he's gotten worse
over the years, but...
He's making a statement.
It's an ironic comment
on our expectations of him.
A funhouse image of
our model of Kevin.
You keep think that.
Me mechanic
not speak English,
but he know what me mean
when me say, "Car no go."
And we best friends.
So me think why waste time say
lot word when few word do trick.
Kevin, I appreciate
what you're trying to do.
Thank.
Here we have
a word code.
Same way we have
a dress code.
And what we're
talking about is
basically the speech equivalent
to just wearing underpants.
Sometimes words
you no need use
but need need
for talk talk.
But save time.
More success.
Does it save time, though? Because
we've been here for about an hour.
No me fault.
Kevin, at most you're saving
a microscopic amount of time.
Many small time
make big time.
What are you going to
do with all this time?
See world.
Kevin, you can't possibly save
enough time to see the world.
Kevin, are you saying "see
the world" or SeaWorld?
See world. Oceans.
Fish. Jump. China.
No, see? Right there, that's
the problem with your method
because I still don't know if you're
saying SeaWorld or "see the world."
And it's taking a lot
of time to explain it.
Fine,
fine, I'll talk normally.
When me president,
they see.
They see.
This week we are rolling out the
brand new Sabre tablet, the Pyramid.
Why is it
shaped like that?
So you can tell your clients,
"Unleash the power of the pyramid.”
It's huge.
How much does it weigh?
Oh, no, no, no.
Without the battery pack
and the optional memory
booster, it's barely 3 pounds.
How much memory does
it have without the booster?
Fifty I.
- I'm sorry, "L"?
- Mmm-hmm.
How many L to a K?
You're really
going to want the booster.
How on earth are
we supposed to sell...
I'll take five.
Andy, don't make us
sell this stupid thing.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
This is Dwight's meeting.
Thank you. The...
I just wanted to pop in
and get your opinions
on ties and tie clips.
Which combo do you think
Robert's going to like more?
What do you think, C-Span?
"C-Span"?
Yeah, C-Span.
Cocker spaniel.
Spaniel because of your Spanish
bloodline. Cocker because...
Is this really the best use
of our collective time?
I am still forming a first
impression with Robert.
Once it is formed,
we can all relax, okay?
I'm sorry to hijack your meeting,
D-Dub-Dog, had to pull rank.
Okay, let's look
at some ties.
Here's how I'm going
to help out from now on.
I'm going to not care.
And I'm going to
sit around quietly
waiting for Andy's
inevitable demise.
Your friend
Neil Patrick Harris
really made me laugh
the other night.
D Dog, you have a message.
Erin, you don't
need to call him that.
Andy wants us to, P Dog.
It's okay, E Dog.
Who called?
Justine. She said
she's coming by later.
Your ex-wife?
Wait, I thought
she was a
And you
hated her guts.
No, no, no, I like her.
Well, I was just
quoting you.
I would never say that about
her. I don't know the woman.
No, man. We get
along now, real well.
All right.
Can't wait to meet her.
I'll introduce you.
Yeah, we had a few fights,
I suppose,
but last night we put
a lot of that to bed.
I can't tell you what I did
with my ex-wife last night.
I have to sing it.
We took a shower
We were naked
We...
Oh.
Hi, Dad. I...
Oh, boy.
Hello, Andy.
Excellent tie.
Would you be requiring a cold
beverage while you're here?
I'd love some coffee.
I was looking over your projections
and I think we can do better.
Are you factoring in the whole
national economy declining and all that?
Andy, do you know
why I chose you?
I think I can sum it up
with what I think
is your favorite
ice cream flavor.
Vanilla?
Vanilla? No.
You'll never guess in a million
billion years, you'll never guess.
You were saying you chose me.
There was a reason.
Andy, can you inspire?
Do you have that skillset?
Can I inspire?
I don't know.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, sorry.
Yeah, just put it down.
Mmm.
That is very cold.
Yeah, it's old.
Why would I...
I asked if you
wanted a cold beverage
and you said coffee.
Why don't we get Robert a nice,
hot, fresh cup and I will have this.
Andy, you don't
want that.
I've been craving a
freezing cup of old coffee.
Mmm.
Sorry.
You like her.
I do. Yeah.
She likes you.
You know, we've both been
into each other at different times
and just never
really synced up.
Now we're in this weird
dance and now we're...
I'm afraid you've
lost my interest.
Let me call you back.
I got to go.
If the office
superstore was supposed to
put us little suppliers
out of business,
why are we still here?
Yeah.
This is where we go.
You'd go some place else.
That's not it. That's not the answer.
It's a answer.
It's a wrong answer.
There are no wrong answers.
Take a look
at where you are.
Where you once worked in a dying
industry, you now work at its birth.
Those superstores
are terrified of us.
Anybody know why?
Wait, they're terrified?
Let me tell you how I
buy something these days.
I know what I want, I go on the
Internet and get the best price.
Or I don't know what I want and I
go to a small store that can help me.
The era of personal service
is back. You are back.
You'll find that customers
will pay our higher prices
and then they will
thank us,
and we will say to them,
"You are welcome."
Thank you.
Ooh!
Andrew, I chose you for a
reason. Lead these people.
Show me the best numbers
this place has ever seen.
Last quarter we saw
4% growth. Double it.
You got it.
Double.
Done.
I'm not kidding.
Neither am I.
It's already done.
I'm just kidding.
It's going to take
some time. Double.
Hey.
What's up, guys?
Just thought we'd have
a little rap session.
Talk about business.
See how things are going.
Why don't you start?
If no one else wants to.
I was just thinking about
Robert. Man, what a boss.
Just throws down goals,
you know?
Anyway, how's the sales
doubling project going?
Yeah, how are we
supposed to do that?
We can't just
press a magic button.
Of course not.
There's no magic button.
You have to summon that.
If we could just double our
sales, we already would have.
You're not
making any sense.
He brings up
two good points.
Do you have any new leads? Any
new territories you want us to look into?
Maybe have an in
with a big client
that we could get
our foot in the door?
Dwight, anything?
We could talk about
how fast children grow up
and before you know it,
they're out of the house.
You know what? We need to
get our heads out of the box.
If we did have something,
what would it look like?
What would it be?
Tuna.
New leads, new
territory to look into,
maybe an in with
a big company
that we could get
our foot in the door.
Fart.
Good sesh.
That leg's asleep.
Hello.
I'm looking for
Darryl Philbin?
Don't...
Oh...
You must think... No,
I'm not. I'm using the fax.
This isn't...
No, wait.
I'm not supposed to
represent the company, right?
There's usually
an Erin here, so...
Okay.
Darryl, a girl!
Rub a dub, dub, apricot scrub
What's up, darling?
Everybody,
this is Justine.
- Hi, Justine.
- Hello.
This is Jim, Oscar.
Hi.
Everybody.
Kevin.
Can we go
some place private?
Follow me.
I got a space.
After you. I've been thinking
about you all morning.
I don't know what you did,
I can barely walk today.
D Bone, there you are.
Let me guess.
Somebody needs a brownie.
Lick the spoon?
No. No. That's okay.
I just,
I wanted to ask you about...
Is this about
the profits?
Because if it is, I just don't
see the point. It's so Wall Street.
I know, right? Yeah.
Um...
How is everything?
Good.
Really, really good.
Must be a tough time
to be a family farm.
It is. And beets are not immune.
I made some inroads in salad, but
heirloom tomatoes are pushing back.
What are
you going to do about that?
I don't know,
what do you mean?
Got to be some way you
could double your beet sales.
You wanted the job, the
job is yours, just do the job.
And I'll do mine.
Walnuts?
No!
Have you seen this?
Parenting? Yeah.
This is Cece's
favorite magazine.
She loves
the pictures of babies.
She looks at it when she's on
the potty and she makes the faces.
Have you read it?
Has an adult member of your
family read this particular issue?
I flipped through it.
So you saw the article
on the importance of
taking frequent walks
while you're pregnant?
- Of course, yeah.
- We know that.
I will be taking a morning
walk and an afternoon walk.
Would you like to
join me?
That sounds nice.
Great.
You have a walking buddy.
I do.
Thanks for
coming in, guys.
You don't have to thank
us for coming in. It's our job.
Well, I never got thanked
for coming into a meeting,
and I always wanted to be,
so I'm going to thank people.
What's under the blanket?
This is what's
under the blanket.
We don't get it.
These are incentives. It's how
we're going to double growth.
Now, you're probably all asking
yourselves, "Well, how does this work?"
It seems like a basic reward
system where you give us points
and then we redeem
those points for prizes.
You're exactly right
and you get a point.
Oh.
Uh, is that a vibrator?
20 points.
How does one get a point?
I've outlined
the exact parameters
in an email,
so check your spam folders.
But basically, you do your
job better, you get points.
So collect 15 points and
redeem them for this polar bear.
Why is it all kids' stuff
and a vibrator? It's so gross.
There's lots of stuff.
John Irving, collected
works, 22 points.
Or you can pool your points and
redeem 55 for this maternity shirt. Ahem!
How about you want us to
work harder, pay us more.
I can't.
This points system
is really insulting.
Ooh!
I didn't mean to offend you
and I hope you'll forgive me
because I am very,
very "sari." 16 points.
That's a tablecloth.
What if we went all the
way up to 500 points?
That's a crazy
amount of points.
But what if?
Well, what do you want?
I don't know.
For such a crazy number,
I'd like
something pretty crazy.
All right, for 500 points,
I will wear a dress to work.
That's pretty good. What
about for 1,000 points?
I'll run naked
through the parking lot
with a donut
on my ding dong.
Yeah, you like that?
All right,
for 5,000 points,
I will let you
tattoo whatever you want
on the stern of
the old S.S. Bernard.
No.
Really?
All right. All right. And
you are totally serious?
Swear to God. Hope to die.
Now let's get to work.
Wait, but you did say we
can pool our points, right?
In that case,
- let's get to work, guys.
- Yeah!
Let's do it, guys.
Good!
I can have it to you by
the beginning of next week.
All right,
thank you very much.
Phyllis, Brachen Auto?
Ask for Donald.
Karen's bananas.
Okay.
T-Bag-Bone.
Andrew.
Hold on, one second.
Have you noticed a little bit
of a mood shift around here?
No. I haven't
noticed anything.
Really? Because I sat next to
Stanley for years and this is nap time.
Open eye nap time. He
balances the phone on his shoulder
and just powers down.
Now look at him.
You've got to unleash
the power of the pyramid.
I don't know what
to tell you, man.
Do you think it has something
to do with that incentive program?
Oh, 100%. We all want
to see you tattoo your ass.
Uh...
I think people thought I
was kidding when I said that.
No. You definitely
weren't kidding.
That came across
loud and clear.
Oh, by the way,
I want to hand this in.
120 points?
Yeah. Big sale.
Don't worry about it, though. I
don't really care about the points.
I would like
a point receipt though.
Hey, yes, this is Jim
Halpert calling for Donald.
Can you hold on for one
second? Thank you very much.
Who talked to
Maggie at Kaufman's?
And I'm back.
How are you, sir?
I think you can squeeze a
couple more golf games in, right?
Where's Angela?
Angela, these are yours.
Hey, Kevin,
what are you doing?
Don't talk to me.
Yeah.
Hi. Professor Frank.
Andy Bernard, class of '95.
Hey there, I'm a huge fan of your
management book, Management.
Uh, quick question, I may
be missing a chapter here:
"De-incentivizing."
What are your strategies?
I'm looking for
a real blow to morale.
Uh, why?
Well, um,
I guess you could say
I'm in one of those
classic ass-tattoo-incentive
situations.
Took 'em one day.
Are you ready?
I like it. I like it.
Okay, keep in mind, it's not
too late to choose another prize
and there are some
great new additions.
My car.
For 1,000 points.
Or best offer.
What else you got?
Oh, and then this
was Phyllis' idea.
Oh! >
So nasty, Phyllis.
Oh, my God!
We were hoping you
could do something like this.
So coming out of
his butt is a...
Baby.
Baby. "
Yeah. No problem.
We should think about this. Does
anyone have any better ideas?
I like what we have.
Yeah, nice try.
It's pretty edgy.
I just need
a second outside.
You getting psyched up?
Yeah.
Andy, nobody really expects
you to go through with this.
Toons, what am I
doing here?
Why did Robert pick me?
Confession, I don't
know what I'm doing.
I mean,
do you like it?
You having fun?
I'll tell you this, everybody
else is having a lot of fun.
And you did that.
My ass is only so big. I
mean, I can't do this every day.
But I think it's big enough
to buy you some time
until your next
great idea.
Which, by the way,
I can't wait for.
No one expects me to
go through with this, right?
Absolutely not.
Let's ink my stink.
Yeah!
My heart belongs to music, but
my ass belongs to these people.
Whoa!
Do your worst.
Uh, you can keep your
pants on actually.
If you just drop them
down a bit, that'd be great.
They are already off,
my good sir.
I'd really prefer
they not be down.
Well, I think down's better.
Sweating pretty heavily down there.
Do you think you
could work from this?
We made some
small adjustments.
Okay, you want me to...
Just those few
adjustments. Yeah.
All right.
Let's begin.
This is where I grin
and bear... Ow, ow!
That was just
a cotton swab.
Invest in
softer cotton, sir.
Ow!
Oh!
Obviously you can go
the ass tattoo route
and obviously I'm
going to like it.
Draw some blood!
Ha-ha!
Why did I choose
Andy to run the office?
Because he's all surface, uncomplicated.
What you see is what you get.
It could be a recipe
for mediocrity, yes.
But then again, it might just
be why people fight for him.
It's a Nard dog.
That's my nickity name.
I love it. I love it.
Pull up your pants.
There's something
about an underdog
that really
inspires the unexceptional.
Um, what should we
talk about?
Well, we could talk about
an ethical dilemma I'm having.
Oh, yeah, sure.
I hope I can help.
A coworker of mine is
drinking caffeine while pregnant
and I don't know if I should
call social services about it.
Angela, that's
pretty transparently me.
Maybe.
You know,
it's just herbal tea.
In mugs with trace
amounts of coffee.
Yeah. I think you
should call social services.
I already did.
You know, maybe we should
just have our own pregnancies
and not pretend like
we're in this together.
Fine.