Mrs Landry,
you're looking lovely as ever.
Jimmy McGill.
What are you doing here?
I was in the area, and I thought...
I wonder how my favourite
former client is doing?
And I have cookies.
Oh, you're so sweet. Come on in.
After I made these, I looked down...
and thought, wow,
that looks just like your Felix.
They do.
- You're so thoughtful.
- Well, I was afraid you wouldn't be here.
Thought with that settlement money you
might've moved somewhere swankier.
What do you mean?
The settlement.
The Sandpiper case?
- That's gotta be wrapped up by now.
- Oh, that.
That... That... That's still years away.
- You haven't settled?
- No, I don't know all the details yet...
but Erin... Erin Brill
of Davis & Main, do you know her?
Lovely girl.
She reminds me of a young Mary Martin.
Oh, yes. I have met her.
It's a... It's a wonderful young lady.
Well, she takes care of all that...
and she said
there's still a long way to go.
But you've received an offer, right?
Something sent to you in writing.
I mean, something more than
just Erin and you chatting?
It's probably all here in this box.
I can't make heads or tails of it,
but you are welcome to look.
You sure?
Of course. It's you.
Well, I gotta say...
I can't blame you
for getting mixed up with all this.
I mean, these legal notices, I mean,
no one really understands them.
You know, I've got a law degree.
Sometimes, I can't even...
I can't even...
You haven't...
accepted this?
Erin says we should wait.
But...
Erin doesn't really matter, does she?
I mean,
you're the class representative.
That's a big deal.
That means you, and you alone, decide.
You're...
You are the legal stand-in
for your friends and neighbours.
I don't know about all that, Jimmy.
I just leave it all to the professionals.
Yeah. Sure, sure. Lawyers know best.
But I'm sorry...
if you won the lottery,
I mean, you'd take the lump sum, right?
I mean,
money now is better than money later.
- Bird in the hand?
- I suppose.
More time to enjoy it.
You really should talk to Erin.
She knows all the ins and outs.
Ins and outs. Yeah.
Erin sure knows those.
I'd be happy to talk to Erin.
But I just can't help but wonder
if she's taking every aspect into...
Oh, Jimmy.
I completely forgot.
I'm on my way to chair yoga.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, it's okay.
I probably should be going.
I have a lot to do.
Jimmy.
- Jimmy.
- Rose, Myrtle, Helen.
That chair yoga really works, huh?
You all look 10 years younger.
- Oh, you honeydripper.
- Hey, hurry up. It starts in five minutes.
- You wanna come with us?
- You're welcome to. We can have guests.
I would love to,
but I'm not dressed for it.
So I'll take a rain check.
Certainly, thanks for the cookies,
Jimmy.
Bye.
That can't be right.
Can't be right.
Seventeen point four total.
Thirty-three percent
is the common fund.
So I'm one-fifteenth.
Fifteen into 17...
Carry the two...
One million, one hundred and sixty.
One million,
one hundred and sixty thousand.
Holy shit.
- Mr Ehrmantraut?
- Yes.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It'll be right this way.
Can I get you anything to drink?
Tea, water, espresso?
No, I'm fine. Thank you.
- Ms Rodarte-Quayle, I have your next...
- Yes, thank you.
Mr Ehrmantraut,
Lydia Rodarte-Quayle.
Mike.
Thanks, Justin.
Have a seat.
Mike...
HR sent up your start paperwork.
I-9, W-2, pretty standard.
Could I have your driver's licence
and social-security card?
- Why?
- My assistant needs to make a copy.
How does this hire work exactly?
Walk me through it.
You'll receive a paycheque from Madrigal
in the amount of $10,000 per week.
I believe at that rate, your employment
should be paid out in about 20 weeks.
Mr Fring has arranged to cover FICA,
social security...
the entirety of the tax burden.
I assume that's all right with you?
Good. So to that end, I have you down
as a logistics consultant.
What is that?
It's a person who consults on logistics.
Does it matter?
I'm not long on logistics.
Security consultant would be better.
I used to be a cop.
That'll look better on work history than
your current employer, SMQ Parking.
So...
you take my money...
run it through this joint,
and it's clean? That it?
Yes.
Who knows this operation?
You? Anyone else?
- No.
- You sure?
May I ask what, precisely,
is your concern here?
I'm concerned about what happens
if you put my real name in your books.
Your Madrigal is a German company.
One thing I know about Germans
is they love a good audit.
I oversee eight freight terminals
across Texas and the Southwest.
Operating costs range between
$800,000 and $1 million per week.
All due respect, Mike,
but your money?
It's a rounding error.
If the IRS or anyone else looks...
you're a contractor for
a multinational corporation...
with 114,000 employees worldwide.
You're like every other person
in this building.
Like you?
You think I'm not on the books?
I am.
Under my own name.
- This is the way you handled it before?
- Handled what?
The money for Fring's other guys.
Other guys?
This is the first time I've done this...
for anyone.
I don't know what you do, but...
Mr Fring must think
you're quite good at it.
Twenty weeks.
The sooner you're off my books,
the better.
Justin?
Can you make a copy of these,
please? Thank you.
What?
This is a very nice office.
Thank you.
Seem to be risking a lot
for a drug dealer.
Drug dealer?
If that's all you think he is...
then you don't know Gustavo Fring.
Let me understand you.
You're proposing to double our premiums
on every one of our practising attorneys?
We know this is abrupt.
New issues have come to light.
New issues?
You mean
Mr McGill's testimony at the bar?
That's a part of it. Yes.
After 25 years of paying full premiums,
I can count on one hand our claims.
This is an underwriting decision.
You shouldn't take it personally.
In some special circumstances,
we have been known to extend a rider.
What kind of rider?
A senior, management-level partner
who would supervise Charles' work.
Attend court
and client meetings with him...
review filings.
We've done this for clients with
a high probability of health failure...
- as a precaution.
- What you're saying is...
for any case Charles takes on,
another partner is tied up as well.
And we don't bill a penny more?
This is ludicrous.
The insurance industry
is heavily regulated.
I can think of a dozen infractions
here off the top of my head.
Mr McGill.
You're hoping we'll either
find another carrier...
or cut you an enormous cheque.
Win-win for you.
I assure you,
neither is going to happen.
What will happen is very simple.
You're going to do right by us,
or we will compel you to do so.
- What do you mean by compel?
- You know exactly what I mean.
If you're threatening litigation,
this meeting is over.
Then it's over.
Thank you for your time.
Mr Hamlin, Mr McGill.
All right. Where do we begin?
Francis should start
digging into regulations.
I'm sorry. I don't have the code sections
at my fingertips just now.
Let's pull a team of associates...
and get them looking at
every angle of injunctive relief.
Before close of business,
we'll hit Santa Rosa...
with a demand letter
that'll make their heads spin.
Odds are, inside a week,
they'll be sitting at the table again.
And if not, well...
we've never shied away from a fight.
Chuck,
do you remember Al McConnell?
Of course. Hell of a litigator.
- Retired now, isn't he?
- He's a professor at UNM now.
Wrote a fantastic book
on SCOTUS during Reconstruction.
Fascinating stuff.
- Okay?
- I was talking to him...
and he mentioned
he'd love you come speak to his One-L's.
Maybe make it a regular thing,
if you wanted.
What are you talking about, Howard?
What I'm saying is...
maybe it's time
to hang up your spurs.
Become partner emeritus.
Leave your name on the firm,
but focus on your legacy.
You always said you wanted to
work on the Commerce Clause.
You can write the book on it.
And no longer be a practising lawyer.
Chuck, there's more to life than this.
That day is far in the future, Howard...
and I don't appreciate
the suggestion.
- What if it's not a suggestion.
- Meaning?
Meaning if enough people
tell you that you're drunk...
maybe it's time to sit down.
You want me to retire over this?
- Insurance?
- It's not just the insurance.
That's the straw
that broke the camel's back.
Oh, so this is about my condition?
Look.
You see?
See?
I'm better.
Howard, I'm fine.
This is not what fine looks like.
Chuck, you are the best
legal mind I've ever known.
Hands down.
But your decision making
has become unpredictable.
I can't be partners with someone
whose judgement I don't trust.
Chuck.
This right here
is the Texas-New Mexico border.
Now...
all of my wells are square...
on the Texas side.
When I negotiated for the mineral
and property rights...
the surveyor said that
the next nearest pool extended to...
about here.
Right.
But after some extraction...
the west wall of the salt dome
gave way...
opening up another pool
that extends what?
- A hundred yards over the border?
- About the size of it.
And now you have the New Mexico
rights holders to deal with.
They should get profit on theirs...
but I've got two states coming after me
for taxes on each and every gallon.
No equipment crosses the border?
No, ma'am.
Nothing below the surface, like the...?
What, is it a drill bit?
It'd be a sucker rod at this point,
but no, none of that.
Only on the Texas side.
That's not stopping
New Mexico from trying to bleed me.
You said on the phone
you have a solution.
You don't negotiate a lease
with the rights holders.
- You offer to pay them damages.
- Damages?
For diminishing their resource.
A significant fraction of the value
of the New Mexico portion...
but without paying for
the rights themselves.
So a kind of a payoff.
You don't get hit with the taxes.
You think you can make that fly?
If someone came to me with this offer...
I'd sure as hell take it.
Wish I'd called you sooner.
Way they're making noise...
if I don't get this wrapped up
by the end of the quarter...
I'm pretty sure
the tax boys are gonna take me apart.
And that's two weeks from now?
I can do it by then.
Really?
If we get the rights holders
in one place...
I can walk them through
what we're proposing.
- If they're smart, they'll go for it.
- Well, hot damn.
Kevin said you're a miracle worker.
I didn't believe him.
I'm starting to.
Yeah. Well, let me work
that miracle first, then we'll talk.
You know the way out of here?
I got a drill-head...
that's acting up on me
out in the North-40 I gotta check.
Yeah. I'm good.
You need anything from me,
you got my cell. Call me.
Will do.
Billy Gatwood meeting notes.
Contact Gatwood Oil...
get names and numbers
for New Mexico rights holders.
Shit.
No, no, no!
Continuing notes from
Gatwood Oil meeting.
Contact rights holders...
begin scheduling.
Howard.
- What are you doing here, Jimmy?
- We have business to discuss.
Is this about Chuck?
Who?
If you have business,
then call my secretary.
I did. She stonewalled me,
as if you didn't know.
Sandpiper.
- What about it?
- It's time to settle.
I saw the current offer.
The clients make their losses back
plus a solid chunk of change.
Not that it's any of your business...
but we project a number
higher than the current offer.
I get it. I get it. You hold out...
maybe you squeeze
a grand more for each client.
Meanwhile HHM nets a few million,
you know?
You're screwing the clients
for your own benefit.
Oh, so now you're worried
about the clients?
It's the right thing to do,
and you know it.
Please.
All you care about
is your share of the payout.
It's like talking to Gollum.
You're transparent and pathetic.
Do you want a handout?
Here.
Next time...
why don't you bring a tin cup?
It'd be more honest.
Listen, Howard.
Settle this now.
It's in everyone's best interests.
Meaning it's in your best interests.
And if we don't,
what are you gonna do?
Peel off members of the class,
leak insider info to Schweikart?
Oh, I doubt it.
I know you're low enough to do that,
but you're too damn greedy.
You do any of that,
you'll be jeopardising your payday.
You'll get your damn money...
you're just gonna have to wait for it.
What's so important?
Had a conversation...
with our friend by the pool.
He's very pleased with our progress.
He feels our consolidated
transportation method is working.
In fact, it works so well...
that our friend says this will be
the only way, moving forward.
Of course, your territory will stay
yours forever.
But this system has less
exposure. Less risk.
Everything moves through
the Chilean.
Can you hear me?
I hear you.
Don Hector...
I never asked for this.
I do not want it.
Don Hector.
Fuck Eladio...
fuck Bolsa...
and fuck you.
Well, we go around about,
you know, six times, I think.
I think we're... Yeah.
I think... I think so.
I know. It's just so good for you.
Hello, ladies.
Good morning.
- Jimmy?
- Hi, Jimmy.
Jimmy. You girls go on a little bit.
I'll catch up with you.
Wow, Irene. Fancy running into you
twice in one week.
How lucky am I?
You're a mall-walker? I had no idea.
Me? Oh, yeah, big time.
I mean, it's great for cardio,
hamstrings, glutes, I-T band.
I'm a huge mall-walker.
Been out of the game for a while.
Developed this damn plantar fasciitis.
Hurts like a bear.
Oh, I'm so sorry to hear about that.
Well, hey, I got the cure right here.
Pow!
These have a special gel
and resistance coils...
and a bunch of stuff.
It's like walking on pillows.
Well, they look comfortable.
You like them?
Well, they... they're quite stylish.
Hey, you know what?
I bought a pair for my girlfriend, and
they don't fit, and the store has this...
Wouldn't you know it?
No refunds policy.
What size are you?
Seven and a half, seven and a half.
Seven and a half. Oh, there you go.
How does that feel?
I... I see what you mean.
They are so nice,
and they fit like a dream.
But I can't take these for free, Jimmy.
Oh, please.
- There is one thing you could do for me.
- What's that?
Don't tell the other folks
I gave them to you.
I don't wanna look like
I'm playing favourites.
My lips are sealed.
Then you enjoy those.
I'm gonna go get my heart rate back up.
- Oh, thank you.
- See you later.
Thank you so much, Jimmy.
The hand of love. Now watch,
and I'll show you the story of life...
You've got some questions.
It's only natural.
And the truth is, if Irene settled,
you'd get some money.
But I mean, it's not like
you guys need it, right?
On the other hand,
I did get a look at their offer...
and I don't wanna speak
out of school, but it's...
But, I mean, hey,
everyone's situation is different.
Maybe Irene
just doesn't need the money.
I don't know for a fact, but...
when you see someone
buying nice new things...
- Like those shoes.
Those must have cost a pretty penny.
If she can afford those,
she's walking on easy street.
And there's something else.
You know, the lawyers?
I mean, that's the lawyer's share
of the settlement...
and your share is this much.
If Irene holds out...
the lawyers get this much more...
and you are gonna
get this much more.
Doesn't seem like much difference.
I know, but that's how it works.
Irene knows it too. I mean,
the lawyers have explained it to her.
It's crazy, but it's all up to Irene.
After all,
she is the class representative.
Does that mean that she gets more?
No, no. It just means in the eyes
of the court, she's special.
She's like your Congressman
or ambassador.
Is there anything we can do?
No.
No. You can't do anything.
I can't do anything.
Only Irene.
She probably knows what's best.
I'm sure she's taking your feelings
into account.
Hey, look at the big picture.
Who needs money
when you got the moral high ground?
Rose.
Helen.
Ladies?
Ignacio?
Hey, Dad.
I was falling asleep to the news.
Yeah, I know.
Are you all right, Mijo?
Dad...
A man is going
to come to your shop. Soon.
A bad man.
What?
He'll want to run the place for a while.
And you'll have to let him.
Do you understand?
And who is this man?
Hector Salamanca.
Salamanca.
I've been working for them again.
I know what you're thinking.
And you can scream at me...
disown me...
never speak to me again,
but whatever happens...
you must do what he says.
I know what you're gonna want to do.
But you can't.
You can't, Dad.
Do what he says, this will blow over
in a few weeks.
If you don't...
I swear.
I swear it'll be over soon.
How can I believe anything
you say?
Promise me you won't do
anything stupid.
Promise me, Dad.
Please.
Get out of my house.
I'm still waiting
for those third-party subpoenas.
- Great. Let me know. Thanks, Francis.
- All right.
Julie, what's up?
From Chuck. It came via messenger.
The instructions say he wants you
to read it as soon as possible.
Here's what I need you to do.
Call around.
Find someplace special
for the retirement party.
Something classy, old school.
La Posada, maybe.
And a band, something jazzy. Upbeat.
Find what's available. Let's set it up.
Okay.
Goddamn it, Chuck.
You're suing Hamlin Hamlin McGill?
Come on in, Howard.
You turned the lights on?
I told you.
I'm back to normal.
And, yes, I am suing HHM
for breach of contract.
Do you have any idea
what you're doing?
I believe I do. I'm calling your bluff.
This is my firm. I built it.
Your father was working
in a two-room office when I joined him.
And you, I tutored for the bar exam.
You're not kicking me out.
If you can't trust my judgement,
as you say, so be it...
but you're gonna have
to pay me for my share.
I believe that comes to around
$8 million.
We both know the firm
doesn't have the money.
You'd rather tear down HHM
than retire?
You think I'm trouble now
as your partner?
Imagine me as your enemy.
Chuck.
The damage you're going to do...
If you'd like to discuss this further,
we can, in court.
Until then...
what else is there to say?
Blue pot. Red wine.
Black burner.
Black burner. Black burner.
I got hot hands. I got hot hands.
I know this is gonna be the one.
B-9.
Let's hope that biopsy
comes back B-9.
B-9.
Okay. What's next?
We got I-29.
I remember when I was 29.
I bet you do too.
I-29.
Here comes O-62.
Oh, my God. Have I called 62
of these already? Feels like it.
O-62.
Here we have B-2, B-2.
Hold tight. It is all bingo.
Here it comes.
O-70, anyone? O-70.
All right. No takers.
Boom.
G-55. G-55.
Oh, my God, bingo. I got bingo.
Big Paul, bring it up.
Kelley, take a look.
We may have a winner.
Kelley, tell me.
Have we got it?
We have a bingo, Paul.
Step up to the winner's circle.
Let's hear it for him.
Let's give him a big round of applause.
Okay. New game, new cards.
Here they come.
Get yourself some new cards,
new cards.
The helpers have them.
You can have one, two.
You can have up to four, as you know.
Here's a lucky blue one for you.
All right. Take your cards
so we can start a new game.
There you go. Add that to your stack.
All right. Get your cards.
Hey, Irene? You feeling lucky today?
I guess so.
All right. Well, here's one on me.
Just for you.
All right.
I sold my soul for B-I-N-G and O.
Let's clear the table.
Load it up.
Locked and loaded.
Here comes a new game.
First number up.
It's N-31.
N for Nancy.
Thirty-one for the number of times
she told me to take a hike.
N-31.
G-48.
G for the Greatest Generation.
Forty-eight for
Dewey defeats Truman.
Here's I-25. The big I.
I-25. It's B-12.
Like the vitamin.
O-67.
Anybody?
I got a good feeling about this.
O-67.
I... I think bingo!
Who is that?
Come on up.
Irene? Irene, come on up here, dear.
Bring it up to Kelley.
Let's take a look.
Kelley has to check your card.
Here she comes.
Could be.
Oh, my goodness.
It is a bingo for Irene.
Let's hear it for Irene Landry.
Give it up for the big winner,
Irene Landry.
Fastest bingo of the night.
Come on. Let's hear it for Irene.
Irene?
Where are you going? Hey...
You know what? Take over.
Okay.
Time for a new game.
Let's get some cards out
for everyone.
Hey, what's going on? You okay?
Oh, don't do that.
Your mascara's gonna run all over.
Irene, come on.
What's wrong?
They've all turned on me.
Who has?
My friends.
Helen, Rose, Myrtle.
All of them.
What? No.
Yes.
They're so cold.
When I walk past them,
they stop talking, and...
I hear them whispering
when they think I'm not there.
It's just so...
They're so cruel,
and I don't even know why.
I think...
maybe I do.
You do?
Could it be the settlement?
I mean, maybe they want the money...
you know, to improve their lives?
I had no idea
any of them needed money.
No one said anything to me.
Well, maybe it's not
about the money itself.
I mean, although...
who wouldn't want more money?
I mean, maybe it's the idea that...
they don't think
you're considering them, you know?
Thinking of their needs.
I... I didn't know.
I don't wanna hurt them.
They're my friends.
I wish we'd never even
started this lawsuit.
I just want everything
to go back the way it was.
What should I do?
What would you do?
I mean, you know
I'm not a lawyer right now.
Please?
Should I settle?
Irene...
you listen to your heart.
- Time?
- Two hours out.
When did I say I was gonna leave?
Twenty minutes ago.
Can I have some more coffee please?
Coming.
I'm missing a survey history
in this one.
On it. Sorry about that.
Not a problem.
Hey, who's ready
to have her life changed?
Kim, can you hear me?
Yep. I heard you. Life changed.
Stop your work,
both of you, for a sec.
I got big, big news.
Can you just tell us later?
I'm so late, it's not even funny.
Mesa Verde can wait.
Look, I got Zafiro.
It's not Mesa Verde. It's a new client,
and if I mess up, a former client.
I thought Mesa Verde
was your one and only.
No, it's... I'm sorry.
Can I explain this to you later? I'm...
Sandpiper is settling.
- What?
- Yeah.
For a bundle.
But they can't be settling.
Class actions don't move that fast.
Don't get bogged down in the details.
Trust me. They're settling.
- Wow, that... that's great then.
- Yeah. Yeah.
So hey, let's celebrate.
I can tell that you pulled
another all-nighter here, you know?
You gotta stop and smell the roses.
Hey, who's got two thumbs,
a bottle of Zafiro...
and 20 percent of the common fund?
- This guy.
- I know. You do. I am happy for you.
Be happy for us.
This is the solution to everything.
- Okay. Could you put these all in my car?
- Kim.
- Yeah. Jimmy, I gotta go.
- Give me five goddamn minutes.
- I don't have five minutes.
- You're already late.
What's five more minutes?
Drive 60 instead of 55.
- Jimmy.
- What...?
You're not hearing me.
Our troubles are over. Come on.
Jimmy, I'm leaving now.
I'll be back in a few hours.
Think of all the things you wanna say
to me and say them later.
Goodbye.
You. Shots.
- I...
- Shots.
We're celebrating.
Cheers.
Smooth.
Yeah.
Under the terms we're offering,
you get a substantial payment...
without any impact to your property
via drilling and extraction...
and rather than waiting years to close,
Mr Gatwood is offering cash, right now.
Given the cost of overhead...
liabilities and other burdens
Mr Gatwood assumes...
we believe this offer
is more than fair.
We believe...
We believe this offer is more than fair.