'Previously on "Hannibal"...'
I can't be with you.
You're becoming.
The dragon is your higher self.
There's a family out there
who don't know he's coming.
They're not my family, and I'm not
letting them die. You are.
- What did you say to him?
- "Save yourself. Kill them all."
Then I gave him your home address.
How's the wife?
I look at my wife and I see her dead.
I see Mrs Leeds and Mrs Jacobi
lying where Molly should be.
Do you see yourself
killing her?
Yes.
Over and over.
It's hard to predict
when brittle materials will break.
Hannibal gave you three years
to build a family,
confident that he would find a way
to take them from you.
And he has.
What's he going to take from you?
Is it important to you that
he take something from me?
Hannibal has agency in the world.
Hannibal has no intention
of seeing me dead
by any other hand than his own.
And only then, if he can eat me.
He's in no position to eat me now.
If you play...
...you pay.
You have paid dearly.
It excites him to know that
you are marked in this particular way.
- Why?
- Why do you think?
Bluebeard's wife.
Secrets you're not to know,
yet sworn to keep.
If I'm to be Bluebeard's wife,
I would have preferred to be the last.
Is Hannibal...
...in love with me?
Could he daily feel
a stab of hunger for you
and find nourishment
at the very sight of you?
Yes.
But do you ache for him?
Will's thoughts are no more bound
by fear or kindness
than Milton's were by physics.
He is both free and damned
to imagine anything.
Now that he's imagined the worst.
Like ducklings, we imprint
on those ideas that grab our attention.
What's got your attention, Doctor?
God, the Devil and
the Great Red Dragon?
Lest we forget the Lamb.
Will is the Lamb of God?
Hide us from the wrath of the Lamb.
Who's "us"?
You, me and the Great Red Dragon.
The Lamb's wrath touches
everyone who errs.
His retribution is even more deadly
than the Dragon's.
It is for you.
The seals are being opened, Jack.
The lamb is becoming a lion.
"For the great day of his wrath is come;
and who shall be able to stand?"
I'll still be standing.
Is your conscience clear?
As clear as yours.
Righteousness is what
you and Will have in common.
"In righteousness, the Lamb
doth judge and make war."
War against the Great Red Dragon.
He's not the Dragon, you are.
The Devil himself bound in the pit.
Then that makes you God, Jack.
Yes, it does.
All gods demand sacrifices.
We don't have anything else.
Eight people dead in a month.
We can't play the long game.
You know and I know
it's the best way to bait him.
Got me on the hook, now you're
dangling me to catch a bigger fish.
It was your suggestion.
And you're thrilled
you didn't have to make it.
You once fooled yourselves
into believing you were in control
of what was happening.
Are you still under that delusion?
The Dragon has a certain
abstract curiosity about me.
All psychopaths are narcissists,
they love to read about themselves.
If you were smart, Jack,
you would use Freddie Lounds.
She will need to interview you, Will.
Take your picture.
I'm in it now.
Can't go home as long as he's loose.
So, I really bad-mouth
the Red Dragon in TattleCrime.
Give him a shot at me.
It's gotta be a really good shot.
What about the set-up?
Something open. Someplace
where he can get close to me.
It feels like a trap to me.
And it'll feel like a trap to him.
Unless you have a professional voice
who will legitimise what you're saying.
Someone to hide the wire of the snare?
Are you volunteering?
No.
I'd have to be a fool.
Since your commitment,
you have written some brilliant articles
for The Northern Medical Journal
of Psychiatry.
Thank you, Frederick.
I just finished your most recent piece.
Extraordinary stuff!
- A particularly good one.
- It may be my favourite.
I have seen a lot of hostility.
But this was quantifiably bitchy!
Do you think I am your nemesis?
No. Nemesis? No.
- You refuted my entire book.
- It didn't hold up to scrutiny.
Of course it didn't, I was lying!
On your behalf!
To save your life!
You refuted your insanity defence.
I went out on a limb for you and
you climbed up there and sawed it off!
"Wood burns because
it has the proper stuff in it;
"and a man becomes famous
because he has the proper stuff in him."
You don't have the proper stuff,
Frederick.
I am a best-selling author.
The journals only still publish
your writing
for the freak value of your by-line.
The attention given to you
is dwindling
since you have been overshadowed
by another creature.
That book is writing itself.
I think I'll call it The Dragon Slayer.
All I need is the ending.
Fate has a habit of not letting us
choose our own endings, Frederick.
This is the ending
fate has chosen for you.
Your teeth will go and your strength.
Nobody will be afraid of you anymore.
After Dr Bloom's reign,
you will be out in the ward.
The young ones will push you around
and use you for sex.
All you'll get to read is
what you write on the wall.
You have seen the old ones.
They cry when they do not like
the stewed apricots.
Oh...
I'm just going to leave an extra copy
of my book right over here.
Thank you, Frederick.
I've personalised it for you.
Are you here to remonstrate me
with "I told you so"?
That's not why I'm here.
She's here
because we need someone
who's less concerned about the truth
than the best story.
Dr Chilton, lay out your theories and
Will will aggravate them for the record.
You're making statements
no investigator would ever make
and no straight newspaper would credit.
You're not
a straight newspaper.
You sell T-shirts that say:
"The Tooth Fairy Is A One-Night Stand."
I can get you one, if you like.
You small or medium? Small, I bet.
They aren't selling so well since
you started calling him "The Dragon".
The killer's objection to the name
"The Tooth Fairy" is likely grounded
in the homosexual implication
of the word "fairy".
Tedious, I know,
but if you really want to piss him off,
that's what you should call him.
Very well. "Tooth Fairy" it is.
The Tooth Fairy's actions
indicate a projective delusion
compensating for intolerable
feelings of inadequacy.
Smashing mirrors ties these feelings
to his appearance...
And not only is the Tooth Fairy insane,
he is ugly and impotent.
There's a strong bonding
of aggressive and sexual drives
that occurs in sadists
at an early age...
He's a vicious, perverted,
sexual failure. An animal.
The savage acts aimed primarily
at the women,
performed in the presence of families,
are clearly strikes at a maternal figure...
The Tooth Fairy is the product
of an incestuous home.
This is the child of a nightmare.
Will, I think we need a key shot of you
here in your "Washington hideaway".
I'd love something of you
in a bathrobe,
sitting at a desk, poring over
this artist's conception of the Fairy.
I'll stand by the window.
Make sure you can see
the fountain and the Capitol dome.
The Red Dragon needs to be able
to find this place, if he wants to.
Frederick, would you like
to be in the photograph?
One for the dust jacket.
That's it, up.
There.
This whole procedure
is way too passive for my taste.
We are playing games
in the dark of the moon.
He thinks he can do anything.
Maybe he thinks he can stop.
If he can hold off until we catch him,
maybe we can help him make it stop.
He almost killed your wife and son.
Hannibal almost killed them.
All right, pedestrian traffic
falls off around 7:15.
You should go for a walk,
say 8:30 or so.
He'll have to cross open ground
to get close.
- He'll want to get close.
- I've got snipers on the roofs.
You'll be wearing body armour.
Seven out of eleven times,
he's gone for the headshot, Jack.
Yeah...
That's absurd.
That's not what I said at all.
Dr Lecter gave misleading answers
in my interviews.
I will refute his refutations
in my new book,
"Blood And Chocolate".
Supermarket tabloids love Hannibal
Lecter more than alien abductions.
That is his demographic now.
We know who his fans are...
Would you like a blanket?
I'll get you a blanket.
Oh, my back hurts.
Oh, my skin.
Oh, did I get burned?
Did I...did I get burned?
Hope, dear God, I am not burned.
Burned?
Burned...
Burned.
No.
You just rest there.
What am I doing here?
Atoning, Dr Chilton.
I have not seen your face.
I could not...
I could not identify you.
I do not know what you look like.
Do you know who I am?
No. No. I do not want to know,
believe me.
According to you,
I'm a vicious,
perverted,
sexual failure.
An animal.
You know now, don't you?
Yes.
Why did you lie, Dr Chilton?
Do you understand what I'm doing?
No. No!
But I think I have an opportunity
to understand.
Then all my readers
could understand, too.
Do you feel privileged?
It is a privilege. But...
...I have to tell you, I am scared.
Man to man, I am scared.
And it is...
it is very hard to, er...
to concentrate when you are scared.
If you have got a great idea,
you do not need to scare me
for me to be impressed, OK?
"Man to man."
You use that phrase
to imply frankness.
But you see, I am not a man.
I have become Other
and More than a man.
Do you think God is
in attendance here?
Are you praying to him now?
We pray to God mostly
when we are scared.
And does God help you?
No.
I don't know, I don't know.
I do not know.
I do...I do...I ought...
I do not think about it after.
- I ought to.
- You ought to.
I ought to.
There are so many things
that you ought to understand.
And in a little while,
I will help you understand.
No, I do not want to see your face!
When you turn around,
you will open your eyes and look at me.
Or I will staple your eyelids
to your forehead.
D? It's me.
If you make a sound, I will kill her.
I don't like surprises.
I bet you don't, either.
I tried to call you.
May I come in?
I won't be long.
I asked my taxi to wait.
How are you feeling?
OK.
- Your office said you were sick.
- The flu.
You shouldn't be here.
I brought you soup.
I...I didn't come
just to give you soup, D.
I guess I'm guilty of liking you.
Demonstrably guilty.
And I know you like me, too.
I do.
I've learned that withdrawal
can be a strategy to avoid pain.
I have a deep vein
of cripple's anger in me.
While I can't get rid of it,
I've made it work for me.
It's fuelled my independence.
I'm not so scarred by life
that I'm incapable of love.
I hope you aren't, either.
Enjoy the soup.
Do you want to know
what I am?
More than anything.
I was afraid to ask.
Look.
- Do you see now?
- Yes.
- Do you see?
Do you see?
- Yes.
Yes!
Do you...see?
Do...you...see?
God!
Do you see?
Please! No!
- No what?
- Not me.
Are you going to tell more lies
about me, Dr Chilton?
- No, no, no...
- Why did you tell lies, Dr Chilton?
It was the police who told me to.
They...they said it.
You quote Will Graham.
Graham...told the lies. Graham!
Will you tell the truth now
about me? About my work?
My Becoming?
My Art, Dr Chilton?
Is...this...Art?
Art.
You said that I,
who see more than you,
am insane.
I, who has pushed the world
so much further than you,
am insane.
I have dared more than you.
I am the Dragon
and you call me insane?
Before me,
you are a slug in the sun.
You are privy to a great Becoming,
and you recognise nothing!
It is in your nature
to do one thing correctly,
and before me you tremble.
Fear is not what you owe me.
You owe me...awe!
For your journey home.
Ice.
You will need that.
But before we go,
I think we should tape
for a little while.
Look straight down the lens.
Repeat after me.
Dr Chilton, you did very well.
You will let me go now?
I will.
Although...
...there is one way...
...that I can help you
better understand...
...and remember.
I want to understand.
And I've got a very good memory.
Hand delivered.
- May I open it privately?
- You may not.
Dr Chilton often offended me,
so I certainly understand the sentiment.
Where's the other one?
This one can provide you
anything the other one can.
I'm sorry, Jack. The tragedy of what's
happened to Frederick has put me
in an excellent humour.
Dr Chilton disappeared yesterday,
under armed escort.
You pretended to burn Freddie Lounds
in a wheelchair to flush me out.
What were you pretending to do
with Frederick Chilton?
He profiled the Dragon.
For Freddie Lounds.
We wanted to enrage him.
Congratulations.
You could've provided
anything Dr Chilton could.
That would've been your lip
I was tasting. Again.
You publicly discredited Dr Chilton.
By refuting him,
you orchestrated his end by proxy.
You orchestrated his end, Alana.
You saw the hole
and let him roll right into it.
That's professional discourtesy.
'I have had a great privilege.
'I have seen
with wonder and awe
'the strength
of the Great Red Dragon.
'All that I said was lies
from Will Graham.
'I have blasphemed
against the Dragon.
'Even so, the Dragon is merciful.
'Because I was forced to lie,
'he will be more merciful to me
than to you, Will Graham.
'Reach behind you and feel
'the small knobs
on the top of your pelvis.
'Feel your spine between them.
'That is the precise spot where
the Dragon will snap your spine.
'There is much for you to dread.
'From my own lips,
you will learn a little more to dread.'
Would you like to talk about what
happened with Frederick Chilton?
The divine punishment of a sinner...
...mirrors the sin being punished.
Contrapasso.
You play, you pay.
Chilton languished, unrecognised,
until "Hannibal the Cannibal."
He wanted the world to know his face.
And now he doesn't have one.
Damned if I'll feel.
We are all making our way
through the Inferno.
Dante's pilgrims.
No, we're not pilgrims.
We are pets.
And the Great Red Dragon
kills pets first.
You put your hand on Dr Chilton's
shoulder in the photograph.
Touch gives the world
an emotional context.
The touch of others
makes us who we are.
It builds trust.
I put my hand on his shoulder
for authenticity.
To establish that he really told you
those insults about the Dragon?
Or maybe you wanted
to put Dr Chilton at risk?
Just a little?
I wonder.
Do you have to wonder?
No.
What did you think
the Great Red Dragon would do?
You were curious what would happen,
that's apparent.
Is this what you were expecting?
I can't say I am surprised.
Then you may as well
have struck the match.
That's participation.
Hannibal Lecter does have
agency in the world.
He has you.
He's trashed. He did Chilton like it
looked like you did Freddie Lounds.
Hannibal said he would
in his own way.
Hannibal told him to.
- You OK?
- Yeah, I'm OK.
I had the SWAT team.
Chilton said your name
when they brought him into the ER.
He's trashed.
You ought to get ready for this.
Frederick, it's Will Graham.
I'm sorry this happened to you.
Can you understand
what he's saying?
He said...
"You set me up. You knew it.
"You put your hand on me
in the picture like a pet."
Did you see anything?
"A black woman. She's blind."
"Reba." The Dragon said her name
when he called Lecter.
We're here.
If I untie you and let you sit up,
will you be good?
I didn't know you cared
this much about me.
I'm glad you feel that way,
but you scared me with this.
I never hurt you.
I never wanted to.
Let's just be friends and have
a good time and forget about this...
Shut up.
I'm going to tell you something.
The most important thing
that you will ever hear.
"Sermon-on-the-Mount" important.
"Ten-Commandments" important.
Got it?
- Yes, D. I don't...
- Shut up.
Some remarkable events
have happened
in Chicago and Buffalo.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
No.
It's been on the news a lot.
Two groups of people were changed.
Leeds and Jacobi.
The police think
that they were murdered.
You know now?
Do you know what they call...
...the Being that visited
those people?
- The Tooth F...
- Think.
Answer correctly.
It's...Dragon something.
Dragon... Red Dragon.
I...
...am...
...the Dragon.