'Previously on "Hannibal"...'
If this is about
my position at the palazzo,
once the path was cleared,
I won the job fairly on my merits.
Two men from
the Capponi are dead.
You are going to be caught.
Europe is where
a man of his tastes would settle.
- His tastes are very specific.
- That's how you'll find him.
Come back with me. We have
a chance to regain our reputations
by capturing the monster.
I'm here for Will Graham.
I have no reason to stay here.
You saw to that.
I'll help you find him.
On still evenings,
when the air was damp after a rain,
we played a game.
Hannibal would burn
all kinds of barks and incense
for me to identify by scent alone.
He was charming...
...the way a cub is charming.
A small cub that grows up
to be like one of the big cats.
One you can't play with later.
The day I met Hannibal,
he was an orphan.
I was meant to meet him
with his sister,
but he was alone.
How did you meet him?
I was his aunt's attendant.
My parents sent me
to learn from Lady Murasaki
when I was just a girl.
I learned from Hannibal, too.
He comes in the guise of a mentor,
but it's distress that excites him.
I'm not in distress.
Not anymore.
You had a strict rule about taking life.
And you broke it.
Is it on your mind?
Do you see yourself killing him
over and over?
No.
I see you.
How do you know
Hannibal's in Florence?
Botticelli.
I've never been to Italy.
I've never expected to.
Birds eat thousands of snails every day.
Some of those snails survive digestion.
And they emerge to find
they've travelled the world.
In the belly of the beast.
I kept cochlear gardens
as a young man to attract fireflies.
Their larvae would devour many times
their own body weight in snails.
Fuel.
To power a transformation
into a delicate creature of such beauty.
To the misfortune of the snail.
Snails follow their nature
as surely as those that eat them.
Fireflies live very brief lives.
Better to live true to yourself
for an instant than never know it.
Not like Will Graham does.
An insect lacks morality
to agonise over.
Will agonises about inevitable change.
Almost anything can be trained
to resist its instinct.
A shepherd dog
doesn't savage the sheep.
But it wants to.
Will has reached
a state of moral dumbfounding.
Empathy and reciprocity.
Reciprocity.
If we keep track of incoming
and outgoing intentions,
Will Graham is en route to kill you
while you lie in wait to kill him.
Now that's reciprocity.
Ciao, Bella.
Grazie.
Here we are.
- Grazie.
- Prego.
You've recently stopped wearing
your wedding ring.
Yes, and you've recently started
wearing yours.
I have a young and lovely wife.
Her efforts have ground
twelve pounds off my frame.
- La Vita Nuova.
- Yeah.
Divorced?
No, widowed.
Erm... I met her here.
It's a little strange
to be in Italy without her.
- What was her name?
- Bella.
To Bella.
- To Bella.
I look at her and I think about
all the things I want to give her.
How you wish to appear in her eyes.
Certainly not in my present role
at the Questura.
I perform menial errands found for me
by my former subordinates.
Interviews in missing persons cases.
They've enjoyed my fall from grace.
You weren't in Palermo
on official business.
Neither were you.
And your subordinates
at the Questura,
they know you're investigating
Hannibal Lecter?
I'll tell them when I know it's Lecter
that I'm investigating.
You already know.
I need to be certain.
I am disgraced and out of fortune.
It has inclined you towards a game
that's outside of the law.
I know.
I played that game and I lost.
- Yeah.
- Let's eat.
Oh, my goodness!
How beautiful.
Pasta?
This is pappardelle alla lepre.
Can you say it?
- Papadelle...
- No, no. It's not "pa-pa-delle".
- No?
- No, it's "papardelle".
- Papardelle.
- Yeah! That's it, yes. With lepre.
Ah, thank you.
A table setting from the home
of Dr Hannibal Lecter.
The silverware is 19th-century Dutch
from Christofle.
The plate is Glen French china
from Tiffany.
The table linen is damask cotton.
Also from Christofle.
You've got to hand it to the man,
he has the most marvellous taste.
I've discovered a pattern of purchases.
An echo of the life
he lived in Baltimore.
He likes music, he likes wine,
he likes food and he likes you.
How do you taste, Dr Bloom?
Sweet, I bet.
I'm sure you got a taste of him, too.
Spitters are quitters,
and you don't strike me as a quitter.
The first step
in the development of taste
is to be willing to credit
your own opinion.
But in the areas of food and wine,
I have to follow Hannibal's precedents.
A receipt from a Florentine fine grocer,
Vera Dal 1926,
for two bottles of Bâtard-Montrachet
and some tartufi bianchi.
And another, and another,
and another.
Once a week,
for the last three months,
a blonde woman has been making
the exact same purchase.
Due bottiglie di Bâtard-Montrachet
e tartufi bianchi, per favore.
'And she always pays cash.'
Grazie.
She's shopping for Hannibal.
Bravo.
Are we obligated to talk?
No.
Strange to talk so much.
Not used to hearing voices
outside my head.
I hear voices from all directions.
In the gnawing sameness
of your days...
...did you look at the shape of things?
At... what you were becoming?
I wasn't becoming anything.
I was... standing still.
Exactly where he left me standing.
Like taxidermy.
Hollowed out and filled
with something else.
Not something else.
I'm not as malleable as you are.
I was violent when it was
the right thing to do.
But I think you like it.
Hannibal and I afforded
each other an experience
we may not otherwise have had.
If you don't kill him...
...you're afraid
you are going to become him.
Yes.
There are means of influence
other than violence.
Dr Fell?
Yes.
I am Inspector Rinaldo Pazzi
from the Questura di Firenze.
I was wondering if you ever met
your predecessor?
Never met him.
Read several of his monographs.
The officers who first investigated
checked the Palazzo for any sort of note.
Farewell note, suicide note...
Found nothing.
The going assumption is,
he eloped with a woman.
And her money.
What is the going assumption
regarding Professor Sogliato?
Still no word?
You may have had the last word
with Sogliato.
Your colleague...
...Signor Albizzi, tells me no one
has spoken to Professor Sogliato
since he declined
your invitation to dinner.
He's the second to have
disappeared from the Palazzo.
Like any good investigator,
I'm sure you're sifting
the circumstances for profit.
Both were bachelors.
Well-respected scholars
with orderly lives.
They had some savings,
nothing much.
Commendator Pazzi?
Yes?
I think you're a Pazzi
of the Pazzi, am I correct?
How do you know that?
You resemble a figure
at the Della Robbia rondels
in your family's chapel
at Santa Croce.
Yeah... yeah.
That was Andrea de' Pazzi
depicted as John the Baptist.
Then there's the most famous
Pazzi of all, Francesco.
He attempted to assassinate
Lorenzo the Magnificent
in the cathedral at Mass, in 1478.
Yeah.
The Pazzi family were all
brought low on that Sunday.
If you come upon anything, Dr Fell,
anything personal from the missing men,
will you call me?
Of course, Commendatore.
WANTED FOR MURDER
'State your business, please.'
I may have information
about Hannibal Lecter.
- 'Do you know where he is now?'
- I believe so.
Is the reward in effect?
'Why haven't you called the police?
I'm required to encourage you to do so.'
Is the reward payable in...
special circumstances
to someone not ordinarily eligible?
'Do you mean a bounty on Dr Lecter?'
Yes.
'It is against international convention
to offer a bounty for someone's death, sir.
- 'Are you calling from Europe?'
- Yes, I am.
That's all I'm telling you.
'I suggest you contact an attorney
to discuss the legality of bounties.
'May I recommend one?
There is one in Geneva.
'I encourage you strongly to call him
and be frank about the matter.
'Would you like the number, sir?
'Sir?'
Yes.
Give me the number.
I prefer the sound and feel
of the harpsichord.
More alive, the music arrives
like experience.
Sudden and entire.
The piano has the quality of a memory.
Today has the quality of a memory.
You've met Inspector Pazzi before.
In my youth.
We shared a fondness for Botticelli,
and crossed paths in the Uffizi Gallery
beneath "La Primavera".
Does he know... what you are?
When I looked into his face
and stood close enough to smell him,
I was well aware that all the elements
of epiphany were present.
And yet here you are,
free to tell me all about it.
He must wait and lurk and think.
It's too soon to flush his quarry.
He's deciding what to do.
Someone's put a price on your head.
As an early-warning system,
a bounty is better than radar.
It inclines authorities everywhere
to forsake their duty
and scramble after me privately.
Should Rinaldo Pazzi join
Professor Sogliato
and the late curator of the Palazzo
down in the damp?
Should his body be found
after an apparent suicide?
No.
Rinaldo Pazzi,
a Pazzi of the Pazzi,
chief inspector
at the Florentine Questura,
has to decide
what his honour is worth.
What is it worth to be known
as the man who caught Hannibal Lecter?
For a policeman,
credit has a short half-life.
Better to sell me.
I like the night.
It's more than a period of time.
It's another place.
It's different from where we are
during the day.
We're different from who we are
Little more hidden, little less seen.
When life is most like a dream.
Why are you searching for him?
What are you hoping to find?
I'm not searching for Hannibal.
I know exactly where he is.
Is he in Florence?
Yes.
Why didn't you tell me you knew?
I told you.
There are means of influence...
...other than violence.
But violence is what you understand.
'Hello, Rinaldo.'
Hello.
'Thank you so much
for reaching out.'
Without the cooperation
of concerned citizens such as yourself,
monsters like Hannibal Lecter
would be running wild.
Shall we?
Let's.
I will privately pay
three million dollars
for the doctor alive,
no questions asked,
discretion guaranteed.
Those terms include
a $100,000 advance.
To qualify for the advance,
you must provide
a positively identifiable fingerprint
from Dr Lecter.
'Capito?'
Yes, yes, yes.
I understand.
I will require a fresh fingerprint
in situ and unlifted,
on an object for my experts
to examine independently.
Now you don't want
to alarm the doctor.
He may disappear too well and...
'I would be left with nothing.'
Sì.
So you have no illusions about
what's going to happen to Dr Lecter?
You would be selling him
into torture and death.
'I'm aware.'
You'll get the rest of the money
when he's delivered alive
and in our hands.
I don't want Dr Lecter
near Florence when you...
'I understand your concern.
Don't worry, he won't be.
'Toodle-oo.'
Hannibal's going to kill him,
you know.
Dr Fell?
Buonasera, commendatore.
Buonasera, Dottor Fell.
Back so soon?
Given the nature of your exhibition
and the contents
of our last conversation,
I brought something
I thought you might like to see.
It was supposedly worn
by Francesco de' Pazzi
when he met his end.
My family's guilt cast in iron.
A scold's bridle.
- May I?
- Of course.
A wonderful heirloom.
I'm so glad you stopped by,
Commendator Pazzi,
as I have a family heirloom for you.
Yeah?
Beneath the figure is written a name.
Can you make it out?
- It says "Pazzi".
- This is your ancestor, Francesco.
Hanging outside the Palazzo.
This particular illustration is "bowels out".
I've seen others "bowels in".
By all accounts, Francesco was led
astray by thirty pieces of silver
from the hand of the Papal banker.
It's hard to see,
but here's where the archbishop bit him.
Eyes wild as he choked,
the archbishop locked his teeth
in Pazzi's flesh.
On a related subject,
I must confess,
I've been giving very serious
thought to doing the same.
Thank you.
He said he would be home by now.
What has he done?
Can you hear me, Signor Pazzi?
Take a deep breath while you can.
Clear your head.
I haven't had a bite all day.
Actually, your liver and kidneys would
be suitable for dinner right away.
Tonight, even.
But the rest of the meat
should hang at least a week
in the current cool conditions.
I didn't see the forecast. Did you?
I gather that means no.
If you tell me what I need to know,
Commendatore,
it would be convenient for me
to leave without my meal.
I will ask you the questions
and then we'll see.
You can trust me, you know?
Though I expect you find trust difficult,
knowing yourself.
When the police didn't come,
it was clear that you had sold me.
Was it Mason Verger you sold me to?
Yes.
Thank you.
I called the number
on his "wanted" site once,
far from here, just for fun.
Have you told anyone
at the Questura about me?
Is that a no?
Excuse me.
Pronto.
Inspector Pazzi,
my name is Alana Bloom.
'You don't know me,
but I know your benefactor.'
Hello, Alana.
I'm afraid the inspector
is otherwise occupied.
Is he dead?
There is nothing I would love more
than to be able to chat with you, Alana,
but you caught me
at a rather awkward moment.
Nice to hear your voice.
So, Commendatore,
which do you think?
Bowels in or bowels out?
Out, I think.
Hello, Jack.
Did you get my note?
I'm truly sorry about Bella.
For her, night and day must've been
very much the same in the end.
When she could no longer
stir or speak...
...did you speak for her?
I imagine you were capable of giving
any medication Bella may have
needed in the night.
Did you practise injections
on an orange, Jack?
What medication did you give her
in the end?
Was it too much?
Just enough?
I brought Bella back from death
and you've returned her to it.
Is that where you're taking me, Jack?
How will you feel when I'm gone?
Alive.