'Previously on "Hannibal"...'
I'm going to cut off your face
without anaesthesia, Mr Graham.
I was trying to save Will from you.
Promise me you'll save him.
I promise.
And I always keep my promises.
You finally caught
the Chesapeake Ripper, Jack.
I didn't catch you.
You surrendered.
I want you to know exactly where I am.
And where you can always find me.
♪ Hallelujah, hallelujah...
Bâtard-Montrachet and tartufi bianchi.
How I found you in Florence.
Betrayed by good taste.
Is good taste itching at you in your
daily rounds of institutional life?
An itch easy enough to scratch
when there's cause to celebrate.
Congratulations, Hannibal.
You're officially insane.
There's no consensus in the psychiatric
community what I should be termed.
You've long been regarded
by your peers in psychiatry
as something entirely Other.
For convenience,
they term you a monster.
What do you term me?
I don't. You defy categorisation.
Do you still prefer beer to wine?
I stopped drinking beer when I found out
what you were putting in mine.
"Who."
Who.
This means you'll be spared
the federal death sentence.
They had enough to convict you
a dozen times over.
A baker's dozen,
lest we forget Mason Verger.
You're welcome.
You're welcome, Hannibal.
The needle was guaranteed,
but you beat it all on an insanity plea.
I'm not insane.
You know that and I know that.
A dozen or a baker's dozen,
enough people have died.
You haven't.
A promise in waiting, isn't it?
A promise you intend to keep.
I always keep my promises.
Shh...
S-s-s-s...
S-s-s...
Sanguinaccio dolce.
A classic Neapolitan dessert,
with almond milk.
Easy on the stomach.
Sanguinaccio dolce.
You have served me this before.
One of my favourite desserts.
Traditionally made with pigs' blood.
In this case, a local cow.
And when you last made it for me?
The blood was from a cow
only in the derogatory sense.
Hmm...
Blood and chocolate.
That should've been
the subtitle of my book.
But I promised myself
I would never use colons in my titles.
Colons lose their novelty when overused.
- You'll have to write another book.
- Hmm, I am.
But not about you.
Like overused punctuation, the novelty
of Hannibal Lecter has waned.
What is the subject
of your new book, Frederick?
The Tooth Fairy.
I find folks are a bit more
interested in him.
He is the debutante.
Although he lacks
your love of presentation.
More of a shy boy, this one.
I'd love to hear your thoughts.
What do you think
about the Tooth Fairy?
I think he doesn't like
being called the Tooth Fairy.
It's not as snappy
as Hannibal the Cannibal,
but he does have a much wider
demographic than you do.
You, with your fancy allusions
and your fussy aesthetics,
you will always have niche appeal,
but this fellow, there is something
so universal about what he does.
Kills whole families.
And in their homes.
Strikes at the very core
of the American Dream.
You might say
he's a four-quadrant killer.
Get out of my chair, Frederick.
Shall we join hands
in a prayer of gratitude?
"Thank you, Father, for allowing us
to remove this monster,
"monster of monsters,
from your flock.
"Thank you on behalf of the souls
we will spare of pain."
Thank you on behalf of the monster.
Was that the magisterial "We"?
It is our cabal, yours and mine.
Hannibal Lecter will spend the rest
of his life in a state institution,
watching the diaper cart go by.
We lied.
You wrote a book of lies.
Not difficult to see lies flying
above my head,
but it's almost impossible
to shoot them down.
Hannibal will shoot them down.
He's written a brilliant piece for
"The American Journal of Psychiatry".
Everything he writes is about
some problem he does not have.
What he's written
is going to be your problem.
It's not so much an article
as it is a rebuttal.
Hard to believe an inmate's opinion
will count for anything
in the professional community.
It's going to count, Frederick,
and it's going to sting.
You think he would've taken
the opportunity to gloat.
He'll have plenty of time to gloat,
watching the diaper carts go by.
- So, what did you two talk about?
- The Tooth Fairy.
I've detected a trace
of competitive vanity in our man.
I would be cautious.
The Young Turk may inspire
the Old Lithuanian
to keep himself interesting.
Thank you.
You don't wanna talk inside?
Huh... You don't wanna let me inside.
I've come too far
to let the cold stop me, Will.
Why should the cold stop
what common sense couldn't?
- So you don't wanna talk about it here.
- I don't wanna talk about it anywhere.
You've got to talk about it,
so let's have it.
Just, er... just don't
get out any pictures
cos Molly and Walter
will be back soon.
How much do you know?
Two families killed in their homes
a month apart. Similar circumstances.
Not similar, the same.
You ever think about giving me a call?
No.
You know what it is?
I didn't call you,
because... I didn't want to.
I don't think I can be
of any use to you, Jack.
I don't think about this anymore.
I don't believe I could do it now.
All dead.
I think this freak is in phase
with the moon.
Killed the Jacobis almost
four weeks ago in Chicago. Full moon.
Killed the Leeds family in Buffalo
night before last.
A day short of a lunar month.
With a little bit of luck,
we might have a little more than
three weeks before he does it again.
People dump small dogs here
all the time,
and I can give away the cute ones.
The rest stay and get to be big ones.
Molly's a sucker for strays.
You're not fooling anybody.
You have a nice life here.
Yeah. Yeah, I'm lucky here.
I know that.
- I'm gonna take the dogs out for a pee.
- OK.
Come on, boys. Come here.
Come on.
- How old is he?
- Eleven.
He's going to be taller than you.
Yeah, his father was.
I'll come with you.
Come on! Come on!
Come on, let's go.
So whatever he says he wants to do,
you'll take him anyway, won't you?
I have to. I promise I'll try to make it
as easy on him as I can.
I know what I'm asking.
I wished to God I didn't have to.
How bad is it gonna be if you stay
here and read about the next one?
If you stay and there's more killing,
maybe it would sour this place for you.
High Noon and all that.
Do you want me to go?
I'd have the satisfaction
that you did the right thing.
He kills families.
If I go...
...I'll be different when I get back.
I won't.
"Dear Will,
we have all found a new life,
"but our old lives hover
in the shadows.
"Soon enough, I fear Jack Crawford
will come knocking.
"I would encourage you, as a friend,
"not to step back
through the door he holds open.
"It's dark on the other side
and madness is waiting."
I cut Mr Leeds's throat
as he lies asleep beside his wife.
I shoot Mrs Leeds.
The bullet enters to the right of her
navel and lodges in her lumbar spine.
Mr Leeds rises, his throat cut...
...to protect the children.
I shoot one of the two boys in bed.
The other boy I pull out from under
his bed and shoot him on the floor.
Losing gallons of blood,
Mr Leeds falls and dies
outside his sons' room.
The smashing of mirrors begins.
I moved the family
after they were dead,
and later put them back
where they were when I killed them.
Talcum powder on the body...
There's none in the house.
I have to touch her.
This isn't my design.
I was told you were told I was coming.
Were you not told?
Your office or agency called me,
of course,
but last night we had to get
the police to remove
an obnoxious flame-haired woman
who was trying to take pictures.
I'm being very careful.
I'm sure you understand, Mr Price.
Agent. Special.
Special Agent Price,
the bodies were only released to us
at one o'clock this morning,
and the funeral's at five this afternoon.
We simply can't delay it.
This won't take very long.
I'll need one reasonably-intelligent
assistant, if you have one.
Cancel the reasonably-intelligent
assistant, mine just showed up.
I can't help you with your thing.
I got a thing.
What kind of thing do you got?
I'm reconstructing teeth
from the bite marks on Mrs Leeds
and this cheddar cheese wheel thing
we found in her refrigerator.
Yeah, the Tooth Fairy
was feeling peckish.
Well, we'll double-dutch.
Woman's gotta get in the ground.
Voilà.
It's a partial. Probably a thumb.
- Jimmy, you're the light of my life.
- I know.
The print was smudged.
Came off Mrs Leeds's eye.
Never did that before.
Er, I just...
Erm, sorry, but I'm just surprised
to see you back.
Welcome back.
Jimmy...
OK. The mirror pieces all had
those smooth prints.
Forefinger on the back of the piece
wedged in her labia,
a smudged thumb on the front.
He polished it after he placed it,
so he could see his face in there.
One in her mouth was obscured
by blood. Same with the eyes.
Ran an AFIS.
He's not in the print index.
We could run a "Have-You-Seen-
These-Teeth?" sort of APB.
They're distinctive.
Pegged lateral incisors, here and here.
The teeth are all crooked.
The central incisor's got
a corner missing.
The other central incisor
has a groove in it.
A snaggletooth son of a bitch.
And he bites. A lot.
He may have a history
of biting in lesser assaults.
May be a fighting pattern
as much as sexual behaviour.
What's he fighting, Will?
You were asking about the dog.
Last night, a vet called the police.
Leeds and his oldest boy
took the dog into the vet
the afternoon before they were killed.
What's going to happen to it?
Please don't worry about the dog.
- What do you expect me to do?
- The best you can, that's all.
There's something else I can do.
I can wait until I'm driven to it
by desperation
in the last days before the full moon.
Or I could do it now...
while it might be of some use.
Is there an opinion that you want, Will?
It's a mindset I need to recover.
I have to see Hannibal.
Hello, Dr Lecter.
Hello, Will.