'Previously on "Hannibal"...'
My palace is vast,
even by medieval standards.
The foyer is the Norman Chapel
in Palermo.
Severe and beautiful and timeless.
You come to Palermo,
and soon a body is discovered.
A valentine written on a broken man.
There are places within himself
he can't safely go.
- Have you ever been a father?
- I was to my sister.
Her name was Mischa.
Hannibal!
I forgive you.
Was it nice to see him?
It was nice.
Among other things.
He knew where to look for me.
You knew where he would look for you.
He said he forgave me.
Forgiveness is too great
and difficult for one person.
It requires two.
The betrayer and the betrayed.
Which one are you?
I'm vague on those details.
Betrayal and forgiveness are...
...best seen as something
akin to falling in love.
You cannot control with respect
to whom you fall in love.
You are going to be caught.
It has already been set into motion.
Is that concern for your patient
or concern for yourself?
I'm not concerned about me.
I know exactly how I will navigate
my way out of whatever it is
I've gotten myself into.
Do you?
I did.
Where will Will Graham
be looking for you next?
Someplace I can never go.
Home.
It's not healing
to see your childhood home.
But it helps you measure
whether you are broken.
How and why,
assuming you want to know.
I want to know.
Is this where
construction began?
On my memory palace?
Its door at the centre of my mind,
and here you are, feeling for the latch.
The spaces in your mind
devoted to your earliest years...
...are they different than the other rooms?
Are they different than this room?
This room holds sound and motion,
great snakes wrestling and heaving
in the dark.
Other rooms are static scenes,
fragmentary.
Like painted shards of glass.
Everything keyed to memories,
leading to...
...other memories.
The rooms you can't bring yourself to go.
Nothing escapes from them
that causes you any comfort.
Screams fill some of those places,
but the corridors
do not echo screaming.
Because I hear music.
The Studiolo is a small, fierce group.
They've ruined a number
of academic reputations.
Appearing before them is a peril.
You were very eager to see me
discredited, Professor Sogliato.
You sang for your supper
before the dragons at the Studiolo.
And you sang very well.
Mm...
First applause,
and then by wet-eyed acclamation...
...the memberships affirmed you
as master of the Palazzo Capponi.
Punch Romaine.
A cocktail created by Escoffier.
Served to first-class guests on
the Titanic during their last dinner.
Mm...
The committees have a new curator.
They do not miss the old one.
If my victory pleased the professore,
I could not tell.
Then you weren't paying attention.
I pay lots of attention.
But not in a wide-eyed,
indiscriminate way.
That may have been impulsive.
Been mulling that impulse ever since
you decided to serve Punch Romaine.
I... I can't see.
Mi ricordo che il curatore...
Technically, you killed him.
No longer interested in preserving
the peace you found here?
You cannot preserve entropy.
It gradually descends into disorder.
Two men from the Capponi are dead.
I can only claim one.
Technically.
You're drawing them to you,
aren't you?
All of them.
As with his crimes in Florence,
Il Mostro collected anatomical trophies,
but left no evidence.
Dr Lecter is careful.
He will strike,
but his needs don't force him
to strike often.
There were long periods
when Il Mostro didn't strike at all.
This is the first in twenty years.
You have new evidence?
You know,
the window of the Questura laboratory
is garlanded with garlic
to keep out the evil spirits.
These are not people
open to new ideas.
My city mocks me.
My hunt for Il Mostro
has let the crows peck at my heart.
How is your heart?
Well pecked.
If he hasn't already,
Il Mostro will return to Florence.
Come back with me.
We have a chance
to regain our reputations,
and enjoy the honours of our trade,
by capturing the Monster.
I'm not here for the Monster.
Non è la mia casa.
Not my house, not my fire.
I'm here for Will Graham.
You're upsetting him.
You're trespassing.
I'm a friend of Hannibal's.
He sent you?
My name is Will Graham.
I'm unarmed.
May I lower my arms?
This trigger has a three-pound pull.
I'm holding two of it.
What's he saying?
He wants you to look at him,
speak to him,
but you're not going to.
Well, you've er...
cast aside the social graces
normally afforded to human beings.
He's cast them aside.
All he's allowed is the sound of water.
It's what the unborn hear.
It's their last memory of peace.
You're keeping him like an animal.
I wouldn't do this to an animal.
What did he do?
He ate her.
Mischa?
How long has he been your prisoner?
We've been each other's prisoner...
for a very long time.
However did you find yourself
in this situation?
That question applies to both of us.
And the answer's probably the same.
What's your name?
Chiyoh.
How do you know Hannibal?
One could argue, intimately.
Nakama?
It's the Japanese word
for a very close friends.
Yes, we were nakama.
Last time I saw him,
he left me with a smile.
All sorrows can be borne
if you put them in a story.
Tell me a story.
In Roman times,
each carcass was divided.
Prime cuts went to nobility,
second to the clergy,
third to the bourgeoisie
and fourth to the army.
The quinto quarto, the offal,
went to the poor.
The fifth quarter?
The innards of a carcass constitute
roughly a quarter of its weight.
"Il quinto quarto" evolved from necessity
to become high tradition.
Sibilo caratteristico.
When the lungs whistle,
the dish is done.
Coratella con carciofi.
Purple artichokes served with
spring lamb's liver, lungs and heart.
Professor Sogliato doesn't know
what he's missing.
So rude of him
to ignore your invitation.
He sends his regrets.
Oh, Madonna, it smells divine.
It is. I say that without ego.
I don't require
conventional reinforcement.
You would agree, Signora Fell?
My husband's ego is not measured
by conventional means.
I first prepared this dish in honour
of my sister when I was very young.
I'm sure you've perfected the recipe
over the years.
The meat...
- You have a very good butcher.
- I do indeed.
The lamb must be newly slaughtered,
the organs cooked the same day.
I always oversee this process personally.
We construct fairy tales,
and we accept them.
Our minds concoct
all sorts of fantasies
when we don't want
to believe something.
I accept what Hannibal has done.
I understand why he's done it.
Mischa doesn't explain Hannibal.
She doesn't quantify what he does.
He does what was done to her.
How do you know it was your prisoner
who killed Mischa?
Hannibal told me so.
Hannibal took someone from you.
Are you here
to take someone from him?
If I were like Hannibal...
...I would've killed you already.
Cooked you, ate you...
...and fed what was left of you to him.
That's what he would do.
You've given that some thought.
Do you know where he is?
Why are you looking for him
after he left you with a smile?
I've never known myself as well
as I know myself...
when I'm with him.
You won't find Hannibal here.
There are places on these grounds
he cannot safely go.
Bad memories.
What do these grounds hold for you?
Hannibal wanted to kill that man
for what he did to Mischa.
I wouldn't let him take his life,
so Hannibal left his life with me.
He was...
...curious if you would kill.
I imagine he still is.
What were you like as a young man?
I was rooting for Mephistopheles
and contemptuous of Faust.
Would you like to talk
about your first spring lamb?
Would you?
Why can't you go home, Hannibal?
What happened to you there?
Nothing happened to me.
I happened.
How did your sister taste?
Go!
Are you a believer,
Signor Crawford?
Aren't we all?
Belief comes with imagination.
We also imagine the possibility
that we all live on after death.
Will Graham died.
Lui era morto.
lo ero morto.
He was dead. I was dead.
We didn't imagine that.
What does Will Graham imagine now?
I borrowed his imagination.
And I broke it.
But I don't know how he managed
to piece it back together again.
People come here
to be closer to their god.
Isn't that
what Will Graham was doing?
Maybe.
Will Graham understands Hannibal.
He accepts him.
Now, who among us doesn't want
understanding and acceptance?
I'm sorry.
You did this.
You set him free.
It was you I wanted to set free.
You said Hannibal was curious
if I would kill.
You were curious, too.
- I didn't want this.
- Yes, you did.
You were doing what he does.
He'd be proud of you, his nakama.
Did you know?
At some level... you knew.
He created a story...
...out of events
that only he experienced.
"All sorrows can be borne
if you put them in a story."
For Mischa.
I'll help you find him.
Why would you help me?
I have no reason to stay here.
Not anymore.
You saw to that.
What your sister made you feel
was beyond your conscious ability
to control or predict.
Or negotiate.
I would suggest what Will Graham
makes you feel is not dissimilar.
A force of mind and circumstance.
Love.
He pays you a visit or he doesn't.
Same with forgiveness.
And I would argue,
the same with betrayal.
The god Betrayal who presupposes
the god Forgiveness.
We can all betray.
Sometimes we have no other choice.
Mischa didn't betray me.
She influenced me to betray myself,
but I forgave her that influence.
If past behaviour is an indicator
of future behaviour,
there is only one way
you will forgive Will Graham.
I have to eat him.