'Previously on "Hannibal"...'
The novelty
of Hannibal Lecter has waned.
This fellow, there is something
so universal about what he does.
This freak is
in phase with the moon.
We might have a little more than
three weeks before he does it again.
I don't think
about this anymore.
I don't think I can be
of any use to you, Jack.
Is there an opinion
that you want, Will?
I have to see Hannibal.
That's the same atrocious aftershave
you wore in court.
Hello, Dr Lecter.
Hello, Will.
- Did you get my note?
- I got it. Thank you.
Did you read it
before you destroyed it?
Or did you simply toss it
into the nearest fire?
I read it.
And then I burned it.
And you came anyway.
I'm glad you came.
My other callers are all professional.
Banal psychiatrists
and grasping second-raters.
Pencil-lickers.
I want you to help me, Dr Lecter.
Yes, I thought so.
Are we no longer on a first-name basis?
I'm more comfortable
the less personal we are.
I smell dogs and pine and oil
beneath that shaving lotion.
It's something a child
would select, isn't it?
Is there a child in your life, Will?
I gave you a child, if you recall.
I came about Chicago and Buffalo.
- You've read about it.
- I've read the papers. I can't clip them.
They won't let me have scissors,
of course.
You want to know
how he's choosing them.
I thought you would have some ideas.
You just came here to look at me.
Came to get the old scent again.
Why don't you just smell yourself?
I expected more of you, Doctor.
That routine... is old hat.
Whereas you are a new man.
Are you a good father, Will?
Let me have the file.
An hour, and we can discuss it
like old times.
Thank you.
Family values may have declined
over the last century,
but we still help our families
when we can.
You're family, Will.
How many people have you killed?
Many more than your father.
Are you going to kill me?
I'm so sorry, Abigail.
I'm sorry I couldn't protect you
in this life.
Blood rituals involve a symbolic death
and then a rebirth.
As with all things in the natural world,
you'll adapt now and mutate later.
Evolve or die.
Even if you know the state
of who you are today,
you can't predict
who you will be tomorrow.
You are defined up to now,
not beyond.
How would you have done it,
if you were going to do it?
How would I have murdered you?
I would have cut your throat
like your father did.
But you're not my father.
You accepted your father.
Would it be so difficult to accept me?
I don't know if it would be smart.
We don't get wiser
as we get older, Abigail,
but we do learn to avoid or raise
a certain amount of hell,
depending on which we prefer.
I'll need to collect some flesh.
Not a pound. Only a piece.
Something you can live without.
You mean, like a finger?
I couldn't bear to take your fingers,
not even one.
They're so lovely.
And I was hoping to teach you
how to play the harpsichord.
That's enough for now.
This will approximate
the amount of pressure.
Blood leaves the body at a gallop
and then a stumble.
Are you ready to die, Abigail?
Yes.
Can I push the button?
Abigail Hobbs is dead.
Long live Abigail Hobbs.
It's good to see you
looking so well, Will.
But I can't help wishing
you weren't here.
Wishing and hoping.
How did it feel to see him again?
Like, erm...
...Hannibal was looking
through to the back of my skull.
Felt like a fly
flitting around back there.
I had the absurd feeling
that he walked out with me.
I had to stop outside the doors and
look around, make sure I was alone.
I know that feeling.
Well, at least Jack Crawford
is pleased.
He showed me
pictures of the families.
I looked at Molly and Walter
and I couldn't say no.
And Jack was counting on it.
Are you still with Margot?
Yes.
We have a baby.
A Verger baby. A son.
- Good for Margot.
- Good for me, I carried him.
He's my son. He's the Verger heir.
So... what are you doing here?
There are only five doors
between Hannibal and the outside.
And I have the keys to all of them.
Hannibal has never been great
with boundaries.
"He who sups with the Devil
needs a long spoon."
I'm not letting him in, Alana.
Don't worry about me.
I'm not just worried about you.
Last time, it didn't end with you.
This is a very shy boy, Will.
I would love to meet him.
I'm sure you would.
Have you considered the possibility
that he's disfigured?
Or that he may believe
he's disfigured?
That's interesting.
That's not interesting.
You thought of that before.
He smashed all the mirrors
in the houses,
not just enough to get
the pieces he wanted.
These shards are set so he can
see himself in Mrs Jacobi's eyes.
Could you see yourself
in their eyes, Will?
Killing them all?
The first small bond to the killer
itches and stings like a leech.
Like you, Will, he needs a family
to escape what's inside him.
You know a fair amount
about how these families died.
How they lived is
how he chooses them.
How is he choosing them?
How did you choose yours?
A ready-made wife and child
to serve your needs.
A stepson or daughter...
A stepson absolves you
of any biological blame.
You know better than to breed.
Can't pass on those terrible traits
you fear the most.
Why are there no descriptions
of the grounds?
I see floor plans, diagrams of the rooms
where death occurred.
What were the yards like?
Big, fenced, with trees. Why?
If this pilgrim feels
a special relationship with the moon,
he might like to go outside and
look at it, before he tidies himself up.
If one were nude, say,
it would be better to have outdoor
privacy for that sort of thing.
One must show some consideration
for the neighbours.
Have you ever seen blood
in the moonlight, Will?
It appears quite black.
You've come to wag your finger?
I love a good finger-wagging.
Yes, you do.
How is Margot?
Your cogs are turning, Hannibal.
I can hear them clicking.
Boom.
I don't know what you're planning
with Will Graham,
but you're planning something.
Why wouldn't you be?
You've already cracked the lid,
can't resist peeling it back.
Will came to me.
Yes, he did.
I advised him against it.
I'm sure.
Are you suggesting I don't have
Will's best interests in my mind?
I'm stating it as fact.
You've got Will dressed up
in moral-dignity pants.
Nothing is his fault.
I've been courteous.
And you've been receptive
to courtesy.
These niceties are conditional.
And the conditions are non-negotiable.
I must behave myself.
I know what you're afraid of.
It's not pain or solitude.
It's indignity.
You're a little bit like a cat that way.
I'll take your books,
I'll take your drawings,
I'll take your toilet.
You'll have nothing but indignity...
...and the company of the dead.
We have a basic affinity
for our family.
We can detect each other
from smell alone.
You recognise this?
My father made it. Out of bone.
Your father never wished for anything
but your happiness.
- My father cut my throat.
- Out of love.
That wasn't love.
Every family loves differently.
Every love is unique.
You deny your love for your father
because of what it might mean about you.
Can you smell him here, Abigail?
Yes.
This is what your father is.
This is all of him now.
This is what death
has reduced him to.
All that's left is honesty.
Can you be honest with me now?
He was as good to me
as he knew how to be.
Hunting with him was
the best time I ever had.
Yes. A fine definition of love.
You have to allow yourself to love him
the way he loved you.
What you need of your father is here,
in your head,
and subject to your judgment,
not his.
Never be ashamed
of who you are, Abigail.
Found it behind the Jacobis' garage.
Flower between its paws,
wrapped in a dish towel, strangled.
Son of a bitch.
Seems like you're more upset about
the cat than you were about the children.
I'm particularly fond of cats,
I'm not particularly fond of children.
- What about the Leeds' dog?
- Punctured in the abdomen.
The vet worked on him.
He should be OK.
Thought he was shot,
but they didn't find a bullet.
Thought he was stabbed
with an ice pick or an awl.
The son of a bitch.
So he feels compelled to hurt the victims'
pets before he comes to kill the family?
It eliminates an early-warning system.
Case the place,
kill the pet, then the family.
We should send a private bulletin
to veterinarians and animal shelters,
asking for an immediate report
of animal mutilation.
Chicago and Buffalo
are four states apart.
Nothing's been found
to link these two families.
What do they have in common?
They were both happy.
I sat here.
And I watched them.
Now are you just keeping America
clean or is that evidence?
You're trespassing, Freddie.
I was trespassing
before the blood dried.
- When did they call you in?
- I'm not talking to you.
We're co-conspirators, Will.
I died for you and your cause.
You didn't die enough.
You came into my hospital room
while I was sleeping,
flipped back the covers and snapped
a photo of my temporary colostomy bag.
Covered your junk with a black box.
A big black box.
You're welcome.
- You called us "murder husbands".
- You did run off to Europe together.
How does the Tooth Fairy compare
with Hannibal Lecter?
I haven't seen anything like this
since the Massacre at Muskrat Farm.
Funny thing about that massacre,
not only did Dr Bloom survive,
she got rich.
Lecter's living in the lap under her care.
What kind of arrangement
do you suppose they have?
A complicated arrangement.
It couldn't be more complicated
than your relationship with Hannibal.
You paid him a visit? Before you lie,
know that I know you did.
Goodbye, Freddie.
"Federal manhunters, stymied
in their search for the Tooth Fairy,
"have turned to the most savage killer
in captivity for help.
"'It takes one to catch one,'
a federal official told this reporter."
"Takes one to catch one"?
You're referring
to Hannibal Lecter or me?
I'll let my readers decide.
If you're smart, you'd use me.
All psychopaths are narcissists.
They love to read about themselves.
Come on in.
I'm Francis Dolarhyde.
The same Mr D who sends the rockets
when the requisitions are wrong?
The very one.
Put your back against
the door, come forward three steps,
until you feel the tile under your feet.
There'll be a stool on your right.
I'll just put this stuff in the black hole.
I was gonna...
Do you think I could have a plum?
Sure. They're really good.
- I need to ask a favour.
- In addition to the plum?
In addition to the plum.
I need some...infrared movie film.
Hot, sensitive up around...
...1,000 nanometres.
- Better off shooting digital.
- Oh, I'm not a fan of that format.
Nobody around here is.
I'm shooting at maybe...eight feet.
I want to photograph
the nocturnal animals at the zoo.
The more sensitive the film,
the meaner it is to handle.
You get in the coolers,
dry ice, all that.
- Do you plan to process it yourself?
- Uh-huh.
Got to be total darkness.
Can't even wear infrared goggles.
They'll give off radiation
and cloud the film.
I'm happy to do it for you, if you want.
Privacy guaranteed.
Thank you for the offer.
- Miss McClane.
- Mr D.
Can I give you a ride home?
Thank you. I take the bus all the time,
you don't need to worry about me.
I'm not worried.
Ride with me...
...for my pleasure.
Come in and I'll give you a drink.
So...how long have you been
at Gateway?
Three months.
I trained newly-blind people
for ten years after I finished school.
This's my first job on the outside.
Outside of what?
The inside.
I was training people to live
in the sighted world.
I didn't live in it myself.
I thought I'd get out,
knock around a little.
I wanted to go into speech therapy for
speech-and-hearing-impaired children.
I expect I'll go back to that
one of these days.
Do you cook?
Uh-huh.
How about coffee?
Let's talk about something for a minute
and get it out of the way.
You haven't said anything
since I mentioned speech therapy.
I understand you
because you speak very well
and because I listen.
People don't pay attention.
If you don't want to talk, OK.
But I hope that you do talk
because you can,
and because I'm interested
in what you have to say.
Huh.
That's good.
Here's what I like, Francis.
I've felt no sympathy from you.
I like that.
Sympathy feels like spit on my cheek.
And I don't do self-pity.
May I touch your face?
I just want to know
if you're smiling or frowning.
I want to know whether
to just shut up or not.
Trust me.
I'm smiling.
- Hello, hotshot. Doing some good?
- 'Nothing you'd notice.'
- I'm lonesome.
- 'Me, too.'
- I'm feeling Randy.
Me, too.
- Randy's our new dog.
- Oh, hell!
Randy's got huge balls.
'Never mind about his balls.'
They almost drag on the ground.
He has to retract them when he runs.
- 'Can you retract yours?'
- Erm...
I retracted them once
when I was a kid.
Had to clear a barbed-wire fence,
carrying a stolen watermelon.
A criminal mind even at that age.
I don't have a criminal mind.
Of course you don't.
We have a new, new dog.
- 'Newer than Randy?'
- Belonged to one of the families.
There was no one left to claim her.
So I claimed her.
'You're a very sweet man.'
I love you and I miss you,
and you're doing the right thing.
'It's costing you, too, I know that.'
I'm here.
And I'll be here
whenever you come home.
- Good night, Molly.
- 'Good night, sweet man.'
As I live and breathe.
I thought I'd seen the last of you, Jack.
Dr Lecter.
You're dressing younger.
Have you taken up some sport
you enjoy with a new partner?
Tennis, maybe?
You've taken up your sport
with an old partner.
I wrote Will a note,
warning him you'd come calling.
Yes, I read your note
before my office forwarded it to Will.
To whet his appetite or yours?
You've placed him back in the pot
and you're letting him cook.
We're all in this stew together, Doctor.
It would be more honest if you ate
his brain right out of his skull.
And you're nothing if not honest.
This shy boy has already seen Will.
He already knows his name.
- Are you chumming the waters, Jack?
- It takes one to catch one.
It takes two to catch one.
Will has never been more effective
than he is with you inside his head.
I agree.
But don't think you can persuade me
to play along
with appeals to my intellectual vanity.
I don't think I'll persuade you, Doctor.
You'll either play or you won't.
Bella used to say your face was all scars,
if you knew how to look.
There's always room for a few more.
How much room does Will have, Jack?
Hello?
'They know.'
They're coming.
Are we going?
We're waiting for Will.
It's important that he sees you.
I want you two to be together.
They'll catch us if we stay.
I'm on my honour
to look after you, Abigail.
You have to look after me, too.
We have to protect each other
in these new lives we create.
I want you to go upstairs and wait.
For what?
Hunting with your father was
the best time you've ever had.
But now you're going to hunt with me.
- It's your attorney.
- Thank you.
- Hello?
- 'Hello, Dr Lecter.
'I wanted to tell you
that I am delighted
'that you have taken
an interest in me.
'I don't believe
you would tell them who I am,
'even if you knew.
'The important thing
is what I am becoming.
'I knew you alone would
understand this.'
Tell me, what are you becoming?
'The Great Red Dragon.'