'Previously on "Hannibal"...'
Dr Hannibal Lecter requests
my company for dinner.
This will be our last supper.
Hannibal thinks you're his man
in the room. I think you're mine.
They've issued a warrant
for your arrest, Will.
- Hello?
- They know.
Hello, Jack. You're early.
'Each of us
'whose life intersected
Hannibal Lecter lost something.
'A limb here, a lung there.
'A few feet of intestines.'
The dead...
at least have the luxury
of being done with what they lost.
You and I, we still itch.
That little itch must be
telling you something.
Would you like to discuss
what that little itch is telling you?
Are you wearing makeup?
How long does it take you
to put your face on in the morning?
Now that I've got the routine down,
no time at all.
I'll tell you what. You show me yours,
and I'll show you mine.
There.
Now we can talk face-to-face.
I understand you have offered
quite a substantial reward
for any kind of relevant information
on Hannibal Lecter,
not just the usual
apprehension and conviction.
Yes, a million dollars.
One million.
We advertised worldwide.
A high price for a fancy pig.
Hannibal would be a prize pig
if I had him in my hospital,
but you do not intend to see him
institutionalised, do you?
I'm saying nothing
that would force you
to break the bonds
of doctor-patient confidentiality.
You don't want a therapist,
you want a profiler.
I want to understand Hannibal Lecter,
to better understand myself.
You survived him. That is chief
amongst what you need to understand.
"Survived him"?
That implies fortune or skill on my part
that somehow allowed me to live.
This is exactly
how he intended me to live.
I know somewhere Dr Lecter
is going to and fro in the earth
and walking up and down in it,
and very likely having
a good, fun time.
How do you relieve the agony
of waiting for Dr Lecter's capture?
What do you fantasise about?
I wonder what would happen
if Hannibal Lecter was in your hands.
I worry we're heading into territory
not secured by your fee.
I think I need to look elsewhere
for someone to tend
to my emotional well-being.
Goodbye, Dr Chilton.
Happy hunting.
You were supposed to leave.
We couldn't leave
without you.
How do you feel?
Thirsty.
Feel well enough for a visitor?
Hello, Frederick.
You were expecting someone else?
I was hoping for someone else.
He knew exactly how to cut you.
They said it was surgical.
He wanted you to live.
He left us to die.
But we didn't.
Couple of suckers we've been.
He set us up and knocked us down.
What bothers me the most is,
I think it was easy for him.
Shooting monkeys in a barrel.
You had encephalitis.
I do not know what my excuse was.
Compulsive imitation.
How dull.
But maybe.
I am learning all sorts of new things
about myself these days.
I'm learning new things about you, too.
Imitation allows us to better understand
the behaviour of others.
I have great empathy for you, Will.
Both of us eviscerated and accused.
I have literally felt your pain.
We have matching scars.
You need a friend, friend.
You will leave this hospital
under a cloud of suspicion.
Not a cloud, a fog.
I can help you get Hannibal Lecter
out of your head.
And into your hospital.
There's opportunity here.
For both of us.
We can catch the man
who framed and maimed us.
There's no opportunity here,
Frederick.
Not for you.
The optimist believes we live
in the best of all possible worlds.
The pessimist fears this is true.
This is your best possible world, Will.
Not getting a better one.
I had hoped
you would come look for me.
But I understand why you didn't.
What can I do for you, Jack?
Well, I'm here to, er...
...make sure that you don't
contradict the official narrative.
Uh-huh.
Well, we're officers of the FBI,
wounded in the course of heroic duty.
That's not true for either of us.
Well, we were supposed to go together.
That's... That's on me.
My foul. My bad.
Not all of our choices
are consciously calculated.
No.
But our decisions are.
You remember when you decided
to call Hannibal?
I wasn't decided when I called him.
I just called him.
I deliberated while the phone rang.
I decided when I heard his voice.
You told him we knew.
I told him to leave.
I wanted him to run.
Why?
Because...
Because he... he was my friend.
And because I wanted
to run away with him.
What I said before,
I will say again,
which is something you cannot say.
That I did not warn you.
Cannot see what you will not see.
Until it shoves you out a window.
I've always enjoyed
the word "defenestration".
Now I get to use it
in casual conversation.
How many bones did you break?
You say that like I broke them.
You got yourself to the window,
Dr Bloom, if not through it.
They told me a lot of marrow
got into my blood.
And that I should expect
to find myself thinking differently.
Hallelujah!
I do not mean to kick you
when you are down.
I'm just reminding you
how you got down.
And who I'm down with.
We could all use a little group therapy
while we're down here.
There's only one "we"
you're really interested in, Frederick.
And that "we" isn't really
interested in you.
Will Graham could use
a breakthrough.
Being broken was his breakthrough.
Being broken was yours.
Will has not had his breakthrough yet.
He is saving that for Dr Lecter.
Would be the best thing
for his therapy, really.
It's only a matter of time before
they are back in each other's orbit.
Shame not to have the good seats.
If only to support poor Will.
That would require some manipulation.
Some English on the ball, as it were.
'You were so afraid of me
the last time I saw you.
'Before that last time I saw you.'
What are you doing here?
I guess I'm looking for you.
That's a good guess.
- What are you doing here?
- Visiting old friends.
You're not tempted to forget?
I don't want to forget.
I'm building rooms in my memory palace
for all my friends.
Friendship with Hannibal is blackmail
elevated to the level of love.
A mutually-unspoken pact
to ignore the worst in one another
in order to continue enjoying the best.
After everything he's done,
can you still ignore the worst in him?
I came here to be alone, Alana.
If you wouldn't mind.
I'm Dr Bloom.
You're the new psychiatrist.
I went one exit too far
on the expressway,
came back along the service road.
I'm not sure if this is my entrance.
This can be your entrance.
It isn't easy to find,
the first time you come.
I'm Margot Verger.
A witchy beauty about this place.
Yes, isn't there?
You should see it in the spring.
Riot of lilacs in the wind
smells nothing at all
like the stockyards and slaughterhouses
one usually associates
with the Verger name.
Can you please
let your brother know I'm here?
He knows.
Some people have trouble
talking with Mason.
So, if it bothers you,
or you can't take it,
I'd be happy to answer
any questions that you have.
Thank you.
Margot, you can leave us now!
If my brother offers you chocolate,
politely refuse.
Ah, good afternoon, Dr Bloom.
Good afternoon, Mr Verger.
You know,
I thank God for what happened.
It was my salvation.
Have you accepted Jesus, Dr Bloom?
Do you have faith?
I was raised in a religious atmosphere,
Mr Verger,
but whatever that left me with,
it's not religion.
Left me with more.
You see, I'm free, Dr Bloom.
I'm right with the Risen Jesus
and it's all OK now.
And nobody beats the Riz.
He will rise me up
and smite mine enemies
and I shall hear the lamentations
of their women.
That was once you, I'm told.
Dr Lecter got deeper inside you
than he did any of us.
Do you want me to get the nurse?
No, no, I'm... I'm fine now.
It's all OK now.
You're supposed to share any relevant
information you find on Hannibal Lecter
with the FBI.
Have you always done that?
Not exactly.
I want you to understand, Dr Bloom,
that this is not a revenge thing.
I have forgiven Dr Lecter
as our Saviour forgave
the Roman soldiers.
Forgiveness isn't all
it's cracked up to be, Mr Verger.
I don't need religion to appreciate
the idea of Old Testament revenge.
'Jack?
'Are you there?'
Did I die?
You did a lot of things.
Dying may have been among them.
For once, I'm glad you're stubborn.
What's good for the goose...
You're not going into the ground
with me, Jack.
So stop trying.
I was dead.
I knew I was dead.
All that was left for me to do was die.
I thought if I could hear your voice,
we both wouldn't have to die alone.
I'm not afraid of dying.
I'm not afraid of what it will be like
to be dead.
I'm more curious...
...of any what-ifs
than I am of any absolutes.
You can do something that I can't.
You can cut out...
...what's killing you.
Every useful hoop
our mind can jump through
begins with a certain degree
of attention.
Focus is the most important thing
any of us can do.
You...
You are losing focus, Jack.
I have refocused.
Forced retirement at the FBI?
You fall in love with the Bureau,
but it does not fall in love with you.
Behavioural Sciences
doesn't have the resources.
Homeland Security is the priority now.
Terrorists are more frightening
than psychopaths.
Not to me.
Really?
The first thing you did
after getting shot in the face
was copyright "Hannibal the Cannibal."
A catchphrase is a trademark
and protected as a form of property.
You are alive because you did not
pull that glass from your neck.
Will Graham is alive because
Hannibal Lecter likes him that way.
Maybe it's one of those friendships
that ends after the disembowelling.
I would argue, with these two,
that's tantamount to flirtation.
Will is going to lead you right to him.
Oh, no, he's not, not to me.
I've let them both go.
I've let it all go.
You dangle Will Graham
and now you cut bait?
You're letting Hannibal have him
hook, line and sinker.
You'll excuse me, Dr Chilton,
I like to be home in the evenings
when my wife wakes.
Jack?
God, I love you in white.
She'll look beautiful.
Bella's dead.
That should change
the view from these windows.
It's not right
if the view stays the same.
It's not right.
'I'm so sorry about Bella, Jack.'
I opened my eyes this morning,
and, at that moment,
before the weight of the day came for me,
I didn't even think about Bella dying.
I still think she was hoping to die
while I was out of the room.
But... I was there
when her heart stopped.
And I held onto her
until her brain died.
I hope she's somewhere today, Jack.
And that she's comfortable.
I hope she can see in my heart.
She had to die on me.
I knew it was coming.
But it still smarts.
I know what's coming for you, Will.
You don't have to die on me, too.
Ow.
- I'm saying "ow".
- Blood is flowing.
Nerves are intact.
Pain is a good thing.
This is why you can never legally
work in the health industry, Cordell.
They were going to throw you away.
You would've been wasted.
Scar tissue is an awesome
demonstration of self-preservation.
The flesh's fight to exist,
down to the most basic cell,
is a wonder.
At Communions around the earth,
the devout believe that,
through the miracle of transubstantiation,
they eat the flesh and blood of Christ.
It is an impressive ceremony.
I need to prepare an even more
impressive ceremony
with no transubstantiation necessary.
Cordell, I have known you
to be absolutely reliable
and capable of almost anything.
Is that true?
It is not untrue.
I pay you a large salary to be responsible
for my care and feeding.
- And all that that entails.
- All that that entails.
I would like you to begin arrangements
for Dr Hannibal Lecter to be eaten alive.
Do you have a preference
for how you would like him prepared?
Oh, Cordell...
If I had lips, I would smile.
Good as new.
All this time he eludes us,
got away clean.
It's as though Hannibal Lecter
has dropped off the earth.
Hannibal obviously has
good papers and money.
Europe is where a man of his tastes
would settle.
His tastes are very specific.
And that's how you'll find him.
Oh?
The wine.
The truffles.
Taste in all things will be a constant
between Dr Lecter's lives.
His name will change,
but his taste will not.
Of course,
you know what he would favour.
Tell me, Dr Bloom,
does he favour you?
I think I amused him.
Things either amuse him or they don't,
and if they don't...
Well, you didn't.
Do you feel he ever
genuinely cared for you?
I have no idea how Dr Lecter
genuinely feels about me.
Last time we spoke,
he promised he'd kill me.
Tell me, how does it feel to use
understanding as a predator's tool?
I'm using it as I've always used it.
A psychiatric tool.
Why not take this to Jack Crawford?
Jack's done at the FBI.
A footnote in his own
Evil Minds Museum.
I'm curious, Dr Bloom,
how I have found you in my pocket.
Do tell.
I'm all ears.
They've just been redistributed.
You're preparing the theatre
of Hannibal's death.
I'm just doing my part
to get him to the stage.
Where's Will?
He's already gone, Jack.
Will knows what he has to do.
Do you?