[indistinct chatter]
[Alex] I died when I was 11.
My mom and I were living in Alaska
at the time.
One of her many failed attempts
at reinvention.
I fell through the ice.
I heard it crack
and watched as the water
started to pool around my ladybug boots.
I remember thinking rather calmly:
"I'm about to disappear."
"There are many...
There are a lot of theories
about who rescued me.
Not that I know.
I blocked it all out.
Some say that it was the dog next door
who barked.
Some say my mom finally came home
and remembered that she had a daughter.
[Alex chuckles]
Some say that it was me.
That I punched my way through the ice.
Crawled my way out.
But I'm not sure.
Maybe I never made it out of there at all.
Maybe I've been a ghost
all of these years."
And that would make sense.
Because none of you guys
seem to hear me at all.
Thank you so much for...
Uh, it's something I've been working on.
[rock music playing faintly]
Look at you.
Reading sad words up there.
Thank you for covering for me.
[chuckles] Thirteen wants another
pitcher of Bud. Six wants cheesecake.
Uh, I have a question.
Who is that guy right there.
Do you know him?
Sean.
You don't know Sean?
Bartends at the Swan.
Would you mind going
and seeing what he's reading?
Are you serious?
- Can I get a pitcher of Bud for 13?
- Sure.
Love is a Dog...Something.
Love is a Dog from Hell. Bukowski.
[Tania] Uh-oh.
[Nate] Alex?
[Nate chuckles]
Nate.
From Neptune. From brunch?
Uh, Nate. Right. Of course.
Hi. Of course I run into you.
Hey. Yeah.
I was just catching the ferry
going into work early and I was like:
"Whoa. That girl looks like Alex."
And it is.
- This must be Maddy.
- Yeah.
Recognize her from Facebook.
What are you guys doing
camped out on the floor?
- What are you, stranded?
- Ah, no.
We just got to the ferry a little early,
so we're taking a little catnap.
- What time do you have? My phone died.
- 6:05.
Why do you have a vacuum?
I'm just really
into vacuums right now, Nate.
Like to keep one close.
Okay. Well, the ferry's here,
so why don't I just help you out
with your stuff?
That's okay.
We're taking a different ferry.
Thank you, though.
It was good to see you.
What other ferry?
I'm gonna let her sleep, is all.
She's just, uh...
That's all I meant. She's sleepy.
I'm gonna let her sleep a little.
Listen, I don't have to go
into work this early.
Um, can I give you a ride somewhere?
Maybe buy us breakfast?
Oh. Uh, no. I'm... We're good. Yeah.
Come on. I got a phone charger in the car.
We'll hit Starbucks.
Let me help you out.
[pop music playing]
Hey, Maddy. You wanna watch Frozen?
I got it on a continuous loop
back there for my son.
- No.
- [Alex] Mm.
She's very afraid of the snow creature.
No Frozen, sorry.
Oh. Okay. Um...
Ah. Brady loves that part
because he's a psychopath.
Is he your only one?
Yes.
And his mom and I just got divorced,
so that's a hard yes.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Don't be.
It was amicable.
She really looks like Sean.
You think?
Yeah, I mean, that's a good thing, right?
Look like the great...
Sean Boyd.
Hey, Alaska.
Hi.
So you're still writing?
Oh, yeah.
All the time.
Because you're so talented, I mean...
- You still working at Neptune?
- No, no.
I'm a structural engineer now.
Remember, I was in grad school at U-Dub?
Honestly, I can't even swim.
I'm just boned.
I would've just sunk.
Yeah, I joined this small firm in Seattle.
I mean, maybe not that small.
We just opened a second office in L.A.
[microphone feeds back]
- Wow.
- Yeah.
[cell phone pinging]
[cell phone ringing]
You don't know
where the 360 area code is, do you?
Merritt, I think?
Do you want me to help you out?
No, I'm good, I'm good, I'm good.
Thank you.
- Thank you, really, though.
- Okay.
Come here, baby girl. I know.
Come here.
- [Maddy babbling]
- What?
Hey.
- Thank you so much, really.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, here. Keep it.
- Oh. Um...
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, I've got more.
And you got my number, right?
So call me if you need anything.
[Alex] What do you say, Mad?
You wanna say goodbye?
Wanna say thank you?
Oh!
Okay.
Oh, wow.
So strong.
Strong, strong, strong.
Yeah? If this is another summons,
you can shove it up your ass.
[Alex] It's Alex.
- Who?
- Alex.
Oh. You. The Dyson thief.
Don't bring that kid in here.
Look, I can explain.
I can explain too.
Value Maids. Ignore. Value Maids. Ignore.
Who am I? Your phone.
- I got into a car accident.
- Sure you did.
No, I really did.
I got into a car accident on Route 20
and I totaled my car.
- Got a photo right here.
- Jesus Christ, that's your car?
I stand corrected.
But I still can't pay you,
if that's why you're here.
I had an emergency.
Client doesn't give a shit.
All she knows is you didn't come back.
I don't get paid, you don't get paid.
I did that cleaning, Yolanda.
I busted my ass for three hours.
I didn't stop to pee.
I bought the supplies, paid for the gas.
I lost two hours of my life
going back and forth to Regina's house.
Hey, sucks for me too.
I'm out the money
and a very valuable client.
Life shits on your balls sometimes.
[cell phone ringing]
Okay, are you sure there's not
any other shift that you have left open?
- I'll take anything.
- I'll keep you in mind.
I really need this work.
I really need this pay stub.
I promise you I won't mess up again.
Leave your uniform there, hon?
[cell phone ringing]
- Hello?
- [John] Is this Alex Russell?
Um, who's this?
This is John Marshal, ma'am.
I represent Sean Boyd.
You have an attorney
or can we speak directly?
I'm sorry, who is this?
I'm Mr. Boyd's attorney, ma'am.
I'm calling to notify you that Mr. Boyd
has filed an emergency petition
with the Family Court of Ludlow County
to have his child, Maddy Boyd,
returned
to his custodial care immediately.
The court has called a preliminary
hearing for tomorrow at 10 a.m.
If you fail to show,
he will file a further petition to forgo
all your parental rights to Maddy.
Do you understand everything
you've been notified of?
Sean didn't even graduate high school.
How does he have a lawyer?
Anyone can get one.
All you need is 1500 bucks.
Sean doesn't have 1500 bucks.
Well, somebody does. His family?
I don't know, that's not your problem.
Your problem is you don't have a roof
over her head.
That's not gonna look good in court.
We need to get you
off the streets immediately.
There's no beds at Shawgit,
not that you'd get there without a car.
- Yolanda advance you that pay stub?
- Nope.
So we still can't qualify you
for transitional housing.
There's beds
at the domestic violence shelter,
but you said you're not DV?
Yeah. I'd really hate to take a bed
from somebody's that been abused for real.
"Abused for real." What does that mean?
Beaten up. Hurt.
And what does fake abuse look like?
Intimidation?
Threats?
Control?
You need to call the DV hotline yourself.
They'll send a cab around to the
closest police station to pick you up.
Call and say what?
"Help."
[pensive music playing]
[Denise] Thank you.
You're Alex, this is Maddy?
I'm Denise. We spoke on the phone.
You're here. You can breathe.
Good, baby girl.
We do a lot of breathing here. Yes, we do.
You carry Maddy, I'll get your bag.
- [speaking indistinctly]
- Mm-hm.
[Denise] This is Cal, he's always here.
On his desk is the sign-out book
where you sign,
in and out.
Now, your phone goes here.
Just check the location is off first.
- I'm not allowed to use my phone?
- You can use it all you want.
It'll be right here for you.
Just have to leave the premises to use it.
Walk a block or two.
Protecting the confidentiality
of our location is our top priority.
[Maddy] No.
No.
I wanna go home.
This whole place is just for us?
It certainly is.
Look at this.
- Look how cute that is. Look at...
- No. No.
I'm sorry, she's very sleepy.
I'll have them bring dinner
so you can settle in.
And a change of clothes for her.
What is she, size 3?
Thank you.
[Maddy screams]
- Wow.
- No, no, no.
Come here. Check this out.
[Maddy crying]
Hi. I live up in 23.
Try this.
The woman who lived in 3 left them behind
when she moved out,
so maybe your daughter will like them.
- Thank you.
- Don't mention it.
- I have something I think you might like.
- Mm-mm.
Do you wanna see what it is? Do you?
You want a special surprise?
All right. Well...
[Alex gasps]
- What in tarnation?
- What?
- What are they?
- Oh, my goodness.
Look at them. Look at all the ponies.
["Like a Woman Should" playing]
Look at these ponies.
- Yellow? Okay?
- What?
It's standing up.
Oh, my gosh.
♪ Your love is a sweet thing ♪
♪ The anger in me chooses to ignore ♪
♪ And sometimes I wish that I was ♪
♪ Wish that I was ♪
♪ Wish that I was born in another time ♪
♪ In the future ♪
♪ See my daughters born ♪
♪ Born into a world where ♪
♪ Suddenly like I could walk the street ♪
♪ I walk the street like a woman should ♪
♪ Like nobody was around ♪
♪ Like I could walk the street ♪
♪ I walk the street like a woman should ♪
♪ Suddenly like I could ♪
♪ Walk the street like a woman should ♪
- Hey.
- I wanted to come by
- and say thank you so much.
- I'll come out.
So?
Did the ponies work? It sounded like it.
Absolutely. You're a lifesaver.
Amazing. Thank you.
They are so fucking creepy, right?
I showed my son and he was like, "Nah."
Super creepy, yeah,
I guess I don't know why anyone
would have that many ponies.
Girl, I got a lot of questions
about the girl who lived in 3.
Smelled like she was cooking turds.
I'm Alex, by the way.
I'm sorry, I don't know
if I'm supposed to...
use real names here.
That's up to you.
Some girl's calling herself
Yasmina Jade Skye over there,
and we all know that's bullshit.
But my real name is Danielle.
My real name is Alex.
How old is your son?
Oh, he's 7. He's in first grade.
How about yours?
She's almost 3. Yeah.
- Uh, your eyelashes are very beautiful.
- Oh, I know, right? Shelter chic.
[chuckles]
Trying to be my own advertisement
'cause I do lashes as a side hustle.
Trying to get more serious
so it could be my main hustle.
Like be a boss babe.
"Lashes by Danielle." No, no, no.
"Luscious Lashes by Danielle."
I love it, yeah.
[both laughing]
Do you need anything?
Um, no, we're all set. Um...
Actually... Unless...
Um...
I'm sorry, you don't have anything
that I could wear to court, do you?
Girl.
Girl, come on!
We're gonna do your makeup
and your lashes too.
[pensive music playing]
[Doreen] Oh.
- She brought Maddy.
- [Sean] Oh, fuck.
[metal detector beeps]
Maddy Moo.
- Hey!
- Daddy!
Hey, baby.
So good to see you.
Okay?
Brought her to court?
Why are you wearing a suit?
Why are you wearing a cheetah?
Look, kids aren't allowed in court.
It's against the rules.
Why's your whole family here?
Why's Ethan here?
To support me. It's been hell for me.
It's been hell for you?
Come on.
We all just want
what's best for Maddy here.
We want what's best for Maddy.
Both of us, yeah.
We can't afford food
and you can afford a lawyer.
- Sorry. We should head in.
- Thanks, John.
Thanks, John.
I'll stay out here with her
since you decided to bring her.
- Come to me!
- Lovely to see you, Doreen.
Here's Schmariel.
Mommy will see you real soon, okay?
Okay.
[Alex] I love you!
[indistinct chatter]
[Silver] Case 549GRT, Boyd v. Russell.
Regarding emergency petition 5937-G
filed by Sean Boyd,
this is a motion for an ex parte order
to return Maddy Boyd, age 2,
to the care of her father Sean Boyd,
effective immediately.
[John] Yes, Your Honor.
[Jennings] Has an amendment
to the Family Plan been filed
and paperwork served?
It's been filed, and with your permission,
since we were unable to reach Ms. Russell,
we will serve her at this time.
- Granted.
- [John] So served.
[Jennings] On what grounds should an
ex parte of Maddy Boyd be considered?
[John] Your Honor, Ms. Russell
has failed to legal, legal, legal,
and she's legally legal, we ask the court
to legal, legal, legal.
- [Jennings] I see, and that's legal.
- [John] Very legal, legal, legal.
Ms. Russell.
- I'm sorry, judge, I don't understand...
- Commissioner.
I'm not a judge. I'm a court commissioner.
And I asked you what your plan is.
My plan?
To provide for Maddy, you removed her
from her home in the middle of the night,
have withheld and concealed
her whereabouts from Mr. Boyd
for more than 72 hours,
and have neither a home nor income.
What's your plan?
I'm figuring that out.
- Do you have a roof over her head?
- Yes.
We're currently at McMullin House.
That's the DV shelter.
Yes. We were referred there
by Social Services
after I told them how unsafe we were.
Your Honor, this is out of left field.
My client has never laid a hand
on this woman or his child.
[Jennings] Ms. Russell, did you file
a police report on the night you left?
No.
Do you have third-party witnesses
to confirm this allegation?
No.
[Jennings] Have you ever filed
a police report at any time
documenting the domestic abuse
of Mr. Boyd?
- No.
- May I throw some more legal at you?
Oh, yes, legal me.
[John] She failed to legal, legal,
which is legally legal per legal.
Ms. Russell, is this true?
You were in a car accident with Mr. Boyd's
child in the back seat unattended?
Yes. I was looking for her mermaid.
Mr. Boyd, the court grants your emergency
petition for an ex parte order
to return Maddy to your custody.
We will reconvene in seven days.
Adjourned.
[gavel bangs]
I'm sorry. What did you decide?
You have seven days
until the temporary custody hearing.
Use that time to obtain employment
and create a cogent plan
to provide for Maddy.
Maddy stays with Sean until then?
You can still see her with a third-party
neutral supervisor present.
- No...
- Ms. Russell, we're adjourned.
[Silver] Case 339GRF.
[Alex] Maddy, Maddy, Maddy, hey.
Hey, Maddy.
Hi, honey. Hi, honey.
- Daddy tell you where you're going?
- Home.
You're gonna go home,
but just for a week, okay?
And then we're going back
to the pony house.
And I'm gonna come and do bath time
with you every single night.
[Sean] Come on, Maddy.
Hey, how did it go?
Uh...
- Alex.
- [door closes]
Alex.
Are you okay?
Those fuckers.
How long did the court say he gets her?
- How long?
- A week.
Seven days?
Girl, that's not bad.
I heard so much worse than that.
Seven... You could do seven days.
That's like seven sleeps.
Do you get to see her?
[Alex] For bath time.
That's good, Mama.
They don't always do that, you know.
Court gave me no visitation rights
the first time I left Carl.
Calling me unfit... [scoffs]
Those suits can say whatever they want.
But you are a great mom.
- No. I never should have left.
- Yes, you should have.
He's a great dad.
He's a great dad and Maddy adores him.
They're home right now snuggling together.
And I'm alone in a shelter
I don't belong in.
- You're here because he abused you.
- He didn't abuse me.
He punched a wall beside my head,
and I didn't do anything about it,
and I didn't file a report,
and I didn't call the cops.
Fuck the police report.
Punching a wall next to you
is emotional abuse.
Before they bite, they bark.
Before they hit you, they hit near you.
Next time, it was gonna be your face,
and you know that.
[sighs]
I don't know what I know.
Okay, all right, stop it. Stop it.
Come here. Look at me. Hey, look at me.
Look at this.
You see that?
This motherfucker tried to strangle me.
You think it started out like that?
You think, on our first date,
he was all, "Pass the salt.
Someday I'm gonna strangle you, girl"?
No.
It grows, like mold.
I lost Maddy.
Okay. We're getting up. [clears throat]
Come on, you gotta get up now.
Come on. Let's go.
Oh, you think I don't know this carpet?
I've been on this carpet.
I've lost weeks of my life to this carpet.
And you gotta get up off this carpet,
Alex, and you gotta fight.
Come on, vámonos, let's go. Get up.
Get up.
Get up! I can't slap you, bitch, 'cause
we in a DV shelter, but you gotta get up!
[shouts] Get up!
- Fuck, okay. Okay.
- Get up!
'Cause seven days is not that long, okay?
You gotta get yourself a DV advocate.
File an account of abuse for the court.
You gotta get your ducks rowed up.
- But instead you're lying here.
- Yeah. Um...
They're just not gonna listen to me, so...
Look at you. "They're not gonna
listen." Whine, whine, whine. Get angry!
You need to dig in there
and pull that shit out, Mama!
What he did to you was fucked up!
And you better start getting
mad as shit about it.
[sighs] Okay, you know what?
I'm gonna fucking help you, all right?
I'm gonna...
Let's see. Tell me one thing
that you're angry about.
Just one thing that pisses you off.
- Um...
- Could be anything. Whatever you want.
- I appreciate what you're doing.
- No.
You gotta tell me
one thing you're angry about.
Anything.
- Quick.
- I'm, um...
- Regina pisses me off.
- Great. Who's Regina?
I cleaned her house on Fisher Island,
and she refused to pay me
and then I lost my job.
So you did the work
and she didn't pay you?
My God, I bet she lives
in a gorgeous-ass house too.
In her Lululemon pants.
With her KitchenAid standing mixer.
- That must make you really angry.
- Yeah.
Good. Get your coat.
Let's go. We're pulling up.
That bitch is gonna pay you.
Let's go.
[hip-hop music playing]
♪ Don't be mad ♪
♪ You so mad ♪
♪ Why you mad? ♪
Hey, there's an open house.
Let's go. Let's fucking go.
We can't go to an open house.
Why not? It's an open house.
The house is open.
- Regina's probably not here, Danielle.
- But her stuff is.
I mean, how much
did she fleece you for anyway?
37.50.
We're doing this for 37.50?
I could have Venmo'd you that.
- You're right. Let's go back.
- No.
No. Fuck that. It's the principle, okay?
You earned that pathetic 37.50.
We're gonna get you
37.50 worth of something.
Danielle, I don't steal.
Who said anything about stealing? Hmm?
How is this not prepping
to steal something?
What? Girl, we're just making space.
- Are you here for the open house?
- I'm gonna stop you right there, Jackie.
I think the real question is,
are you ready to make a sale?
["Girl From Ipanema"
playing faintly over speakers]
My wife and I are friends of Regina's
from spin class.
She said that we had to come by
and check out her designer nursery.
Gorgeous. Eco-friendly, heated floors.
May I have your names?
Taylor Swiftman.
Yasmina Jade Skye.
Oh, lovely.
Welcome. Make yourselves at home.
My associate's in there to answer
any questions and show you around.
Is Regina home?
She stepped out. I'll make sure
to let you know you say hi, Taylor.
Oh, my God.
What do these people do?
[Alex] No clue.
Well, damn, girl.
This house is clean. You're good.
- Thank you. Can we get out?
- Okay.
So you distract him, and I'll look around.
[woman] It's gorgeous.
Hello.
Do you have any questions?
Uh, it's a beautiful property.
Yes. So much light.
- These walls look solid.
- They're earthquake retro-fitted.
The roof goes over the whole house.
It doesn't cover the backyard,
if that's what you mean.
Well, honey,
it's lovely, but we're gonna have
to think it over, so...
Okay, so don't be mad.
But I saw something in her office
I had to take for you.
No. No.
- Her business card.
- No, that's not it.
That's just so we have her number,
so we can text her. The item's in my bag.
Take a look.
- You stole her dog.
- No.
She came to me, okay? She was
just chilling there in her kennel.
- "Hey, buddy." "Hello, friend."
- No. You can't steal the woman's dog.
We're not stealing her. Just showing her
the sights. We're gonna give her treats,
then I'll text that bitch
to bring 37.50 or we cut a paw.
Turn around. I'll throw him over the gate.
Him? Oh, no.
- Are you a boy? [laughs]
- It's not funny.
I was already in court once today.
I'm not getting in trouble for a dog.
- Okay, okay.
- Pull over, and I'll call this number.
I'll call her, and I'll say
I found your dog on the street.
- It's not funny.
- Sorry. It's funny.
Regina's on her way.
She's gonna be here in five minutes.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean
to ruin your dog fun.
I just can't get arrested right now.
- No. It's not that. I...
- [cell phone buzzing]
This is the second call.
The first was when I was in line.
Can you hold it?
- I don't want it in my hand.
- Yes.
- Can you press Ignore?
- Mm-hm.
Ignored. Done. Done.
It's just... His face, you know.
- Why don't you turn it off?
- This is what he does.
He says, "I love you. I wanna see my boy."
He's just gonna call again. Fuck it.
You know what the fucked-up part is?
I want him to see Max.
It's his son.
[cell phone buzzing]
Be right back.
The fuck are you calling me for, huh?
Oh, yeah?
Mr. Darcy.
Oh! Oh, thank God.
I don't know how he got out of his kennel.
How did you get out of your kennel?
Oh. Where did you find him?
Uh, the street. Yeah.
How did he get all the way over here?
Dogs run far.
But your legs are so short,
Mr. Darcy, yes.
- I'm glad I was able to help you.
- Oh, yes.
Thank you so much, truly.
You don't recognize me?
I'm sorry?
Uh... I'm your maid.
I cleaned your house.
Right. You, um...
You passed out in the nursery.
You stiffed me.
Oh, my...
Oh, my God. Is this...? What...?
What is this?
Did you steal my dog?
My slightly insane friend borrowed your
dog for a potential hostage situation.
But I'm returning him to you.
And here you go,
giving your dog back. I'm the hero.
Oh, my fucking God!
I am calling the police.
Call the police, yeah. Call the police,
and I'll tell them that you're a thief.
You owe me $37.50.
Unbelievable.
I do not negotiate with criminals.
Pay me what you owe me.
I am not paying you one dime.
You didn't even come back to finish.
No, I did. I came back to your house.
I was on my way back to your house.
I got into
a horrible car accident on Route 20.
And my daughter and I,
we've been living in that car.
So we became homeless.
And then,
because you're a cheap motherfucker,
I couldn't feed her, I couldn't house her,
and I couldn't get her off of the floor
of the ferry station, so then...
this morning,
the court took her away from me.
Yeah.
[emotional music playing]
You lost your dog for five minutes,
and I lost my daughter.
You can go fuck yourself.
[Alex] Keep on going down,
and it's on the right. The yellow one.
[Danielle] Gotcha.
Okay.
This is where you were living?
No wonder you were sweating out $37.50.
["Sound & Color" playing over speakers]
Five hours, 30 minutes, nine seconds.
Wow. Sweet.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
[Alex whistling]
Take it off.
Too bad I can't feel my nuts. Otherwise,
I'd give you a proper show, Alaska.
[giggling]
Yeah.
How many hours are you
supposed to be able to bike?
Not hours, miles. Forty.
With three months' worth of gear
on my bike.
You supposed to blow through
the whole syllabus before class starts?
Why else would they put it online?
It's nerd catnip.
Anything good?
A River Runs Through It. Makes me
wanna move to Montana immediately.
Good thing you are, then.
I'm not gone yet.
♪ With me, in my mind ♪
♪ Sound and color ♪
♪ With me, for my mind ♪
♪ And the ship shows me where to go ♪
♪ When I needn't speak ♪
♪ Now, far down
Now, far down ♪
♪ Now, far now
Far, far now ♪
[pensive music playing]
[cell phone buzzing]
What is it, man?
I mean, how many more times am I gonna
have to listen to that sad-ass pity party?
- Hey, Danielle, uh...
- Yeah?
This trailer wasn't always quite this bad.
I don't want you to think
this is what I chose for my daughter.
I think your daughter's lucky.
That's what I think. She's got you.
Look, I know
that bitch didn't cough it up today,
but you should feel
really good about yourself.
You should feel fucking proud of yourself.
You started fighting back.
You started standing up for yourself.
You were yelling, "Go fuck yourself"
in a random parking lot.
[both laughing]
Thank you for getting me off that carpet.
I got you.
You sure you ready to go back in there?
It's soon.
I promised Maddy I'd do bath time.
That's our thing.
Want me to come back?
- No. I'll walk.
- Okay, boo, don't miss curfew.
Oh, yup. I won't. Yes, ma'am. Thank you.
[lock clicks]
- Hi, Doreen.
- Hi.
- I'm here to do bath time with Maddy.
- We already did it.
It's 5:45.
Well, she got dirty on the playground,
and so we did it early.
Can I come in and tuck her in, then?
She's already down.
Sean did it before he went to work.
She's asleep at 5:45?
She had a cough, so we gave her
Robitussin to help her sleep. Okay?
No. She can't have cough syrup.
She's a baby. What do you mean?
I gave it to all my kids when
they were her age, and she's fine. Okay?
Have a good night.
[lock clicks]
["Let Go" playing]
♪ Brother's smile ♪
♪ Taking on its own ♪
♪ Identity ♪
♪ Only to then leave it behind ♪
♪ Foreign light in the afternoon ♪
[inaudible dialogue]
♪ Held by what-be-nots ♪
♪ Stay until remembered ♪
♪ Here ♪
♪ What's in a name? ♪
[cell phone pings]
[upbeat music playing]
[laughs]
Sorry.
[continues laughing]
Danielle!
Regina paid.
Denise, hey, where's Danielle?
- Let's meet in my office to speak.
- Uh...
- Did you kick her out? What happened?
- No.
Okay, well, she's gone.
All her stuff. She's gone.
I apologize, baby girl.
Can you go on down to apartment 23,
and I'll meet you there in a sec?
[woman] Let's go, guys.
Danielle checked out. She left.
What do you mean?
She left shelter, early this morning.
That's all I can say.
Okay. Where'd she go?
Uh...
Denise, he strangled her.
This happens.
They go back more often than not.
It takes most women seven tries
before they finally leave.
This was Danielle's third time here.
It took me five tries.
[emotional music playing]
[Alex] The armchair in the front lawn
of our trailer belongs to me.
And you can't tell under all the mold,
but it's pink velvet.
And when I moved in to Sean's,
it came with me.
And when I told him I was pregnant...
he sat me down on that chair...
and he brought me a cup of mint tea...
and he told me that he would
hold my hand every step of the way.
All tenderness.
But then...
when I told him
that I wasn't gonna get an abortion...
he took the chair...
and all the rest of my belongings,
and he threw them out into the rain.
And he screamed at me,
and he told me that I was a fucking whore.
And he said that
I was ruining his bike trip
and that I was also ruining his life.
And he also said that, uh...
he would never forgive me.
And he hasn't.
What the fuck are you thinking?
Fucking bitch!
Think for a fucking second, Alex!
For a fucking second!
And I've been afraid of him
every day since.
Anyway...
Just something I'm working on right now.
Notes?
["Down the Line" playing]
♪ I'm movin' on
I'm headed down the line ♪
♪ I'm gonna leave everything
In your little world behind ♪
♪ I'm movin' on
I'm headed down the line ♪
♪ Somebody broke your heart
I heard you say ♪
♪ Only thing to do is walk away ♪
♪ Somebody let you down, this I know ♪
♪ Only thing to do is let 'em go ♪
♪ 'Cause every thought you ever had
You're only gonna have again ♪
♪ And again and again ♪