[Sean breathing heavily]
Hey, no.
- I've got to get home to Maddy.
- No. Come back to bed. It's so early.
It's barely light out.
I wanna take the next ferry.
Can you drive me?
Can I cook you breakfast?
I'll wait in the car.
[pensive music playing]
[Sean] Hey.
Want coffee?
- You okay?
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah.
I'll wait here.
For what?
You. I was gonna
take you back to the hospital.
That's okay.
There's no way I'm letting you
deal with your mom on your own.
- Grab Maddy. We'll go as a family.
- Can we meet you at the hospital?
That makes no sense.
I'm here now. We could take one car.
I need a minute, Sean.
You don't owe that dork anything, Alex.
You slept at home, in your bed.
Can I just...?
You're awake.
Well, you said
you'd be home soon, ten hours ago.
So yes.
I'm sorry. I had a really weird night.
I saw Sean.
How hard is it to just send a text,
"Hey, I'm not coming home.
I'm gonna fuck my ex"?
Uh...
Something happened with my mom, actually.
She was manic, and she put her hand
through a window and severed a tendon.
She's in the hospital now.
And I'm accusing you
of being on a walk of shame.
- I'm really sorry.
- No, uh... I did sleep with Sean.
I'm not gonna lie to you, and I'm sorry.
Oh. Uh...
No, you don't have to apologize to me.
It's not like we're a couple.
It's not like you sat here yesterday
and told me you couldn't be with anyone.
I really can't. I meant what I said.
- Unless it's Sean.
- No.
What is it about this guy?
Fucking peach fuzz.
Okay, he can make a drink.
I can make a skyscraper,
but you're going back to him.
I'm not, though.
No, I'm not going back to Sean.
You are.
- No, I'm not.
- Of course you are.
You were hurt, and you went to him.
You cried on him.
I just provided daycare.
That's really not what happened, Nate.
That's not what happened.
I don't wanna watch your kid for you
while you fuck Sean.
So...
I'm gonna have to ask you to move out.
I'm not trying to be a dick.
I care about you.
I just can't do a front-row seat.
No.
I understand.
I'm gonna get Maddy,
and we'll get out of here.
- Alex.
- Yeah?
Um, keep the car.
No. I mean...
You need a car, so keep the car.
Thank you for being so kind.
That's me.
Mr. Kind.
[pensive music playing]
- [Alex] Schmariel?
- [Maddy] Check.
- Mommy's stuff?
- Check.
- Grammy's stuff?
Kisses.
Check.
[Paula] What you mean to do
and what you intend to do
are not the same thing!
I cannot be held accountable
for someone else's false intention!
Miss Langley,
whatever you say can and will be...
[Paula] Oh, my God! You're reading me
my rights over a motherfucking scratch!
- Excuse me, what's happening here?
- Get that child out of here!
- [Sean] Okay. I'll take her outside.
- Get her out of here! I can't do her.
- Uh, I'm sorry, who are you? Sorry.
- She's a fucking bitch.
I'm the DCR, Designated Crisis Responder.
It might be best if you waited outside.
This is about intent! Intent! Intent!
She's my daughter, she'll tell you!
All I need is my good weed
and a fucking hairbrush.
I'll be right with you.
[groans]
All right, Miss Langley,
I need to ask you a couple of questions.
Are you taking any current medication?
Is she under arrest?
No, no,
the tenant is not pressing charges.
- Why were you reading her her rights?
- I'm a court-appointed DCR.
I was evaluating whether or not
your mother meets the criteria
to be placed
on an involuntary hold or not.
You mean, commit her?
She had a severe manic episode.
She's still symptomatic.
Pressured speech,
delusions, irrational thought.
She told me she thought she owned
the house that she was breaking into.
Oh, she does, or she did.
Ah, well, she also told me
that she's the goddess Aphrodite
and she fucks the sun.
She just says that stuff.
Well, your mother
has refused voluntary treatment,
so I am filing a petition to detain her.
She's a danger to herself and to others.
She would never hurt anybody.
She's harmless.
Well, she hurt herself, seriously.
Unless you wish
to provide collateral information
and take responsibility for her,
then this is just what we have to do.
What's collateral information?
You tell the courts why
you think she's a good-faith volunteer.
You give examples of things she's done
that would make you believe
that she would attend
an outpatient program
and take her prescribed medications
while in your care.
In my care?
[Renee] We can discharge her to you,
if you're prepared
to give that collateral.
Is that something you're prepared to do?
I have work today. And a 3-year-old.
She scared me last night.
There is an evaluation
and treatment center in Port Orchard.
- How long would she be there?
- Usually 14 days, sometimes 30.
Do I tell her, or do you?
Generally, we don't inform the patient
until it's actually happening.
More soon.
[pensive music playing]
[Paula] You gotta get me out of here
and away from that woman
trying to lock me up.
Your father tried to lock me up.
Did you tell them I'll take the medicine?
Because I'll take the medicine.
I'm not saying I won't.
I just wanna choose the medicine.
Purple Kush. And I'll go to a life coach.
They're gonna keep you in here
a little longer, keep an eye on your hand.
[Paula] Wow. Just not past dinner, okay?
Because I saw the menu, it's meatloaf.
Whatever happened to Meat Loaf?
The singer.
♪ Paradise by the dashboard light ♪
[Alex] I'm worried about you, Mom.
[Paula] Baby, I just
caught a wave I couldn't handle.
Took me under.
Threw me and my board around.
But I'm like the tide, I roll back in.
Look at me. Surf's up.
- You did that to your own hand.
- Why are you so blue? It's my hand.
Plus, I can paint with this hand.
That's my truth.
Baby. They don't know, baby.
[Alex] What don't they know?
[scoffs]
That the sun bends towards me.
That I contain the sun in here.
[Maddy laughing]
Maddy!
Hi, baby girl. How are you?
- You didn't tell me you had people here.
- They just got here.
We just...
We swung by uninvited, such a cliché.
I hope you don't mind
that I brought these.
No.
[sighs]
Sorry to hear about your mom. You okay?
Sounds like you saw her
at a ten out of ten.
- Well, she's got a DCR now. That's good.
- Yeah.
- Maybe she'll get the help she needs.
- All right, say goodbye to Grandpa.
[Maddy] Bye, Grandpa.
Okay, guess that's my cue.
Bye-bye, honey bee.
- Let me know how it goes tomorrow.
- I will. Thank you.
And we will be praying for your mom, Alex.
There's decades' worth of blood, sweat,
and popped blisters on those things,
- so take care of them.
- Gross. Will do.
You told him about my mom?
I had to. He was worried
I didn't show up this morning.
And why do you have his tools?
I'll tell you later. Come here.
Should we give Mommy her surprise? Yeah?
[emotional music playing]
You ready?
Surprise! We made dinner.
Show her, Mad.
- Did you write this?
- All by herself, she wrote that.
- M-O-M-M-Y.
- And you did that all by yourself?
Chili. Extra bland
and spice free, per the chef's request.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Hey. Come to bed.
I'm good out here.
[Sean] It's not like I'm gonna make a move
on you, Alex, we'll just sleep.
I like the couch. Good boundaries.
Well, if you're back, be back.
I'm not back, Sean. I left for a reason.
I'm just staying here
until I get a place for me and Maddy.
- Shouldn't be too long, I've been saving.
- Copy that, commander.
I'm quitting. That's why
Hank was dropping by with his tools.
- Quitting what?
- Bartending. I will become a carpenter.
Hank knows this guy Dwight
that's agreed to take me on.
- To become a carpenter?
- Yeah. I've been thinking about it a lot.
Talking about it in meetings,
bartending's rough on my sobriety.
I'm up all night,
turning down shots, getting no sleep.
Besides, I like working with my hands.
I like being outside.
Why are you saying nothing?
I'm just surprised.
That I don't wanna be
a piece of shit my whole life?
[Alex] I didn't say that.
It's a good gig once you get started.
Once you're done apprenticing,
I'll be bringing home 25 an hour
by the time Maddy's in the first grade.
That's really great, Sean.
It's gonna be good for Maddy.
It'll be good for all three of us.
Please don't factor me in.
Come to bed.
No.
No. I have three cleans tomorrow.
I have to see my mom during lunch,
and I need my sleep.
All right.
Guess I'll sleep alone, then.
Maybe naked.
Get the light, please.
Good morning, Miss Maddy.
Wanna have some fun?
Now grab some maracas,
and we're ready to rock.
Bye, Mommy.
[pensive music playing]
[Regina whispering] Alex.
Over here.
I'm on the Ring, the doorbell camera.
Can you come to the garage?
Regina?
Shh.
[sighs, then groans]
[whispering] God, I have to pee so badly.
- Can you please watch him?
- Oh. Baby Leo's here?
Shh!
Little fucker only sleeps in the car.
I have been doing loops
around Whole Foods.
I'm gonna pee my pants.
Hi, sweetheart.
Why don't you transfer him to the crib?
That's not a thing. He doesn't transfer.
If I so much as breathe on him...
his little eyes rip open
and he starts screaming like a banshee.
Have you tried doing it to music?
Worked great for Maddy. Can I try?
No, no, no. You're kidding.
I'm gonna try it, okay?
[mellow classical music playing]
[Regina] No...
We're okay so far. Sorry.
Regina?
[Regina sobbing]
I can't do this.
He's been here four days,
and I can't do this.
I'm having hallucinations.
I thought my mug was upside down
this morning.
I turned it right side up,
and I dumped coffee all over myself.
And I keep smelling this horrible smell.
It smells like rotten fruit.
It turns out it's me.
I have body odor!
A week ago, I was eating
arugula salad in my corner office!
You just need a nap.
I'm not in college.
I can't nap.
You've gotta nap when the baby's down.
It's the only way.
Maybe just...
Maybe just ten minutes.
Yes.
Go. It's gonna be okay.
[mellow pop music playing]
[cell phone ringing]
- Hello?
- [man over phone] Hi, is this Alex?
- Hi, yes.
- This is Steve Till.
I'm the chair of the creative writing
program in Missoula. I got your message.
- Thank you so much for returning my call.
- Yeah, sure.
So departmental scholarships
are for the forthcoming academic year.
I'm afraid the one we offered you
four years ago is no longer available.
Okay. Figured I'd just check.
We can consider you for this academic year
if you reapply.
The committee's reading right now.
How much is the application fee?
No, there's no fee to re-apply.
You'd have to submit
an updated writing sample.
Do you have anything new?
Yes. I think so, yes.
Great. Upload it with your application,
and send me the e-mail confirmation.
Does it have to be typed?
["Now I'm In It" playing]
♪ Took me so long ♪
♪ To fall ♪
♪ Now I'm in it ♪
[toilet flushing]
- Where's Leo?
- He's asleep.
I feel like an entirely different person.
I didn't sleep. I, um...
I died, briefly.
Thank you.
No problem, and I'm almost done.
Just gonna do your master.
I wanted to ask. Did you and your daughter
ever find a place to live?
- We did, yeah, thank you.
- Good.
I'm sorry I was rude when you asked
if you could be my nanny.
- I shouldn't have asked.
- No, probably not. I mean, read the room.
I have OCD, attachment disorder.
I am an unlikely candidate
for an impulsive
and ill-thought-out childcare plan.
But you weren't asking for yourself.
You were asking for your daughter.
[Leo crying]
Fuck. I'll see you next week.
Hi, I'm here to see Paula Langley.
Oh, thank God.
You've gotta get me out of here.
This is hell.
This place is hell.
They won't let me use my phone
until phone time.
And they're saying that I have to stay
14 days. Fourteen days.
And I've gotta take xeno-pan
and panda-land and God knows what else.
Honey, they've made a mistake.
You have got to get me out of here.
I don't think I can, Mom.
It's court-mandated.
No, but, baby, you don't understand.
These people are really crazy.
They're crazy, okay. Like, you know,
mentally ill. I'm funny mentally ill.
I run hot, you know. I mean, you know,
I feel things. But these people scare me.
[man] I know.
This guy Ray, okay, honey,
you know what he did?
Chewed his fucking toe off.
Chewed his toe off. I mean, what the fuck?
Well, while you're here,
I guess, you know...
try to make the best of it.
And who knows, maybe
some medication isn't the worst thing.
Oh, my God.
What?
You think I belong here, don't you?
Did you help put me here?
No, Mom, I didn't. The court decided that.
But you didn't say anything
to stop them, did you?
- Mom.
- What did I ever do to you
- that you would do this to me?
- Hey, Mom.
No.
You showed up at my door
with your toddler,
crying because you were homeless,
and you had no place to be.
And I let you stay with me in my tiny RV.
I let you ruin my marriage
with my new husband...
because that's what you do,
when you love someone.
- I love you, Mom.
- No.
Baby, I would...
I would give you the skin off my bones.
I would drink turpentine...
before I would let a bunch of doctors
do this to you.
Mom.
Hey, hey, Mom, Mom, we have 23 minutes.
Can I please just talk to you? I love you.
I love you, and Maddy loves you.
So many people.
Please get this bitch out of here.
Just get this bitch out of here.
- Mother. Mom.
- No!
You need to go. No, sorry. Right now.
- Are you fucking kidding me? Mom!
- [door locks]
Hey, Yolanda.
Just swapping out a filter
for 351 Armstrong.
- Swapping out a filter, she says.
- Okay.
- Okay. Is that a problem?
- Of course not. Go ahead.
Help yourself to all my filters.
I'm having a really shitty day. So is
there something that you wanna say to me?
Just had a call from my clients
over at 19 Glastonbury.
She canceled last-minute last week,
which isn't like her.
And then, this week,
she didn't schedule at all.
So being the good businesswoman
that I am, I called her
and asked her,
why is she ghosting Value Maids
after five years of loyal service?
You know what she said?
I got stood up,
and you weren't gonna pay me.
You stole business from me.
Took money directly from my pocket.
I wasn't gonna be able
to pay for daycare, Yolanda.
- I told you I needed another shift.
- And I told you that I expected loyalty.
You're fired.
Leave your ferry pass. Get out!
And if I hear you contacting
a single one of my clients,
I will track you down, beat your ass
and take you to court. You hear me?
- Do you hear me?
- Yes.
Can I get my last paycheck?
Not out yet.
Can I leave you my address
for when it is out?
You can go fuck yourself.
[pensive music playing]
[children shouting]
Oh, Miss Russell, your invoice.
I sent it home with Maddy's backpack
last week, but I don't think you saw it.
- I missed it. Thank you.
- Yeah.
There's WCCC paperwork in there too.
We need signatures from your employer.
You got it.
Also, it was ice cream day,
and we didn't want Maddy to go without.
We took it out of the petty cash.
- Oh, thank you. How much do I owe you?
- It's $6.
For ice cream?
Two scoops, and each kid
got three toppings.
- Awesome.
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
- Okay.
Fuck!
Uh, hi, I'm sorry,
you don't happen to have $3
that I could bum off of you for gas?
I can't get home. Sorry.
Um...
- Here.
- Thank you.
All right. Go.
No more cartoons.
Let's go on a hike like old times,
what do you say?
- We're going on a...
- Bear hunt.
- We're gonna catch a...
- Big one.
What a beautiful day.
- We're not scared.
- Oh, no, a forest.
- A forest.
- A big, dark forest.
Oh, no. What?
- We can't go over it.
- We can't go under it.
- [Maddy laughing]
- We're going on a...
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna get you.
Let's jump over that one.
You sure can. See any fairies?
So...
[gentle music playing]
- [Alex] Rock.
- Rocks.
[Alex] Here. Right here?
[vehicle approaching]
[car door opens, then closes]
[door opens]
- [Alex] Hey.
- Hey.
- I saved you some ziti. Are you hungry?
- Yes.
So how was carpentry 101?
Pretty cool, actually.
Yeah, Dwight's a cool guy.
He's got a kid Maddy's age.
Hank wasn't kidding
when he said he'd be tough on me.
I literally can't feel my fingers
or my ass right now.
- So it was good.
- Yeah, yeah.
Good.
I got fired today.
- You?
- Yeah.
Oh, my.
Well, you've gotta let me have this.
What did you do?
I stole a shift,
and then I pocketed the cash.
You embezzled? Very juicy.
[Sean laughing]
- You've been saving up, right?
- Yeah.
You have enough until you get
something else?
I think so, yeah.
I was thinking, I'm actually gonna
try to get my own cleaning clients
because I still have my supplies
and my car,
- I can probably get a vacuum secondhand.
- Makes sense.
I just have to figure out daycare
because Yolanda took my ferry pass.
Oh, shit. That's goodbye, Island Friends.
- We can't afford ferry trips every day.
- I know, but she loves it.
- She loves being with you more.
- Yeah.
But I can't clean houses full-time
and watch Maddy.
Well, I'm with Dwight
Monday through Friday,
so who else is gonna watch her?
I need to work, Sean. So I can make
my own money so that I can be independent.
Okay.
Yeah.
Um...
Could you clean on the weekends?
I'll watch Maddy.
That's not gonna be enough money
with you apprenticing all week.
- I could pick up some shifts at the bar.
- And watch Maddy all day?
- You're gonna be exhausted.
- Would you relax?
It's fine.
Worst-case scenario,
- Hank and Sharlene can watch Maddy.
- No.
Hank cannot watch Maddy.
That's not an option.
- What is with you and your dad?
- He's not a good guy.
He got me a job.
He's really sweet with Maddy.
He takes me to meetings.
I need you to listen to me, okay?
Just trust me and promise me
that he won't be near Maddy.
Okay. No Hank.
We'll figure it out ourselves.
I think we can.
Okay.
[emotional music playing]
I love these flowers.
[Alex] You look good, Mom.
I brought you a lipstick.
I don't care if you don't talk back.
I'm still gonna come every day
that Sean has Maddy.
- [Alex] We're going on a...
- Bear hunt.
- We're gonna catch a...
- Big one.
She's been asking about you.
- We're going on a...
- Bear hunt.
[Alex] They said that she's
artistically gifted, in her preschool.
And I was like, "Yeah, of course."
She's been painting with my mom
since birth.
Blink if you hear me.
Mom.
- [Alex] We're going on a...
- [Maddy] Bear hunt.
- [Alex] We're gonna catch a...
- [Maddy] Big one.
I'll get you.
- Uh-oh, what do you see?
- Trees.
Can I tell you a secret?
I applied to the writing program
in Missoula.
It's a long shot because my writing sample
is about cleaning toilets.
And what if I did get in?
What if we moved there when you get out?
You could paint and hang out with Maddy.
Float down that river
with some cold beers.
When you get better,
there's so much light waiting for you.
And so much love.
[footsteps approaching]
Hey.
- I made you a grilled cheese.
- Thanks.
Are you too tired to do this?
[chuckles]
- I don't need to be awake to bartend.
- So, um...
My phone's almost out of minutes,
and we're out of milk and snacks.
- I have a coupon, but...
- How much?
Uh...
Well, I also need money
for gas, so, like, $50.
Uh, do we have to keep your phone on?
Can we just share mine?
I've put my number on the cleaning ads.
- People need to be able to call me.
- Yeah, but nobody is.
I mean... Right?
I'm trying.
Nobody wants weekend cleans.
Everybody wants weekdays and referrals.
Well, I'll have cash tonight,
and we'll figure it out. Okay?
[vehicle approaching]
Fuck.
What?
- Nah...
- What?
Your dad's here.
Stay here, okay?
[Hank] Hey, stranger.
You wanna give me a hand?
What's all this?
Oh, this is just some of Alex's stuff
from the apartment with the black mold.
I told her I'd go back for it
with my truck,
and I do what I say I'm going to do.
[Sean] Should have called first, Hank.
[Hank] Right.
Guilty.
Came to get eyes on you too.
Drinking again?
No.
- Haven't seen you in any of the meetings.
- I've been working a lot.
- I thought we got you out of bartending.
- I'm doing both for a while now.
Well, there's a meeting at the VFW
in half an hour, so...
- Come on, we can go together.
- No, thanks.
I've been where you're at before.
But you can't do it alone.
Okay, you've got to...
You've got to tap into something stronger.
You can't come by here anymore.
Who says? You?
Or her?
Her.
But I'm with her.
Mm.
Is she with you?
Because you're not
going to meetings any more,
she's got you working two jobs.
Doesn't seem like it.
You done?
You need to get yourself to a meeting.
Well, that was fun.
Being an asshole to somebody
without knowing why.
[vehicle pulling away]
Do you wanna wait up for me?
All right, I'll hurry back.
I'm gonna do some fucking
lightning-speed bartending.
Woo-hoo!
We're going on a...
Bear hunt.
We're gonna catch a...
Oh, look, you found one. See it?
[cell phone ringing]
- Hello?
- Where the hell are you?
Uh, who is this?
Regina.
Some random girl is here from Value Maids.
I got your number from her. Where are you?
I got fired.
So?
I'm not loyal.
I am home. With a newborn.
And this woman is totally incompetent.
How soon can you be here?
I have Maddy today.
How about tomorrow?
I can't afford the ferry.
I can offer you three shifts a week.
Twenty dollars an hour,
15 hours guaranteed.
You can clean
and help me take care of Leo.
I will provide a ferry pass and supplies.
How's that?
Yes, yes, yes.
Hello?
[call drops]
- Hello?
- Regina?
Okay, Mad.
We're going on a bear hunt.
We're going to get some phone minutes.
[Alex] Yes, I'll be there tomorrow. Yes.
What number is this?
This is Alex, sorry, I'm at a payphone.
My phone ran out of minutes.
What?
I'm at a payphone,
but you can e-mail me the ferry pass
and I can print it out at the library.
What's your e-mail?
Hi, Magda, how's it going?
Sign in here?
Wait here, please.
Miss Langley's daughter is here. Okay.
- Miss Langley's daughter?
- [Alex] Hiya.
We dropped the hold on your mother.
She was discharged at 1:45 today.
- What do you mean?
- The DCR determined
she no longer met the criteria
to be detained.
The DCR can just change their mind?
If collateral information
is given from immediate family.
What family? I'm her only family.
A Basil Desmond.
He gave collateral
and she was discharged into his care.
How the fuck did Basil know she was here?
Was she allowed to call him?
It's not a prison, Miss Russell.
[Sean] Maybe it's good.
You've been responsible for your mom
your entire life.
If she wants to run off with Basil,
what can you do?
I don't feel like doing this.
- I'll just drop you guys off and go home.
- No. Everyone wants to see you.
Tania was your best friend for years.
- I should have given collateral.
- Hey, don't beat yourself up.
She's not your child.
You can't force her to do anything.
And you got a job today.
Island Friends agreed
to let Maddy come part-time
so I can drop her off,
clean Regina's and then pick her back up.
Yeah, see? You rocked it.
For Maddy.
[indistinct chatter]
Can I have your attention, please?
I'm gonna say a few words about Ethan.
[all clamoring]
The man who has done nothing right
since I met him in the second grade.
Including second grade itself,
which he repeated twice.
- Yeah, true story.
- [Ethan] Dick.
Nineteen years I've known this guy.
I thought I knew
what his life would look like,
and I thought I knew exactly who he was.
But what I didn't know
was the power of Tania.
- Thank you.
- [crowd applauding]
Thank you.
Yeah. She smoothed his rough edges.
You encouraged him to get an education.
Got him to stop wearing
those lime-green Crocs.
[all laughing]
- Yes.
- [Sean] Well done.
You saw what he could be.
Helped him get there.
So let's all raise a glass to Ethan...
who is doing what we all told him to do
from day one:
Marry this magnificent woman.
Cheers.
[all cheering]
[rock music playing over speakers]
- That was really great.
- Thanks.
You can relax.
Hey, come here.
That's it, come here, sweetie.
Hey. You.
Thanks for coming.
I wasn't sure you would.
Me neither, but then I was like,
"There's probably gonna be free food..."
Yeah.
Congratulations.
I love that you did it at City Hall.
Very cool.
Yeah, with the reception in the bar
I've worked in for six years.
Very romantic.
- Amazing.
- Yeah...
Yeah, we're trying to save money.
I'm, uh...
pregnant.
- Oh, my God, wow!
- Yeah.
Congratulations!
That's amazing. Wow.
Yeah. [laughs]
So you and Sean are back on?
Oh, no. Uh...
No, I'm just staying there
for a little bit.
Oh. Does he know that?
He's been saying the opposite to Ethan.
[Alex] Um...
Um...
Can I use your printer?
I need to print my ferry pass.
At my wedding?
Yep. Sorry, my phone's out of minutes.
Yeah, my iPad's behind the bar.
[laughs]
What are you smiling about?
I...
I got a scholarship to Missoula,
the same as four years ago,
I just found out.
No fucking way.
That's awesome!
Oh, my God.
What's awesome?
Well, this smarty-pants here
just got a scholarship to Missoula, again.
[Ethan] Yeah, get it.
When did you apply?
I reapplied a few weeks ago. It was free.
Why didn't you tell me?
Wasn't anything to tell. I literally
just found out 30 seconds ago.
You didn't think
taking my daughter to Montana
was something that we should discuss?
Um...
Hmm?
[pensive music playing]
I don't know why you're acting this way.
How else should I react?
You could be happy for me?
I'm working two jobs, busting my ass
to be a better person for you.
For absolutely no reason.
You had a getaway car
parked outside the entire time.
- That's not what this is.
- Oh, what am I doing any of this for?
I really don't even...
Do you have any idea
how hard it is not to fucking drink!
You're gonna wake up Maddy.
I thought we were building something
together, as a family.
It's a writing program, Sean.
- This has nothing to do with you.
- It has nothing to do with me?
Is Nate going with you?
- [laughs] No. No.
- You say that like I should know better.
But I don't know shit.
I don't know what you're applying to,
I don't know what your plan is without me.
This whole thing is fucking fucked!
Get in the car!
[pensive music playing]
[engine revving]
[tires screeching,
then vehicle pulling away]
[whispering]
The chair of the English Department
said my stories were really good.
Sean.
Where's my car?
Nate's car.
What?
[clears throat]
- What are you talking about?
- I gave it back to the prick.
I'm sick of looking at another man's car
in my driveway.
You didn't do that. You didn't do that.
- You gave it back to him?
- Yeah.
No. No.
- Look, if he wants to do charity work...
- No, no!
- ...he could donate it to the Red Cross.
- Sean! That's my car!
That is my life. That is my only way
for me to leave here!
Sean, that is the only way
- for me to do anything...
- [yelling] I'm late for work!
[engine starting]
[vehicle pulling away]
[sobbing] I'm so stupid.
I'm so stupid.
[Alex] We're going on a...
Bear hunt.
We're going on a...
We're going to catch a...
[Maddy] Big one.
Big one.
We're going on a...
Bear hunt.
Come on, Maddy.
[ominous music playing]
["The Last Man On Earth" playing]
♪ Who are you to ask for anything more? ♪
♪ Do you wait for your dancing lessons ♪
♪ To be sent from God? ♪
♪ You'd like his light to shine on you ♪
♪ You've really missed a trick
When it comes to love ♪
♪ Always seeking what you don't have ♪
♪ Like what you do ain't enough ♪
♪ You'd like a light to shine on you ♪