(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
(COME DOWN PLAYING)
You sure Mama
won't notice we're gone?
Better hope not.
(COME DOWN CONTINUES PLAYING)
(GIRLS LAUGHING)
(SNOWFALL PLAYING ON STEREO)
-(GASPS)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
(CONTINUES RINGING)
(SIGHS)
Preaker.
Sure. Bye.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Mmm-hmm?
-Am I in trouble?
-Always.
But you don't need me
to tell you that.
Wind Gap. What's it like?
Oh. Okay, well...
It's at the bottom of Missouri,
boot heel.
Spittin' distance from Tennessee.
I know where it is.
I asked what it's like.
Small. Population's held
at 2,000 for years.
Only real industry is hog butchering,
So you got your old money
and your trash.
Mmm-hmm. Which one are you?
-Trash. From old money.
-(CHUCKLES)
What the hell's goin' on?
In Wind Gap, or...?
Your mom's still there,
right, Preaker?
Mom? Yeah.
Step-dad. They had a kid.
Have. I don't really know her.
-But you talk to 'em?
-Not if I can help it.
Well, read the wires then.
Jesus Christ, there was a murder there
last August.
Little girl got strangled.
I didn't know.
Well, then you also don't know
that another one's missing now.
Might be a serial.
So, get your ass down
to that heel or whatever,
and get me a story. Now. Today.
We have murders here, Curry,
so I don't see
why I gotta go to Wind Gap.
Because nobody else is covering it.
Do you remember that piece
in the Tribune last year?
Guy who wrote about a Killing
in his hometown?
It made an impact,
because it was personal.
People give a shit
when you give a shit.
I'm not gonna win a Pulitzer
off of Wind Gap.
You're not winning a Pulitzer
‘cause you're only half-good
at writing.
-This could change that.
-(SIGHS)
And I'm your boss.
So, goodbye.
All right, look, if you can't,
you can't, but it might be good.
You know,
flush some things out,
get you back on your feet.
-And it's a good story.
-Yeah.
Could be a damn good story
if you do it right.
No pressure, right?
Life is pressure.
Grow up.
Get the hell out of here.
(SIGHS)
(ZIPS BAG)
(POURING LIQUID)
-(ENGINE STARTING)
-(I CAN'T QUIT YOU BABY PLAYING)
(MUSIC STOPS)
(GUNSHOT)
BOY 1: Get out!
BOY 2: Come on.
(FLIES BUZZING)
Come on!
-(BOYS CHATTERING)
-(BOTTLES CLINKING)
(CAMILLE BREATHING HEAVILY)
(MOANING)
(SMALL TOWN HEROES
PLAYING ON RADIO)
Hi, Betty.
(ENGINE STOPS)
RECEPTIONIST:
That was Natalie's favorite color.
Oh.
Well, actually,
her folks said it was black,
but that just seemed too grim.
So, her second favorite.
Little girls, first pink,
and then it's purple, purple, purple.
My two looked like grapes on legs
until they were 11 or so.
It's a terrible thing.
Practically the whole town
is out there, searching the woods.
Chief Vickery, he set it up.
You have children?
-No.
-Well, I hate to say it,
but right now, that's a blessing.
I won't even let mine out of the house
to get the mail, even.
You can't imagine.
My girls, every night,
gettin' in bed with us.
My husband, usually,
he wouldn't allow that,
but now, not one of us
is gettin' a good night's sleep,
but at least we know they're safe.
(BELLS JINGLING)
Chief Vickery?
Well, the thing is,
I have no intention
of letting this thing get out, so.
Yeah, I understand.
This isn't going to be
a exploitative piece,
more like a think piece
on how something like this
can affect a town.
If it makes you feel better,
I'm from here.
Just up off Bluebird Circle.
What's your name?
Camille Preaker.
My mom is Adora Crellin.
She married out of her maiden name
about 30 years ago, to Alan...
Crellin. Sure, okay.
You're the...
-You moved away.
-Yeah.
Amma, she's your half-sister.
Yeah.
Damn.
Jesus. Hot as hell in here, isn't it?
-My kids give me that.
-Oh. Yeah, sorry.
No, it's all right. Stress relief.
Because of this case?
Look, I just can't have you here,
Ms. Preaker.
You know,
this story gets out in St. Louis,
suddenly that's all
Wind Gap's known for.
We're already "the hog killers."
Some publicity could help,
get you some information.
It's worked in other cases.
I have a right to be here,
and I will let you do your job
if you let me do mine.
Fine.
I got no comment.
On Natalie Keene, fair enough.
But what about the other girl?
Ann Nash.
I can ask around
and I can get the local version,
or you can have a say
in what gets out.
CAMILLE: First girl,
Ann, found last August,
strangled with a clothes line
and dumped in Falls Creek.
Some hunters found her.
That's all Vickery said? No leads?
Well, I don't think he has any.
It's just the way he was...
He was defensive.
Not like he was hiding something,
more like he was pissed off
that he wasn't.
-Theory.
-(KNOCKING ON WINDOW)
Jesus, Curry, I just got here.
Well, you have the police.
Get me some local stuff.
I need facts and color.
Fine. I will write you
a fuckin' rainbow.
You know what I mean.
If you think this place
has some small town charm...
Well, give me local bleak,
then, kiddo,
paint a goddamn picture.
I'm goin' out to join
the search party now.
Hopefully, we'll turn up
a dead little girl.
Go get 'em.
You lookin' for the search?
-Yeah.
-That way.
Thanks.
Are you... You're...
That reporter, right? From St. Louis?
Well, that was fast.
Gotta hand it to Wind Gap,
you guys do gossip like nobody else.
That's ‘cause this place
is so totally dead.
(LAUGHS)
"Dead."
That's awful.
Anyway, better get goin'
if you want to catch up.
Thanks.
-(TRAIN WHISTLE BLOWING)
-(GIRLS LAUGHING)
BOY: Camille!
RICHARD: Did you see something?
No.
You with the search?
In a way.
-Detective Willis.
-Ah.
You're not from here, huh?
No. You?
Used to be.
I'm up in St. Louis now.
I'm with the Chronicle.
A reporter. Great.
JACKIE: Camille Preaker!
-(JACKIE LAUGHING)
-Jackie O'Neill.
Detective.
JACKIE: Oh, Lord.
I see you met our new detective.
I'd like to take him home
and turn him into pound cake.
Cover him in chocolate.
He's single, by the way.
Oh, hey, settle down.
(LAUGHING) Aww!
Come here. Look at you.
Your mama didn't say
that you were in town.
'Course, she's not
talkin' to me right now.
I disappointed her again.
Probably forgot to send her
a card or something, you know.
-You know how that goes!
-I haven't seen her yet.
I'm gonna head over there after this.
Ah, she's gonna be thrilled.
Baby girl, look at you.
What about you, are you well?
You know, well as I can be.
Pretty grim around here.
I'm in charge of refreshments
for the guys.
It's the least I can do.
You want a sweet tea?
I got sweet tea
with a little bit of a kick in it.
No one should face all this
without a little kick.
I'm fine. I'm on the job.
You still workin' for that newspaper?
Yeah, that's why I'm here, actually.
I'm writing a story.
Oh.
Yeah, those girls...
I see you, when you were the same age.
And it just makes me so sad.
So much has gone wrong.
I just can't make sense of it all.
You mind if I quote you on that?
Yeah, I suppose so.
If you think anyone
would be interested.
You are nothing
if not interesting, Jackie.
(BOTH LAUGH)
-I'm glad you're home.
-Mmm.
We'll see.
Beauty, beauty, beauty.
CAMILLE: Preacher.
PREACHER: My Lord, Camille Preaker.
It has been a long time, girl.
CAMILLE: Yeah, it has.
(ENGINE STARTING)
(I CAN'T QUIT YOU BABY
PLAYING ON RADIO)
(COME DOWN PLAYING)
(BEEPING)
MARIAN: Mama said
she saw a ghost once.
YOUNG CAMILLE:
Mama says a lot of things.
You don't believe her?
MARIAN: I don't know.
I'm not scared of them ghosts.
Are you?
YOUNG CAMILLE: It's stupid
lo be scared of stuff that's not real.
MARIAN: What if, after you die,
part of you goes to heaven,
but part of you stays here?
Just to look after stuff, you know?
See how things turn out
for you, for Mama?
YOUNG CAMILLE: Stop that.
That kind of talk is for quitters.
Are you a quitter?
-No.
-Say it.
I'm not a quitter.
Why are you mad at me?
ADORA: Camille?
Goodness. Is something the matter?
No, Mama, not at all.
I'm just in town on business.
Business. I didn't expect you.
My house is not up to par
for visitors, I'm afraid.
Looks just fine.
Come on inside. Goodness.
Can I get you something to drink?
Alan and I are having amaretto sours.
I'll just have
what you're having, thanks.
We're in back.
It's nice and cool now
with the breeze.
(DIETRO CASA PLAYING ON STEREO)
Where are you stayin'?
Well, it's funny you should ask.
I was hoping that I could
stay here for a few days.
I just wish you'd phoned.
I would have known, had dinner ready.
Go say hello to Alan.
-Alan? Camille's here.
-ALAN: Hmm?
-Who?
(CAMILLE SCOFFS)
Camille.
-Hi.
-Oh, hello, there!
Adora didn't say you were comin'.
Oh, she didn't know. I'm sorry to...
Just drop in like this.
My editor sent me down
last minute, so...
Your editor.
-Did he?
-Yeah, I'm here about Natalie Keene,
and that other little girl, Ann Nash.
ADORA: To write a story?
Yes, Mama. It's a newspaper.
Camille, I just don't understand
why a young woman like you
would want to even
dwell on such things.
Well, it could be an important story,
and being from here...
I knew those children.
I'm having a very hard time,
as you can imagine.
And to... To write about it?
"Wind Gap Murders its Children."
Is that what you want people to think?
Well, it can be really helpful
to get information out.
People come forward...
I just can't have
that kind of talk around me.
Hurt children. Just...
Don't tell me what you're doing,
what you know.
While you're here, I'll just pretend
you're on summer break.
(FOOTSTEPS PASSING UPSTAIRS)
How's Amma?
Amma?
She's managing,
you know,
the children have a curfew now.
She's asleep already.
-Why do you ask?
-Just being polite.
We do that in the big city, too,
you know.
I'll go make sure
your room is in order.
Thanks.
-(MUSIC STOPS)
-ALAN: Well, this is my new toy.
ADORA: Your old room
is the best for visitors.
It has that nice bath.
(THE WAY IT USED TO BE
PLAYING ON STEREO)
Good night, Camille.
Good night, Mama.
(EXHALES)
(SIGHS)
MARIAN: See? It's a heart.
YOUNG CAMILLE: You're high.
MARIAN: What?
It's something kids at school say.
It's, like, "You're crazy."
You're high.
No, you are. It's a chicken.
Clearly a chicken.
Where?
See? There's its eyes, okay,
and there's its face...
(GASPING)
Mama! Mama!
(THE WAY IT USED TO BE
CONTINUES PLAYING)
(MOTHERLESS CHILDREN PLAYING)
Camille?
I heard you were back in town.
How about we catch up over
your finest well whiskey? Hmm?
Well whiskey? No. Screw the well.
This is a homecoming drink,
and this homecoming drink
iS on me.
-Thank you.
-Yeah.
So, how about the place, huh?
It's mine now.
Yeah, I bought it from those guys.
They moved out to California.
We don't really get that type
around here anymore.
Whatever they call 'em now.
I mean, I got nothing
against 'em, but...
They would have tried to eat
that one down there alive.
Always recruitin'.
Oh! (LAUGHS) Still a smart-ass.
Still a dumbass.
Dumbass with the hottest
karaoke club in seven counties.
Shit, you oughta see this place
on Friday nights.
Tell me, what's your song?
Ring of Fire.
Oh, nice! Bohemian Rhapsody.
I crush it. (CHUCKLES)
Gay bait down there
seems a little young to be drinkin'.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm cuttin' him some slack.
It's John Keene.
John Keene, Natalie's brother?
Yeah, yeah. Poor son of a bitch.
He's takin' it really hard.
-Excuse me for a sec, okay?
-Yeah.
Ms. Preaker. At Sensors.
Yeah.
What, is this your spot?
This what you do?
You come here and you drink,
and you just, I don't know,
dream about the one that got away?
Sarcasm. Thank you.
Most I get from your hometown pals
iS a sugary passive-aggression.
Well, that is our specialty.
We just nod and smile
until the out-of-town asshole
leaves us alone.
Is that what I am?
Where are you from?
Kansas City,
by ways of a lot of other places.
So, yes on the "out-of-town,"
and jury's still out on "asshole."
How long have you worked on the case?
Since the Keene girl.
Vickery called for backup.
I think he regrets it now.
He doesn't like my style.
Which is?
Not his, I guess.
Hmm.
At least I'm investigating.
You don't think he is?
-Funny girl.
-Come on.
You know I'm gonna get the story
one way or another.
Wouldn't you rather be
in control of the conversation?
That's a good line.
Maybe, but it's true.
(SIGHS)
Well, like you were about to go talk
to young Keene over there.
Oh, is that who that is?
Reporters aren't supposed to talk
to minors without parental permission.
Jesus, I was just gonna hit on him.
(SCOFFS)
Well, that's different.
So, is he a suspect?
-You know I can't answer that.
-So he is.
Everybody's a suspect right now.
So, that's it.
You don't have any leads? Nothin"?
Camille, can we just talk?
I'm starved
for some city folk conversation.
I'll ask you a question
about your life,
you can ask about mine...
Yeah. I don't really do that. Chat.
Got it. Okay.
Well, Camille...
Enjoy your evening.
Detective.
Shit.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(RING OF FIRE PLAYING)
(LAUGHS) Come on.
(SINGS ALONG)
(WHAT IS AND WHAT SHOULD NEVER BE
PLAYING)
Shit. Fuck.
ADORA: Camille?
Mornin'.
I just left my bag
in the car, so I was...
Camille.
I'm happy you're here...
But, please, don't embarrass me.
Not again.
What?
When you're here, everything you do
comes back on me.
Understand?
Honestly, no.
‘Cause that might have been true
when I was a kid,
but I'm an adult now.
Not in Wind Gap.
When you're here, you're my daughter.
You can move away and forget,
but I can't.
You don't know
the people here anymore.
Yeah, believe me, I do.
I haven't heard from you in months!
And you just show up
askin' such horrible,
morbid questions,
stirring everyone up,
staying out all night.
(GRUNTS LOUDLY)
Look, Mama, please.
-(ADORA BREATHING HEAVILY)
-Stop, Mama. Look, stop.
I'm sorry, okay?
I'm sorry.
Honestly, it was nothin'.
I just... I went for a drive.
I was beat, so I...
I pulled over, to be safe.
It was stupid, so...
You spent the night in the car?
Did anyone see you?
No. No one saw me.
-Look, and about my story...
-I shouldn't have said anything.
You know...
You know I can't have
that kind of talk around here.
(DOOR OPENS)
I just want you
to understand that I...
I didn't come back
to cause any problems.
That wasn't my intention.
Are you ready for some eggs?
(SNIFFLES)
Thank you.
GIRL: Bobby. Come on.
Sorry, Kool-Aid's all I got left.
Oh, no, that's fine. Thank you.
And thank you for speaking with me.
With all the attention on Natalie,
I think it's important
to remind people that...
Ann was first.
Yeah.
Um...
We should talk in the bedroom.
Thank you.
-You mind if I just set this...
-Yeah.
Just...
Ann, she'd been...
Riding her bike all last summer,
just ride around, around the block.
My wife wouldn't
let her go no further,
‘cause we're protective parents,
like anybody.
Sure, you kept tabs on her.
-Yeah.
So...
So, just ‘fore school starts up,
she begs to ride over
to her friend Emily's house.
Not far...
But we usually wouldn't let her,
but she's whinin'.
So, my wife finally gets fed up
and says, "Fine."
Ann never got there.
To Emily's.
She left around 7:00, must've been...
8:00, 'fore we realized.
I'm sorry.
Somewhere, in those ten blocks,
they got her.
My wife...
Could never forgive herself.
I would love a chance
to speak with her?
Your wife.
She's at the store.
I'll ask, but she's not...
This thing...
She hasn't been the same.
(DOOR OPENS)
AMANDA: Daddy?
I'm still hungry. Can I make...
What do you do
when that door's closed, Amanda?
-l knock?
-You knock.
Next time you forget,
it's goin' on your chart.
Go.
She knows better.
Thing about Ann,
she was plain, but she was smart.
She did for herself.
Um...
So, were you here when it happened?
When Ann left for Emily's?
Mmm-mmm, I was driving back
from my office in Hayti.
It's about an hour away...
Don't write that down.
Why are you writing that down?
I'm sorry?
People round here don't like us
‘cause we keep to ourselves,
but that doesn't mean I hurt my kid.
No, no, no,
I wasn't suggesting that, Mr. Nash.
I was just wondering if you had
a chance to see her that day.
In the mornin'.
But four kids, it gets hectic. I...
I don't remember what we said.
You know what I think?
A faggot did it.
‘Cause he didn't rape her.
And the cops say that's unusual.
I'd say it's the only blessin' we got.
I'd rather him...
Kill her than rape her.
That's her.
See?
She was a willful thing.
Night before that picture was took,
my wife wants
to put her hair in rollers,
and Ann wasn't having any of it,
so she chops her hair off instead.
She gave him hell.
She gave that guy hell.
FRANK: So you got a feeling about him.
CAMILLE: His wife wasn't around.
It looks like she left.
He was kind of cagey about it.
FRANK: Could be embarrassed.
Private, you know.
Yeah.
He says that
people are pointing the finger at him.
Do you think he's a suspect?
I don't know.
I mean, he's odd, for sure.
But, I'll do some diggin'.
Good, good. Follow it up.
Things at home, they're all right?
(TEENAGERS CHATTERING)
Camille?
-At home?
-Yeah, with your family.
-Yeah, I mean, they're peachy.
-(FRANK COUGHING)
They're great.
Okay, well,
(COUGHS) you call me if you need me.
1 will.
Tell Eileen I said hello.
-Will do.
-All right.
-Okay. Bye-bye.
-Bye.
She sends her best.
You'd better be right.
Just because you've seen Dr. Phil
-doesn't make you a real doctor.
-(CHUCKLEYS)
(TEENAGERS LAUGHING)
Hey!
You can't take that stuff.
GIRL: We knew those girls.
Natalie was his sister.
John, right?
Yeah. No, they didn't
mean anything by it.
GIRL: We just wanted something
to remember them by, that's all.
What's the point of lettin'
all the flowers die and stuff, and...
It's not just the families, you know.
We're all sad.
(WOMAN WAILING)
MAN: Help! We need help!
"The wicked is thrust down
by his wrongdoing,
"but the righteous has a refuge
when he dies..."
(INDISTINCT)
(EXHALING SHAKILY)
Thanks, man. I got this.
Looks like you got your serial,
Detective. Congratulations.
This fuckin' business.
The things you wish for, and then...
And then it happens.
Yeah.
It's never real until it is.
You should let me drive you home.
You're shaking.
Not for long.
-I'll give you a lift.
-No, no, I'm... I'm fine.
I brought my car,
and I'm fine.
You can get it in the morning.
It's no trouble at all.
Is Bob Nash a suspect?
I was gonna ask Vickery before.
He won't tell you, like I won't.
And how about John Keene?
Jesus.
Why? Did you find something?
I'll show you mine.
This isn't... I'm not gonna...
(CLEARS THROAT)
Let's table the games.
At least until that little girl's
in the morgue.
(CHORD LEFT PLAYING ON STEREO)
(DOOR OPENS)
Where were you? I was worried sick.
I had to give the police a statement.
-l was there when they found her.
-Don't.
-That's enough.
-You asked me where I was.
I suppose
it was foolish to hold out hope.
I'm exhausted. I'm gonna lie down.
ADORA: Bob Nash called.
He said you spoke to him.
That's not right, Camille,
not right at all.
Aren't these families in enough agony
without you
-hashing over it?
-Mama. Mama.
I can't... I can't talk right now.
Okay? I need to sleep.
AMMA: I don't think
I'll sleep for a million years.
It's just so awful.
Ann and Natalie? In our nothin' town?
It could happen to any of us.
Amma.
Yeah.
You've been around, though.
Why haven't you said hello?
I can be shy, I guess.
I don't know.
Well, I never
would have recognized you.
Adora stopped sending
those Christmas pictures a while back.
ADORA: Amma, you are not to leave
this house alone. Understand?
It's not safe.
I need to know
where you are at all times.
But we already have to be in by 9:00.
ADORA: It's not enough, sweet.
ALAN: No.
Let's not make rules tonight, Adora.
We'll all be more sensible
in the morning, I think.
Come look at my dollhouse.
Needs reupholstering now.
Mama changed her color scheme
from gold to gray.
You promised you'd take me
to the fabric store
so I could make
new coverings to match.
ADORA: I know I did, sweet.
I've just been so distracted.
AMMA: Isn't it beautiful?
This dollhouse is my fancy.
Yeah, well, looks like you've done
a really nice job with it.
AMMA: I try. Thank you.
CAMILLE: Yeah.
I'm gonna go get some rest.
ADORA: I put your dinner
in the icebox for later.
-You have to eat.
-Okay, thanks.
I'll go up with you.
I think I'll rest a while too, Mama.
Let the girl rest.
You knew it was me, didn't you?
When you saw me around town.
Not at first.
Not for sure.
Then I just...
It was interesting
seeing what you were like
before this, you know?
You're not mad, are you?
No.
Just surprised, I guess.
Have you gone in to Marian's room?
No.
It's like a museum.
Mama keeps it that way.
Yeah.
I miss her sometimes.
Marian.
Even though I didn't know her.
Well, Adora talks about her
all the time.
Or at least alludes to her.
Was she perfect?
She was, wasn't she?
No. She was close.
But now we could be sisters.
Everyone always says you were
the prettiest girl in Wind Gap.
-No, Amma.
-You are.
You're so pretty.
And you won't tell?
Mama would go bananas if she,
you know,
saw me in my civvies.
Is that what you call them?
You know how she is.
I'm just her little doll to dress up.
Easier to go along.
You never did, though.
Mama says you were incorrigible.
I bet she does.
I'm incorrigible, too.
Only she doesn't know it.
We're alike.
I knew we would be.
(ADORA AND ALAN
CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
(INAUDIBLE)
Get off of me!
Camille!
YOUNG CAMILLE: Get off!
Get off of me!
(SHOWER RUNNING)
(TUMBLING LIGHTS PLAYING)