(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
CAMILLE: Amma!
Bless you
for finding her.
I never loved you.
Good morning.
You want a cup of coffee?
I got French vanilla
in a vacuum-sealed pouch.
CAMILLE: No, thank you.
I should probably get going.
I got a busy day.
RICHARD: What about tonight?
CAMILLE: Well, I have plans.
Unless you feel like joining a bunch
of ex-high school cheerleaders.
You could see
what I might've been like
if I'd have stayed in Wind Gap.
You slept in your clothes?
If you want, I'm the proud owner
of a 14-year-old flannel.
Sounds like you're halfway
to a question you wanted to ask me.
No, it was an offer.
You're gonna have to do better
than a cup of coffee
and an old flannel shirt.
(CAMILLE CHUCKLES)
(ALARM RINGING)
(MUSIC PLAYS)
-Be safe out there today.
-POLICEMAN: (ON RADIO) Chief...
(EXHALES)
(SIGHS)
(GARGLING)
(PHONE RINGING)
What is it?
Don't do a thing till I get there.
ADORA: Have you seen Alan?
No. Why, do you need a ride?
No. Thank you, I'm just...
A quick trip to the pharmacy.
CAMILLE: I don't mind.
I gotta pick up some cream anyway.
-For your scars?
-For my hands.
I can pick that up for you.
Finish your breakfast.
This is the first time I've seen
you eat since you got here.
What?
You tell me.
ADORA: Alan?
-What do you think?
-Millie, you're beautiful.
Mama, couldn't you just
take a bite out of her?
Like a plump, juicy cherry.
Thank you.
-Where you going?
-Just to hang out.
Well, not that I'm the best
to give advice on getting loaded,
but after yesterday,
you should slow down.
I'll be fine.
It's just a few scratches.
You should really put something
on those cuts.
Look.
Check this. If I connect these two,
I could make a "C" for "Camille."
That's not funny.
I wasn't serious.
Okay, well, just
don't ever do anything
-like that, all right?
-Yes. I won't.
Okay.
Thank you,
for coming for me last night.
I get funny ideas sometimes.
RICHARD: Paying your respects?
That's good of you.
It offsets the bad I do.
It's a losing battle,
but it helps me sleep.
I think a young girl prefers daisies.
Adora's always roses, roses, roses.
But these look like
what a child draws.
-It's sweet.
-Yeah.
Can I ask you something?
Adora mentioned that Camille
had some sort of episode recently.
Well, that's interesting.
I'm not one to talk
about people's touchy areas.
Not when I'm sober, anyway.
You're getting warmer, Detective.
And not just ‘cause it's hotter
than a whore in church today.
(PHONE LINE RINGING)
-POLICEMAN: KCPD.
-Hey, it's Willis.
I need to run a 522.
Admittance records, area hospitals.
Okay, what's the name?
Camille Preaker.
(PHONE BEEPING)
I gotta call you back.
Chief.
I'm on my way.
(CREAKING)
Thank you.
RICHARD: Who found it?
ADORA: My workers.
Bob, I'm so sorry
they dragged you down here.
-I'm sorry.
-RICHARD: Is it Ann's?
Might be. I don't know.
Let's hose it down.
RICHARD: No, we still might
be able to pull a print off it.
Bob, you think you could
identify it by the seat?
It was white, with flowers on it.
POLICE OFFICER: Here you go.
(FLIES BUZZING)
(CRYING)
(SOBBING)
ADORA: I'm sorry, Bob.
I'm so sorry.
RICHARD: We're gonna need
the employment records
of everyone who's worked here
for the last five years.
Why don't you come rub me down?
(MUSIC PLAYING ON SPEAKERS)
Where's Ashley?
Cheerleading practice.
What time does she get home?
Why?
‘Cause there's you, me
and an empty carriage house.
(DOOR SHUTS)
AMMA: Who do I remind you of?
JOHN: A bad little girl who thinks
she's a lot cuter than she is.
AMMA: Then you should
stop watching me.
You know how Ashley gets
when she's jealous.
JOHN: I like to keep on you, Amma.
Just know I always got an eye on you.
AMMA: You sure do, now.
JOHN: It'll be your day. Soon.
Hi.
-Is everything okay?
-JOHN: Not really.
My mama says you take your problems
with you wherever you go.
Sounds about right.
AMMA: There are places you can go
for help. You know that, right?
Maybe the voices in your head
can talk to somebody.
We don't want more little girls
showing up without their teeth.
CAMILLE: Amma.
ASHLEY: I am so rude.
-Have you been waiting long?
-No.
Oh, good. Good.
Hi, girls!
Jodes, Mama wants you to call her.
Would you go get us
some lemonade, please?
John.
Come in.
I'm so sorry about the mess.
ASHLEY: You could've been
a model, you know?
-I highly doubt that.
-No, you could have.
I always wanted to be like you
when I was growing up.
You're a legend around here.
CAMILLE: There are far better women
to aspire to.
Not in Wind Gap, there aren't.
I used to think about you.
I pictured you in a big mansion
with a few curly tops
and a big investment banker husband.
That sounds nice.
So, what can you tell me
about the girls?
Straight to business, huh?
Yeah.
Okay.
(EXHALES)
They were darling little girls.
Very well-behaved.
Sweet little things.
It's like God plucked
the very best girls from Wind Gap
to take to heaven for his own.
Hey, why'd you do that?
Because you were just wasting my time.
No, I...
Okay.
I was just trying to protect John.
He's already been hurt enough.
Why does he need your protection?
Do you think he did it?
No. Of course not.
He would never do something like that.
What makes you say that?
Because it would make him popular.
(DOOR OPENS)
ASHLEY: Thank you, John.
ASHLEY: Do you ever miss cheerleading?
CAMILLE: Shit.
-YOUNG CAMILLE: Cramps.
-That time of the month?
My calf, bitch.
Thank you.
KATIE: When you're done with her,
I'll go next.
Oh, fuck off, Katie.
I'm good, Becca. Thank you.
Whoa. You sure it wasn't
the other cramps?
(PHONE RINGING)
CAMILLE: Hi.
RICHARD: How about homemade sauce
with pasta and red wine?
I mean, it's progress.
RICHARD: You just tell me when.
So, homemade.
Does that mean you're gonna cook?
RICHARD: You bet I will,
in my fancy kitchen.
I mean, that is if you don't mind
having dinner in bed.
CAMILLE: Well,
that's very convenient of you.
Guess what we found today.
Thanks to your mom.
(CAR APPROACHING)
ADORA: Even the lawn
is not safe from her.
Shall I ask her to move it?
Why cause a scene?
I left your hand cream
in the bathroom.
-Oh, you got it.
-Of course, I did.
Was that before or after they found
Ann Nash's bike down at the factory?
Well, that was a business matter.
It did not concern you.
The first piece of material evidence
in a double homicide
certainly does concern me.
Now you know about it,
so there's no reason
to be upset with me.
Camille, your mother would like you
to move your car...
CAMILLE: Was the first call they made
to the police or you?
I heard that Bob Nash was there.
What was his reaction
when he saw the bike?
Are you interviewing me?
Yeah. Yeah, I guess I am.
ADORA: I'm your mother.
I'm not a source.
I'm sure you found other ways
to get your information.
-Thanks for the hand cream.
-ADORA: You're welcome.
I believe she's outstayed her welcome.
You've been more than tolerant, dear.
Thank you.
Let her know
how you feel about it, please.
Hi. I have an appointment
with Dr. Hafia.
-What's your name?
-Richard Willis.
Willis?
I'm trying to get a handle on
the personality type
that might come in here.
It might help me get somewhere
on this case I'm investigating.
There isn't any one type
that we see here.
Some of them are suffering
from underlying psychological problems
such as depression,
psychosis, bipolar disorder.
And then a lot of our patients
are just trying to distract
from painful feelings
resulting from trauma or stress.
That's a pretty wide net.
Like I said, nothing typical.
But if a person
was to end up in a place like this,
their behavior would have to be
pretty severe?
Well, people come in here in a crisis.
Our patients can be
impulsive and aggressive,
but they are very rarely violent.
Whatever is going on with them,
they take it out on themselves
more than other people.
ASHLEY: (ON TAPE)
Do you ever miss cheerleading?
CAMILLE: (ON TAPE)
So, is that why you think that
the killer is doing this,
for popularity?
ASHLEY ON TAPE:
What other reason is there?
(PHONE RINGING)
-Hi.
-FRANK: Cubby! What's the story?
Well, potential break.
They pulled the bicycle
of the first victim
out of a lagoon of pig shit.
FRANK: Holy fuck!
Were you there?
No. My mother was.
What does the book of journalism say
about using a family member
as a source?
FRANK:
They're called "anonymous sources.”
CAMILLE: Right.
Why would someone hide the bicycle
in a shallow pool of pig shit,
unless they were stupid
or trying to frame someone?
FRANK: So you think
it's someone from town.
CAMILLE: Maybe. Everybody thinks
that a man is behind this
and no one's looking at the women.
No, ‘cause it doesn't fit the profile.
Women don't kill like that,
that violent.
CAMILLE: Until they do.
EILEEN: Get it yourself.
Why aren't you in the office?
FRANK: ‘Cause the old ball and chain
won't let me.
She's got me tied to the bed.
That's what an animal I am
in the sack.
Hey, honey. How are you?
I'm worried about you.
CAMILLE: I'm fine, I'm just
looking forward to coming home.
Which is a weird thing to say
when you're sitting
in the bedroom you grew up in.
It's closing in on you, huh?
Well, that's a nice way to put it.
EILEEN: Well, sometimes the Lord
offers you the very thing you need.
CAMILLE: Yeah.
CAMILLE: I'm moving the car now.
Oh, Camille, that can...
You know, that can wait.
Please, come have a seat.
We haven't talked in a while.
Listen,
you're making your mother ill.
And I'm gonna have to ask you to leave
if these conditions don't improve.
I don't understand.
How am I making her ill?
You cannot day after day
churn out the grisly details
of dead children
to the mother of a dead child!
Alan, I have done
nothing of the sort with Adora.
Oh, please, Camille.
I know how jealous you've always been
of anyone else's well-being.
And to think that I used to regret
that we didn't communicate.
(LAUGHS)
That is something Joya would say.
Yeah, you really are
like your grandmother.
She would stand guard over this house
like a witch.
The only time she ever smiled
was when you refused to nurse
from Adora.
Well, it has been really nice, Alan.
Thank you.
ALAN: Camille,
Adora has had a hard life.
Joya would come into her room
in the middle of the night,
and she would pinch her.
She said that she was worried
that Adora would die in her sleep.
You know what I say?
She just liked to hurt people.
Yeah, I think you've made your point.
I just think that
if you knew these things,
it might make you
somewhat kinder to your mother.
Yeah, I'll be leaving
as soon as I can, all right?
ALAN: That would be a good idea.
What was that all about?
You know, family.
Oh, look at you.
When you ride with me,
you ride in style.
Smooth.
That's good bourbon,
but the key is in the ice.
Large ice trays, distilled water,
these cubes will change your life.
Not that I'd know ‘cause I'm carrying.
(CAMILLE LAUGHS)
That husband of yours has gotta be
missing you something awful.
Nope, no husband.
Well, honey, you just string
that boyfriend of yours on
as long as you can,
and he'll be begging to marry you.
Yeah, no boyfriend either.
You didn't hear this from me,
but Lisa is thinking about
getting separated.
Son of a bitch. Let's go, asshole.
She walked in on her husband
jerking off
on a copy of a credit card bill.
Don't ask me what that's all about.
Gretchen was the one that told me.
Don't believe her
"I'm so sweet" act for a second here.
She's already repeating every word
you say to any bitch who will listen
before you can even
get it out your mouth.
Katie, too.
But I don't need to tell you that.
We've known that bitch our whole life.
Here you go, baby.
Oh, God. There's Lisa's husband's car.
Overcompensating for you know what,
if you ask me.
And just think of the house you
would've had if you had stuck around.
Finish that up.
For an expensive house,
she pours cheap liquor.
I'm so glad you're here.
This is gonna be like the old days.
We gonna have us some fun.
(MOVIE PLAYING ON TV)
I waited for you.
I'm here now.
I wanna go.
I don't want them to see me here.
Are you sure? Are you really sure?
(WOMEN CRYING)
(CHATTER)
-Hey.
-Get a Jim Beam, please.
What's this I hear
about you and Ms. Preaker?
This town. Don't you people
have anything better to do?
No.
(LAUGHING)
Don't believe everything you hear.
Yeah, well,
you might want to take
your own advice on that one.
BARTENDER: Just saying.
(WOMAN CRYING)
ANGIE: This isn't about the movie,
is it, darling?
No.
Oh, it's okay, honey.
You can talk to us.
You're amongst friends.
I went back to work.
KATIE: Good God, sweetie, why?
With Stephie in preschool,
I felt like I wanted to,
like I needed a purpose.
ANGIE: You have a purpose.
Don't let feminism tell you
what to do with your family.
BECCA: She's right. Feminism means
letting women
make the choices they want.
(WOMAN CRYING)
Dear heart, what is it? What is it?
Jack doesn't want
to have any more kids.
-He says four's enough.
-KATIE: For him or for you?
LISA: I don't know.
This shit happens every week.
GRETCHEN: You deserve it.
If you want five, you want five.
You're the only one
who has said that to me.
Well, he's not gonna say it.
LISA: He's such an asshole.
I had no idea my life was so miserable
until I started coming
to Katie's little get-togethers.
Well, being conflicted
means you can live a shallow life
without copping
to being a shallow person.
Hm. Sounds about right.
I guess we are
who we were in high school.
I set the bar low for myself then,
so there's no way to go but up.
Well, I'm glad you two
are having so much fun.
Considering what's going on
in this town.
What's wrong with this world?
Why would somebody hurt little girls?
-Oh, poor things.
-There she goes again. Jesus.
And to take their teeth?
Just plain sick is what it is.
How can you even report
on these things, Camille?
KATIE: Hey, that's not fair.
Camille doesn't have any children,
and I just don't think
you can feel the pain
the way that we do.
Right.
I feel, for those little girls.
It's terrible.
I don't mean to sound cruel,
but I don't think part of your heart
can ever work if you don't have kids.
I didn't really become a woman
until I felt McKenzie inside of me.
I mean, there's all this talk
of God versus science,
but it seems like with babies,
both sides agree.
The Bible says,
"be fruitful and multiply,"
and then science...
I mean, when it boils down to it,
that's just what women were made for.
(KATIE GIGGLES)
Girl power.
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
-Hi.
-Hey.
Didn't expect to see you here.
I thought this was kind of like
a "girls only" thing.
Yeah, well, Katie
doesn't know I'm here.
Well, I will not tell her.
-Thanks.
-Okay.
Hey, I'm glad...
Oh, let's...
Listen, I'm glad we can have a minute.
I just, I
felt I owe you an apology
for what happened.
What happened?
Well, that day.
In the woods.
And what we did to you.
I have daughters now,
and it makes me sick thinking that...
That a bunch of football players
would pull a train on them
at the end of a big game?
Camille...
As I recall,
you couldn't even get it up,
SO unless you're apologizing
for that...
-Hey.
-Oh, come on.
Just forget about it, all right?
I have.
That day, it's haunted me.
Well, looks like we both got fucked.
Perky little titties,
shining in the sun.
-This gun loaded?
-lt is.
Look at you.
(CHUCKLES)
I have had my hand on your thigh
for the past 15 minutes, Detective.
This isn't turning out
like I was hoping,
so why don't you just get to
what you need to get to, all right?
Camille.
Mm.
Why was she in rehab?
I know she was hurting herself.
What I'm asking is why?
Mm. Well, I don't know.
I'm pretty fond of Camille.
You know?
She's sensitive.
Special. Beautiful girl.
She wasn't the same
after her sister died.
How did she die?
Marian was sickly, a sickly child.
Was there an autopsy?
(SCOFFS) Adora Crellin was not gonna
let them carve up her little girl.
"Carve up."
That's an interesting choice of words.
You seem to know
a lot more than you're letting on,
so why don't you just tell me
what you know?
I know she checked herself out early
after her roommate killed herself.
Jesus.
Well, that's news to me.
Dead girls everywhere.
How'd she die?
She drank poison.
BECCA: Are you sure
I can't drive you home?
CAMILLE: Yeah, no, I'm good.
I'll just walk.
BECCA: All right.
Why are you being nice to me?
(CHUCKLES) Why wouldn't I be?
We were bitches to you in high school.
Bitches.
-You were better than most.
-Well, that's not saying much.
You were going through a lot.
Lost your sister,
and you took it out on yourself.
Remember
when I was rubbing your leg
and you were bleeding?
Everyone thought you had your period,
but I saw.
On your thigh, the cuts.
It said "cherry."
That made sense.
We were so shiny.
Luscious on the outside.
But on the inside,
there's that dark, hard pit.
Yeah.
-Can I quote you on that?
-(BECCA LAUGHS)
-Alan?
-Hm?
I see you didn't take care
of what I asked you to do.
Oh, well, you were always better
at handling the girls, dear.
(MUSIC PLAYING ON RECORD)
(CASH REGISTER BEEPING)
AMMA: I can't...
I can't believe she's here.
(LAUGHING)
(KNOCKING)
Come on!
-What if she gets mad?
-She's gonna be fine.
She's gonna be fine.
-Hi!
-Hil
What is that?
-That's mine.
-What you got there?
-None of your business.
-Look who's here, boys!
-I see that.
-AMMA: That's my big sis, Camille.
-Hey, Camille!
-That's Nathan. This is Damon.
-AMMA: We're gonna take you home.
-CAMILLE: No.
-Come on.
-Yeah.
-We're gonna take you home.
-Getonin.
-Amma, I'm gonna walk.
-Go on, get in.
-Come on.
-No way.
-The seat's warm.
-We'll drop you off before we go.
-Oh, sweet!
AMMA: We're dropping her off
before we go.
Gotcha.
You're like my ma's age, but hot.
CAMILLE: Yeah, I doubt that.
How old is your ma?
Like 33, 34.
-CAMILLE: And what's her name?
-Casey Rayburn.
-Must be before my time.
-Dude, seriously?
This chick is obviously way too cool
to be hanging out
with your crackwhore mama.
-Fuck you, Damon!
-Hey. Hey.
Well, I think that was
a very nice compliment.
Thank you very much.
That was very sweet of you.
What the fuck's taking so long?
Let's go!
Par-tay, par-tay.
Come on!
(GIGGLING, CHEERING)
ALL: Whoo!
BOY: Let's get outta here!
You sure you don't
want to come with us?
It'll be fun.
Come on, chiquita.
OxyContin. Makes you feel really good.
I'm sure it does, but doing it
with my kid sister won't, so...
Come on, Mille, just one?
I feel so happy and good right now.
You just... I mean, you just have to.
Come on, do it.
ALL: Do it! Do it! Do it!
(LAUGHING)
-AMMA: Come on!
-BOY: Yeah, okay!
Just five minutes.
Then we'll take you home.
I promise. Come on, Camille! Please.
(GIGGLING)
Yeah.
Yeah!
(KIDS CHEERING)
NATHAN: Damon, let's go!
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
(LAUGHTER)
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God.
They came! They totally came!
-Do we say hello?
-BOY: Just let J.C. handle it.
Hi! Justine, how are you?
Good to see you.
Hi!
I thought you guys said
you weren't coming.
Oh, I thought that was stupid.
Anyone with a brain
knows that John's cool.
And plus, we're not gonna be
fucking outcasts.
Excuse me.
What the fuck are y'all doing here?
GIRL: I can't believe you're here.
That he showed his face.
God, you're such a little bitch.
You don't know anything,
you druggy fucker.
Hey. Hey, come on.
(ARGUING)
CAMILLE: Hey. Hey. Come on, girls.
It's okay. Just don't talk.
Okay, that's enough. All right?
-AMMA: Bye, murderer!
-Amma.
Why don't you go drink
a little bit more?
Fuck off.
It's like she goes out of her way
to irritate me.
I don't think you're alone
in that regard.
ASHLEY: So,
how's my article coming along?
To be honest,
you didn't really say anything
particularly quote-worthy.
But I already told people
that I'm gonna be in it.
Yeah, well,
I'm on to different stories.
-Okay.
-Like the one about
how someone
took a chunk out of your ear.
-Was it Natalie?
-Who told you about that?
With you withholding
information like that,
that's not gonna help you.
It's just not something
I like to remember.
JOHN: Let's go.
J.C. doesn't want me here.
If you want to know about Natalie,
you should ask your mom.
Besides, who really cares about
your stupid article, anyway?
Nobody reads the newspaper anymore.
See you later, baby killer.
Fuck y'all! Fuck all y'all!
(CHEERING)
BOY: Get this show on the road, huh?
Come on. VIP room!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
(PARTY MUSIC PLAYS)
(CHEERING)
Don't push me, Kelsey.
(LAUGHING)
CAMILLE: Sorry.
AMMA: Have you ever played a game
of Rolling Roulette?
No.
We pass the X around...
-Okay, here.
-Here.
-Jodes.
-Thank you!
...and the tongue it dissolves on last
is the lucky winner.
This is Damon's best shit, though,
so we'll all roll a little.
NATHAN: Hey. Hey, wait a minute.
Amma! Hey!
Drink lots of water.
Oh, fuck, Amma,
the game barely started.
Camille's my guest and my sister.
Plus, she could use a little sunshine.
She's had a pretty shitty life.
And just so you know,
we have a dead sister,
just like John Keene,
and she's never, ever dealt with it.
Anyway...
(GROANS)
Why are you doing this?
You are a Union woman!
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
(PARTY MUSIC PLAYING)
(CAN'T TAKE MY EYES OFF YOU PLAYING)
ALL: Whoo!
(IMITATING MUSIC)
I'm coming with you.
I wanna come with you.
Fuck off. All right?
Come on.
CAMILLE: These are really beautiful.
AMMA: I love yellow when I'm stoned.
AMMA: Mama says I need
to be careful around you.
Are you dangerous?
(HORN BLARING)
CAMILLE: Let's get out of here.
Let's get out of here.
-Kansas City.
-Chief.
(GROANS) Breakfast for dinner.
-Thank you, Jessie.
-JESSIE: My pleasure.
I gotta say, I really miss seeing you
in that Robert E. Lee getup.
First off, I was Stonewall Jackson.
I'd rather die under friendly fire
than surrender like a coward.
The more I know about you,
the less I want to know.
That's Wind Gap for you.
But you're gonna be
going home tomorrow.
Oh, yeah? Why is that?
Mexican worker at the hog farm
ID'd Keene
as the guy who dumped
the bike in the lagoon.
No shit.
Good shit.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Can't wait to get out of here.
I'm bored all the time.
That's why I act the way I do.
I know I can be a little off.
Did girls like you growing up?
I mean, boys are easy.
You just let them do stuff to you.
You shouldn't let them do that.
When you let them do it to you,
you're really doing it to them.
You have the control
and they like you.
It's not the same with girls.
I mean, I can get them
to do what I want,
but they don't like me.
"It's safer to be feared than loved."
Machiavelli.
How do you know that?
You know how.
Sometimes you need to be mean
or hurt.
Amma, do you cut?
(LAUGHING)
-I'm so happy with you!
-Shh!
You're like my soul mate.
You're like my sister.
I love you.
Take me back to St. Louis with you.
I can get a job after school
at a boutique
or a fancy fabric shop.
You think I could put my dollhouse
on a résumé?
(GROANS)
I thought you liked it rough.
-Want to sleep in my room?
-No.
No, I'm dead tired. I think I should
just go to my bed tonight.
Can I sleep over with you?
No, I...
I think we should just
sleep separate tonight,
and then we'll hang out
tomorrow, okay?
Amma. Amma! Fine! Fine!
Fine. You can sleep
in my room. Come on.
You can sleep with me.
Oh, Jesus, Amma.
AMMA: I just can't remember
being this happy.
(WHISPERS) I wanna bring
my dollhouse upstairs.
I know you think
Adora likes me better,
but that's not true.
She calls out names
when she's sleeping.
Marian, you.
(GIGGLING)
-Here.
-Wait.
Wait.
(GROANS)
AMMA: Do you ever feel like
bad things are gonna happen to you
and you can't stop them?
You can't do anything?
You just have to wait?
It's not safe here for you.
(SONG PLAYING)