(SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING)
CAMILLE: What the hell?
(GASPS)
ADORA: Good morning.
You took off my clothes?
They were ruined.
I brought some ice.
That ankle of yours is very swollen.
You must have taken
quite a nasty spill last night.
Amma knows better.
Tearing down those stairs
with the landing light off...
Thank God you caught her.
She could have cracked her skull.
You're quite the protector.
Mama, I gotta go. I gotta go to work.
Lie back, Camille.
-No, I have a deadline...
-Lie back.
A little bit of sweet
before the bitter. It helps.
Open.
Then a bit more sweet,
and a day in bed,
that's my prescription.
Mama, I really do have
to get to work today, okay?
Camille.
Will you let me wrap
your ankle for you, please?
Ow! (GROANS)
Go away, please.
(GROANS)
I'm sorry. I'm just...
I'm tired, and I really gotta
get some work done today.
ADORA: Well, make it a short day,
and come right back to me.
This has been coming a while.
Your health
is not a debt you just cancel.
The body collects, Camille.
(MUSIC PLAYING ON CAR STEREO)
Hello, ladies.
Here. Keep it.
(BELL TINKLING)
Fueling up for the day, there, Billy?
I see you are, as well.
Hmm, just helps the fuel go down easy.
VICKERY: Oh.
I still owe you a conversation.
No, I... I got what I needed.
Really? There something I should know?
Okay, then.
-How's our girl?
-Jocelyn is fine.
I'll give her your regards.
No, I meant the other one.
Are we gonna keep doing this?
Well, we can do
what we always do around here,
and pretend it doesn't exist.
-I like that better.
-Do you?
Mmm.
Well, I'm off to protect and serve.
I'm off to mix and serve.
-(BELL TINKLES)
-(JACKIE LAUGHS)
(FLOORBOARD CREAKING)
CAMILLE: You okay?
She gave you the blue?
No, I didn't want it.
You know what my favorite part
about getting wasted is?
Mama takes care of me after.
I think you can take care of yourself.
I want Mama,
and she wants me like this.
Don't do this for her, okay?
You don't have to.
(KISSES)
(CHUCKLES)
What? I'm not allowed
to touch her room?
Not even here?
They're arresting him today.
John?
AMMA: Roy says
killer going down today.
Roy's Kelsey's cousin.
Works for, like, a judge or something.
Didn't Dick tell you?
(BUZZER SOUNDS)
(WOMAN COUGHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Hey.
Checking in? Or just a bupe-and-go?
I'm looking for a Beverly Van Lumm.
We don't give out names.
But she's not a patient.
She's a nurse.
We don't give out names.
WOMAN: Oh, shit.
You're that cop. (CHUCKLES)
Oh. Oh, man, I never met
anybody famous before...
Could you just help me out here?
Beverly Van Lumm.
You're looking for me?
I got your name from Jackie O'Neill.
She said you might know something
about a Marian Crellin.
RECEPTIONIST: Go back
to your seat, ma'am.
I'll call you
when the doctor is ready.
VICKERY: Go on in.
I'll be right there.
All right, Chief.
ASHLEY: What is going on here?
Ashley, just wait one second.
Just wait one second.
ASHLEY: No.
Just let me go inside.
-Why are you at my house?
-We have a search warrant.
-Why?
-Just go on inside.
Go on.
(WIND CHIME TINKLING)
VICKERY: Where's John at?
ASHLEY: He went for a drive,
and he hasn't come back.
VICKERY: When?
ASHLEY: Last night.
(INDISTINCT POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
Ashley, sweetheart.
For his sake, for your sake,
you don't want to go to jail.
-You need to tell me where he's at.
-I don't know where he's at.
I can't just abandon him.
I'd look like a total bitch.
Fact is, you'd be helping him,
and, in the eyes of the town,
you'd be a hero.
Ashley, you help us, everyone,
everyone will know how brave you were
to help save
the lives of little girls.
You mean, like, my name in the paper?
Face on TV, I reckon.
(RADIO CHATTER CONTINUES)
He'd never have sex with me.
RICHARD: What did she die from?
That's the thing.
She got passed around.
Different doctors,
different diagnoses.
Crohn's. Heart palpitations.
Respiratory issues.
Gastrointestinal issues,
renal issues...
Jesus.
All those conditions suspected,
but none confirmed.
The night she died,
the attending was a guy
who'd never seen her before.
But she was treated there
for years. She has a chart.
This chart?
It's a choose-your-own-adventure.
The records weren't great back then.
The nurses, we were the records.
I kept a copy.
Thought it might
come in handy one day.
Munchausen's by proxy syndrome, MBP.
That's what killed Marian?
Yes.
It's a mental illness, in adults.
Munchausen's is when
you hurt yourself to get attention.
You make yourself sick,
everyone's at your beck and call.
Munchausen's by proxy,
on the other hand,
is when you make someone else sick
so you can care for them,
SO you can save them.
Or try. Be seen trying.
You're saying Adora has this.
I'm saying people have this.
Mostly mothers.
Mothers who need to be worshiped,
to be heroes.
Nothing more laudable than a woman
who puts all her energy
into her sick child.
You denied every request
for information.
I did what the doctors told me to.
Why didn't you tell the police?
I did,
and I lost my job at the hospital,
after which I never heard
another thing about it.
I still have friends
at Woodberry Hospital,
if you're curious to talk to them,
not about Marian.
About the other one.
Come on. Let's get you in bed.
Come on.
-Come on.
-I don't want it.
-Amma.
-I'm not really sick.
-I'm just...
-You're just what?
Had a few beers last night. I'm sorry.
She was a bad influence on Marian.
She's a bad influence
on you.
AMMA: No, she's not.
Well, the cure's much the same.
What is all this but dehydration,
vitamin deficiency, exhaustion...
Mama, I really feel okay.
Just some sleep...
Maybe a grilled cheese.
I don't think so.
I mean, you don't need me
to make you feel better.
(SIGHS) You don't need me to
make you a grilled cheese.
But I don't know how.
No, no, no. Go on.
Do your own laundry
while you're at it.
-Mama...
-Clean your own room...
Pay your own way, oh, and...
Yeah, you don't need
this anymore, do you?
-No, Mama, please. Stop.
-Playtime is over, right?
You're much too mature
for all of this...
Don't... Stop it!
It hurts me, that you don't trust me
to do the best for you.
MAN: Check this. One, two.
WOMAN: Three, four.
One, two, three. One, two...
Hi. You know where else
you can get a drink this time of day
in this shitty town?
This is it, unless you head over
to Bean Town.
But you'd have to like
the smell of blood and piss.
Oh. Thank you.
Maybe I'll see you later.
-Check, baby. One, two.
-Three, four.
(BELL TINKLES)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
VICKERY: There he is.
(DISHES CLATTERING)
(RICHARD SIGHS)
Well, looks like we caught our Killer.
I thought I'd celebrate.
WAITRESS: (CLEARS THROAT)
Can I get you anything?
Yeah, let me get a coffee, black.
That guy that saw John dump the bike,
I read his statement.
He works days, for one.
He just happens
to be there at midnight...
Yeah, I know. He's a shit witness,
but he said what we needed
to get a warrant.
Turn up the heat.
We found blood under John Keene's bed.
-Uh-huh.
-What?
Yeah. His girlfriend gave him up.
Something about the women around here.
Yeah. They'll climb over anybody
to get their name in print.
God forbid you should be ordinary,
nobody pays you any mind.
But, once we get
the forensics on the blood,
we're done here. Case closed.
What do you know about
how Marian Crellin died?
Now you're just falling prey
to what this town does best, son.
Ugly gossip.
Well, the nurse that treated her
feels differently.
Is that the same nurse
that got fired for malpractice?
Ended up working in a methadone clinic
‘cause she liked methadone so much?
You talking about that nurse?
Ugly gossip.
Seems to me like your priorities
are a little confused, son.
You wanna help me find
John Keene, that's fine.
If not, you can go home.
It's your choice.
(BELL TINKLES)
(SWING CREAKING)
(KIDS CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
(MUSIC PLAYING ON SPEAKER)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Two bourbons. Dos. Double.
Por favor.
(CAMILLE CLEARS THROAT)
Gracias.
Here you go.
What are you doing here?
CAMILLE: What are you doing here?
Thought I'd come have
one last drink or two
before I get arrested.
Can't go back to Ashley's.
Sure as shit
not going back to my house.
Rather go into the fucking woods
and kill myself. (CHUCKLES)
Thanks.
I don't blame you.
-Cheers.
So, here I am.
(CHUCKLING)
You know, people think I did it
just because I cry about it.
Well, you're a guy.
Guys aren't allowed
to have soft emotions.
(LAUGHING)
Well, my mom got me this book,
when Natalie died,
about how guys deal
with death and stuff...
CAMILLE: Mmm-hmm.
...and it said
denial was good for men,
so I pretended I didn't care about it,
and that lasted about an hour.
So...
Drinking helps more.
Yeah.
It's like they took
the two girls in Wind Gap
with minds of their own, and they...
They just killed them off.
Do you think our sisters
would have been friends?
Marian, I mean.
Hell no.
(BOTH LAUGH)
So what? Your dead sister's
too good for my dead sister?
-You know.
-Whatever.
(CHUCKLES)
John, tell me something.
Did you kill 'em?
‘Cause you... You never said
you didn't.
You said, "Nobody thinks
I killed my sister."
But now's your chance.
Tell your story. Defend yourself.
I'm done with that.
I want it over.
Then say the words.
"I didn't kill my sister."
Oh, you just want a story...
Hey, you killin' little girls
is what I'm supposed to want.
Something tells me
you got another story.
No.
All right. Okay.
So, uh, why kill Natalie?
I mean, Ann, I understand.
She was a nasty little cunt.
She hurt your sister.
I might have done the same thing,
but Natalie?
Feeling the windpipe snap...
She couldn't scratch me
because she always bit her nails.
That's right.
The teeth were easy.
We had tools at the hog farm.
Pull the pig teeth out
so they can't bite you.
Feels good when they come out.
The release.
Why Kill little girls?
I want to rape them,
but I won't let myself,
because I can't control the desire,
so I kill them instead.
-Hmm.
-Destroy the desire.
I thought Ann would be enough for me,
but it was Natalie
that I really wanted.
See, I can tell stories, too.
Use that one if you like.
I truly don't give a shit.
(BOTTLE THUDS)
Or how about this one?
A brother misses his sister
so bad that he...
He wants to die.
But that's boring as shit, right?
So, spin another.
CAMILLE: Hmm.
You don't come back from this, huh?
(SNIFFLES)
Her fingernails were painted.
When they found her, someone...
Someone painted her fingernails.
Natalie would never do that.
(CHUCKLES)
You're kidding me.
Feminist folk singers
for a bunch of pig slaughterers.
I didn't kill Natalie.
I know.
You're beautiful.
(JOHN CHUCKLING)
I'm sorry. That, just...
It's a compliment, all right?
Don't get any ideas.
So are you.
(CHATTER CONTINUES)
Either I drive myself
into the station,
or I drive straight into a lake.
-Stop.
-(CHUCKLES)
Okay, you cannot go into
an interrogation like this.
-They'd eat you alive.
-(BELL DINGING)
I don't care if they arrest me.
I don't care if they execute me.
(TRAIN CHUGGING)
I was dead the minute it happened.
No, you're not.
(CAMILLE CLEARS THROAT)
You are too.
(CHUCKLES)
Fuck you.
Go ahead, Camille.
Prove you're not dead.
RICHARD: Thank you.
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT ON PA)
What's a G-tube?
It's a feeding tube.
It's inserted through the tummy
when the patients can't eat,
so Mom could put food
right into the stomach.
Jesus Christ.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATES)
(BELL DINGING)
WOMAN: (ON RADIO)
Suspect has been located
at the El Camino Motel
15 miles north of your position.
(DEVICE BEEPING)
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
ADORA: Girls,
please don't knock so loudly.
Sorry, Mrs. Crellin. Is Amma here?
Amma is under the weather.
What is this concerning?
We just wanted to tell her
about John Keene.
They're about to arrest him, ma'am.
Well, I'm sure we're all happy
to see justice done.
Amma will be relieved.
Oh, and please don't
come back again today.
-(DOOR CLOSES)
(WHISPERS) Bitch.
(FOOTSTEPS RECEDING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
What do you think I'll be, Mama,
when I... When I grow up?
-(CHUCKLEYS)
-Do you think I'll have kids?
I don't know.
How would I know?
It's years off.
-Do you think...
-Years.
...I'won't grow up?
Is that why you want me
to stay little?
So I won't be like Marian?
You are like Marian.
No. I'm not as good.
You can never be as good
as someone dead.
Oh, hush, hush.
That's fever-talk.
Just a little.
Good girl.
(COUGHING)
I'll be back in a little.
You rest, and let me
have your cellphone.
The other one.
Camille leaves tomorrow,
and things will go back
to the way they were.
AMMA: I like Camille here.
CAMILLE: Why don't you just drink some
water and sleep it off, all right?
(GROANS) Thank you.
I saw this the other day.
Can I look?
It's okay, Camille.
Let me see.
John, nobody sees.
I do.
Hey. It's okay, Camille.
Let me see you.
It's okay.
Is it everywhere?
(CAMILLE SNIFFLING)
"Laid.
-"Drained."
-(EXHALES)
"Cherry."
-(SNIFFLES)
"Sick".
"Gone."
You're reading me.
"Wrong."
-(EXHALES)
"Falling".
"Wicked."
(SOBBING)
(CONTINUES SOBBING)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(MOANS)
It's okay.
(CAMILLE BREATHING SHAKILY)
JOHN: It's okay.
(GASPS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
ALAN: How bad?
Very bad.
Poor thing.
(BOTH SIGH)
All right, then.
Go relax.
Play some music.
(MUSIC STARTS PLAYING)
(SIGHS)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(GLASS CLINKING)
CAMILLE: Your sister do that?
JOHN: Mmm-hmm.
I never thought she was bad.
She was just completely herself.
-Town hated her for that.
-Hmm.
Well, what was with the biting?
-She an animal?
-Fuck yeah, she bit people.
Self-defense. This fucking place...
Hmm. Yeah.
The only person that ever
gave a shit about my sister
was your mom.
Oh.
I know she knew Natalie
and Ann, too, right?
The lost girls.
The ones everybody else gave up on.
She just kept coming back for more.
Natalie fought her and fought her,
like physically.
Did she win?
-(CHUCKLING) Yeah.
-Yeah?
Yeah. She had to get stitches
one time.
That was from Ann, though,
not from Natalie.
But she, uh... She never gave up.
Yeah, like she was gonna...
Solve them.
I never let her solve me.
Maybe I should've...
What's wrong?
(LOUD KNOCKING ON DOOR)
VICKERY: John Keene, you in there?
JOHN: Yeah. One second!
Come on out, son.
Jesus Christ. Put your pants on, son.
Come on. Get your pants on.
Face the wall.
Put your hands behind your back,
interlock your fingers,
spread your legs, don't move.
-You of age, son?
-Yeah, I'm 18.
All right, John Keene,
you're under arrest.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will be
used against you in a court of law.
You have a right to an attorney.
If you can't afford one,
we'll try to rustle one up for you.
Mike, grab those clothes.
You understand your rights, son?
-Yeah.
-All right.
-You got him?
-I got him.
We'll give you a minute
to gather your things, Miss Preaker.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
RICHARD: Where do you want to begin?
It's just... It's not how it looks.
I mean, I know
that sounds cliche, but...
-This room fucking stinks of you.
-(SCOFFS)
Believe me, I know the smell.
He just wanted to have a few...
Get a little liquid courage
before he got arrested.
I thought maybe I could
get a quote or two,
and then he wanted me to
bring him back here to sleep it off.
He didn't do it, Richard.
Is that what you discussed
when he had his dick in you?
Look, you know that he didn't...
Fuck you?
Kill them.
They found Natalie's blood
where he's been living.
Yeah. You and I have been
jerking each other off, haven't we?
It's so kinky,
there's more to the story.
Back on Earth,
it's the family, Camille.
It's always the fucking family.
Man, I should have fucked
the prime suspect.
Don't... Don't do...
I should have fucked him.
I would have cracked
this fucker weeks ago.
We both lost
-people, Richard, and...
-(SCOFFS)
What comfort you must've been
to each other.
That's...
You know what I've been doing
for the last 24 hours?
Do you now? I've been
studying you, Camille.
Yeah, I've been studying you
because you're so fucking fascinating.
Who is she? What is she hiding?
You know, you really had me there,
but whatever happened, I'm done.
Richard, don't...
Please don't go. Please.
Please don't hate me, okay?
Please. Please don't hate me.
Stop. Stop.
What are you doing? Get up!
Please... (SOBBING)
I don't think you're bad, okay.
I think one bad thing happened,
and you blamed the rest
of your shitty life on it.
People really buy it, your sad story.
But, really, you're just
a drunk and a slut.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Chief, what do you wanna do
about the girl?
-Just leave her be.
-All right.
Dispatch, we've got
the suspect in custody.
(INDISTINCT POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
(ENGINE STARTS)
(TRAIN HORN BLARING)
Well, look at what the cat dragged in.
Come onin.
(MUSIC PLAYING ON RECORD)
It's so nice of you to drop by.
I'll make you something to drink.
You look like you could use it.
CAMILLE: All right.
Sit down.
Let me turn this crap off.
This is how I do 'em.
(MUSIC STOPS)
Just enough Stoli
to make the stomach bleed.
Ohl
Oh, darling. Woman-to-woman,
you look like pure-T blue ribbon shit.
Believe me, I know that look.
I own that look. (CHUCKLES)
Mmm.
My husband gave me
this ugly-ass thing.
I keep my beauty secrets inside.
Go on. Help yourself there.
I got plenty.
I got endometriosis,
pelvic floor dysfunction,
I got cysts, IC, IBS,
and fibromyalgia.
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, and hypochondria!
I've been diagnosed and undiagnosed,
rediagnosed with all of it.
Hmm.
I hurt is all.
Jackie...
You've always been
really nice to me.
-Always.
-Hmm.
I read Marian's medical file.
Your name is all over those records.
Information requested, explanations,
every test, every diagnosis.
-Information...
-Yep.
Requested.
All denied.
What were you looking for?
Hmm.
What do you...
What do you remember
about her funeral that day?
Just looking at her... Marian, mostly.
Just looking at her.
In that beautiful dress of hers.
That tiny little body,
all the stories it could tell...
Gone.
Drink with me.
Let me host you for a little while.
(CHUCKLES) There you go.
Mmm. See how easy that was?
Anyway, it was gorgeous.
Goddamn Martha Stewart funeral.
Marian looked like an angel.
Your mother never looked
more beautiful than that day.
She cried and cried...
...and then she burned her.
What?
Cremated.
Oh, they simply loved
your mama at Woodberry!
Mmm. Those nurses would line up
like chorus girls
whenever she'd come
promenading into that ICU.
She'd always bring sweets.
Imagine that.
The mother of a sick child,
and she'd still come
to bake for the staff.
Goddamn Mother of the Year.
Drink up, doll.
Drink up. (CHUCKLES)
-(GLASS THUDS)
-You don't like my bloodies?
That's 'cause they're shitty.
I know.
But every time I ask you to drink it,
you do.
Why is that?
It's easier.
Easier...
For Marian.
You made it hard.
Hard on yourself, hard on Adora.
Marian, it was easier.
Just lie back and...
take it.
And you knew?
And you just let it happen?
Well, what was I gonna do?
Who was I gonna tell?
Who the fuck's gonna believe me?
Well, no wonder you're sick.
I did what I could.
-You're sick.
-Don't you walk out of here.
You come back here.
God damn it! I did what I could!
(LINE RINGING)
EILEEN: (ON PHONE)
Hi, honey. How are you?
Hi, Eileen. Can I, um...
Can I talk to Curry?
Sweetheart,
what is it? Are you okay?
(CAMILLE SOBBING)
I just really...
(SNIFFLES)
Sweetie, you're scaring me.
-You're not hurting yourself, are you?
-(SOBBING)
No, no, no. I just, uh...
(BELL DINGING)
No, I just...
CAMILLE: (VOICE BREAKING) No.
Honey, honey, Something's wrong.
Camille, what's going on?
CAMILLE: / just... My mother...
Come on, Cubby. Talk to me.
My mother did it. My mother did it.
(EXHALES)
FRANK: Camille, listen to me.
You're under a lot of stress.
I was very wrong
to send you down there.
What I need you to do now
is go to the nearest airport
and fly back home here.
CAMILLE: No.
Charge the ticket.
I'll pay you back when you get here,
but I really need you
to get home now, Camille.
You understand?
No.
(SNIFFLES)
She's doing it again,
and I need to take care of it.
-No, Camille...
-(LINE DISCONNECTS)
Camille?
Shit.
(MUSIC PLAYING ON RECORD)
(GAGGING)
ADORA: Get it all out.
-(COUGHING)
-Good girl.
(GROANING)
Good girl.
Oh.
-(AMMA CRYING)
-Oh.
(BABY CRIES)
ADORA: God has given me
another sick baby.
(MUSIC PLAYING ON CAR STEREO)
(MUSIC STOPS)
VICKERY: Hello, ladies.
-Hey, Chief.
So, the streets are safe
to skate on again, huh?
Well, as I recall, safe or not,
doesn't stop you girls.
What's gonna happen to John?
It's up to the system.
Where's your other roller pal?
Don't you three travel in a pack?
Her mama wouldn't let her come out.
-She's sick.
-VICKERY: Well, word of advice.
You keep your eyes open.
Some drunk comes
flying down this road,
he'll hit you before he sees you.
Or she. Don't be sexist, Chief.
(VICKERY CHUCKLES)
Sick.
(SNIFFLES)
(MUFFLED MUSIC PLAYING ON HEADPHONES)
(MUSIC PLAYS LOUDER)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)
(INAUDIBLE)