Shit.
Still in Wind Gap.
You be safe...
today.
Camille.
I wanna talk to you.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
Another time, OK?
- Yeah.
- So ugly.
Hey, sis!
Please don't be mad.
I was just pissed at you
for blowing me off last night.
I wasn't blowing you off.
I was doing my job.
With that hot cop.
I'd totally fuck him.
Shut up, Jodes.
My sister's boyfriend
you're talkin' about.
That's not my boyfriend.
Not yet,
but he likes you.
I can tell.
Please forgive me.
Sometimes when I show off
in front of my friends,
I get carried away.
I don't feel like
fightin' with you.
Wanna see something funny?
This kid at school, J.C.,
came up with a crazy meme.
Hilarious!
Everybody thinks he did it, huh?
- Want some?
- No. Thank you.
OK. Well, if you
change your mind,
we'll be out
behind the stables.
- Camille.
- What?
Don't tell Mama.
Oh, my God!
Is your hand
getting any better, dear?
You know us Crellin women.
Slow healers.
Oh, could you slice those
a tiny bit smaller, please?
Why aren't you ready?
I'm gonna have to ask you
to give my regrets to Jackie.
This cut on my hand
is giving me fits.
It's barely a scratch.
To you, maybe.
Well, I'm sure the ladies
will be disappointed
you're not there.
I'll be giving them
the gift they so enjoy--
the opportunity
to talk about me.
Luckily, I'l have you
there to defend me.
Well, I'm certain that occasion
will not arise.
In Wind Gap,
recyclables go out
on Wednesday.
Jesus Christ.
Make yourself
at home, Detective.
I hope you don't mind.
The door was open.
- What do you want?
- I need to know
why you're following
John Keene.
Who says I'm following
John Keene?
John Keene. I bumped
into him at the store.
He said, "Are you
following me, too?"
- That boy's paranoid.
- Come on.
There's only so many
cop cars in town.
What are you gettin' at?
We need to share information
before another little girl
in this town loses her teeth.
That's what I'm gettin' at.
And I'll go first, since I'm
the visiting team here, okay?
I'm meeting today
with the reporter.
- Who, Preaker girl?
- Yeah.
That woman knows something.
I don't know what it is.
Once she tells me,
I tell you.
How do you know
she'll tell you?
Call it intuition.
Well, in Wind Gap
we call that something else.
So, we have a deal?
What do you got for me?
Keene.
Keene!
I'm letting you go.
- What?
- Take off.
Excuse me, what?
You're done! Go home!
Are you fuckin' serious?
What did I do?
This fuckin' town.
Camille Preaker!
- Hey, honey.
- Hi, honey.
Hi.
She's here.
Mwah.
Where is that
mother of yours?
Uh, she is tending to
an injury, I'm afraid.
But she's fine. She just cut
her finger on some rose bushes.
But she really wanted
to be here.
Uh-huh. Well,
that's a crock of shit.
Adora'll be fine.
She's a fighter.
Calhoun Day is comin' up.
It always gets her spirits up.
Calhoun Day.
Is that a good idea?
That's a crime reporter's mind
at work right there.
Every suspect in town
is roamin' around Adora's lawn
with all that young,
fresh meat.
Good Lord, Jackie,
that is so morbid.
It's stupid is what it is.
Excuse me!
Hello! Excuse me.
Can we get some menus
over here, please?
Thank you.
So, Camille,
we're dyin' to know.
Who do you think did it?
We want the inside scoop.
Well, I want to know
what y'all think.
What is the matter
with that girl?
Well, I think
Anne's daddy--
Bob Nash.
He did it.
Now, that man
is a hot mess.
Every time I'm in the store,
all he does is stare
at my titties.
Well, everybody does that.
Maybe you should invest
in a better bra.
Besides, Bob Nash has always
had it in for the Keenes.
We all know why.
Now, that
is just plain gossip.
John Keene
and Julie Wheeler's
little Miss Perfect
cheerleading daughter, Ashley,
doing Lord knows what
in her own backyard.
Well, I want to make him
my boy slave.
I'll bet that boy
killed the Nash girl
and then killed his own sister
to cover up his tracks.
No, I don't-- No.
I don't think that John
killed his sister.
He seems a little sweet.
Too sweet, if you ask me.
- Oh, hush.
- That is one strange family,
and he is the strangest
of them all.
♪ Glory, glory, hallelujah ♪
♪ His truth is marching on ♪
♪ His truth
is marching on ♪
Zeke, you cannot go
and fight those Yankees.
Who will defend
our children?
I know you're afraid,
Miss Millie,
evil is about to descend
on Wind Gap.
What must be do,
my brave husband?
You must fight
as I fight.
I must go now, my love.
My men await me.
And so...
Millie Calhoun did what
was unthinkable at the time.
She taught the women
of Wind Gap to shoot.
And she formed
the first female militia
the world had ever seen.
Wah, wah, wah.
Very nice, guys.
Very imaginative.
Let's take a break.
I don't think he liked it.
Shut up, Jodes.
What do you know?
He's a freakin'
weirdo anyway.
Takes one to know one.
Didn't you like
our performance today?
It was entertaining.
There was never an all-female
militia in Wind Gap.
How do you know?
You weren't around.
My mama says all of history
was written by men, so...
of course they're gonna
make themselves look good.
History is history, Amma.
You can't change it,
you just learn from it.
That why you're
always so sad?
That because you can't
change your history?
Don't be sad,
Mr. Lacey.
Mom. Hey.
Come on, Mama.
Let's get you showered,
get some food in you.
All right? I got you.
Come on, I got you.
Dinner's ready.
Where the hell are you?
On the record?
Yeah.
Huh. What makes you so sure
he's gonna do that?
Because he's ambitious.
Cops like to see
their name in print.
And I look good today.
Yeah, so do I.
Hey, uh, how is it
being back home?
What doesn't kill you
makes you stronger.
Unless it kills you.
Thanks. I needed that.
And I need a new piece.
- You go get it.
- Yes, sir.
Not today, child.
Your mom isn't well.
You know, most first dates
are a dinner and a movie.
I get a tour
of crime scenes.
What does that say about you
that you think
this is a date?
Doesn't say much
about my social life, I guess.
No, it doesn't.
We had a deal,
remember?
You are gonna answer
a question on the record
for every crime scene
I show you.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, that's the deal.
That's the deal.
I get it.
All right, so,
crime scene number one.
Two teenage girls,
madly in love,
were found with
their wrists slashed.
One of 'em
left behind a child.
A baby, actually.
Oh, I went to school
with that baby.
Her name was
Faith Murray,
but everybody called her
"Fag" Murray,
like it was hereditary
or something.
- Kind of ironic, considering.
- What?
Well, Faith had sex
with a bunch of boys
to prove that she wasn't
a lesbian like her mother.
But no one ever
found a knife, so...
murder-suicide.
- That's strange.
- Yeah.
What ever happened
to your friend Faith?
She paid for the sins
of a mother
that she had never met.
So, instead of being a lesbian,
she became a slut.
See, in Wind Gap,
every woman gets
a nasty label if
they don't conform
to the rules
of engagement.
What's your label?
No, no. Too many.
Too many to name.
- Oh, come on.
- No.
I can handle it.
That is so
Wind Gap of you.
You know?
You figure out someone's secrets
to use it
against 'em later.
No, that's not my style.
Okay, well, it's
my turn now, okay?
You have to answer
one question on the record.
- So official.
- Thank you.
All right, why'd
you become a cop?
- Really?
- I like to take
my interviewees
off-guard.
You like to suck up
to your interviewees
So you get
more information out of 'em.
Gosh, you're so smart.
When I was a kid,
I wanted to be a vet,
and I volunteered
at this animal shelter.
I'd see the animals come in
burned, tortured, mutilated.
I got less interested
in treating the animals
and more interested in catching
the animals who did that to 'em.
You volunteered
at an animal shelter.
Don't tell anyone.
I won't.
Your secret
is safe with me.
Even in Wind Gap.
So, for various
reasons, this...
is what they call
"the end zone."
Double entendre
intended.
This is where the football team
would have their way
with that week's
lucky cheerleader.
- Ninth grade, you said.
- Yep.
Makes me sick.
- Were the police notified?
- Of course not.
Some people would
call that rape, you know.
Eh, some people
would call that
consensual, you know?
Wait, who are you
talking about?
Were you one of the girls?
If I say yes, you'll think
less of me, or you'll
feel sorry for me.
No, I'd think those guys
took advantage of someone
way too young to make
an informed decision.
- Typical.
- What?
Well, a boy has sex
with five girls,
they're gonna put up
a statue in his honor.
- You know? Yeah.
- Yeah, double standards exist.
But having your way
with somebody,
that sounds criminal.
Literally.
Even on game night.
But now that I know
your feeling
on the subject,
have a sip.
Bless your heart.
Bless your heart
very much.
What's your
second question?
That tire sample that you
took off of Bob Nash's car,
- Yeah?
- where was the tread?
- Did it match?
- That's two questions.
That's a two-part question.
Give me that.
You know
it wasn't a match.
Well, that kind of
blows up my
Bob Nash-killed-
Natalie Keene
in-revenge-for-Anne
theory.
You think
there's two Killers,
and Bob Nash
killed Natalie Keene?
That's a two-part question.
Um, I mean,
the teeth pulling matches,
but that could be a cover-up.
They were killed differently,
and one of the bodies
was hidden,
and the other
was put on display
for the whole town
to see, like,
"Fuck you, Wind Gap,
look what I can do."
Mm, that's
an interesting theory,
but Nash's alibi
checks out so far.
Yeah, well, a lot of women
think Nash is a pervert,
and sometimes perverts
like little girls.
That's where
the teeth pulling comes in.
In our guy's mind,
it's equivalent to rape.
It's about power...
for someone who
feels powerless.
Stay.
Hello, Amma.
Did you catch
the killer yet?
Is your mama home?
You didn't?
Shouldn't, uh,
you be out there
looking for him?
Well, you're certainly
your mama's daughter--
I'll give you that.
Is there a problem, Chief?
Oh, I just came by
to discuss something with Adora.
She's in bed, resting.
Mama, Chief Vickery's here.
Oh...
Is everything okay?
Yes. I was just hoping
you and I could have a word.
Of course.
Give me a moment
to put myself together.
Uh, Alan,
please fix
the Chief a drink.
Gayla?
Well, I assume
you'll have the usual.
Mm-hmm.
Take a seat.
This place
I already know about.
Ann and Natalie
used to play here.
Creepy place for two
young girls to hang out.
No?
Yeah.
The way these killings
went down,
it makes sense they knew
their attacker, right?
I'm certain of it.
Certain? Why?
This guy's a hunter.
Hunters track their prey.
Where do they lead to?
A clearing.
This shed.
It's no coincidence
that the only two girls
that were killed in this town
used to play here.
He probably
hid out there
waiting for them,
watching them.
Waiting for one
to arrive before the other
so they'd be alone,
and then-- then he struck.
Well, I thought that Ann
was taken from her bike.
That's what they said,
but they never found it,
so could've happened here.
Well, that's an
interesting theory,
but there's
no proof of that.
No, but I'm getting close.
Someone in this town
is hiding something.
What makes you say that?
People are getting nervous.
Oh.
Did something happen
to you in that shed?
Good instincts, KC.
You holding out on me?
I might be.
And I was under
the impression
you were starting
to like me.
No.
How's your hand, dear?
- Better, thank you.
- Oh, good.
Mm.
Ow.
The roses.
If you'll excuse me.
How's Jocelyn?
Fine.
Sends her love.
Well, that's sweet.
Send it back, of course.
Of course.
Is there a break
in the case?
You'd be the first to know.
- However--
- Ah, the "however."
Mm. Calhoun Day, Adora.
It's not appropriate
given the events.
Mm-mm.
I think the town needs
a bit of frivolity,
don't you think,
given the events?
Possibly.
Then why would you
have me cancel an event
that's been a part
of this town
for half a century?
Because I haven't
caught the killer.
Ahh.
Well, you do have
the power as chief,
to do whatever's
in the interest
of public safety.
I do.
And some have the power
in this town...
to remove you as chief.
Oh, that's what I love
about you, Adora.
You never pull
your punches.
That's the only thing?
We need to talk
about your daughters.
What about them?
Well, one of them
is dangerous,
and the other one's
in danger.
I'm working on some things.
Any "some thing"
you'd like to share?
The girls were dead
when their teeth
were pulled, right?
Yeah, that's enough questions.
One more.
What about John Keene?
He seems, maybe,
too broken up
over the whole thing--
could be an act.
Well, his sister
was murdered.
Yeah, but I'm a guy,
and teenage boys,
they would sooner die
than cry in public.
Oh, look who's here.
Everything okay?
Kansas City.
Miss Preaker.
No need for alarm.
Just a friendly house visit.
Yeah. I'd like
to hear all about
your conversation
later on.
And I yours.
Good night.
What was that
all about?
Small town cop,
big time problems.
Now we kiss?
I'm an unconventional girl.
That's what you
like about me.
Shit.
I'm sorry, Mama.
You just scared me.
Sorry.
l... I couldn't sleep
with everything that's
going on around here.
Yeah, well...
You don't need
to worry about me.
I'm okay.
Okay.
How was La Mere?
Um, it was good.
The ladies
were disappointed
that you didn't come.
You were always
so willful.
Excuse me?
Never sweet.
I-l remember when you
were about six or seven.
I wanted to put
your hair up in curlers
for your school picture.
Instead, you cut it all off
with my fabric shears.
No.
No, no, no, Mama.
That wasn't me.
- I think you're--
- When I was expecting
with you, I thought
you'd save me.
I thought you'd love me,
and then my...
my mother would love me.
Even from the beginning,
you disobeyed.
You wouldn't--
wouldn't eat,
like-- like you were
punishing me
for being born.
You made me
feel like a fool,
like a...
like a child.
You were a child.
And now you
come back here...
...and all
I can think is...
What? What, Mama”?
You smell ripe.
You gonna finish soon?
Wait, what are you doing?
I'm gonna go
for a ride.
I'll let you put it inside me.
Can I get you anything else,
Miss Camille?
No, thank you.
Gayla, all these years...
We both know how Adora is.
Why did you stay?
Not a lot of choice
in Wind Gap.
You got domestic work.
You got the hog farm.
I don't like pigs.
Besides...
Miss Crellin's bark
is worse than her bite.
They're both pretty bad
if you ask me.
Good night,
Miss Camille.
I'm glad to see that
that hand of yours
is doing better.
- Me, too.
- Yeah.
I was just wondering
if you needed me
for anything
else tonight.
I can't think
of anything.
You know, I lost
a daughter, too.
What are you saying?
I don't think that you've
ever stopped to consider that.
It's late.
Marian was taken
from me, too, Adora,
and I would just like
to see some appreciation
for how I have borne that.
What you're saying--
What do you
want me to say?
Thank you?
Nobody asked you
to suffer in silence.
How is it that you
show more compassion
for the local
civil servants
than for your
own husband?
How is that?
If you are speaking
about the Chief,
I am-- I am done
with this conversation.
Hmm. Seemed to me
you could talk
to him all night.
It's Camille,
- isn't it?
- Oh, come on, now.
She brings discord
into this house.
Not everything
is that girl's fault,
and you know it.
Why are you
trying to hurt me?
Hurt?
You have a very peculiar idea
of the word, "hurt," dear.
Stay.
Vickery, Jocelyn know
that you're out
calling on another woman
late at night?
Not if you don't tell her.
I need you help.
Okay.
What is Adora
not telling me
about the Preaker girl?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Can I have two
of those? Thanks.
Thank you.
Oh, these are, uh,
both mine, actually.
- Oh.
- I'm kidding.
I could totally
two-fist it right now.
Bad day?
Yeah, my mom is--
My mom is losing it.
And your mom had me
fired from my job today.
My mom fired you.
It's okay.
It's not really
a fun place to work.
Pigs are smart, you know?
They know what's
happening to them.
Or... what's
about to happen.
That's why they
shit so much.
‘Cause they're afraid.
Do you ever
get over it?
- Losing a job?
- Losing a sister.
I wish I could
tell you "yes",
but that would be a lie.
People in this town
actually believe
that I killed her.
Yeah, I know.
If it means anything
to you, I don't.
Natalie collected spiders.
Did you know that?
No.
She got into some trouble
back in Philly.
That's where we
used to live.
What kind of trouble,
if you don't mind me asking?
She got mad at a girl
for stealing her pencil.
So, she took it back
from her and, uh...
...she stuck it
in her eye.
Jesus.
Please, do not put
that in your story.
I've never told this
to anyone before.
I won't.
Bob always thought
Ann was on the--
the straight-and-narrow path
before she met Natalie--
the "devil child."
That's what he
used to call her.
I think they were
two peas in a pod,
those two--
those two weirdos.
Nothing wrong with that.
I'm a weirdo.
Yeah, me, too, I guess.
I always thought
those girls
were gonna end up
killing each other.
They were always
going at it.
Amma was the only thing that
stood between them some days.
Amma?
Yeah. Yeah, she was always
keeping 'em off each other.
I knew that Adora
tutored the girls,
but I didn't know that
Amma was close with them.
Oh, yeah.
I guess the three
would all go play
in that creepy
hunting shed.
You okay?
Fuck, dude!
Fuck.