(MAN HUMMING)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
(CAR HONKS)
(DISTANT CHATTER)
Hurt me if you can,
but my wounds will heal
stronger than before,
and my scars will armor me.
I will never give up my husband!
I will never betray my town!
(ALL LAUGHING)
ADORA: Alan?
ALAN: Look at you. Perfection.
-Can you...
-Yeah.
ALAN: Today celebrates
what is unmovable about this place.
About us.
I just want things to be nice.
And it will be.
It's gonna be
the best Calhoun Day ever.
Now, which jacket do you like?
FRANK: People are talking, Cubby.
This story is blowing up.
CAMILLE: Do not say "blowing up."
We are both too old for "blowing up."
FRANK: Well, it's got more hits
than our site's ever got.
What do the kids call that?
Look, we need to feed this thing.
Can you turn me around
a new installment in 24 to 487
CAMILLE: 48, maybe.
We need more about those girls.
Who were their best friends?
What's the pattern here?
What the hell's wrong with this town?
Well, that I cannot fit
into 800 words.
FRANK: Big picture. Rotting America.
Fall of Rome stuff.
Yeah, it's more like
the fall of the South.
My backyard's about
to be littered with Confederate flags.
FRANK: Oh, now, that's good. You gotta
milk the shit out of that cow.
Yeah, I'm not sure
those two metaphors go together.
-You been drinking?
-(FRANK LAUGHS)
Funny girl.
Hey, kid, I'm proud of you.
CAMILLE: Yeah,
I'll get on it. Thanks.
FRANK: You're doing...
(DISTANT CHATTER)
(CLATTERING)
ADORA: If it's the floor
your readers want,
the light flatters it best
from the doorway.
You a shutterbug, Mrs. Crellin?
I just... I know this floor,
and this house has been
a part of my family for ages.
There's soldiers' blood on this floor.
My mother was a Calhoun.
She married into the Preakers.
They had the money,
the Calhouns had the house.
That's never gonna make it
into the magazine. Anyway...
(PHOTOGRAPHER LAUGHS)
No, it's just...
I am just the photographer.
Good background.
ADORA: Oh, this was added in the '30s.
And do you see
where the ivory ends here?
Lean times for the...
For the Calhouns.
And of course,
you can't get ivory anymore.
Camille!
No, no, that's... That's all right.
And youe shoes.
ADORA: How many times...
(GASPS) Camille!
PHOTOGRAPHER: It's fine,
it's fine. See?
ADORA: Thank you.
(PHONE VIBRATING)
Hey. Uh, call me back
when you have a minute.
I want to talk to you
about this article I just read.
Beautiful.
Right on Calhoun Day.
CLYDE: Here you go.
VICKERY: K.C.
(MUSIC PLAYING ON RECORD)
Well, it's tradition.
Wear it every year.
I gotta look my best.
Yeah, I still think
your tradition's a bad idea.
Be right with you, Detective.
RICHARD: Take your time.
Can't call it off now. Besides,
-people need to blow off steam.
-That's what I'm afraid of.
Well, you should
have thought of that before.
"Wind Gap victims knew Killer.
"Police scrutinize community.
"Sources close
to the investigation... "
-I like that word, "close."
-I didn't tell her anything
she hadn't figured out already.
And I got something out of it, too.
Ooh, I hope you did, son.
Now everybody's all het up,
going on about Keene and Nash.
I never mentioned them.
She never mentioned them.
I don't know how many folks
sent me this article
in the space of two hours.
And you still think it's a good idea
to get these het-up people
convened in one place?
You ask me,
if you cancel
you're asking for trouble.
There's a lot of folks ready to drink,
and no place to be? No, thank you.
There you go.
I doubled the detail.
I got good men and true
coming in from up county.
I'm not worried about Calhoun Day.
Thank you, Clyde.
A little worried
about you, though, son.
Your Preaker girl?
Good tree, bad apple.
Hey. There's things
about her you don't know.
You watch yourself.
VICKERY: And Kansas City,
if you're coming,
don't dress like a Union soldier.
-Thank you, Clyde!
-Chief.
ADORA: Anything with fleurs-de-lis
is gonna be dining room service.
Without is veranda.
AMMA: Mama,
will you run lines with me?
ADORA: In a minute, sweet.
And of course, anything past
the tents is plastic ware.
It's a big job.
Thank you. These look beautiful.
-CAMILLE: I'll do it.
-It's okay.
-Okay...
-l want Camille to do it.
Camille never liked
our pageant history.
Did you?
No, I just thought
it was an odd thing to celebrate.
-But I don't mind.
-I'm Millie Calhoun.
You're the Yankee rapist.
All right. "You're gonna tell us
where he's hiding,
"girl, or else."
I will never give up my husband.
I will never betray my town!
You'll have to burn this tree down.
I forgot how creepy this play was.
Tried to change it,
but Mr. Lacey wouldn't go for it.
Just let it be. It is what it is.
You said it's that way
only because it's written by men.
Wow, you did, now? Wow.
So you're a feminist?
That is not what
you're wearing to the party, is it?
It's a barbecue,
and I'm wearing jeans.
It's not a barbecue.
And you're in all black.
On Calhoun Day?
Well, I'm not really a part of it.
Folks don't understand that, Camille.
You're under my roof.
Field trip to find you
something appropriate.
ADORA: Let's go!
Just girls. Hear that, Alan?
Yes, dear.
(LAUGHS)
She's so easy to rile.
My other phone. Don't tell Mama.
You have Ann and Natalie in there?
You guys were friends, right?
You used to hang out with them?
Not that much.
I mean, like, a million years ago.
-Seventh grade.
-ADORA: Alan?
-ALAN: Coming.
-That was, like, a year ago.
Do you feel like
you can talk to me about them?
-On the record?
-Come on.
Kidding.
I just...
I don't like to think about them.
It scares me.
I feel bad,
because we weren't friends
anymore when it happened.
They still wanted to,
like, play in the woods,
build forts and shit.
Kid stuff.
(AMMA SIGHS)
You guys used to hang out
in that hunting shed?
Shit.
"Wind Gap protects its own'
"You hear that a lot
in a small Missouri town.
"But two grisly child murders
have changed
-"the meaning of 'protect."
-Don't read that.
Don't read that.
Where did you get that?
Kelsey. Jodes shared it to her.
"Sources close to the investigation
"confirm that the local community... "
(SCOFFS) John, right?
"Is under scrutiny."
Can you keep it down, please?
Holy shit. Three more people
just shared it to me.
Shared it "with" you. And put it away.
Fucking Jodes saw this before I did?
ADORA: Girls! Let's go.
AMMA: Bitch.
(IT'S IMPOSSIBLE PLAYING)
ADORA: Oh,
she still has that ugly grate.
Such a shame
people in town feel the need
for that sort of thing.
SARABETH: Good morning!
We have some great things
set aside for you ladies today.
And who is this lovely creature?
This is my eldest daughter.
-Camille. It's a pleasure.
-Hello.
She takes after her father.
His coloring, his temperament.
How are your hands? I heard.
ADORA: Roses are so cruel
to my soft skin.
(IT'S IMPOSSIBLE CONTINUES PLAYING)
That's more than I ever
heard you say about my father.
There's not much else to say.
Mama, help me pick.
I've got this one. Or these.
Give me a minute, sweet.
I must concentrate on
this five-alarm fire here.
-AMMA: Come in the dressing room.
-Amma, give me a minute.
No.
AMMA: Camille wrote a new article.
-Everyone's talking about it.
-What's that?
She said it's either John Keene
or Bob Nash who killed those girls.
No, I just said that authorities
think it might be a local.
AMMA: ".. Mexicans or drifters
or truckers."
-Amma.
-Says it in the article, plain as day.
-"Wind Gap kills its children."
-Stop!
Right now!
(WINCES)
Oh, you've made me bleed.
Both of you.
SARABETH: I'm not sure
of your taste, Camille,
but I think you'd look
lovely in these.
ADORA: Oh. Sarabeth,
you do have an eye.
Why don't you take Camille
to the dressing room
while I pick out something for Amma?
Right this way, darling.
Amma.
SARABETH: And you let me know
if I can get you anything else.
CAMILLE: Oh, you know what?
-I think I would like to try this one.
-Okay.
-AMMA: Mama? This one?
-SARABETH: There you go.
Can I please have the one
that I picked out, please?
Excuse me, Sarabeth?
ADORA: You all right in there?
Where are my clothes?
ADORA: Which one fits better?
Well, none of these are gonna work.
-ADORA: Just try one!
-AMMA: What's wrong?
Your sister's being stubborn.
Can you have her go wait in the car?
-Why?
-I have no idea why.
CAMILLE: Amma,
just go wait in the car.
Can you have her go wait in the car?
Amma, can you just wait in the car?
Camille, just let me see you.
I have got to get home,
for heaven's sake!
CAMILLE: You happy?
ADORA: Go wait in the car.
ADORA: Go.
That's what you wanted, right?
It's worse than I remember.
You weren't there at the end.
So it's over?
Yes.
Hardly matters. You're ruined.
All out of spite. You want to know
who your father was?
That's who he was.
All spite. I'm glad Amma saw.
(SCREAMS)
I'm sorry.
I started it
with the article. I didn't...
I didn't think she'd...
I didn't know about your...
I'm sorry. I was mad.
Did it hurt?
‘Cause I know a girl like you.
Not like you, but...
(SIGHS) She says it doesn't hurt
because the cut's already there
under the skin.
The knife just lets it out.
Your friend sounds like
an after-school special.
What's that?
-Do you have my name on there?
-I don't do names.
-Not even boyfriends?
-I don't do boyfriends.
AMMA: Come on,
I want to show you something.
Please.
POLICEMAN: (OVER RADIQ) Chief,
we've gotta respond to a 288.
-VICKERY: Copy that. I'm here.
-WOMAN: Be safe out there.
(CHILDREN CHATTERING)
Come on, you don't want
to miss your turn.
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
Wait for me!
Please stay.
I don't know if I can.
If I can, you can.
(LAUGHS)
WOMAN: Well, lookit here.
Veranda girls,
35 Calhoun Days running.
-Got to be a record.
-It's classic Adora.
"On this special day,
"everyone is welcome in my home.
-"P.S. Don't come in my home."
-(LAUGHTER)
That's so true.
WOMAN: Oh.
Hello, Avery!
Oh, thank you for coming to my party.
I love you.
You okay?
And there is
our most beautiful hostess.
Ladies, enjoy.
Girls. (LAUGHS)
It's good to see you.
Jackie, you finding everything?
Everything found me.
ADORA: Well, enjoy,
and please save some liquor
-for the rest of us.
-(ALL LAUGH)
-I enjoyed Camille's article.
-Oh, I haven't read it.
JACKIE: You should
really take a look at it.
You should.
It's honest, it's refreshing,
-it's timely.
-As are you.
Cheers, ladies.
Okay.
ADORA: Hello, boys.
I think that I should probably
just head home, okay?
FRANK: What are you talking about?
Just give it a few more days.
Cubby, you holding up?
Um...
Well, I guess that's not
for you to worry about, is it?
FRANK: Oh.
Look, I thought that
sending you home would help,
but I forget sometimes
how parents aren't always
good for their kids.
(FRANK SIGHS)
-Camille?
-Yeah.
It's just that whenever I'm here,
I just...
(CRYING) I feel like a bad person.
(CAMILLE CRYING)
Oh, Camille.
Camille, you are
one of the most decent people I know,
and there aren't that
many decent people left in the world.
With my folks gone,
it's pretty much down
to you and Eileen.
-No, I'm not decent.
-FRANK: Camille, you are.
No, I'm not.
FRANK: Even to the most worthless
pieces of shit.
Hey, why do you think
I keep you around?
It's not because
you're a great reporter.
(FRANK CHUCKLING)
Kiddo, was that funny?
I meant it to be funny.
You know I'm funnier when I drink.
I'm not allowed to drink.
So here's the deal.
Go get a drink. Make it a double.
FRANK: Camille.
You want to come home, kiddo?
No.
I should see this through.
That's my Cubby.
You know we're here for you.
CAMILLE: Thanks.
-We'll talk soon.
-Okay.
-Bye.
-FRANK: Bye.
(SIGHS)
Fuck it.
Oh, fuck, no.
-Kansas City.
-Chief.
I'd like you to meet my wife, Jocelyn.
Ma'am. Pleasure to meet you.
Detective Willis.
I've heard so much about you.
Well, I hope I can change
your opinion of me.
Charming, as advertised.
Don't flatter yourself, Betty Sue.
Come on, honey.
-Have a great day, Detective.
-Happy Calhoun Day.
-Hey.
-RICHARD: Yeah.
JACKIE: Camille Preaker!
Why don't you come over here,
hang out with us for a little bit?
That does sound delightful,
but I can't right now.
Maybe later.
My, my. Those Crellin girls
sure do like their boys with badges.
(JACKIE CHUCKLES)
What's up, James?
BOB: Hey, Big City.
RICHARD: Hey, Bob.
What the hell you doing here?
It's Calhoun Day.
I'm just enjoying the festivities.
-Really?
-Yeah.
You sure you're not following me?
You're the one that came up to me.
-Hey.
-Do yourself a favor
and don't touch me again.
You got it?
Is this a joke to you?
I lost a kid, remember?
(CLEARS THROAT)
It's no joke, Bob. Okay?
Look, I'm telling ya,
we're gonna get this guy.
There'll be justice.
Oh.
What, are you gonna...
You gonna strangle him
and rip out his teeth?
That'd be justice, wouldn't it?
All I'm asking you to do
is lock him up.
Jesus, he's right over there.
You cut my stuff? All of it?
I gave you good stuff.
I gave you John. We had a deal.
-There was no deal, Ashley.
-I am John's only advocate...
-Let's just go.
-No. We are not leaving.
You don't want to burn this bridge.
I know things, Camille.
Come on.
-Let's keep it that way.
-Yep.
-Hey. There she is.
-Hi, guys.
Read your article, Big City.
Where'd you learn to write like that?
Couldn't have been here.
Where'd you learn to read like that?
-(MEN LAUGH)
-Hey, we're starting a pool.
Nash or Keene.
Who you got your money on, Preaker?
-It was the brother, right?
-I'm gonna get myself a beer.
-Now, don't go.
-Say, Camille.
Why don't we take
a little tour around the grounds
and get reacquainted?
I bet your wife
would just love that, huh?
She won't mind.
One of us has gotta get some.
These gentlemen
bothering you, Miss Preaker?
-No.
-Excuse me?
No, no. Come on.
You ain't in Kansas anymore, Toto.
All right?
CAMILLE: Let's just enjoy
the festivities.
Son of a bitch.
Can't-get-laid motherfucker.
-Yeah.
-It ain't me.
No, no, no, it ain't me
CAMILLE: You feeling all manly now?
RICHARD: No, no,
just a little frustrated,
‘cause the girl
I'm seeing won't call me back.
CAMILLE: Oh, we're seeing each other?
-We are now.
-Hm.
Plus, she wrote
this inconvenient article
about my case.
Published it on
the worst day possible.
Well, she has a talent for that.
WOMAN: Can I help you?
MAN: Yeah, I'll take two beers
and a glass of wine.
WOMAN: Here you go.
Can you carry all that?
MAN: I got it.
JOCELYN: Adora.
ADORA: Welcome. Hello.
Thank you for having us.
-The town needed it, don't you think?
-Yes.
How's the case coming, Chief?
It appears my daughter
has some notions.
Do you share them?
Well, I'm afraid...
(CLEARS THROAT)
I'm not at liberty
to comment, Mrs. Crellin.
Oh. Yes, well... Enjoy the barbecue.
Thank you. (CHUCKLES)
You look beautiful, as always.
Thank you so much.
CAMILLE: Jodes.
Lovely, beautiful girl.
So, what is this thing, anyway?
Calhoun Day.
So what, it's Confederate pride?
We don't use the "C-word" here
in Missouri.
Right. Bite my tongue.
Silent racism is best.
So, Zeke Calhoun,
our founding pedophile,
he fought for the South,
and his child-bride, Millie Calhoun,
she was my great-great-great
grand-victim or something.
She was from a Union family.
Hell of a pairing.
Yeah, well, one day,
the Union soldiers
come down here
to collect hubby, dead or alive.
But brave Millie, who is with child,
she refuses to give Zeke up,
she resists.
But it's how she resists
that people in this town just love.
The Union soldiers,
they tied her to a tree,
did horrible things to her.
Violations.
But Millie never said a word.
Lost the baby.
The end. Applause.
And this is a holiday?
We don't have a lot
of happy stories around here.
Yeah. I got that on our first date.
Mm? That was a date?
I don't know. I'm just fishing here.
Don't beat anyone up.
Oh.
WOMAN: Camille! How are you, sweetie?
I'm good, thank you.
I was just looking for Amma.
We need to calm her down.
She's a little nervous. Stage fright.
There isn't enough beer
at this party to calm her down.
I mean, you didn't hear this from me,
-but she's a bit of a wild...
-Gretchen.
Whose lawn are you standing on, honey?
Well, thank you
for not telling me, Gretchen.
WOMAN: Look who's putting on airs now.
I hate her dress.
Kansas City, here I come.
No, no, no, it ain't me
JOCELYN: Confederate and Union
soldiers drinking together. (LAUGHS)
Detective.
-Mrs. Crellin.
-It's so good of you to come.
Thank you
for your hospitality. This...
-This place is amazing.
-Would you like a tour?
I could have a plate sent up
to the house if you like.
I don't want you
to go to any trouble. That's okay.
Well, it's no trouble at all.
My home is your home.
(CHATTER, LAUGHTER)
ADORA: Amma.
Mama.
This is Nathan.
He just wanted to see the dollhouse.
-Ma'am.
-ADORA: Hello.
Your sister's waiting to rehearse
with you backstage.
AMMA: She is?
Yes. You better get down there.
My daughters might be a lot of things,
but they really do care
for one another.
Uh...
This wallpaper is hand-painted
on silk from Paris.
Inside invite. That's a first.
Hey. Have you seen Amma?
I think she went back to the house.
Okay. Thanks.
KIRK: Camille.
I'm glad you're back.
That makes one of us.
(LAUGHS)
(SIGHS) I always knew
you'd get out of here.
Thanks.
I've thought a lot about you.
Camille Preaker.
Good luck with the play.
Guess who's inside with your mama.
Mama said you wanted
to rehearse with me.
I did. I just got something
that I need to do.
I'll run lines with you, sweetheart.
I'm fine, thanks.
This ivory floor,
all ivory, was a wedding present
for my great-great-grandmother.
Before anybody knew
what "endangered" was.
(LAUGHS)
It was supposed to last forever.
-And it has, just.
-Mm.
Things fall apart awful quick.
Good things, good people, gone,
just like that.
Richard, some people
don't understand loss,
because some people haven't lost.
But the people here...
And I know all this
must seem strange to you,
these country folk,
our backward ways...
No, ma'am, I never said that.
I don't want
to tell you your business.
It's your job to see the bad in us.
That's not my job, Mrs. Crellin.
I just want to remind you,
there's good here, too.
No matter what you might have heard.
Would you mind
taking your shoes off, please?
-Sure.
-Thank you.
You've spent time
with my daughter lately.
We're both after the same thing.
And what might that be?
ANNOUNCER: Ten minutes
to showtime, everyone.
Ten minutes to showtime.
WOMAN: Camille? Camille.
You know the detective, Willis,
from Kansas City?
-Yeah, I've talked to him.
-Which way is he leaning?
To the left, if you ask me.
Stop it!
You know what I mean.
We think it's Nash.
They don't really tell me much.
Well, your piece
said it was John or Bob Nash...
CAMILLE: No, I didn't say that
it was John or Bob Nash.
Someone should tell that to Bob.
(LAUGHS)
GRETCHEN: Wouldn't it be nice
if he did it?
WOMAN: You're such a class act,
Gretchen.
GRETCHEN: Then it wouldn't have
to be sweetie John.
WOMAN: Windfall for the inmates.
(LAUGHS)
GRETCHEN: You must think we're awful.
ADORA: She lost a sister, you know?
I do. I'm sorry.
Camille's strength went with her.
People avoid the topic.
But I can speak of it.
Camille can't.
Even now, she's recovering
from a recent episode.
She's delicate.
A rare rose.
But not without thorns.
You should come
to our Pity Party tomorrow night.
It's a tradition,
we sit around, we watch Beaches,
and we cry and we cry.
-It's fun.
-CAMILLE: I don't think that I can.
You'll get a month's worth of articles
in the first 10 minutes.
Plus, it'll be a giggle.
It'll be like old times.
-Please, Camille?
-Okay, sure. Why not? Right?
Oh, yay.
Wear something kicky.
Okay.
-RICHARD: Quite a place.
-Yeah, it is.
I'm starting to get
a picture of your upbringing.
CAMILLE: What did she say?
Did I do something wrong?
Is your mother off-limits?
Is that part of the tradition?
No. I'm sorry.
No.
The only Calhoun Day tradition
you really need to respect is
drinking enough
to get through Calhoun Day.
KIRK: All right, boys and girls.
Showtime.
(DRUM ROLL)
There you go.
I just can't believe that
she didn't use any of my stuff.
That bitch.
(DRUM ROLL CONTINUES)
(DRUM ROLL STOPS)
Why must men always fight?
I know you're afraid.
Evil is about to descend on Wind Gap.
What must we do, my brave husband?
At the first sign of trouble,
you must flee.
So what did she say, really?
A lot. I know a lot.
About that floor
made of elephant tusks.
Kinda fucked-up standing on it,
for a guy that wanted to
be an animal doctor.
That's all she talked about?
Was there something else
she should have said?
That you could take advantage
of me maybe, when I'm drunk?
(CHUCKLES)
AMMA: Zeke, you cannot go
and fight those Yankees.
Who will defend our children?
GIRL: The Yankees are coming!
AMMA: I will distract them.
Once I do, you'll get help.
(AUDIENCE GASPING)
BOY: You are a Union woman.
You've honored your bond.
You best tell us
where he's hiding, girl...
-KIRK: (WHISPERING) Or else.
-Or else.
(AUDIENCE LAUGHING)
Do with me what you will.
Hurt me if you can,
but my wounds will heal
stronger than before!
My scars will armor me.
I will never give up my husband!
I will never betray my town!
You'll have to burn this tree down!
(DRUM ROLL)
(MOCK GROANING)
(PIANO MUSIC PLAYS)
(GIGGLING)
(WHISTLES, APPLAUSE)
(SINGING)
-BOB: You son of a...
-(ASHLEY SCREAMS)
ASHLEY: Somebody get him offl
-Ammal
-Get him off!
ADORA: Amma!
Look out! Look out!
Get out of the way!
Woo!
-All right! All right!
-Fucking killed my daughter!
-God damn!
-Look out! Look out!
-Fucking pervert!
-Bob, shut the fuck up!
POLICE OFFICER: Go on. Go on.
BOB: Did I get you there, John?
(BOB LAUGHS) Woo!
Take that, you candy-ass.
Baby killer!
ALAN: I think the situation
has been resolved, so...
Why don't we give
another round of applause
to our fine,
young Wind Gap performers here?
And for Mr. Kirk Lacey,
who set all of this up!
-Come on, have some water.
-No.
-Please?
-She left without her phone.
(CRYING) She never leaves
without her phone.
Well, she might have
her other one. Right?
What other one?
Three hundred people
and no one saw a thing.
Adora, it's gonna be okay.
We're gonna check the woods.
We got some men together, all right?
-I mean, my God! My God!
-Sweetheart, please.
(SHRIEKING)
Ammal
Come on, boys.
ADORA: Amma!
Ammal
MAN: Amma?
(GASPS)
(DISTANT SHOUTS) Amma! Amma!
Ammal Amma!
Amma? Hey.
Amma, are you okay?
Amma, what the hell?
(AMMA CRYING)
CAMILLE: I've got her!
She's shaken up, scratched.
Poor thing.
So, what? She claims she ran away
‘cause she was upset about the play?
ADORA: She's not really up to talking.
The important thing is
she's all right.
Yeah.
Would you have a drink
with me on the veranda?
Please?
I wanted to apologize.
No, Mama... Mama, you don't have to.
I just... wasn't thinking,
and I should have
told my editor to wait
on the article, so...
Mama, can I talk to you about Amma?
She's scared of something.
I think that's the reason
she's doing what she's doing.
What's she doing?
Her mood swings. Her acting out.
Oh, that's just being a teenager.
Well, I'm sure you'll do
what you think is best.
I try.
And I...
I appreciate you not telling
that detective about, um...
But, darling,
he'll find out, won't he?
I mean, not to be blunt, but...
When you get close...
I won't
get close. I don't. I never get close.
But that's what I wanted
to apologize for.
You can't get close.
That's your father.
And it's why I think...
I never loved you.
You were born to it,
that cold nature.
I hope that's some comfort to you.
(SONG PLAYING ON CAR STEREO)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(KNOCKING)
Let me see you.
It's okay.
Do you like that?
No.
My way.
We do it my way.
(MOANING)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)