2x01 : The Dundies
by Belkiss, Occeanne et Unfold
http://pmag.f2o.org/theofficeus/
Tonight is the Dundies, the annual employee
world's night here at Dunder Mifflin
and this is everybody's favorite day,
everybody looks forward to it.
Because, you know a lot of the people
here don't get trophies very often
like Meredith or Kevin. I mean, who's gonna
give Kevin an award ? Dunkin Donuts ?
Plus, bonus, it's really really funny.
So I..., you know an employee will go
home, and he'll tell his neighbor :
"Hey, did you get an award ?"
And the neighbor will say :
"No man, I mean I slave all day,
nobody notices me."
Next thing you know, employee smells something
terrible coming from the neighbor’s house :
Neighbor’s hanged himself,
due to lack of recognition.
So you're ready for the Dundies ?
You know what they say about a car wreck
where it's so awful you can't look away ?
The Dundies are like a car wreck that
you want to look away
but you have to stare at it
because your boss is making you.
It's fat Halpert
- What ?
- Fat Halpert, Jim Halpert.
So why don't I take you on a
tour of past Dundee winners ?
We got fat Jim Halpert here, Jim why don't
you show off your Dundies to the camera ?
Oh I can't, because I keep them hidden,
I don't wanna look at them and get cocky.
- Oh, that's a good idea.
- And mine are at home,
in a display case about my bed.
TMI, TMI my friend.
TMI ? Too Much Information.
It's just easier to say TMI. I used to
say "Don't Go There" but that's lame.
And here we have Stanley the manly, now
Stanley is a Dundee Allstar, aren’t you
Stan ?
Why don't you show them some of your bling ?
I don't know where they are,
I think I threw them out.
- Oh, no you didn't.
- I think I did.
Why did...?
Say, we gotta order some
more appetizers this time.
- We ran out last year, remember ?
- Yes we should, you know what ?
I wanted one of those skillets of cheese,
but when I got on stage,
someone had eaten all of them.
To Oscar Martinez,
It's the "Show Me The Money" award !
Michael has taped every Dundies Awards,
and now he's making me look through
hours of footage to find highlights.
That's the type of song
we're gonna play to the ladies,
Hit it Dwight !
A little bit of Pam, all night long.
A little bit of Angela, on the sing.
A little bit of...
This is the part where Kevin stands in front
of the camcorder all night. It's great.
- It was you.
- It wasn't me, I swear.
So what's the joke ?
You're not perfect either !
- We're not laughing at you Dwight !
- So who are you laughing at ?
- Just something somebody wrote.
- Who ? Dave Barry ?
No, no. That was just something that
was written on the ladies room wall.
What is it ? Who wrote it ?
- It's kind of private,
- It's about Michael !
That is defacement of company
property, so you'd better tell me.
Kelly, if you tell me,
you'll be punished less.
- Ok, now I'm laughing at you !
Will her highness Jan Levinson Gould be
descending from her corporate throne
this evening to visit us lowly serfs here,
Dunder Mifflin Scranton ?
- It's a two and a half hour drive
from New York Michael.
- Well, you could take the bus, you could
work on the way here, sleep on the way home.
- No.
Come on Jan this is important, I mean,
this is validation to my employees here
that you and corporate approved of this.
We don't approve of this Michael.
You only have the budget for
one office party a year so,
we're not paying for this.
- Are you here ?
- Yeah, I'm here, I just wanted to
talk to you for a second about that.
What..., what is..., I mean, come on Jan !
You're dropping a A-bomb on me here !
- Really ? I'm dropping an atomic bomb on you.
- Well, yeah, what is... no you can't !
- You already had a party
on May 5th for no reasons ?
No reasons ? It was the 05-05-05 party !
- And you also had a...
- It happens once every billion years !
- And the tsunami relief fund raiser
with somehow lost a lot of money
Ok, no that was a fun raiser, I think I made
that very clear on the flyers. Fun, F-U-N.
... don't have a tsunami Fun raiser, Michael.
- Well...
I think a lot of people were
very affected by the footage.
It's a little character I like to do.
It is loosely based on Karnack,
one  of Carson's classic characters.
We got... the PLO, the IRA and the
hot-dogs stand behind the warehouse.
Name 3 businesses that have better
healthcare plans than Dunder Mifflin.
Here's the problem : There is
no open bar because of Jan,
and it's the reason why comedy
clubs have a 2-drink minimum.
We'll be fine. I just wish
people gonna be drunk.
- Dwight get out of here what are
you doing into ladies room...?
- No no no, it's not what you're...
- Why were you in there ?
- You are a pervert !
- What were you doing in there ?
- You are a pervert !
- I am not !
The Dundee award, for longest engagement,
goes to Pam Beesly, Pam everybody !
When will that girl gonna be
married ? That’s what I have to say
- Oh Roy's accepting ?
- Yes.
Thank you, you have any words you'd
like to say, at Pam's behalf ?
- We'll see you next year !
- Yeah ! Oh nuts ! Oh gosh !
- I'm not changing that, that's the best one.
- No it's hilarious, you're right.
I just think, world's on disengagement,
we're all expecting it you know ?
That's why it's funny, every year that Roy
and Pam don't get married it gets funnier !
Well I think if you use the same jokes
it just comes across as lazy.
- Ow, lazy !
Excuse me, everyone, can I
have your attention please ?
I just wanted to say that the
women in this office are terrible.
Especially the ones who wrote that stuff
about Michael on the bathroom wall.
Having a bathroom is a privilege,
it is called a ladies-room for a reason,
and if you cannot behave like ladies, well
then you are not going to have a bathroom.
- You're taking away our bathroom ?
- We are going to have 2 men rooms.
- But where would we go ?
- Be prepared to hold it folks, from 9 AM...
- Michael ?
- Yes ?
Dwight is banning us from our bathroom.
- Ok, well that's ridiculous, just don't...
I don't have time for this right now.
- There needs to be repercussions
to people's behavior...
- Don't don't talk don't touch stop it oddment !
- Ok, look I know there have been a lot of rumors
flying around about the Dundies this year,
how there is no money, and how there is
no food, and how the jokes are really bad.
But what the hell everybody ?
I mean, god the Dundies are about
the best, in every one of us.
Can't you see that ? I mean...
ok, we can do better, so,
tonight, for the first time,
We  are inviting all of your friends and
family to attend the awards with us.
- Yes !
- Yeah, not bad right ?
So let's make this best Dundies ever !
Best Dundies ever !
Welcome to eighth annual Dundies awards !
Before we get started, a few announcements :
Keep your acceptance speeches shorts,
I have wrap it up music and I'm
not afraid to use it, Devin.
The Dundies, how can I explain it ?
A word to auto mated,
You've all made it
You had a was, you work so hard
You fell a no, no
This isn't just a name
And now the N-O
And he's been says Hello
Cut, come on !
The Dundies are kind of like a kid's
birthday party, and you go,
and there's really nothing for you to do there,
but the kid's having a really good time, so,
you're kind of there.
That's kind of what it's like.
... Dundee, you wanted that Dundee...
- The waitress tripped on the cord.
- All right, joke'o'landed, so we are here,
Thank you all for coming,
to the 2005 Dundee Awards,
I am your host, Michael Scott,
and I just want to tell you
please, please, do not drink and drive, because
you may hit a bump, and spill the drink.
All the flotties on the group tab.
No, actually this year no group tab
we're gonna be doing separate checks !
- You said we could bring our families.
- I did, and why didn't you Stanley ?
- I did, my wife's name is Terry.
- Well, I'm looking forward to meeting Terry.
It's this person whose hand
I'm holding Michael.
Oh yeah !
- Shut it !
Good,  speaking of relationships,
of all way shapes and forms,
I was out on a very very hot date
last night with a girl from HR Dwight.
- Really ? We don't have any girls from HR.
- Know that, for the sake of the story.
And things were getting hot and heavy, - Yeah
- and I was about to take her bra off,
Yeah !
When she had me fill out
six hours worth of paper work.
- Like an AIDS test ?
- No... god.
- All right. So let's get this party started !
- Hey let's go to Poor Richard's.
- Yeah, let's get out of here.
- Guys, where are you going ?
- Just... Pam shows is getting started.
- Sorry.
- And now
- You're staying ?
- Yeah. I have to eat somewhere.
- The Busiest Beaver award goes to Phyllis Lapin !
Way to go Phyllis ! Nice work ! Per usual !
- This says bushiest beaver.
- What ? I told them busiest... idiots !
- It's fine,
- Well we can fix it, we'll fix it up !
You don't have to display that.
- Because that's what happen every time !
- He's a jackass, every year !
- Come on, we're going to Poor Richard's.
- No, I don't want go I don't want to !
Pam !
If you would have asked me
that then you would know !
Herro everybodeeee.
Hey ! How are you ? I thought you'd left.
No, I decided to stay. I'll just
get a ride home from Angela.
Jan Levinson Gould !
- Good I'm just in time for Ping !
- Yeah
You know what I'm talking about !
Can I get a drink ?
This next award goes to somebody
who really lights up the office.
Somebody who I think a lot of
us cannot keep from checking out.
The hottest, in the office award goes to...
Ryan the temp !
Here you go !
What am I going to do with the award ?
Nothing, I don't know what I'm gonna do.
That's the least of my concerns right now.
And the Tight Ass award goes to Angela,
not only because she is everybody's favorite
stickler, but because she has a great caboose !
- So come on down !
- No.
I think those might be empty.
No, no ‘cause the ice melts,
and then it's like second drink !
Second drink ?
The spicy curry award goes to our
very own Kelly Kapoor !
Get on up here !
There you go !
- Spicy curry, what's that mean ?
- Not everything means something,
this is a joke.
- Yeah, but why did you give it to me ?
- I don't know, I'd just...
- This is a bowler !
- I know ! They didn't have
any businessmen so...
- Yeah but everyone else...
- Just sit down Kelly.
It's so freakin' hot in there.
now I know what Bob Hope was going
through when he performed in Saudi Arabia
I got Dwight, sucking the
funny out of room, but,
you know, you do what you can do...
here we go, he's early with the cue !
Got to go !
("Tiny Dancer"- Elton John)
- "You have won a tiny Dundie."
- Sing it Elton !
- Hey thanks guys !
- Hey where you guys from ?
- We has came from your mama's house.
Hey guys can I finish that ?
Sing on a song dude !
You know what guys we're just having
a little office party so if you wanna...
- Hey ! You know cool it guys !
- You suck man ! You suck !
Let's cut it !
I've a few more Dundies to give out tonight,
but I'm just gonna cut it short, and rapid up.
So everybody can enjoy their food.
Thanks for listening,
those of you who listened.
This last Dundee is for Kevin,
this is the "don't go in there after me"
award, it's for the time that
I went to the bathroom after him and
it was really, really smelly, so.
Here you go.
Yeah Kevin, for Kevin,
for stinking up the bathroom !
- Hey I haven't gotten one yet !
- Yes, I have not gotten one either !
So keep going !
- More Dundies !
Dundies ! - Dundies !
All right, we'll keep 'em rolling.
This is the fine work award, this goes to
Stanley, for all the fine work he did this year.
You know you did !
Speech-speech-speech-speech
Well, last year I got great
work, so I don't know...
I don't know what to think about this award,
but at least I didn't get smelliest
bowel movement like Kevin !
And this next award is going
out to our own little Pam Beesly,
I think we all know what award
Pam is gonna be getting this year,
It is the whitest sneakers award, because
she always has the whitest tennis shoes on !
Get on down here ! Pam Beesly
ladies and gentlemen ! Here we go !
I have so many people
to thank for this award !
Ok, first off, my Keds, because I couldn't
have done it without them, thank you.
Let's give Michael a round of applause for
MC-ing tonight because this is a lot harder than it looks,
and also because of Dwight too.
Finally I want to thank God,
because God gave me this Dundee,
and I feel God in this Chili's tonight.
Pam Beesly ladies and
gentlemen ! Ow, thank you !
What a great year for the Dundies !
We got to see Ping, and we learned Michael's
true feelings for Ryan, which was touching.
And we heard Michael change the lyrics to a
number of classic songs, which for me,
has ruined them for life !
- What ?
- Nothing.
-  Okay.
- What ?
I don't know, what ?
Oh my god ! You are so
drunk ! Did you get that ?
Please tell me that you got,
this is all gonna be on.
- It's ok I'm a sheriff's deputy.
- Well, he's volunteer !
Don't get into that now.
We need something
to caution her head, throw a pillow, a cush ?
- Dwight come on !
- I'm gonna use my shirt.
- Get off of me !
- No !
- I'm sorry, sir, you gotta have to put
your clothes back. We're trying to eat...
Was this year's Dundies a
success ? Well, let me see :
I made Pam laugh so hard that she fell out
of her chair and she almost broke her neck.
So I killed, almost !
Oh my god ! I just wanna say that
this was the best Dundies ever !
We have a strict policy here, not oversunk.
Apparently this young woman was
sneaking drinks off other people's tables.
Eyes at her officer driver's license and she is
not welcome at this restaurant chains ever again !
- Great work tonight !
- Watch your step !
Excellent.
Thanks, I do check her pupils to
make sure that wasn't a concoction.
Yes that too but I mean
with the audio, great work !
I feel bad about what I wrote
on the bathroom wall.
No you don't.
Oh, here she is. Careful.
All right, easy. Almost there.
- Hey hum, can I ask you a question ?
- Shoot.
- I just wanted to say thanks.
- That's not really a question.
Ok let's get you home, come.
- Good bye.
- Good night, have a good night.
Thank you Angela !