Where is my desk?
That is weird.
This is not funny. This
is totally unprofessional.
Okay, well, you're the one
who lost the desk.
I didn't lose my desk.
Hey, calm down. Where was
the last place you saw it?
Okay, who moved my desk?
I think you should
retrace your steps.
Okay, I am going
to tell Michael
and this entire office
will be punished.
Colder.
Warmer.
A little warmer.
There you go. Warmer.
Warmer.
Warmer. Warmer. Warmer.
Cold. Cold. Cold.
Back up.
Warmer. Hot. Red hot.
Hot. Very hot.
Dwight Schrute.
Hi, Dwight.
What sort of discounts are we
giving on the 20-Ib. White bond?
Jim, I've given you this
information, like, 20 times.
I know.
It's by the ream?
Yeah. Ream...
It is now $9.78,
so it's a discount of 7%.
Okay, thank you.
Got to get back to work.
Wash your hands, Kevin.
Right.
Oh, let me just check the
pricing list. Hold on one second.
Sensei, hello,
it's Sempai.
Dwight.
You know what, let me
give you a call right back.
I'm gonna find it and then
I'll call you back. Thanks.
Yes, I just had a question...
Yes, Sensei.
Was that your mom?
No, that was my sensei.
Oh, I thought it was your mom.
I am now Sempai,
which is Assistant Sensei.
Assistant to the Sensei,
that's pretty cool.
Assistant Sensei.
Okay.
I am a practitioner
of Goju-Ryu Karate
here in Scranton.
SENSEl: Two!
Dwight, snap your kick back.
Three!
My sensei, Ira, recently
promoted me to purple belt.
And gave me the duties
of a sempai.
Not that a lot of people here
in America know what a sempai is.
But it's equally
as respected as a sensei.
I don't wanna stay
until 7:00 again this year.
I don't really have any
control over that, Stanley.
Michael tends to procrastinate
a bit whenever he has to do work.
Time cards, he has to
sign these every Friday.
Purchase orders have to be
approved at the end of every month.
And expense reports,
all he has to do is initial
these at the end of every quarter.
But once a year it all falls on
the same Friday. That's today.
I call it the perfect storm.
I don't wanna work
I just wanna bang
on this mug all day
Did you ask me here
for any specific reason?
Yes, I did.
Here's the dizzle.
I have a very top-secret
mission for you.
I want you to update all the
emergency contact information.
Why is that secret?
Hello. Oh, God. Busywork.
Oh, get away, cretin.
I put stickers,
so you know where to sign.
Yes, thanks,
I know where to sign.
It's just that
last year you...
Yeah, well, last year they were
out of order, weren't they, Pam?
Well, the last pick-up for
overnight deliveries is at 7:00.
So you need to have them
signed by then, or much earlier.
Chillax, Pam.
Stop Pam-MS-ing.
That's pretty good.
Actually I'm sending Ryan
on a top-secret mission.
Tell her what it is.
Updating emergency contacts.
Well, is that really
a priority?
Is it a priority?
Oh, I don't know.
What if there's
a tornado, Pam?
People's legs
are crushed under rubble?
Please, would you be so kind
as to call my wife?
No, I can't, because we don't have
any emergency contact information,
because Pam said
it wasn't a priority.
Think. Think with
your head, Pam.
Okay, well, she walks out.
That's the problem
with being a boss,
is that when you are tough
they resent you
and when you are cool
they walk all over you.
Catch-22.
Catch-22. Yes.
Why don't you give me your
contact information to start with?
Okay, what's your cell?
Larissa Halpert.
What's her address?
117 Von Bergen Street.
Hello?
Hey, Ryan!
This is Michael Jackson
calling from Wonderland.
You mean Neverland?
This is Tito.
What?
Calling from...
Your major and minor lines
cross at a ridge.
That sucks.
You're making this up as
you go along, aren't you?
I am just following
the website.
Well, at least
I don't have cavities.
Yes, you have
very nice teeth.
Thanks.
Who's your emergency contact?
Stacey.
Pick up!
Hello?
This is Mike Tyson.
Hey, Dwight?
As sempai, do you ever think
that there's gonna be a day
where humans and robots
can peacefully coexist?
Impossible.
The way they're programmed...
You're mocking me.
No, I'm not.
Well, let me offer you
a little piece of advice.
I am not afraid
to make an example out of you.
Well, that's not advice.
What advice sounds
like is this:
Don't ever bring
your purple belt to work
because someone might
steal it.
Okay, give that back to me.
Okay. Say "please. "
No. That is not a toy.
Please?
Please!
Good. And it absolutely
is a toy.
Arigato.
Arigato. This is not a toy.
This is a message
for the entire office.
So that everyone can see that I am
capable of physically dominating them.
And this is more of a
ying-yang thing.
The "Michael" is all cursives,
"Scott" all caps.
Left brain, right brain,
or duality of man.
Could you practice
on the forms?
No women or children,
unless provoked.
Okay.
Roy.
Warehouse guy,
doesn't count.
Okay.
Michael. Could you
beat up Michael?
Yeah, I don't think
that would happen.
Because we're friends.
Because I would
kick his ass.
Well, Dwight's
a purple belt, so...
So?
I've beat up black belts.
Yeah.
And how did you know
they were black belts?
They told me after.
See, I used to run with a very
tough crowd, street fighter types.
Real, real bad people.
I'm just lucky I got out.
Is your wife still
your contact?
Ex-wife. Yeah.
Her last name's Becker now.
Okay.
You don't need to write "Ex. "
And after that, nobody ever messed
with the Damn Rascals ever again.
Sounds tough.
When you're a Jet, you're
a Jet all the way, right?
You're a jet?
Have you signed
the expense reports yet?
Yes, in theory I have.
I just need to cross
some t's and dot some i's.
All right.
I am going to be in my office,
if anybody needs me.
Michael!
Oh, wow!
Sleeper hold!
Bedtime for Bonzo.
You are the weakest link!
I'm friends with everybody
in this office.
We're all best friends.
I love everybody here.
But sometimes your best friends
start coming into work late,
and start having dentist appointments
that aren't dentist appointments,
and that is when it's nice to let
them know that you could beat them up.
Just hit me, you'll see.
I can't, 'cause
I just got a manicure, so...
Oh, queer! Eye...
Queer Eye, that's a good show.
Important show.
Go ahead. Do it.
Just have Dwight punch you.
Oh, yeah.
Well, that would be kind
of worthless because I know
a ton of 14-year-old girls
who could kick his ass.
You know a ton
of 14-year-old girls?
What belt are they?
Look, Dwight is a wuss.
When we rented Armageddon...
No.
...he cried at the end of it.
He did.
Michael, I told you. That was
because it was New Year's Eve
and it started to snow
at exactly midnight.
"Bruce Willis, they're gonna
leave him on the asteroid. "
Okay, I'll punch you.
Oh, okay, here we go.
All right, come on.
Did I want to harm Michael? The
one man I've been hired to protect?
No, I did not.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Are you sure you're all right? Yep, yep.
Thank you.
I come from a long line
of fighters.
My maternal grandfather was
the toughest guy I ever knew.
World War II veteran,
killed 20 men,
then spent the rest of the war
in an Allied prison camp.
My father battled blood pressure
and obesity all his life.
Different kind of fight.
Okay, he has to be stopped.
Please, please, please,
please, just ask Michael.
I don't know.
Okay, I'll buy you
a bag of chips.
French onion?
Obviously. Why are you spinning around?
Okay.
Yes.
Take this pen, okay,
stab me with it.
Go away.
I just have a quick question.
I haven't signed them, okay?
No, it's not that.
I was just wondering, since I'm
probably gonna have to stay late,
could you ask Dwight to stay late,
too, so he can walk me to my car?
Come in.
Pam, I hate to
break this to you,
but Dwight can't stop you
from being mugged.
He's just not tough enough.
He's a purple belt,
that's really high.
Oh, God, I could
beat up Dwight.
That's ridiculous.
I can murder him.
It's just that
out there you...
Oh, is that what
they're saying?
Yeah, kind of.
Okay, all right.
Where's Dwight?
Kitchen.
Okay.
All right. Here we go.
Good. Wow, that's actually
pretty cool, Dwight.
Excellent. Now, watch.
Let me take you from behind.
What?
Watch out, Kelly,
he might sucker punch you.
I didn't sucker punch you,
Michael.
No, really?
In case you'd remember,
I was defending my honor.
Oh, is that it?
Like a samurai.
Yeah. Really? Well, the offer, Dwight,
was for one punch,
which I absorbed.
I had no idea that there
would be a second punch.
So, catch-22.
Okay, fine.
Tit for tit. Give it your
best shot. Two punches. Go!
Look, if we were in a bar right
now, there would be two punches.
Me punching you
and you hitting the floor.
No, I'd block your first punch... Yeah?
...rendering you ineffective.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
You know what,
you're just lucky
that we're at work right now.
What about, uh,
Dwight's dojo?
No, they just have classes.
No, it's free during the
day. It's fine. Look...
I got the key.
Hey, Michael.
Hey, Toby.
Any word on those time cards?
I have an idea.
Why don't you leave right now?
Why don't you walk away
from the room, okay?
Fine. We'll go at lunch.
Pam, make an announcement.
Figure out car pools.
Well, we're all getting
excited to see this fight.
The Albany branch is working right
through lunch to prevent downsizing,
but Michael, he decided
to extend our lunch by an hour
so that we could all go down to
the dojo and watch him fight Dwight.
Fight! Fight! Fight!
Fight! Fight!
I'm coming. Fight!
Sorry.
I recognize that.
That is Japanese
for California Roll.
No, it's not.
I think it is,
a guy told me about that.
Actually it's a symbol for
eternal discipline.
Oh.
Wow. That is
really interesting.
What?
Your love line... I'm just
kidding. I can't see anything.
Look closer.
Oh, okay.
One point for me.
Tied up.
Oh, you're dead.
What? What are you gonna do?
Bring it, Beesley, bring it.
Oh, yeah. Good move.
Not such an ultimate
fighter now, huh?
Hey, put me down.
Put me down!
Oh, my God!
Hey, put me down! Hey!
Okay, gentlemen,
listen up.
After a clean strike to the
chest, stomach or kidneys,
I will separate you
and award a point.
The first person to three
wins, all right? Yes, Sensei.
Lot of rules, lot of rules.
On the street, we didn't
have any rules. Maybe one.
No kicks to the groin,
home for dinner.
Hey, what the hell
was that?
Yes!
Dwight, one point.
No way! Okay!
Eat it!
All right, that's the way
you wanna do it?
You wanna play dirty, huh?
Okay, game on, man!
Sweep the leg.
Yeah, I'm coming
at you, man!
Okay, purple belt, okay.
I got it.
No.
I got his pants.
That was my pants.
No points for pants.
Dwight, you have... No, look. No,
you have something, you have some...
God, you look like
such an idiot!
Clean technique, gentlemen.
Come on, do that again!
Do that again, I dare you.
Okay, break. Break!
No holding! Break.
Oh, you can't see!
You can't see!
One point, two points,
three points!
Break!
How many points was that?
I win! I win!
No, you didn't! No, you...
Eight points, nine points.
Stop it! No!
Come on, Michael!
Open your mouth!
No, Michael!
You talking to me?
Raging Bull. Pacino.
Oh, I want that footage,
I want it. I need it.
Oh, I have to get back to
work. I have lots of work to...
Check this out. Come here.
There he is.
Mr. Temp having lunch
by the car.
Let us play with him.
This is going to be hilarious.
Oh, we're playing phone tag.
Seven new messages.
First new message.;
Hi, Ryan.
This is Saddam Hussein.
Next message.;
Hey, Ryan,
this is your girlfriend
and I'm mad.
My emergency contact
is Todd Packer.
Todd F. Packer.
Know what the "F" stands for?
Fudge?
Yeah. Come in.
Oh, hey, Karate Kid.
The Hilary Swank version.
Hi. How are you?
I need to change my
emergency contact information
from Michael Scott.
Okay, to what?
Just put
"The Hospital. "
Contact number, just put 911.
He is such a sore loser.
You heard, obviously, that I mopped
the floor with him this afternoon.
You know what,
do yourself a favor.
Just leave me as his contact
and I will call the hospital.
Cut out the middleman.
Later, Jim.
Later, Kev.
Have a good weekend.
Yeah, you, too.
Yeah?
I have the emergency contacts.
Just lay them on a chair.
I'll take it from here.
So, what you up to
this weekend?
Hanging out
with some friends, probably.
Well, if you do anything
crazy, give me a shout.
Yeah. All right,
I will see you Monday.
All right.
Bye.
Dwight?
Michael, did you finish yet?
This close.
Dwight, may I speak
with you for a minute?
I'm busy.
Well, busier,
but I'm making the time.
Michael, can't your
conversation wait till Monday?
We wanna go home.
Well, you don't even have
anybody to go home to, Toby, so...
The shipping place
closes in a half hour.
I know,
but I have been carrying
the load on my back all day.
And if everyone would
just chip in a little bit,
it might help me out.
What do you say? Let's
gang-bang this thing and go home.
Good? Dwight.
This is illegal.
I don't care.
I have been testing you the
entire day. Did you know that?
Of course.
And I'm happy to say
that you passed.
So, effective immediately,
I am promoting you
from Assistant to the Regional
Manager, to Assistant Regional Manager.
Michael, I don't know...
I know,
I know, I know, I know.
I wouldn't be offering it if I
didn't think you could handle it.
I can handle it. I can.
I know. Okay.
So, I guess,
this will just be my office.
No, no, title change only.
I'll have Pam send out a memo. No, no.
Three month
probationary period.
Let's just not tell anybody
about this right now.
Just a formality.
Absolutely. But not really.
Michael,
I have so much
to learn from you.
Yes, you do.
Thank you,
Sensei.
And, ditto.
I told Dwight
that there is honor in losing,
which, as we all know,
is completely ridiculous.
But there is, however, honor
in making a loser feel better,
which is what
I just did for Dwight.
Would I rather be feared
or loved?
Easy. Both.
I want people to be afraid
of how much they love me,
and I think I proved that
today at the dojo.
Typewriter torture!
Sensei!
Stop!
Typewriter!