My grandfather is one of the
wealthiest men in the New World.
If I plead our case
and gain his support,
that might be all we need
to emerge from this intact.
I alone am to be left in
charge of Nassau's security.
And I gave our lord
governor my solemn oath
that I would see it protected.
Israel Hands.
It's a pleasure to
make your acquaintance.
- You want to withdraw?
- If we don't,
it will be the end of
whatever trust exists
between us and the slaves on the island.
I'm through following you down a path
only you seem able to see.
Fire!
The neighboring estates must've
heard the guns and rallied.
We need to be gone before
that militia arrives.
I board the sloop and I run.
The door will be open for you to reach
your grandfather and gain his aid.
- It's the governor's banner.
- Do we pursue?
Set a course to overtake her.
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
Captain?
I would've thought you'd retired by now.
Bulletins...
from my scouts in the field tonight.
I was contemplating my
response after the sunrise.
Anything we should discuss?
You have enough on your mind.
Let this be my concern.
Have you told her, my Lord?
Your wife.
About what lies ahead?
Good.
She doesn't need it
on her mind, either...
what lies ahead.
I have found that
contemplating these things
is the most difficult part.
That when the dread moment arrives,
your true nature will assert itself.
The confusion will lift
and all will appear as it should be.
You've given me good men to lead.
I'll do my best by them.
There isn't a good man among them.
Not anymore.
Some of them may have
been, before all this.
Some of them may be again
on the other side of it.
But right now,
good men are not what
the moment requires.
Right now,
the time calls for dark men...
to do dark things.
Do not be afraid to lead them to it.
Prepare for departure!
Today is the 24th.
David is five today.
My son.
I didn't know that.
Mr. Grandal has not
contacted me in weeks.
With the war apparently occupying
Spain's attention elsewhere,
there is a good chance the
entire unfortunate affair
surrounding the Spanish
gold is behind us.
So, when we reach Philadelphia,
once you are under the
protection of your family...
I was hoping you might see fit
to release me from my service,
that I might return to London...
to my children.
Of course.
Ma'am...
I've just been informed our permission
to depart has been suspended.
Suspended? Why?
I'm told the soldiers that
were to comprise your escort
are otherwise needed ashore.
What the fuck is this?
- Get out.
- Get dressed.
Mr. Harrison,
proceed.
Six men with you.
They never looked my way as I
stayed a considerable distance.
Saw you meet two others late last night,
one of them standing on just one leg.
Saw it all.
I had him follow you
after you left town
so abruptly last night.
I assume the one-legged
man was Long John Silver.
Would you like to tell me
what the meeting was about?
I was summoned by him
in a failed attempt to
extort money from me.
I would hope that your
spy also informed you
that four of my six men
attempted to arrest him
and died in the effort.
I was barely able to escape myself.
Surely this should mitigate any
doubt you may have about my loyalties.
If you were loyal to the governor,
why did you not inform me of
the meeting before the fact?
If you are loyal to the governor,
why attempt to arrest
a man as dangerous as he
rather than simply eliminating him?
If you had informed me,
I'm sure I could have
helped in that regard.
My questions about your loyalty, ma'am,
are not mitigated by
last night's events.
If anything, they are now
aggravated to an intolerable degree.
Does the testimony presented
satisfy a charge of treason?
- Wait.
- It does.
This is outrageous.
When the governor returns,
he will not stand for this.
The governor is not here. I am here.
And you are now under an indictment
that carries with it
the penalty of death.
Mr. Harrison here
trailed Long John Silver
before losing him in the wrecks.
Men and horse await in the square,
preparing to clear that
area and apprehend him.
Today is the day the
pirate resistance dies,
its leader eliminated,
its supporters in Nassau
exposed and arrested.
If you cooperate with me to that end,
perhaps your death
might still be averted.
We have no choice but
to leave the island.
No one is leaving anything.
We came here to take Nassau.
We leave once that
is done or not at all.
Take Nassau?
With what army?
Whatever slaves are
still alive on this island
will never fight
alongside a pirate again.
- Not after last night.
- Last night,
there were also pirates
who fought alongside us.
Against terrible odds and at great cost.
Billy and his men are our enemies
now, but these men are not.
And as long as that is true,
our alliance with them holds.
You know where you're going?
I saw her last employed in the tavern.
I'll begin there.
We don't need to persuade
her to do anything yet.
Eventually, we'll need to garner support
to help incite Nassau to
revolt against the governor,
but what we need right
now is information.
How many soldiers there are,
what kind of sympathy
exists for our cause.
I know.
Thank you.
- What for?
- Last night.
You did not have to side with me.
It was costly for you to do so.
Well, it would have cost far
more for me not to have done so.
We might be able to take Nassau alone,
but there will be no greater
victory, no widespread revolution
unless we can somehow
keep our alliance together.
You truly believe it is possible?
That as disadvantaged
and disabled as we are,
that anything we do here
is going to make the least bit of
difference to the men in London?
Well, that's the trick, isn't it?
If no one remembers a time
before there was an England,
then no one can imagine a time after it.
The empire survives in part
because we believe its
survival to be inevitable.
But it isn't.
And they know that.
That's why they're so
terrified of you and I.
If we were able to take Nassau,
if we are able to expose the illusion
that England is not inevitable,
if we are able to incite a revolt
that spreads across the New World...
then, yeah...
I imagine people are gonna notice.
"Too much sanity may be madness,
"and the maddest of all,
"to see life as it is
and not as it should be."
Get the main sail.
I'll say this for him, he's not shy.
If he misses this tack, we'll
be on him in less than an hour.
He's completed his last
three tacks. Why stop now?
Not that close to the wind.
Not nearly that close.
Don't you think?
Any chance he could slip away from us?
- Not really, no.
- No.
He's pointing higher,
but we've got the speed.
He can't hold us off forever.
Once we've stopped him,
you and I will take the
vanguard aboard on longboats.
You can stay close, provide
support until we're boarded.
Ever captained a ship
of this size before?
God, no.
Have you captained a
ship this size before?
- Sure.
- Good.
This ain't ever gonna end for us, is it?
What?
You always wanted to
stand next to giants.
Now there you are.
And I'm wondering how it is you and
I are ever gonna move on from this.
He's brilliant, you know?
I've heard him
underestimated on that score,
perhaps owing to his physical strength.
People finding it
hard to accept the idea
that one man can be two things,
but I've seen it.
He is brilliant.
And last night, all
he wanted was revenge,
and all that would satisfy it was
Eleanor Guthrie's head on a plate.
And in a moment in which he had no
appetite to be persuaded otherwise,
I persuaded him otherwise.
If the story of the pirate Jack Rackham
is to end with him standing
alongside Blackbeard as an equal,
together defeating the
governor who hanged Charles Vane
and in so doing restoring
pirate rule over Nassau...
that is an ending I can live with.
Defeat Rogers...
and we walk away.
They've missed stays!
We've got him.
Ready the guns!
The end is about to begin.
Our invasion failed.
But we are not through.
There is support for
our cause inside Nassau.
There must be, however dormant.
But we need to find it.
Need your help to find it.
There was support once,
but now Nassau is frightened.
What you would ask, openly
defying those soldiers...
I doubt you'd find that kind of support.
I have lost more than you
can know to reach this moment.
Captain Flint has lost
more than you can know.
- But we are here.
- Captain Flint?
He awaits with a small force of men.
But if we can see those
prisoners broken free...
And you are with him as well?
Yes?
Him... who?
Long John Silver.
He died in the bay
during the invasion.
What?
A posse just departed for the wrecks
under instructions
from Captain Berringer
to locate and arrest Long John Silver.
Are you all right, ma'am?
Ma'am?
Fuck.
- Fuck, fuck, fuck.
- That's enough.
We should be running.
There's nowhere to run.
Then we have a serious problem,
as Captain Berringer is going to demand
she identify her connections
to the resistance, which is us.
She won't.
How can you be so sure?
Because she doesn't like
her friends being threatened.
And she doesn't like
to be pushed around.
I sincerely hope you're right,
as I believe our lives depend upon it.
She won't tell on us in there.
What we should be worried about
is how we're going to
help her from out here.
Fuck.
The other day,
you refused to name the source you used
to undermine the pirate
invasion of the bay...
as a matter of principle.
Since that time, Long John
Silver and his associates
have murdered one of my men...
murdered four of your men...
murdered a family of three
on the Underhill estate
in cold blood last night,
including an eight-year-old girl.
Knowing now how high
the bodies are piling,
how real the threat is,
I am giving you an opportunity
to remedy your error
and help me end this
threat once and for all.
I want the names of your sources.
I am sorry,
but I cannot do that.
Cannot or will not?
These men would turn on
you in a blink of an eye.
Why would you go to such
lengths to protect them?
I told you,
I have an understanding
with the governor...
- ... in which he acknowledged...
- Give me the names.
... the benefit of my being
able to honor my word...
- ... to my sources...
- Give me the names.
- ... such that I might continue...
- to serve his regime in the future...
- Give me the names.
- ... as I have served it every day...
- ... until now.
- Give me the names!
You can't go in there, ma'am.
What is going on here?
Go!
I'm not shackled.
You plan to run?
Do I need to run?
That'd be fun for me to see.
How would you do it?
With great difficulty, I imagine.
How would you take Nassau?
When I did it...
drove the governor away,
I had Teach and an army of
my once-brothers at my back.
You want to play Teach?
Who's to play the rest?
Or do you believe we
two could do it alone?
Find him!
Look over there!
Right. Over there!
Behind them. Check the brush!
Find him!
Search that wreck!
Get in there!
It's all right.
How are we going to take Nassau?
That's how.
Cease fire!
Cease firing!
Shall we reload, Captain?
There's nothing more
we can do from here.
They're on their own now.
They've struck their colors!
She is the most influential
member of the Governor's Council.
Whatever tension there has been,
he relies upon her to maintain control.
Ma'am.
If when the governor does return
I have to explain to
him that I discovered
the most influential
member of his council
conspiring with our enemies
and took action to stop her,
that is an explanation
I will offer happily.
Now, I apologize for the delay
in your transport to Philadelphia.
The men were most needed
to address today's crisis.
Please trust I will have you on your way
by the time the sun rises tomorrow.
I explained the situation to him.
He's in no mood to be
reasoned with on the issue.
You saw him, Silver?
What happened?
It was him and one other.
I had six men.
I thought it would be sufficient
to apprehend him myself.
Apprehend him?
No one asked you to apprehend him.
All you had to do was
report the invitation to meet
and let the captain handle it.
How in God's name did
that not occur to you?
I did not fail to do it.
I refused to do it and would again.
Why would you refuse
to adhere to the law?
Because the last time the law
got its hands on a
pirate of that stature,
it yielded the following...
anger, hostility, resentment,
purges to combat it all that only
resulted in amplifying it all,
and a resistance movement that,
since Captain Vane was hanged,
has done nothing but grow strong enough
to control almost every part of
this island outside of Nassau.
And you ask why I chose
not to help start the
cycle all over again?
There is a ship in the bay
that is supposed to
be taking me to a place
where I might actually
solve our problems here.
But instead, I am stuck here for
as long as it takes to fix this.
In order to do that,
you are going to have to give
me something to fix it with.
But you'd better come up with
something of value I can use
to get him to walk away from this.
You think you can control him.
And by the time you realize
he has been controlling you,
it is going to be too late.
Riders returning!
Give me something I can use
because otherwise I can't help you.
And I beg your pardon, but what
the fuck have you got to lose?
- What happened?
- Fugitive escaped.
Though, not before
killing three of my men
and fixing that to one of the bodies.
What does it say?
"To the men and women of Nassau,
"the strength of the governor's
force is now reduced by three.
"The time to lend us
your efforts is now.
"See my brothers held captive freed.
"Join them. Join me.
"Signed, Long John Silver."
You heard him.
The time is now.
Who among you would like to lend
his efforts to Long John Silver
and resist me?
Here.
I am unarmed.
No one will stand in your way.
If the time isn't now, when
the fuck is it going to be?!
None of you?!
No one at all?!
You fucking cowards.
I don't understand.
- Billy.
- Yep.
- Tried to kill you?
- And Madi?
- Her, too.
Why are we not angry about this?
Who says we're not?
Well, I'm not sensing a whole lot
of urgency to do anything about it.
There isn't anything we can
do about it at the moment.
Isn't there?
Look, Billy's not stupid.
He's almost certainly
consolidated by now,
intimidated or eliminated anyone who
would challenge him or support me.
He has control of the Underhill estate,
control of the army that calls it home.
There will be a time to
deal with him, but not now.
This one, however.
He's fine.
If you'd asked me yesterday,
when he was considering selling
me to the governor for a profit,
I'd be in agreement we
should be rid of him.
But now, I don't know.
I feel like we need as
much help as we can...
get.
Execution of the pirate
prisoners is scheduled for today.
Captain Berringer stood in the square
and said if Long John Silver
had a problem with this,
he was welcome to show
himself and voice it.
Uh, even if we could get
through their outer defenses,
10 of us walk into town against
what could be 100 soldiers.
And then what?
The threats have been
made. The story's been told.
Everyone in Nassau knows
what Long John Silver's return means,
what's expected of them
when he does return.
All that remains to do...
is for him to return.
It would help if Nassau
knew I was coming.
Can you see to it?
Of course.
Ooh, lovely.
I don't make this request lightly.
But after everything Max
has done for the council,
for you,
it seems like a moment when
she's owed something back.
The charges against her are
of the utmost seriousness.
It sounds as if the
law is being adhered to.
And what standing do
we have to interfere?
People are angry, Mr. Frasier.
At the soldiers, at Captain Berringer.
Some of them even at our lord governor.
You may not see it, but trust me, I do.
If the council won't resist the captain,
then some of those people might find
their own ways of resisting this.
Ways you might not like.
Don't send for me again.
Fuck.
- What did he say?
- Nothing helpful.
What's going on?
You're about to make a terrible mistake
and I am asking you to reconsider.
I am entitled to exercise these
sentences at my discretion.
But I'm not asking you
to cancel the hangings.
I'm asking you to cancel
the theater around them.
You intend to lure Silver in.
Force him to appear in
the square to save his men
so that you might defeat him
in full view of all of Nassau.
Demonstrate your fearsomeness to them.
Don't.
- Why not?
- Because you don't need to.
Because they know it already
and because at a certain point,
there is only so much
fear a man can endure.
All you are doing is antagonizing them.
And who is that serving?
Because there is a better
way to solve this problem.
What is that?
This is information
about the preferred routes
used by the resistance
to enter into Nassau.
- She gave it to you?
- She did.
Send men to lie in wait.
Set an ambush that can
overwhelm Silver and his men
when they attempt to pass.
End this quietly and easily
and definitively.
What do you imagine happens next?
If you are fortunate
enough to capture Teach...
what will you do with him?
Years ago...
as a privateer during the war,
I was in a running fight
with a Spanish galleon.
Hounded her for days.
By all rights, she should've
surrendered long before she did.
Just before her colors were
struck, a shot was fired.
A cheap, cowardly shot...
fired with the knowledge they
were about to surrender anyway
and the presumption that
they be entitled to quarter.
This particular shot found its mark.
Took three of my men...
one of them, my brother, Thomas.
He'd always been smarter than me.
Braver.
Better.
Protected me when we were young.
Taught me to sail when we were older.
He was my closest friend.
Lost to a cheap and cowardly shot.
So, after they surrendered,
I went aboard the ship.
And I began with the captain.
I was more deliberate with him.
It took some time.
Then I moved to his first mate.
The gun captains.
Gun crews.
74 men aboard that
ship when I boarded her.
But by the time we reached
Acapulco, there was only one.
The one I delivered
alive to recount the tale.
You asked what would happen next.
My instinct is the
same now as it was then.
I will show them what
the consequences are
for threatening that
which I hold most dear.
I will leave no doubt about it.
Do it.
Heave!
Let's get the slack.
Now.
Pull!
Pull it away!
Hold him.
Again.
Heave!
- Heave!
- Get it out!
Heave!
Him next.
Again!
Heave!
Let fall.
Can you see?
Secure the rest of them.
Set a course for Nassau.
Raise sail!
Keep moving. Don't drag your feet!
Go on.
Move it.
Go on through.
Sir...
What did he say?
Your men lying in wait
for Silver and his men,
were they successful?
Do it.
There was no ambush set, was there?
- I reconsidered.
- We had an agreement.
Nassau will never fully come to heel
until we can demonstrate control.
And control that no one can see
makes for no demonstration at all.
So, I will let them see it.
Remove them.
Ready the next three.
Take them down.
Next three prisoners.
You know Lieutenant Utley
from the captain's staff?
- Yes.
- Find him.
Tell him I ask that he gather
as much food and supplies
as he can move into the
fort within the next hour.
The fort?
And tell him to gather six men he trusts
to escort it and us up there.
And tell him to get Max.
Why do we need an escort to the fort?
Quickly, please. We
don't have much time.
They'll come.
Company, fall into two ranks!
Make ready!
Present!
Ready!
- Fire!
Charge!
I need B Company!
Fall back!
B Company, make ready!
Wait for my command!
Mark your target!
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com