It's lost. For the moment,
Nassau town is lost.
That much is painfully clear.
It is our duty now to
secure ourselves here.
I think we're all properly angry
about what he did on
the Underhill estate,
but Billy has influence
that is best not ignored.
Billy told me I should worry
that you will be Madi's end.
After you fled, reprisals were visited
upon our loved ones
upon the Edwards estate.
I wonder, ma'am, if he
might want you to leave
when he learns of your
current state of being.
She's flying the
governor's banner. It's him!
Ready the men. We'll make our landing
under cover of the fort's guns,
reinforce them, and
move to retake Nassau.
I am prepared to surrender the
governor's remaining forces to you,
control of the fort, all of it,
in exchange for the cache.
- No.
- Trust me.
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
Give me a hand with this chest.
Where have you been?
And where's Flint?
In a moment, a woman I don't know
is going to walk out of that fort.
She's going to move towards a longboat
in which we'll have placed two men
to row her to Governor Rogers' ship.
We have ensured that
she'll arrive unharmed
to deliver a message to the governor.
We ensured?
I'm sorry.
When and why did we decide to do that?
Because Captain Flint
has offered himself
as collateral to Eleanor
Guthrie inside the fort.
If we breach our pledge, he dies.
Collateral?
What the fuck are you talking about?
To guarantee our compliance...
as part of a bargain
in which the British
will be surrendering
their position in Nassau.
Every man on the beach
will need to be told.
Pass the word.
Now.
I would appreciate it
if you'd double check...
- ... the transport.
- Yes, ma'am.
There are some supplies that I would
like to be transported over, too.
Thank you.
Go and find Mrs. Hannah.
She'll know what to do.
No one will harm you out there.
How can you be so sure?
Because they know if anything
happens to you, Flint dies.
No one is going to test me to
see if I'm serious about that.
When you get to the
ship, when you get to him,
you know what to say to him.
Yes, ma'am.
And you know what not to say to him.
If he balks about leaving,
which he is almost certain to do...
it might help if he knew
it wasn't just your welfare
that was in question.
I won't have him learning
about it like this.
I just won't.
I understand.
You should be going.
Eleanor Guthrie...
Eleanor Guthrie told you
she'd surrender the fort
and all of Nassau with it
if Flint agreed to act as her
hostage to guarantee the deal?
Are you really gonna make me ask?
It wasn't all she got.
What else did she get?
It was agreed...
that in addition to guaranteeing
the safe departure from the island
of her and all her people...
that we would retrieve
and surrender to her
the cache of gems remaining
from the Urca gold.
It guarantees a quick victory
to a fight we'd otherwise be
far from guaranteed to win.
Guaranteed?
When is anything ever...?
- And you agreed to this?
- I didn't agree to anything.
The offer was put to Captain
Flint. He had little time to decide.
I trust his judgment.
They're right in our path.
What do you want to do?
I have this.
What the hell is this?
Mrs. Rogers has asked
me to relay a message
- that is of the utmost importance.
- I should certainly hope it is.
- She intends to surrender her position.
- What?
She has negotiated an
arrangement with Captain Flint
in which he will pay for this
surrender with the stolen cache of gems
to secure your future together.
She asks that you withdraw
to allow for this
transaction to proceed,
retire to Port Royal for a
fortnight and await her arrival.
- If she has not arrived...
- Someone clear that launch.
Mr. Molin, get us underway. We proceed.
- Prepare to make our landing.
- My Lord.
Clear away that launch.
Prepare for landing!
Is the governor still approaching?
He is, ma'am.
If I wanted to fire a warning shot,
how close would I have to
aim for it to be effective?
How close?
I'm not interested in holing his ship,
but need him to understand
that I am committed to this.
What's the distance to his ship?
What's the distance
to the governor's ship?
1,200 yards, approximately.
Closing.
I'd lead her by two ship lengths.
Continue our approach.
Again, please.
Ma'am.
Reload.
I beg your pardon, my Lord,
but she demanded that
I relay what follows...
her words precisely...
in spite of any protest you offered.
She says she knows
that you will be angry
and that this will be hard
for you to understand...
... but she said...
She said you should trust
that her commitment to you
remains inviolable...
and that this is no betrayal...
but an act of love.
And an act she is determined
to see through to its end.
Mr. Molin.
Come hard to starboard and make
your course north-northwest.
- Sir?
- Stand down the gun crews.
Hard to starboard.
Set course north-northwest.
Stand down the gun crews.
Set course for north-northwest.
Thank you.
Are you all right?
I am.
What happened?
I heard the governor
took Captain Teach's ship
and threatened an invasion.
Why now does he sail away?
Flint just agreed to trade the cache
in exchange for a complete surrender.
To trade it?
- All of it?
- All of it.
The money that was to be our treasury
upon which the viability of this
entire enterprise was premised.
If this bargain
consummates, it will be gone.
So much to give up.
But I think he made the right decision.
Controlling Nassau without
the cache will be a challenge,
but one I don't think can be avoided.
You're kidding me!
No.
Are you kidding me?
You did not see what I saw
at the Underhill estate.
There has been immeasurable,
unspeakable suffering on this island
as a result of Billy's actions.
Whatever trust may have been
between the slaves here
and our alliance is gone.
This enterprise is on
the verge of collapse
and it cannot withstand a fight
against the governor's men right now.
What price can be too
high to prevent it?
Drastic measures will need to be taken
of which, I'm afraid, this
will only be the first.
What is that supposed to mean?
The damage done to this
alliance was caused by Billy.
It may be that the only
way to repair this damage
is to remove that which caused it.
Remove him?
It will be the only way to regain
the trust of those slave communities
uncertain about what
this alliance stands for.
And you know as well as I
Billy cannot exist alongside
Captain Flint for long.
Sooner or later, one
or the other must go.
If we win Nassau even through surrender,
we are still going
to have to control it.
Without the resources
afforded by the cache
or the force supplied
by Billy and his men,
how the fuck do you imagine
we're going to do that?
We will struggle through it,
train men, gain
strength through numbers,
hunt for that which we need.
It will be difficult.
But since when did we expect
this would be anything else?
What?
Jesus.
You sound exactly like him.
Why is this a problem?
Where are you going?
I have a siege to manage, for which
I'm going to need Billy's help.
Wait!
Billy was your friend.
This is not easy for me,
but I know it is harder for you.
Please.
Don't forget that I know that.
I haven't.
If this goes away,
Flint's war,
if it all ended and we
had to walk away from it...
Walk away?
... would I be enough for you?
You know what? You don't
have to answer that.
We'll send Kofi to retrieve the cache.
Your mother will trust him.
No news from outside the walls?
A ketch was seen departing
the day before last.
We were told it was sent
to retrieve the cache,
but since then, nothing.
He's dead, isn't he?
Mr. Scott.
Were you with him?
I've heard about his role
amongst your maroon allies.
Were you with him before he died?
I was.
I've been told that he departed the
island before all of this started.
That he killed two
soldiers in the process.
Everyone assumed he'd turned,
that somehow one of you had turned him,
but that isn't what happened, is it?
No, it isn't.
For how long had he been
secretly aiding them?
He began, he said,
after the Spanish raid.
Did he say why he did it?
He told me that he feared for the
safety of his wife and his daughter,
so he had them transported
to a place they'd be safe.
They weren't killed in the raid?
Are they still alive?
Yes, they are.
For so long, I thought
I knew what I was.
A daughter who usurped her father.
A woman who had taken
control of a wild place.
Scott was proof of that.
The one who saw me that way, too,
who substantiated it.
And all that time, all he
saw was a girl so ambitious...
she would never doubt his story.
So, she would continue to play the part.
Draw everyone's attention
away from himself.
You did do all those things.
I know I did.
But always with a man behind me
doing his damnedest to
bend it all to his benefit.
My father, Scott, Charles, you.
So many goddamn men here.
Too many goddamn men here.
Woodes Rogers.
He's really so different
from the rest of us?
There's very little I
wouldn't do to protect my wife.
Of course, my Lord.
I had concerns when we
first arrived in Nassau,
and I told her as much...
that the instincts that had allowed
her to survive for so long there,
to thrive there,
would eventually return.
And that when they did, it
would cause conflict between us.
I don't believe that's
what's happened, my Lord.
You don't?
She's done this out of devotion to you.
There's no doubt in my mind about that.
No, I don't doubt it either.
I know she has no love for Flint,
nor any sympathy for his cause.
I fear the instincts
that have awoken in her...
are more insidious than that.
She has begun to believe again
that disorder in Nassau is inevitable,
that civilization is powerless,
either through lack of will
or capacity to do anything about it.
Civilization...
has a number of faces.
To think them all powerless
to alter Nassau's future...
is a terrible mistake.
Yes?
Harbor patrol is deploying.
We've arrived.
Harbor patrol?
My Lord, where are we?
There is very little...
I wouldn't do to protect my wife.
What the hell have you done?
If the British Empire will not aid
us in fighting our present enemy,
perhaps a different empire will.
Strike our colors.
Raise the white flag and make
a course to enter the harbor.
Strike our colors!
Raise the white flag!
If they fire on us...
we'll be sunk before we
get our gunports open.
They won't fire on us.
I beg your pardon, sir,
but we're at war.
Why wouldn't they?
The most recognizable British
governor in the New World
is attempting to sail a man-of-war
requesting parley into
the port of Havana.
If you were them,
wouldn't you want to know why?
Your contact?
Juan Antonio Grandal.
Colonial Intelligence.
_
That's the Walrus.
Everything we've put
that ship through...
and she just refuses to die.
It's fucking unnatural.
They'll all follow you.
You know that, don't you?
Flint thinks these people would run
when confronted by the governor's men.
He's so convinced they won't
stand behind you and fight,
he's ready to hand over the
cache to avoid the outcome.
And he's wrong.
You're exactly what I hoped you'd be.
A rational man to lead Nassau.
That's the first in recent memory.
And one that they'd allow to lead
them into a rational future...
This doesn't have anything to
do with reason, and you know it.
You want them following me
only to the extent that I,
in turn, will follow you.
I'm a convenience...
designed to aid you
in ruling over Nassau
with the same uncompromising
grip you'd vilify from Flint.
If I choose to side with him,
trade the cache for
the fort and his life,
are you honestly suggesting
you'd let it happen?
That you wouldn't use your men
to force a scenario by
which he ends up dead?
I'm not gonna stand by and watch
while all our futures are destroyed.
No.
But perhaps it's worth
focusing on how hard I'm working
to persuade you not
to make that decision.
I would far, far rather do
this with you than against you.
And I have faith you can see
what is abundantly clear here.
We have Nassau.
We have a ship with which
to hunt and acquire more.
And when that cache arrives, we
will have the money to govern it all.
We made a deal, Billy.
We gave our word to Madi,
her mother, their people
that we were all
committed to the same war.
That's Flint's deal, not mine.
And not yours.
Their people need a place to call home?
Here it is.
And we are contemplating
throwing it away
to continue a war that,
sooner or later, is
guaranteed to end in defeat.
You know I'm right.
Slow them down.
The sooner that ship's afloat,
the sooner they'll all want to hunt,
and we need them on the beach.
Consider it done.
I would like to be alone.
All right.
You'd like to be a part of this?
What would you do?
Sooner or later, that
cache is going to arrive,
and there'll be no more delaying.
I'm committed to Flint.
I'm committed to Madi.
Yet the road they intend to travel
is one I'm losing the
ability to understand.
I know what Billy's done...
what should be unforgivable...
and yet till so very recently,
there's no one in the world
I called a closer friend.
The more he talks, the
more I remember why.
To turn on him now,
to have him killed... which is what
it would take to side with Flint...
seems like something...
I don't know I have it in me to do.
You don't know, hmm?
You don't know?
Why should I follow
you if you don't know?
Why would anyone?
I don't give a shit
what goes on in there.
Fuck Flint. Don't fuck Flint.
Fuck Billy. Don't fuck Billy.
I don't give a shit what you choose,
but fucking choose!
And don't make me suffer the thinking.
Worry ain't a good look for a king,
not in a kingdom like this...
where loyalty is in short supply.
- Did you counsel him to come here?
- No.
But the urgency of his
situation demanded it.
It was a mistake.
Inglés?
I think you know who I am.
I think you know what I am.
You and I are enemies as our
kings are at war with one another.
But their war...
right now their war
is meaningless to me.
I came to Nassau before it
began to foster commerce,
and toward that end, to
combat piracy, to defeat it.
That was my war.
And I had that victory within my reach.
I had it.
But my enemy has remade
itself since then,
made allies with an army of maroons,
and has now dedicated itself to
disorder of the grandest scale.
Inciting others... slaves, sailors,
wage laborers alike...
to join their fight and give their lives
to destroy the civilized world.
Labor fuels commerce
and commerce fuels security.
If these people are successful
in compromising the first,
there is no end to the damage
they can cause the rest.
In this war...
you and I have far more
that unites our interests
than separates them.
For if Nassau falls,
if it becomes a dark symbol
of what mayhem these men can unleash,
a rallying cry that might be
heard throughout the New World...
how long before these same
men turn their eyes to Cuba?
To your plantations and your ships?
How long before Spanish
slaves are emboldened by it
and set their eyes on you?
When you are forced to
write to King Philip,
begging his assistance
in staving off the army of slaves
and pirates on your doorstep...
would you not wish in that moment...
that you had this one back...
when it was possible to kill
this monster in its cradle...
cheap and quick and quiet?
I had a younger brother once.
Simón.
He was a midshipman
aboard Nuestra Señora
de la Encarnación.
Beneath a flag of surrender,
he was butchered.
And I'm told...
you likely wielded the sword...
personally.
Am I misinformed?
No.
You are not my enemy,
because my king tells me so.
Don't insult me...
by suggesting otherwise.
If the situation in
Nassau is as you say it is,
why are you here?
Why are you not in
Williamsburg or Kingston,
seeking help from your own?
I've tried.
They won't listen.
Maybe because they care more about
the war against Spain than I do.
Maybe because this just
isn't as personal to them
as it is for me or for you.
This is personal to me?
Of course it is.
The pirates offered me
a cache of stolen gems
to persuade me to surrender.
The cache of gems representing
the last remaining share
of the Urca plunder.
They're paying for their
war with your money.
What is it you think
will come from this?
You think I'll commit
men and sail with you?
To fight an insurgency
on your territory,
force my men to decipher
friend from enemy,
amongst that sort of confusion?
My friends are all
besieged within Fort Nassau.
My wife is there.
I'd beg you to spare them,
avoid the fort entirely.
And in exchange,
the fort will offer no
resistance to your landing.
Once you land,
once you are past the fort...
I envision no confusion.
You needn't decipher anything.
I'd simply ask that you
burn it all to the ground.
The ship was spotted on the horizon,
approaching the rendezvous
beach from the south
and flying no colors.
Kofi and his men are returning.
The wind is dying out.
The cache will be on the
sand in a few hours, at most.
Who knows they've arrived?
So far?
Him, you, and I.
That's it.
Sooner or later, people
are going to know.
And we're gonna have to
give them instructions
about what happens to
that cache once it lands.
There's no more putting off a decision.
Giving up that money
is an impossibility.
Flint will just keep
pushing for these things,
costly things that we pay
for with our own suffering,
with our own lives.
You know this.
You've always known this.
Sooner or later, it has to end.
You send word to the fort
and tell them it's here.
Arrange for them to come out.
I'll have men waiting there.
I'll end it quickly.
All you have to do...
is look the other way.
I don't want it happening
in full view of that beach.
Yeah.
What was that?
It's arrived.
The cache?
What else does it say?
It's across the island.
Mr. Silver insists that we exit
through the northwest tunnel
where we'll be escorted over
land to the southern coast.
The transport will meet us there.
This wasn't part of the deal.
Sailing a fortune in
jewels into that harbor...
in full view of a beach
filled with enraged pirates,
you can understand his reluctance.
This way, there will be far less risk
of anyone disturbing the exchange.
I saw his face when
you accepted this deal,
and I imagine you did, too.
If there is anyone on that beach
with a desire to disrupt this exchange,
I'm concerned Mr. Silver
may be first among them.
I'm not concerned.
Lieutenant Utley.
Select six of your men to escort us.
Mr. Soames is in charge until I return.
The men are all in position?
They are.
About a dozen of them
beyond that tree line.
Once Silver gives the signal,
they'll... close in.
They'll have soldiers with them.
Tell Silver it's important we wait
until they've all cleared the tunnel
before we make any kind of move.
When the time comes, I don't
want anyone else touching Flint.
I'll handle it.
This isn't right.
All those men out there that
you and I have fought alongside.
I can't believe I'm the only
one who knows this isn't right.
You built all of this.
The resistance.
It wouldn't have worked without you.
But part of what you
built, it worked too well.
Long John Silver.
All he had to do was open his mouth,
say your name,
and everyone listened.
What was it that he said about me?
He said the reason Flint's fleet
never got warning of the
barricade in the harbor
wasn't because Mr.
Featherstone didn't relay it...
wasn't because Max intercepted it.
He said it was because you
never sent it in the first place.
And they all believed him.
I don't think anyone
actually believed it.
You weren't indicted based on the facts,
or our suspicions of your motives.
He just said it.
Only, no one had the balls to defy him.
I told them...
I should be the one to do it.
If it was gonna happen,
I thought it should be a friend.
But fuck it.
I won't do it.
You've all forgotten your oaths.
They were given to this man...
when that man was just a fiction.
To hell with all of you who
can't tell the difference!
To hell with all of you!
Stop!
Take him to the Underhill estate.
Do it.
Captain?
Is the cache on the sand yet?
The cache isn't here.
What the fuck is this?
I don't know.
Stand down. Just wait!
What are you doing here?
We escaped the governor's men.
Came back to rejoin the fight,
but didn't know if the
harbor was safe to enter.
What are you doing here?
You want to trade it?
You want to trade the cache, my cache?
It was the only way
we could avoid a fight
we were more than likely to lose.
And it guarantees us control of
the island today and for certain.
All it guarantees is we
no longer have the cache
that we all agreed was critical.
And who decided this?
You and Mr. Silver?
Ah.
- It won't work.
- It's done.
It's already agreed to.
She agreed to it.
Her people agreed.
You've agreed.
But it's all meaningless
unless and until...
he agrees.
Woodes Rogers.
He left the island for Port Royal,
as she asked, to await
her arrival with the money.
He's already agreed to it.
No, he hasn't.
What is it?
What do you see out there?
I watched him defeat
Edward Teach in battle...
outnumbered...
and through sheer force of will.
I saw his bloodlust with my own eyes.
That man will never
surrender his position here.
He will never allow himself
to be defeated by you or I.
Not because we bribed him,
not because Eleanor Guthrie told him so.
He simply will not allow it to happen.
I don't know where that man went
or what designs drew him there,
but this I know...
Woodes Rogers will be returning...
and this fight isn't nearly over.
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com