I am suggesting that we help each other
by an alliance of pirates and slaves,
bring down Nassau,
maybe bring it all down.
My name is Woodes Rogers,
and I am the next governor
of New Providence Island.
Spain... what did you
have to promise them?
That I would secure the remains
of the Urca de Lima's gold
and return it to Havana.
- You set aside some of the gold?
- She did.
- How much?
- Mm.
A cache of gems.
Spain is willing to burn
Nassau to the ground.
The only way Rogers can prevent this
is to find the cache and return it,
which means if we were to find it first,
we could dictate what happens next.
Where's Vane?
The militia arrived
before he could get away.
We had no choice but to run.
You cannot stay.
The war is going to follow that chest.
I'll go back and address the situation.
We're creating the appearance
of a man out of nothing
that the resistance against the English
feels compelled to rally around.
When he's ready, he'll
step into the role
we've created for him.
Does he have any idea
you're using his name?
Long John Silver.
It's a hard thing to look
your successor in the eye.
But as far as successors go,
your mother could do far worse.
Charles is dead.
Governor in Nassau
hung him in the square.
The resistance in
Nassau is now underway.
I think you and I both know who it was
that fashioned that noose.
I know this enemy.
He took that cache
with the express purpose
of compelling us to commit your force
to a battlefield of his choosing.
If you allow him to
dictate the terms of battle,
you court a disastrous outcome.
Tell your governor!
You tell him I'm coming!
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
"And the Lord said unto Rebecca,
"two nations are in thy womb.
"Two peoples within you
who shall be divided.
"One shall be stronger than the other.
"And the older shall serve the younger."
Twins...
as close as two things can
get to being the same one,
and what's the first thing
they do to each other?
Fight over who gets to be the first one
to see the light of day.
And here I sit at the
head of an army of men,
each of whom, present company included,
has probably at some point considered
killing the man he now fights alongside,
each of whom, present company included,
has certainly considered killing me.
If it makes you feel any better,
I haven't considered
killing you in months.
A little bit.
We're so close.
So very close.
If we can just hold
this alliance together
just a little longer, if we can just...
will it forward just a little more...
And nothing will ever be the
same for anyone ever again.
You and I have willed our
men through unthinkable things
to get this far.
Why not one more?
To call Nassau home again.
Two flags on the starboard bow!
There's no sign of
the alarm being raised.
Is it possible they
trust our false colors?
Well, anything's possible,
but I wouldn't count on it.
Maintain our current
approach, present heading.
Prepare to take courses.
Aye, Captain.
Maintain course.
All hands, stand by to change course.
Lookout reports had
five two-masted vessels
in the harbor while you were below.
That's what Billy's information
suggested we should expect.
I want more men in the yard.
With the governor's naval consort gone
and the fort lightly armed, if at all,
they won't be able to prevent
us from making our landing today.
Hmm.
Keep the course.
Stay with the land.
You still don't trust him, do you?
I understand why you do.
I don't believe that's what I asked.
I don't believe you want me
to answer what you've asked.
We are in sight of the
end of this journey,
and he's still worried this
alliance all falls apart
before we get there.
Please don't give him any more reason
to indulge that feeling.
Gun crews, prepare the
starboard batteries, double shot!
Sharpen up the yards now.
And clew our courses as
we approach the harbor.
Helm, once we've cleared the reefs,
head up two points so that
we might begin our run.
Aye, sir.
One of us should probably say something.
About what?
I don't know, the moment?
Remind the men in whose name
this fight is to be fought?
You think they've forgotten?
No, but we are emotional
beings, after all,
and rhetoric is the
fuel that feeds the fire.
For 10,000 years, a man
anticipating conquest
- has stood before his army...
- Do it.
Friends, a word before it all begins.
It's no wonder you don't say much.
If you please.
Lads, hey, listen up.
Thank you.
All of us have given
some part of ourselves
to reach this moment.
Today, we reclaim what is ours.
And we seek retribution
for what was taken from us.
Today there will be vengeance
for the death of Charles Vane.
What is it?
The governor's sloops aren't moving.
Well, what would you have them doing?
Outgunned as they are, maybe nothing.
Maybe something.
What the hell does that mean?
The Revenge is almost
in range of the fort.
No guns.
It's just as Billy said.
Standby the anchor!
And signal the Eagle to
offer her larboard batteries
to hold those sloops at bay.
What the fuck is the Defiant doing?
Why is she cutting across our bow?
The Defiant's altering course!
Helm! Hard to starboard!
Hard over!
Trim in all the sails!
Brace up sharp!
Take the larboard bow! Move ahead!
- Let the sheets fly!
Let the sheets fly!
Let go of the line!
Watch out for the cannons!
Look out! Brace yourselves!
Can we get free?
Get to the guns!
Get the shots!
Looks like the barricade held, sir.
Your orders?
Open fire.
Eastern battery, open fire.
- Fire!
Take cover!
Brace ahead!
Signal the sloops to engage.
Engage the sloops!
Signal to pursue!
I'm giving the order!
Not yet.
If we don't get these men
off the ship, they're dead.
If we don't find a way to harass
those guns, everyone's dead.
Harass them with what?
The starboard guns can't elevate enough
to get anywhere near that fort.
All hands!
Reset the topsails and t'gallants!
Now!
Ready top sails!
Ready those guns!
T'gallants!
- Pull! Pull!
- Put your backs into it!
Pull those lines!
Pull! Pull!
Top sails in the corner.
Top sails!
Reload with chain shot
and target their canvas.
- Reload with chain shot!
- Go!
Fire!
Gun crews!
On my mark!
Fire!
Ah!
Abandon ship! All hands!
Abandon ship!
Get the ladders over!
Get on the longboats.
What are you doing?
I'll be the slowest one.
Get on the ladder!
It's all right. Go.
Go!
Why aren't we moving in closer?
We cannot fire the great
guns into that mess.
We'll kill as many of
our own men as theirs.
But if we run with the one ship
that still presents a
threat to the governor,
he may very well chase
and give the survivors
their best chance of escaping
to the fallback position
on the eastern shore.
And if they don't chase?
Come on! Get in the longboat!
I got ya!
Fall, sir!
We're not gonna make it!
Return fire!
In the wind!
Shall we pursue the man-of-war, my Lord?
It'd be the cost of
rounding up those longboats.
Are you certain your
men can capture her?
Teach is a formidable opponent,
but his ship is weakened, and my
men can attack from three directions
with greater numbers
with greater discipline.
Tactically, he's greatly disadvantaged.
Between tactics and passion,
I'll take the latter.
If our information's
correct and he seeks revenge
over the death of Charles Vane,
he will fight with passion today.
Revenge is a powerful
motivator, undoubtedly.
Fortunately, my men would like
a little of it for themselves as well.
Do it.
Signal to pursue!
Inform the council I'll return
once the street is secure.
And please have someone
retrieve my wife.
Of course, my Lord.
Oh, fuck.
It has been quiet for some time.
Is that bad for us or bad for them?
Hard to say.
If it were bad for us, I
assume we would know by now.
For whose benefit is that?
I'm told that once mastered,
it's actually quite soothing.
At this moment, I'm finding
that hard to believe.
But if I am to play the role,
I ought to make some
effort to look the part.
It bothers me that this
does not bother you.
What's that?
This. That.
All of it.
The world is changing so
rapidly and we with it.
I fear the day will soon come
when we will no longer recognize either.
We are who we are.
Nothing so important changes so quickly.
Mrs. Rogers?
The governor requests your presence.
Two ships grounded and only
one escaped the barricade.
Three ships grounded.
Teach is still loose.
All things considered,
we are very lucky.
I'm sorry you weren't there to see it.
I know it cannot be
comfortable to be so removed.
I don't know.
I got to make this.
I am sure there were
others that found themselves
more uncomfortable today than I.
Company at the ready!
Company!
And I told you before we
ever set foot on this island
I will do whatever necessary
to ensure your success here.
If the street understands
us better when I sit
among your men's wives
rather than your men,
if the world makes more
sense to them that way
and your authority grows because of it,
as uncomfortable as it may be,
then that is a compromise
I am willing to make.
Governor?
I'll send for you as
soon as I'm satisfied
the street is secure.
Captain.
That's the last one.
According to the men who just landed,
that is the last longboat.
I heard the same.
I'm told they saw an injured man
pulled aboard from out of the water,
almost drowned.
I heard the same.
Here I must be careful.
I have well over 200
men unaccounted for.
Those who remain, it will be very hard
to explain to them why,
with all I have to attend
to, I choose to stand here
hanging onto the fate
of just one of them.
I know that you and he
had been working
closely together of late,
become friends even.
I don't know what I'm trying to say.
Perhaps just that...
he is my friend, too.
- They obstructed the harbor!
- I know.
Two ships they sunk!
It must have taken them days to arrange!
- I know, I...
- Then why the fuck didn't you warn us?!
I did warn you!
There were three ships, not two.
He bought them cheap out of Abaco.
He scuttled them six days ago.
The moment I learned of it, I
sent word to Mr. Featherstone.
He was supposed to send word
to you not to enter the harbor.
Then Mr. Featherstone has fucked us all.
Yes, I know that, too.
Is this all that's left?
Teach and the Revenge
are unaccounted for.
I saw them sailing north
away from the harbor under pursuit.
The rest...
are presumed dead or captured.
And Silver?
Which is he?
There'll be debts to repay after today.
And there'll be plenty of time to do it.
But right now, we need
to get off the sand.
Where are you?
What?
We sail for Nassau soon.
There are many other places I could be
in this moment to prepare.
I choose to be here.
Where have you just chosen to go?
We received word today from Nassau
that Billy's resistance movement
has proclaimed its fealty
to a pirate king,
a man who would one day return
to Nassau from his exile,
expel the English,
and punish those who betrayed the cause.
You left my bed for that?
Now, the pirate king's name...
is Long John Silver.
Long John Silver?
Yeah.
Who is Long John Silver?
Well, that's a very good question.
I assume he saw value in the tall tales
told about me after
that night in the tavern.
Saw mystery in it, perhaps.
Use my name upon which
to build his story.
And this bothers you why?
We've come this far because when
Flint and I are of the same mind,
there's no obstacle yet
encountered that we cannot surmount.
I don't know why that is.
He doesn't know why it is.
But it is.
To elevate one of us over the other,
even as a fiction,
seems to me to be tempting
fate in a most dangerous way.
And...
And it upsets you because
you believe he is your friend?
Yes, it upsets me.
And I know that Billy's
been looking for a way
to remove Flint from
our lives for months now.
I'm sure that's somewhere
at the root of this.
And I don't like having him
conscripting me into his cause
without me even having a say.
I'm sorry.
Because I believe he is my friend?
Are you questioning
whether I'm qualified
to have an opinion on that subject?
Did you not once tell me of your worry
about the fate of those
whom Captain Flint has
called friends before you?
A lot has changed since then.
A lot has changed since
then, but what has not changed
is that when a man first needs you
and thereafter calls you a friend,
a little suspicion is a healthy thing.
That'd make a lot more
sense if I didn't need him
just as badly as he needs me.
I don't believe you do.
Whatever he is to you,
whatever you are to him...
I don't believe you need
him to be the man you are.
I think you would be a very good king.
If I were a no-good pirate,
I would follow you wherever you led.
Take the courses. Brace
the main and mizzen aback.
Haul in the guns.
Close all the gun ports.
You're letting up?
With the damage done to the rig,
I can't maneuver our broadside around
fast enough to be of any effect.
The sloops are too nimble.
But hauling in the guns?
They'll board us easily.
I was always told that you
were the one without fear.
Was I misinformed?
It ain't fear to want
to do a hard thing smart.
He wants this fight.
Let him have it.
Prepare to be boarded!
My Lord,
the squad is returning
from the outer beaches.
All told, the captives number 75.
Well, there are more
out there. There must be.
With our numbers, our ability to search
outside Nassau town is limited.
Without any sense of where to look...
And what about informants?
Informants?
Well, there must be
someone in town who knows
where the pirates would go to hide.
I understand they might be
hesitant to come forward yesterday,
with the outcome in doubt, but today?
Are you telling me that literally no one
has offered assistance?
Oh, of course they haven't.
Why would they when it is so much easier
to do nothing at all?
Somewhere on the other
side of the world,
Spain and England are
fighting yet another war
over what king will
sit upon what throne.
Meanwhile we fight an enemy here
determined to see all
of civilization collapse.
The only thing standing between
them and their goal is you and I,
and no one else seems willing
to lift a finger to help.
I hope at some point
someone will explain to me
what sort of sense any of that makes.
Don't look at me! Keep moving.
You heard, move.
How many others?
On your knees!
Captured nine more just
east of the fence line.
We think this one's
Flint's ship's master.
You are part of Flint's inner circle?
If you have information about
Captain Flint's contingency plans,
it may argue in favor of leniency.
Go fuck yourself.
Pull him up.
You don't remember me, do you?
I was there that day in the forest,
when your trap was sprung.
I saw what your people did to my men.
I was told that after the fact,
the children of the camp...
were encouraged to remove the
ears from men I called friends.
Trophies to mark the victory.
We that remain do so in violation
of our orders to return home,
a breach of our duty
to His Majesty's Army.
Someday, if we see England again,
I imagine we'll have to answer for it.
Hold him.
But some things are
more important than duty.
No, n-no!
I doubt they'll turn on
their own kind, my Lord.
This isn't that sort of a war anymore.
I want the trials started
as soon as possible.
I want this behind us.
Of course.
After you defeated his forces,
the naval commander notified the
governor he was quitting Nassau,
took his fleet right to London.
One subordinate, Captain Berringer,
he led a mutiny of a few hundred men
determined to stay and
avenge their defeat.
Swore a loyalty oath
to Rogers personally,
and then began a purge in town of anyone
even suspected of having
a connection to our cause.
What kind of purge?
Well, hangings, torture.
Eventually the street was
more afraid of him than of us,
and the black spots had
ceased having any effect.
So we challenged him directly,
tried to force our way into town, but...
his men are fanatical,
and the fighting was most bloody.
At its worst, Berringer tried to
reach out from town into our camp,
turned two of our men against us,
help finish us off for good.
Fortunately we were able to
discover the plot in time.
The lines are settled now.
He controls the town but little else.
My people have free reign over
most of the rest of the island.
Your people?
The scouts are returning.
I'll meet you inside.
Is it over?
Is what over?
You looked into my mother's eyes
and you said a great
war lay ahead of us,
one in which pirates and
slaves would stand together
and strike a blow that might
shake the very foundation
of the British Empire.
Now our ships are gone,
our army is fractured,
battered, and beaten.
And the only man among
you I trusted is dead.
I'm asking you...
if this war died with him.
Come down! Open this
door! Get over here!
It is the opinion of this court
that the evidence brought to bear
against this particular defendant
is both abundant and incontrovertible.
Having afforded him ample opportunity
to speak in his own defense...
121 prisoners we took today.
Had our enemies 121 prisoners of ours,
I imagine their deaths
would be swift and cruel.
For us, it means 121 prisoners
to be housed and guarded,
121 mouths to feed,
121 trials to process.
Never let it be said
that civilization came
to anyone easily here.
And these trials,
they will all be taking place here?
It would please me if you
would accommodate it, yes.
Judge Adams and his... court,
we have all seen in recent
weeks since their arrival
that their appetites are significant.
Shall I expect to be reimbursed
for the costs of this?
You stood in my office
and said you wished us to be friends.
As my friend, I would think
you would be eager to do your part
to see our common enterprise
survive its current crisis.
I beg your pardon, my Lord,
but have I not proved
to you my friendship?
At great personal risk to
myself and my interests,
I made enemies of the pirates
in order to ensure your success.
Made enemies of them?
They've been my enemies
for some time now.
Are you saying that
they haven't been yours?
- May I suggest...
- I thank you for your aid today.
It is, I believe, to be expected,
today, tomorrow, every
day till the war is won.
That is the burden that
we all ought to share.
I serve you best, my Lord,
when I am seen by the street
as having some independence from you,
as your silent partner, I am able...
There are no silent partners anymore.
I will have no more of them.
This is now an island of true friends
and mortal enemies
and nothing in between.
Now, in this moment, I still
believe you are among the former.
Should I have any reason
to believe otherwise?
Of course not, my Lord.
Thank you.
Give us the room.
I don't have exact numbers,
but it sounds as though there's already
been a significant number of prisoners
captured from the harbor.
I assume they'll push to
start the hangings right away,
which doesn't leave us much time.
Now, even with your men here,
we don't have sufficient numbers
to move on Nassau directly
and be assured victory.
But if we could dramatically
increase those numbers...
Increase them how?
The Underhill plantation.
It's the largest and richest
of the interior estates,
and it's home to well over 200 slaves.
It's well-defended.
Until now, I haven't had
the manpower to take it.
But now, with the men we have
here, I think it's possible,
and if we could convince even half
of those slaves to join our fight,
we might then actually be
in a position to take back...
Too long.
What you're suggesting, we
don't have time for that.
- Well, it'll take a few days...
- The governor may be on his heels,
but he won't stay that way for long.
It will be days, hours
maybe, before he finds a way
to set his feet beneath
him and retrench.
We need to strike
quickly, directly at Nassau
with as many forces as
we can muster and today.
- Hang on...
- We are two battered fighters
at the end of a long fight.
The next blow struck
may be a decisive one,
and we have to be the one that strikes.
Stop.
I prepared these men to
follow Long John Silver
upon his return.
Now, if you assume that in his absence,
that role now reverts to you...
then you assume wrong.
See, my men know your name,
but you weren't the one who
recruited them into this.
You weren't the one who led
them in those midnight raids
in the western plantations.
You weren't the one
who has lived with them
and drank with them and bled with them.
So in the absence of Long John Silver,
the men will look to me, not you,
for answers to what happens next,
and I will be the one to
give them those answers,
not you.
I have become so easily
set aside, have I?
Do you have value to me? Yes.
Would your skill in a
fight aid us in our efforts?
Of course.
But do we need you here?
No. We do not.
You're forgetting one thing.
Somewhere on an island a
few days' journey from here
is a chest filled with treasure
buried in a secret place,
and of the three men
who know of that place,
I may be the last one alive after today.
Are you threatening to withhold
the location of the chest
that every man here is counting upon
to provide for Nassau's
treasury once we secure it
solely so you can maintain
your own status here?
There is an unthinkable
victory within our reach,
and I will see this through
by whatever means I have at my disposal.
This seems like the act
of a small man to you.
Were he here, I'm sure,
Mr. Silver would make this all sound
more agreeable to you.
But without him, think what you like.
My word will govern.
I know, too.
Three men know the
resting place of the chest,
and one woman.
He told it to me before we left home.
It would be preferable
if there were one voice
to govern here tomorrow,
but I don't think it's
going to be quite so simple.
There will be no pirate king here.
Of that much, I am certain.
Are you through?
Yes.
Then go.
When was the last time
you fought in a vanguard?
He ain't never gonna see
you in that way, Teach.
I know why you want him to,
but it ain't never gonna happen.
You think that little
of me that I care so much
how I'm seen in his eyes,
I'd be willing to lose my life over it?
Then why did you do it?
When I was in that
carriage with the governor,
when your horses first appeared,
I had a chance to end it all.
Had my hands round his neck.
Had I done more in that moment,
had I been more in that moment...
Charles would still be here.
The idea that he might
be looking down on me
in this moment and find me not doing
everything in my power to
see his death answered for,
that is something I'm willing
to put my life at risk over,
how I'm seen in his eyes.
Charles Vane stood by us
when no one else would.
Charles Vane risked his life for us.
Charles Vane...
Oh, fuck Charles Vane.
I know how you felt about him.
I felt the same way, and you know it.
But he's dead.
And I can't see what
fucking sense it makes
to keep trying to make him happy.
And all it's actually gonna
lead to is you joining him.
If it had been me
strung up in that square,
you'd feel the same way?
I came here 'cause we all agreed
we had a chance to take Nassau back,
have a place of our own.
I ain't here to prove anything!
I ain't here to figure out who I am.
And I sure as shit ain't
here to pretend a dead man
might think better of me for it.
We are all here towards the
end of retaking the island.
In terms of motive,
maybe we'll all just have to accept
that we're driven by different things.
Yeah?
And what happens when those motives
start demanding their own ends?
And this thing we're all a part of
starts splitting right down the middle?
That isn't going to happen.
It already is.
What did he do?
Set a course for Nassau...
to send a message when we return...
that this can all end...
if the governor turns over
the one thing he wants.
When I made the choice to see
Charles' sentence carried out,
I did not know what the
consequences would be.
I knew it was the only way
to protect our future here,
to protect you, so I did it.
And when the backlash followed,
the resentment over my
relationship with you,
which I knew could only
be soothed by my pretending
to have no influence
at all, I did that, too.
I did all of it, contorted
myself into the role,
mutilated myself so that it
would fit because I believed
as long as you believed
I was your partner,
it didn't matter what
anyone else believed.
I've never believed you to
be anything less than that.
Good, then can you tell me
what the fuck just happened back there?
I am asking her to
bear no more sacrifice
than you or I or a dozen others.
You're not asking her to bear anything.
You have saddled her with
the cost of those trials.
You might as well have stolen
the money to pay for it,
but that is not what I am
talking about and you know it.
To be my partner in
this, there are things
that you are better off
letting me worry about.
That is not what you said.
No more silent partners.
We all bear the burden of this together.
What is it you are not telling me?
I don't want to be
protected. I don't want it.
I need to know why you're behaving
as if victory is so far away
when to me, it seems that
it is so close at hand.
When I informed Sarah of my intent
to formally end our marriage,
I did not know what the
consequences would be.
I didn't imagine they
would be significant.
We'd barely spoken in years.
Her reaction...
was more significant
than I'd anticipated.
What did she do?
Her family intervened with
a few of my larger creditors
and persuaded them to accelerate
my timetables for repayment.
And if those creditors call the loans,
it will force the others to follow suit.
I would default.
The courts would issue the warrant,
and I would be a fugitive from the law.
England is at war.
There is no money from them
to support our efforts here.
So I have had to assume substantial
private debts to do so...
Debts which grow by the day.
And as it would seem,
the only thing more costly
than our defeats are our victories.
Debts which will
require the swift return
of commerce here if they
are ever to be repaid,
commerce whose return at the moment
seems so very far away.
Why didn't you tell me?
You are not a compromise to me.
I do not regret what I did,
no matter the consequences.
And I didn't want you to have
any reason to think that I did.
Her family has the ability to do that,
to manipulate your creditors so easily?
Creditors respond to money.
And they respond to influence.
Her family has both.
I understand.
But...
so does mine.
Long John Silver.
Welcome home.
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com