My instinct is the
same now as it was then.
I will show them what
the consequences are
for threatening that
which I hold most dear.
Secure the rest of them.
Set a course for Nassau.
- You want to withdraw?
- If we don't,
it will be the end of whatever trust
exists between us and
the slaves on the island.
The only way to free them safely
is if it is all at once...
simultaneous revolts across the island.
Billy and his men are our enemies
now, but these men are not.
Why do we need an escort to the fort?
Quickly, please. We
don't have much time.
Threats have been made.
The story's been told.
Everyone in Nassau knows what
Long John Silver's return means,
what's expected of them
when he does return.
All that remains is for him to return.
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
We're not apart on this island.
We cannot be apart.
Many of you have got kin
at the Underhill estate.
A reminder of how our fates
are bound together here.
And then that kin of
yours aided in a revolt
where three...
Mr. Underhill, his wife,
and nine-year-old daughter
were murdered in cold blood.
What happened there is paid for here.
I pray a lesson that will
not soon be forgotten.
Have you got something to say, Julius?
Get them back in the barracks.
- Nassau's fallen.
- Aye.
Get them back inside!
- Come on, protect the lady!
- It's okay, it's okay! Stay down.
- Quick, get on out of here!
- Help her up! Help her up!
Get on!
Go, go, go!
- Over here!
- Yah! Yah!
Yah!
- You're hurt.
- I'm fine.
Is there a list of
everyone who made it inside?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Bring it to me, please.
And find Max as well. I need
to speak with her right away.
Move the harbor-facing guns.
I want them pointed toward the town
and ready for our first barrage.
- What is going on here?
- Everything is under control, ma'am.
We'll have our counterattack
underway before nightfall.
We're not moving those guns.
There will be no barrage and
there will be no counterattack.
I beg your pardon?
Firing those guns isn't
likely to achieve anything
other than advertising
our panic and fear.
Not to mention wasting shot and powder,
which will be invaluable when
the time does come for its use.
With all due respect, madam,
it is our duty to do
everything within our power
- to retake Nassau town.
- It's lost.
For the moment, Nassau town is lost.
That much is painfully clear.
It is our duty now to
secure ourselves here,
conserve resources,
and hold out until the governor returns
with whatever aid he was able to
muster to combine with our force.
Then we will launch a credible assault
to drive out Captain Flint and his men.
I've ensured we have stores
and provision to last us weeks.
But what if the
governor does not return?
He will return.
And we will be prepared to join him
in fighting our enemy when he does.
Mrs. Rogers.
Is that the list?
- Yes, ma'am, but...
- Where is Max?
- I thought I asked you to fetch her.
- She's not here, ma'am.
She isn't here? What do
you mean she isn't here?
She was the first name
I gave you to secure.
I sent two of my best
men to retrieve her.
But apparently between there
and here, they were unsuccessful.
Nassau works best when its men know
what crews they belong to
and what captains they answer to.
Without structure, disorder
is only to be expected.
Now, you will begin...
with men that you know and trust.
And from there, you will
begin to reorganize your crews
as quickly as possible.
Crews? With no ships?
Well, we've all hunted
small... piraguas or less.
It'll have to start there
until things are settled.
But it is the only way there will be
any semblance of order in the meantime.
There aren't gonna be many men out there
eager to take orders anytime soon.
You were chosen...
because I thought you were worthy
to be the first captain's counsel
of a restored Nassau.
Do I need to reconsider?
You heard him.
What did he think?
He was going to get a
different answer from me?
Well, if in doubt, ask
someone else, I suppose.
The more they realize there is
no daylight between you and I,
the more they will learn to
accept our shared authority.
Is it safe, then, to admit
that I'm not sure he's wrong?
It's bad out there.
Worse than I anticipated.
All life begins in violence
and wailing. It will pass.
A lot of things begin
with violence and wailing.
A lot of them end up that way, too.
- Though, I admire your optimism.
- Captain.
What news from the beach?
The governor's close council
and several dozen soldiers
have managed to secure
themselves inside the fort.
- Eleanor Guthrie, is she among them?
- She is.
And she sent a note.
She sent it?
She's taken charge of them all already?
It's an offer of an exchange.
20 of our men captured
during the invasion
and held in the fort...
for Max.
20 men following orders would
make a big difference out there.
I agree. Unfortunately,
I don't think we have Max.
Do we have Max?
Does anyone know where she is?
All right. Grab some men.
Set about finding her.
She's not in the fort. She
couldn't have gotten very far.
And Billy?
Where is Billy?
I couldn't say. I saw some
of his men by the beach,
but I assumed we were keeping
our distance from them.
Keeping our distance?
He's stolen the army that
pledged its allegiance to us,
not to mention the damaged he's caused
with our alliance to the slave
communities on this island.
There are a thousand men out there
who've been awaiting my arrival.
They're now armed and angry and
I haven't yet said a word to them.
If the first five are,
"Billy Bones has crossed you,"
would you care to
guess what happens next?
Go out there and put forth the word.
If Billy isn't in this
room within the hour,
I promise him...
he will regret it.
You heard him.
Sails!
South-southwest!
Heading north.
She's coming from Nassau.
A boat that small headed to open water?
- Set a course to intercept her.
- Aye, sir.
Coming aboard.
Mr. Rawls!
Governor. Thank you.
You've no idea how
grateful we are to see you.
What happened in Nassau?
The pirates, they took it.
They killed him, Captain
Berringer, right in the square.
Slit his throat on the gallows.
We just barely escaped
before it was all overrun.
- Gloucestershire, has she departed yet?
- Sir?
My ship in the harbor,
the one that was to depart
for Philadelphia with my wife,
was she still there when you left?
I am about to make haste to Nassau.
I cannot afford to tow that sloop along.
You will take her and
sail for Port Royal
where you will deliver
the prisoners in her hold
to Governor Addison and
his men. Do you understand?
I... I could send Mr. Chase, sir...
I would like for it
to be you, Lieutenant.
There are 42 pirates in
the belly of that ship
and I can spare no more than
a handful of men to see to her.
I beg your pardon, my
Lord. I want to be a part...
I understand you wanna be part
of the fight that's coming.
I understand you want
retribution for Captain Berringer.
Right now, the successful
transfer of those prisoners
is what I need from you.
Do you understand me?
Yes, my Lord.
There's a fight
soon to be underway in Nassau.
A fight that...
we are entitled to be a part of.
A fight to answer a cowardly crime.
A fight...
that's been stolen from us
by you fucking people.
So...
the way I see it,
each one of you owes us a fight.
And Mr. Milton...
is here to collect.
Excuse me.
Still reports coming in.
Gonna need more muskets!
I think we're all properly angry
about what he did on
the Underhill estate.
- What he did?
- Yes.
But a very wise woman recently told me
that one should not allow
their personal feelings
to cloud the reality of the situation,
which in both that case and this...
is that Billy has influence
that is best not ignored.
That sounds like good advice.
Was it given before or after
he tried to kill the two of you?
Here he comes.
The Boyd brothers launched a raid
on one of the governor's
munition stores.
We just managed to put it down.
I think we can all
agree it helps none of us
to have those idiots armed to the teeth.
Yeah.
Lest you think I've been avoiding you.
We've had our hands full out there,
trying to manage the transition.
That's good.
Though, uh,
I think we ought to discuss...
what it's a transition to.
Certainly.
Where would you like to begin?
What happened on that estate?
Was the aftermath not what we feared?
As it will be difficult
to fully defend Nassau
without the assistance of the
slave communities of this island,
as our relationship
with those communities
is likely severely damaged
as a result of this,
it will be critical...
that she proceed to the estate at once
and attempt to repair that relationship
to whatever extent is possible.
Can we trust...
that you will guarantee
she will be received there safely?
'Course we can.
Of course Billy would never violate
the trust I place in him as a brother...
as a friend,
to allow harm to come
to those closest to me.
For if Billy
were to do something
as disloyal as that,
he knows I'd stop at nothing
to see that offense repaid against him.
- I will see to it.
- I should fucking hope so.
Is everyone feeling better...
now they've got that off their chests?
I ask as I'm wondering
when would be a good time
for us to talk about Max.
What about her?
You don't think there's anything
going on in Nassau right now
that I don't know about, do you?
I'm aware of the prisoner exchange
offered by the holdouts in the fort.
Meaning what?
You're going to help us find her?
Find her?
I have her.
I am responsible...
for delivering all 42 of
you to the law in Port Royal.
Let me dispel that
notion for you right away.
It won't be happening.
I assume there is some token number
I must actually deliver
for appearance's sake.
How many that is I...
I honestly couldn't say.
You're the captain now
that Teach is dead, yes?
I am.
Then you choose.
Choose?
Which of your men is
going to be the first?
Fuck you.
You choose...
or it starts with your partner here.
Mr. Carver.
- Come on!
- Ah!
Who's next?
We'd found her with a small escort,
trying to move her up
to the fort, I assume.
If you want her,
I think there are some things
we ought to discuss first...
about our transition.
And I think it would be for the
best if it was just you and I.
I'm walking out of here with her.
To whatever extent you think
you have leverage enough
to extort something from me over it...
I'd reconsider.
Five minutes.
Five minutes?
You listen to what I have
to say for five minutes,
and she's yours.
Do we have a deal?
Clock's ticking.
Have you stopped to ask yourself...
why they want her so badly?
Because when I first heard
what happened in the harbor,
I knew it couldn't have been
Featherstone that fucked us.
He's been with us from the start
and he wouldn't have had the
nerve to cross me like that.
So, I knew it had to be someone else,
someone in proximity to him.
Someone bold enough to want to cross us
and dangerous enough to follow through.
So, from there, the list
got very short very quickly.
Max fucked us.
If it wasn't for her, we
likely take Nassau whole,
fleet intact, no prisoners in the fort,
no fight between you and I.
Instead,
here we are.
Now, one would think
we could go a long way towards
soothing all that chaos out there,
and the anger driving it...
if we could draw everyone together
to see justice done to the
one responsible for all of it.
- All of it?
- Enough of it.
Did they not hold their
trials in her tavern?
Did she not finance the regime directly?
You don't think I could
sell that out there?
Because Eleanor Guthrie knows I could.
That's why the first thing she asked for
the moment those gates
closed behind her was Max.
That's how valuable she could be to us.
And you wanna trade
that away for 20 men?
Those 20 men are your brothers.
Those men's lives mean as
much to me as they do to you.
And I assure you...
they mean a hell of a lot more
to me than they do to Flint.
You know as well as I do
the only reason he wants them free
is because the only
soldiers in town are mine
and the prisoners in the fort
are likely to still follow his...
I'm going to stop you right there.
From the moment you began
concocting this story,
I knew it was with an eye
towards pushing him out.
- Separating the two of us so you can...
- The two of you?
How long ago was it
that the two of us agreed
that Flint threatened
to be the end of us all?
That he would find ways of
driving us over and over again
into that storm till
there was none of us left?
We survived him...
you and I.
And now you want to
follow him into what?
A massive slave revolt?
A war against the British Empire?
How is this not just the next storm
in a very long line of them?
You told me once that the
people he holds closest
are the most at risk of
being consumed by him.
And he and I have
discussed it at length.
So, I thank you for your concern.
But I'm going to be just fine.
And I'm not talking about you.
I understand that you've
come to care for her.
Madi.
Be very...
very careful, Billy.
If anyone is at risk
of being consumed by
his need for this war...
it's her.
Time's up.
I heard you were there.
What?
The last time when we
ran off the English,
took control.
I heard you was a navy man then.
Heard you saw it all.
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
That was a good day for me.
Did a thing no one else would.
Or could.
Thought I'd earned a place by
Blackbeard's side for an age.
Turns out it wasn't nearly so long
as I thought it would be.
Before Blackbeard decided
he could do better than me.
Is there a point you're trying to make?
You're counseling Long John
Silver to be reasonable.
Hmm?
To do what you want him to do
instead of what he wants to do.
Just wondering how long
you think he'll suffer it...
before he decides he
can do better than you.
Go get her now.
What the hell happened in there?
We won. That's all that matters.
There will be no
mission to Philadelphia.
I assume that much is clear by now.
Our chances of success there
were slim to begin with.
That the idea that I might
stand in front of my grandfather
and suggest that Nassau
is still a viable concern,
worthy of his investment, when...
refugees are fleeing in droves...
planters face a revolt
of their laborers...
and men with swords murder
wantonly in the streets.
Oh, Christ.
I am right back where I started.
Every fight I have ever won...
every death I have escaped,
every sacrifice I have
had bled out of me,
it will all have to be repeated
just to get things back to
where they were a few hours ago.
There's some kind of
hell it seems to me to be.
But I want you to know,
at the first opportunity,
I will see you returned back home.
I gave you my word.
I intend to honor it.
This fight ahead does not belong
to you, nor to your children.
I won't have you bear any more of it.
Would you consider joining me?
To London?
You have been living in
our home for some time now.
I don't imagine there's much about
my husband and I that you don't know.
With the debt he owes, he is
going to be fighting this fight
for the rest of his life.
And for as long as he
is chained to this place,
then I am as well.
I wonder, ma'am, if he
might want you to leave.
Especially...
when he learns of your...
current state of being.
I beg your pardon, ma'am,
but seeing what I see in your service...
I fear there are things
I may know about you
that even the governor
does not yet know.
I have grown quite fond of you, ma'am.
You are someone who is
determined to be better today
than you were yesterday.
And in this world,
that is in short supply.
And so I find myself
feeling protective of you.
And if I am feeling that way,
fearing the thought of you bearing
a child in this environment...
I can only imagine how concerned
your husband would be.
When my family first arrived here...
I remember my...
mother and father had
a terrible argument.
She told him that this was
no place for a little girl.
That it was cruel.
I stay,
and our child is raised
amongst all this brutality.
I go, and my husband...
is left alone to face it on his own.
Amazing, this place.
Somehow leaves no options other
than to hurt the ones you love.
Ma'am, there's a messenger at the gate.
They've agreed to the exchange.
That's it!
Another one now!
Knock his fucking teeth out.
Any man stood a chance
against him is dead.
If we don't try something
they ain't expecting,
then we're all fucking dead.
If any of the men who stood
a chance to beat him are dead,
then what do you suggest?
Any man.
Absolutely... absolutely you can not.
The ones of us they don't get down here,
we're just gonna swing in
Port Royal in a few days.
- Get up. Get up!
- You gotta trust me.
He asks you for a name,
you don't say shit.
And you let him take me.
Another name, Captain.
Captain?
Will you be choosing or will I?
All right.
Her.
Nice and slow.
You like it rough, don't you?
Make her bleed.
I think she likes you, Mr. Milton.
Well, take her!
Yes, my love.
Get up. Get up!
Ooh.
On your feet. Get up!
Come on, Mil, what you waiting for?
Come on, get up!
On your feet.
Come on, my pretty.
Anne, get up.
Move!
I would think some sort of
thanks might be in order.
Billy was more than ready to
throw you to the wolves out there.
And to be honest,
I was undecided about whether to
go through with this deal at all.
Sure..
I get my men back in exchange for you.
But something tells me...
if I free you,
you'll find a way to be
a problem for me again,
and soon.
Of course not.
Why would I do that?
When you and I last saw each other...
you had every reason to see me killed.
Certainly would've solved
a lot of problems for you.
And yet you didn't.
Why?
You know,
I've had a rough few days owing to you.
I'd be angrier about it,
but I'm a little preoccupied
being angry with other people.
I just asked you a simple question.
Why didn't you kill me
when you had the chance?
It would have solved some problems.
It would have caused others
that I chose not to live with.
What sort of problems
would it have caused?
That I would have had to live with it.
You said you wished to send me away.
Somewhere where I couldn't return.
Out of curiosity,
how were you planning to manage that?
When Anne was recruiting
spies in Port Royal,
she met a man with an
estate in the wilderness,
north of Spanish Florida.
A reform-minded man...
who uses convicts as laborers.
Convicts he solicits
from prisons in England
where their treatment
is far less humane.
This man, we were told,
found it profitable
to offer his services
to wealthy families,
some of the most prominent
in London on occasion,
with a need to make troublesome
family members disappear.
Cared for,
tended to,
but never to be seen
or heard from again.
What families?
Do you know what families
in London made use of this?
I have no idea.
They're ready.
Billy told me I should worry...
that you will be Madi's end.
That's all he wanted
in exchange for Max.
For me to sit still...
while he warned me that your commitment
to the greatest possible
victory in this war of ours...
would consume her and
eventually lead to her death.
Well, that's a smart
thing for him to say
if his intent is to split us apart.
I suppose we should've
expected nothing less.
Do I need to be concerned
that you took almost two
hours to tell me about it?
We are at our least rational...
when we're at our most vulnerable.
If nothing else, this is a good reminder
that without a doubt
she is the point at which
I'm my most vulnerable.
The thought of losing her...
I see.
If we assume...
that we are on the verge
of some impossible victory here,
a truly significant thing...
if we assume that is real
and here for the taking...
wouldn't you trade it all to
have Thomas Hamilton back again?
I think if he knew how close we were
to the victory he gave
his life to achieve...
he wouldn't want me to.
I see.
Though, that wasn't really
what I asked, was it?
Assume his father was just
as dark as you say, but...
was unable to murder his own son,
assume he found a way...
- to secret Thomas away from London...
- He didn't.
Would you trade this war to make it so?
It is some kind of hell
to be forced to choose one
irreplaceable thing over another.
And while Billy's motive to
separate us is painfully transparent,
it took me two hours
to tell you about it
because try as I may to get the
conversation out of my head...
I just can't seem to do it.
The closer we get to
the end of this journey,
the more the contradictions
will accumulate...
confusing issues we
once thought were clear.
I suppose the good news
is that's how we'll know
we're finally getting
somewhere interesting.
- All clear!
- Clear the fort!
Close the gate!
What can I do for you, ma'am?
Why are they still in chains?
We freed the ones that understood
we came as friends here,
not as enemies.
But some, it seemed, bore us ill will
over some of the consequences
of our victory here.
You have to know,
it is important to ask
to repair the alliance
between Captain Flint's people and ours.
Important to me.
After you fled,
the pirates sent warnings
to the other estates that...
any violence done to the slaves
in their possession
for what happened here
would be answered.
The next morning, an
answer was left by the gate.
A sack filled with fingers.
White fingers.
Reprisals were visited
upon our loved ones
upon the Edwards estate.
Reprisals of the cruelest kind
intended to instill fear,
break spirits, reassert control.
It did not have the intended effect.
They revolted.
One of the men there started it.
A man named Julius.
Now he's forming an army out there,
organizing, building strength,
an army with designs on
taking and holding Nassau.
But with as much anger
towards the pirates
and anyone who would call
himself friend to a pirate
as they do towards the English.
That is why they are still in chains,
out of fear that they might
rise up and join Julius's army
before ever submitting to yours.
We tried to prevent the reprisals
the moment we learned of them,
Captain Flint and I.
- They must know that.
- They know.
But they also know that
when it comes to these men,
neither you nor Captain Flint
are fully in control of them.
Then we will get control of them.
You must see by now that when
you wage war on the world,
the world fights back.
Your mother knew that.
Knew that the best one can do
is to find a place you can protect,
build a wall, and save who you can.
You'd be wise to learn from her example.
I'm sorry for what happened today.
The moment I realized
what was about to happen,
I sent men to find you.
I'm just thankful we were
able to get you in time.
You are sorry...
for what happened today.
What happened today...
was exactly what I have
been warning you about
from the moment you and your
husband first arrived here.
Again...
and again, and again.
That the decisions
you made at every turn
would eventually lead us to this.
Everything I have is gone...
because of it.
If you wish to apologize,
what happened today...
does not begin to cover it.
Where would we have gone?
What?
A long time ago, you asked
me to leave Nassau with you
to avoid ruin.
If I had said yes,
where would we have gone?
I have no idea.
I was so close to saying yes.
There were good reasons
to say yes and...
I heard it in my mind,
tried to speak it over and over again.
But when the moment finally came...
I had put so much of
myself into this place,
in that moment, I honestly didn't
know where I ended and it began.
There may be ways of severing
oneself in that way...
sacrificing one part to save the other.
But...
in that moment...
I honestly couldn't find something
sharp enough to make the cut.
What would have been enough?
I truly am sorry.
For all of it.
If there was a way I could
make things right here,
I'd do it.
But now,
given everything you have
seen here in recent months...
can you honestly say that you believe
that Nassau will ever really
be what you wanted it to be?
Neither can I.
But there may be a way that we
can take something from it...
if you'll help me.
What is it?
Sails have been spotted on the horizon.
Sails?
Whose sails?
The Revenge?
Are we certain?
She's a man-of-war and she approaches
from Captain Teach's
last sighted position.
If it were Teach returning,
wouldn't he be flying his
banner as he approached?
Sails on the horizon!
They are saying there are no signs
of a prize ship anywhere on the water.
So, at least it is unlikely
Captain Teach caught the
governor's sloop before returning.
Teach would never have
given up so quickly.
If it is his ship,
then in all likelihood, the
governor's ship was captured.
Ma'am?
Perhaps you would like to wait below...
in case the news is not what we hope.
She's raising a banner.
British colors.
She's flying the governor's banner!
And those are his signs!
It's him!
Make a course towards the fort.
As close as we can get.
Ready the men.
We'll make our landing under
cover of the fort's guns,
reinforce them, and
move to retake Nassau.
Ma'am?
Shall I begin moving
the guns to the beach?
Yes.
Yes, of course.
Let me know when it's done.
Heave!
Ready?
They will all be preparing
for the fight ahead of us.
Would you like to tell me what
it is you are preparing to do?
An hour, maybe less,
until his guns are in range of the
beach and he starts his landing.
Once he can bring his broadsides to bear
in concert with the fort's power,
it'll be hard to keep
his men off the sand.
Do we need to consider falling back?
No.
If we leave Nassau now,
we may never get her back.
My men can defend this beach.
We'll have the numbers.
The first barrage, maybe.
But as soon as those
soldiers hit the beach,
nine in 10 of ours will flee.
With Nassau at stake, that's
not a gamble I'm willing to take.
What choice do we have?
Well, that's a very good question.
Should this fight above us come to pass,
at best, the outcome is not certain.
But what is certain
is that many will die
and much will be lost.
I think we've all seen
our fair share of loss
and I have had enough of it.
So, I'd like to ensure that
this fight does not come to pass.
How do you suggest we do that?
I am prepared to surrender the
governor's remaining forces to you...
control of the fort,
its guns, its magazine,
the unconditional release of
the remainder of your prisoners.
All of it.
- You're prepared to do all of that?
- Yes.
In exchange for what?
In exchange for the cache.
The chest with the remains
of the Urca treasure.
I'm told it is hidden...
buried in a secret place known only
to Captain Rackham and the two of you.
I get the cache,
and guaranteed safe passage off the
island for everyone in this fort...
and you get Nassau.
The money isn't ours to give.
We have partners who
would almost certainly
rather fight this out
than lose their treasury.
Your partners are your problem.
There is a reason why I
invited you here and not them.
As soon as the governor's
ship is in range of the beach,
this offer disappears.
I will not undermine his
position once the shooting starts.
So, right now in this moment,
what do you want to do?
How?
How would you see it done?
One of you surrenders himself
and remains here to ensure
these terms are honored.
You send someone to retrieve the cache,
and once it arrives, I
take possession of it.
And my people exit the fort
to a transport waiting
to take us away from here.
The answer is no.
Absolutely no.
If she thought she could win this fight,
why would she be offering
to sell the victory to us
even for a fortune?
I have had enough of this.
And I am ready for it to end.
No.
Trust me.
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com