[Boyd] Previously on From...
- [screaming]
- What's wrong with her?!
- What happened to you?
- What do you mean?
Since you fell asleep
and your eyes got all white,
you've been different.
Do you feel that?
We should go.
You feel it.
You do.
What the hell's going on?
It was my idea.
She needed to come out here.
Mom saw this place
when she was little.
There might be a part of you
that wants so badly
for all of this to make sense.
This wasn't just
a random nightmare, Jim.
This was a dream
I had for months.
Miranda said she was chosen.
If you were destined
to come to this place,
then one way or another,
you were always gonna come
to that tree in the road.
He knows things.
I heard him tell Christopher
a story about this place once.
We'll make him tell it again.
Can I go in your basement?
I need him to tell me a secret.
Help me, Elgin.
I can save all of you.
[camera shutter clicking]
[ominous music playing]
Is this really where it happens?
Whatever is inside me,
it's getting stronger.
The cravings...
they're getting stronger.
- I'm angry all the time.
- It's okay.
- Aah!
- Fatima, it's gonna be okay.
- I said go!
- [gasps]
Help!
What have I done?
What have I done?!
[crow cawing]
Come on.
Have a seat.
Tell me what happened.
We were in the...
the greenhouse.
I was...
And... and I didn't wanna eat
those rotting things anymore.
[cries] Tillie came in,
and she was trying to help me,
and I felt this wave of...
of anger come over me,
like this rage.
It was like this thing...
inside me. It was...
It was like I was there,
but I wasn't.
And... and I felt my hand
reach for the shears.
And I couldn't stop.
[breathing shakily]
I didn't wanna do it.
- There was nothing I could do.
- Here's what we're gonna do.
You're gonna
stay out here tonight.
And come morning,
Ellis and I are gonna
figure out the best way...
We're gonna figure out
how we move forward.
There's no way forward.
Hey. Look at me.
You are my family.
And what happened back there,
we are gonna
find a way to deal with it.
Okay?
Fatima.
Okay.
If you need to eat...
No, no, no, no. Please...
Please take that away.
Look, whatever
is happening to you...
Take it away!
...I don't want it
to get any worse.
So, you need to eat, you eat.
What about Tillie?
We just...
I left her there.
- I left her there.
- [Boyd] Okay.
- My God, I left her there.
- Listen to me, listen.
We're gonna have to
let someone find her.
Oh, my God. [crying]
No. No, no, no. I know. Hey.
Look at me, look at me.
Look, I need you to be strong
right now, okay?
I need you to be...
Ellis needs you to be strong.
Please.
[breathing shakily]
That's right.
Okay.
Now it's getting dark.
This door stays closed,
no matter what.
Right.
We're gonna be okay.
[sobs]
["Que Sera, Sera (Whatever
Will Be, Will Be)" playing]
♪ When I was just a little boy ♪
♪ I asked my father ♪
♪ "What will I be?" ♪
♪ "Will I be handsome?" ♪
♪ "Will I be rich?" ♪
♪ Here's what he said to me ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ Whatever will be will be ♪
♪ The future's not ours to see ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ What will be will be ♪
♪ Now I have
children of my own ♪
♪ They ask their father ♪
♪ "What will I be?" ♪
♪ "Will I be pretty?" ♪
♪ "Will I be rich?" ♪
♪ I tell them tenderly ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ Whatever will be will be ♪
♪ The future's not ours to see ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ What will be will be ♪
[man in distance]
We're coming in two minutes!
Hey, uh...
[clears throat]
I'll, uh, I'll catch up
with you guys later.
Hey, Ethan, Ethan...
[footsteps ascend stairs]
[sighs]
[bottle clatters]
[clatter in distance]
[clatter continues]
Hello?
[grunt]
Okay.
Hello?!
Hey. Uh, sorry.
[chuckles]
Who the fuck are you?
Sorry, I'm, um...
Henry Kavanaugh.
You probably know my son.
Victor?
Oh.
Right.
Nice to meet you.
Same.
Uh... it's quite
the set-up you've got.
You making any progress?
No, not really.
I hope you don't mind if
I grab a little pick-me-up.
Help yourself.
Cheers.
[sighs]
[coughing]
[humming]
[door opens]
We need help!
Help! I need help!
- Somebody get Donna!
- What is it?
[man] It's Tillie!
Shit.
[camera shutter clicks]
[ominous music playing]
I'm going home.
Have you seen
Kristi or Marielle?
- Uh, no.
- Can you just tell them
I said thank you
for letting me stay the night?
I don't get a thank you?
Thank you, Randall,
for letting me stay at the place
that Marielle and Kristi
are letting you stay at.
You're welcome.
We should go back.
To that place, whatever it is,
we should...
we should go back
and check it out.
What?
Well, typically,
when a place makes the hair
on the back of my neck stand up,
it's enough for me to stay away.
Yeah, but we both felt it.
Right? What if it can, like,
I don't know, help
with whatever's happening...
And what if
it makes it worse? Huh?
Look...
There is nothing here
that wants to help us.
Okay? Nothing.
So, stay the fuck
away from that place.
Right?
Remember what I said.
Anybody asks,
you and Fatima were
with me last night. Okay?
What if we just tell them
the truth
and explain what happened?
- Ellis...
- That it wasn't her fault.
I know. I know.
Maybe some of those people
will understand that.
There's no version of us
explaining this away.
Look, they're
gonna put her in the Box.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
Look at me.
Get yourself together.
Go in there,
get up to your room,
put some things in a bag.
Don't pack too much,
just enough for her
to spend a couple days
out there at the shack.
And what are you gonna do?
I'm gonna... [clears throat]
- [Kenny] Boyd!
- ...buy us some time. Hey!
[Kenny] Hey, uh...
We found something.
Anyone see anything?
Uh, not that we've...
Not that we've heard so far.
Any idea when this happened?
Could've been this morning.
It could've been last night.
There's not a whole
lot of people coming in,
with the snow and everything.
[Acosta] Those things
that come out at night,
I'm guessing they don't
use gardening shears?
No.
We should talk to
everyone in the house.
[Kenny] Boyd?
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Start talking to people.
I'll take Ellis out
to walk the road.
- Walk the road?
- This could've been done
by people we know
or people we don't.
We need to rule out
the possibility
we had
any new arrivals yesterday
that we don't know about.
- [Boyd] All right?
- Yeah.
Yeah. Hey.
I know,
you're not my deputy, but...
Yeah, no, I got it.
We'll get the interviews
started.
Yeah.
Hey, Sheriff?
We good?
Let's find out who did this.
[gasps]
Hey, you okay?
Hell, we're gonna
have to talk to Sara.
- It wasn't her.
- [Donna] You don't know that.
And I am not the only person
who's gonna be asking about her.
[breathing shakily]
If you don't think
she did it, fine.
Then, we'll just have to...
go talk to her and make sure.
- Listen...
- No, no, no, you listen.
Hiding every night from
those things, that's one thing.
But this? This is something
that people are gonna
have to blame someone for.
And if we don't figure out who,
then it's gonna be Sara,
whether she did it or not.
Okay.
You get things
straightened out here,
then meet me at the station, and
we will talk to her together.
[Sara] "Hello, Victor.
Do you want to play today?
I can tell you a secret."
No, no, not... not like that!
I just... I told you!
It doesn't
sound like that, Sara!
I'm doing the best that I can!
I'm trying
everything that I know!
I don't know
what you want, Victor!
- [mumbling]
- [thudding]
- Hey, hey, hey!
- [Victor] No!
No! He d...
he doesn't... you need...
he needs to talk,
and you're not doing it right!
I'm doing the best that I can!
No, you're not
doing it good enough!
No, you're not good enough.
You're not good enough!
- Victor! Hey!
- You're not good enough!
- Hey, don't! Stop! Stop!
- Stop! Stop!
Look, I know you want
all this to mean something,
and this place has you
convinced that you need
to save these children.
It's got you trying to fix
something that we can never...
[sighs]
Do you know why
the phone is off the wall?
Because it rang the other day,
and the voice on the other end
said his name was Thomas.
What?
Something here
knows things about us,
and it knows
which buttons to push.
[knock on door]
[exhales]
[knocking continues]
I'm sorry.
I know I shouldn't
be here, but...
Victor is in my basement,
and he's in really bad shape.
He said he only wants
to talk to you.
I wouldn't have come
if it wasn't important.
Just wait there.
I'll get my coat.
I have to go.
[Elgin] Hello?
[door closes]
- Hey.
- [Elgin gasps]
If you're looking for drugs,
you're in the wrong spot.
Oh, no, no.
Uh, no, I was...
just looking for a Band-Aid.
- Oh.
- I cut my foot.
Mm. You better not
let Kristi or Marielle
find you rooting
through their shit.
You hear about Tillie?
Yeah.
It's fucked up.
Hey. I'm sorry
I was so hard on you
on the bus that day.
I guess you were right.
We should've turned around.
Sorry I, uh, threw up
all over your shirt.
[chuckles] Yeah.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[Sara] Victor?
Oh. Oh, you're here.
- [Tabitha] Hi, Victor. Hi.
- Good. Come.
Hey.
[grunts]
You sit... come sit here.
- Okay.
- There. Take this.
Okay.
- Okay.
- Victor, what are we...
You were there. You were there
when I remembered Eloise,
so you're the one
that can make him talk.
Okay, Victor, I'm so sorry.
I don't know...
I don't understand.
He needs to tell me!
You need to make him tell me.
[Tabitha]
Tell you what, Victor?
[Victor] The secrets
that he told Christopher
'cause he can help us.
[Tabitha] I'm sorry, honey.
He's... he's just a doll.
[Victor] No!
No, you have to be the one!
You have to be the one!
- Okay, okay!
- You have to be the one!
- [Tabitha] Victor! Hey! Hey!
- Hey! Victor, stop it!
- Stop it! Don't do that!
- You have to be the one.
Calm down.
Don't do that, Victor, please.
Shh. Look at me.
Look at me. Look at me.
Look at me, Victor.
It's okay. You're okay.
- [Tabitha] You're okay.
- Okay.
- It's okay.
- Yeah.
Do you want to draw a picture?
No. No, it doesn't work
like that.
See, the pictures
always remembered
so that I didn't have to.
But I never drew one,
so now it's gone, and I can't...
I can't remember.
No. No, okay, okay.
First of all, sit down.
It's okay. You're okay.
You're okay. Sit down, okay?
It's okay, Victor.
Just sit down.
Nothing is gone.
Nothing's gone.
It's okay. Um...
Tell me about...
tell me about the doll.
His name is Jasper.
Jasper? Okay.
Uh, tell me about Jasper.
I heard him once,
telling Christopher things
that we need to know.
But I don't remember.
[Tabitha] Hey, it's okay.
Victor, look at me.
- But...
- Look at me.
We'll remember together,
just like last time.
- Okay.
- We can do this together, okay?
Yeah. [sniffs]
Hello?
Anyone home?
Hey.
Uh... how were things
at the settlement?
Uh, not great.
Oh.
Listen, your brother's upstairs.
Would you mind
hanging with him for a bit?
- Well, where are you going?
- Something I gotta take care of.
Okay?
- But...
- [door opens]
[door closes]
[knock on door]
[door opens]
Ethan?
You doing okay?
- I'm fine.
- 'Cause I thought,
maybe you might wanna
go see something really cool.
My wife had visions
of this place.
Yeah, I've heard.
I thought she was crazy.
I should've listened to her.
Well... shoulda,
woulda, coulda, right?
What exactly makes you think
you're gonna be
the one to figure this out?
I imagine a lot of pretty
smart people have tried.
- [door opens]
- I'm smarter.
- Oh.
- Oh, please, come on in.
Make yourself at home.
It's done.
Right now.
Do you understand me?
What are we talking about?
Who the fuck do you think you
are dragging my wife and kid
out into the middle
of the woods?
Okay, first of all,
- I didn't drag anybody anywhere...
- I only wanna say this once.
Tabitha is not
in a good place right now.
She doesn't need you
filling her head with ideas
about how somehow,
she's this chosen savior,
responsible for getting
everybody home...
You get
your fucking hands off me!
Filling her head with ideas?
What is she, nine?
Jim, she... she came here!
She came here, okay?
She saw the drawings,
she recognized the, uh, s...
You know what? I don't need
to explain this to you.
All right, then,
let me explain this to you.
You are a lonely, selfish,
narcissistic asshole,
who doesn't give a shit
about anything but yourself
and your own goddamn ego.
If you wanna kill yourself
trying to figure this thing out,
be my guest.
But I have a family
to look out for.
- Mm.
- I have people
who mean more to me
than you will ever understand.
Jim, I'm getting a little tired
of this sanctimonious
blue-collar bullshit.
You wanna talk
about your family?
Let's talk about your family.
Of the two of us,
I am the only one doing
a goddamn thing to help them!
[scoffs]
Look at this!
You see this?
This...
this helps people!
No! You know
what this does?!
This shows people
how you are the smartest
fucking prick in the room!
So what?!
If it gets us home,
who gives a shit?!
And I'm not gonna do this.
I'm sorry.
I'm not gonna do this.
I'm not gonna waste
any more of my time.
Listen, if you wanna keep
your kids under lock and key,
more power to you.
Tabitha's a grown-up.
You got a problem with what
she's doing, talk to her.
Sorry.
We're not done here!
Yeah, we fucking are, Jim!
[grunts]
Well, that was
certainly productive.
[Ellis] Fatima?
Hey. Come here.
We're gonna get
this through this, okay?
Ellis, I need you and your dad
to stop saying that.
I killed someone.
How, I mean... help me.
No, listen to me.
Listen to me.
Whatever this is,
it's you and I.
We are in this together.
I don't care if we need
to take that talisman
and go live in the woods.
No. You don't understand.
Ellis, whatever is inside me,
whatever made me...
it's still there.
- No. Babe, hey.
- It's still there. I...
What if it happens again?
What if I... what if I...
what if I do something...
You... You won't. You won't.
Look at me. Look at me.
You won't. Okay?
Because you are
stronger than this.
Whatever this is,
we are stronger than this.
Okay?
Fatima?
Okay.
I brought you some things.
Some...
Some clothes
if you wanna change.
- [bag thuds]
- Hey...
Lucky handkerchief.
Remember?
I love you.
I love you, too.
Okay.
I'll be back soon.
Okay. Soon.
[shrieking and gasping]
[ominous music playing]
[sighs]
♪
[breathing shakily]
[inhaling sharply]
♪
[camera shutter clicks]
You mind if I give you
some unsolicited advice?
I don't see why not.
Maybe, sometimes,
when you're with your wife...
you should
shut the fuck up and listen.
Excuse me?
Jim, I-I look at you right now.
All I see is me
standing there 40 years ago.
I was so sure I could "fix" her.
[chuckles] It never occurred
to me she wasn't broken.
That, uh... arrogant fella
who stormed outta here?
He... He was right
about one thing.
What you're doing,
how tight you're
holding on to everything...
You may tell yourself you're
doing it for your family.
But you're doing it
because you're scared,
and you're
doing it for yourself.
I'm probably the only guy
in this whole place
who can tell you that
and say... it's true.
It's true.
[glass clatters]
Uh, you want a drink?
No. I don't...
- Oh.
- My dad was a drunk.
Mine, too.
The night my daughter was born,
after Tabitha fell asleep, I...
I went to the bar across
the street from the hospital,
and I asked the bartender
for the tallest glass
of whiskey she could pour,
and I stared
at that drink for hours,
and I promised myself I would
be a better father to my kids...
...a better husband
to my wife.
What are you doing?
Giving you the chance
to renew your vows.
Sit there as long as you like.
I could use the company.
What is this?
I don't know.
But if I tell you something,
can you promise that
you won't tell Mom and Dad?
Ever since I woke up,
something has been
happening in me.
I... I hear things
in my head.
What kind of things?
I hear people screaming.
And it won't stop.
But yesterday,
I was out here with Randall,
and when I saw this place...
...everything went quiet
for the first time
since I woke up.
But that's... good, right?
I don't know.
[inhales and exhales deeply]
I feel...
I feel like something...
Like it wants me to go in here.
And I don't know what to do.
It's just
a pile of rocks, right?
But I'm scared.
So... what do I do?
What?
All I keep thinking about
is that this sounds like
those stories
that you always tell us.
If I was a character
in one of those stories...
what would I do?
What would...
What would this be?
You're at a threshold.
It's always scary, but...
the hero has to be brave.
We can go in together,
if you want.
[crows cawing in distance]
Yeah.
Ready?
[ominous music playing]
♪
[gasping]
[breathing rapidly]
[whimpering]
[shrieking and screaming
in distance]
[screaming continues]
[screaming]
[gasps]
[screaming continues]
No! No! No!
[screaming]
Julie! Julie!
[grunting]
Help!
[Tabitha] Victor, do you
remember where you were
when you heard Jasper talk?
It was dark in a basement.
Do you remember which basement?
No, I don't...
No, I don't remember.
- Victor, it's fine.
- Yeah.
What were you
doing in the basement?
I don't remember!
I don't remember.
- Hey, don't do...
- Was it nice that day?
What?
The day you heard Jasper talk...
what was it like outside?
It was sunny.
It was... I was...
We were playing.
- Wait. You mean, you and Eloise?
- [Victor] Yeah.
Yeah. I was...
We were playing hide-and-seek.
- Yeah?
- 'Cause Eloise was good
at hide-and-seek.
I could never find her,
no matter how hard I looked.
Okay. Um...
Where did you look
that day, Victor?
Everywhere. The bar, the diner,
the houses, the... church.
I looked in the church.
She'd never hid there before.
- Mm-hmm?
- She said it always scared her,
but I'd already
looked everywhere else.
That was where it happened.
That's where I saw Jasper
talking to Christopher
in the church!
We just need to know
if you saw anything.
I mean, did I see someone stab
the old lady
in the greenhouse? No.
What about Tillie? When was
the last time you saw her?
I don't know.
Yesterday morning.
Why aren't you guys talking
to the one person in town
who actually murdered someone?
What?
Oh, you don't know about Sara?
She doesn't know about Sara.
Look, I'm not sure why
you guys are talking to us.
It's pretty fuckin'
obvious who did this.
Okay, look, we're gonna
talk to Sara after.
- But for right now, let's...
- Didn't she kill your Dad?
The fuck are you
defending her for?
Goddamnit, I said no!
Then what is your solution?!
Okay, we are running
out of time, okay?!
Maybe...
maybe if you explain to them,
all right, and then give it
a little bit of time...
And in the meantime, what?
What?
You two are living
out there in a tent?
Yes! We'll have talismans!
We'll be safe!
You won't be safe from her.
So, that... is that what
you're afraid of?
- Whatever made her do this...
- She would never hurt me.
She just stabbed someone
in the fucking chest!
Son, listen to me!
I love Fatima. I do.
But we do not know what...
Boyd, look, I have
a whole lot of people up there
just ready to march on
Sara's house with torches...
What's going on?
It wasn't Sara.
Boyd, look,
I know you care about her...
It was Fatima.
[Donna stammers]
Was what that guy said
about Sara and your dad true?
[sighs]
It's not that simple.
Okay, you didn't think
it was worth mentioning the girl
that already murdered
two people?
Look, it's just, uh,
she's different now,
and Boyd trusts her.
Who gives a shit
what Boyd thinks, okay?
- [Ethan] Help!
- You know, you people got
- a real funny way...
- I need help!
Hey, hey. What's wrong?
What's wrong?
Julie! She's on the ground!
She's shaking!
- Okay. Wait, wait, wait.
- Come on, we have to help her!
[screaming]
Tell it to stop!
[voices shrieking]
[shrieking and screaming stop]
[breathing rapidly]
[Martin]
You have to climb!
[Boyd]
What? No. I ca...
[Boyd groans]
I can't!
[Martin] Wait.
Julie?
- How do you know my name?
- He needs the rope.
Please.
[breathing rapidly]
Who is that?
[Boyd]
Hey, what... Fuck!
What?
[Martin] You have to hurry!
They'll be back soon.
Okay.
[Julie breathing rapidly]
Thank you.
- Who's down there?
- [Martin] You need to leave.
It isn't safe here.
Go!
[rustling]
[breathing rapidly]
What...
[whimpering] Plea...
[Tabitha]
No, no, Victor.
Can you just please tell me
what's going on? Where are we?
[Victor, whispering]
We're underneath the town.
This is where the monsters live.
This is where they sleep,
but I can get us out.
[Tabitha] They what?
Mom?
[child] Anghkooey!
[child 2] Anghkooey!
[children] Anghkooey!
Anghkooey! Anghkooey!
Please...
[voices screaming]
[Ethan]
Julie! Julie! Julie!
- Just get her up. Julie!
- [Acosta] Come here.
- I got you.
- [Kenny] Just get her up.
[screaming]
- [Kenny] Hey, hey, hey, hey!
- [Ethan] Julie!
- Hey. Hey.
- It's okay. It's okay.
Oh, my God.
What happened?
- Are you okay?
So I took her outta town
before everyone woke up.
You need to bring her back.
I can't do that.
Not yet.
- Not until we...
- Until you what?
Manage to resurrect Tillie?
Look, I don't wanna...
I love Fatima
as though she were my own.
But we have a town we have
to worry about here, Boyd.
And if you try to hide this,
and people find out...
They will understand,
just like they did with Sara.
Is that what you think?
You think they
- understood about Sara?
- Yes.
No, no, no!
They didn't understand.
They accepted it.
People swallowed it.
But they certainly
did not understand it!
They let it go because
you told them they had to.
Great, then,
I will tell them again!
- It's not gonna work this time.
- Why not?
Because they don't
believe in you anymore.
Not like they did.
I'll tell them I did it.
- No, no, no!
- No, no, I'll, I'll... I did it!
- No, no, no, it's not enough!
- Why?
Because it doesn't change
that it made it happen
in the first place!
There is either something
horrible growing inside of her,
or else this place
has finally broken her mind!
Either way, it's only a matter
of time before it happens again!
They can stay with me.
[exhales heavily]
She won't be
a threat to anyone else.
I can watch her.
We can watch her.
No, no, no, Boyd. Boyd, you may
both want this to be okay,
and God knows
I want it to be okay, too.
But if you are not gonna
tell everyone, then I am.
Please, don't make me do this.
[door closes]
What are you doing?
You're gonna need supplies.
[Victor] It was in the basement.
It happened in the basement.
When I opened the door,
I heard voices.
So, I was quiet,
and I wanted to get closer.
When I got...
to the bottom of the stairs,
Jasper was telling secrets.
[muted speech]
- [muted speech]
- Christopher got angry.
[continues, muted]
No, no, that's not right.
It wasn't Jasper.
[muted speech continues]
It was the boy in white.
He was the one
that was down here.
He who was telling secrets
to Christopher.
[muted] The answers to the end
are at the beginning.
He said, "The answers to
the end are at the beginning."
[boy in white, muted]
It started with the children.
That it started
with the children...
- What the others did to them.
- ...what the others did to them.
What others, Victor?
The people they loved.
The people they trusted.
The children are born
in the dark.
[Victor] He said the children
were born in the dark.
[boy in white, muted] And then
they were murdered in the dark.
And then they were murdered...
in the dark.
[muted] But someone
who loved them...
But someone who loved them...
- ...told them a story.
The story gave them hope.
And when the children
laid on the stones,
they poured their hope
into the roots
that made the symbol,
and those roots became the tree.
The Faraway Tree.
The boy in white was
trying to tell Christopher
that to save the children...
he would have
to go through the tree.
But he wouldn't...
he wouldn't listen, and he...
he got angry.
[muted] You're a liar!
Everything lies here!
Christopher
wouldn't listen, so I-I...
What?
Christopher wouldn't
go to the tree, so...
I told my mother
what the boy in white said.
And that's why she left us.
[Elgin] Fatima?
It's Elgin.
[door creaks open]
You...
Okay, stay close, all right?
But not too close.
Four or five hours out,
that should be, uh, enough.
[Ellis] Okay.
And, whatever you do, you stay
off the path to the settlement.
Last thing we want is anybody
tripping over your tent.
I'm gonna leave supplies for
you at the shack twice a week.
You need anything,
you leave a note behind.
- Okay.
- You bring a pen and pad?
Yeah, it's in the pack.
And if things...
Look, if things get worse,
you promise me that you'll...
Look, um, Dad,
I know you don't
want me to do this,
but if you'd had the chance,
if you and Mom coulda ran,
even after she did
what she did...
what would you have done?
[whispers] Come on.
Let's go. Come on.
Come on.
No.
Fatima?!
What? Fatima!
Fatima!
- Almost there.
- Elgin, where are we going?
It's just through here.
It's...
Are you sure we're supposed
to be this close to town?
I told you.
Ellis is waiting for you.
Right here,
there's a room down here
that nobody knows about.
[grunts]
Come on. Please.
Fatima.
[breathing heavily]
It's right through there.
[Fatima] Ellis?
I, uh, I'll wait
for him at the shack.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
You can't do that.
Elgin, get out of my way.
No, you don't understand.
You have to be here.
It's the only place
that the baby will be safe.
- There is no baby.
- Yes, there is.
It...
It's just not yours.
Elgin, get out of my way.
Get out of my way!
Get out of my...
Elgin! Get out of my way!
- Fatima!
- Aah! [groans]
[groans]
[gasping and groaning]
You see?
The baby knows you have to stay.
[groaning] Elgin, stop.
Fighting it is just
going to make it worse.
Elgin, get out of my way.
Please, get out of my way.
Get out of my way!
[panting]
I'm sorry.
[gasping]
I really am.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
No! No!
This is for the best.
No, please! Help!
Help!
Elgin, no!
Elgin, please!
Help! Aah!
Help! Help!
Help!
♪