[Boyd] Previously on From...
I'm sorry.
This is the only way.
[screams]
- Where am I?
- You're in Camden, Maine.
Get the hell outta here.
You deaf? I said get the...
Where did you get that?
You're Victor's father.
I'm gonna go look for my wife.
Someone's gotta make sure that
Jim comes back in one piece.
I know what it's like
to lose a parent here,
and I'm not gonna watch
Julie and Ethan lose
both their parents
in the same week.
[in Cantonese]
Ma...
What the fuck?
These look pretty solid.
We could just start
from here in the morning.
- Just give me a second.
- [Nicky] Come on!
My stomach just
hasn't been right.
Those animals are the only food
that we have now.
They are a resource.
We have to make everything last!
There's goddamn cows
in the street!
Get those smaller animals
into the barn!
- [Ethan] Alma's outside!
- No! Go! Ethan, run!
- Julie!
- [Julie] Go!
- [muffled gasp]
- Shh!
[screams, howls]
- Let's go!
- [Boyd] Come on!
No, no, no! You go back!
- We do together!
- [grunts]
- [gasps]
- No!
Boyd!
You think this place
can't break you?
Let's see.
- [screaming and crying]
- What the fuck?!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
I know, I know, I know!
I know! I know! I know!
[hooves clopping,
goats bleating]
[clopping and bleating continue]
[breathes deeply]
[bleating continues]
- Don't.
- [bleating continues]
Somebody has to go and see.
[bleating]
[speaking Cantonese repeatedly]
[door opens]
[Boyd continues in Cantonese]
Oh, God. Oh, Jesus, no.
- [continues in Cantonese]
- Boyd?
Boyd! Hey, hey, hey! Hey!
- [continues in Cantonese]
- Key.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, Boyd.
[speaking Cantonese]
Where's the key?
[breathing heavily]
In my pocket.
They left it in my pocket.
[resumes speaking Cantonese]
[gasping]
[sobbing, speaking Cantonese]
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry.
[sobbing] I'm so sorry!
[screaming]
[yells]
I'm so sorry!
Please...
[sobbing]
[Jim, in distance] Kenny!
No. No.
[Jim]
You gotta come down here!
Look at this.
It's growing in patches
all around the lake.
There's enough food here to feed
everybody in the entire town.
Look.
["Que Sera, Sera (Whatever
Will Be, Will Be)" playing]
♪ When I was just a little boy ♪
♪ I asked my father ♪
♪ "What will I be?" ♪
♪ "Will I be handsome?" ♪
♪ "Will I be rich?" ♪
♪ Here's what he said to me ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ Whatever will be will be ♪
♪ The future's not ours to see ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ What will be will be ♪
♪ Now I have
children of my own ♪
♪ They ask their father ♪
♪ "What will I be?" ♪
♪ "Will I be pretty?" ♪
♪ "Will I be rich?" ♪
♪ I tell them tenderly ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ Whatever will be will be ♪
♪ The future's not ours to see ♪
♪ Que sera sera ♪
♪ What will be will be ♪
What happened?
Oh, no. It's okay.
You, um...
You passed out
on my front porch.
Maybe...
maybe I should just...
You should sit.
Okay. Okay.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You showed up on my doorstep
with the lunchbox
my son left here with...
...a very long time ago.
So, you're gonna tell me
how you found that,
and you're gonna
tell me right now.
Okay.
Yeah.
Okay. Um...
[sighs]
My name is Tabitha Matthews.
My family and I
were on a road trip
to see some
relatives in Colorado,
when we had to take
a detour off the highway.
There was a massive tree
in the middle of the road,
so we thought we were
just driving around it.
[cawing]
But we never
got back to the road.
We kept driving, and...
and we got to this... town,
a place that we couldn't leave.
But there were people there,
and some of them had
been there for a while.
I don't know how long
they'd been...
No, no! Where did you get
the lunchbox?
Well, that's what
I'm trying to tell you.
The place we ended up,
there are people that had been
there for years, I mean, for...
Where did you get the lunchbox?!
- He gave it to me!
- Who?
Your son. Victor.
He... he gave it to me.
Oh. He gave it to you.
Yeah.
When?
Um...
- Three, four... Four days ago.
- [groans]
Victor is alive. The town
I was telling you about,
he's been stuck there
all these years.
Okay, all right. If, uh...
If you won't talk to me, then
maybe you'll talk to the police.
No, sir. Please, please.
You can't call them.
I can't tell them who I am.
If I try to explain any of this
to them, I'll sound crazy.
When they ask
where my family is...
what am I gonna tell them?
I don't...
I don't know where they are.
Please, sir,
you have to believe me.
- Please don't call the police.
- Well, Tabitha,
I called the police
about 20 minutes ago.
They should be here any minute.
So, we're just gonna
sit here together...
until they arrive.
I know how to prove
I'm not lying.
No. You don't come in here.
You understand?
Boyd might be okay
with everything you did,
but if you think for a second...
Tian-Chen died.
What?
Something happened last night.
The animals...
got out into the street,
and she...
I didn't... I thought
you would want to know,
and I wasn't sure if anyone...
I'm sorry.
- Kristi? Who was that?
- [door closes]
Baby?
Hey, what's wrong?
Um...
What?
[breathing shakily]
Uh, Kenny's mom died.
What?
[wheels squeaking]
[somber music playing]
♪♪♪
Over there.
Okay.
[straining]
♪♪♪
Okay...
[breathing heavily]
Here. Okay.
We... We need to, um...
Uh...
We need to make sure she gets
buried with her husband.
She would have wanted that.
She wouldn't...
Uh, right.
- Yeah.
- Boyd...
Yeah.
You were in the barn with her,
with those things.
Yeah.
How are you still alive?
They wanted me to watch.
They...
Yeah.
[crowd murmuring]
[Tian-Chen] No! Let me go!
[sobbing] Boyd!
[screaming]
[screaming continues]
- [flesh tearing]
- [screaming]
[Tian-Chen sobbing]
Boyd!
Is it true?
[breathing heavily]
[whispers] Oh, fuck.
[weeping]
I wanna go see her.
I just... I don't think that
a good idea right now, okay?
She's gonna be okay, right?
Kristi can fix her.
Ethan...
We should bring her her blanket.
She'll be more comfortable
when she has her blanket.
- Hey, hey...
- I wanna go see her.
It's okay.
Tell her that we have
to go see Tian-Chen!
That we have to help!
[Julie] I could use
a little help in there.
[Victor] No. I have to go.
- [Julie] You... You have to go?
- [Victor] Yes, I have to go.
- Hey, hey! I'm talking to you!
- I have to go!
Wait! Where are you going?
- I can't stay here anymore.
- Why?
- Because!
- We have to help her!
We can't help her! She's dead!
She's dead, Ethan!
People die here!
I told you that!
It's not make-believe!
I told you that
bad things happen here!
It's not my fault
that you didn't listen!
[breathing unsteadily]
I have to go.
- [breathing unsteadily]
- [door slams]
[both sobbing]
[Julie] It's okay.
[Tabitha] I mean, there's other
people you can look up.
Boyd Stevens.
His family went missing.
Uh... Donna. Um, Donna...
Um, okay.
Liu! Liu!
Tian-Chen and Kenny Liu.
That family...
that family's there, too.
You're lying. I-I...
I don't know how you're
doing this, but you're lying.
No, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
I swear to you I'm not.
I swear on my children's lives.
My family is trapped,
and Victor is trapped, too.
Then how did you get here, huh?
You want me to believe you just
happen to be the one person
who somehow managed to escape
this terrifying place?
Listen, I don't understand,
but yes, yes.
And Victor helped me.
No, don't... [scoffs]
[sighs] Please.
Victor is a good man.
He's nice and sweet,
and my son loves him.
And my daughter...
He saved my daughter's life.
I thought that
if I saved the children
locked in the tower, then...
somehow, I could save her from
whatever's happening to her...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What did you say?
Well, when I was in town,
I started seeing children,
or at least imagining I was.
And they were
really frightening.
Victor said that they were
children locked in the tower,
that if I saved them,
then maybe I could...
I could somehow help my daughter
from what she's going through,
and I don't know
if I'm doing it...
- [knock on door]
- [officer] Camden PD!
Please.
Don't let them in. Please.
- Uh...
- Please!
I'm not lying.
[breathing unsteadily]
[officer] Henry!
Henry, you in there?
- [opens door]
- Hey, man.
I screwed up, man.
I thought I had an intruder
and turned out to be
just a dog off the leash.
The owner came back to...
Look, I owe you a dozen,
okay? I'm sorry.
[officer] All right, Henry.
Take care of yourself.
[Henry] Yeah, you, too.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
- Thanks.
- [door closes]
I, uh, bought that
almost 40 years ago...
a few years after
my family disappeared.
I never once had the courage
to even load it, much less...
I'm gonna make you
something to eat.
It was an ambush.
They knew we'd
go after the animals.
Goddamn things opened the pen
and just waited for us
to walk right to them.
How many did you save?
What's... What?
Animals.
How many did you save?
Was it worth it?
Risking everyone's lives,
for what?
An extra goat? A cow?
How much better off are we
today than we were yesterday?
Wait, wait.
Are you saying
that I had a choice?
- [scoffs]
- Those animals are all we have!
No, Boyd!
We are all we have!
Us! These people!
This family!
That is all we've got,
and now we've got one less!
So, what was...
what was I supposed to do?!
Just stand there,
watching our only resource go
wandering off into the woods?
We would have starved!
We would have found another way!
Yesterday you were ready
to crawl into a fucking hole
because the crops had spoiled!
And now you're standing there,
telling me
that we would have found
another way?!
That I shoulda just...
I shoulda...
That I should just...
get the fuck outta here!
- What the fuck am I...
- No, okay, No, you're right.
You're right.
You did what you had to do.
You did the only thing
you could do.
And you lost...
...because the game here
is fucking rigged.
And no matter what
hand you play, you lose.
Donna. Donna...
No, no, no.
I'm not angry at you, Boyd.
I'm not. [sighs]
I'm angry at me.
Angry at me
because you told us that,
someday, we'd go home...
[sighs] ...and I was stupid
enough to believe it.
- I'm...
- Get off!
[sobbing]
[inhaling sharply] Oh!
We gotta dress that cow
before the meat spoils.
[door opens]
- [knock on door]
- [retching]
[Ellis] Hey.
You been in there for a while.
You okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- You know, I was thinking,
maybe we should go see Kristi,
uh, just as a precaution.
Ugh. [gasping]
Look, that's not necessary.
- It's just morning sickness.
- [toilet flushes]
Can you at least open the door?
Give me a second!
You know, why don't
I go see if Kristi
can just come up here,
and that way, you can just stay?
- Look, I said I'm fine!
- [water running]
I don't need everybody...
It doesn't feel right.
You're not sleeping.
You're barely eating.
Fatima?
Fatima? Hey, look, come on.
What's going on?
[crunching]
Fatima, you're scaring me.
Come on.
Can you please open the door?
[door creaks]
Uh, I think you're right.
Maybe we should go see Kristi.
Kristi? You here?
Wait here.
Hello?
[Marielle] Coming.
- Hey.
- Is Kristi here?
Uh, she's...
She's down in town.
She's taking the news
about Tian-Chen pretty hard.
Listen, this can totally wait.
- The poor woman...
- No, it really can't.
Come on in.
I'll take a look at you.
You know what?
Maybe we should wait for Kristi.
Kristi's dealing
with a lot right now.
Yeah, but...
Look, no offense.
You're not a doctor.
I am, however,
a pediatric nurse.
So, as far as pregnancy goes,
I've pretty much seen
everything.
Come on. Come.
Kinda cold out for a swim.
What are you doing out here?
I just realized that...
I can't even remember
whose truck this was.
That's how many people we...
Danny.
And his, um...
his girlfriend Shay.
Right.
Danny and Shay.
They were good kids, yeah.
What happened last night, it...
wasn't your fault.
You know,
with all due respect, Kristi,
I'm... not here
for a pep talk.
All due respect, Boyd,
I don't really give a shit.
[sighs]
Look, after what happened
with Sara,
when she tried to hurt Ethan...
you sat with me in that diner
and you told me
it wasn't my fault,
that it was this place,
that I had saved a lot of lives,
and that I was gonna save
a hell of a lot more by the time
this all was finished.
So, was that just
a bunch of bullshit
to make me feel better,
or did you mean it?
[stammers]
Hey. This isn't your fault.
Okay?
Now, come on.
Let's go get you cleaned up.
[Kenny] Guys!
Hey! We found food!
Look! Look at this!
There's a... there's a lake,
and it's got everything.
It's got vegetables...
[Jim] We found food!
All right.
There's, uh, there's potatoes.
There might even be
fish in the water!
What's going on?
[indistinct murmurs]
Where are my kids?
They're fine.
They're...
they're okay.
Whose blood is that?
Kenny...
Where's...
Wait. Where's...
Where's my mom?
Kenny, maybe we
should go inside.
Kenny!
Mom?
Ma!
Mom! [shouting in Cantonese]
- Hey, Kenny...
- Stop! No, no, no, no, no.
[shouting in Cantonese]
- Hey, bud. Ken?
- No, stop!
- Bud, I'm...
- No.
- ...so s...
- Stop, stop. No! No, no!
- Listen, I'm so...
- No, no! Stop! Just... just stop.
Okay.
[Kenny] Okay?
[breathing rapidly]
Okay. Yeah.
[breathing deeply]
I got it.
[murmuring continues]
[door creaks]
I'm so sorry. I'm so...
I'm so sorry.
- [door closes]
- [sobbing]
Kenny, hey.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. I'm okay.
I'm okay. I'm okay.
[inhaling, exhaling sharply]
I'm okay.
[exhaling sharply] I'm okay.
Where is she?
In the church.
[breathing shakily]
I just, uh...
I just... I need to
sit here for a minute.
'Kay?
Yeah. Okay.
When was the last time you ate?
Uh, three... four days?
She can't keep anything down.
I've tried to.
It's just even
the smell of food,
it's just...
- [exhales deeply]
- Deep breath.
Look, are you sure we
shouldn't just get Kristi?
- Ellis, just...
- How've you been doing
since, you know...
Since what?
Since I went through withdrawal,
or since this place...
mind-raped me?
Look, I know this is scary,
and if it's any consolation,
you're doing exactly what
you're supposed to be doing.
In the tradition of
first-time fathers everywhere,
you're scared out of your mind,
and you're asking every
question you possibly can.
As for you,
you're severely malnourished.
It's a wonder
only one tooth fell out.
You also may have something
called hyperemesis gravidarum.
What is that? Is that bad?
It's essentially really
bad morning sickness.
We really just need
to get you eating again.
[sighs] Well, you tell that
to the world's pickiest eater.
[chuckles] I'm gonna see if
maybe we have something
that can settle your stomach.
But as far as the baby?
- Everything's okay?
- As far as I can tell,
everything's fine.
- I'll be right back.
- [sighs]
Ah, you see?
I told you.
- Everything is okay.
- Was that you?
- Yeah.
- That was... that was you?
Yeah, yeah,
it was totally me, you know,
calm, cool, collected.
Yeah. Might have missed that.
[sighs]
You hear that in there?
Everything's gonna be okay.
Whenever things got
really bad here, she'd...
...she used to always say...
"No matter how bad it gets,
we'll never
have this day again."
She'd always repeat it
to make sure I got the message.
[speaking Cantonese]
Did she...
Did she suffer?
- Kenny, I...
- No, I...
It's okay. You don't have to...
[sniffles]
[sighs]
Have you seen her?
Have you seen what
they did to her?
Not yet, no.
Whenever I think about my dad...
I can't...
All I can see is him
lying there in that basement.
I can't think of him
and not see him like that.
I don't want it
to be like that for her.
[sniffles]
Can you do me a favor?
Yeah, of course.
Can you... [sighs]
[sniffling]
Can you make her...
Can you make her look like her?
Can you make sure
she looks nice?
She would be really upset,
if she, uh... [sniffles]
...if she didn't look like her.
Yeah. Yeah, of course.
[sniffling] Thank you.
Thank you. [sniffles]
You, um... You need
anything at all,
anything, you get someone
to come get me, okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah.
["Celebration" plays]
♪ Celebrate good times!
Come on! ♪
♪ Celebrate! ♪
- ♪ Celebrate ♪
- Stop it.
- ♪ Good times, come on! ♪
- Stop.
♪ Let's celebrate ♪
♪ There's a party
going on right here ♪
♪ A celebration to last... ♪
- Stop!
- ♪ Throughout the year ♪
Fucking stop!
Shut the fuck up!
♪ And your laughter, too ♪
Stop! Fucking stop!
♪ We gonna celebrate
your party with you ♪
♪ Come on now, celebra... ♪
[clattering]
[breathing heavily]
You're back.
Yeah.
Tian-Chen is dead.
I know.
Ethan's upstairs.
- Julie...
- No.
Don't. Just please don't.
Julie, whatever
you're feeling right now,
it's okay.
No, it's not.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Ethan almost died, too.
Did you know that?
You should have been here, Dad.
I... I can't.
I can't be like before.
Hey, hold on.
What are you talking about?
I can't be the fill-in parent
while you lose your shit.
I was looking for your mother.
Mom is gone!
Okay? She's gone!
She went through a tree,
and now she's gone!
We don't know that.
Dad... people can't survive more
than a few hours at night
without a talisman.
She's been gone four days.
I know...
I know you feel bad that you
didn't stop her, but I can't...
[breathing shakily]
When Thomas died,
you and Mom fell apart,
and there was
no one there for Ethan.
I was 15.
I can't do it again.
I can't. Not this time.
I need you to
get your shit together. Okay?
Okay.
[stammers]
I don't get a lot of visitors.
At least now I know
you won't pass out on me.
[chuckles]
Back before she disappeared,
my wife, Miranda,
started hearing voices.
She said they were children,
calling out to her,
that they were...
locked in a tower somewhere,
you know,
crying out to be saved.
She was terrified of them.
The only person
I ever repeated that to
was the investigating detective,
and he died 20 years ago.
When you're done,
I-I wanna show you something.
Yeah.
I want you to look at this room.
This is where my children slept.
My little boy.
My little girl.
They were the lights of my life.
And when they disappeared...
it ripped my life to pieces.
I didn't care
about the accusations.
I didn't care that everyone
thought that I did it.
But...
all I could think,
all I could... remember,
even now,
is that the last words
I said to them,
"Clean your room
or no TV."
And then, I went to work.
When I came home...
they were gone.
Why are you showing me this?
I don't know how you know
about those children
my wife heard.
I don't know how you got a hold
of my son's lunchbox or...
or how you could have possibly
faked those articles online.
[stammers]
The only possible explanation
I can come up with...
...is that you're
actually...
telling the truth,
and that means my son is alive.
And that...
That means something
I-I don't...
I don't even have
the words to... express.
So, if you,
if this isn't real...
you tell me right now.
If this is all just
some cruel, elaborate...
No, no, no, no, no.
I swear to you, it's not.
I believe that the reason
I was sent here...
was to find you.
No.
I think you're here for
what's in the basement.
[Jade]
I didn't want her to be alone.
She made me tea.
[murmurs in horror]
I'll... I'll give you some time.
Wait!
I have to...
fix her before Kenny sees her,
and I don't know how to do that.
I'm...
I'm not a mortician.
Hey, hey, hey.
- I don't...
- Hey. Let me help you.
[exhales deeply]
I used to
play dress-up a lot as a kid.
We can do this. Right?
[townspeople chattering]
There we go.
All right, let's get
you inside... whoa,
get you fed.
See if Marielle's magic
elixir does the trick, okay?
Why don't you go see your dad?
All I gotta do is get in bed,
and he's having
a really hard day.
Are you sure?
Yeah. Go. Go.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Um, here.
- Oh.
- I'll be back soon.
Give him my best, okay?
Okay.
[woman] None of these are
any good. They're all gross.
[Nicky]
Take those to the kitchen?
Are those the crops?
Yeah. We figured
we'd try composting them,
see if we can't
get the soil turned around.
- You think that'll work?
- Who the hell knows?
Sorry about yesterday,
the bathroom, I just...
It's okay. Everyone's on, uh,
on edge these days, so...
Still, no reason
to be a dick. Sorry.
[door closes]
[sniffing]
[ominous music playing]
♪♪♪
[straining]
Victor?
Ethan,
what are you doing up here?
- Have you seen Victor?
- I haven't, no.
He's not in his room.
He was pretty upset.
[breathing heavily]
Is that the cow that
died from last night?
Yeah.
I've never seen what things
look like on the inside before.
Is that what
Tian-Chen looked like...
after what they did to her?
No, sweetie.
Everything's covered in snow,
and it looks
so different outside.
I think she'd like that.
Hey, how about you and me...
I'm gonna go home.
Ethan?
She loved you... Tian-Chen.
She loved you very much.
I know.
[door opens]
- [exhales deeply]
- [door closes]
[footsteps approaching]
Excuse me. Um...
When I worked at the diner,
one of the...
We used to try on
dresses sometimes,
when things were slow.
We'd go to the storage and...
Well, it was silly.
But this was
the one she always...
This one was her favorite.
She said she'd wear it
the day we all went home.
I just thought, um...
Thank you, Sara.
Thank you.
[door opens]
[bottles clank]
[liquid pouring]
That's a heavy pour,
even on a day like today.
What I'm about to do...
I'm gonna do, and that's it.
I don't wanna talk.
I don't wanna listen.
Kenny, what are the bottles for?
I'm going into the tunnels.
I'm gonna find those things...
and I'm gonna burn every
last fucking one of them.
- You think that'll work?
- We burned the last one.
- The last one was already dead.
- I don't care.
I don't care.
I'm gonna make those
fucking things hurt.
- Okay.
- Okay what?
Okay. Let's do it.
Let's go.
Victor and Tabitha
said they're, uh,
everywhere down there.
Yet Jade went down there,
clearly saw
some disturbing shit.
What he didn't see...
creatures, not a single one.
Do you still think
they're down there?
I don't know.
Maybe they went
somewhere else after Tabitha
and Victor found them
or maybe they went deeper in.
This is one thing I do know.
This is how they want us...
angry, stumbling around
in the dark.
I also know this.
Hey, if we find them,
there's a good chance
we are not coming back.
But if this is
what you want to do...
I will go with you,
side by side,
and we will take out as many of
those motherfuckers as we can.
I can't stop thinking about...
how...
...scared
she must have been,
how alone she must have felt.
Hey.
She wasn't alone.
What?
They made me watch.
I couldn't help her.
I couldn't...
hey, they made me watch.
They made me watch.
[sobbing]
I couldn't help her.
I couldn't...
- [sobbing]
- Hey. But...
- Hey.
- [sobbing]
She was strong, Kenny.
- She was strong.
- No, no.
Listen, listen to me.
She was brave.
She looked at me, and she did
not take her eyes off me.
And before...
before... before
she died, she said...
[speaking Cantonese]
You know, I don't even know
if I'm saying this right.
[sobbing]
[sniffling]
"Take care of him"...
that's what it means.
"Take care of him."
"He'll be alone now."
[sobbing]
Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, come here.
Come here, man.
Come here.
It's okay.
[sobbing]
I got you, brother.
Hey, let's go back, okay?
Let's go back.
[continues sobbing]
Think her hair's okay?
Yeah, I think her hair is great.
What about the makeup?
Do you think...
do you think her makeup's okay?
Honestly, I think if you try
and put any more makeup on her,
Tian-Chen might sit up and slap
the lipstick out of your hand.
I just... I just... I just
want it to be right for Kenny.
It's right. Okay?
It's right.
You'll come with us when we go.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[somber music playing]
♪♪♪
[indistinct conversations]
I just wanted to say thank you
for what you did last night.
You're welcome.
Something happened
to me a few days ago.
- I was...
- I heard. You okay?
No. [sniffles]
No, not really.
[breathing shakily]
I think this place
has gotten in my head now,
and I'm scared of
what that might mean.
I don't want to hurt anybody.
I don't...
It's okay. You can say it.
I don't wanna end up like you.
I wouldn't either.
If you ever want to talk...
Thanks.
Well, believe it or not,
it all started on my birthday.
See, me and Miranda were
hippies back in the day,
but we gave up all the drugs,
all the drinking when she
got pregnant with Victor.
Then, one day, years later,
it was my 35th birthday,
Miranda gets it in her head
that we're gonna take
a stroll down memory lane.
She gets us two hits of acid.
We take the kids to her parents'
house for the night,
and we take one last trip
for old times' sake.
That's when the voices started,
when she started seeing things.
She painted everything she saw.
[Tabitha] Oh, my God.
[breathing heavily]
I've seen that, too.
She said it was like
she'd been chosen.
She said it was a place
that was everywhere, but you
couldn't find it if you tried.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Somewhere you could
stumble into from anywhere,
but never find a way to leave.
♪♪♪
She said there
were people there...
...people who were lost...
and afraid...
...who found themselves
living inside a nightmare
that they couldn't escape...
...fighting a battle
they knew they couldn't win.
She said they
were holding on to hope.
And when that hope was gone...
...they held on
to each other.
It all sounded like riddles,
gibberish.
She said that, of all the people
who would find
their way to this place,
she was the one who had been
chosen to free the children.
But she wasn't the first.
Others were chosen before her.
She could see
each and every one.
And all of them had failed.
None of them had ever
set the children free.
And none of them
had ever gone home.
So, if you've seen the children,
if they've called to you,
then I guess...
you've been chosen now, too.
- So, how did you get out?
- Oh, my God.
[indistinct conversations]
[tense music playing]
[clears throat]
How you holding up?
Dad?
Not good. Not good.
Look, I know you, uh,
carry a lot of weight
from this place,
and... I know...
I know it feels like
everything that happens here...
We can't keep doing this.
We can't just
keep sitting around,
waiting to see what...
we need more information.
Yeah. Yeah.
I'm gonna need your help with
something tomorrow, okay?
Yeah, all right.
But with what?
We're gonna catch
one of these fucking things.
[Ethan]
Are we still gonna live here?
Even though Tian-Chen is gone?
I don't know.
I have to take
that one step at a time.
Are you not coming inside?
No, I'm gonna go
check on the animals,
and make sure they're fed.
It's almost dark.
- Won't be long.
- I'm gonna go, too.
- Well, just be careful.
- Yeah, okay.
I love you guys.
[exhales deeply]
[telephone rings]
[ring]
[static hissing]
Hello?
[male voice] Dad? It's Thomas.
[static loudly hissing]
♪♪♪