This is Ian Reilly.
Leave a message, I'll get back to you.
Ian.
Oh, my God.
Happy retirement. Hang up your handcuffs.
Bit kinky, sir.
No, thanks.
I wasn't offering.
It's my piece.
This came for you.
Yeah? Yeah, Loftus.
My God.
Hi, sorry.
I'm just checking that Blanaid Williams
turned up for camogie this morning.
Okay. Thank you.
I... She was at a sleepover and...
Okay, bye.
This is Ian Reilly.
Leave a message, I'll get back to you.
He's blocked me. He's fucking blocked me.
Shit.
Oh, fuck.
- What?
- Where are you?
It doesn't matter. What's wrong?
We have a problem.
All my sisters have been arrested.
That's unfortunate.
I just... Can you tell me
why they've been brought in?
What are your sisters called?
- Garvey.
- Garvey?
Oh, yeah, I remember you.
Take a seat.
No, I just... No, I need to...
Look, can I speak
to Detective Loftus, please?
Can you take a seat please, madam?
Madam.
And?
And? How do you mean "and"?
I mean, your point is?
- Angelica Collins is missing.
- That's news to me.
So my point is,
it doesn't look very good, does it?
I haven't got my glasses. Sorry.
Is it the marina?
Yeah, I know it's the marina.
Why were you there?
Why were we there?
Do you mean, like,
was it business or pleasure?
'Cause I'd say it was a bit of both.
The footage was sent in anonymously,
so someone knows why you were there.
Or someone's trying to set us up.
Are you sure that's legit?
Your sister Eva was in here that day
telling us that Angelica
had threatened Grace,
so it makes sense
why you'd want to talk to her.
Did it just go too far?
Did Mr. Reilly get involved?
Because we know that he's--
- A word, Detective Houlihan.
- Not now.
- No, now, please.
- I'll come and find you later.
Detective Houlihan, outside, now.
Why are all the Garveys here?
Because I have video evidence of them
taking Angelica Collins out on a boat
and coming back without her.
I think they killed her.
Only a couple of days back,
you wanted to haul in Ian Reilly.
- Yes, well, it's all connected, isn't it?
- That's good to know.
Angelica Collins has been found.
Her body's been found?
Her body.
Her head.
All of her.
Jesus. Alive.
And you don't just round up people
you suspect of murder on a whim.
Do you understand me?
- Everything you do, it goes through me.
- Yeah, with respect, sir,
- I have tried to contact you.
- A missing woman found.
Money found.
There is nothing here.
You're chasing nothing.
- Grace Reilly shouldn't have--
- Grace Reilly knew we were onto her
and was clearly making a run for it
with 20 grand in her pocket.
So you go back to the family, you tell
them we found the money in the car.
You give it back to them,
and then you leave them alone.
This investigation is closed.
Do you hear me?
Don't need your bullshit on my last day.
Thank you for your service.
What about you, Sis?
I heard you got to go up in a helicopter.
Very happy to see that face.
That woman must have nine lives.
She'll tell the Guards now
it was an accident, right? Angelica.
We don't know what the mad bitch will say.
Yeah.
Why did Grace have
all that money in her car, lads?
She wouldn't have been legging it
from the cops, would she?
She wouldn't leave Bla behind.
She wasn't thinking straight, I know that.
You don't know anything.
Well, Houlihan was sent that CCTV
footage from the house at the marina.
- What?
- I thought Ian sorted that?
Where is he now?
- Eva.
- Eva, where are you going?
I thought she was gonna give us a lift.
Perfect.
Oh, shit!
What are you doing?
The... Children crossing.
Fuck off.
I need to check
Blanaid Williams's account.
I'm her aunt, her guardian.
I came in the other day.
I need to check her account, please.
Can I see your ID?
Yes.
Sorry. Shit.
Oh, fuck.
That account is empty.
A transfer was made yesterday, actually.
What do you mean a transfer was made?
Moved to another account.
No, I know what a transfer means.
I used to be a bloody finance manager.
But how can that have--
how can that ha...
I haven't even handed in the forms yet.
It's over a hundred grand. Look...
Look, can I just speak to someone just...
just someone older, more experienced?
Thank you.
- Oh, God, you're not...
- Miss Garvey,
Blanaid's other trustee came in yesterday
and moved the money to a new account.
No.
No, how could that have happened?
You should have done checks on him.
And surely you should have had just
some sort of better system in place that...
Is this your signature?
Yeah, but that doesn't just...
Surely that doesn't mean
he can just take all of her money.
The gentleman was on the account
and had the proper documentation.
And he didn't take it, he moved it.
- Shit.
- Everything done was authorized
first by you and then by us.
Are you okay, madam?
Do you want to take a seat?
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
Where were you?
You need to talk to us, Eva.
- No, Eva, don't. Stop.
- Please don't. Just...
She's scaring me.
It's not even chilled.
Did Ian call the cops on us?
I think so, yeah.
Are you shitting me?
Where is he?
- He's gone.
- He's gone where?
Will you all just sit down?
Please, just...
- I don't know where he's gone.
- I knew it.
He's just gone.
There's no sign of him at Grace's.
And he's cleaned out Blanaid's account.
What are you talking about? How? How?
I thought I was protecting her.
He said...
I made him a co-trustee.
I signed some fucking bank transfer forms.
- What do you mean?
- I mean he played us.
Me.
- He played me.
- Oh, God, Eva.
Sorry, I am beyond rage.
How could you be such a--
Stupid dumb bitch? I don't know.
- What are you doing?
- I'm calling the Guards.
You can't bring the Guards into this.
He knows everything.
We'll be the criminals.
He'll get custody of Blanaid.
That man no more wants custody of Blanaid...
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Grace must have found out
that he was just using her too.
You think what happened to Grace
was Ian's fault?
Yeah.
Yes.
That's what she needed my help with.
The money she got out was for him.
Oh, God.
Angelica's innocent.
I didn't think this could get any worse.
I feel sick.
We need to go talk to Angelica.
We need to say sorry
and to explain it was an accident.
Seriously, the last thing we need now
is her pressing charges,
- but bagsy not me.
- Bagsy not me.
I'll go then.
I think she likes me.
If not best, then not least.
You, go get Ian.
Get Bla's money back.
Find the fucker.
He's blocked me.
Can you talk to Joe?
He spent time with him.
See if he knows anything
that can help us find him.
And you, lay off the lady petrol.
Okay? The last thing you need right now
is to fuel your anger.
You're wrong.
That's exactly what I need to do.
- Roger.
- Hey, you.
No, no. I... I've-I've-I've just brought you
some Maltesers.
And...
- that actually... that cancels the alarm.
- Roger.
- Angelica, I just--
- Shit.
- No, hang on. I--
- I think you should leave.
- Please just let me explain.
She remembers getting on a boat
with you lot and then nothing.
It was an accident.
The boom hit you.
Got you a right old wallop.
Becka almost drowned trying to find you.
We thought you were...
So glad you're alive.
Miracle.
We couldn't do this on purpose.
You know that, don't you?
You know us, Roger.
Why didn't you say anything?
Ian convinced us not to.
He said that we'd get done for murder.
I'm sorry. It's no excuse,
but we were scared for Bla.
Scared for ourselves, if I'm to be honest.
He's pulled the wool over our eyes,
Roger, and now he's gone.
You told me you knew nothing,
and I'll not forgive you for that.
Now we'd like to be alone,
so could you go now, please?
Are you all right?
Can I get you anything?
And is she capable of
having a conversation, do you think?
Oh, shite.
It's just important
that we talk to her as soon as possible.
Oh, come on.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
Intimidating a witness is a serious crime.
I was bringing her Maltesers.
You can't intimidate somebody
with Maltesers.
Well, I'll talk with Mrs. Collins.
Hear her version of events.
Pretty sure we'll be speaking again soon.
Fuck.
Jesus Christ.
Fancy a game?
No, I think I'm done
playing games with you.
I need your help, Joe.
Are you serious?
You came to ask for my help?
Not to explain yourself, no?
- Explain myself?
- Yes, Becka.
Explain what happened with you
and Billy Bassist.
Explain why you never told me
you were fecking pregnant.
I didn't tell you 'cause
I was gonna get a termination.
Sorry, I wasn't gonna tell you that.
Definitely not like this.
You weren't gonna tell me?
Like, that you were pregnant,
or you were gonna terminate our pregnancy?
My pregnancy.
Our pregnancy, Becka.
'Cause you're not an onion, okay?
You might think you're God's gift
or whatever,
but you can't actually self-sprout.
Self-sprout?
I don't even know why I'm assuming
it's my baby anyway.
Who else's would it be?
When it comes to you, Becka,
who the fuck knows?
It could have been his.
Now keep it calm there, both of ya.
I'd tell you to shove
your cue up your hole,
but you'd probably miss
'cause you're shit at pool.
God, no, no. Not my pool skills.
Your breath stinks
in the morning. Like, foul.
Oh, well, it didn't stop you trying to get
your leg over every five minutes, did it?
- No wonder I ended up in this mess!
- No, Becka. I ended up in the mess.
Jesus!
Oh, fuck's...
Okay, that's it! Out! Both of you.
Jesus fucking God.
Joe!
Oh, God. Sorry.
- Watch out.
- Sorry.
Will you slow down, please?
You said you were gonna have
a termination, so you haven't yet?
No, I'm not going to.
What? So what?
You're gonna raise the baby with him?
- Joe, no.
- Look, he's got amazing eyes. I get that.
But are eyes enough?
You know, one day he's gonna get older
and they'll get all milky and cloudy
and they won't look amazing.
I don't care about his eyes.
Well, you're not gonna tell me
it's his personality or his talent?
Oh, my God.
You frustrate me so fucking much, Becka.
You don't even realize what we have.
Like, what this is.
When we're laughing
at the same stupid thing.
When we're close, like, when we're just...
we're just comfortable
breathing the same air.
You know, that's actually worth something.
Joe, I...
Joe, will you just stop walking?
What do you want? Like, what?
Look, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for the secrets
and for shutting you out and...
It's just what my lot do.
So why'd you ask for my help earlier, huh?
What was that all about?
Ian.
He's done a runner.
He lied to Grace.
He shagged Eva and left.
He stole all of Blanaid's money.
He's a Dirty John
or a con man or whatever.
Jesus, Becka.
You Garveys really know
how to pick a prick.
But it's not my problem.
God.
Just a little bit of pressure.
Now lean forward.
I'm sorry about
what happened to you, Mrs. Collins.
Do you wanna tell me what you remember?
There you are.
If you make a complaint
about the Garvey sisters,
about what they did to you,
I'll have it dealt with.
You can tell me what happened.
Jonah spent three days in the whale.
I spent three hours in the water.
A small miracle in comparison,
but a miracle all the same.
Yeah.
It's always grapes or Maltesers, isn't it?
Grace...
would have baked me a cake.
She baked for the entire group.
Your bereavement group?
We both knew grief.
That's how we became friends.
And then Ian came along,
just changed everything.
Ian was grieving his sister, right?
I don't think he was.
You don't think he had a sister?
Not a dead one anyway.
How'd it go?
Good.
Not sure.
No, she's in rough shape.
Oh, God.
Yeah. I think she'll be okay though.
Yeah. Houlihan turned up.
What? Well, did she see you?
I hid behind a trolley, so yeah, she did.
What the hell, Ursula?
- Yeah. Joe hates me.
- Great.
Where's Eva?
I've never seen her like this.
All she's done is shower and cry
and drink warm white wine.
Hey, how you doing, honey?
I know what you're all thinking.
What kind of an excuse of a woman
shags her dead sister's husband?
And you're right.
I just followed my fanny.
I just followed my...
You followed your heart.
Who hasn't done that?
Why are you looking at me?
We've all done it, including Grace.
I'm gonna fix it though.
I'm gonna fix it.
I'm gonna find Ian
and get Bla's inheritance back.
I mean, Grace would never have
left her... daughter.
She just wouldn't have...
Wait, Becka, she's gonna be
home soon, okay?
We need answers. I need to f...
Just please. Just...
Sorry.
I'm not drunk.
I'm just broken.
I know. And drunk.
Bibi.
No! No!
Jesus Christ.
Oh, my God. What are you doing?
What am I doing?
You almost split my face open, Bibi!
Why are you here, Joe?
He's a gambler.
What? Who?
Ian.
Every time I had a pint with him,
he had one eye on the horses.
Sorry. And I've never seen him
without one of those little blue pens.
You know, the ones they have.
He's a gambler.
Of course he is.
You know the thing about gamblers?
They never stop gambling.
So, what do we do with that?
I didn't order that. You know I'm trying
to stick to my one a day.
You're on your second already, Roger.
Cornering a man in his local again?
I won't be bribed.
Can we just talk to you
for a minute please, Roger?
- I've had enough of you lot.
- You're right to be raging, Roger.
- But we never wanted Angelica dead.
- Shut up.
I did hate her.
I thought she was blackmailing Grace.
But I never wanted to hurt her.
Okay, well, maybe a bit,
when she tried to ruin my marriage.
Made our lives hell.
She's not a bad woman.
What is it they say?
Hurt people hurt.
Ian did a real number on us, Roger.
And Grace.
And Angelica tried to warn us about him.
She said he was a player.
We need to find him to honor Grace.
Apparently, he's a gambler.
Loves a gee-gee.
And you love a flutter too,
so we thought maybe--
The horses.
I knew it. I knew I recognized him.
And I asked him one time and he denied it.
I saw him at the course.
If we could just find some lead.
One person who knows something.
Please, Roger.
Girls, you had me at honor Grace.
You not coming to the party?
He'll flip if he's catered for you,
and you don't show.
Couldn't give a cat's tit. Have fun.
Go get yourself some cake.
- Really smooth moves, Kavanagh.
- Thanks.
Congratulations.
Now you can do nothing
without worrying about getting caught.
Thank you, sir. And I...
And I'm sorry I couldn't get you
your heads to throw to the press,
but it was just one of those cases.
- Listen...
- Dead ends.
...listen, it could have been a good one
for you to go out on.
But you're like me old dog, Loftus,
digging away and coming up with sweet FA.
You're lucky Grace Reilly's death
was enough of a sideshow
to keep the newshounds happy.
There's been a real mix-up with the boxes.
Only vegan arrived,
so it's good for the planet
but terrible for whoever has
to clean tomorrow's toilets.
Don't talk to me.
Yeah, with pleasure.
I mean, don't talk to me about bullshit.
You had me lie to those sisters.
Oh, Christ. Houlihan, not tonight,
all right? I'm tired.
I'm a divorced man
with an unsatisfactory golf handicap.
My fucking feet ache,
even when I'm sitting down.
And the only human being I love
in this world is leaving in a few days.
So, stick a fork in my arse.
Turn me over. I'm done.
So, because you've given up,
we all should?
No, no, you fire away, all right?
No better woman.
Because you still believe
that good people do the right thing
and bad people get punished.
You didn't get punished, sir.
Yeah. Well, sometimes the only way
of making something good
is by doing something bad.
Spare me. What were you
gonna use that money for?
- The broken world charity?
- No, actually.
I was gonna use it to pay a solicitor
to block Nadine from taking Jess away.
All I'm saying is it wasn't
for an all-expenses golf trip.
Do you ever think that move
might be good for your daughter?
That her mother
isn't doing it just to piss you off?
Or are you that self-involved?
I don't like to swear at women
but go fuck yourself.
Fuck.
I just wanted to give
DI Snatcher Loftus a proper send-off.
I've had the privilege
of learning at his knee this last while.
And he's taught me all the things
that are needed to be a great detective.
A great passion...
for golf.
Giant ego.
No one will ever call you sir again.
How will you cope out there
in the real world,
with no badge to protect you?
But most importantly,
the thing that he's taught me
when you can't go by the book...
is...
is how to dig hard and dig deep.
Dig 'em up, Snatcher!
Happy retirement, sir.
Happy retirement.
- This suddenly seems bonkers.
- I'm not expecting to find him.
Might get a tip-off
of where to look, is all.
She was so happy that day.
Remember my three-way? It was glorious.
Feels like another life.
I hate him for ruining that memory for us.
Sorry, ladies.
That took me by surprise.
Nerves, I think.
Okay, girls. Divide and conquer.
See if you can't set your wee peepers
on anything interesting, okay?
Yeah.
I'm just gonna get a drink first.
Thanks very much.
Oh, wait, do you recognize that lad?
Nah.
I have a question I wanted to ask you.
Have you ever seen a man like this
hang around here before?
I'm really sorry. I don't know him.
Guys? Anybody?
Sorry. Have you seen this guy before?
He's about 5'11"?
- He's not familiar to you?
- Sorry.
No? Okay.
People don't respond well
to a one-eyed woman looking for a man.
Yeah, it's a bit Kill Bill, all right.
Will you try and keep a lid on that?
No.
Thank you.
What the fuck?
Fuck.
- What are you doing in here?
- Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
Sorry, I'm just looking for the loo.
Is it this way?
Oh, shit. Fuck.
Urs.
- I just saw him. I just saw Ian. He's...
- Are you sure?
Yeah... There. Oh, shit.
He's going... Come on.
Ladies, have you got a pass?
Yeah. It's in there.
I left it in my handbag.
So, while I go and...
That handbag?
What's so important in there anyway?
Michael D. Higgins
and a bloody chocolate fountain?
- Okay, just... Okay. Okay.
- Come on.
Sorry. Just talk to you for a sec?
- Thanks. I'm her nurse.
- Okay.
She's actually on a day release,
she hasn't been out in a while.
What's your name?
Shit.
Ian.
What are you doing?
Get out of here.
Who the fuck is she? Do you know her?
Anyway...
Oh, shit.
Can I ask you a question?
Only if I can ask you one first.
Go on.
What are you doing later?
My Kegels. I'm pregnant.
Oh, Christ. All right.
Do you know this lad?
Oh, yeah, I've seen him around.
You have?
But you wanna ask him over there, Murph.
He's a regular of his.
He only ever uses lucky number five.
Let's go.
Eva, did you see him? Is he here?
No, he's not here. Let's just go.
And even if he was here,
we've got nothing on him, okay?
He's got everything on us.
Roger's got something.
It's not much, mind, but Ian's not Ian.
He's Cormac from Tyrone.
What?
His first name's Cormac.
Yeah, we've got that.
His lucky number's five?
I'm gonna have a shower.
Empty the booze cabinet.
Not in me.
I can't deal with any more drama.
You go in.
I got this.
You look lovely.
Thanks. I was at the races.
- Did you win?
- No.
Actually, a little win.
Do you want to go inside?
Yeah. Yeah.
- I've been thinking about getting in--
- I've been thinking about us a lot.
- Oh, sorry.
- It's okay.
You go.
Well, I've been thinking about your baby.
And you, of course, obviously.
- Not just your baby.
- Okay.
I've been thinking about
how great this could be.
And how great a mam you'll make.
And I think you should
- try and make it work with Joe.
- I've realized it needs to be with Joe.
- We should stop doing that.
- Yeah.
I don't think I can break up a family.
I don't think I could ever
let go of what happened...
if I keep holding on to you.
Thank you.
You saved me.
At the worst time of my life.
You too.
And that's the truth.
I was gonna name the baby Minna,
but it's a boy.
Well, you could always
call it Mattie then.
Little Mattie?
No.
Oh, shit.
What?
I got his stupid, dodgy phone open.
I think I know where he lives.
What?
Or the area anyway.
Maybe that's where Grace was headed,
up North, to try and find him.
I'm gonna go and look for him.
No, you won't.
Don't be a stupid cow.
Wait for us and we'll all go together.
Okay.
Hi. Hey, sorry.
I'm visiting my cousin Cormac.
It's my first time visiting though,
and I dropped my phone down the loo,
so no number and no address.
Did you try putting it in rice?
No. I will. I will though.
Do you know him?
Cormac Sweeney's your cousin?
Last big house on the left.
Last big house in the...
on the left, this fella?
Yeah, opposite the house
with the red car outside.
Okay. Thanks. Thank you.
- Sorry, I don't know him.
- I was told he lives here.
Maybe before I moved in.
I haven't been here long.
Okay.
He might go by the name, Ian Reilly.
No, I'm sorry.
I don't know him, whatever his name is.
Mammy?
What about... Sorry.
What about this woman?
Her name's Grace.
Has anyone called that ever come here
or called or...
What's all this about? Who's she?
She's my sister.
Or was. She's dead.
I'm sorry.
And I'm sorry that I can't help you.
I hope you find whoever
you're looking for.
Yeah, me too. Okay.
Yeah. Listen,
Why don't you find me some of those
little yellow bricks, okay?
Good boy.
You said they'd never come to our door
or anywhere near our kids.
You need to sort this out.
Found it, Dad.
I'm up in Donegal.
Are you nuts to go looking
for him on your own?
Well, I didn't find him, did I?
So chill out.
I've got a last name though.
Sweeney.
And he definitely used to live there.
What if finding this bastard
is worse for us than letting him go?
It's not about us.
Not for me.
I'm doing this for Grace.
For Blanaid.
We'll talk when I get back, okay?
Make a plan.
Are you all nodding?
Sorry. Yeah. See you in a bit.
I have an idea.
What?
- Thank you very much. Keep it coming.
- Hi.
Hello.
White wine for the lady?
- Yeah.
- Coming right up.
Please. Thank you.
Are you drunk?
Am I drunk?
Am I drunk? Yeah, absolutely.
Yeah. I'm celebrating.
I'm celebrating the end of my career
and the end of everything.
My daughter moves to Oz tomoz.
- Okay. Well, sorry to hear that.
- Here you go.
Thank you.
Hey.
To new beginnings.
Listen. Your text was a nice surprise.
Good.
Yeah, 'cause it all felt a bit, you know,
with me... on the case.
And never the twain etcetera.
- But now--
- No.
No?
No, I didn't--
You didn't?
No, I'm just here to ask for your help.
- Fuck.
- Yeah.
My sisters and I just really
need to track down Ian Reilly.
He also goes by the name Cormac Sweeney.
No. No. No.
I'm... That's over for me.
Like I said, I'm retired.
I told you that, right?
RIP me.
What do you want to
bloody find him for anyway?
Because he's a lying
piece of shit for one.
Quit while you're ahead.
Put the 20 grand into an account for
Grace's daughter and you cut your losses.
And yeah,
count yourself lucky that I even found it
because those turtles
could have had it for their din-dins.
What are you talking about?
They found it in Grace's car.
- Houlihan told us.
- Yeah.
It was found in the car, right?
Yeah, it was. Yeah.
You found the money at Grace's?
Yeah. Grace's car.
You're a disgrace.
Reggie.
Yes. Sorry. Thanks for calling me back.
Well, DI Loftus said I should call you so...
Adolf, yes. Oh, my God, yes. So funny.
It's not problematic at all.
Yeah.
Did you...
Did you get everything I sent through?
I need something on him, Reggie.
I think he could be dangerous and--
Well, I'm pretty sure
that he's from the North
so you might have better luck
through the PSNI.
Please. Just keep trawling.
Okay.
Yes, Reggie.
Come on, you sexy bastard.
What the fuck?
You nasty piece of shit.
Leave a message for Blanaid.
Is Blanaid still inside?
Don't think so.
Okay. Did she go into town or...
I saw her leave with her stepdad.
Hello, Eva.