I have to tell you something,
and I'm a bit scared.
I killed him.
I killed my husband.
Don't look at me like that.
I think I need to get some air.
No, no. Don't walk away from me.
- You can't walk out on me.
- I can't talk to you like this.
Please. Please don't leave me.
Please.
Grace.
Grace, are you okay, honey?
Has something happened?
I'm so sorry.
My sisters are gonna talk to Roger
and I can fix it.
It will be like it was.
No, it can't.
I don't want this now. I don't trust you.
You turned my life upside down.
I have to start over again now.
Grace, look.
If I have to carry this,
if you want me to keep your secret,
not go to the Guards,
then you need to make it worth my while.
- Hello?
- Hello.
You don't know me,
but I found your number in...
a phone that I think
belonged to my husband, Ian Reilly.
Who is this?
And why are you calling on Cormac's phone?
- Colleen, who are you talking to?
- Who's Cormac?
- He's my husband. Who's this?
- Let me deal with this.
- Ian?
- Which one is it this time?
Don't ever ring this number again.
Do you hear me?
Who was that? Where are you?
She said, "My husband."
What does that mean?
You demanding answers from me?
In your position?
Just bring the money to the Dundalk bar
and we'll talk then.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
It's last orders if
you want something to drink.
You look well.
Are you gonna explain any of this?
No small talk?
Okay. What do you
want me to explain exactly?
That you're not who you say you are.
- That you're a liar. A cheat.
- I'm not who I say I am?
Just give me what I asked for, Grace.
You're not getting money from me.
I want what's owed to me.
I want what's mine. I want my house back.
Your house?
Yes, my fucking house.
I want what's in the bank,
I want everything, or I'll go to the cops.
Now, your daughter is very fond of me,
as you know, and she's not stupid either.
So she'll listen when
I tell her what her mam did.
What's happening?
No one needs to know anything.
I'll go away.
I'll be just another
husband you carelessly lost.
Did you never love us at all?
You were just a mark, Grace.
Nothing personal.
Stay away from me and Blanaid.
Stay away from my family.
You're getting nothing.
Come on.
Hi, Eva Garvey's phone,
please leave a message.
Hey, Eva.
Eva, it's me. I'm...
I really need your help. I'm so sorry.
Please call me back.
Oh, no.
No, where is it?
Blanaid.
Oh, f...
Hiya.
Hey.
Are you okay?
What do you mean?
Yeah.
- Bla, are you having a cup of tea?
- No, thanks.
Hope you didn't mind me letting myself in.
Mi casa tu casa though, right?
What are you doing?
Can I go hang out with Saise?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Course.
Do you need some squids?
Will you give me a lift?
Do you wanna take the bike, honey?
I need to speak to your auntie Eva.
Sure.
Bye.
I can tell you're upset.
Look, I'm sorry
I left without saying goodbye,
but it just all got too much for me. I...
I regret what happened, Eva.
Which bit?
Being a thieving scam artist
or killing my sister?
Well, I don't think
you can pin that one on me.
You targeted her.
You found her at
a bereavement group, you psycho.
You lied to Grace
and now you're lying to me.
I never lied to Grace.
- She knew I had a past.
- You didn't just have a past.
You have another name.
You have another life.
You don't know anything
about my situation.
Just give me Blanaid's
money back and fuck off.
I think we need to get
a few things clear, don't you?
Or we're just gonna go round in circles.
Do you want a cup of tea?
You know, actually, I'll do a pot.
I assume that was
your sisters you were texting?
Jesus.
Come in.
Sorry to disturb.
Not as sorry as I am.
Bone broth.
My wife doesn't like me eating red meat,
but she's happy enough to
poison me with this piss.
May I have a word, sir?
Grace Garvey's husband's real name
is Cormac Sweeney and he's ex-PSNI.
Don't be wasting me time.
That Garvey case closed with Loftus.
He's done it before, sir.
And he's dangerous.
A bloody ex-cop. I want to go after him.
You know what happens to Guards
who turn on their own, don't you?
They find themselves going for
promotions and not getting them.
- But he's...
- Even though you're the best candidate.
And they'll tell you
not to let it put you off applying again
but then a year after that,
same thing would happen.
The year after, same again.
Until the penny finally drops
that the reason you're being passed over
is because there's something you did
when you were too young
to know how it all works.
Now, do you still want to go after him?
I've not got all day.
What are you doing?
- Let's go in.
- Just...
Maybe we should call someone first.
In case we need muscle.
What about Joe?
Joe's not really muscle material.
I mean, he's tall
and he's got big arms, but he's a softy.
- What about Donal?
- No, he's with the kids.
- What about--
- I am not calling Nora.
She's about to have an embryo implanted,
so she's...
- Oh, my God. No way.
- Oh, my God. We could have Irish twins.
Yeah. Thanks, it's wonderful,
but can we just go in, please?
Eva's on her own in there.
If looks could kill, what?
- Shut up.
- Don't make light of this.
This is no fun for me, I assure you.
All I ever did was help this family.
- Well, that's a joke.
- Is it?
I cared for Blanaid.
I haven't said a word to her.
I came back knowing
her mother was a murderer
just so the poor kid
could have some sort of consistency.
You stole that poor kid's money.
- We want it back.
- I bet you do.
For her.
Of course.
So it makes sense that
I keep it safe until she needs it.
I'm gonna kill him.
Hello?
Hi.
No, I'm just home now. Call you later.
Fuck.
Why is no one answering their phones?
- Just--
- Christ.
Saise's being a pick-me and
hanging out with Charlie instead of me.
What a pick-me bitch.
- I'm gonna watch TV.
- No, Bla,
there's no... nothing going on here.
Why don't you...
Why don't you hang out with Molly?
Where's Molly?
It's a pi... pizza night.
They're at Casa Romanos.
- Casa Romanos.
You used to love Casa Romanos.
Why are youse all acting weird?
We're not. I'm gonna take you there.
I don't have my car.
Ian, can Urs take your car?
- Or Bibi's car?
- Perfect. Thank you so much.
We just don't want him going anywhere.
I'll see you, Bla.
Have fun. Bring us back dough balls.
- And then there were three.
- Fuck off.
Why aren't you at work? Una?
Jesus, why aren't you at work?
I just...
I wasn't having a great day.
It's not sorted with your friend, Loftus?
Doesn't matter now anyway.
He's retired. So...
So then you start afresh
with new people, different people.
No, but... They're not different.
They're all the same.
I just need to do what I'm told.
- What?
- You never do what you're told.
When you were eight, you arrested
your father for smashing my coffee table.
You do what's right.
You can't help yourself.
This is Ian Reilly. Leave a message.
I'll get back to you.
The only reason our sister is dead is you.
Yeah, nothing to do
with her choices at all.
She crashed running from you, you creep.
That's not what happened.
I told Grace about you, Eva.
What do you mean you told her about me?
The way you were always looking at me.
That it made me uncomfortable.
She was coming to you that night.
- That's a lie.
- Maybe you were next. I mean...
You all knew she was capable of killing
the ones she loved.
- Becka, stop!
- Becka!
- Jesus Christ.
Get off her!
Jesus. Becka.
She's pregnant, you asshole.
Are you gonna blame me for
this one attacking me now?
- Oh, God.
- I'm okay.
I used to deal with
women like you all the time.
First ones to tell a fella to fuck off
and then the first ones to ask for
our help if it's not going your way.
Let's just go to the Guards.
Seriously.
I would happily do a stretch if it meant
I didn't have to listen to your shit.
A lot of use that would do you.
Who do you think
the Guards would listen to?
Why the hell would they listen to you?
You're a lowlife
living off vulnerable women.
Is that you, Eva?
Is that you you're talking about?
Poor, fragile you.
I'm a police officer, actually.
Bullshit.
Fine, think what you like.
But I have a lot of colleagues,
North and South,
who'd back me over a bunch of
hysterical women crying wolf again.
- He's lying.
- Try me.
If you're lucky, I won't go to the Guards
and tell them that
you covered up a murder.
And if you're lucky, I won't tell Blanaid
that her mother killed her rapist father.
Right?
Did you ever love her?
Because she loved you very much.
It's funny.
Grace asked me the same thing.
"Did you ever love me?"
I mean, what a question.
How could anyone love a murdering nutjob--
Shit!
Oh, my God.
- Yeah, this is a great idea, guys.
- Bla!
Isn't it?
Eat some pizza, hang out with
some younger folk, do a sleepover.
What's going on, Urs?
- Hey.
- Hi.
Ally. Look at you.
Big, happy family pizza night.
Okay. Look, I'm gonna see youse anon.
- Ursula.
- Ally, I--
I have never had a problem with you.
That's all. I...
I have always liked you and I am not
gonna try and muscle in on those kids.
Thank you.
- Oh, God.
- Thank you.
Okay. Sorry, I'm on
the night shift, so I've gotta rush.
I've gotta earn
the euros to buy the churros.
- Okay, bye.
- Okay.
Jesus Christ. That family is insane.
Sorry.
I didn't like what he said about Grace.
Is he winded?
Angelica, is he winded?
You killed him.
Oh, my God.
Well, he's definitely...
He's...
- Oh, no.
- Oh, my God. We...
- Oh, Christ.
- We killed a cop.
- Jesus.
No. She killed a cop.
Angelica.
Oh, shit.
- I came over here to say I'm sorry.
- Angelica... Yeah, okay.
- And I was guided...
- Could you... Give me the...
- ...to come and just join you all...
- Please give me the stick.
- ...in your grief for Grace.
- Angelica, will you just--
Oh, Jesus.
It'll be Urs.
Urs wouldn't knock.
- A delivery then.
- I haven't ordered anything. I haven't...
It could be bath towels.
Answer it before someone looks in. Go.
The door's locked.
Sorry.
I don't know where the key is.
I can't see the key.
Go round the side door.
You wanna do that?
Shit!
Okay, it's the cops. It's that bloody cop.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Angelica.
Angelica, just... Please just...
What do I do?
Do I tell them what happened?
What should I say?
We're fucked. We're totally fucked.
Sorry, I...
I lock the front door at night.
It's 5:00 p.m.
Yeah, well, I live alone, so...
Right. I was just trying
to get hold of Ian Reilly.
Have you seen him recently?
No, we haven't. I haven't. Sorry.
I just... I'm here with my sisters.
We were just watching a box set--
I'm just... I can't get a hold of him.
That's weird.
Well, I'll just...
I'll keep you posted if I hear from him.
Pretty sure he'll be back soon.
Can I just ask what you
needed to speak to him about?
Not your concern.
Just watch yourselves.
Fuck me.
Is she gone?
The... Where... Where is he?
- Where's the...
- We put him behind the sofa.
- You moved the body?
- We hid him.
- What happened, Eva?
- Why...
why did you move... why'd you move the body?
- Because the cops were here.
- We didn't discuss moving the body.
- What if she walked--
- Just shut up. I need to think.
Thinking.
No, it's not.
Oh, my God.
Hiya.
- Long time no see.
- I was just in with your sister.
Nice. How is she?
Why are you driving Ian Reilly's car?
I...
I just borrowed it
to drop Blanaid to dinner.
It's convenient.
Let me off with a warning.
No, he's fully comprehensive,
as far as I know.
- Where is Mr. Reilly?
- No idea.
Well, have a lovely evening.
Jesus.
How'd you kill a man
in the time it takes
to get to Casa fucking Romanos?
- How did you kill a man...
- Urs. It...
No. Wo... Women are...
are supposed to just
put up with this shit, but no.
Oh, no, we have to kill them.
We cannot keep killing
the men who wrong us.
It was Angelica.
Yes?
Jesus. She's in shock.
Would you get her a cup
of sweet tea or a Wispa?
Get her a bloody Wispa.
- So you moved the body?
- We had to think on our feet.
- There was no thinking.
- Please. Will you stop? We just...
We need to figure out
what we're gonna do, okay?
And we need to do it quick.
We don't know if that cop will come back.
Thank you very much.
We get rid of him.
No.
We tell the cops that
Angelica killed him. Sorry.
Why should she be
punished when he's the criminal?
I think she broke a few laws
when she bludgeoned him to death.
Yeah, I'm not
taking responsibility for that.
No, no, this is on us too.
We broke her.
He was a cop.
They all look after each other.
Even the bad ones.
No, you're right. We get rid of him.
Are you insane?
They'll never believe
we weren't involved, okay?
If we get rid of the body now,
there's a chance we'd get away with it.
- So we take him back to Donegal.
- What are you talking about?
They know Ian Reilly is missing.
They're out looking for him.
Ian Reilly isn't missing.
Oh, my God. Am I losing my marbles?
There is no Ian Reilly.
It's Cormac Sweeney who's dead
and we've never even met him.
We could drive him to those cliffs.
Sliabh Liag.
Throw the body over,
make it look like he lost his footing.
Are you...
This is horrible.
Yeah. Yeah, it is.
So is the alternative.
It's a good plan.
Okay, that's not gonna work.
What if we...
Can't we just put him in,
like, child's pose or something?
It's not big enough.
Can I make anyone a cup of tea?
- I'm no use to any of youse at all.
- It's fine, Angelica. Just...
Just go in. Just go back inside.
What the actual fuck
are we gonna do about her?
Poor thing's off her nut.
I don't care. Let's just deal with this.
This is heavy, lads.
Okay, let's just use your car.
What?
I'm not into that.
You're not into it?
She can't drive
with a dead body in the boot.
She's barely got her license a year.
Fine, I'll drive. I'll drive.
I just had it cleaned.
Oh, Jesus. Your poor eye.
I could kill him.
All right.
If we're going, we should go.
You stay here.
No, I should be with my sisters.
No, you're pregnant
and you've already got an injury.
- No, I'm coming.
- Okay, fine. Let's just go.
Wait. What about Ian's car?
It can't stay here.
Look, I've made
some sandwiches for the journey.
Ham and coleslaw.
This is Tom O'Rourke,
and after the break, I'll be bringing you
back to the '70s right here on 95.6 FM.
- Who'd wanna go back to the '70s?
- ...for our regular listeners.
Me. Right now.
This guy's annoying me.
...you never know what you'll end up
talking about on this show. He's--
There. He's gone.
Holy God.
Who the hell is...
Oh, Jesus, Mary and Joseph.
What are you doing, you mad bitch?
Oh, God. Oh, God... Christ.
Can I help you, Guard?
Are youse playing musical cars or what?
Can I ask why
you're driving Ian Reilly's car?
Does Mr. Reilly know
that you have his car?
No.
Would you mind stepping out?
I've changed my mind. I'm not ready.
To open it?
No. For what happens after.
Nothing's gonna happen, okay?
We have it covered.
Are we sure?
Of course we're sure.
Oh, my God!
- Fuck!
- Oh, my God!
Fuck. Shit. Shit.
Quiet. Be quiet. Will you be quiet?
Is he alive, Eva?
- Yeah.
- He's gonna be so cross with us.
Was that him?
Are you okay? What was that?
The boot just springs open
like that sometimes.
What?
It's an old car. That's just how...
It just pops open.
Oh, God.
Then why did we run?
You all ran, I followed.
- You frightened the shit out of me.
Okay. Come on.
Becka.
- Come on.
- I don't want to.
Come on.
What the hell?
- Oh, no.
- Oh, my God.
What?
What is happening?
- I'm gonna be sick.
- You didn't check for a pulse?
You're the bloody nurse,
why didn't you check it?
- Because you said he was bloody dead.
- He was dead.
Well, he's definitely not dead.
There was no pulse.
Okay, look, at least nobody's dead.
Right? That's the...
the upside of the whole...
We haven't killed anyone.
Yeah, that's the upside.
- Where is he though?
- Fuck's sake.
Guys?
- What?
- Oh, shit.
Oh, Jesus Christ. Oh, shit.
- What do we do?
- Shut up.
Don't move.
- Can he see us?
- Just quiet.
Oh, God. Oh, shit.
Ian. Ian. Ian!
Oh, no. This is terrible.
- Becka. No.
- Becka.
Becka. Be careful.
Oh, my God.
- What?
Come on.
That is fucking ridiculous.
This is a nightmare.
Oh, no!
He's wearing my robe!
Oh, no. That's not good.
I think I stitched your name in it.
I've had enough of this shit.
What are you doing?
- I'm gonna push him off.
- You are not going to push him off.
- Bibi! No!
- Bibi!
- Christ!
- You get back here!
- No, do not...
- Bibi, you're gonna fall!
I know what I'm doing!
Let's just finish it.
- No!
- Bibi. No.
Bibi.
- Give me your hand.
- Just mind the rock.
Careful!
- Do you have me?
- Pull her!
I've got you. Pull!
Come on.
You stupid cow. You could have died.
- Thank God.
- Fuck.
What are we gonna do about him?
What now, Eva? What now?
- What are you doing?
- I'm gonna call for help.
What?
So we just go to prison for that pig?
We just give up. Is that it?
No. We just...
We say it was an accident or we just...
we take our chances. Okay?
But this ends now.
You don't get to make that decision.
Just... No. Just...
We can't leave him there!
- Fuck him.
- We're not murderers.
We're not.
Hello.
We just saw someone
go over Sliabh Liag cliffs.
Yeah. I'm looking at him now. He's...
He's conscious
but he's got a bad head injury.
He's got a couple of head injuries.
Can we just get an ambulance urgently?
We did the right thing.
What's that?
What do we think?
- Run.
- Let's just go.
Oh, shit.
My knee.
I'm gonna put on some music.
Maybe Radio 4.
Something soothing.
Yeah. That's nice.
Oh, shit.
Why is Ian's car still here? Fuck's sake.
I don't know why
you asked Angelica to move it.
She was in no fit state.
Oh, God love her.
Hey.
Some walk of shame.
Big night?
Nobody move.
Somebody open the boot.
- Somebody move.
- Sorry.
Sorry, it just does that sometimes.
- Where is he?
- Where's who?
Ian Reilly.
- Never heard of him.
- Becka.
Well, Angelica told me
that she killed him. Is that true?
Not...
No.
She said that you put his body in the boot
with the intention of disposing of it.
Right, I'm arresting all of you.
- No, wait.
- Just... No, no, no. Please. Please.
Just take me, not them
because God will forgive me.
- Just leave the sisters out--
- He's not dead!
Angelica, you didn't kill anyone.
I didn't kill him? Thank God.
I was sure I killed him.
I mean, all that blood. I mean...
Do you mean it's not murder?
But will it still be attempted murder?
- Angelica, shut up.
- Everybody inside.
All of youse, now.
- We were mopping up for hours.
- Go inside.
When I say, "I'm going to the toilet,"
you say you're going
to the toilet too, okay?
Go to the toilet,
and you go to the toilet.
- Yeah. I need to go to the toilet.
- I need to go to the toilet too.
No, nobody's going to the toilet.
You know, I prayed for this.
I prayed and the Lord listened.
I mean, it's another miracle.
- Sure.
- Okay.
I'm gonna ask youse again. Where is he?
He had an accident,
and we called an ambulance.
What hospital was he taken to?
I don't know. I don't kn--
I should bring him a bottle of something.
- Apologize.
- Please, can you just...
can you just be quiet, please?
Where were you
when you called the ambulance?
- Where were we when we--
- Sliabh Liag.
At the cliff's edge.
Sorry.
Wait, are you calling the Guards?
- I am the Guards.
- Yeah, but I mean--
I don't think that you all understand
how much trouble youse are in.
- Hello? Are you there?
- Yes. Yes.
Kavanagh. Can you...
Can you check if Cormac Sweeney
has been taken into whatever
hospital's close to the Sliabh Liag area?
Will do.
You know his name.
Can you sit down, please?
- What the hell?
- Just... Can you just sit down?
I've only just found that out.
I haven't known it--
Wait. What's going on?
She knows about Ian.
Yeah, well, like I said,
I hadn't long worked that out.
And I am sorry about your sister, but--
You're sorry about our sister?
Loftus lied about Grace too.
She wasn't running away.
She died trying to get away from Ian.
From what I was told,
the money was found in the car.
That's crap.
You're just trying
to cover up for your mate.
Did you know Cormac Sweeney was a cop?
Is that why you kept it quiet?
'Cause he's one of yours?
No.
I wouldn't do that.
You waited for us to come back.
Why?
Well, because...
because I needed the facts.
Because I needed to--
You could have taken
Angelica to the station.
You could have been out looking for us.
Why didn't you?
It's because you're covering up
criminal behavior.
No. What they did
has nothing to do with me.
But you're the Guards, you said.
Look, I...
I tried to help Grace.
And I wanna help you now.
Then do.
Help us.
Hello?
Okay.
Okay, thank you.
He's alive, right?
Yeah.
Our sister's dead.
What more punishment do we need?
I need your help.
What do we do now?
Pray?
Worked for Angelica.
Brought Ian back from the dead.
Angelica. Angelica, it's...
it's probably time to head home now.
Well...
I am sorry about what I said.
No, listen, we...
We lost our minds a bit, I think.
And we're sorry about the boat.
Aye, sure.
What doesn't kill you makes you stronger.
Am I right, girls?
You're going to have to stop
disappearing on me.
I was worried about you.
What happened?
Angelica? Talk to me.
Maybe I can help.
No, you've helped enough.
Put the kettle on.
Were you at the Garveys? Nice time?
Yeah, they are great girls.
God.
I need to lie down
before I have a heart attack.
I need to see Joe.
Jesus Christ.
Good to see you too.
What happened to you?
The Garveys tried to kill me.
Twice.
I'm gonna make you press charges.
Yeah, well, you can try that.
They'll have their own
stories though, of course.
You ripping them off,
causing their sister's death.
If you had any evidence
that I was involved
in the death of a woman,
you wouldn't be here on your own.
You know, that Garda badge
doesn't make you invincible.
Beg your pardon?
May I?
Yeah.
You're looking well.
I was just catching up
with Cormac Sweeney here.
The artist formerly known as.
Yeah, you've been a very naughty boy
from what I hear.
Fraud, embezzlement, bigamy, of course.
Old school.
Spousal abuse.
And thrown out of the PSNI.
I didn't even think that was possible.
He was just saying that
the Garvey sisters tried to kill him.
Well, that's just silly.
No, they would have succeeded.
I've checked with the Garveys' whereabouts
and they were nowhere near you that night.
Bullshit. You know they f--
The thing is,
I will contradict every word you say,
and I will destroy evidence if I have to.
I'm dodgy like that.
A bit like you.
And you're not the only one
with pals in the PSNI.
Me too.
So you'll give Blanaid's money back
to the Garvey sisters
and we'll call it an accident.
Yeah. And a miracle, am I right?
Yeah, you should count
your lucky stars you're still here.
I'll deny everything, am I clear?
Crystal.
And we're even stephens now.
Even stephens.
And you watch yourself, all right?
You can't just hand out lone justice.
You'll get yourself fired.
Yeah, it's okay. I'm packing in the job.
What?
Well, it's not what I thought
it was gonna be.
And I'm not sure
it's who I wanna be either.
Houlihan, I don't mind telling you
that I found your personality
very challenging.
And your wardrobe too.
But with the likes of me leaving
and you sticking around...
I mean, the place
would only get more broken
if someone as good as you goes.
Think about it.
Hey.
There she is,
rubbing our noses in her pious bullshit.
What, like you rubbing my nose
in Beyoncé at 4:00 in the morning?
Your voice has gotten more
horrible over the years, by the way.
How dare you?
Not sure I'm in a fit state for this.
Well, there'll never be a right time.
How's Bla?
She's...
She's quiet still, you know.
Let's see.
Hey, walking partner.
What were you talking about?
Just, you know, nothing.
It's okay. You can be cagey about it
like you're cagey about everything.
No. Don't say that.
I know you're trying to protect me
but I'm not deaf and I'm not blind.
How do you mean?
My dad.
I know he wasn't a good person,
but that's not me.
I know who I am.
I know how good my mam was,
and that's who I am.
That's what I think about,
not the other stuff.
Jesus, Bla,
you haven't even had any therapy yet.
- Shall we go?
- Yeah.
Okay.
- Okay. Ready?
- Yeah.
How do we say goodbye?
- Bye.
- Bye-bye, Gracie.
- We love you, Gracie.
- We love you, Grace.
- Love you, Gracie.
- I love you, Mam.
- We love you!
- Bye-bye, Grace.