That's it. Come on. Keep on going.
Nine, eight-- Raise your knees! Seven...
Three, two, one.
How are you finding
the adjusted testosterone dose?
I wanna hit you more.
How about your libido?
Oh, Jesus, Eileen. I'm old. I'm grieving.
And actually, I'm happy on my own.
I don't need sex anymore, I've decided.
I'm 50.
Today, actually.
I'm done with all that.
You are not done.
And happy birthday,
you smoking hot, mid-century legend.
And hey, I'd do you.
Thanks.
Seriously though, how are you feeling?
I don't know.
I don't know. I just--
I just miss her on such a deep--
I just-- I miss her so deeply, like in my...
No, I'm grand for hugs.
I'm too angry for hugs.
I just feel like her death
was so completely avoidable.
If I'd just kept a closer watch on her
after everything.
What's everything?
Just knowing what was going on
in her head a bit more,
I would've been able to help her.
And minding Bla
it's way harder than I thought.
Suddenly, I'm not her favorite auntie
anymore, you know?
I'm just some basic bitch.
Do you wanna go for a cure-all dip?
No, I've gotta meet the coven.
Bibi heard someone calling us that
in town yesterday.
Wear it with pride.
See you soon.
I've a new client.
You know, your one, Angelica?
How funny is that?
She couldn't stop talking about you.
Where are you all?
Why is no one answering their phones?
We still have to plan.
Is the door not open?
I swear to God,
I've never wanted to kill that wagon more.
The door was open.
What wagon did you wanna kill?
No one. Just my sister, Ursula.
She's late and a bitch.
Well, you've met her.
Yeah.
Well, we just wanted to chat
if that's okay with you.
No.
Well, I mean, it's my birthday.
Also, there's stuff to plan.
We're scattering our sister's ashes.
It won't take long,
just wanted to ask you about
the money Becka told us was missing.
The money your sister
took out the day she died.
Well, I don't know
what that was all about.
Was she in some kind of trouble?
Had someone been threatening her,
anything like that?
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
Was Becka looking for the money
in Angelica Collins's house?
Did you not ask her?
You had her locked up long enough.
- Sir? Return the call.
- Fuck's sake.
I've got this.
Well, I've got, you know,
stuff I have to be getting on with.
A lot of organizing.
Yeah, one question. Then, I'll head.
Isn't it strange that you don't know why
Grace needed that money.
Seem to let each other
into every part of your lives.
You really have no idea?
I don't know, sneaky facelift.
Will you sign for this?
It's nice that they met, you know, after...
Sometimes it's worth putting yourself
out there. Online, I mean.
How'd you mean, online?
They met at a bereavement group.
- Ian lost his sister. But, yeah...
- Thank you.
...good to put yourself out there.
I'm not being stubborn.
I told you, I'm busy at work.
I will call you later.
I just signed for it.
Don't forget to bend your knees
when you're picking it up.
We'll see you again.
So Ian told us that he met Grace online,
but Eva's just said that they met
at a bereavement group,
which is a weird thing
to lie about, right?
Yeah. Which one's lying?
Let's get the thumbscrews out.
Yeah, if your spidey's are tingling,
go see him.
Hey, bring him back Grace's effects.
Catch him off guard.
I've got family stuff to take care of.
Was that Nadine on the phone?
Yeah, and her ole fella,
threatening to wheeze me into submission.
Here, what do you think of him?
- Like, as a man.
- Of Nadine's fella?
No, Ian.
No, he's not my type.
Seriously, get over here.
Sorry, I'm late. What's that?
Grace sent Eva a present from the grave.
No.
Seriously?
I didn't get you anything.
You never get me anything.
I love you.
It's almost a directive
from Gracie to throw a party.
No. Wha--
No, we're not going to do a party.
There's too much going on.
Had the Guards here earlier
asking about the money.
Sorry.
And Angelica's
taken things to the next level.
She's hired Eileen.
My trainer, Eileen.
Well, it's a warning, isn't it?
She's a loose cannon.
It's hardly a horse's head.
I don't give a shit
about your menopause nanny.
She had Becka looking at jail time.
She scared Grace to her grave.
She is lucky she's still walking.
I can't go to jail now.
Yeah. Save your own skin, Becka.
- It's not that. Shut up!
- You shut up.
If the cops find out
what that money was for,
they're closer to finding out
what we all did, okay?
So we give Angelica what she wants
and then we just disengage.
We're not really gonna give her
Gracie's ashes though, are we?
No, we're not. We'll clean out my hearth.
She'll be scattering the ashes
of briquettes and takeaway cartons.
You really shouldn't burn that stuff.
Oh, my God, that's her.
Don't answer it.
Angelica, hi.
Well-- Okay, then we'll come to you.
Okay, bye.
She wants to discuss the details
with us at high noon.
Did she really say high noon?
No, she said midday in fairness.
Good morning and welcome.
I can't stay long.
I have to take Ruben to the dentist.
Busy lives you all lead,
but there's always time for a cuppa.
Yeah, I've gotta get back to Bla too, so...
The wee pet.
I mean, she is a credit to Grace.
Yeah. You wanted
to discuss the details, Angelica...
Grace's ashes.
Becka, how do you take your tea?
I'm not a big tea drinker.
Yeah, not big on apologies either.
I'm sorry for shoving you.
And for breaking in.
And the rabbit?
Gaybo's been found.
He's back with me now.
Poor bastard.
- Sugar?
- Three.
Three.
You're fierce good to yourself,
as Mammy used to say.
Now, this is really a very modern idea,
but I feel that Grace would like it
if we scattered her at sea.
What?
Have you any idea
how much the sea meant to her?
You know, we could take one
of those tours of Dublin Bay,
and we could just, you know,
scatter her ashes along the way.
And then I could bake
some of Grace's flapjacks.
We could fill a flask.
We can make a day of it.
I'd really love your help on this.
I have dropped the charges.
And I'd hate to go back to the Guards.
I know where my pal keeps his boat.
He's away. He won't mind.
Great, but no Blanaid.
We have to protect her.
- Yeah.
- And no Ian,
because I don't feel safe around him.
Tea, Eva?
Yeah, no, I'm good.
So, tomorrow, noon, the marina.
Yeah, and maybe you should stay at home
and you know, mind Blanaid.
- But Eva's coming.
- Eva has to be there.
I'm sad to say this,
but I don't think you've been
respecting Grace's memory of late.
What are you on about?
You and Ian comforting each other
shamelessly.
Oh, my God.
Unbelievable.
There's nothing going on
between me and Ian.
We know that. She's just shit-stirring.
It's just-- You know,
we're rearing a child together,
which is-- you know,
it's weird and intimate
and-- That's totally the wrong word.
Wagon!
You still wanna humor her?
Yeah, because I got hauled in.
You couldn't bloody vamoose fast enough.
- Come on!
- Do you think this party's a good idea?
- She's a lot on her plate.
- Exactly why she needs one.
And I've swapped my shift now.
It's open if you wanna get in there.
Check out my cup holders.
I wanted to return Grace's
personal effects that have been processed.
Oh, sorry.
I've also been tasked
with just following up on a few details
if you've got a minute.
- Death admin.
- Thanks.
It's time-consuming.
This house has me beat.
Who's this?
That's my sister, Colleen.
She died two years ago in Canada.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Might you go back
to the bereavement group?
Angelica Collins's?
That one. No, I don't think so.
Well, I understand
that you met Grace there.
You told us it was online...
Well, we met online first.
Initially the group was online.
Did it help?
Well, meeting Grace did.
But, Angelica,
it's like she feeds off your grief.
Grace and I used to joke
that she got high on our lows.
Sorry, that is awful to say.
One more question.
Grace withdrew 20,000
the day that she crashed.
Do you know about that?
No idea.
I mean,
unless it was something for Blanaid,
but she would have told me.
Yeah, you think?
So, did you get those few details
you came for, Detective?
I did, Mr. Reilly, yeah.
And I'm sorry for your loss.
Well, your losses.
School's okay?
Yeah. Don't know. It's all right.
There's a girl who I sit with
in Spanish who's Spanish.
Nice. Handy.
Yeah.
How do you feel about Australia?
Who will look after Prince when I go?
Prince?
Cathy's pony.
I'll miss my friends.
It's too far away, Dad. I don't wanna go.
They can go if they love it so much.
If it's such a great place.
You can mind me, right?
- Dad?
- Yeah, of course I can.
Hey, I'll fix it, Jess, all right?
I promise.
Swear, Dad?
I swear.
Come here.
Hi, it's Nadine.
Leave a message
and I'll get back to you when I can.
I'm gonna fight you for custody,
and I'm gonna win.
How's that for stubbornness?
Hey.
Hiya.
There's something blocking your gutters.
Want me to take a look?
No, I'll do it.
No one's looking for 50-year-old
finance managers anymore
so it could be the start
of a new career for me.
Shit shoveler. Perfect.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah. No.
A present arrived from Grace earlier.
Karaoke machine.
She was so bloody organized.
- Eva--
- Sorry.
Sorry, I feel bad because
you lost her too, but--
Today's really hard.
I'm not...
I just feel very lonely.
Hey...
come here.
I won't let you get lonely.
Or we can be lonely together.
I mean, not, like, together together--
- Yeah, no, I know.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- Here.
This can't compete,
but I got you a present.
Happy birthday.
My favorite pope.
Hi, Francis. Thank you.
I thought you could do with a fresh pair.
You noticed my disgusting slippers?
I love them.
Thank you.
So, we had tea with Angelica earlier.
Yeah?
She said she didn't feel safe around you.
- I was wondering--
- Yeah,
I did something stupid.
What?
I wanted to have a word with her,
you know, tell her to leave you alone,
but I just...
- Oh, my--
- I just kind of lost it.
- Jesus, Ian!
- Sorry.
We don't need you
fighting our battles, okay?
You're only gonna make it worse.
Please, you can't rile her.
- Sorry.
- Hey, honey.
Did you get a bit of lunch or...
No.
There's nothing to eat in this house
except rice cakes and tomatoes.
Blame Becka, she's the food Hoover.
I'll get you some nosebag on the way.
Do you have all your gear?
And look, Bla, I don't want you going over
to Angelica's after school anymore.
I'll do what I want.
No, you will not do what you want,
you'll come straight home.
Calm down.
You look insane.
I wanna say she's being
a mean little bitch, but I can't.
You can, yeah.
She's so mean.
And for the record, you don't look insane.
You look lovely.
Okay.
- I'll see you later.
- Yeah.
Wait, what? Why?
Ian?
All right, you didn't hear it from me,
but they're throwing
a surprise party for you.
And just so you'll really hate it,
it's fancy dress.
Wha--
Kill me now.
Party cups.
Hi, Urs.
Yeah, we're just finishing up.
You want a what?
We've got to get an urn.
Well, it says Biscotti.
We'll tell her Grace loved Biscotti.
What's going on with you
and the baby stuff?
We're trying again.
I convinced Nora
that I was fully on board.
Angelica did us a favor
when she lobbed that grenade.
It's all so hard though.
It seems unfair.
Straight couples get families
when they don't even want them.
I'll give you my eggs if you like.
Nah, you're all right.
Nora's pretty adamant
she wanted a smart donor.
Get off me, you needy leech.
I asked for a short, Fergal.
Well, I got you a pint, Gerard.
You're welcome.
You still only have me for ten minutes
gratis and then you're on the clock.
My ex is trying
to take my daughter to Australia,
who doesn't even want to go.
How do I keep her here?
Do you really want to make her choose
between her mother and father?
So what? You--
I'm just supposed to roll over?
She's got the house, the car--
which her new fella's
been driving around in, by the way,
15 miles an hour, geriatric prick--
she's not taking my daughter too.
I want you to stop her.
Are you gonna put your money
where your mouth is, Fergal?
Once they're in Australia, it would be
almost impossible to get her back.
You want to do this now,
you're gonna need funds.
I'm good for it.
I'm 50.
- There? Yeah? You sure? Okay.
- Yeah. Perfect. Yeah. It's spot on.
One, two. One, two.
I can't get this thing to work.
We've been trying to work it all day.
One, two. One, two.
I don't even know if that's working.
That's amazing.
Surprise.
Surprise!
Oh, no! Surprise!
...birthday.
You were tipped off.
- You look like a hooker.
- Hey.
It looks amazing.
Big surprise, hey?
She's somewhere over here, I think.
- Roger.
- Becka let me in.
Didn't realize it was a party.
Yeah. Well, neither did I.
See you had your hair done. Very nice.
A few oysters for ya.
Oh, Roger.
Maybe I could come round some night
when you're not busy.
Take you out somewhere.
Sorry?
Help each other
through the loss like Ian and Grace did.
Are-- You're asking me out?
Or in. We could stay in.
It's fine if it's a no.
Yeah, it's a no.
But do you wanna stay and join us?
No, I don't want to intrude.
There's karaoke.
His pretty colored skin
Had been all frosted with the dew
"Oh well," she cried
"I'll take you in
And I'll take care of you"
Everyone.
"Take me in, oh, tender woman
Take me in, for heaven's sake
Take me in, oh, tender woman"
Nice.
She wrapped him up all cozy...
- You having a good time?
- Yeah.
Better than I thought, but...
And laid him by the fireside
...you know.
With some honey...
I know.
Go Roger!
She'd have loved this.
...Had been revived
"Oh, take me in, oh, tender woman
- Take me in
- For heavens sake
Take me in, oh, tender..."
Gotta put the dishwasher on.
"Take me in, oh, tender woman
Take me..."
Roger asked me out tonight.
Wow.
Think of those liquid hips.
He's a catch for someone.
Well, he asked me out first,
so that makes you sloppy seconds.
Well, Grace first really.
So, you know, sloppy thirds.
I missed her so much tonight.
I missed her laugh.
Yeah.
She loved this.
No.
Doo-be da, doo-be da
Eva.
Doo-be da
Hold onto love
That is what I do
Now that I've found you
And from above
Everything's stinking
They're not around you
- I'm pregnant.
- What?
Are you kidding me?
Did you know?
Not long. Just a couple of days.
- Oh, my God. Oh. Sorry.
- Careful. My boobs.
Sorry, but your world's going to implode
and explode in one glorious--
- I don't know what I'm gonna do yet.
- Okay.
Sorry.
It's okay.
But I miss you when you're gone
That is what I do
Hey, baby
And it's going to carry on
That is what I knew
Hey, baby
Doo-be da, doo-be da
Doo-be da
- We've got the Biscotti?
- Yes.
Come on.
She'll hold every minute against us.
Let her.
Today is about keeping her sweet.
Don't rile her.
And don't mention the money, right?
What's with the bag?
It's my wet weather gear.
Geez. Sort yourself out, why don't you?
Which boat is it?
Who'd you borrow that off?
Michael Flatley?
I'd never sleep with Michael Flatley.
Where the hell is she?
Bla? Are you awake?
I made you granola.
I didn't make it. I put it in a bowl.
Can I come in? I'm coming in.
Bla?
Blanaid?
Right. Now,
there is a sight for sore eyes.
Hi.
Just park your bike round the back there.
Hey, I was just thinking about you.
Ian, is Bla with you?
No. Is she not at school?
No, I gave her the day off.
- Why?
Because her bloody mam just died.
Sorry.
When did you last see her?
Well-- Oh, shit. Last night.
- Think she's with Angelica?
- Yeah, but that's where my head went.
Look, I gotta go.
I'll ca-- I'll talk to you.
Urs, is Angelica there yet?
'Cause Bla's not here.
She's not answering her phone.
- Not yet. No.
- Oh, my God.
Do you-- You don't think that she's--
Oh, shit. Hang on.
Eva? I can't get a proper signal out here.
Well, you don't think
that this whole ashes thing
is all a ruse or something, do you?
Like, she's taken her or... Fuck.
Hello?
- Yeah? Yeah.
- Eva Garvey?
My name's Tina. I'm from social services.
I've been trying your phone.
I can't hear you. I can't--
I'll call you back, Urs.
- Social services?
- Yeah.
I'm so-- Nearly flashed you there.
Can I come in? Have a chat?
Can I just ask-- Did someone call you or...
This is just a standard welfare check.
Can I-- Sorry, it was--
We had a party last night.
Well, not a party.
More like a family get-together.
A soiree. It's my birthday.
- Happy birthday.
- Oh, thank you. Fifty.
But I'm a young 50.
That's my sisters'.
That-- I don't even drink anymore.
Thank God.
Not that it was ever a problem.
Do you mind?
Yeah. Sure.
That's just guest wine.
What time is Blanaid home?
Ian Reilly's place was chaotic.
I'm telling you, sir.
He was looking for that money.
I just have a-- kind of a f--
If you say the word hunch,
gut, or feel in the next sentence...
I just can't buy that
it was a plain old road collision.
I mean, even if we did spook her,
she wouldn't run
and leave the daughter behind.
And what about the 20,000 euro?
Where's that?
I reckon-- I was thinking
and it's most probably somewhere
in her life, like her house.
My auntie was in an abusive relationship,
and he was a real dirtbag.
Anyway, she would save any money she could
and hide it in an old Quality Street tin
behind the shed.
You know, for when she needed to run.
Her hen money, that's what she called it.
I'll look into it.
She better not be messing with us.
She better not refresh the charges.
Seriously,
which one of your friends owns this?
Mikey.
Can't remember his last name.
Sounds made-up.
How'd he make his money?
I'm not sure.
Drugs?
No, guns.
Can you believe that wagon
called social services on me?
- You don't know that she did.
- Yeah, I know it like I know my name.
Look, let's just find Bla first,
and then we'll deal with her after.
Jesus Christ.
Look, I know you're worried sick,
but just try to stay calm.
I can't.
I'll call you back.
That wagon turn up yet?
I can't find Bla anywhere.
Will you just call me back?
Blanaid.
Shit.
Where are ya?
Fuck's sake.
Oy, do any of you know Blanaid Williams?
Is she the fresh orphan?
Yeah. Have you seen her today?
I wanna feel your hair on my balls.
Oh, God.
- Any joy?
- No, I can't--
I can't see her anywhere.
I'm gonna go to the cop shop.
Wait, look, it's too early for that, Eva.
She could be anywhere.
She might be down at the seafront.
She's not, okay?
She's not anywhere and I'm freaking out.
Angelica's done something to her
and I don't know what else to do.
So just call me if you hear anything.
There she is.
Permission to come aboard.
This is gonna be a long day.
Christ.
Look, we don't have time for this, okay?
She's only 14 years old.
- She just lost her mam. I need someone--
- I'll take this, Sergeant.
Ms. Garvey, come with me.
This way.
Check out Kate Winslet.
I'm scared she's gonna
make us pray together.
Grow a fanny, Urs.
Yeah, grow a fanny, Urs.
Should be here.
I feel Grace here.
Merciful God...
may Grace be relieved
of the burden of shame
she carried here on Earth.
Although she was betrayed
by those she loved...
she remained gracious till the end.
Oh, we pray too for beloved Blanaid,
may she find happiness.
Would you like to say a word?
Grace...
fly free as a seagull.
No,
fly close to try and help us
make sense of a life without you.
We love you so much.
Amen.
Fuck's sake.
Would you like to scatter a few?
No, you knock yourself out.
Jesus Christ.
Right, let's just go home.
Why do we need to talk about it?
We need Guards out there
looking for her now.
Eva, the wheels are in motion,
literally, okay?
The cars are out there.
Anything we can be doing, we are doing.
- Geez, you don't understand.
- I've got a 12-year-old at home myself.
- I know how tricky they can be.
- No, it's not about tricky, okay?
It's the-- It's other stuff.
It's people I can't trust
that are around her.
You mean Ian Reilly?
What?
No, I mean Angelica Collins.
I mean, thank you for today.
It was very healing, wasn't it?
Oh, yeah, praise the Lord.
I'm just wondering now whether I shouldn't
have brought my wee Blanaid along.
- And she's not your wee Blanaid.
- She's our niece.
We've got her.
And yet it was to me
she came this morning.
She's with you?
You had Eva worried.
Grace wouldn't want you
anywhere near Blanaid.
Brainwashing her with your blood--
You just need to stay away from her, okay?
She came to me.
Angelica, she was stalking Grace, okay?
She's zoned in on Blanaid now.
She's got this room in her house
that she's all done up for her.
It's just-- Something terrible's
gonna happen. I can feel it.
Like what?
She shouldn't be allowed around her.
I mean, are you even investigating her?
Well, I'm not being smart, but for what?
For being too intense?
No, for driving my sister to her death.
Are you saying you think
Angelica drove Grace off the road?
I'm not saying she literally drove her,
but she was wrangling money off her.
I mean, have you even found it yet?
We asked you about the money
and what it was for.
Oh, shit. Ian.
Oh, thank God.
Oh, Jesus Christ. Okay.
Will you put her on to me?
Well, where the hell was she?
Okay. I'll see you at home.
He found her.
He-- Yeah, sorry about all the
hysterical-- I was panicked, I think.
So, yeah, sorry. Forget all that.
Forget Angelica?
Yeah.
I think I was just crazed with panic and--
You know, it's my sister's daughter
and I lost her,
and also just hormones and--
But thank you for your time,
and sorry again.
Best wishes.
You ready?
Come on. Play nice.
Blanaid.
Where were you?
Were you with her?
Bla, I need to know where you are!
So you chase around town,
asking questions, making a show of me?
Yeah, because I was worried about you.
Why? You're not my mam.
You're no one's mam.
Bla!
Look, all she did was go shopping
with some money Angelica gave her.
- She's embarrassed by the fuss.
- I don't care.
I care that she is sneaking around
behind our backs with her.
Fine, but you overreacted.
I mean, you all do it, all the Garveys.
- There's always bloody drama.
- How is this my fault now?
I'm not saying it's your fault.
- I'm just saying that you ne--
- It's too hard.
It's too hard. I can't do it.
I can't do it.
- Eva.
- I ca--
Eva, come here. Come. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Yeah? I'm sorry. Look at me.
Hey.
Sorry.
Bibi, don't. Don't rise to her.
Do you know Grace was pro-choice?
Voted yes for marriage equality?
That's what she told you.
That girl needs someone to guide her.
And Eva is too busy making a play
for Grace's Ian to care about her.
- You're deluded.
- Well, she did it before. Why not again?
What the hell do you mean
she did it before?
She made a play for John Paul.
She did not make a play for JP.
He raped her.
He raped his wife's sister.
That is a very convenient tale.
Will you hold this a sec?
- I'm gonna fucking kill you!
- No, Bibi!
Calm down!
Eva is playing a player.
I know a snake in the grass
when I see one,
that man is not to be trusted.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about--
What do we do?
Ursula, point to where she went over.
Do not take your eyes off that spot.
- Where'd she go?
- Becka, call for help.
I can't see her.
Becka, downstairs! Now! Right now!
Call the coast guard from downstairs!
Ursula, keep your eyes on the water!
Hello?
- Hello? Oh, please.
- Oh, God.
What the hell just happened?
- Hello? Crap.
- Becka, look for a flare!
It'll be in a red box!
Oh, fuck you, Mikey.
- Christ's sake.
- Shit.
Bibi, I see her.
- Bibi, she's right there.
- Where?
- Okay.
- Go! Go straight back!
- It's not a fucking Volvo, Becka!
- Go back!
She's right there!
We're going to lose her.
Becka, no! Absolutely not!
You're pregnant, you stupid bitch!
- Becka! Come back!
- No, Becka!
Bibi, do something!
Angelica!
Becka!
Oh, shit!
It's not her.
It's not her!
Angelica!
Fuck that wagon!