Okay. Okay.
Oh, fuck.
Eva. Eva!
- Eva!
- It's not my car!
Sorry.
It's not my car.
Ready?
I've changed my mind. I'm not ready.
To open it?
No. For what happens after.
Nothing's gonna happen, okay?
We have it covered.
Are we sure?
Of course we're sure.
Are you counting yourself down
from a hundred?
Can we please just get it done?
Grace. Grace!
Wake up, Grace!
I'm sorry. Oh, my God. I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
Fine. I'll marry you.
It's not funny.
Since I'm the one getting choked,
I decide what's funny.
Come here.
Oh, God.
Ach,
your heart is going like the clappers.
Can I ask you something?
You ready to be my wife?
- Wow.
- Ladies and gentlemen, she has boobs.
Oh, my God.
They look great.
Oh, my God, girl.
You're gorgeous. Look at this.
- Bride to be.
- You don't have to wear that.
No, I want it.
Just promise me
there won't be any strippers or dwarfs.
You can't say dwarfs, love.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
There'll be no little people
taking off any clothes.
That's not true.
Put it away, Becka.
Really? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
That used to be your job.
This used to be yours.
Yeah, well, luckily I don't miss it.
Samesies.
What can I say? We're all grown up now.
I'm stuck here now.
Stop.
What?
Waiting for something to go wrong.
I'm not.
I just don't know
why she needed to get married again.
She's a different breed of woman to you.
She likes to play by the rules.
Yeah, I don't have a problem
with the rules, just the rule-makers.
Right on. Fuck the system.
Forty-eight euro.
What?
Jesus. It's so easy for that bitch.
What, you wanna be chatting up little men?
No, I want little men chatting up me.
Go on Hinge.
I am on Hinge.
Don't pity me.
You know?
Hi.
- Hi. I found a jockey.
- Are you busy? Busy, busy?
She has three kids. FYI.
That's not true.
One's an adult.
I don't give a shit.
I'm just gonna steal her away now
if that's all right.
Mind your little noggin now,
jumping all those tall fences.
It's the boots. Oh, my God.
We got the champers.
- He's so cute...
- He was too small.
- House champagne.
- So, what's the plan?
Out of funds, so out of fun.
What? Are we?
What the hell? Where'd you get that?
- I did a three-way on Cherry Pop.
- It's called an each-way.
Whatever. I won 500 quid.
- Oh, my-- No. No, no, no.
- Stop.
I think I changed my mind
about the stripper.
I have the number. Let's do it.
- No penises.
- I can call him now.
No, I'm not looking at any penises.
Who's your one?
That's Angelica.
- Is she Roger's girlfriend?
- His sister.
You didn't answer my question.
Look.
Gracie, how are ya? Long time no see.
Hey, Roger. I'm grand.
Angelica.
It's so good to see you.
I'm sorry I haven't been in touch.
Not at all. I'm just delighted to see you.
You're looking so well.
Thanks. So are you.
I just poured myself into this
this morning. I just poured.
You must remember my sisters.
- Yeah. Hi. How are you?
- Hello.
Look at The Nolans, what?
And this one. The beauty of the family.
A little birdie tells me that you and Ian
are getting married.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Sorry, it was all a bit of a whirlwind.
So finally you put this fella
out of his misery.
Oh, no.
He's always held a candle for her.
Angelica.
I'm only joking with you.
Sure, we've given up on all that.
Did he tell you
that cohabitants we are now?
As the final runners arrive...
Oh, God. Have you got the kitty, Rogey?
A wee tip for the next race, girls.
Yeah, yeah.
Hurry Stiles.
I'm just going to put a few quid on.
Delighted, thrilled to have
just bumped into you, Gracie.
And you too.
And again,
I'm sorry for not getting in touch.
Not at all, sure, why would ya?
Great to see ya, Sister Sledge.
God bless.
Sister Sledge?
You're moving out of your lovely cottage?
It's, you know, time to move on.
A lot of memories in that place
and not enough good ones.
It is lovely to see ya.
- Hurry.
- You should come to the wedding.
It's nothing fancy. It's just at Eva's.
- Oi.
- Sorry.
I have to have a look at my diary.
Of course.
That's a joke. I don't have a diary.
Well, see you there.
You all set for shellfish?
We're shellfished up to our gees.
Just bring your lovely self, Roger.
- See you.
- You too.
- Okay. Right. What'd she say?
- Hurry Stiles.
- Hurry Stiles. I just got it.
- Hurry. Hurry.
- Come on.
So the runners are now riding down
towards the post,
and loading is almost ready
to get underway for our future contest.
Come on guys. Put on each-way.
- Okay. Hurry Stiles.
- Okay, 300, please,
- on Hurry Stiles--
- No. Wait.
- 350.
- Put 350 on it.
Anyone else? What's your bet, sir?
I'll have 15 quid on Stiles.
Oh, my God!
If we win, it's over two grand.
Trouble on legs, them Garveys.
That's a good name for a horse.
Be a better name for a strip club,
though, wouldn't it?
Watch your mouth.
And give me a note.
We're not in bloody Vegas.
Yeah, Justin, can I get a fiver there?
Now the runners are straightening up,
they've got just over
two furlongs to race.
And as they do so, it's Mr. Elsom,
the first who leads them
into the straight towards the outside.
You happy now you've seen her?
I think she was happy to see me too.
Wasn't she?
- Sure.
- They're the leading trio
as they head now to make their way
towards the final furlong.
Now Mr. Elsom and Calamity Casey
are beginning to quicken...
Go on, boy.
Yes.
Go on, Stiles. Go on, Stiles.
Come on, Hurry Stiles! Come on!
Go on, lad. Push on. Push on.
There you go, lad. There you go.
Go on, Stiles!
That's it! Yes! My God, yes!
Hurry Stiles has won the Emerald Cup.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
How much did we win?
Did I not say?
Eamonn Doyle slowed me down talking shite.
I didn't get the bet on.
What?
Oh, my God! We won!
We won!
- Did we?
- We did. We won!
It's a bit more than sediment buildup.
Heave it.
- What is it?
- Weighs a fecking ton, whatever it is.
Mam.
- What's in it?
- What's that, darling?
What do you wanna do?
Do you wanna open it?
Sure.
Oh, God Almighty.
Gust of wind came out of fecking nowhere.
That's some flyer, all right.
Did you check out
that deejay I sent your way?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm not hiring a bald deejay.
No, thanks.
You don't want crooner music
at a retirement party either.
You want pop.
Swift, Beyoncé, Bulldog.
- Pitbull.
- Yeah, he's good too.
Sir!
Who the hell is that?
- Shall I come to you, sir?
- Is that Houlihan?
Houli-- Who?
Just stepped up from uniform to the unit.
Oh, yeah.
I didn't recognize her in her clothes.
In her civvies, I meant. Get a grip.
What the hell is she do--
Get off the green.
Get-- Why? Walk around. Walk around.
- Don't touch the ball.
- Sorry. Sorry.
- Leave it. Get--
- Don't touch that!
Sorry. Thank you.
Jesus fucking Christ.
Sorry, sir. The D Super sent me.
You're needed at a house in Skerries.
Right. Yeah, well,
I'm finishing my round first.
He-- The boss is keen
to get you there ASAP, sir.
A dismembered body's
been found in a suitcase.
- What?
- In a suitcase,
in a pond,
in a back garden on Yeats Street.
Dismembered?
Not all in one piece.
Yes, I know what bloody--
I know what dismembered means.
Oh, for God's sake.
Tango Foxtrot 7224 to Control.
- Yeah, Loftus has arrived.
- Roger that.
- Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
- Go that way.
Sorry now. Sorry.
Sorry, sir. Sign in there.
She's with me.
Unfortunately.
He's not very nice.
Is it this way?
Houlihan, stay close.
We're waiting for the DI to arrive.
So as soon as he's here,
we'll check out the suitcase. All right?
All right, Snatcher.
Snatcher?
What have you got for me?
I've seen prettier corpses.
Keep your private life to yourself.
- Hello.
- Any personal property found?
He'd a nice suitcase.
Oh, Jesus.
What do you think?
Could it be a sex thing, sir?
What?
No, it couldn't. A bloody sex thing.
Sorry. Sorry, sir.
Just 'cause of the suitcase,
I was thinking about that spy fella.
And when do you think
the sex bit happened?
Before or after he lost his feet?
Bring in the state pathologist, yeah?
Don't want Kathleen bloody Murtagh
fitting this in between her salsa classes.
If he's been in the water awhile,
it'll be like trying to find
a pulse on a beef bourguignon.
And I want all eyes on this.
I'm gonna take a look around.
Apparently a pal of yours
used to live here.
How do you mean, "a pal of mine"?
That fella you dug up two years ago,
John Paul Williams.
No. No.
Fuck.
Jesus. It's your sister's wedding.
Take a day off.
It was an hour.
I've been up since 05:00 rolling pastry.
Stick it up your hole.
- That was brilliant.
- Great. Thank you.
You were pretty slow today.
Fuck off, Eileen.
You don't think five smoked salmon's
a bit excessive, no?
No, I don't think so. No.
Don't mention or say salmon.
- There she is.
- Shut up.
The most important person of the day.
Chief bridesmaid.
Head flower girl, actually.
All the aul ones have taken
the bridesmaids' spots.
Cheek.
- Mam said she's ready for you now.
- Did she? Princess Grace?
Oh, shit. It's 11:40.
- Let's go up. Let's go.
- Wait!
Fish hands.
Oh, God. Yeah.
- Where the hell's Becka?
- Becka!
- Jesus Christ.
- Get up, you lazy cow!
Becka! Do not make me come up there!
- Jesus, that's horrible.
- The hell?
What's that?
Oh, God.
Shall I come with ya?
Not unless you want
my sisters to braid your hair.
They like me though, don't they?
They can't stand you.
Becka, I'm serious. They--
Your sisters, they all like me, right?
Jesus, yeah, they all like ya.
Well, except for Bibi 'cause
you asked if lesbians got periods.
Oh, for God's sake.
No sense of humor.
That's the problem with lesbians.
- Yeah, just... just...
- No. Joe!
...come here for a sec.
Not yet.
- Welcome to you both.
- Thank you.
Your sisters would like you to know
that Mam and Dad
would be very proud of you today.
We are gathered here
to celebrate the unique and timely love
of Grace Garvey and Ian Reilly...
Two years ago,
you dig up John Paul Williams
at a cost of nearly 30 fecking grand
because, apparently,
there's compelling evidence
that his life was under threat.
And with respect, sir,
that's information I couldn't ignore.
And then you close it again
as an accident.
Hugely embarrassing at the time,
but not nearly as embarrassing
as it's going to be
when the department see that you missed
an entire house of fecking horrors
while you were at it.
Well, the results of the postmortem
were inconclusive, so...
So? So you left it at that?
Nothing to see here.
Well, I followed
proper policing procedure.
I knew you were a lazy bastard,
but this-- this is incompetence.
This is next-level.
I want to know exactly
what happened in that house
and if you mess things up again this time,
you're finished.
Do you hear me?
No retiring with glory.
I'll make sure of that.
I want heads arrested and sent down.
Do we understand each other?
Sir.
And Houlihan will be staying on with ya.
No, no, no.
It's not my job to teach little girls
how to be detectives.
It is.
It is literally in your job description.
- But she's-- she's a-- she's--
- She's what?
But she's an oddball.
She's 25. She's made detective.
She's also a diverse female officer.
Probably non-binary
or some bollocks by the look of her.
You overlook those ones at your peril.
I'm not comfortable with that language.
What? What language?
"Those ones."
But you called her a bleeding oddball.
Look, get out of here and get on with it!
Can you RSVP to the invite to my party?
For numbers.
Thank you.
"My party."
Jesus.
Well done, young lad!
I am done.
- Lightweight.
- I'm gonna get a pint.
I didn't know you invited Angelica.
She hadn't.
It's fine. I should've asked her really.
Why? I didn't even know
you were that friendly.
Oh, yeah, we got close after--
you know, when I was volunteering, and--
but then, it got a bit suffocating.
But sure, it's fine.
It's no one's fault.
Eileen? No?
- Joe, I hear you're a man...
- Joe, pint?
- Grand.
- ...who enjoys a bit of salmon.
Did Bibi tell you?
We've chosen an egg donor.
Wait, you're doing it?
What? Oh, my Go-- Oh, my God.
An egg donor?
Isn't that like a bonus
of being a lesbian couple?
You have loads of eggs?
Not anymore.
So you're gonna use Bibi's sperm, or...
Stop.
Sorry. I don't know why I said that.
- Nerves. Sorry.
- Wait. So you're--
You'll be carrying it or...
Yeah. Yeah.
Thank God.
Could you imagine Bibi pregnant?
- What? She'd be cute.
- You'll be next.
No fucking way. Thank you very much.
Hold on a sec.
Why the hell not?
- No.
- Come on.
Gross. Get your sperm away from me.
Nah.
Yeah. If I--
We're the same, you and I.
Are we?
In what way?
Well, we're women of a certain age
who understand we can't have it all.
But we're happy with that.
We're content with our lot.
- Eileen, this is Angelica.
- Hello.
How are you blessed
to know this family, Eileen?
Through Eva.
We've been working together.
I'm her menopause coach.
Menopause coach?
Is that real?
It sounds make-y up-y.
No, it's-- Yeah. Yeah.
There's a thing.
Out in the open with it all.
Good Lord.
Speech.
- Speech. Come on.
- That's important. The speech.
We met when we weren't
looking to meet anyone at all,
but we couldn't believe
how easy it all felt.
And I think now
that was down to you, my love.
I have never met anybody kinder,
more gracious, generous,
horrible taste in pets.
I thought the tortoises were Blanaid's,
so I was like, "Grand."
But they're not. They're hers.
They give me nightmares, Grace.
But anyway, forget all that.
I am a lucky man because I married
the most beautiful woman.
- And littlest B, yeah, well, no.
- Don't do a speech to me.
You are as important in all of this as us.
We love you.
Very cheesy. I know.
Jesus.
- She is actually vomiting.
- Sorry.
- What the hell, Becka?
- Sorry. Becka.
- In the plant? In the plant.
- To Grace and Ian!
Yeah.
- Are you ready for this? For us?
- Yeah.
Yeah. Are you?
Yeah.
- Jesus-- Christ, Ma!
- Sorry. Sorry.
A little something for
your first week, Detective.
What?
How was it?
Okay. Good. Good.
I saw my first dead body.
- No, you saw your father when he was in--
- Yeah, I--
I meant my first murdered body.
Found it about a garden, decomposed.
Bet you're glad you did
your driving license now.
What?
No, no, no. Mammy, Mammy,
I didn't make detective
just 'cause I got my driver's license.
Is that enough?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah. Don't go a little mad.
Ally and I are off.
Great to meet you all.
- It was a beautiful wedding. Yeah.
- Lovely to see you. Yeah.
- I-- Yeah.
- Yeah.
Do you want some salmon to go?
Would you stop pushing salmon on everyone?
Kids said you were dropping
them off later. That all right?
Yeah, absolutely. Yeah.
You guys go and have fun or whatever it is
you do together with each other.
- Right. Catch you later.
- See ya.
- See you. Have a good one.
- Bye.
- See you at work, nurse.
- Nice to meet you.
It would kill me if Nora was leaving
with a young, fit blonde.
She's not that young.
She's not that fit.
I love you, Ian.
Let's take a photo before we get gee-eyed.
- Salmon sandwich?
- No!
Wait, wait, wait.
- Wait.
- Okay, wait. Hang on.
- Oh, no, wait. That's too...
- It's your thumb, Becka.
- Becka, it's your thumb.
- Cheese.
- Your thumb is in the way.
- Becka--
I'm gonna get my camera. That's terrible.
Urs?
Hi.
- I was just looking for a tampon.
- For all that dust up there?
Up yours, bitch.
I'm sorry I said she was fit.
Absolutely fine.
That's some news about the egg donor.
I'm shitting myself, actually.
I didn't connect with Ruben
for the first two years
and that was without some stranger's egg.
I think Nora's chosen to forget all that.
- Hello.
- Jesus, you made us jump.
I was just having a pee...
and a bit of a gander.
It's like a museum, this place.
If walls could talk.
Am I right, girls?
I'll leave you to it.
Happy?
I'm so happy.
Mind if I cut in for a dance?
I'll let my wife answer that.
Of course I'll dance with you, Roger.
You okay?
Remember you said you wouldn't forget me?
I did, and I won't.
Well, your situation's
all changed suddenly, huh?
Well, life can take you by surprise.
Yeah. Mine stood still.
Do you ever think about what we did?
I don't, Roger.
I don't like to think about it.
I try not to,
but I carry it with me every day.
Should we rescue her?
He's pissed as a fart.
I'm so sorry.
You'll never know how sorry I am.
Grace?
Grace, do you want to--
Should we throw the bouquet?
- Really?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Yeah, go on, love.
Okay. Here we go, ladies.
Molly. Molly.
Come on, girls!
Get in there.
Who's gonna be next?
- It's gonna be me!
- Ready?
- All the single ladies.
Grace!
Rogey, I got it! I caught it!
We've got something to celebrate!
Well, what do you know?
Hope springs eternal in the human breast.
- So aggressive.
- Yeah.
Are you okay?
Sir.
Sorry.
- What do you want?
- Do you want me to get you some water?
No. Talk.
Forensics have got back at us.
After three days?
That's a record for that lot.
Well, I personally lit a fire
under their arses, demanded--
Just tell me.
Yes. Well, there's more to come,
but they've identified the body.
It's George Williams,
John Paul Williams's father.
Well, I could've told us that.
The bloody suitcase could've told us that.
- Anything else?
- Not yet.
But should we inform
the nearest next of kin?
Yeah, yeah. Do that.
The next of kin is Grace Williams, sir.
Rogey?
Are you home, Rogey?
Why didn't you answer me?
There's something going on
up at the Williams's old place.
I tried calling Grace. Police everywhere.
What do you mean?
What do you mean, "what do I mean"?
Are you awake?
And that's the trouble
when you rise at 03:00.
Angelica.
I mean, the Guards, they've got
the whole place cordoned off.
I mean, everyone is in hazmat gear,
like ET has just bloody landed.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
Do you know something about it?
How would I?
Hey.
Where are you, Trotsky?
You're lucky you caught me.
This won't take long.
Please.
- Can I ask, Mrs. Williams--
- It's Mrs. Reilly.
Married again? Congrats.
Yeah, I thought I spotted his clubs
out in the hallway, actually.
A Cobra Fly XL man?
Very nice. Yeah.
Can I ask you, when you last saw
your father-in-law, Mrs. Reilly?
My father-in-law?
Your late husband's father,
George Williams.
Years, I suppose.
He walked out on his wife, Minna--
God-- more than a decade ago.
And did you have any contact
with him after he left?
No. Why would I?
Do you recognize this?
It's a suitcase.
Yeah, I know...
I know it's a suitcase. Yeah.
Have you seen it before?
Don't think so.
My suitcase could go
round an airport carousel five times
and I wouldn't be able to
pick it out of a lineup.
I'm sorry. What has this got to do
with my father-in-law?
Well, it looks like we found him.
Really? How is he?
He's not good.
No. We found him dismembered
in that suitcase.
What?
Yeah, in the pond
of the Williams's family home.
I don't understand.
Are you saying he was murdered?
It's unlikely to be an accident.
We're still in the middle of forensics.
Yeah, I can see you're in shock.
Is there anyone home with you?
I think that's my husband back now.
Great. Well, we'll head off, so...
Just needed to pass on the news,
you being the closest living next of kin.
Yeah.
Hello.
Straight up the stairs.
Yeah, I have a teen myself.
It's a mystery to me
what they do up there.
- Detective Inspector Loftus.
- Right.
- Detective Houlihan--
- We'll get out of your hair, so...
Come on.
- What the--
- It's nothing. It's fine.
How did your insurance claim
pan out in the end, by the way?
Sorry?
Your husband's life insurance.
What has that got to do with you?
Well, I'm the man who signed off on
Mr. Williams's exhumation, Mrs. Reilly.
And I haven't heard the last of it,
to tell you the truth.
So actually, it has a lot to do with me.
They all call him Snatcher,
like body snatcher because of--
I withdrew the claim.
John Paul, Mr. Williams, took his life.
I didn't want my daughter
knowing about it.
I didn't want his suicide
getting out there.
So I withdrew.
It's a lot of money to say goodbye to.
I didn't feel like I had a choice.
No. Of course.
Well, my condolences
and my congratulations.
I'm off to The Gravedigger's.
You can drive yourself home from there.
What was that all about?
What? Yeah, yeah. I'm fine.
Just let me get the oven on.
Why were the Guards here, Grace?
Hey. Why were the Guards here?
There's a dead body been found.
What? Where?
At John Paul's old place. His father.
I'm the only living next of kin,
so, it's awful.
But it's nothing to do with us.
It's just an awful, awful thing.
What's for dinner, Mam?
Can you handle goujons again?
Yeah, all right.
I don't believe her, sir. About the claim.
An odd way to commit suicide, all right.
You should say "died by suicide."
What?
"Commit" implies that it's a crime or,
like, it's a choice.
And it's not really a choice.
- And, of course--
- But it didn't fecking happen, did it?
So calm your ham.
Why is she lying?
Do you think she offed him, sir?
I mean, she was very quick to remarry.
Yeah, no, don't say that.
Annoying little bastard.
You've called Thomas Claffin.
Leave a message.
Detective Inspector Fergal Loftus here.
I need to talk to you ASAP
about the Garvey sisters.
You and your lanky brother.
Yeah?
What, back from the pit?
Like, that's midfield.
Jesus. Do you want me to--
No. Sorry, sorry. I'll get it.
- All right. Mind yourself.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Uh-oh.
Wait.
Roger.
I'm sorry, Grace. I--
Sure, I'll talk to you another time.
What's going on?
There's a body been found
at the Williams's place.
I know, but that's nothing to do with us.
I'm thinking of going to the police.
I need to unburden myself.
What? No, why would you do that?
'Cause it's just a matter of time.
I read about these things.
It's better to come clean now.
I'll tell 'em what he did.
- I'll say what I saw.
- Roger, you're scaring me.
You could unburden yourself too, you know?
No, no, no!
It's not just ourselves you'll be hurting.
It's Blanaid. It's my sisters.
You have to hold fast, Roger.
It was our secret. It can still be ours.
Please. Please. Please.
Please, Roger. Please. Please. Please.
You looking for this?
What's going on?
I could ask you the same thing.
I'm a woman of the church, Roger.
I'm in the guilt industry.
I know guilt when I see it.
Talk to me, Roger.
Where's Blanaid?
She's gone up to bed.
I have to tell you something,
and I'm a bit scared.
Don't be. Hey, y--
Hey, you can tell me anything.
He-- He... raped Eva.
He-- He raped my sister.
He... abused me.
I lost my mind, I think.
I don't know what I was doing.
What do you mean? Who abused you?
John Paul. John Paul.
I killed him.
I killed my husband.
Did you hear what I said?
You didn't kill him, Gracie.
I did.
And Roger?
He knows.
He says he's gonna tell the police.
Say something, Ian. Talk to me, please.
Please, please, please.
Jesus Christ.
What are you doing?
Don't look at me like that.
I think I need to get some air.
No, no. You... Don't walk away from me.
I can't talk to you like this.
Please. Please don't leave me. Please.
Eva!
Oi!
You're not going into work?
Breakfast meeting.
Jesus. They're getting
their money's worth.
Cheeky bitch.
We're off to Cork now.
What? No, no.
We've eaten all the smoked salmon, Eva.
It's time to go.
Jesus. Why do you always jump
when someone comes to the door?
We didn't get many visitors as kids.
What?
Bla.
It's very early, honey. Are you okay?
Come here. What's happened?
What's happened?
- Ian's gone.
- What do you mean he's gone?
Mam won't stop crying.