Are the kids awake?
Are the kids awake? Candy,
it's 6:30 in the morning.
Are you alright?
Yeah, why wouldn't I be alright?
Did Mrs. Montgomery ever
mention getting a divorce?
She mentioned it once.
She said
maybe when her kids were
grown, that she still had
a life to lead and...
- A life to lead with you?
- No.
No, that was never...
We never contemplated a future.
I loved Betty, and
Candy knew that.
Did your wife ever find out
you were having an affair?
If she did, she never
let on. I don't think so.
Did you kill your wife?
No.
Do you know who did?
Mr. Gore, at this
time, we're gonna have
to read you your legal
rights as prescribed by law.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say can and
will be used against you
in a court of law. You have
a right to an attorney.
If you can't afford one,
one will be provided to you.
Do you understand these rights
as I've read them to you?
Hello?
Mrs. Montgomery?
Yeah, Chief Abbott here.
- Oh, hi.
- Sorry to bother you at home.
Listen,
we had a couple more
questions and so forth.
Wondering if you could
just pop back in here
if it's not too much
of an imposition.
It's just routine.
We need to take your prints,
so we can screen out the prints
of family and friends who
were in the house that day.
Okay.
Sure are a lot of
folks here today.
Yes, ma'am.
So, you made mention of
a "Marriage Encounter"?
Yes, well, we mainly went because
Allan and Betty swore by it.
As did the Garlingtons.
Very big on communication,
expressing your feelings,
and so forth.
Yeah.
Do you know if Betty Gore
was having an affair?
No.
No, I wouldn't know about that.
Do you know whether Allan
Gore was having an affair?
No.
What about you and your husband?
Have either of you had
any outside affairs?
Pat wouldn't do that.
But you would?
I did.
You did?
With who?
I had an affair with Allan Gore.
You murdered Betty
Gore, didn't you?
No, I didn't.
I think you did.
You're wrong.
You seem pretty
composed in your denial.
Most people get
accused of murder,
they react with hysterics.
You're cool as a cucumber.
Betty Gore was your friend.
You slept with her husband and
then you cut her up with an axe.
You just chopped and chopped
and chopped and chopped on her
and then you sit here
and lie to us about it.
You make me so sick, I can't even stay
in the same room with you anymore.
Well.
You know, my grandfather
always used to say,
"Sometimes in a bad situation, all
you can do is make the best of it."
I think the best thing
that you can do here,
Mrs. Montgomery,
is tell us the truth.
I didn't murder her.
I didn't do it.
Well, I think you did.
And I think a jury
might think you did.
If I show 'em this fingerprint,
and I tell 'em it's your print,
and I show 'em the footprints
- in Betty Gore's house...
- They're gonna think I did it, too.
But, I didn't.
You care if we
looked over your car?
No.
You're tryin' to pin something
on me and that's not right.
You're tryin' to manipulate me
to admit something I didn't do.
Those sandals?
Mind if we kept those
shoes for a while?
No.
Appreciate if we could have
the shoes you're wearing, too.
This is not fair
what you're doin'.
They actually came right
out and accused you?
And they weren't very
nice about it either.
- Jesus.
- Honey.
Tell him about the affair.
Go ahead.
Hold on. Hold on.
Before we say anything else,
you need to retain me as counsel
so we have
attorney-client privilege.
Pat, write me out a check.
Doesn't matter what it's for.
- $100, and put the date and time on it.
- Okay.
And do it outside
in the outer office.
- I need to talk to Candy alone.
- Why?
Because I do.
Just wait outside or drive
around for 10 or 15 minutes.
Okay.
What affair?
I had an affair with Allan Gore.
But it's over. It has been
over for eight months.
Did Betty know about that?
It seems she might have. She
brought it up. On the day.
Did the police read
you your rights?
No.
I'm gonna pay a little visit
to the police on process.
Meantime, I want you to call
all the women at church.
Everyone who saw you at
Bible school last Friday,
ask them if they remember
what you were wearin'.
What? Why?
For you to have done
what they're suggesting,
you'd have had
blood all over you.
I wanna establish a record
that you looked normal,
and you'd be surprised how
fast memories can fade,
- so do this today.
- Don.
Just do it, Candy.
And if you can pass a
private polygraph test,
we might be able to
clear this up right away.
And no communication whatsoever
going forward with Allan Gore.
We don't know what
he's saying or to who.
You do not talk to him.
He leaves for Kansas today anyway.
There's another service tomorrow.
Yes, sir.
No, I wouldn't...
I wouldn't have a
problem with that.
I don't have anything to say
that I haven't already told you.
I understand.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
What's going on?
Is there some place where we
can go and talk in private,
you, me, and Bertha?
Sure. Come over here.
This is the hardest thing
I've ever had to do.
I had
an affair with a woman.
And it wasn't
anything. She didn't
mean anything to me.
It's over now.
It's been over for
more than six months.
My God, Allan. How could you?
The reason I'm telling you this
is because I've
talked to the police
and...
they tell me she is a
suspect in the murder.
The woman you had
an affair with?
Yes.
Her name is Candy Montgomery,
and she was the woman.
They think she did it?
It seems so.
Has she been arrested?
No, I don't...
Honey, can you please just
give us a few more minutes?
From what I understand,
she is the main suspect.
But these recent developments have
the quiet Dallas suburb on edge.
No evidence of a break-in,
you'll recall there was
no sign of forced entry.
And we've been told the police
consider it more than likely
that Betty Gore was murdered
by someone she knew.
And now, an Eyewitness News
report on the recent...
It's in the papers, too.
"Female friend of Allan Gore."
What are the
lawyers tellin' her?
She hasn't said.
She say anything to you?
No.
It's okay. I'll get it.
Thank you.
I'll get it.
- May I help you?
- Hi.
I'm looking for
Candy Montgomery.
- A reporter from where?
- "The Times Herald."
And there's stuff on the
television, in the newspapers.
The police are clearly
talkin' to the media.
This is gonna get rougher
before it gets better.
I think a little media
prep would be a good idea.
Can you come to my house?
Yeah. When?
- Like, right now.
- I'm on my way.
The police aren't
exactly sharing,
but I can't believe they
really think you did it.
And I don't think you did it.
That said,
there are three people in the
world you should never lie to.
Your pastor, your doctor,
and your lawyer. So
don't lie to me, Candy. Okay?
Okay.
I think you know who did do it.
I think you're
covering up somethin'.
Who are you covering for?
No one.
Candy.
The truth has a way of comin' out,
and I need to be prepared for it
if I'm gonna do you any good.
Did you walk in on somethin'?
And get scared?
No.
Candy.
Allan didn't do it.
- You're sure?
- Positive.
How can you be positive?
Because I did it.
What?
I did it.
I don't believe you.
She came at me.
So, I did it.
Pat doesn't know?
Of course not.
What would he do
if you told him?
I don't know. He's a very
honest person.
He might tell the
police for my own good.
Then, you definitely
do not tell Pat.
You understand?
You tell nobody.
The only person you talk
to about this is me.
Also, you should know.
I talk a pretty good game
in the church parking lot
but I've never tried a
criminal case in my life.
I'm a personal injury guy.
You're gonna need an
experienced criminal attorney.
Now, I got a young kid.
His name is Robert Udashen.
Smart as hell.
But, we may need to get somebody
beyond that even.
Somebody big. 'Cause
this here is...
No, I want someone that
I can trust. I want you.
Candy, you need a real
criminal attorney.
I want you.
Do you know who caused
your wife's death?
- No.
- You went outside to pet the dog?
They just got a new puppy, yes.
On or about June 13th, 1980,
are you yourself the one who
caused your wife's death?
No.
After you pet the puppy,
you went into the utility
room to get Alisa's swimsuit?
- Yes.
- At the time your wife was killed,
were you physically
present in the home?
- No.
- Is that when you cut your foot?
In the utility room?
Did you plan or set up with
anyone to have your wife killed?
No.
Did you cut your foot
in the utility room?
I don't wanna talk about that.
- No.
- I don't wanna talk
about anything that
happened in that room.
No.
I don't like that
you're smoking again.
Well, if someone accused
you of chopping up a person
with an axe, you would
maybe smoke, too.
Hey, what happened...
to that pair of thongs
that you used to wear?
I gave those to the police.
No, not, not those.
The other pair.
I don't know. I threw them away.
When?
A while ago. I don't know.
Why are you being so
curious all of a sudden?
Maybe if I'd been a little
more curious before,
we wouldn't be in
this situation.
What's that supposed to mean?
It's supposed to mean
what it means, Candy.
I don't like this tone.
I'm wondering if she's maybe got
some split personality or something.
Have you seen signs
of that before?
Never.
She's like the most normal
person on the planet.
Word is Allan Gore
passed his polygraph.
What are they waitin' for then?
I don't know.
I'm also hearing that Betty
was universally unliked.
At the church. At the
school where she taught.
They could still be running down leads,
going through the process of elimination.
Come on.
Eliminating people who'd
wanna take an axe to her?
How long can the list be?
Do people actually think
that I'm involved in this?
Of course, they don't. The people
in this town know you, Candy.
And they know that
the idea of you...
It's ridiculous.
Even Pat.
But you know that I'm
innocent, don't you?
- Of course, I do.
- No, I couldn't do that.
- Hello?
- Candy.
I'm afraid it's happenin'.
They just issued a
warrant for your arrest.
Are you there?
- Yeah, I'm here.
- Okay.
I'm passin' the phone to
Robert. You do as he says.
Candy,
after we hang up, get yourself
to Don's office right away.
We wanna have positive control
over the surrender, okay?
Where's Pat?
At work.
Okay, call him.
The bond will be
set for $100,000.
That means you'll need to
come up with $10,000 today
to avoid you being put in jail.
We're in the process of
tracking down a bail bondsman
but we need to have all that in
place before we turn you in, okay?
Yeah.
Alright.
If anything, this just shows
how desperate they are.
You are low-hanging
fruit, that's all.
Our top story today
is local housewife
Candace Lynn Montgomery is
being sought this afternoon
after being charged with murder in
the hacking death of Betty Gore...
Are they gonna
put Mommy in jail?
We know Mommy,
and we love Mommy.
We know she didn't do it.
We...
We all love her.
She lives here, for God's sake,
and she's been under
investigation for a week.
If she wanted to run, she
woulda done it already.
- Robert, judge's clerk on three!
- Alright. Just...
I'm sorry. Give me one moment.
Hello?
Good. You're here.
Why don't you wait
in the kitchen
while we sort this bond
business? It could take a while.
I got Judge Ryan's clerk
calling. He wants her there now.
Well, he's not gettin' her now.
He doesn't even have
jurisdiction yet.
Could you take her
in the kitchen?
You okay?
- Fine.
- Okay. Come on.
We were told Mrs. Montgomery
would be surrendering herself
but that hasn't happened yet.
Now, Mrs. Montgomery has
no prior arrest record,
has a stellar reputation
in the community,
and is an active member
in the local church,
which makes bail a possibility, even
in a gruesome murder such as this.
We are not delaying, Your Honor. We're
just having a problem with the bond,
which should resolve
itself any moment.
Look, given the hour, maybe it makes sense
to bring Mrs. Montgomery in the morning.
Oh, bullshit. I don't give
a damn how late the hour is.
Get Crowder on the
phone in a hurry!
Yes, sir.
He'd like to speak to you.
It's Judge Ryan.
How we doin', Judge?
Crowder, what the hell
you trying to pull?
- We're working on the bond.
- Bullshit.
And what do you even care?
This is not in your
court or any court.
This is still a sheriff's matter.
We will have her up there.
Well, you better.
Like, right now if you
know what's good for you.
Fat fuck.
Hey, we better get her up there.
Pissing off a district
judge is not what we need.
You go and I'll stay here and
lock down the bond. Fat fuck.
Candy.
I made cookies.
It's time.
So, why isn't Don coming?
It's a bit "all hands on deck."
This will just be
an arraignment.
You won't have to do
anything or say anything.
We'll enter a plea of not guilty,
have a brief discussion of bail.
We should be in and
out in 20 minutes.
Okay.
Oh, shit.
What's all this?
This would be us.
Oh, my God.
What's gonna happen?
Say nothing and stick by my side.
I'm gonna pull into the sally port,
and they'll close the door down
- after the public. Okay?
- Okay.
- Just do not open your door.
Follow me.
Candace Lynn Montgomery?
You are under arrest.
You're under arrest for
the offense of murder.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Are you kidding me?
Anything you say can and
will be used against you.
You have the right
to an attorney.
- No, you can't go with her.
- What? Why not?
You gotta go through
the main entrance.
Don't talk to anybody!
Take off your shirt
and hand it to me.
Alright, now take off your
pants, and hand them to me.
Now, take off your bra.
They fucked us.
She's in jail!?
They wouldn't accept our bond.
Don, Don, you told me
you would get her out.
- Pat.
- You told me!
Robert negotiated the terms of
surrender with the sheriff and the DA.
They didn't do what
we agreed to do.
Why? Why the hell not?
Because they're assholes, and they
wanted to make a grand showing.
The bond came from Dallas
County. Technically,
they have the right to refuse
an out-of-county bond,
and that's what they did.
Oh, my God!
We will have her out first
thing, I promise you.
They want a war?
We'll give it to 'em.
She reportedly was having an affair
with Betty Gore's husband, Allan Gore.
She was also the last person
to see Betty Gore alive.
And we're being told the bloody
thumbprint from the freezer door
is a match with the suspect.
Be with me.
- Elaine?
- Hey, Allan.
I'm dropping off.
The food, remember? I called.
It's my turn tomorrow,
- but I'll be out of town.
- Yes, yes.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
Well, I'll leave you to it.
Anyone who has looked at this crime
for more than five minutes knows
it had to be performed by a man.
Candy Montgomery couldn't
even lift an axe like that,
much less swing it.
What do you think happened then?
Well, we got a number of
people we're investigating.
I'm not at liberty
to use any names,
but I'll say this right now.
The case against Candy Montgomery
is one big pile of wet hooey.
I'm not sure talking to the
media like that is a good idea.
The police are talkin'.
We need to keep pace.
It could backfire.
Are you lookin' at
these newspapers?
She's suddenly
the Scarlet Woman!
The brazen, axe-wielding hussy!
If we don't stay ahead of that,
she's gonna be as
good as convicted
by the time we call
the first witness!
Candace Montgomery surrendered
to authorities last night
with a curious,
bewildering smile.
She had been a suspect
for more than a week.
Her lawyer and the
Collin County DA
struck an agreement allowing
her to turn herself in.
Bond was set at $100,000.
Here's the thing about trials.
They're fuck-fests.
Both sides trying to
fuck each other over.
It's not cat and mouse,
it's not a chess game,
and it's not civil.
I'm not going to go gently
on them and, full disclosure,
I won't be treading
lightly on you.
If we're gonna win this,
I need to take over,
and you need to do
everything I tell you.
- Okay.
- First thing, lose some weight.
I want you as small as possible.
I'm not exactly sure what my
legal strategy will be yet,
but I want the full
menu available,
including, "Look
how tiny she is.
"She couldn't possibly have overtaken
Betty Gore and swung an axe that big."
You also need to
change your hair.
Somethin' more conservative.
I'll choose your wardrobe.
And this is a big one.
No matter how tough you think you
are, I don't want you acting tough.
I'll be the tough guy. You'll
be the mousy housewife.
The mother. The singer
in the church choir.
Speaking of that, no
more in that choir
- till after this is over.
- That choir is my salvation.
Pick another one.
You are being very
aggressive with me.
You're damn right I am.
I don't feel I got the
whole picture here.
There's the Candy
Montgomery I know,
and the one who
chopped up Betty Gore.
She. Came. At me!
Robert thinks it's a good idea for
you to meet with a psychiatrist.
His name is Dr. Fred
Fason, outta Houston.
Houston? I can't go to Houston!
Yes, you can!
For me to help you,
I need to know exactly
what I'm dealing with.
Which, right now, I don't.
He also wants to change venue.
He thinks Galveston.
Galveston?
Or Port Arthur. Just
someplace where people
are more used to murder.
Okay.
What's he saying about
the case? The strategy?
He doesn't want me
to talk about it.
What do you mean?
He doesn't want me
to talk about it.
- Not even with me?
- No, not with anyone.
And honestly, Pat, I don't
want to. I'm so tired.
I'm just gonna turn this whole
matter over to God and Don
and just not talk about
it with anybody else.
Candy, I am your husband.
You need to talk to me.
Do you know what I need?
I need to follow
my lawyer's advice.
He's in charge. Don
Crowder. And God.
In case you haven't noticed,
I'm not doing too good.
I know, baby. And I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
We will get through this.
I'm not exactly sure
how, but we will.
She's gonna need the support
of this congregation.
I still can't believe it.
Every worshipper here is a
potential character witness
and knows the idea of her
doing this is bullshit.
And Ron...
- it ain't just gonna be Candy.
- What do you mean?
This church will
be put on trial.
Lucas Methodist will never
survive a murder conviction
against one of its congregants.
But
we just built our new sanctuary.
God knows Candy
couldn't have done this.
The congregation needs to
understand that God knows this.
The pastor is the one
that needs to tell 'em.
I understand.
The courtroom is already packed
with those lucky enough to get in.
Of course, the lawyers and
members of the media are present,
but one person not in that room today
is the defendant, Candy Montgomery.
For pretrial motions, in
this case, change of venue,
her attendance is not required.
And we're being told that
not only is she not here,
she's not even in
the jurisdiction.
Alright now. Before we get
to the matter of venue,
y'all better listen to me.
Been a little too much
jabberin' by both sides
to the newspapers and whatnot.
I don't wanna see or hear or
read anything in the media
that has Don Crowder's name to
it, Robert Udashen's name to it,
Tom O'Connell's, Jack Pepper,
anyone involved in the
prosecution of this case.
And if I do,
I'ma put you in jail.
And then you're gonna
have to try your lawsuit
from a cell block.
Show's over, gentlemen.
And if you want to test me,
I invite it.
Now, on venue.
Mr. Crowder, I've seen your
papers, and I am not impressed.
Actually, Judge, those
papers are meant to be read.
If you look closely,
you'll see words on 'em,
arranged in a
particular order, even.
- What are you doing?
- I'm not gonna let him walk all over us.
Fat fuck.
I've already got half a mind to
bounce you from this whole deal.
On what grounds?
On the grounds you're
outta your league some.
What business do you have
taking on a criminal case,
especially one of
this magnitude?
I'm here because my client
hired me. As is her right.
Maybe we could kick off
with that little refresher.
Criminal defendants get rights.
- Tread carefully, Mr. Crowder.
- Come on, Don.
This trial should not be
held in Collin County.
I would think you'd beg for
it. Folks here might know
your client to have a
modicum of goodness.
To the rest of the nation,
she's an axe murderer.
And what is she to you, Judge?
I just call balls and strikes.
And it's strike one
on you right now.
The defense called a
total of seven witnesses,
submitted nine sworn affidavits,
and, without exception,
they all testified that every
living, breathing person
in Collin County with access
to a radio, TV, or newspaper
thinks Candy Montgomery
to be guilty of murder.
In the end, Judge Ryan felt
that they would be able
to ignore their preconceived opinions,
and he denied the motion to change venue.
I'm not running a beauty
pageant. I'm not running for God.
I'm Tom Ryan.
Don doesn't like him one bit,
and I'm beginnin' to see why.
What is this trip
to Houston about?
They want her to meet
with some psychiatrist.
I don't, I don't
know exactly why.
Well, what's Candy tellin' you?
She doesn't wanna talk about it.
That doesn't make sense, Pat.
I don't wanna put
pressure on her.
Is she guilty of this?
No.
- No.
- You have doubts.
Questions, maybe.
- Like?
- Like,
why would she throw
away her thongs?
Why can't she discuss
the case with me?
And
why did she have cuts
and bruises all over her?
Did you ask her
about those things?
No, I can't. Any time I...
What'd I miss?
I don't understand why you
have to be so secretive.
Oh gosh, I told you, Pat.
It's because the lawyers
want it that way.
Candy!
You oughta be more open with
Pat. And me, for that matter.
Is there anything that happened
that day you haven't told us about?
I did not murder Betty Gore.
You and I are back-door friends.
I did not do it.
Everybody thinks I'm a monster.
My former pastor,
maybe my husband.
I don't know how much more
of this I can take, Don.
Candy, let's first
secure your freedom,
then we can worry about
what folks think of you.
I have to tell Pat. He
knows I'm not being honest.
For today, our
focus is Dr. Fason.
I don't know what's so
special about this Dr. Fason.
He can help us win at trial,
which makes him special to
me, and I would think to you.
What exactly do I tell him?
I told you. You
tell him everything.
Which includes the room.
You have to tell him everything
that happened in that room.
Hello.
Hi.
Did you see that?
I'm a sideshow!
It's not right!
It's not right that I'm
being kept in the dark!
She's gonna fall apart!
I can't help her if I
don't know what's going on!
It's lawyer-client
privilege, Pat.
I'm her goddamn husband!
I want you to pick a
point out on the wall.
Focus on it.
Now, take a deep breath.
Filling your chest. Good.
Slowly let the air out,
completely emptying your lungs.
Very good. Again.
Deep breath in.
Slowly let the air out,
completely emptying the lungs.
Everything here is safe.
Calm.
Peaceful.
As you relax, your eyes may
feel heavy and want to close.
That's okay. Let
them drift and fall.
Listen to your body.
You are in complete
control of this time.
You really think this will help?
I have no idea.
It can't hurt.
We're going to go
back to June 13.
When you went into Betty
Gore's utility room.
When I snap my fingers, you
will begin re-experiencing
and relating that time
as you go through it.
One.
Two.
Three.
What's happening, Candy?
You can tell me.
When I reach the count of three,
your thoughts and your feelings
will get stronger and stronger.
Stronger and stronger
and stronger. So strong,
you will have to verbalize
them and express them.
One.
Two. So strong, you will
have to get them out.
Three. Let them out.
What's that you're
feeling, Candy?
Hate.
Okay.
You hate her.
Express your feelings.
Stronger and stronger.
I hate her.
Say it loud.
Louder.
I hate her!
She's ruined my whole life.
Look at this.
I hate her!
When I count to three,
I want you to go back in time
to when she's shoving you.
You're in the utility room, and
she's shoving you. Just relax.
One.
Two.
Three.
What's happening now?
Go through it.
Feeling's very strong.
You hear that?
She sounds like
a wounded animal.
I don't want him.
- You can't have him!
- No.
The feelings are
getting stronger.
I don't want him!
Why are you doing this?
Betty!
What is she doing
now? Tell me, Candy.
You.
Stop! You stop!
Stop! Stop it! Stop!
Stop!
- What the hell?
- Should we go in there?
Oh, no.
It's okay.
It's over now.
You're okay.
You can't do that.
Candy, do you ever recall
being this mad before?
Maybe when you were little?
Let's go back in time.
One. Back in time. Two.
Three.
- How old are you, Candy?
- Four.
Four years old.
Why are you so mad?
Why so mad?
What will they think of
you in the waiting room?
Stop crying. Shh!
And how does it feel
when she says "shh"?
I wanna scream.
Candy, on the count of three,
- you're gonna scream all you want. One.
- I can't.
You can. Two.
Three.
Is this real?
Could she be faking?
Candy, on three, you
will feel no pain.
You are incapable of
feeling any pain whatsoever.
One, two, three.
On three, you will
feel very, very cold.
Very cold. One. Two.
Three.
Look there.
You ever know anyone
to fake a goosebump?
Well, what did he say?
That
you snapped.
That you're not a sociopath.
You, you just snapped.
So, what exactly
did you talk about?
Just all kinds of this and that.
Honestly, I'm not really
sure of the point.
I'm just glad to be back.
Can you eat your Brussels
sprouts, young man?
You, too, missy.
Can Alisa still
come for sleepovers?
Of course, she can, sweetie. She's
still your best friend, right?
It would be nice to have Alisa
over. I bet she misses you.
I'll get it.
Hello?
Pat, it's Don Crowder.
Don't say anything. Just
listen for a bit, okay?
Candy says you wanna know
the truth about everything.
I'm thinking that's a good idea.
So I'm gonna tell
you what happened.
- Is that okay, Pat?
- Yes. Yeah, that's fine.
I'm gonna tell you exactly.
Mom?
- What's gonna happen?
- Well
there will just
be a little trial.
And they will present
evidence and so forth.
And then, the jury
will find that
I'm innocent.
And we can all go back
to being a normal family.
- Wouldn't that be fun?
- Yes.