(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
(OLDIES MUSIC
PLAYING ON RADIO)
"Diary of a Thin Man."
- Where you been?
- Hospital, helping Carmela.
The devotion that kid shows.
I just think of
my Marie, the kids,
in that situation, God forbid.
My ma... who the fuck would take care
of her something happens?
Except Sil and you guys.
Colombians knock off at noon.
Then it's empty.
Manager's unit's down a flight.
(BABY CRYING)
(LATIN DANCE MUSIC
PLAYING)
Look out!
Somebody's coming!
- Who's in there?
- Open it.
Don't shoot!
What the fuck?
Get back!
- Shoot the prick.
- Get the fuck out of the way.
Cocksucking miserable Spic shit!
It's supposed to be
empty here daytimes.
Jesus, my fucking balls!
(MOANING)
The money!
Fuck, my fucking balls.
- Oogatz here.
- The freeze.
Nothing.
Come on, let's blow.
Lot of fucking noise we made.
Fuck that.
- Close the goddamn door.
- (DOOR CLOSES)
This fucking shit
for a lousy two Gs?
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
Oh, Anthony.
- Hi, Uncle Bobby.
- Hiya, sweetheart.
Cugin'.
I'm gonna go ahead.
What's up?
You were at South Mountain
Arena yesterday
trying to buy a gun
from that asshole in the snack shop.
Who told you that?
We know how you feel,
but you can't do this.
I can't believe you know this.
Who told you this?
Look, if my pops was
laying in there shot up
- I'd be thinking the same thing.
- But you can't go there.
- Yeah, why the fuck not?
- Listen to me,
I'm your uncle.
Junior's in federal lockup.
No one's getting to him there.
Well, it's difficult,
but not impossible.
Trust me. Your dad does not want
you to get involved.
You gotta channel that rage elsewheres.
Golden Gloves.
- What?
- Dumbbells or something.
Fuck your girlfriend more.
You little hothead here.
- (MACHINE BEEPING)
- (LABORED BREATHING)
- Hey.
- Hi.
Did you park in emergency
or in the garage?
What's going on in there?
They're on rounds or something,
Dr. Plepler and the Indian girl.
Hi, did you bring me my sweater?
Your sweater?
Man, Jesus, fuck!
All right, take it easy.
What is your problem?
My problem is I'm old enough
to sit with Dad all night,
be a messenger boy,
bring shit from the house,
but I'm too young to deal
with the larger issues?
- What are you talking about?
- Like you didn't put them up to it.
Put who up to what?
God, he was in such
a good mood this morning.
I told the nurse
that I thought he moved
his eyebrows at around 5:30.
Did she pass that along?
'Cause if not, I'm gonna be furious.
Mrs. Soprano, you're really
gonna have to recalibrate
your expectations at this point.
We can't even maintain
his blood pressure
at a level that we'd like.
Until his fever dissipates
and his white-cell count comes down,
we're a long way from home.
But he's really fighting.
Mom, he's really strong.
That is true.
Hi, Dad.
Monastery?
Oh!
I, uh...
I received these this morning.
Do I really look
that much like this guy?
To a certain extent,
all Caucasians look alike.
Look, I'm not Finnerty.
I didn't sell you
this heating equipment.
But I am kind of worried about what
I might have done.
Because, you see, yesterday...
Yes, tell us, there's no fraud
without a fairy tale.
Yesterday, I was diagnosed
with Alzheimer's.
- (LAUGHING)
- Oh, my.
And I'm in this
strange city and...
Please come inside.
I came here because I thought
you could help me
reach Finnerty.
I have his wallet.
I have his briefcase, but I'm not him.
(CHUCKLING)
Excuse the brothers
for laughing.
One day we will all die,
and then we'll be
the same as that tree.
No me, no you.
Be that as it may, we need heat.
We need to find someone who will
take responsibility.
Well, I can't do that.
Then the lawsuit proceeds.
- (MACHINE BEEPING)
- (LABORED BREATHING)
Hey, go home and I'll stay.
I just had Chinese food.
- Carmela?
- Dr. Melfi, hi. How are you?
How are you is more the point.
I'm running around crazy.
My son was supposed to get coffee,
or tell the maid to.
It's the one thing I have to have.
I got your note.
It was so thoughtful.
I've been calling the hospital
and they say that
Anthony's stabilized.
That's what they say.
If you or anyone needs anything,
to talk or to run
interference with the doctors,
- don't hesitate to call.
- I appreciate that. Thank you.
I have plenty of people
around I can talk to.
Of course.
Good luck.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
- Morning, Gab. Is he ready?
- He's eating.
We're picking up
Mrs. S. at 10:00.
I saw her Tuesday.
How's she holding up, poor thing?
Not so hotso, really.
- Coffee?
- Yeah, thanks.
You hear about the thing
in the old neighborhood?
I'm not busy enough
for all this?
Couple of guys left three
on the floor in some Colombian laundry.
Thank you.
Two guys we know, huh?
Total bloodbath.
Somebody said a million plus.
What a score.
Fuckin' A.
- Sil, Benny says you have to go.
- Yeah, all right.
- Listen, don't forget...
- (INHALING)
Oh, honey,
your asthma kicking up?
Springtime.
Pollen's out of control.
- I am so proud of you.
- Acting boss.
I hoped the day
would never come.
You've always
sold yourself short.
You know, that's not what I mean.
You know me.
All I ever wanted
was to carve out a little piece,
enjoy some grandkids.
But how many guys
could step into Tony's shoes
- and do the job you're doing?
- You think?
You have such strength
in crisis.
Benny told me
he feels honored to drive you.
You're firm about what you want without
being obnoxious about it.
Sil, have you asked
yourself what happens
if, God forbid,
Tony Soprano doesn't recover?
Listen, Gab,
I never talk to you about my work.
And?
I'm gonna tell you something
I never told anybody.
Back when Jackie was at the end,
he floated the idea
of me stepping up to the big seat.
Not Tony, me.
- Really?
- Yeah, but I thought...
- it's not for me.
- Still, you wouldn't sneeze at it.
I never saw myself
as that kind of guy.
I'm more behind the scenes...
advice, strategy.
But here you are, Sil.
The times make the man, honey,
not the other way around.
Asians flip for horror films.
Plus, there's ancillary...
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
No change with Tony.
Carmela's in goddamn pieces.
Memo... get some coffee
up to Carmela's house.
Sil, Bobby was making collections
up in Roseville again last night.
My time is limited.
Get him over and let's resolve this.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(INHALES)
- How's the skip doing?
- Same.
You forget something,
like my cut?
You believe this guy? You should've
lost some weight in that nose,
keep it out
of everybody's business.
I'm working on it.
It's these fucking
flowers right here.
Get this shit out of here.
That was Junior's
neighborhood, so now it's mine.
Keep your voice down here.
A va' Napoli...
it was Eugene's going on three years.
And Eugene was with me.
You should have never
had it to begin with,
except for the beef with
the Tastee Freez route.
Junior ruled on it,
and it wasn't right then.
This fucking guy.
Easy.
- How much we talking about?
- Three Gs a week.
Maybe that's what that miserab'
admitted to you.
- I heard five.
- You heard wrong.
What do we do here, Sil?
- Here's the thing.
- What, skip?
For the time being,
it's Bobby's.
But he's still gonna
kick up to you 20%.
- How long's for the time being?
- Yeah, Sil.
What, do you speak Norwegian?
For now. We'll see
how much is there.
Hi, everyone.
My God, you poor thing.
Hey, we just need
some Irish Spring.
Good morning.
(JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
Another one?
Know what I found out yesterday?
What's that?
Thank you.
I was diagnosed actually...
with Alzheimer's.
Man, I'm sorry to hear that.
My uncle has memory loss.
Maybe it's hereditary.
Someone's probably
studying that.
Is it possible
that I am Kevin Finnerty?
All right, I'll stop.
(POP MUSIC PLAYING)
- Sil.
- What?
You heard about this
Orange Street takedown?
The Colombians?
That you?
My guy had the tip.
Should be a nice
chunk for everybody.
Everybody?
Carmela, she gets T's cut under
the circumstances, correct?
It's your call.
I know it's my fucking call.
Yes, that is the correct thing.
Oh, ladies' room's next door.
I can reach it from here.
Grim fucking scene, that ICU.
She's one brave lady.
I was just saying, I'm gonna get
T's piece of my half to Sil for her.
- Of the thing.
- Back up there, Bluto.
Your half? I did
all the heavy lifting.
You would never have
heard about it without my information.
Big help.
It was fucking mayhem.
You said the place was empty.
Doc says I need an ultrasound on
my groin and balls.
Sil, you wanna weigh in here?
It breaks half and half.
You both kick Tony's
to me to deal with.
I'll have it for you,
Sil, the whole 80K.
Ho, ho, ho, 80K?
How's that 20% of a million?
Have a cookie, you're delirious.
It was 750, tops.
Fuck it all, Paulie.
Tommy cased that shithole.
What's with the fucking
accounting out there?
That's 100 grand apiece.
You got it?
We're looking after Carmela.
- No question.
- Of course.
Sooner than later, Paulie.
I gotta piss first.
You want half of that, too?
In a prior incarnation, I would
get my load on,
blow 20 residuals at the track.
As writers,
we are all hung up.
But we are also hung up
on our own hang-up.
We mythologize
our inner narrative.
Take for example,
"Beowulf."
Who is Grendel,
but the habit, the disease.
Ah, fresh casualties
in the battle of the blank page.
Welcome to the Writer's Guild.
Have a seat.
Take me...
my past as an addict.
(CLASS GASPS)
Get the fuck up!
Come on!
Give me that fucking fisheye.
I'm offering you a way to wipe
your fucking obligation.
Wasn't me who told you
to start gambling again.
I can't write a feature now.
I just landed a staff job.
People are seeing huge profits
with these digital horror movies.
Douchebags who never
made a film before.
That "Saw" thing,
400 grand to make,
took in 100 mil worldwide.
I'm 100% well.
I deliver this script,
I owe you nothing?
You hear this dude?
100% well.
He's a bad boy, huh,
with that lingo?
Real fucking dark character.
My idea is "Saw" meets
"Godfather 2."
Proven track record...
both genres.
Young wiseguy, assassin,
gets betrayed by his people.
They whack him,
leave his body parts
in dumpsters all around the city.
Long story short,
he is put back together by science,
or maybe it's supernatural.
And he gets fucking payback on everyone
who fucked him over,
including the cunt
he was engaged to.
She was getting porked by his boss
the night the hero was killed.
We'll have a meeting tomorrow.
We hear what you've fleshed
out before we go to script.
Bing, 2:30.
Don't make me come look for you.
(TIRES SCREECH)
An entire room full of writers,
and you did nothing!
Sir, it's family only
in the unit.
I'll be out of your hair
in a minute, sister.
I keep telling you people, I'm gonna
have to call the hospital administrator.
I wanted to let you know
there's a major package coming your way
from Paulie and Vito,
very significant.
You all have done
so much already.
We just found out insurance won't pay
for physical therapy.
Bastards.
So thank you.
You wanna come in, say hello?
Uh, sure.
- (MACHINE BEEPING)
- (LABORED BREATHING)
- Hello, Father.
- Silvio.
I have Napoleons,
but I also got fruit
for a certain party.
Either's good.
The program says sugar after meals
- tells the body you're full.
- When you married my cousin,
everybody used to say you
looked like John Travolta.
He's almost back
to his white suit.
The Bacala question.
Bobby don't have any claim.
I don't know why Sil ruled so
half-assed on you. It's not my style.
He's worried more
about taking care of Carmela
- than the actual fucking earners.
- Please.
With Johnny awaiting trial and the feds
freezing his assets,
who do you think's
keeping Ginny in butter brickle?
Lucky for me, those last years
I was in the can,
my kid brother Billy
took care of Patty and the grandkids.
Only to have that
motherfucking animal Blundetto...
Don't do it to yourself, Philly.
It's hard to forget.
I don't forget.
I forget what
we were talking about.
Me too.
What the fuck was it?
Oh, yeah, Jesus.
Carmela.
The thing is...
You want coffee, coz?
If you're already making it.
Hot water and lemon, hon.
Honestly...
how can I short Carmela?
Maybe I'm not following you.
I'm as supportive as the next guy,
but there's a point.
And what if Tony takes a turn
for the worse?
I'm gonna hand her $100,000,
and he dies the next day?
Be money down the drain.
It's tempting,
but you can't think that way.
You all set now?
Yeah, I'm living it up here.
You still stewing
about that money?
Spend some, you'll get over it.
I'll never get over it.
Certain people...
let me tell you.
Oh, come on, not Sil again.
Carmela.
He's a fucking vegetable.
But I still gotta pay
tribute to the princess of Little Italy.
- The boss' wife. What are you gonna do?
- Fuck her.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
I'm on my way in now.
Yeah, good, and you might want to take
care of that thing we talked about.
Which thing?
That big piece of pie
you were bringing to the hospital
She's expecting you,
so make it happen.
What are you worried about?
I think I know who
I'm fucking dealing with here.
I resent that.
You have a problem
taking orders from me?
Keep your shirt on.
It's done.
(INHALES)
Don't get in bed with him again.
You dislodged his drains.
That was my daughter.
And I can't help but think
that physical affection means something.
They refrigerate
this place, huh?
There you go.
What are you still
doing out there?
I got involved in a lawsuit.
- A lawsuit?
- Could create problems later.
What kind of lawsuit?
Hello.
- Also...
- What?
I had an accident.
I fell down some stairs.
Oh, my God!
The doctor said...
What did he say?
"Mild concussion," he said.
Told me I'd be okay.
That's it.
I'm coming out there.
My mother's over here anyway.
She can stay with the kids.
No, don't do that.
Are you telling me everything?
- (MACHINE BEEPING)
- (LABORED BREATHING)
JT, I want to introduce you
to Carmine Lupertazzi
my co-executive
producer on the project.
Nice to finally meet. I heard tidbits
of what Chris has got in mind...
the genre and so forth.
But, JT, I gotta warn you,
I'm very hands-on.
I learned that the hard way.
I wanna welcome all
of you to the first meeting
of possible investors
on this project.
Some of you know I've had nine pictures
under my subspecies,
four in the "South Beach
Strumpet" series alone,
each with 30,000-plus
DVDs in print.
That being said, I usually find it
helpful at this stage
to include my
prospective partners
and get your inputs
or notes as we call them.
JT, you're on.
Well...
we've been working on a new
kind of slasher film.
It takes place
in the world of...
you know...
um, the mafia.
It's about a wiseguy with a big mouth
and bigger dreams.
Anyway, they call him
"The Butcher."
- No, they don't.
- Why the fuck not?
Need I remind you
of a certain butcher out of A.C?
Right.
Not "Butcher."
Go on, JT.
So, right.
He's kind of
outshining his boss.
So the guy has him clipped,
but he's still alive
when they cut him up.
He's gonna feel
that the next day.
- Right. So at the dump,
- (ALL LAUGH)
his body reassembles itself,
all except for
a hand that got crushed.
So he ties a cleaver
onto the stump
and he goes out
to get revenge on everyone,
especially the boss, which
is a pretty solid role.
Right now it's called
"Pork Store Killer."
But I'm thinking...
just...
"Cleaver."
I'm confused.
You said he's dead.
How's he evening up with anybody?
He's a ghost?
As I understood,
a zombie of sorts.
Great title, by the way.
But if they jointed him,
he's not gonna end up
all in the same dump.
- And how's that a slasher film?
- What are you talking about?
A slasher.
A couple of kids naked in a lake.
Certified maniac
on the loose, not a ghost.
Actually, the maniac is almost always
a supernatural force.
Freddy, Jason, Michael Myers
from "Halloween."
Get the fuck out.
Easy, Sil, easy.
He's making a point.
Michael Myers is
an escaped mental patient.
Jason and Freddy,
different kind of movie.
Well, that's the kind
we're doing here.
"Saw," "The Ring"...they made millions.
And that's not even including
"The Godfather" angle,
which we got here.
What if...
they disposed him at stops
that happened
to be along the same route?
Then he would all end up
in the same dump.
But he's a ghost?
I don't know.
"Ghostbusters"...another fucking
money machine.
Cavalry's here.
I brought some cannelloni.
Again.
It's got bechamel on it,
so five, six hours
out of the fridge, tops.
Thank you.
- Hey.
- Howdy.
Look at her.
That word "plucky,"
is that what it means?
Only, when do I get to spend
some face time with the skip?
Hospital gets ticked off.
We'll try to sneak you.
...in this mob family
domestic shooting,
which some observers note carries
the echoes of the death of soul great
Marvin Gaye.
As 20-year-old Anthony
Soprano Jr. himself
told our Amy Kean,
"Growing up Soprano,
it's just plain weird."
You just wanna bite it!
Big Lots! What's your
deal today?
Carmela?
I swear to God,
I'm gonna fucking kill you!
- What the fuck?
- You made a fool of yourself
and our family on national
fucking television?
I didn't even say that shit.
They totally misquoted me.
- Holy shit.
- Well, of course they did.
That's what they do, which is why I
and everybody else
told you, "Don't talk
to the press!"
You're the one
who looked like a total asshole.
Dragging me around like
I was five years old.
You are a cross to bear.
That's all you are.
To your father, to me,
to everybody.
Fuck this.
Fuck it all!
Jesus, Mel, the hell's
wrong with you?
What's wrong with me?
Mom.
It had to happen.
She's fried.
(CRYING)
You have any extra compensation
for what you've been
going through?
Nah, part of the job.
Like they say,
with great power comes
great responsibility.
You know, Vito called me
"skip" the other day.
Really?
Slip of the tongue, no doubt,
but I noticed he didn't correct himself.
See?
If it did become permanent,
- your compensation might be...
- Don't go there.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Hi, Gab.
I need Sil for a second.
Can you keep it short?
He's pretty beat.
(SIL COUGHS)
This better be important, Bobby.
Got a new baby and two kids
in private school.
This arrangement
with Vito is killing me.
It's 9:30 at night.
Bobby, I don't remember
what the fuck it was.
Roseville, this temporary shit.
I need an answer already.
I'm going out of my fucking mind here.
I'm liable to do
something drastic.
Calm the fuck down.
Let me think.
- Mornings are better.
- (WHEEZES)
I'll come up with a solution.
I don't want you
to worry about it.
(COUGHS)
I must have sounded odd
at the supermarket the other day.
See, you're Tony's therapist.
Whether it's appropriate...
How can I help you?
It's about my son.
Both kids, really.
The situation with the shooting.
I'm very worried about them.
Sure.
It's a very serious problem,
you know, guns in the home.
It's a societal concern.
Obviously, we learned
our lesson too late.
I immediately removed
all the firearms from the house
after the goings-on
at Tony's uncle's.
Anyway, last night,
I was shrieking
at my son,
and I said something very cruel.
And especially since
he's been trying so hard...
How are you doing?
You know,
I'm frazzled certainly,
but I am more
worried about them.
They're not kids anymore.
When they were young,
there were certain things
we could tell them about Tony's life.
You know, lies.
We'll just call them what they were.
- But now...
- So the issue isn't just
guns in the home.
Honestly, I think about my son
in front of those cameras,
having to vouch for all this.
My daughter and her friends.
They have to face
all these years of facading.
They do or you do?
The minute I met Tony,
I knew who that guy was.
On my second date, he brought me
and my mother each a dozen roses
and my father
a $200 power drill.
Not the typical story
of young love.
And I don't know
if I loved him in spite of it...
or because of it.
My parents weren't like that.
And I knew, whether
consciously or not,
I knew that behind
that power drill,
there was probably
some guy with a broken arm,
you know, or worse.
And you coped with that, how?
I'd go to my priest,
and I would cry,
and say how bad I felt
about how my husband made his money,
but that was bullshit.
Because there are far bigger crooks
than my husband.
But the kids...
they don't decide
who they're born to.
So now what?
Yeah, that's just it.
Now what?
It's all out in the open now,
the whole thing.
And them, they're not
in grade school anymore.
They become...
the longer they stay with us...
Complicit.
Oh, God.
Putting aside the moral
and legal issues,
clarity can't be a bad thing.
Yes.
Tony's second night
in the coma, I told him I loved him.
When was the last time
I said that?
Are you afraid you aren't
going to feel that way
when he wakes up?
Anthony tells me
things have been...
better between you.
Come here, honey.
It's okay, honey.
You're gonna be okay.
I can't breathe.
- It's all right.
- Come here, honey.
Can't breathe.
It's okay, honey.
You're gonna be okay.
- What's going on?
- Would you move your car, please, sir?
Sil, I didn't hear from you.
Sil's on the canvas now.
Fucking 100% disaster.
Point is, Tony goes,
let's face it,
somebody's gonna have to
step into the breach.
I'm a young man.
Now without the weight,
I'm a healthy man
with longevity.
I hear Sil
is at St. Barnabas.
My God, what is
happening to us around here?
Sil's gonna be fine.
You have enough worries.
Listen, sweetheart,
you're expecting something,
and I can't get into specifics,
and Tony wouldn't want me to,
but there are certain people looking
over our shoulders right now.
It's okay, Vito.
I'm not expecting anything.
Money's not an issue.
Like you said, I got bigger worries,
like this son of mine.
You gotta trust me on this, hon.
Suspicions get raised if we were
to move it to you at this moment.
I got this.
Your ma says now's our moment.
The main thing,
when people come to sit with dad,
the doctors want positive talk.
- It helps in his recovery.
- Got it.
Oof, Madonn' he looks terrible.
Uncle Paulie,
you can't say stuff like that.
You have to stay positive.
Yeah, it's just
nothing prepares you for that.
Uncle Paulie!
Only one person
at a time, please.
She's a ballbuster.
Finn's on his way up.
I'll be back in a few minutes, okay?
Remember, stay positive.
I gotta wear a jock,
the doc says.
Keep the testes elevated.
Of course, it could
be a lot worse, right?
(SLOW BEEPING)
They gave me
an ultrasound, no rupture.
I mean, the good thing is
I hurt it doing a major
piece of business.
I saw a little action,
and the next thing,
I was at the urologist.
(BEEPING INCREASES)
Fucking guy tells
me I can't expect the same things
from my body no more.
I tell you, T,
first the eyes, then the teeth.
Next you find out
you can't take pissing for granted.
Some joke, huh?
When I was in the service,
I won the chin-ups cup
three weeks in a row.
Fucking beautiful
definition, too.
Guy asked me to model
for the boxing poster.
He was half a fag,
but I was flattered just the same.
Now look at this.
Fucking wrinkles like
an old lady's cunt.
You don't think it's gonna happen
to you, but I'm feeling it, Tony.
Phineas Fogg back in town.
He forgets
all the little people.
Hey, Vito,
how's Mr. Soprano doing?
Let's hope he
pulls through, huh?
Hi.
So glad you're here.
I'm gonna let
you two lovebirds be.
That... don't worry about him.
He's harmless.
That fucking agita, T.
I mean, do I blame
myself for this life?
The shit that happens,
like with Puss.
Standup one day,
FBI rat fuck the next.
I felt it here, T.
- I felt it right here.
- Will you please shut up in there?
I'm sorry.
Yes, the Inn at the Oaks.
(TV BLASTING)
Left on Jamboree Boulevard?
Out towards the beacon.
What is that beacon anyway?
Oh. God damn it!
Shut up!
Shut up in there!
So I said to Ma...
(ALARM SOUNDING)
What the fuck?
Dr. Budraja,
stat to room 3.
Nurse, don't leave!
Help!
- Out of the way, sir.
- Oh, my God! What's happening?
Soprano, V-tach on the monitor.
- Thready pulse.
- Take his pressure. Get a board ready.
- 80 palp.
- All right, let's bag him.
Oh, my God, is he dying?
Where's my mom?
I don't know what's happening.
- (ALARM SOUNDING)
- One, two, three.
Oh, my God!
Still V-tach at 210.
150 mg of amiodaraone.
Grab the paddles.
Clear the room.
Cardiovert at 100.
- Dad!
- Stand back.
- Daddy!
- All clear.
Clear.
- 200.
- Stand back.
- All clear.
- Clear.
(ZAPS)
(THUNDER CRASHES)
(FESTIVE MUSIC PLAYING)
Excuse me.
Is this the Finnerty reunion?
Hello there.
They're waiting for you.
- Me?
- Of course.
Has Kevin Finnerty arrived?
We don't talk like that here.
What do you mean?
Your family's inside.
- What family?
- They're here to welcome you.
I don't understand.
- You're going home.
- I am?
Everyone's in there.
- You can't bring business in there.
- Daddy.
I lost my real briefcase.
My whole life was in it.
Don't go, Daddy.
(WIND HOWLING)
- What is that?
- Briefcases aren't allowed.
- No, the voice.
- Please, let me take that from you.
- Looks like it weighs a ton.
- I don't want to.
Well, you need to.
You need to let go.
We love you, Daddy.
Don't leave us.
(APPLAUSE)
For some reason...
I'm scared.
Well, there's nothing
to be scared of.
You can let it go.
Just come say hello.
All right.
(MAN LAUGHS)
Daddy!
(THUNDER CRASHES)
(FLAT-LINING)
Please don't leave us,
Daddy. We love you.
Dad?
His eyes are open.
Daddy, look at me right here.
All right, normal sinus rhythm.
- Pulse and pressure?
- Good.
Oh my God!
Thank God. Thank God.
Hang an amiodaraone drip
and send off a set
of electrolytes now.
Dad, look, here you are.
So I'm holding his hand,
and all of a sudden
the machines go bullshit.
You told us, for Christ's sake.
Those fucking doctors,
it's their fault.
Skip's gonna make it.
He's conscious.
Oh, thank God!
(DOORBELL RINGS)
I got it, honey.
Fuck took you so long?
I had to get it
together, didn't I?
We gotta get
that cut to her now.
Easy, that's
a fucking guilty move.
Tony's conscious.
You capisce?
Everybody and his
mother was in there talking to him
when he was in that coma.
Carmela.
Who knows what
the fuck they said?
Maybe he's expecting that money.
Jesus Christ.
He can't talk yet because of the tube
that was in his throat.
Maybe we should consider
ourselves lucky there.
But we are very happy,
aren't we?
Anthony, you had us so worried.
I haven't been to church that much
since I quit playing bingo.
What, honey?
I'm dead, right?
No, no, you're in the hospital
with all of us.
In Newark.
Mr. Soprano,
how are you today?
I'm Dr. Vahapsideh.
I'm a neurologist.
How's he doing, sweetheart?
I don't know if we're out of the woods
yet, but he's hanging in.
He just passed his
first simple mental acuity test, so...
Your strength,
that was the difference.
Oh, a little something from us.
Help defray medical costs,
rehabilitation.
Jesus, I don't know what to say.
This is what we do, honey.
I'd want the same for my Marie.
Or my ma.
We're here if you need anything.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
Great fucking news, T.
See you're up and around.
Best.
"Sometimes I go about
in pity for myself,
and all the while,
a great wind carries me
across the sky.
Ojibwe saying."
Indians, right?
Who put this up?
Listen, T, something I wanted
to talk to you about.
I'm gonna take another run
at the movie business.
I know you haven't
liked that in the past,
but I'm going about it
in a whole different way.
In fact, I'm hoping
you'll become an investor
when you feel a little better,
and I can explain what we're doing.
It's pretty exciting.
We'll own the neg.
That's what they call it.
It means negative.
I'm holding a large
ownership position
open for you.
I hope you approve.
Actually, frankly...
all due respect,
I think you owe me this,
as I came to you about Adriana.
You've got him up?
I know how it looks, but he should
be upright as much as possible.
- I'm gonna leave you two alone.
- Thanks for everything.
Okay.
I don't know how you do it.
That's gotta feel good, huh?
The simple things.
(OLDIES MUSIC PLAYING)