(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
(GASPS SOFTLY)
(SIGHS)
(ENGINE REVVING)
Stupid thing.
The pressure is shot.
Can you live with regular
instead of espresso?
Never mind, sweetie.
Thanks anyway.
T, hey. Sorry for the ambush.
I brung up your paper.
I am meeting the new realtor.
Yeah? Good luck.
Got a call from Sergeant Danny
over in Newark P.D.
- Yeah? And?
- (LAWN MOWER BUZZING)
T? The feds are doing some digging
over by Branford Avenue.
Willie Overall, the bookie?
Labor Day, 1982?
(JACKHAMMER POUNDING)
Danny says he hears
it's Larry Barese been talking.
Lot of work
for a dead fucking bookie.
Come on, kid. Do it.
You made your bones
with that prick, eh?
Yeah.
Old Zepupin's house.
You were shaky a little,
but you did good.
I remember telling your old man.
Twenty-five years, T.
Possible there's nothing left.
There'll be bones, teeth.
What are we gonna do?
We're gonna pack
our toothbrushes.
Call you in a few days
on the alternate cell.
Any emergencies, call Sil or Bobby.
And if you need more cash, call me.
I know the drill, Tony.
You know, it's not like
I won a trip to Paris.
You have everything? Your razor?
Yeah. Yeah, I think so. I...
I can buy whatever I need.
You make sure you wear sunblock?
It's nothing. A little gambling charge,
that's all. It's gonna be fine.
It's just, you know,
better safe than sorry.
I know, it's just...
This is what life is still like...
...at our age?
My tomatoes are just coming in.
(VOICES CHATTERING)
- It's good to see you.
- Yeah.
You seem good, Junior, I gotta say.
Fuck does that mean?
I'm fucking incarcerated, for chrissake.
The medicine, the Aricept,
it agrees with you.
You're not repeating yourself so much.
You gotta get me out of here.
The smell alone in this fucking place.
- What do you hear from my nephew?
- Tony?
They sent me a card for my birthday.
I'm still waiting for an apology. Tell him.
All right.
Which one of youse gonna tell him?
We'll figure it out, Junior.
If you made an appointment...
...with an outside dentist...
...that might do the trick.
What trick?
We'll meet you there
and sneak you off in our car.
Dinner, 10 minutes.
So, what do you think, Junior?
Enchiladas tonight.
(QUIETLY)
Here's the electricians's union.
(SPEAKING ITALIAN)
Don't let them take my plate, kid.
(WHISPERING)
Make sure there's enough
so everybody can buy in.
- Sixty dollars.
- For sodas and fucking candy?
Caffeinated sodas and sugar.
You know some of them
ain't allowed this shit.
Gets them all riled.
I could lose my job.
Fucking stick-up artist.
I gave you my watch.
Don't count my money, nigga.
You're making 500 percent
off these motherfuckers.
You're good till lights out.
I'll steer people away from the door.
All right. No-limit five-card stud.
Forty-dollar buy-in to the house.
The white buttons are 5 bucks.
The red buttons are 10.
(LAUGHING)
Red Buttons.
What'd you say?
Today, we got Coca-Colas...
Fuck was I just saying?
- The soda, Junior.
- What soda?
Right, the Coke.
The real kind, not the diet shit.
Ice-cold, five buttons.
Plus, we got Snickers,
Kit Kats and Sprees, also five.
I'll take some Sprees.
Okay, ante up.
(ENGINE ROARING)
This is nice, huh?
A little road trip, just you and me.
All things considered, of course.
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah, just like the old days.
Willie-fucking-Overall...
...after all these years.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah.
You remember driving around with that
prick in the trunk looking for a spot?
(BOTH LAUGH)
What was it, like a week
before A.J. was born, right?
No, Meadow.
- Now she's gonna be a doctor.
- Yeah.
Remember we took you
to Luger's after?
Me, Puss, Ralphie.
Chevy Chase.
Fuck ever happened to him?
Let me ask you something.
You mentioned Ralph before.
A few years ago,
he had a beef with Johnny Sack.
He made a crack about Ginny...
...huge fucking mole on her ass
or some shit.
Yeah?
Who the fuck would tell Johnny
about that joke?
How should I know?
Nine of clubs.
You know, I try to be cooperative,
but it's that message, over and over.
Walter, what do you got?
Flush.
No, you don't. George?
- What?
- Thought I had it.
George, what do you got?
Your hand.
He's got Alzheimer's.
Help him, for chrissake.
Pair of jacks.
Guy comes home
with a bouquet of flowers for his wife.
"I guess I'll have
to spread my legs now," she says.
"Why?" he asks.
"Don't you have a vase?"
(ALL LAUGHING)
- (SOBBING)
- (KNOCK ON DOOR)
High rollers only.
Keep walking, professor.
I'm not here to gamble.
I'm looking for Keith.
Keith's busy. Take a hike.
We had a chess match, Keith.
The pride of Rutgers.
Slits his wrists in the faculty lounge...
...after he stabbed the dean.
(ALL LAUGHING)
At least some of us
know when we need help.
Get the fuck out of here, you fuck...
(MAN CONTINUES SOBBING)
What did the blind man say
when he passed the fish market?
(TEARFULLY)
I don't know.
"Good morning, ladies."
- (MAN BAWLING)
- (ALL LAUGHING)
What's going on, guys?
- They're gambling, Warren.
- Relax, Brian.
What did we say about this?
- What? It's a friendly game.
- Corrado, it's too stressful.
- Look at him.
- He's not even playing.
Come on, guys. Let's wrap it up.
I saw your girl today at pet therapy.
How does she keep her coat so shiny?
(LAUGHING)
They can be unexpected,
frightening events.
But here,
at beautiful Crater Lake National Park...
...they're just
part of the scenery.
(KNOCKS)
Crater Lake is located
high in the Cascades...
...of south-central Oregon,
about 250 miles south of Portland...
I brought you your tea.
You did a good job tonight, kid.
Here's your taste.
- That's all right.
- (TV AUDIO PLAYS)
Take it. You earned it.
(TV OFF)
Time once, I was a kid.
You know, my old man
was a stonemason.
He took me to work...
...a job building a wall
around some rich lady's garden.
She comes home.
I help carry her groceries.
She goes to give me a quarter...
...which was a lot in those days,
but I say no.
She goes in. No sooner
does she close the door, when:
My old man gives me a belt
right across the mouth.
"What are you, millionaire?
You no need money?
You no like eat?"
Even still, he was right.
He made me walk home that night.
Eleven fucking miles from Essex Fells
back to Newark.
I'm from Essex Fells.
- A rich kid, huh?
- (KNOCKS)
Warren said
I should get my buttons back...
...on account of we weren't
supposed to gamble.
Tell Warren he can fuck himself.
Got a problem with that,
tell him to come see me.
Can I get a Kit Kat at least?
Do you believe this guy?
Get the fuck out of here.
Once in third grade...
...I got a 96 on my spelling test.
Highest mark in the class.
I was so proud.
I brought it home to show my dad.
"What happened
to the other four points?" he says.
(SNIFFS)
Fuck you! Fuck you!
UZ-FM, Fredericksburg.
Your home for classic rock...
...96.9.
Paulie, we should stop.
- Fuck are we?
- Virginia.
You remember that place...
The dive with the fucking
massage beds?
It was in Culpeper, Virginia.
The Havenaire.
(LAUGHING)
We met
those 16-year-old hillbilly whores...
...near the taxi stand.
Yeah.
- YEAH.
- (CHUCKLING)
You want the old days,
let's go there.
We'll get a room,
bucket of ice from the machine...
...bottle of Scotch,
order up a couple steaks.
Now you're fucking talking.
Excuse me. This place, is it new?
I think maybe, I don't know.
There was a motel
on this spot, though, right?
- The Havenaire?
- I don't know.
Fucking guy.
(SNORTS)
(EASY LISTENING
MUSIC PLAYING)
Mr. Spears, you're all set.
Two king rooms, one night,
checking out tomorrow.
From 6 to 10, we offer
a complimentary buffet breakfast...
...in the courtesy room off the lobby.
Sign there, please.
Can you have room service send up
two fifths of Glenlivet?
I apologize, sir,
we don't serve bottles.
There is a minibar
in the room, however.
- All right, a couple steaks.
- With baked potatoes.
Wraps and salads only after 11.
Buckingham's is still open, though.
You could get some nachos.
(SMOOTH JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
Your dad, boy.
Him and me made this trip
a thousand times...
...back in the '60s.
He had a piece
of that dog track, right?
Among other things.
(CHUCKLES)
This one time, my first trip ever...
...we're going through Georgia.
He's got a '59 Eldorado with the fins.
The Biarritz. He used to let me steer.
I'm like 20 at the time. I'm a kid.
Never been five miles out of Newark.
Anyway, I'm driving,
we get pulled over.
State trooper with the hat,
fucking sunglasses.
- I got no driver's license.
- (LAUGHS)
Of course not.
I'm shitting a brick.
This is the deep fucking South
we're in...
...and we're Italian.
I turn to your dad,
"What do I tell this prick?"
"Relax," he says.
"Tell him your cousin's on the job."
He gives me
a Southern-sounding name.
The guy comes over.
"Oh, my cousin's a state trooper too,"
I tell him.
"Maybe you know him."
"What's his name?"
"Barney Fife."
(LAUGHING)
The prick gives me a shot,
I don't know what the fuck hit me.
Your dad's fucking pissing himself.
I mean, I never watch TV.
How the fuck do I know, right?
So, what happened?
Your dad had to duke the guy
100 fucking dollars.
Probably a month's salary
in those days.
(LAUGHS) You know, I remember
you around that time.
When I was bad,
my dad threatened me...
...he was gonna get Uncle Paulie
to come get me.
(LAUGHING)
Fucking Johnny boy, eh?
He loved you, my friend.
I remember the night
you were born.
Only time I ever saw him cry.
It's funny, you know...
...I never knew where
I stood with him.
Like he didn't believe in me
or something.
Fucking kidding?
He trusted you enough to give you
the Willie Overall thing.
And you were what, 24?
- Twenty-two.
- So there you go, then.
(CHUCKLES)
I tell the guy, I said, "Listen,
I don't mind paying for the tailpipe...
...but that fucking muffler's
still under warranty."
- All set?
- Yeah.
- Nice talking to you.
- Yeah, you too.
- Enjoy Miami.
- (PAULIE CHUCKLES)
- What the fuck is wrong with you?
- What?
You tell some fucking goober
your life story?
We're supposed to be laying low.
I'm gonna grab some Danish
for the road.
- You have shit on your pants, Don.
- Please be patient with him.
Yes, ma'am.
Visiting day at the zoo.
- Don't feed the cetriolo.
- (LAUGHS)
- Ma.
- How was church?
It was fine. It was good.
You remember Mr. Soprano?
Corrado, please. Hello, my dear.
- How are you today?
- I'd complain, but who'd listen?
They have me on a new medication.
It makes me salivate.
I'll leave you two to visit.
I have some letters to answer.
- He's a good boy, this one.
- Thank you.
I have this new medication
they put me on. Makes me salivate.
How are you feeling?
- Fine.
- Maybe you can clear something up.
Dr. Mandl says you've been acting
aggressively toward other patients?
First of all,
that is total fucking bullshit.
- Carter...
- Secondly, why not lead off with that?
What are you talking about?
Instead of pretending to give a shit
how I feel.
Now, apparently,
you are becoming a bully.
Dr. Mandl feels you're modeling
your actions on the wrong people.
- Really? Like who?
- You know who. That gangster.
You of all people should not believe
what you read in the paper.
All that crap they wrote about Daddy.
That was The Wall Street Journal.
- It was entirely different.
- It's never enough, is it?
At MIT, you told me,
"Get out and make friends."
Now I finally do learn
to assert myself a little...
...suddenly that's a negative.
- (PAULIE GRUNTS)
- Checking in. Spears.
(SEAGULLS CAWING)
(PHONE RINGING)
- Sil.
- I'll get us settled in.
- Hey.
- It's not good.
Feds found a body.
Skeleton. They tentatively ID'd it
as the guy.
- Fuck.
- Try and relax, huh?
How's Paulie holding up?
Jaws are holding up fine.
He won't shut the fuck up.
- That's too bad.
- What's he gotta worry about anyway?
Scenario like this...
...the feds ain't interested in him,
believe me.
Look, I love the guy. It's just...
- You know how he is.
- Believe me, I hear you.
What else? Let me think.
I looked in on Carm and she's okay.
All right, thanks.
Call me if you hear anything.
(MEN CHATTERING)
Use your hat.
(CHUCKLING)
- And hope to hear from you soon.
- (KEYS TAPPING)
Sincerely... No.
Respectfully, Corrado Soprano.
Read it back.
"Dear Vice President Cheney...
...as a powerful man all too familiar
with accidental gunplay...
...I am writing in the hope that you will
intervene in my case.
Like yourself, I was involved
in an unfortunate incident...
...when a gun I was handling misfired."
(KNOCKS)
- (DOOR OPENS)
- Head up, yo. I was you...
...I'd lay off the card games a while.
Fuck's the matter?
The professor snitched you out
to Dr. Mandl.
What do you do with those, Jameel?
Autographed pictures of the man
who capped Tony Soprano?
Shit, them motherfuckers
go right on eBay.
Come on now, sign.
That was our deal.
You wanna keep getting them sodas?
Sick fucking world.
(MARIACHI MUSIC PLAYING)
For you.
I got one for Cristina and Gia too.
Thanks.
Where's the DVD?
That never occurred to me.
I'll have Sil FedEx you one.
Long as you're here...
Listen, before the girls
get here.
Remember that Cuban guy I was telling
you about? He knocks over trucks.
Last load was American Standard...
...sinks, toilets, tubs.
No shit? All right, let's talk.
I'll give you his number, you call him.
Now, check this out.
You're not gonna believe what I found
when we moved into the new house.
Holy fucking shit.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Mickey Pinto took that in 1963.
Look at that hair.
Handsome fucking guy, eh?
That wristband, the leather thing.
I remember getting one just like it,
me and all my friends.
Wanted to be a tough guy
just like him.
That big one, that's your Uncle Junior...
...and your old man in front of Satriale's.
(CHUCKLES)
- There he is.
- It's the Biarritz.
We were just talking about that.
Tell you what,
I'll have my daughter...
...scan them into the computer
so I can get a couple of copies for you.
(PHONE RINGING)
Oh, that's my wife. I gotta take this.
No, stay. It's all right, come on.
I gotta empty my bag anyway.
Hey, honey, sweetie, how's everything?
- Gia says, "Hi," guys.
- Hello, Gia.
(SPEAKS ITALIAN)
He pisses in a bag now?
Jesus Christ, fucking kill me now.
Supporting them with
a huge warehouse covering 28 acres.
Stuffed to the rafters
with over 3000 products...
...you can order
at rock-bottom prices...
...and sell for profits
of up to 300 percent and more.
It's easy to wish for a better life...
(PHONE RINGING)
Just pick up the phone
and call this toll-free number...
- Hello.
- Junior, it's Pat.
You put any thought to our plan?
- What plan?
- The dentist. You know, like we said.
- Who is this?
- It's Pat.
The dentist, remember?
You were gonna make an appointment.
You sneak me off...
...where would I lam it?
A safe house, I don't know.
The time's not right.
I'm being watched. Call back later.
Because I'm headed
back to Sarasota soon.
(CLICKS, DIAL TONE HUMMING)
Free to get started.
They give you
plenty of ideas and support.
The quality of the products
is even better...
...than what you see
in the catalogs.
I wanted something
where I was my own boss...
Back in the day, '70s, fucking '80s...
...you didn't make a move
in north Jersey...
...without this one up your ass.
(GIGGLING)
I wasn't even born yet.
Please. Wanna talk
about stand-up guys?
Sorry, Beans.
Hey, Carlo, can we get
some more champagne, please?
Hey, remember that yokel at the feast,
mouthing off to your cousin?
This maniac threw a vat of hot oil...
...right from the zeppole stand
on this prick.
(GIGGLING)
Oh, my God.
Little powdered sugar,
he would've been done.
(LAUGHING)
And Ton, remember when we all rented
that house down the shore?
- With the bedbugs?
- Summer of '78.
Carlo, Silvio, Frankie Napoli...
Place up the beach.
Sonny Spits in the Bronx rented it?
That's where that hippie kid
mysteriously drowned during that party.
(CHUCKLES)
Hey, Ton.
- You okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
You sure, T?
You're being kind of quiet.
That's because...
..."remember when"
is the lowest form of conversation.
I told Tommy DeLeo
you're the boss now.
This fucking DeLeo Construction
has always been a problem.
Tell him I personally am upset.
- Nice gravy, huh?
- Yeah.
Anyway, your taste.
How's Patricia? You mind?
Go ahead.
Now, I'll start by making
a mountain fold on each corner.
Folding the corners
into the center of the paper...
Touché, Captain Blood.
(GIGGLES)
Checkers, the thinking-man's game.
Looking for a smack in the mouth?
Corrado?
Language, please.
- What do you want?
- If you'd move...
...perhaps I could reach the chess set.
If I don't, what the fuck
you gonna do?
- You don't intimidate me.
- Corrado.
You're lucky she's here,
you little prick.
Naturally. You're only tough when
there's an authority figure nearby...
...so things don't go too far.
Oh, how the mighty have fall...
- Corrado!
- (GLASS SHATTERS)
- (WHISTLE SCREECHING)
- (SHOUTING)
- (SCREAMING)
- (ALARM BEEPING)
Get him! Get him!
- (SCREAMING)
- How do you like that, huh?
Fucking smart guy.
How do you like that?
God, no.
I'm gonna kill this prick.
Would you describe
Mr. Soprano as the aggressor?
Is he generally a troublemaker?
(LAUGHS)
No, he cool.
You just gotta know
how to talk to him, is all.
That's a lovely watch you're wearing.
Is that vintage?
Bulova, yeah. Flea market.
Must have been quite expensive.
Why am I the only caregiver
being interrogated here?
It wouldn't happen to be because
of the color of my skin, now would it?
Thank you for your cooperation.
You can go.
I'm gonna write a change order
for Soprano's meds.
Yeah, I need a bridge loan.
If you could.
- Two hundred K.
- Done.
What can I tell you? I've been mush.
It happens.
I lost the 1:00 game
by a field goal.
It was a "pick them."
Then I'm chasing the money...
...I picked the 49ers minus two...
Fuck it.
You don't wanna hear this.
It's been this way
the last couple months, though.
- (DOORBELL RINGS)
- Listen, this too shall pass.
- Thanks, tatteleh.
- Anytime.
All right.
(TONY GRUNTING)
Is this a nonsmoking room?
Go ahead.
(LAUGHING)
- Dinner was fun the other night.
- Yeah.
How do you know Peter?
Who Peter?
Beansie?
He's an old friend...
...from the neighborhood.
So the other guy, the one with...
White hair thingies.
What's his name again?
- Paulie.
- Right.
What is he,
like, your best friend?
- He say that?
- I just figured.
The way he was talking.
Honestly, I thought
he was your dad at first.
There was a time
when I wished he was.
He used to work for my dad.
I know, he told me.
(SNORING)
Corrado? Corrado?
It's time for group.
It's these new pills
last couple of days.
I got no pep.
Oh, that'll change.
There's a slight adjustment period.
But I'm sleeping all the time now.
I can't focus.
Give it some time.
You'll feel a lot better.
And your memory will improve too.
You know that's bullshit, right?
They're trying to numb you out...
...because of what you did
to the professor.
Where the fuck is this guy?
West on 84, Beans said, right?
(CAR APPROACHES)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
There.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
What the fuck is this?
Goddamn it.
Who's Ramon?
- Waiting long?
- Everybody come tonight except Charo?
All right, hold on. Hold on, hold on.
I'm Tony, this is Paulie.
This is Esteban
and the rest of the guys.
We stepped away from a wedding.
Our friend in the wheelchair
says you get regular access to goods.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Okay.
I got a trailer full of power tools...
...coming in later on this month.
Factory-sealed Black & Deckers
and Makitas.
I can get for you
50 cents on the dollar.
Sixty grand.
Well, 55 would work,
but that includes shipping to Jersey.
We look like fucking UPS?
Look, you send the truck up north,
we send it back loaded.
I got a line on air mattresses, pool toys.
And I can round the load out
with Kérastase.
It's a French shampoo.
Twenty dollars a bottle, retail.
Now, you get 5 percent after sale
but that's gonna involve a little trust.
All right.
We're looking
for a long-term relationship.
- We'll be calling.
- All right.
You okay, tío?
(TONY CHUCKLES)
(KNOCKS)
Corrado, how you doing today?
I'm dying a slow death,
that's how I'm doing.
Just take your meds, yo.
Real fucking Nazi now, huh?
- Stop fucking pushing!
- I wasn't!
Yo, stop bumping dickheads out there.
(ITZHAK CRYING)
You should have seen him out there.
The fuck can handle himself.
He's got the cazzi
of a 20-year-old.
He's my friend, but Jesus,
what a fucking chiacchierone.
(LAUGHING)
He tells me, "Don't say nothing
to nobody. He's got prostate."
I say, "Sure." He tells everybody.
He was always like that.
He was Gary-fucking-Cooper.
You forget.
One time, I fell asleep
while he was on the phone.
I wake up 20 minutes later...
...and he was still going.
I gotta say...
It concerns me. Lately.
Come on, huh?
Hey, people live alone,
they get like that. It's sad.
I'm leaving for my card game.
Are you two okay?
- Dinner was great.
- Anytime, you know that.
Thank you.
That's a great girl you got there.
The way she stood by you.
Now, you see,
that's what Paulie doesn't got.
Now, I'm speaking to your point.
He's got no wife.
He's got no kids.
He's got no steady income stream.
Except for Barone,
which is coming to an end.
I told him,
"If you can't show legit income...
...you're vulnerable to the feds."
He don't do shit about it.
I think you're worrying
for nothing, Tony.
Things are going great.
Finally.
Maybe I'm just...
...waiting for the other shoe to drop.
All I know is...
...Paulie Gualtieri is a stand-up guy.
Has he ever
really been put the test?
You know,
he had this painting of me in his house.
I was all dressed up
like a fucking general.
(LAUGHS)
I heard about that.
Yeah, it pissed me off.
I thought it was a fucking joke.
- But I don't think it was.
- He loves you, Ton.
You're all he's got.
You, the guys and his image.
I love him too.
You always did.
(WHISTLING)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
- Hey, Sil.
- I'm here with Bobby.
- He just got a call from Jenna.
- Who?
Karen's sister.
Works in the courthouse.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
- And?
- Are you sitting down?
Just fucking tell me.
Jackie Aprile.
- What?
- You heard me.
Larry told them
J.A. was totally responsible...
...for the death of a certain
African-American person.
- He covered your ass.
- Congratulations, Anthony.
Yeah, well...
You gotta wonder what's next, huh?
Yeah, but for tonight, huh?
All right, thanks.
Talk to you later.
(SIGHS IN RELIEF)
(DISTANT TV PLAYING)
(PAULIE LAUGHING)
We're off the hook
on this Willie Overall thing.
Thank God.
That's fucking beautiful.
Yeah.
(SIGHS)
Know what we ought to do?
We ought to treat ourselves
before we leave.
I was thinking
maybe we'd do some sport fishing.
- You serious?
- Yeah. What are you kidding...
...the fucking marlin they got out here?
We'll rent a boat.
Yeah. Sure.
"What's that got to do
with chicken farming?" he asks.
The whore says,
"Last year, I raised over 5000 cocks."
- Where you going?
- The head. I gotta piss.
- One more?
- Yeah. One more.
Two fags decide they want a baby.
So they jack off in a cup...
...use the sperm
to get a lady friend of theirs pregnant.
Nine months later,
they go to the hospital.
They see all the babies in the nursery.
"Look," they say.
"Our baby's the sweetest one.
He's not even crying at all."
Goddamn it, what the fuck is it?
"Now he's not crying,"
the nurse says.
"Just wait till we take the pacifier
out of his ass."
Right, yeah.
Fuck me.
Accident! Accident!
- (CRYING)
- God-fucking-damn it.
Corrado, what happened?
Oh, Jesus Christ on the cross.
It's all right.
Come on.
I'm an old man.
It was an accident, for chrissake.
You're on Ditropan
specifically to avoid incontinence.
Not to mention Celexa, which should be
curtailing your aggressiveness.
I'm taking my medication.
Ask Hormel,
you don't believe me.
Jameel. He's been let go.
Mr. Soprano, there's a trust among staff
and patients regarding treatment.
That means you have a choice:
You can either wear Depends while
you await transfer to another facility...
...or you can take your medication
as prescribed.
(PLAYING SOFTLY)
(KNOCKS)
Here, Corrado.
Time for your medicine.
(SIGHS)
Where the fuck is my iPod?
Every day it's your iPod, Carter.
Stop causing a commotion.
What'd you do that for?
I should piss myself again?
But I did the thing.
They're muscling me,
what do you want me to tell you?
I could have gotten in trouble.
You don't even give a shit.
- Let's get a card game together.
- They fired Hormel.
Jameel? Fuck him. You got me.
Maybe tomorrow, kid.
I don't know. I'm tired.
Old Ironsides.
You're supposed to say,
"Who, Beansie?"
Yeah.
(CHUCKLES)
(MOTOR STARTS)
(GUN FIRING)
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
(DOOR OPENS)
Where you been?
You didn't come to lunch.
I brought you these...
...from Keith. He owed me money.
"Hootie and the Blowfish."
Thanks.
That was a nice letter
you wrote to Cheney.
But he don't read them himself.
They got computers that do it.
I asked Lynch, the professor.
What are you talking to him for?
Says we'll have a better chance
if we write him at his outfit...
...Halliburton.
My father owned Grumman stock.
My grandpa said
my dad lacked character.
Grandpa was a lion.
You're very smart, Anthony.
I'm sure you're very good
with spelling too.
Rigatoni à la Paulie.
But since you're eating it,
maybe it should be rigatoni à la Tony.
What, you're not hungry?
My fucking stomach.
You know, when you went down below,
I thought I saw a whale.
- No shit.
- It made me think of Ginny Sack.
(SNORTS)
That joke Ralph made about her,
that was some funny shit...
...no matter what John said.
- Gotta have a sense of humor, right?
- Yeah.
I heard she took an office job.
Chubb Insurance.
It was you told him, right?
I mean, it's no big deal.
I could hardly resist.
Grapevine, Ton. I don't know.
Yeah.
He was a funny prick, that Ralph.
His Gladiator fixation...
...the time he hit Georgie in the eye
with the chain.
I'd have loved to have seen John's face
when he heard that crack.
Always fucking holier-than-thou
because he didn't fuck other women.
Mr. Broomstick-Up-His-Ass.
You know...
No offense, but you ever
had yourself checked for Tourette's?
- What?
- Tourette syndrome.
Seriously.
- Like you got a tick or something.
- I don't know.
It's like some people grind their teeth.
When I'm nervous, tense or something.
Come on,
you told John about that joke, right?
- It wasn't me, Ton.
- No?
That's right.
You want a drink?
All right. Stewart's.
- Think fast.
- Jesus. Ton.
Fuck, that hurt.
(ALL SINGING
FOLK SONG)
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
(ALL SHOUTING)
What does it take
to get something to eat?
(RUSTLING)
(SIZZLING)
When my time comes, tell me...
Will I stand up?
- Who was at the door?
- "Williams-Sonoma. From Paulie.
The Elektra Semiautomatic
Chrome Espresso Machine."
- So?
- My God, Tony.
This is like $2000.
- I mean, what is wrong with that man?
- What's wrong with him? Nothing.
It's guys like him
that allows our whole lifestyle here.
Take me over to Jeanette's house.
(ALL SCREAMING)
(GIRL SCREAMS)
In an apparent escalation
of a Mafia power struggle...
What year? Let me see...
...'72, '73,
back in the Feech La Manna days.
I'm on a roll. I mean,
I haven't lost a bet in fucking months.
After a brazen ambush by...
Hey, Ton, you see this shit?
Skip.
Hey.
Looks like Phil's the main guinea
over there now, huh?
Anyway, we're at Maxwell's Plum...
...the Saturday night before the game.
Who walks in but fucking Namath.
Three sheets to the wind,
fucking staggering like a sailor.
So I know the game is going
into the toilet.
I said to my brother Gerry...
He was just a kid at the time.
"Take this money down
to old Caruso on the corner...
...and put it all against the Jets."
My brother was just recovering
from rheumatic fever...
(SWING MUSIC PLAYING)
(DOG BARKING)
(MEWS)
(MUSIC CONTINUES)