(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
(RATTLING)
Twenty-three, red and odd.
- No!
- Yes, motherfucker!
You fucking nailed it, T.
Jesus, 23. Sophia's birthday.
I should've had that.
- He's got it like five ways there.
- Six. He's on red too.
- You cocksucking motherfucker.
- What happened?
- Tony hit one straight up.
- Finally.
Sixty-six-10, going out.
Don't you spill those.
- You wanna take it or play it?
- Let's play it.
- All right.
- All right, all right.
- That's my man.
- Twenty-three, and all around.
- Are you fucking kidding?
- You gotta ride that.
(RATTLING)
- All right, one more time.
- Come on.
- Do it again.
- Come on. Come on.
- Two three.
- Come on.
- Come on, bounce.
- Come on. Come on, 23.
- Do it again.
- Eleven.
- (MEN GROAN)
- Big shit.
- What the fuck?
- Jeez.
- Douchebags...
...are taking it all back tonight.
What the fuck, Vito?
You almost hit me.
Timber, motherfucker.
(LAUGHING)
Stop right there.
Ten-1 odds, Poor Boy's Delight,
she fucking comes in.
Look at this mezza morta.
Oh, hey.
- How are you, baby?
- Sil.
Good to see you. Hey.
Sit down.
Can I get you something?
A coffee or a bun?
Well, I'll let you two talk.
- So...
- I really appreciate...
...you letting me see you.
And you've been so decent
about everything since Vito's death.
I just don't know who else...
All right, all right.
Come on. Come on, Marie.
- What can I do?
- It's Little V.
The social worker says
he's just acting out.
- Social worker?
- Boy stuff mostly, but so angry.
Although some of what he's being
accused of is just persecution.
They claim that he hung the
Petruzzo's cat on their garage door...
(SNIFFS)
...but it's totally unfounded.
(SOBBING)
Well, you know, in a way,
it's to be expected, with Vito passing...
...and all that that entrailed.
I think the only solution...
...is to move away from that house
and the kids at school.
(SIGHS)
I figured it out,
and I know it's a lot...
...but for 100,000...
...we could be someplace where
no one knows him or what happened.
My friend Cheryl lives in Orono, Maine,
by the university...
...and there's this two-story cape,
with solid schools.
You always said if there's
anything you could do...
Sure.
Have you talked to his uncle?
- Who?
- Phil.
Phil's not his uncle.
Him and I are second cousins.
Before we get too drastic here
and uproot little Vito and all of you...
...from your friends and your family,
I should talk to him.
He's impossible to talk to.
It's not easy
to substitute for a dad.
I know.
But maybe I can fill in here.
Okay, but you'll think about it?
Believe me, I'm gonna take care
of you, and he's gonna be okay.
(OLDIES MUSIC PLAYING)
Well...
...apparently Vito Jr.'s
a whack job.
No surprise there.
Family history.
She wants 100K
for a change of scenery.
That never works.
- She should get him a dog.
- I don't think that's a good idea.
(SIGHS)
The point is, how the fuck
is this my problem?
Because I'm the boss of the family?
And where the fuck is Phil Leotardo?
He created the situation
by clipping Vito to begin with.
My best fucking earner.
Now second time around
I'm getting my pocket picked.
Not to mention he's his uncle
or cousin or whatever the fuck.
Not your problem. I agree.
I agree, Jim.
I argued against the on-side kick.
Let's face it, they rarely work.
Yet here they are, the overworked
Bucs D falling apart...
...as the Bills, with that play,
are inside the 30 and loaded for goal.
- Let's go. Come on, come on.
- Just watch.
- Bills get another seven.
- Yeah, you think?
- No, I say a quick field goal wins it.
- Absolutely.
They'll choke. That's what they do.
You got Buffalo, right, T?
No, line is three.
I'll settle for a push.
Buffalo!
Fucking go for it!
(CLAPPING)
Third and two, the snap.
Losman's back, he hands it off.
- (MEN GROANING)
- Fumble. Ball's loose.
Buffalo recovers.
- No, put the...
- Now it's fumbled again.
- Boston has picked it up.
- Get him! Get on him! Come on!
- Got it. Careful.
- Get him!
Get him! Thunder up!
(SHOUTING)
Touchdown!
Buffalo scores as time expires.
Un-fucking-believable.
Buffalo! Fucking-A!
(CHEERS)
(SQUEALS)
(LAUGHS)
Listen to this fucking guy.
Probably won $35 down there.
Final score, Buffalo 28,
Tampa Bay 24.
Skip, another beer?
No. No, no, I'm gonna go
take a snooze.
(SOFT ROCK PLAYING)
Beautiful, sweetheart.
(APPLAUSE)
Nancy Sinatra, everybody.
- Congratulations, Philly.
- Thank you.
We were gonna go the festival route,
but we found a guy...
...who wants to distribute it himself,
so we'll see what happens.
It's a good little movie.
- All right. I'll talk to you.
- Yeah.
Jesus Christ, it's 11:30.
Ready to call it?
An hour ago.
I saw him bring
Dean and Jerry back together.
I was there at the telethon.
I cried.
- You leaving already?
- Yeah. Yeah, it's late.
Got a long hike
to Jersey from here.
Sure, I used to drive it myself.
No more though.
I'll be right back.
Congratulations again.
Listen, I gotta bring this up.
- A favor already?
- Excuse me?
Anthony, you always have
business on your mind.
Take a night, smell the cognac.
Marie Spatafore came to see me.
She wants
a hundred grand to relocate...
...on account of Vito Jr.
already has his own social worker.
Patty told me there was doings.
I guess the turd doesn't
fall far from the faggot's ass.
That's beautifully put,
but you're family, right? Cousins?
What can you do?
Throw money at the problem?
Well, somebody's gonna.
I'll talk to the kid...
...set him right.
Good.
You two going home together?
How the fuck are you?
Fucking prostate keeping me
pissing all night.
I wouldn't wish it
on my worst enemy.
(GROANS)
(TRICKLING)
Nu?
I talked to Phil about the split
on the MRI centers...
...and your cut is on the way.
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah, so is Christmas.
Oh, you should have
heard it tonight.
- Comments, smug.
- Really?
Worries me.
I thought we were getting along pretty
good finally, you know, considering.
Could be the hubris,
making boss...
...but I still think it's what
went down with his brother Billy.
I thought all that
got buried with your cousin.
You enjoy the dinner?
- Yeah, and I left right after.
- Oh, yeah?
I don't know...
I look at my key guys...
...Paulie, Christopher,
my brother-in-law.
What's number one
on their agenda, you know?
They're all fucking murderers,
for chrissakes.
Lonely at the top, boychik?
What I'm trying to say is...
...it's nice being here. Always is.
(CHUCKLES)
I brought you something.
Cover up that dome.
Actually, I was
expecting something else.
What, the fucking DVD?
Honestly, it's a very unflattering portrait
of Italian-Americans.
No, I was thinking maybe
some of that 200,000 I loaned you.
Oh, Jesus.
Yeah, that's right.
I know it's covered.
It's just after a while with no vig...
You know, I lost track.
- I'm glad you didn't.
- I don't wanna be a stickler.
- No.
- Anthony, come on.
No. No, it's okay. It's okay.
I got about three grand here.
Point and a half good?
- Oh, come on, fuck this.
- You gotta have it.
- Don't want you eating cat food.
- Come on, stop it.
I don't gotta have it.
I don't want a vig from you.
No, come on. (SIGHS)
I should have been on it.
- You sure?
- Jesus Christ, are we good or what?
Well, it's late.
I should be getting back.
And you should get back to pissing
or whatever you...
(BOTH LAUGH)
(WOMAN TALKING ON TV)
I lend the guy money,
suddenly I'm the schmuck.
Why does he need your money?
Why? To cover his nut.
Between his gambling
and the lifestyle and that boat...
Three point two mil.
I warned him.
It has absolutely
no resale value whatsoever.
Does he listen? Yeah.
I've lent lots of money.
Once the chiseling starts,
"Oh, I forgot."
Who forgets? Fuck him.
This is why I don't like you seeing
him before bed. You're all upset.
Makes a big show
of giving me a vig.
Three thousand a week.
You got a lot of Jews
in your business?
- My business?
- Yeah, this.
You gotta hand it to them,
when it comes to money...
In my experience, that's nothing more
than an ugly stereotype.
Really?
I got a friend, let me tell you,
you tie a Krugerrand...
...to a fishing line,
you're gonna land him.
(SCHWOOPS)
Right up on the dock.
Doesn't sound like
you think of him as a friend.
Come on.
We go way back.
But that didn't stop him
from busting my fucking balls...
...because I owe him
some money.
Anyway, I needed a little bridge loan
to cover some of the gambling losses...
...we've been talking about.
- Still?
- You know, good money after bad.
- Why not just stop?
- Big part of my life.
I know, but you've
been talking about it a lot.
Well, you lose sometimes.
You gotta act like it hurts a little more
than it does, you know, for your guys.
But if you're gonna lose,
what's the fucking point, huh?
So you need the risk.
What are you chasing?
Money or a high from winning?
Before we end,
there's something I need to bring up.
You miss a lot of appointments.
Excuse me, I always give you the
required notice or I pay for the hour.
- That's not my point.
- Well, I get busy.
It's my fault. I've condoned it
for a long time.
I haven't had a panic attack
since my uncle shot me.
- Did you notice that?
- Yes.
Well, it must be nice
to know everything.
Is that the only reason
why you're here?
- The panic attacks?
- No.
This is an...
...oasis in my week.
So this is vacation?
No, I benefit in many ways.
Decide if you wanna
keep coming...
...but know there are protocols
that have to be followed...
...or I won't be able to continue.
Okay, I will.
(SIGHS)
Now, I know Brian wants
the media room downstairs...
...I think it's better
if the gym has access to the pool.
(DOORBELL CHIMES)
That's the inspector.
Well, I told the guy
to run cable for computers...
...but I can't promise the damn thing
is not already obsolete.
- Hi, how are you?
- Ted Yacanelli...
...Yacanelli Home Inspections.
Yeah, come on in. These are
our cousins Hugh and Carmela.
- How are you doing?
- They're also the builders.
Oh, great.
- Wanna start over here?
- Yeah.
You know, I didn't come out here
just to buy you a couple of sundaes.
It's a Silo.
I don't give a fuck what it is.
What the hell's wrong with you?
You look like a Puerto Rican whore.
You make me sick.
So? What's it gotta do with you?
Listen, pally,
you need to be rebellious.
I raised kids. I get it.
- Good for you.
- You want a smack too?
You ever think what this is doing
to your mother?
What she's been through,
how you're upsetting her?
- She's just embarrassed.
- She cries for you.
I'm gonna say this because
you're old enough to understand.
Your family's had enough shame.
You should set things right.
- You understand me?
- No.
Jesus Christ. Be a man.
Be the kind of man she needs.
Strong, masculine.
(GRUMBLES)
I said my piece.
Finish that thing.
There's no eating in the car.
I'd like to take a minute
for everybody to enjoy the fact...
...that your mother
has sold her house.
- Oh, my God, that's fantastic.
- Congratulations, Mom.
- That's so good.
- Well, actually...
...it just passed inspection.
Brian needs to get
loan approval before we can...
All right, all right, enough.
Congratulations, Carm.
It's not an easy thing to do these days.
I had a lot of support.
Brian and Janine must be so happy.
- I hope so.
- Just the two? It's big, right?
- It's a mansion.
- Pass the salad.
They have a baby on the way.
(SILVERWARE CLINKING)
- (THUNDER RUMBLING)
- (PHONE RINGING)
- Hello.
- Have you looked outside?
- (RAIN POURING)
- (THUNDER RUMBLES)
Oh, Jesus, Mellie.
We replaced 60, 50 percent
of the bad lumber with Doug fir.
Well, what about the studs? And
those headers upstairs? I'm nauseous.
Oh, for the hundredth time,
I done a ton of houses...
...using the same construction...
...before these sob sisters
took over the building department...
...and I'm not losing any sleep.
- (DIAL TONE)
- (PHONE BEEPS)
(THUNDER CRASHES)
Lunch.
- Mortadella and prov.
- That's Chrissy.
The mysterious stranger.
- Hey.
- Long time.
Sit.
I had to drop Eli off
at physical therapy.
I thought I'd check in
on the brain trust here.
- Sit, play a hand.
- Yeah, don't be shy, Shylock.
- I got a little time. Why not?
- "Why not," he says.
Did you hear the one
about the Jewish terrorist?
He was gonna hijack a plane,
but he didn't wanna use his miles.
(ALL LAUGH)
- You want a sandwich?
- No, I just ate, thanks.
He's not here to eat.
He's here for the rent.
The rent, the rent.
What are you talking about?
You know what? I'll have a beer.
- Here you go.
- Will you stop already?
That should get me through
another week, right?
I got some spare change here too.
(SCRAPING)
It's a joke.
Where's that sense of humor?
Should put this in the pot,
make things interesting.
I'll take a shot at that.
- Let's play.
- Let's see it.
- Are you sure you did it right?
- Yes, and it's normal.
Maybe it was the Kung Pao.
- Get me a drink.
- Sure, alcohol, that's good for it.
Get one yourself.
It's not the fucking MSG.
It's Tony Soprano.
(SIGHS) You know, he really helped
when I was in the hospital.
- Never lend friends money, Eli.
- He still won't pay?
That's the least of it.
He's all worked up or something.
And I don't like the way he talks.
Hostile remarks.
It's not like him.
Makes me worry.
Yeah, I can see that.
What are you thinking?
Come on.
Tony's not gonna hurt you.
Yeah.
You've seen how
these Italians work.
For the most part, it's okay.
Get them cornered...
...you're dealing with nothing more
than an animal.
(CHUCKLES) What, do you think
he's gonna kill you now?
I don't fucking know.
He's the guy I call
to deal with people like him.
- He's a rich man. He'll pay.
- Minus assets...
...I'd say under six.
- Come on, he's a boss.
- I've known him a long time.
Money goes in one hand
and right out the other.
The more he makes,
the more he spends. That wife?
Eli, at what point
is it cheaper for him...
...to settle it another way?
(JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
Come on, Lisa.
(ALL CHEER)
- That's three in a row, assholes.
- I'm bumping up here.
Thank you, gentlemen.
Roger will take care of you
from here on. Enjoy the Borgata.
Yeah, right. Time to go.
- Along with the chips.
- Yeah, we're up about 18.
I could go for a rib eye,
Flintstone size.
Oh, no kidding.
Why, because I'm up?
- Holy shit.
- What?
Batavia, in the fifth.
Two-to-1.
Meadow Gold in the fifth.
We gotta do that.
Three minutes to post.
- Glenlivet, rocks.
- Seven and seven.
What do you have on tap?
Give him a beer, anything.
Fuck it, I don't wanna miss this.
Batavia, here we go.
- Where's the goddamn sound?
- The boss put 18 plus on this.
- Maybe 25.
- Yeah?
What the fuck's your problem?
Nothing, I'm excited.
Now, what do you want?
All right, they're running here.
Where's the fucking sound?
- It's on, Ton.
- Rounding the clubhouse...
All right, go, girl.
- Go, you fucking nag.
- Come on, girl.
- (ALL YELLING)
- Come on, Med.
There you go.
- Come on, baby.
- She's in the lead.
- She's in the lead. Come on.
- Come on. Go, girl.
- (ALL SHOUTING)
- Come to daddy. Come to daddy.
Go, go, go!
Attagirl!
And rounding the turn, Swelligant,
Meadow Gold, Mestizo...
...Kir Royale and Smoosh Baby
falling back.
It's Swelligant and Meadow Gold.
- Kir Royale on the outside.
- Come on, baby!
Swelligant and Meadow Gold.
- Swelligant and Meadow Gold...
- Fucking go!
...and it's Swelligant by a nose.
Meadow Gold to place,
Kir Royale rounding out the top.
(VOICE SLOWS) Mestizo,
Smoosh Baby in the five spot.
- By a cunt hair, Tony.
- Heartbreaker.
What are you gonna do, huh?
Madam, your desert.
- I didn't order nothing.
- I ordered for you.
You know I'm trying
to watch my weight.
What is this?
Oh, my God.
Anthony...
You like it?
It's gorgeous.
I don't know what to say.
Look, I know you're scared, okay?
I mean, all the problems you had
with Hector's dad. I'm not like that.
I know. It's not just that.
Well, what then?
I'm gonna work my ass off.
You know I'll always
take care of you guys.
In three months I've made
night manager of the pizzeria.
In another three I'll be in charge
of the day shifts too.
A couple of years,
I'll own a chain of restaurants, clubs.
You'll never have to work again.
- Look, I love you.
- I love you too.
So marry me then.
And we'll have kids.
I mean, you always say you want
Hector to have brothers and sisters.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Okay.
- Can I get you some coffee?
- No, I think it's time for our talk here.
So, what happened at school today?
- I get blamed for everything.
- The girl was developmentally disabled.
Uncle Phil said he talked to you.
He's just wasting his breath?
Is that what you're telling us?
Look, this trouble you're causing...
...I'm very disappointed,
because you always were a good kid.
- You don't even know me.
- What is that supposed to mean?
Sometimes you call me Carlo Jr.
All I know is I couldn't shut your dad up
about what a good kid you were.
- We were friends, you know.
- Butt buddies?
Oh, you're being funny.
That's good.
Because I'm sure
you miss him a lot...
...whatever he was.
And now I'm gonna
say some things...
...you're gonna look at me...
I'm not moving to fucking Maine.
You think anybody wants that?
You know how much
that's gonna cost your mother?
- Whatever.
- Listen to me.
Okay? I'm not
some fucking social worker.
Now, you knock this weird shit off...
...or I'll introduce you
to a plate-glass window.
Somebody should have told my dad
to knock off the weird shit.
You go about in pity for yourself.
What about your mother?
What she's been through?
What am I supposed to do about it?
Look, your dad's gone, okay?
You're the man of the house now.
Start fucking acting like it.
You get me?
(SIGHS)
Well, I just got back
from the closing.
- Come here.
- (BOTH LAUGHING)
- (TONY MOANS)
- (CARMELA GROANS)
(SIGHS)
We should pop the champagne,
or, I don't know, go out or something.
Oh, maybe, I don't know.
- Why not?
- You know why not, Tony.
- It's upsetting, this whole thing.
- Jesus, the lumber again?
Carm, your cousin Brian has
fucked over a lot of people. Trust me.
So how much in the end? All in?
Well, after construction,
the purchase of the land...
...closing costs,
it must be close to six.
You know what you should do?
You should take a chunk of that
and put it on the Jets.
Oh, yes, very funny.
- I'm serious. We can't get hurt.
- Oh, it's we now?
It's a sure thing.
Celia, she works at the Bing...
...she's got a sister
lives in San Diego...
...she's an osteopath,
and she says that the Chargers' qb...
...has a hairline fracture
in his right leg.
And even Vegas
doesn't know about it.
I didn't say all of it.
You know, just a piece of my half.
You're rich, Tony.
Use some of those bundles to cover it.
That money's for emergencies only,
Carm, you know that.
And my other money's tied up
in asset allocation.
- What is that?
- Listen to me, okay?
This is the gravy.
Windfall cash.
This is the kind of shit
you play with.
I'm telling you.
We are golden here.
(CLINKING)
Listen, listen.
Forget it.
I shouldn't have mentioned it.
I mean it.
It's all right. It's just I thought
this was my money.
You're right. You're right.
It is.
Renata?
- What?
- Go to the bedroom and lock the door.
- Hesh, what's going on?
- Do as I ask.
(KNOCKING)
- What are you doing here?
- Nice to see you too.
Oh, I was watching CNN.
Fucking Hezbollah.
We're running down
to the boat show in Edison.
- Thought you might wanna join.
- I'd love to...
...but Renata's got a migraine.
That's too bad.
The vig. Three grand.
Should put us up to date.
Listen, I can't take this.
Give it all to me whenever you can.
- You're gonna do this every time?
- Whatever you say.
Sit down. Have a drink.
- We should get going, probably.
- Okay. But next time.
- For sure?
- Yeah, next time I'll call first.
Did you see that pissy attitude?
Come all the way out here
to pick him up...
...not to mention give him
his fucking vig in person.
I mean, do you believe
this fucking guy?
You should tell him to go
fuck himself and his 200K.
What's he gonna do about it?
To not pay my debts?
Head of the family?
- How's that gonna look?
- Who's gonna know?
- It's like Eddie Valentine.
- The guy from Philly?
With the polio leg
and the built-up shoe?
No, from the fucking Twilight Zone.
You must have seen that one.
He's a smalltime hood,
he gets shot...
Maybe you should start sucking cock
instead of watching TV Land...
...because Vito brought in three times
what you do on construction.
Yeah.
And I didn't have
this fucking problem.
God fucking damn it!
What?
That's good, right?
No. I only bet 10.
- But you won.
- What did I say?
What did I tell you?
It's a sure thing.
You talk about this crap
like it's science, Tony.
- I lost a lot of fucking money.
- You didn't lose.
We could have turned your bullshit
into a fucking million dollars.
My bullshit?
That spec house was my investment.
- For my future.
- Here we go.
Ginny Sack had to move in
with her fucking daughter, Tony.
Again with Ginny Sack, huh?
John provided.
She's a fucking hysteric.
Did you ever think
I might know what I'm doing?
You and the furniture
and the clothes and the cars.
You would have spent
everything I made! If I let you.
You know what?
The next time you win, I'll take a cut...
...and I'll roll the fucking dice.
You already took your cut,
from the bird feeder.
And don't fucking deny it again.
What, 40 grand on the stock market?
I'd ask for my piece,
but wait, there's nothing.
And that spec house?
I made the down payment.
I bought the materials.
I leaned on that building inspector...
...when you had
your thumb up your ass.
So stop talking about your money!
Let go of me, you piece of shit!
You're a shitty businesswoman
who built a piece-of-shit house...
...that's gonna cave in and kill
that fucking unborn baby any day!
And now you can't sleep.
Go fuck yourself!
When I'm gone, you can live
in a fucking dumpster for all I care.
(CARMELA SOBBING)
(DOOR SLAMS)
I was so "I told you, dude."
At three-point range, there's no way
the ball would hit the rim.
- That was the worst pass.
- Get lost.
- You're such a ball hog.
- Yeah, whatever.
Hey, nobody drop the soap.
Spaz-a-fuckwit's in the house.
(BOYS LAUGHING)
Hey, you can see his pussy.
(LAUGHTER)
What the fuck you looking at, fag?
(FARTS)
- What the fuck?
- He shit.
- Oh, God.
- Jesus, what's wrong with you?
He stepped in it.
- (ALL SCREAMING) Gross!
- He shit in the fucking shower!
Are you crazy?
Cocksucker's Corvair Monza
is still in his garage...
...so we boost the piece of shit.
We're heading down
Communipaw Avenue...
...and the fucking thing
starts to do-si-do...
You got word on the power tools?
What? Yeah. Spics in Florida
sending the first truck Friday.
How about Alphonse
at the hardware store?
- Ready for the whole load.
- Speaking of loads...
...hear the latest on Vito Jr?
- What?
- Marie called.
He got expelled because he took a shit
in the shower in gym class.
- That sick little fuck.
- You should see him, the makeup.
And without school, Marie says
he's shut in his room all day.
Probably thinking about
how to pull a Columbine.
- But the little girl, you know...
- Francesca.
Dad's gone, brother's a psycho,
mother's a basket case.
She's 9 years old.
- What the fuck did she ever do?
- Tragedy.
Like a pebble in a lake.
Even the fish feel it.
It's not right.
Vito was one of us.
So he sucked a cock.
Prior to that, he was our friend.
Can't just cut his family loose.
That piece of shit, Phil,
he's never gonna pony up.
And I'll tell you what, I will never, never
forget that he didn't come through here.
- Never.
- Let it go, Ton.
- This is good of you, Ton, helping Marie.
- I'll always remember it.
All right, let's go.
I gotta swing by Slava's...
...liquefy some offshore monies.
(SPANISH MUSIC
PLAYING)
Yeah, dude.
Vamos al Latino Day Parade.
Yeah.
Hey, Jesus,
you got out of work early.
I need to talk to you.
Why? What's the matter?
- What's this?
- Your clothes.
I just did laundry
a couple days ago.
It's not laundry.
No, Papi, stay.
What are we doing?
What about the parade?
I'm going with my brother.
- What?
- I need to give this back to you.
I can't keep it.
But why? I mean, I love you.
I love you too, Anthony.
Look, I don't know. Maybe I don't.
All's I know is
I just don't feel it.
(BASS POUNDING)
Did you hear about this thing
with the Dolphins' kicker?
He went under a whole truck.
Yeah, fucking motorcycles, huh?
Helmet saved his life.
- He out for Sunday?
- Maybe the whole season.
And the backup kicker?
He's right out of college.
- Against Philly.
- Too good to be true.
You know what? I'm gonna put
the whole 100K down on Philadelphia.
And if I win, Marie Spatafore
gets her free ride and then some.
Yeah, good for you.
Because Carlo said that kid went into
the litter box and ate some cat shit.
No, he took a shit, in the shower.
Glad we got that straight.
Hell of a finish.
Injuries, even tragedy,
unable to stop Miami.
Final score,
Miami 21, Philadelphia 7.
When you get
special team support like that...
...it makes all the difference.
And also, when you see...
(SHUTS OFF)
(PHONE BEEPS)
Hey, Marie. How you holding up?
He snuck out again last night.
Like I told you, I want to help.
God bless you, Tony,
because I don't know what else to do.
Well, I do.
There's this camp in Idaho,
and they handle kids like him.
- Idaho?
- You know, like tough love?
You know?
Saw it on TV, and honestly...
...I was moved to tears
by some of the success stories.
- It's a camp?
- A school camp.
Tony...
...they allow corporal punishment.
His guidance counselor
told me about those places...
...and they're in Utah and Idaho...
...because state law allows them
to strike the kids.
But that's
just for the deterrent factor.
Look, it's 18 grand, but I'm gonna
take care of it for you, so don't worry.
There's no geographical solution
to an emotional problem, Marie.
Maine, wherever.
- Marie?
- Yeah?
I know it's hard,
but it's the best thing for him.
- Okay?
- Thank you, Tony.
- Okay, just make sure you're done.
- I'm all over it, Tony.
All right, Tony.
(ENGINE STARTS)
(JAZZ PLAYING)
Hey, Ton, isn't that...?
What's-their-names?
Used to hang out at the Bing.
- Wake up, Vito.
- What?
Vito, my name is Steve.
I'm here to help you.
You're gonna come
with us now, all right?
- Come on.
- Mom?
- No, let me go. No. Mom.
- Come on. Hey.
- Let me go.
- It's all right.
- It's gonna be okay.
- Mom, no!
I'm so sorry, honey.
- Stop. Let me go. Mom, help me.
- It'll be okay.
Hey, you have to be strong.
You're doing the right thing.
- Who are you?
- Franny, go back to bed.
Mrs. Spatafore, really,
he's gonna be fine.
- No!
- I'm sorry, honey.
No.
- Oh, God.
- No! Stop!
This one coming right down
to the buzzer.
Stackhouse draining
a three-pointer...
...as time ran out, leading Dallas
to a 109-to-108 victory...
...over the visiting
San Antonio Spurs.
A sterling effort for sure,
but you really can't...
(MUTES TV)
So, what,
we're not speaking now?
Listen, come here.
(CLOSES DRAWER)
What?
Sit down.
Come on.
I'm sorry.
I really am.
You did real good with that house.
And I should know,
I'm in construction.
Well, I'm glad to hear you approve.
I have been losing.
I'm fucking losing right now.
Real shitty streak.
So your solution is to risk more
and make things even worse?
Well, you start chasing it.
And every time you get
your hands around it...
...you fall further backwards.
So this is about money?
Because it didn't feel like it.
Carm, I swear to you,
you're not gonna be like Ginny.
I've been real good about that, and
frankly, it's not gonna happen to us.
And I hate that you're going around
acting all the time like it will.
I worry, Tony, I do.
You already got shot.
Now you won't even go down
and get the paper. Who is out there?
- Come on...
- What is it?
What are the million
other possibilities?
The FBI waiting to take you away?
Right? You eat and you play...
...and you pretend like there's not
a giant piano hanging by a rope...
...just over the top of your head
every minute of every day.
See, that's it, okay?
I've been thinking about this.
Now, I survived a fucking
gunshot wound.
- What are the odds on that?
- Terrible.
So if you think about it,
big-picture-wise, I'm up.
What?
Way up.
That was me, not a fireboat.
Ten-thirty.
What would you like for breakfast?
Renata?
Oh, God, Renata.
Wait, wait, Renata.
(DIALING)
Renata?
Renata, please. Oh, wait.
- Renata? Renata?
- 911. What's the emergency?
(SOBBING)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
She was a great girl.
Thanks.
The best.
I brought your money.
Sorry for your loss.
(JAZZ PLAYING)