I'm gonna have to ask you
to switch that off for now.
OK. Thanks.
You know what it's kinda like?
It's kinda like...
It's kinda like a rollercoaster.
You know what I mean?
It's like a roller coaster.
Try it, try it with me.
How tall... how tall is the Eye?
How tall... how tall is Big Ben?
Since then, I've been working
as a technology correspondent
for about two years now.
It's been great.
Cool, that's awesome.
So you do, like,
TV reports and, like, you're like...?
- No, just the website.
- Just the website?
I mean, there's some video stuff,
but tech industry pieces mainly.
Cool, tech, tech.
Tech's awesome. Tech's...
So where have you been so far?
Travelling around the
map like Indiana Jones?
Brazil?
Yeah.
- The red adventure line
goes zigzagging all
over the place.
Yeah, um, actually,
I'm almost done.
But I started off,
flew into Sydney, went to Thailand.
- Jealous.
- India. Yeah, um...
Did Rome, went to Rome.
Did the whole Europe vacation.
- Even I haven't done that.
Really?
It was... it was awesome.
I went to Pamplona in Spain.
Is that where they do the bull runs?
- Ran with the bulls.
You ran with the bulls?
- I ran with the bulls.
That's how I got this.
- Look at that!
You really are Indiana Jones.
Have you got your whip
in your bag and have you got your hat?
I do, yeah.
I saved the world from the Nazis.
That was pretty cool.
Like, you know, just... trying to do,
you know, shit I've never done before.
I mean, is that what you're
doing on this trip?
You're, like, finding yourself?
Yeah!
Um... in a way.
I mean, ... I...
I really needed to get away from
the family home is what I'm doing.
Yeah, that was...
Whatever, that's boring.
Yeah, well, I'm afraid Britain's
pretty tame
as far as daredevil opportunities go.
- Yeah?
It's alright, it's the last leg
of the trip anyway, so...
I'm unfortunately home next week.
Not much time...
- Next week?
- Yeah.
- That's not very long.
No, it's not.
So... I could use, some suggestions
on fun shit to do.
- Fun shit to do?
- Fun shit to do.
Jesus!
Hello.
I'm up. Good morning.
- Morning.
Another battle scar.
Kind of.
Let me guess, you were, like
totally shark fishing in
Cape Town, dude.
Is that your best
American accent?
Yes.
- That's pretty good. No, um...
It was courtesy of Josh Peters,
high school dick.
He and I got into a fight
in shop class.
And he hit me with this, like,
metal rod thing.
What an arsehole.
'What an arsehole.'
That's terrible.
- I am sorry.
Is that you or me?
It's gotta be you.
'Mom.'
You're so American.
Yes, I am.
Are you not gonna get that?
OK, that was a little impersonal.
What, you wanna talk
to her now?
You wanna talk to my mom?
I'll call her back.
Fair point.
I don't think so.
You hungry?
Wow.
Look at all these games.
You're, like, a gamer.
Cool.
Of course I am. For my job.
What, a girl never beat you
at Street Fighter?
Is this... Like, this is, like,
your dating manual?
What? The Singularity?
It's when computers learn
to outsmart man
like women did years ago.
Wow!
See, um...
what I was doing
it was like a joke.
You know?
- Really?
- Yeah.
Well, that's what you call a joke?
Yeah, you guys have those...
you guys have those here, right?
- Yeah, yeah. We do at the moment.
That was a good joke.
Enjoy your Marmite.
Whoa! My...
What?
Do you guys seriously
eat this shit?
It's f...
OK, alright.
Alright, saved by Mom.
The best way to actually just
stop her from calling is...
I don't know, answer it.
Yeah, it's just kind of like
a can of worms
I just don't want to open
right now, so...
She's worried. You're her son.
You've been travelling.
And I just think if you
speak to her, then...
Yeah, well, um, I still live at
home with her back in Syracuse.
That's... that's cool. That's fine.
- Yeah.
Um...
I was taking care of my dad.
Shit. Is he OK?
No, he died.
- My God. I'm sorry.
- Last year. No, it's OK.
It was coming for a while.
It was early-onset Alzheimer's.
God, then that must have
been really... er... tough.
Yeah, he was, my best friend.
Um...
Sometimes he'd just look at me
and wouldn't even know who I was.
Well, my mom, like, I don't even...
I don't know how to talk to her.
You know, like, I don't have
that connection.
I don't even know where to start.
So that's...
that's why I left.
That's why I went on this trip.
Just to get away and make,
you know
all the memories that I can...
while I can.
And I know I gotta talk to her
and I gotta just...
But not on this.
You know, I just...
I just want to deal with it.
I'll deal with it when I get back,
you know.
It's just...
You're a good guy, Cooper.
Call your mum.
Zero, zero, one, nine, three,
nine, two, nine...
No, I did not buy a pair of sandals
in Ko Samui last night
because I'm in...
And how long...
and how long does that take?
Because I need to buy
a ticket back to America.
My God.
Can I just say, this is the most
blatant cover story
for a second hook-up ever?
Yes! Yes!
My God.
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
Alright. Don't forget your bag.
The bag, yep, that's my bag.
Alright. You are a top bird.
I don't know what that means,
but I heard somebody say it once
and you're it.
I got a plan.
Yeah. It's, um, OddJobs.
For who?
- For, like... It's an app.
You can kind of...
Like, I've used it all over
when funds were low, so...
- Some interesting ones.
- ...it's pretty cool.
'Thrill seekers wanted.'
- Ooh!
This looks right up your street.
- OK.
OK, four pound signs.
That's a biggie. That's good.
It's a little out of town.
And some kind of play test deal
for a company called Saito...
Saitogoo...
- Saitogemu?
- Saitogemu. Yeah.
They're huge.
They're really big.
- Really?
Horror games?
Have you heard of...?
What's one of theirs?
Er, Harlech Shadow.
Harlech Shadow? Yes, I have.
I used to play that in my buddy
David Ludwig's basement
when we were, like, seventh grade.
Well, that's Shou Saito.
It's his company.
He's like this genius, super secretive.
- OK.
And apparently they're working
on this new project.
Big money involved.
Ground-breaking.
But nobody knows anything about it.
Well, maybe if I play my cards right
I can get you an exclusive
with Shou.
Fo' Shou?
You should take a photo.
What, like...?
- Seriously.
If you get a photo of anything
that they're working on
that's a fuck-load more money
than four pound signs.
Cool.
Um...
Well, where is this place?
Mr Copper.
Hi. Um... Just Cooper.
Mr Cooper, I apologise.
Just Cooper is fine.
Then, in that case, I'm just Katie.
Hi.
- Hi.
- Follow me.
- Yeah.
I'll just get my pack here.
- Rav will take care of that.
Rav will...
Rav will take care of that.
OK, great.
That's good.
I don't wanna carry it in there anyway.
Rav kind of reminds me
of like an end-of-level boss.
You know... 'Haiuken!'
Just...
How was your journey?
- Great. Thanks.
The car pick you up OK?
- Yeah.
Wow.
This way.
Are they... seeing...?
It's cool. Very cool.
Wow.
Come on.
Feel like I'm gonna go meet
Dumbledore.
Hope I get...
hope I get Gryffindor!
I'm gonna need your phone
and anything else
you might use to send and receive.
A little paranoid, don't you think?
- Can't be too careful.
OK, there you go.
Wow, you really are paranoid.
Whoa!
It's white.
Um...
OK, so I'm guessing this says, like,
I agree to have my kidneys harvested?
Actually, it's a pretty standard
NDA-disclaimer thing.
OK.
It's important that you realise there
is a small medical procedure involved.
Sorry, for a game?
Nothing permanent
and we don't harvest your kidneys.
I promise.
- OK.
It's no more invasive
than having your ears pierced.
Confidential information,
brain downloaded into the game...
Duration, termination..."
Um, the signature page...
Where do I sign?
The signature... Yeah.
- There's a page missing.
OK.
- Just a moment.
Alright. I'll just wait... here.
What the fuck?
All good?
- All good.
What we're working on is an interactive
augmented reality system.
Like VR?
- More like layers on top of reality.
OK. Um...
Um...
What's that?
- We call this a mushroom.
Like... Mario Brothers?
- If you like.
You're qualified
to do this, right?
I haven't killed anyone yet.
May 1?
Yeah.
All done.
- That was it?
- See, I told you I'm good.
Don't worry,
it's not permanent.
Um...
OK. What is this, like,
some kind of like memory test
or something like that?
- You'll find out.
- OK.
You might feel a slight twinge
as it initialises.
OK. Um...
Commencing at 5:38.
You ready?
- Yes, sir!
Nearly there.
I thought I turned that off.
All done. You feel OK?
I feel great.
Watch the targets.
- OK.
Um...
Is...?
What do you see?
Like a... um...
Like a video game gopher.
Is there more detail now?
- Yeah.
Yep, yeah.
And now?
- Holy fuck!
- Ta-dah!
- Holy shit!
He... Fuck. He's right...
He's right... He's right... Can I...?
Whoo!
He's not real.
He's just a sort of mental projection.
You can see him. I can't.
- You can't? The...
Wow!
OK.
Give him a whack.
Give him a whack?
OK, alright.
OK! Alright, so just like
whack-a-mole.
I've played it a million times. OK.
Alright.
Here we go. Come on up.
Where you coming up?
No. No.
No.
Alright. Stay down.
OK. Stop. Got it.
Good game. Very good game.
You are so adorable!
OK. Bye.
Bye.
- Is that it?
- Afraid so.
Now, were the gophers
two-dimensional or three?
Three. No, no, no.
3D, super 3D. Like... Yeah.
And this is just a limited test demo.
- That was a demo?
I think you should beta test the full
experience we're working on.
There'd be more money in it,
of course.
If you're game?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I'm game.
I'm game.
This is Shou Saito.
You must be our latest volunteer.
- Hi.
This is really great. Hi.
- Konnichiwa.
Ko... Konnichiwa. Hi.
- Nice.
Um, I just... I wanted to say that
the mole game...
Super fun.
Super fun... fun.
Fun?
- Fun.
- Fun is good.
- Yeah.
Playing games is... is good.
Your heart goes faster.
You smile.
- Yeah.
Yeah. Or, um... scream.
Right?
I have always liked
to make the player jump.
Frightened.
You get a scare, you jump.
Afterwards, you feel good.
- Yeah.
You glow.
Why?
Um...
Because of the adrenaline rush.
Yes.
- Yeah.
But mostly because you
are still alive.
You have faced your greatest fears
in a safe environment.
It is a release of fear.
It liberates you.
Yeah. I mean, totally.
What we are working on now
is the most personal survival
horror game in history.
Wow. Cool.
One that works out how to scare you
by using your own mind.
Whoa.
That... that sounds crazy.
Can't wait.
I'm uploading a neural net package.
Neural net packing, neural net.
Name could use a little work, I think.
It's all 90s.
I'm just kidding, it's a good name.
It's state of the art intelligent
software.
It learns and adapts
on the fly.
It'll monitor your brain activity
and try and work out
how best to frighten you
and then adjust your
experience accordingly.
Whoa!
- Are you ready?
- Yeah.
Beam me up. Here we go, lock and load.
- Eyes closed.
- Time is currently 6:17 p.m.
- OK.
It's uploading.
Five, four, three, two, one.
How are you feeling?
Um...
I feel good. I feel normal.
OK. Stand up, slowly.
Are you ready to play?
Isn't this
the Harlech Shadow house?
Well, it's part of the estate.
The gamekeeper's lodge,
actually.
But, yeah, this was the model.
The layout was replicated for
the game and the textures scanned.
Wow!
Very, very cool.
So, what's the game?
What do I do?
You don't have to do anything.
You just stay in here alone.
See how long you last until
you're too scared to continue.
So all I have to do is,
like, stay here?
And I get paid for that?
I'll be back in the control room,
watching.
There are cameras all over,
so no stealing the silverware.
And now there's this.
OK... And what's this?
- It's an earpiece.
Yeah.
Just pop it in, and you and I will be
in contact the whole time.
Cool.
And I can, like, talk to you,
and you'll hear it?
Right.
- Great, great, that's great.
Now, nothing you'll see can
physically harm you.
It's all just audio-visual,
like the gopher game.
OK.
But if it does get too intense,
we can pull you out at any time
and stop the experiment.
- OK.
Is there a safe word
you can think of?
Something easy to remember it
under stress?
How about the word 'stop'?
Good choice. 'Stop' it is.
- Yeah.
OK, we'll leave you
to enjoy your evening.
Alright.
- You'll hear from me in a moment.
And just make yourself at home.
OK, alright.
Well, take her easy.
Harlech... Shadow.
Is this real?
Yeah, yeah, it's real.
That's real. It's really dead.
- Cooper.
- Hey.
Are you hearing me?
- Loud and clear.
Reaching for the Dutch courage
already, I see.
I'm afraid that wine's non-alcoholic.
Lame.
Well, we need you with a clear head.
- OK. Fair point.
That's a fair point.
This is high-quality craftsmanship.
This is nice.
Yeah. It's good woodwork.
That's this place.
- Full marks for observation.
Yep!
Alright, there we go.
- Shit.
- What's up?
I just forgot I don't have my phone.
I keep going for it,
I forget it's not in my pocket.
And there's, no TV here,
Welcome to the 19th century.
- Yep.
No TV, no Internet, no wi-fi.
Yeah. No wonder people
were seeing shit.
Probably were just bored
out of their gourds.
Well, that's the leading theory
about ghost sightings.
The mind plays tricks
when less stimulated.
Fewer distractions,
people saw more ghosts.
Isn't that a nice piece of info?
Well, they got literature, though.
That's pretty sweet, right?
My God, I can't even remember
the actual last time
that I read a book.
To think people used to do
this on purpose.
I know. Crazy. Why?
You know, I don't think I've...
- Shh, alright?
I need to get into some
old-school shit here.
And concentrate.
Pardon me.
Can I point out your heart rate
just increased?
Yeah. Well, it should have
'cause there's a huge crazy spider
I just saw
You see a spider?
- You don't...?
You don't see that?
- No.
Don't...
Don't walk... Don't...
Holy shit!
Tough guy like you,
scared of spiders.
Yeah, well, I'm just not
fond of 'em.
It's worked out you're
an arachnophobe quickly.
- God.
- It's probing for weak spots.
God damn it.
Fucker!
Yeah!
Um...
OK.
Yeah, well, yeah.
Whole lot more realistic
than the gopher game.
It's good. It's good graphics.
It's good...
Yeah.
Weak sauce.
- What is it?
- Just a...
Nothing. Nothing.
Here with...
because there's a...
No. There's a light on...
now, in the... in the...
Can you... zoom in and...
Zoom in on it.
And you can see what
I'm talking about.
Whoa!
- Cooper...
- And now there's... Shh!
There's a guy in the window that...
And that wasn't...
Yeah.
And now he's gone.
Now nobody's in the window.
Which is the...
Yeah, there's a...
Just leaky pipes.
I knew it.
It was leaky pipes, like...
Holy fuck!
No!
Fuck!
OK.
That got me. You got me.
What are you seeing?
Like a creepy... fucking guy.
Wow, just...
My God.
My God!
He kinda looks like Josh Peters.
It's Josh Peters! You're Josh Peters!
- Sorry?
You're Josh Peters from high school!
From a guy I know at high school.
The system could be mining
some of your personal memories
for texture.
My God.
Was Josh Peters someone
you were scared of?
He was a bully.
I wasn't scared...
I wasn't, like, scared of him,
but he was a bully and...
Man!
Take a couple of Krav Maga
classes
and I would be ready!
I'd be ready!
Kali maa!
Dah!
I'm gonna get some wine
and re-up.
I'd offer you some, but I don't
think you can drink it so...
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Catch ya later, Peters.
This non-alcoholic wine is pretty good.
I'm not like a expert or anything,
but it's kinda great.
Um. I was in France.
I stayed at this, like, vineyard
and they had this... this wine, like,
grape-stomping festival.
Now, that, that wine was good.
I know that.
You're being discursive.
What is discursive? Discursive?
- Talkative.
Rambling.
Is that a problem?
People sometimes talk more
when they're afraid.
Helps compensate for the fear.
- Masks it, too.
- Yeah?
Similar to when you've got
the TV on late at night.
The voices make you feel less alone.
Even though you are alone.
You, aren't scaring me, Katie.
Pity.
Is there like a refrigerator
here or...?
There's some snacks in
the cupboard.
Alrighty.
Eenie, meenie, miney...
...mo! Alright.
OK, ginger snaps.
Let's see.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This'll do.
And that... um...
He's gonna be right behind this door
when I close it, isn't he?
Yeah, that's how this works.
Knew it.
Jump scares get pretty old...
Fuck!
God!
What the hell is that?
- What do you see?
Holy shit!
A fuckin'...
Hard to explain.
It's like a huge-ass spider
with a face
and dicks coming out
of his mouth.
It's...
Peters. Peters is inside.
Like a Peters-spider...
mash-up.
Katie!
Are you doing this,
or is this fucking me?
- I think that's all you.
- I'm so fucked up!
God! Fuck!
Holy shit, you're fucking gross.
Yeah...
Sorry, can you say that...
say again?
Katie, hello?
God damn it.
Katie!
Just... whenever you come back online,
just say the word.
No, I'm not scared, just... bored.
That you guys?
Coming to fix the earpiece?
That's probably... that's a good idea.
Yeah. Yeah.
Cooper, fuckin' man up!
Fuck it.
Come on!
You're in danger.
Sonja?
Now we're talking.
Alright, this is incredible.
This... very impressive.
I am thoroughly impressed.
I am... Wow! Wow!
You look so real!
You're, like, just like her!
I mean, wow.
Except... you're just
unfortunately not... um...
Cooper, what are you doing?
- Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hold on, hold on, hold on,
hold on.
Cooper, you're in danger.
- Shh! Quiet. Quiet! I need to think.
You're fuckin' real.
You are real. You're real.
Cooper, you're in...
- You're Sonja. You're actually here.
Are you actually here right now?
- I'm real. I'm actually here.
- God.
- And we have to go.
And you have to listen to me.
- How are you here?
You know that photo
that you sent me?
Well, I dug around and apparently
Shou Saito took out a patent
for a computer brain interface
last year.
How are you real? I don't...
OK, fuck. I don't...
They brought you here!
You are, you're real,
and they brought you here
and they're trying to
fuck with me.
Nice try, good try.
I get it. It's part of the test.
His patent got rejected outright.
They said it was insane,
it was dangerous.
Wow. Really?
How much are they paying you?
Honestly.
'Cause you're killing it right now.
Cooper, have they given
you something?
Sorry, I thought you were fake.
But now I know that you're real,
I'm being a really terrible host.
I got some non-alcoholic wine.
Might put us in the mood.
Cooper, Cooper,
what I want to do is get...
We'll talk about it in the kitchen.
Come on.
Cooper!
- Sonja, relax, OK?
Give it up. I know, the jig's up, OK?
Let it go.
Look, Cooper, there's more.
Five people have disappeared
in the past year.
All tourists, all registered
with that stupid OddJobs app.
Yeah?
Wow. God, that's crazy.
Whatever they're doing to you,
whatever they've done to you
it's dangerous, and we really
have to go now, Cooper.
OK, OK. Alright.
Um, well, if your story's true...
- Cooper.
...um, then how'd you find me?
- What?
How did you know
where I am?
It's a games company,
I looked up the address.
Yeah, really?
No, no, no, no.
How'd you find me here?
This place.
I tracked you.
- You tracked me?
Yeah, with your GPS on your phone.
Find My Friends.
Find My Friends?
That would've worked,
but they took my phone.
And it's in a building, like,
a mile away.
So, yeah, nice try.
That's right.
So much for women outsmarting men.
Singularity that!
Look, all I'm saying is that
I think that you could've come up,
like, with a better story.
It could have been funny or...
OK, alright, don't be pissed.
Do you ever wonder how your
bank account got hacked?
What are you doing?
I cloned your card as you were asleep.
- Whoa. OK.
Put the knife down.
What are you going to do with that?
I drew your attention to this job.
Sonja, put the fucking
knife down, OK?
It's not funny.
Should've called your mum,
Cooper.
But you called me, and I led you here...
- Sonja.
You know what?
- ...like a breadcrumb trail.
Put the knife down. Drop the act.
OK, seriously, drop the knife, Sonja.
It's not fucking funny.
Put the knife...
This isn't what I signed up for.
I'm fucking done, OK?
Fuck!
What the fuck!
Holy fuck!
Fuck!
Stop!
Come on! Stop!
Fuck!
- Cooper.
- Katie!
Katie!
- Cooper.
- Cooper, what's happening?
What the fuck happened?!
What's happening? We've been talking.
You've not been responding.
You said I wouldn't feel anything!
- What are you seeing? What's there?
Fuck! But she's gone now!
- Who's gone?
My God, I-I felt it!
There's a knife in my arm!
In my shoulder!
- Cooper, who was there?
- Fuck... Son... Sonja.
- Who?
Sonja. She's this girl that I know,
that fucking...
She stabbed me.
She had a fucking knife.
- Nothing can harm you...
Nothing can harm you, Cooper.
- No, no, no, no.
She was solid.
- No, she can't have been.
She... she...
I was stabbed! I would know!
Nothing you see can harm
or even touch you.
It's purely audio-visual.
There's no physical sensation.
- Fuck!
Yes, there was!
Cooper, you need
to calm down.
I know because I felt it, OK?
I felt her arm, it was warm
and I felt her fucking
stab me in the shoulder.
- That's not possible.
- My God.
It's not possible, Cooper.
- Yeah, it is! Yeah, it is!
Physical sensations shouldn't
be possible.
- Unless, I mean...
- God. Unless what?
! don't know.
The neural net...
- It could have maybe worked out...
- Fuck me!
...some means of replicating
physical experiences
but that would be unprecedented.
- Jesus Christ.
OK, you know what?
Stop the game.
I want out.
Just pull me out now.
Stop, stop, stop.
Safe word. Fucking stop!
- OK, OK, just let us work it out.
- God.
No, I want this fucking thing out now.
Cooper, do not attempt to remove
that yourself.
Removing it yourself
is extremely dangerous.
Stop that! That could kill you!
Just stay calm!
Is that Shou?
Is that Shou? What's he saying?
What's he saying?
OK, Cooper.
- What's he saying?
We're gonna commence
with deactivation.
That's great news.
We need you to follow instructions
and make it to the access point.
The access point?
Great.
Where the fuck's the access point?
- Fuck! More stairs? Come on!
- Just one more level.
Trust me.
- OK.
Left at the top.
OK, which door?
- Room at the end.
What is it?
There's gonna be something
behind there.
I can feel it.
Something like...
Like what?
Some personal fucked-up shit.
Like... I don't know, I could feel it
digging around in my head.
Cooper, get to the door.
It's gonna be like my mom...
I don't know, dead.
- Your mum?
Fuckin' swinging from a fuckin' beam.
Your mother is not in there.
- You're not in control of this!
It's in my head.
It fucking knows. It knows!
It knows!
- It knows what?
It knows I got this thing
with my mom.
Cooper, I promise you,
she's not in there.
- Now open the door.
- My God.
It's the only way I can get you out.
Listen to me.
- OK.
OK. Fuck. OK.
Whatever's in there cannot harm you.
But I can't get you out unless
you open that door, Cooper.
Fuck, OK.
- Would you kindly open the door?
Here we go. Here we go.
OK.
OK, OK, I'm in the...
I'm in the room.
Where's the access point?
Access point?
There is no access point.
- What?
!'m fucking with you, Cooper.
! told you to come up here to see
if we've broken you enough
to obey instructions
without question.
- And we have.
- No, no, no, no, no.
Katie, come on.
Katie, come on!
Let me out!
Katie, let me out, come on!
What the fuck!
What are you gonna do?
What are you doing to me?!
- Why are you doing this?
- You thought you'd see your mother.
- Fuck!
- What does she look like?
Your mother,
can you describe her face?
Um...
Her hair colour?
She...
Is she tall, short, fat, thin?
Where did you grow up?
- She...
What's your favourite band?
Your favourite flavour ice cream?
The name of the girl
who stabbed you?
You don't know any
of these things, do you?
Don't you think that's odd?
It's fucking taking my memories!
Overwriting them, technically.
Fuck.
Look in the mirror, behind you.
Do you recognise yourself?
Do you even know
who you're looking at?
Soon you won't be anything.
You'll be just like your dad.
Shut up, shut up, shut up.
That's what really scares you, isn't it?
- Stop it.
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
- You're going the same place he did.
You're going nowhere.
- Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up...
You should have called mom.
She's all that's left.
You abandoned her.
- No, no, no, no!
Get out of my head!
You'll never see her again.
- Get out of my fucking head!
You'll never speak to her again.
Never see her face. You'll be all alone.
- Get out of my fucking head!
Get out of my fucking head!
- You should've called.
You abandoned her.
- Get out of my fucking head!
You're a bad son.
- You'll never see your mother again.
- No!
You're going nowhere.
Straight into oblivion.
And you deserve it.
- My fucking head...
You should have called her.
Get out of my fucking head!
Get it out of my head!
Get it out of my fucking head!
Cooper, I'm gonna shut it off, OK?
I just need to connect.
Get it out of my head!
My God.
Where am I?
Who are you?
I can't stop it.
I don't...
I don't know who I am.
So I...
So I need to go home.
The interface has data
tendrils like roots.
They've dug in deeper
than they're meant to.
Threaded through your brain,
taken over whole areas.
I can't stop it. I...
I can't remove it
and I can't stop it.
But I... but I don't know...
But I don't know who I am.
I don't know...
I don't know who I am.
I don't know.
On behalf of Saito Game Team,
I most humbly apologise.
Who are you?
What have you...
what have you done to me?
What have you done to me?
- Put him with the others, please.
No, no, no, no!
No, no, no!
Stop, stop, stop, stop!
Stop, stop, stop!
No, don't, don't!
Don't! Don't! Don't! Don't!
Stop!
No!
Fuck. Wow.
That was one second.
Either he's super susceptible to this
or the software is
way too powerful still.
It's jumped from zero to 18K
in five milliseconds...
I'm sorry.
The experience was more powerful
than intended, Mr Cooper.
I hope you can forgive us.
...all luggage under
the seat in front of you.
All electronic devices should now
be turned off and stowed
as they may interfere with the aircraft's
navigational and communication...
Mom?
Mom...
I have to call him.
Mom?
Why did Cooper go?
...- Mom, I'm right here. I'm...
I'm right here, Mom.
I have to call Cooper.
I have to call and make sure
that he's safe.
I have to call him. I have to call him.
I have to call him.
Mom?
Mom!
Mom! Mom! Mom! Mom!
Fuck.
'Mom.'
"Mama Liked the Roses"
by Elvis Presley
♪ Oh, Mama liked the roses ♪
♪ She'd grow them in the yard ♪
♪ But winter always came around ♪
♪ And made the growing way too hard ♪
♪ Oh, Mama liked the roses ♪
♪ And when she had the time ♪
♪ She'd decorate the living room ♪
♪ For all us kids to see ♪
♪ When I hear the Sunday bells ♪
♪ Ringing in the morning ♪
♪ I remember crying ♪
♪ when she used to sing ♪