[unsettling music playing]
[tires screeching]
[breathlessly] Harlan?
Over here.
[breathing heavily]
Oh my God.
I got so worried when you called.
Are you okay?
I messed up.
-Okay.
-I had these tight pains.
-I couldn't breathe.
-Okay, I got you.
-I got you. Do we need the hospital?
-I'm all right. It passed.
-It didn't feel like a heart attack.
-What happened?
I tried to take your advice.
Talk to him. Work it out.
It didn't work out.
[breathing heavily]
[grim sting]
Okay. We're going to fix this, okay?
["True South" by Rodney Atkins playing]
♪ Carhartt, sitting in a church pew ♪
♪ Thank God for the mud
On our work boots ♪
♪ Youngings running wild like kudzu ♪
♪ Dog napping on a bale 'neath a lean-to ♪
♪ Raised on hard work, grits, and grace… ♪
Left or right? Which hand?
He was right-handed.
We need to clean everything up.
Wipe it down.
Make it look like nothing happened, okay?
I'll call Drew Jr.
He's lead deputy now.
I came for a drink.
Found him like this.
Will he buy it?
-If he gets to be the new sheriff.
-[Belle exhales]
Hey.
Thank you.
[exhales]
Let's get on with it.
♪ We are the true south ♪
-[Belle grunts]
-♪ We are the true south ♪
♪ Homemade right here in the USA ♪
♪ Amen ♪
♪ We are the true south ♪
-[metal clangs]
-[wet crunch]
[ghostly echo ringing]
["Broken Bones" by KALEO playing]
[pastor] Honesty, integrity, and trust
are the true marks of a leader.
And never a more accurate way to describe
our beloved Sheriff Clyde Porter.
Law enforcement for him
was not just a profession.
No, for him, it was more of a calling.
♪ I've busted bones, broken stones ♪
♪ Looked the devil in the eye ♪
♪ I hope he's gonna break these chains ♪
A man respected…
♪ The devil's gonna make me a free man ♪
♪ The devil's gonna set me free ♪
[pastor] A shepherd
who sacrificed his time and effort,
and who risked life and limb
on behalf of you, his flock…
♪ The devil's gonna make me a free man ♪
♪ The devil's gonna set me free ♪
[music fades]
How you feeling?
Sure you're up for this?
Doctor says I'm fine.
It was probably just a… arrhythmia.
I can handle the reception
if you wanna go and rest.
No, we should carry on like we would.
Pay some damn homage to the man.
-You go on, I'll meet you inside.
-Where are you going?
To have a little chat.
Okay.
Hey, Stevie.
Coming inside?
We got drinks and food for everyone.
I don't think so.
Oh, come on.
It's a hard day for all of us.
Cut the shit.
I know you killed him.
I can't prove it, but I'm on to you.
That's a strong accusation, Stevie.
But I'll let it go since I need your help
getting hold of Grady.
I don't know any Grady.
Your face just told me different.
So here's what.
You tell Grady I wanna talk to him
about the future.
Go to hell.
If you could tell Grady
I'd like to meet him,
I'd sure appreciate it.
[pensive music playing]
Heads up.
It's about to get real busy in here.
Uh, open bar on the well drinks.
And how about a two-second pour
instead of the regular four?
Yes, ma'am.
-Did you know the sheriff well?
-All my life.
I'm sorry for your loss.
It's okay, Shawn.
If you get in the weeds, holler.
I'll be right back to help you, okay?
Thank you very much.
-I haven't said anything yet.
-Timing kind of sucks.
Thank you.
I didn't even know
he was into vintage cars, did you?
I just knew him as a sheriff.
Imagine your head crushed
under a Chevy Chevelle.
-One way to kill a hobby.
-[Peyton scoffs] I'll get us a table?
Hey, your wife's talking to you, dipshit.
Yeah, okay. I'll see y'all in a minute.
-You could've done so much better.
-[chuckles]
Now you tell me.
Hey, have you talked to Dad?
What's the plan?
He wants to find Grady.
No, it is time to stop. We have to quit.
The money's not worth it.
Dad is out of control.
You know it. We have to stop.
Tell him about the land deal.
That's our way out of this.
Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
What, what--
What do you mean that's not happening?
I don't like the terms
of Wes Benson's offer.
[Cane] Wait, what?
-Bring me in. I'll talk to him.
-He's not the right partner for us.
I see nothing but trouble with him.
We hired lawyers to vet him,
and he checked out.
Well, I rethought it!
This deal's gonna kill your father.
I'm not going through with it.
I'm allowed to change my mind.
Mom, this doesn't make sense.
There's something you're not telling me.
-I wanna know what it is.
-Your father wants to continue, we should.
No, he has gone too far.
I mean… everything with the sheriff,
everything he said happened,
is that really what happened?
I mean, was it even self-defense?
Don't you ever let me hear you
talk about your father like that again.
He's a lot of things,
but he's not a cold-blooded killer.
You understand?
Get out of my face.
Ooh, that bad?
[Cane chuckles]
I didn't know
you were close with the sheriff.
Who is close to a sheriff?
Right. Oh, hey, double fisting.
Oh, Aunt Sylvia wanted to come.
We don't let her drive anymore.
I saw it as a chance
to get out of the house.
Well…
Your dad?
Mm… [smacks lips]
We're already at a wake.
Let's not bring the mood down more.
Right. Yeah, no.
It's all good. I'm laughing on the inside.
Thank you.
-Cheers.
I'm worried about the DEA.
There's an agent
asking for Sheriff Porter's case file.
I thought the DEA left town.
He's right over there.
His name's Sanchez. He stayed behind.
Wants the autopsy report,
photos at the scene of the accident,
everything we've got.
I don't see a problem.
Give him what he wants.
We didn't exactly
do a thorough investigation.
We cremated Porter's body
without a complete analysis.
Because it was an accident.
Agent Sanchez
will come to the same conclusion.
Give him anything he wants.
There's nothing to hide.
How's Lynette and the kids?
April just took her first steps.
Before you know it,
she'll be doing cartwheels.
Lynette must be proud
her husband is the new sheriff.
Acting sheriff. Until elections.
That was always the plan, Drew.
You told me that
back when you were a squirt.
I never forgot that.
Look, Belle's on the town council.
She has lots of sway.
With their support,
I'm sure you'll do fine.
Thank you, sir.
That's very kind of you both.
We're family.
You'll always have our support, Drew.
Cane.
-Cane, did you hear me?
-Mm?
What?
I said, are you okay?
You're awfully quiet.
Yeah, I'm-- I'm fine.
I got a lot going on right now.
You seem really stressed.
[huffs] I'm fine.
Whoa. Whoa!
Okay. Hey, what are you doing?
You remember
that little restaurant in Seattle?
[Cane exhales]
Yes.
Right on the water?
The food was so good.
What are you doing?
Actually, I don't even remember
what we ate.
I just remember what we did.
Stop, stop. Stop, Peyton. Stop.
Hey.
What you staring at?
Porter's family don't seem too torn up.
I knew he was divorced
but didn't know the extent of things.
[man] Harlan.
Hello, Belle.
What the hell are you doing here?
Just paying my respects.
Clyde and I go way back, you know that.
Hello, Emmett.
It's always a surprise to see you.
If you'll excuse us--
Now, Harlan, I heard a nasty little rumor
that you dipped your toe
back in the water.
Now, I'm-- I'm hurt
that you didn't even call me.
-You heard wrong.
-Huh.
And if it were true,
you'd be the last man on earth I'd call.
[tense music playing]
Pretty as ever, Belle.
I saw him at the service.
I didn't think he'd show up here.
Oh, thank you. Thanks so much.
-Um… Hi.
-I saw your Aunt Sophia.
-She's looking good.
-Yeah… Yeah.
I'm sorry about dinner the other night,
that wasn't my normal--
You don't usually get high
with married men?
[sighs resignedly]
Where's Scott?
-He had to go to work.
-Mm.
Should I be worried?
I… I know what it must look like,
but it's--
it's just old memories resurfacing.
Nostalgia. It's… It's nothing more.
Do you really believe that?
Look, let's just put it out there.
We've barely seen each other
over the years.
You may not remember much about me,
so I need to clue you in a little.
I was really hoping
that we could be friends.
I'm not saying this to guilt you
or appeal to some girl code nonsense,
but to be straight up honest.
I cut deep, Jenna.
And if you touch my husband,
I will come for you.
[indistinct chatter]
Hey there, I'm Cane Buckley.
I, uh, saw you inside with my folks.
Were you friends with the sheriff or…?
Just paying my respects.
Huh! [chuckles]
You don't remember me, do you?
No.
Well, I haven't seen you
since you were a kid,
but I remember going
to a few of your games.
Your dad and I used to work together.
Your grandfather.
Are you a fisherman or…?
[chuckles softly]
I've been hearing a lot about you, Cane.
I thought you'd make a run at pro ball,
but you found something else to do.
Didn't you?
-Uh, I didn't get your name.
-Emmett Parker.
-Got it.
-May I give you my number?
Your dad used to have my number.
It's just in case he's lost it.
[quietly foreboding music creeping in]
If ever you find yourself
in need of something to do,
other than what you're doing
and who you're doing it with…
please, give me a call.
[foreboding music continues]
[uneasy sting]
What the fuck…
[Marcus] The sheriff was no accident.
He was murdered.
How do you know that?
I think he came across something
that proves Cane is dirty.
-[laughs]
-All right.
[chuckling] No, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Cane may be crooked,
but he is not a killer.
-Okay.
-You seem fired up.
-I'm not.
-You're not thinking clearly.
I know it's a lot to process.
Your brother's in deep shit.
A lot more than you thought.
If someone killed the sheriff,
it was not my brother, I can assure you.
He does not have it in him.
I gotta get back.
[Marcus] Okay.
I wondered where you went.
Right here.
Nice breeze, isn't it?
My dad's been in my head a lot today.
What happened…
I don't wanna put you
in that kind of hurt.
If you wanna stop, we'll stop.
I'm not gonna lie. I'm scared.
The money's helping.
We're starting to breathe again.
Three or four more runs
will get us out of trouble.
Whether you like it or not,
you're good at this.
It's brought you back to life somehow.
I don't wanna lose everything we've built.
Everything my dad built.
The land.
Then we keep going
a little while longer.
Just when I know what you're thinking,
you go and surprise me.
Is that a good thing?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah?
Hey! Got your text.
What's the emergency?
Whoa, okay.
You need to let go of me right now.
Jesus Christ.
-What were you doing with the DEA agent?
-Were you spying on me?
Are you fucking him?
I don't think that's any
of your damn business.
-[Cane scoffs]
-Okay?
[Cane scoffs louder]
-How could you do something so stupid?
-Stupid? Why would it be stupid?
Unless you're involved
in something illegal,
in which case it's your problem, not mine.
Just when I think you can't get any lower.
-I'm not the one stoopin' here.
-Why do you hate me so much?
-Answer that for yourself.
-You still mad about the court hearings?
Seriously? We've moved past that.
My child was taken from me.
I will never move past that.
-I get you don't like the way things went.
-Oh, you get it?
But bottom line is,
you were a danger to your son.
I was declared an unfit mother
because of your testimony!
-You burned a house with your kid in it!
-I pulled him out--
How is that my fault?
You never should've come for me!
You took him from me!
Took? He works at the fish house!
-You can see him anytime you want!
-But he's not with me!
I'm not his mother anymore because of you!
No, because of you!
Take some accountability
for once in your life, Bree!
Jesus Christ, I'm tired of your bullshit!
-You're complaining. You think--
-[thwack]
Oh! Ow!
[Cane groans]
Fuck, man.
[groans]
Ow…
I screwed up.
I own it.
All you had to do was say nothing.
That's it. Nothing.
But instead, you hammered
every fucking nail in my coffin!
[low, aching music playing]
I told the truth.
Oh, Mr. Truth Teller.
The more superior, most perfect Buckley.
I am not superior.
You're just so low in the gutter,
you have to, like, rise up
and meet me at my level,
which is at "fucking miserable"
if you haven't noticed already.
You need a Band-Aid.
You really wanna see me end up in prison?
Golden boys don't go to prison.
Not with fancy lawyers.
I want you to get knocked down.
It's your turn to hurt a little.
You don't know the hell I've gone through
to keep this family going.
Oh, here we go.
You think you're screwing me?
No. You're screwing all of us.
-'Cause Dad is involved in this.
-Dad would never.
Not after what happened to Grandpa.
Mom wouldn't let him.
Do you have any idea how broke we are?
I know things are tough.
I know Mom borrowed from the bank.
Yeah, she did.
And she leveraged
all of our assets for it.
And it's not me
who's gonna take the fall for this.
It's our entire family.
[exhales]
[mouths words, trembling]
Did you have something to do
with what happened to the sheriff?
It wasn't me.
-[exhales shakily]
-Listen to me.
You end things with the agent.
Now.
[tense music thickens]
[door opens and closes]
Oh, my.
How you feeling?
Like I like this.
Mm.
It's been a while.
I'm sorry for that.
We don't need to rehash it.
[sighs]
Hey, when you were looking
at Porter's family today…
Yeah?
…it bothered you
to see them so unaffected, huh?
The word apathetic came to mind.
-Mm.
-Is that the right word?
That works.
I have no idea
what happened with that family.
We're not like them.
-Stronger.
-And more fucked up.
[chuckling] For sure.
[Harlan chuckles softly]
And…
there's something I need to tell you.
Mr. Buckley, sir.
Johnnie Walker on ice?
Please.
Have one with me.
If you want.
More of a gin guy.
Belle told me.
[gentle music stirs beneath silence]
Sorry I showed up this way.
I wanted to meet you
before I dropped a bomb on your life.
I, uh…
I wanted to know you.
Maybe you didn't wanna know me,
so I understand--
Stop, please.
I'm only sorry it took this long.
You look like her.
[music continues]
I didn't know. Bebe never told me.
It's what she wanted.
Your mother was
a far better person than me.
That's for sure.
I was in a bad place back then.
Not sure I'm any better now, to be honest.
Belle tells me you're a lawyer.
I graduated law school.
UT Austin. I haven't, um…
I haven't taken the bar yet.
I bet Bebe was proud of you.
[gentle music rising]
She worked here years ago.
It was a much smaller place.
Just a few employees then.
She was good with people.
So beautiful.
And she had this laugh
that could blow the roof off.
She was here a few summers.
And I was already married.
But we got close.
We both felt guilty the whole time.
Then she up and left one day.
Ended it.
None of what we did was right.
But now,
it sure doesn't seem wrong either.
Come, sit.
Talk to me.
I think we have a lot to talk about.
[gentle music continues]
It's really nice to meet you, Shawn.
In late, up early.
I couldn't sleep. [exhales]
-[Cane grunts]
-Mm.
You gonna tell me what happened,
or we just pretend I don't see it?
It's nothing.
Nothing?
I got into it with Bree.
Bree did that?
With her fist?
We could talk about it.
-Or finish what you started yesterday.
-Mm…
Too late now.
I don't understand you.
What was that even about? Huh?
I was trying to connect with you.
So what, like a hand job at a funeral
was your way of connecting with me?
There was a time when it would've worked.
I don't think you were connecting with me.
I think you were marking your territory.
-Oh, that's bullshit.
-What?
I saw you watching me and Jenna talk.
You wanna go there?
[chuckles softly]
There's nowhere to go.
What I was trying to do
was remind you of the time we were good,
because there was a time.
We are here together right now, okay?
I don't know what you want.
You could start with the truth, Cane.
You've been lying to me for months.
You think I haven't noticed
the late-night phone calls,
the family fighting, you racing off
to the fish house after hours?
I'm busy. There's a lot going on.
I'm running a business, okay?
-There's a lot of pressure on me.
-I was attacked, Cane!
Not robbed, but attacked,
and you still won't tell me the truth.
Baby, everything is gonna be okay.
People are dying around us.
If our daughter is in danger,
damn it, you better tell me!
I don't want to!
I'm trying to protect you
and Savannah, okay?
I know that's not what you wanna hear,
but it's the way it's gotta be!
[low music hums with unease]
-[chuckles derisively]
-Okay?
'Cause I--
Um…
I think I'm gonna take Savannah to Durham
and visit my folks for a while.
Wait.
[uneasy music continues]
So, what? You're-- You're leaving me?
Do you want me to?
We have a life here together.
[music deepens ominously]
["Hang In There"
by Stephen Wilson Jr. playing]
[Peyton slams door]
♪ It's comin' up on two years ♪
♪ It's not right, he's not here ♪
♪ In the passenger seat sayin'
"Boy, would ya go a little slower?" ♪
♪ "You're worrisome, son
Make your old man…" ♪
[imperceptible]
♪ It's more than beaded jewelry ♪
♪ It's more like a prayer ♪
♪ Remindin' me to hang in there ♪
[imperceptible]
♪ It's more than beaded jewelry ♪
♪ It's more like… ♪
[Belle] Am I interrupting?
Just doing my morning AA-ing.
[Belle] Is everything okay?
You want the truth or the bumper sticker?
Go for it. Hit me.
When am I gonna be a part of this family?
You are a part of this family.
Don't be silly.
Don't dismiss me, please. It--
I get it. I've screwed up.
I've exhausted every ounce
of goodwill, but I am trying.
And I'm sober.
And that's a good thing.
But you've been sober before.
Why does that have
to relegate me to the outside?
I have always been
on the fringe of this family.
We have been through this before.
-Okay? Get a little time on your side.
-That's not what I'm talking about.
You set the temperature in this family.
You always have.
I wanna be a part of it.
I wanna be a part of it the way Cane is.
Why-- It's so different for me.
-You are my child too, honey.
-No, I'm what became of your child.
Isn't that what you mean?
My God. See?
You do it to yourself.
You put yourself on the outside.
You want to be included? Earn it.
Stay sober. Show up.
We're all here waiting for you.
I wish you'd seen me as an ally
and not an obstacle.
We could've been
so much more to each other.
None of this would've happened.
You're talking in riddles, hon.
What's really going on, huh?
Just forget about it.
I'll deal with it.
-Deal with what?
-I gotta get ready.
-I'll talk to you later.
-Bree! Come on.
[phone buzzing]
[pensive music playing]
The shrimp season has been pure crap.
But with fall coming,
the blue crab and trout
are coming in strong.
And your father started this place?
The fish house came first
and then the restaurant.
Then we expanded over the years.
Sorry if I'm asking too many questions.
And thank you
for taking the time to show me everything.
-What your family has built is impressive.
-[chuckles softly]
Lawyers are impressive.
I wouldn't encourage this as a career.
It's a dying industry.
But until it does die, or I die,
here I am.
What's next for you?
Go to Texas and study for the bar.
I missed it this year,
so I've applied to take it in February.
I see.
You can always stay here a little longer.
If you want.
Thank you.
-[Cane] Wes.
-Yeah.
Hey. Cane Buckley.
-Yes.
-Thank you for meeting me.
-I know it's last minute.
-Oh, no. Is, uh…
-Is Belle joining us?
-Uh, she's not here.
It's just the two of us.
I thought maybe we could talk alone.
Great.
Look, my mom has done
a total 180 with this whole thing
and, uh, it's just… Well, it's what
I wanted to talk to you about.
We've been working this deal out
for months now,
and I guess I just want to understand
what made it fall apart
so I could talk to her,
and maybe get everything back on track.
Yes, uh, if the issue was the negotiation,
that would be one thing.
What do you mean?
I don't think
the deal points were the problem.
Your mother never even responded
to the finalized terms.
Huh.
Um, okay, so what went wrong?
We met,
we talked through the whole thing,
got real, got personal,
she got cold feet, and, uh, it happens.
Uh, what do you mean, personal?
Look, Cane, I don't want to get involved
in any family drama or marital conflict,
but if you can get your mom
and your dad on board,
I'd still very much like
to make this deal happen.
Me too.
Um… I guess I just don't…
I still don't understand what happened.
I need more context, so…
Call your mom.
And let me know if we can forge ahead.
I'll stand by.
Thank you, Cane, for calling.
[ominous music playing]
Can I help you?
You're in luck.
Grady wants to meet.
My car's outside. I'll take you.
I'll follow.
[gritty music playing]
[man] There he is.
There he is, Mr. Harlan Buckley.
Thank you for making it all the way here.
I know it's quite a trip.
Sorry, I'm a hugger.
You want a drink?
Let's drink. Drinks? Thanks.
So, I wanna know everything about you.
I mean, I googled, obviously,
but I wanna know what's not on Google.
-Please.
-Well, I don't know what you know.
Well, I guess I know the basics.
Your father played a significant role
in the Cali Cartel's descent
on the South in the late '80s.
Sorry. Uh, alleged role.
He died.
Uh, rest in peace.
Tortured to death by a man
who was then also found dead
from an apparent "suicide," wink-wink,
but your family was never indicted.
Excuse me, but I already know all of this.
Of course you do. What am I doing?
I'm fanboying out on you.
It's because you're the GOAT.
[chuckles] I'm not worthy.
Oh, thanks.
Here. You know what?
Take a little stroll with me.
Come on.
By the way, chef's kiss.
The way you smoked that sheriff?
And then immediately replacing him
with your cousin's husband?
Fucking baller move, dude.
[chuckles] Right?
I love it. You don't fuck around.
Your dad's probably like, uh,
thumbs up from the grave, right?
"You're killing it, son."
And correct me if I'm wrong.
You work with your son too.
See? I dig that.
Family man.
This used to belong to my grandparents.
They had it forever. Now it's mine.
So it's just you
at the helm of all of this?
You?
[chuckles]
Are you surprised?
Just… little old me.
I wanted to build something
that was… all mine, you know?
My… legacy, I guess.
Come here, let me show you.
[uneasy music playing]
[knocking on door]
[Jenna] So, what's up?
Uh, I just thought we could talk awhile.
How's he doing?
[sighs]
Who knows?
He just lays there.
Not awake but not asleep.
You?
How are you doing?
Work sucks.
No assignments.
I-- I haven't written a single thing
since I got out here,
and my marriage is dying
faster than my dad.
I'm no journalist, but I'm pretty sure
that's called burying the lede.
What happened?
Scott, uh…
Scott's all about work,
and if it gets too hard
or it interferes
with his train of thought,
he tunes it out.
So… I've been tuned out.
What about you?
Peyton left.
She took Savannah and went to her parents.
For a while.
A while?
Don't ask me what that means,
'cause I don't know.
But I don't think I could see you anymore.
Ah. [chuckles dryly]
And you've come to tell me that.
[gentle music playing]
Yeah.
I like that you stayed a good guy.
Don't.
See?
Still a good guy.
[door opens and closes]
[knocking]
You gotta look at this.
Troy Smith and Curtis Sutton drowned.
-I have to tell you something.
-Right? Then Hoyt Piper goes missing.
Marcus. Marcus, can you stop?
What?
I was wrong about my brother.
I looked in his computer, his files,
his e-mails, everything. There's nothing.
You saw Cane talk to Hoyt
about a drug run with Curtis and Troy.
I made a terrible mistake
bringing you here.
Sheriff Porter gets ironed out
by 4,000 pounds of metal…
Are you listening?
…and this investigation report
is a complete joke.
There's no autopsy.
His body, cremated.
Get this. Guess who finds it.
Your father.
No, my… my dad is not responsible.
No, no, no, Cane is.
Your father's just protecting him.
-No, no, you're wrong, Marcus.
-Yeah. Hey, I know it's a lot to digest.
-I'll help you.
-You can't build a case on lies.
-Babe, you have to stop!
-Hey.
I know it's hard to hear…
[breathing shakily]
…but you're gonna get through it.
It's gonna be okay.
[unsettling music playing]
Ta-da!
Welcome to my humble little opium startup.
We're stockpiling.
You produce this much opium?
We have a friend in Miami
who sends up large-scale orders,
but as an eager entrepreneur,
I'm building my own harvest to go solo.
Come here, check it out.
We're planting the poppies in the spring,
but first we've got to plant all the corn.
Corn?
Uh, yeah, the corn stalks hide it
from the satellites and the drones.
I bet a lot's changed
since your last foray into the biz, huh?
You didn't have to worry
about eyes in the sky,
electronic leashes.
The risks have multiplied,
so loyalty's even more important.
That's why I love
how you keep it in the fam.
I could learn a lot from you.
You know, Harlan, I've been looking
for someone I can depend on.
For a long time now.
-You can count on me.
-Yeah?
All I ask is,
you let me do what I do, my way.
And which way is that?
We use my guys.
I run two shipments a week.
Any more, the risk is too great.
We deal with each other directly.
You don't tell me how to do my job,
I don't tell you how to do yours.
I…
Okay, yeah. You got it.
I should get going.
Oh, uh, just, uh, one more quick thing.
Stevie, come here.
Come on, man.
Now, Stevie here was saying something
behind your back before you got here.
What was it?
[tense music creeping in]
Come on, you had a whole song and dance.
Let him hear it.
Now?
Yeah.
Right now.
You can't trust a Buckley.
That-- that's just what Porter said.
Oh, come on, man. You gotta own it.
And there was more to it than that.
I should be the one
to take over for Porter.
[Grady huffs]
Wow, this is a little awkward. [chuckles]
Harlan, do you think
we need a middleman anymore?
No.
And Steve-o,
what did you want for your cut?
-Twenty-five percent.
-Yikes.
That would eat into your cut, right?
Think that's fair?
No.
Oh, there was one other thing
you said at the end. What was it?
What'd you say? You said this other
one little thing. What'd you say?
[softly] People should know
he killed Porter.
Man, you gotta speak up.
-We're right here. We can barely hear.
-People should know he killed Porter!
[Grady] How's that make you feel?
I told you I run a smooth operation here.
You can be honest.
Communication is…
just so important for that.
Want me to kill Stevie here?
[music turns menacing]
Because if not, I'm gonna let him go.
He could talk to the cops.
I don't know. It's your call.
Please. I was never gonna tell anyone.
Keep your mouth shut and work for me.
Ooh.
Yes. Whatever you say.
[menacing music builds]
Let him go.
Aww.
That's so nice.
Yeah. Go for it.
["Black Leaf" by The Cave Singers plays]
You tried. That's what's important.
[cries frantically]
This is gonna get loud.
[whirring]
[blistering machine gun bursts]
[Grady chuckling]
[grunts]
[Grady laughing]
Oh!
I'm not sure, but… I think you got him.
[laughs]
He's like…
[mimics exaggerated death throes]
[chuckling] It's a real trick
to miss with that thing.
Anyway, I got a really good feeling
about this, Harlan.
Let's have fun! All right?
["Black Leaf" continues playing]
[Grady speaks indistinctly]
[Grady laughing mockingly]
Can you stand up like that?
[Grady laughing]
[gritty music playing]
[music fades]