Okay.
Yeah.
Okay. Okay.
After you talk to her,
I will discuss some options.
Okay. Are you, uh--
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Yeah?
It's my job.
I'll need a second.
-  Oh, man.
-  He can talk.
- Yeah.
-  Hi.
- Hi.
I'm Amy.
- Hi. Sorry.
- Hi.
Well, now that Dr. Pankowitz
has talked to you,
I'm here to talk to you about hospice.
What do you mean a hospice?
Has Dr. Pankowitz...
Shoot.
Eh, shoot, shoot. Um--
You know what? Don't worry about it.
I'm gonna come back later. How about that?
Hi. There was
a little misunderstanding and,
I'm not gonna sugarcoat it, I boned this.
Oh, Jesus, Amy!
Molly. Hey.
I'm so sorry you found out this way.
Hi.
Hi, Molly.
Dr. P.
Uh, we got the results
from the lumbar puncture,
and they showed that the cancer has spread
to the lining of your spinal cord
and your brain.
So you failed?
You said five years.
- I didn't.
- He didn't.
I think we're looking at a few weeks
to a few months.
But we could still do
another round of chemotherapy.
We could do... We could do...
What the fuck... Immunotherapy.
If that's what you want.
I ca... I can't do that.
Okay.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
I can come back at better time.
Well, fuck, Amy.
Now we need you.
Goodbye, Jerry. Thank you.
Bye, Molly.
- Bye, Nikki.
- See you around.
Yeah.
Ooh, welcome.
Let me know
if I can help you with anything.
You gals like puzzles? Or books?
I got so many art supplies.
Hey, you can put anything
on the walls too.
Just don't drill into 'em.
Yeah.
We didn't bring a drill to hospice.
Oh, you'd be surprised.
You'd be surprised.
Hey.
You have the power here.
You tell Amy what you wanna feel and when.
What I want to feel.
Thank you.
I want a different room.
I wanna change rooms.
Hmm. I think they're all
pretty much the same,
but we can make this good.
We can decorate.
Not that painting.
That painting's screwed on.
I think it's a masterwork,
but why don't you tell me what you think
is worst part of this gorgeous painting?
The fishermen.
No, it's the boat.
Hmm.
Actually, the fish.
Why are there so many fish?
Such an in-your-face, like,
obscene amount of fish.
I think my mom is calling.
My phone's not ringing.
Hmm.
- Is it--
- Oh, my God!
How did you know that?
I think I'm starting to be magic.
I believe it.
Mom, hi.
I'm in hospice.
Okay. Okay.
I, uh... I'm here if you need me.
You just tell me
when you need me. I'm nearby.
Where are you?
I'm in the lobby.
Of the hospital?
- Yes.
- Of this hospital?
I'm in the lobby.
How many times do I have to say it?
Where else was I going to be?
I want you here, Mom.
- Hi, there. Are you--
- Gail. My name is Gail.
Mom!
Mom.
Oh, baby girl.
My baby girl.
Hey.
That kid over there was wondering
if he could play with that puzzle
for a little while.
No.
No. Okay. I'll tell him that.
She wants to stick with it.
Is she dying?
No.
But neither are you.
Neither am I, so let's just be cool.
How about search a word?
Hi, Gail. I'm just...
I just need to get my bag.
The nurse is gonna bring a cot in
so I can sleep here.
Oh, good, Gail.
Well, I'll just be in the, um...
the waiting room finishing my puzzle.
- Nikki.
- Yeah.
What you've done for her...
Oh...
Uh, who's taking care of your dogs
while you're gone?
Scotty, my lover.
Would you... Would you like
to finish your puzzle in here?
This is cheese.
This is lemon.
Lemon! No, cheese.
This is sun.
We're gonna have
to start another pile for the sun.
I'll do sun.
Okay, good. And can you also do the mouse?
Oh, I'd love to do the mouse. Thank you.
What happened to your hair?
What?
- Wait, is there something weird about it?
- Yeah.
Oh, my God! What did you do to me?
It wasn't me, man!
It just seems like you might
be coming down with something.
- She always wanted pink hair.
- She wouldn't let me.
It looks dope.
Thank you.
So, as you are filling out those forms,
who would like to hear
about what happens when you're dying?
That's good enough for me.
Death is not a mystery.
It is not a medical disaster.
It is a bodily process,
like giving birth,
or like going to the bathroom,
or coughing,
having an orgasm.
'Cause your body knows what to do.
Your body knows how to die!
How cool is that?
Okay. Here's what to expect.
In the last month of your life,
you're gonna stop getting out of bed.
You're gonna to eat and drink a lot less,
and you're gonna sleep a lot more.
Uh, delirium is common.
And some people say
they get this feeling like...
time stops being real.
Is that something
that you've been feeling?
- Yes!
- Yes.
Okay. Two to three weeks out,
you're gonna need help
with all daily activities.
But my favorite part
of the dying process is--
Amy!
I know. I've been talked to
about my enthusiasm.
I should dial it back. Sorry.
It doesn't work for me right now.
Should I keep going?
Yeah. But will you hold my hand?
Your body knows what's coming
and it goes into a state of ketosis,
which decreases hunger and pain
and it increases the sense of euphoria.
And when you start active dying--
What's active dying?
Oh, active dying is a sacred time.
At least it used to be, and it still is
in some parts of the world.
It's the moment
when you're very close to death,
and your body starts shutting down.
How's everyone doing?
I'm looking at you, Gail.
If, uh, Molly wants to hear it,
I can hear it.
You guys, come here.
I'm good. I'm good. I'm good.
In active dying,
you won't be fully conscious.
And your jaw muscles will relax.
Your breathing changes.
And there might be this gurgling
at the back of your throat,
caused by something, unfortunately,
called terminal secretions.
I know.
And when you are very close to death,
your breathing goes into a cycle
of deep slow breaths and long pauses.
And then eventually, there's a breath out...
that is not followed by a breath in.
And that's it.
- Hey.
- Yeah, yeah.
Can you make sure
that my mouth isn't open when I die?
Okay.
Just don't bite me.
Why would I bite you?
I don't know
why I need you to tell me this,
but please say that you won't bite me.
How long have you had that fear?
I understand that you would not.
It's very intense in here.
I... It's an irrational fear!
Okay. And at a certain time,
if you're just feeling too weak or...
you know, too much pain
or you're just done,
you can talk to me about sedating you,
but then you'll be unconscious.
I-I wanna feel everything
for as long as I can.
Okay, good.
Wait, I forgot to tell you
about the rally!
God! Jesus!
The last week of life,
some people experience
what's called the rally.
And it's this just surge
of energy and mental clarity.
So enjoy the rally.
Just know that you're another step
closer to death, okay?
I fucking love your vibe, Amy!
You're nuts, man!
I didn't know
if you were gonna wanna see me.
Honestly,
I just like making you cry.
Cool.
You in pain?
Yeah.
I had a lot of stuff
that I wanted to tell you in here,
but I'm blanking on everything.
Um, Beth is pregnant.
Oh, that's so good.
- Yeah.
I've been reading a lot of baby books.
And did you know for the first few months
they think everything they see
is a part of them?
Isn't that wild?
Like, they don't know
the difference between themselves
and the rest of the world.
Wow. Yeah, I like that.
Yeah.
Me too.
Hey!
Hey, Johnny!
The fish are really biting today, huh?
Time to get all these goddamn fish!
- Molly.
Molly. Hi.
Oh.
Oh, bye, little fella.
Mom!
Look at this!
Wake up.
Mom, wake up!
Wake up!
Molly, I'm here!
-  Molly.
- Mom.
- Good morning, Molly.
- I've got your morning pills...
- ...check on your blood pressure.
- ...your left arm.
- Molly, over here!
Time isn't real
It's a circle
You're gonna die pretty soon
I've been having these visions.
Like, shit is flying off the walls
and rotating around the room.
Wow!
Like, it felt like I was unlinking
or something.
Like from the world?
Yeah, and also from, like, time?
Hmm.
Like...
I think everything exists at once.
Like, I'm talking to you,
but I'm also talking
to every version of you I've ever known.
And it's all in the room with me.
Holy shit.
Like the version of me from 2009
when I got the same hairstyle as you?
Yeah.
Is it scary?
No.
I can see how much pain she's in.
What should I do?
Well, take a breath.
'Cause it is very common
for people to hold on
when they're waiting
for something to resolve
or they're just concerned about
causing their loved one a lot of pain.
You think she's worried about you?
No.
Not me.
I just wish I could see into the future.
I wish I could see you when you're old.
Oh, that? I mean,
we're basically almost there.
That's gonna be exactly
whatever you think it's gonna be.
It's like, "Oh, hello.
I take art classes at the museum,
and I have loose mints
that are rolling around in my purse.
And I... My breath smells like crayons,
and my farts sound like little marbles
being dropped on a floor."
I wish...
I wish you could be there for that too.
Did you call Noah yet to tell him?
No. I'm...
No.
Oh, hey.
I just matched with someone.
Oh. Whew. Just in the nick of time.
Oh.
Look at that.
"What are you up to?"
Um, funny that you asked.
Where have you been all my life?
Yeah.
This is a corner piece. Yes!
And that's for me.
Hey.
Hi.
What's... What are you doing here?
Gail called me.
Molly wanted me
to play percussion for her.
Gail said she's been listening
to a lot of classical music.
-  Hey, man.
- Hey.
- I don't want to put this on you...
- I thought it would be a nice surprise.
...but it is actually insane
what is going on here.
She broke into my phone.
Guilty. I used her face.
- Mom.
- While I was sleeping, she did that to me.
Is this real, or am I hallucinating again?
I hope it's real.
And her master plan was
to get in touch with Noah
and then she wanted me
to get back together with him,
so that you would be happy.
I'm not... I'm not really sure.
Mom.
You said you would
be respectful of boundaries.
With you, not Nikki.
Oh, my God.
She thinks that you're worried
about leaving me alone.
If that's the case,
you can completely not worry about me.
Like, I am gonna be okay,
and I'm cool. Like, I'm good.
Just don't,
don't even keep that in your mind.
I'm not... I'm good. I'm okay.
Okay, well, I hope not that okay.
Noah.
I'm sorry
that I asked her to do this with me
right when you were beginning
to make a life together.
Oh, I'm not sorry.
She loves you.
With everything that she has.
I'm not sorry about that.
I think that you should break up
with your girlfriend.
It's my dying wish.
Whoa. Don't break up with your girlfriend.
That's... I don't--
You should break up with your girlfriend
or I'll haunt the shit out of you
in your dreams.
- Why is everyone being insane?
- We broke up.
Oh, Okay.
Oh.
Yeah.
- When did you break up?
- Gail...
When did you break up?
Um, like a week ago. So...
Hmm.
- Yeah, I didn't... That doesn't mean...
- Oh, no.
I know. Of course not.
I didn't come to hospice today
trying to hook up.
That's not... No.
You've got a big instrument.
- Oh, God.
- Yeah. Thanks, Gail.
Um... You wanna see what I can do with it?
- No.
No.
If you gotta go, you can...
You don't have to...
- Or you can wait. Okay.
- I want to.
I...
I didn't think that I was capable...
of loving someone this much.
But I know I can now.
It's nice.
Yeah, that's how I felt
when Winter was born.
- Hmm.
- It's crazy. It's... Yeah.
Yeah.
For me, it's like I'm never gonna be there
at the start of someone's life,
like at the beginning.
But I am gonna be there at the end.
And I'm just gonna love this person
right up until the end.
That's amazing, Nikki.
Probably go ahead and love you too.
FYI.
Got it.
Oof.
That's him.
I don't wanna go,
but I got a five-star rating,
and I'm not gonna fuck with that.
- I understand.
- Yeah, I know.
I know you do.
Walk me out?
I wasn't in the running,
I wasn't in the race
You move in a way
That I've known before
Now I want your love, heart and soul
-  Tired eyes, tears that dried
-  Leaving you ain't easy now
-  On the bed where the love has died
-  Loving you's the harder part
-  Through the door you go
-  You never want me for myself
Now I've needed you right
From the very start
Everything you said was to the point
-  Oh, won't you even try to?
-  Can't you try to?
Give a little bit of heart and soul
Give a little bit of love to grow
And don't you make me beg for more
Give a sign, I need to know
A little bit of heart and soul
Whoa.
What is going on here?
It's the rally!
We think it's the rally.
That was the heart
Of the love we shared
-  Do you keep a secret left untold?
-  Is all that I need
Can't give love, heart or soul
I used to have a lover
With a Midas touch
I turned to gold but he turned to dust
Left me for another, I turned to stone
Now give me love, heart and soul
-  Tired eyes, tears that dried
-  Living in a fantasy
There's never any room to breathe
Hoping every waking hour
You'll turn around
And say that we can start
Everything you did just said it all
-  Oh, won't you even try to?
-  Can't you try to?
Give a little bit of heart and soul
Give a little bit of love to grow
How's the water, honey?
It's good.
I'm gonna be outside.
The labor and delivery nurse
told me you have 20 minutes,
and then a rich person's gonna
come have a baby in here.
Yeah.
I thought it would feel good.
But it just hurts.
Oh, honey.
I think I'm ready.
Okay.
Good.
I'll go back to the room...
and talk to Amy.
Maybe she'll have some sedation option.
Mom...
I know.
I already know.
Anything you could say to me,
My body did a really good job.
Oh...
It did so good.
Okay, I have the first dose here for you.
Gonna ease your pain. It's gonna make
your breathing so much easier.
Know what?
Honestly,
it's not that fucking serious.
Let's get this show on the road.
I'm kind of excited.
You know how many plans and trips...
I've had to cancel
because I wasn't feeling well?
And now it's like I get to go on a trip
that's just for me.
- Yeah.
-  Okay.
I am so proud of you.
And I love you.
And I am so grateful for you.
You are my favorite person
in the whole wide world.
I'm here.
I'm here and I got you.
Oh, shit.
Thank you for not biting me.
Our revels now are ended.
These are actors,
As I foretold you, were all spirits
And melted in the air, into thin air:
And, like the baseless fabric
of this vision,
The cloud-capp'd towers,
the gorgeous palaces,
The solemn temples,
the great globe itself,
Shall dissolve
And, like this insubstantial
pageant faded,
Leave not a rack behind.
We are such stuff
As dreams are made of, and our little life
Is rounded with a sleep.
No!
You're terrible. I can't...
Tell me...
Hey.
Sorry we're late.
Hi, Winter. How's school?
Well, I woke up
This morning without you
Don't ask me how, but I got through
The floor of this room
I've been pacing
Trying to drown out
The sound my heart is making
It's calling for you
Well, I woke up
This morning without you
Don't ask me how, but I got through
The floor of this room, I was pacing
Trying to drown out
The sound my heart was making
It was calling for you
Calling for you
Oh, oh, oh