Previously on Prison Break:
Yes. I'd like the number
for Channel 11 News, please.
Hang up the phone now.
This is Michael Scofield.
I'm at the Cutback Motel, room 11.
And I want to turn myself in.
Where is that?
It's Holland,
where I grew up. You know that.
It's beautiful.
This message is for Maricruz.
I'll be there in the airport.
In Ixtapa, waiting for you.
Hi. My name is Sara, and I'm an addict.
Hi, Sara.
I'm just looking to do my time.
I don't want any trouble.
Hey! Break it up, convicts.
This isn't fun, what was fun was
when Caroline and I talked about you...
...and the schoolboy crush
that you had on her.
He proposed to her.
- Hey!
- Terrence!
I'm leaving!
Terrence, listen to me.
Just listen. So many people have suffered
because of this, because of you.
But when the press get here,
you can tell the truth.
You can end this.
- Sorry.
- Terrence, no!
We interrupt this program
for a special news bulletin.
It's breaking news
out of Cutback, Montana.
Lincoln Burrows
and Michael Scofield...
...two of the prisoners who broke out of
Fox River State Penitentiary in Illinois...
...have continued to elude the authorities,
leaving a trail of crime in their wake.
And today,
they left behind something else.
My name's Lincoln Burrows,
and I'm innocent.
- We're done.
- No other way out.
Next time you hold a press conference,
do it from a room with a back door.
Just let me think.
This is the Montana Highway Patrol.
Michael Scofield and Lincoln Burrows...
...you need to exit
with your hands in the air.
- This is a warning.
- You got line of sight from there?
Exit with your hands up.
- What about him?
- Him? He's useless.
Dead body?
We got fingerprints everywhere.
You worried someone
will pin a murder on you?
What's your plan?
Leave the body, walk out the door?
Yes. That's exactly
what we're gonna do.
Michael Scofield and Lincoln Burrows,
you need to exit with your hands up.
- FBI, hold your fire.
- FBI?
- I have Burrows and Scofield.
- Start rolling.
We're coming out. Hold your fire.
- Hold up, who are you?
- Federal Bureau of Investigation.
- We're going to Billings.
- Wait, let me see that ID again.
- Okay, okay.
- Drop the gun!
Everybody calm down
and this won't get ugly.
All right. I want keys
to both of the cop cars, now!
- Don't do it!
- Don't listen to him!
- Get the keys. Linc, get in the car.
- What's going on?
Getting out of here
before anyone gets hurt.
Lincoln, start it.
- Come on, come on!
- This is your last chance.
- I'm not gonna tell you again.
- One more step, and I drop him.
Come on!
Open my door.
Welcome back.
- You feeling...?
- Much better.
- Update?
- Okay, you got it.
Yeah.
You got a lead on something?
One of the CO's from Fox River,
Brad Bellick.
Got locked up last night
for the murder of another guard.
Wait. We're looking for CO's now?
What about the escapees?
- Scofield, Burrows?
- Nothing on them currently.
Also, Franklin's wife...
...was taken into custody
in North Dakota.
His wife?
Line two.
This is Agent Mahone.
How long ago?
I'll make you a deal. You don't move
a muscle, I won't blow your head off.
- No one's gonna hurt you, Greg.
- Where are we going, Michael?
We can't keep driving. Lost Steadman.
- Sara's in the wind--
- Shh, shh. Turn it up.
--murder of Terrence
Steadman, President Reynolds' brother.
The president could not be reached
as she continues to tour the Midwest...
...shoring up support in key states.
For entrepreneurs and orange
growers, iron workers and artists...
...the American dream is alive
and well for all of us.
Reynolds travels to Colorado today...
...for a scheduled appearance
in Denver that--
- Pull over.
- What for?
Just pull over.
Get out. Over here.
- You want to drop off this kid?
- Later.
We should get rid of Kellerman too.
We don't need him.
Actually, we do. We still have assets.
It's just a question
of how we use them.
Bradlee.
Nurse.
You ain't no nurse.
You're right about that.
That's a pretty shiner you got,
captain.
Must make you think
about the times...
...you walked around here
in your fancy guard outfit.
Turning a blind eye
to everything you saw that was wrong.
"Who, me? Oh, I didn't see nothing."
How's that blind eye feel now?
- You son of a bitch.
- You get used to it.
Hear old one-eyed Jack's
gonna be getting screwed in the socket.
- Over my dead body.
- No.
A dead man can't feel a beat down.
And you got a lot more
coming your way.
Come on, now. Let's go.
It'll take the feds a while
to figure that out.
What time is it?
- A little after 9.
- It's gonna be tight.
Four hundred and fifty miles
in six hours.
- What do you think?
- Gotta move now.
Eyes front.
Hey, look at this.
- It's perfect, you ready?
- Yep.
Puerto Rico.
Here, Larry, this is for you.
What about this?
What is this? This is too small.
Why didn't it float? Why didn't it...?
I need more wood.
Wood floats.
This'll work.
Hey, man.
We were just wondering
if you could buy us some beer.
Yeah, sure.
Can I get some food for my dog too?
Do whatever thing you gotta do, man.
You can keep a beer for yourself.
Huh? Oh, no.
My dad used to drink.
You're gonna wanna see this.
We've shut down every freeway
in central Montana.
- So far, no sign of them.
- Go wider.
Put troopers on 90 and 94,
all the way through Wyoming.
Call Whitefish. Have them lock down
the Canadian border at 15.
--have continued
to elude the authorities...
...leaving a trail of crime in their wake.
And today,
they left behind something else.
My name's Lincoln Burrows,
and I'm innocent.
I escaped from Fox River Penitentiary...
...because I was sentenced to death
for a crime I did not commit.
I did not murder Terrence Steadman.
He committed suicide last night
in the Cutback Motel...
...30 miles outside from his home
in Blackfoot, Montana.
He killed himself out of fear...
...fear of the people who've been
hiding him for the past three years.
The same people
who want my brother dead.
They don't want you to know
who they are, but know this:
They've stolen billions of dollars
and murdered dozens of innocent people.
And yet, they plaster our faces
on the news, and tell you to be afraid.
They are a group
of multinationals, corporate interests.
Together, they're known
as The Company.
They are working
with the highest levels of government...
...including
the president of the United States.
- Damage control.
- They've stolen billions of dollars.
Before this hits page one.
- It's already airing, sir.
- Start a wildfire in Florida!
Find a storage unit full of Arabs!
I do not care!
As long as it's
not about Lincoln Burrows!
- And they operate with impunity.
- Go!
Under the cover of the Secret Service,
the people meant to protect and serve.
Much blame has been placed...
...on another innocent person,
Dr. Sara Tancredi.
Do we know how long
the videotape lasts?
Twenty-six minutes, beginning to end.
It's all online.
I know I can't ask you
for another chance.
I can only hope that by now
you've found your safe haven.
Start a transcript. I need every word.
And I put you in a place
that's every doctor's nightmare.
I wish I could do things differently.
Call Montana. Send an agent
to talk to the cameraman.
I wanna know what he saw, heard,
what they're wearing.
- Anything he can give us.
- Yeah.
Special Agent Alexander Mahone,
is responsible for multiple deaths.
He murdered not only
John Abruzzi and David Apolskis...
...but also the last fugitive
he was assigned to chase...
...a man names Oscar Shales.
A man who escaped from prison
two years ago...
...who remains one of this country's
most wanted...
- ...despite the fact he'll never be found.
- Guy's nuts.
They'll do whatever it takes
to make the deaths look official.
Like they happened in the line of duty.
Disappearances...
- Hey, thank you.
- Sure. Here you go.
What's the wood for?
I'm building a raft.
I need more wood
if I'm gonna make it to Holland.
- Holland?
- Yeah.
You want to see it? The raft?
You're gonna try to get
from here to Holland in that?
Uh-huh.
- Yeah, good luck, Gilligan.
I'm gonna take a leak.
Um, how are you gonna know
where you're going?
Do you have like a map or anything?
Yeah, I do.
It's right...
Oh, it's right here.
- That's your map?
- Uh-huh.
Well, I really hope you make it.
You know, every morning I wake up
and wonder...
...what it would be like
to just disappear.
And you're just gonna do it.
I think it's great.
Okay.
What happened to your arm?
My dad drinks too.
What's going on?
- Oh, nothing.
- No, no. No, no, don't...
- I...
- Let me go.
- I just want to fix it. I just want to make--
- Let me go. Stop.
Matt, will you take me home, please?
No, I...
Freak.
All right, now, Brad. How we doing?
I could be better.
Yeah, that's a nasty contusion,
but it should go down in about 24 hours.
I got your paperwork here
for your transfer back to gen pop.
Already?
Move them in, move them out.
You know the policy.
- Katie.
- Um-hm?
You look nice today.
You've worked here
over 10 years, right?
Something like that.
That's a long time we've been friends.
If you think I can pull some strings to
keep you out of gen pop, I can't do that.
Please, please,
you can't send me back there.
Do you want that responsibility,
knowing what they'll do to me?
Just listen, please. One more night.
Just let me stay here tonight.
I know you can do that.
And when you go home,
just leave that door open for me.
They hung a sheet behind their heads
on the wall.
Uh, one of them,
the guy with the gun...
...he found it while Burrows and Scofield
talked about how far they had to go.
Uh...
Scofield said something
about 450 miles in six hours.
- Four hundred fifty miles to where?
- I don't know.
Four hundred fifty miles in six hours.
Any point on this circle
could be their final destination.
Seventy-five miles per hour,
stopping for gas.
- It's doable.
- Yeah.
Where are they?
I'm not sure. I still need more time.
This can't happen fast enough.
They've already done irreparable damage.
Scofield made the video
in a storage facility...
...somewhere between Great Falls
and Helena not long after sunrise.
From there, the witness said...
...that they had 450 miles
to get to where they were going.
There's Seattle, Portland,
Salt Lake, Denver...
- Denver?
- Yes, what?
The president is speaking there
this afternoon.
- Three o'clock.
- Six hours after they made the video.
They're going after the president.
A tape made by escaped convicts...
...Lincoln Burrows
and Michael Scofield...
...was immediately dismissed by the
Justice Department as entirely baseless...
...which brings us back to the story we'll
continue to follow throughout the day.
Terror threat
has been raised to orange...
...as a storage unit rented by several
Arab-Americans was suddenly seized.
They buried it. Dumped it off
the front page and buried it.
It's what they do.
They can spin it all they want.
It's out there now.
Give it time, the tape is gonna work.
- It's a Hail Mary if we don't get to her.
- Getting to her is easy.
- What we do after's the problem.
- Which is why it has to happen quickly.
Once anyone knows we have her,
the curtain comes down.
- I'll notify the White House to cancel--
- No.
If there's a change, the brothers
will know and go back into hiding.
We've found them before.
We can find them again.
These are not pets, Agent Wheeler.
Yeah, thanks. I'm pretty clear on that.
But if you use the commander in chief
as bait, that's not gonna--
You have a problem
with the way that I do things?
Yeah.
And I'm not the only one.
Is that right?
Internal Affairs asked me to run all your
moves through them from here on out.
Then get a pen...
...and make sure
you get this word for word.
The president's day does not change.
The only lead we have is that we know
where these men are headed.
So we're gonna
keep quiet about this...
...and let them come.
Now get out of my office.
They're two of the most
recognizable faces in America.
How do they think they're gonna get
anywhere near the president?
Because it's not
just the two of them anymore.
I'm gonna go take a closer look
at that video.
If I may, sir, the president...
...are you certain
we should keep her in the dark on this?
Because there is...
...a scenario where she could be useful.
It is her ass on the line, sir.
I think we're pretty clear...
...she's been known to get her hands
dirty when that line gets too close.
Maybe we should let her know...
...just how close it is.
No.
They did a good job masking the room.
No reflections or flares.
Audio markers: church bells,
construction, traffic. Anything?
The room tone tells us they were
in a large space, 100,000 cubic feet.
So the kid with the camera,
his story matches up.
We clocked the quality of light
with the time of day.
It fits his wheres and whens.
All right, content.
The usual tells: eyes, hands, feet.
Burrows, we're able to baseline
off his trial footage...
...so we got even more clarity there.
I escaped from Fox River Penitentiary...
...because I was sentenced to death
for a crime I did not commit.
- I did not murder Terrence Steadman.
- Okay, there.
The eyes. See it?
A slight shift to the left, then up.
Yeah, the blink rate's
up here verses the pattern.
He committed suicide last night
in the Cutback Motel...
...30 miles outside from his home
in Blackfoot, Montana.
- He's lying.
- Seems so.
Okay, here. Burrows, arms folded.
He's protecting himself.
Not a lot of confidence in these words.
Like they happened in the line of duty.
They mean something
other than what he's saying.
The posture. Shoulders in for emphasis.
He wants your attention here.
Okay, there.
- Adam's apple.
- Zoom in, zoom in.
See? He's swallowing.
Throat's dry. That's a lie.
- Yeah.
- His behavior is textbook.
If there's anything about
what they plan on doing in Denver...
...they're gonna tell us.
- Say it that way, it plays too earnest.
- Of course it will, it's the truth.
But the truth sends them home
to their wife and kids.
Lies will keep them busy.
I'm not telling a lie
to the whole country.
- It's our one chance to say it how--
- Say whatever the hell you want.
Tell them you're the Green Lantern.
I know how
they break down these tapes.
I've done it. Every detail matters.
Bin Laden crosses his legs right over left,
something different than left over right.
It's not the same message.
To them, it is.
If you want this plan to work,
whatever you say with your mouths...
...you need to say something different
with your bodies and eyes.
Slightly up and to the left.
Yes.
Much blame has been placed
on another innocent person...
President's motorcade is rolling in.
No sign of the brothers.
Right there.
What's Scofield doing with his hand?
We've been throwing them fastballs.
What do you say we mix it up a little?
Like what?
I think it's Morse code.
- For what?
- Well, right now, we got a phrase:
"The water is warm."
Any idea what that might mean?
- What the hell does that mean?
- Nothing.
It'll take the feds a while
to figure out.
We have teams checking the
surrounding counties for water temps.
Yeah, it might be a message
to an accomplice.
The North Platte River
runs through the city. Maybe--
It doesn't mean anything.
He's with an ex-Secret Service guy.
They're spoon-feeding us
every lead they want us to follow.
So this is a distraction
while they go after the president.
They had to know
the tape would be discredited.
that we'd talk to the cameraman.
- There's something else going on.
- Much blame has been placed...
...on another innocent person,
Dr. Sara Tancredi.
Sara, if you're listening...
...I know I can't ask you
for another chance.
I only hope by now
you've found your safe haven.
I took advantage of you,
of your commitment to help others...
...and put you in a place
that's every doctor's nightmare.
Sara, if you're listening...
...I know I can't ask you
for another chance.
I only hope by now
you've found your safe haven.
I took advantage of you,
of your commitment to help others...
...and put you in a place
that's every doctor's nightmare.
...of your commitment to help others...
...and put you in a place
that's every doctor's nightmare.
I've considered many ways to apologize,
but I must arrive at one.
It's more of the same here. Uh...
Body language, his tells. If you ask me,
it doesn't look like he means this at all.
- Don't care what it looks like. Play it.
- I don't see how--
Play it again.
I only hope by now
you've found your safe haven.
I took advantage of you,
of your commitment to help others...
...and put you in a place
that's every doctor's nightmare...
His voice.
Would you say he sounds sincere...
...when talking to her as opposed
to talking about their crimes?
I guess you could say that.
I did say that. Would you say that?
I wish I could do this differently,
but it's too late for that now.
- Yeah.
- It's too late for you and for others.
People murdered...
This isn't about Terrence Steadman
and it's not about their innocence.
- What?
- They're not after the president.
They're going after the doctor. I want
everything we got on Sara Tancredi.
Friends, families, pen pals.
If anybody wrote her a thank-you note,
I wanna know where the hell they are.
Now!
Sara Tancredi. Dad dead, mom dead.
E-mail account shows a minimal list
of contacts, with very little activity.
Credit cards used mostly for groceries,
sporadic clothing shopping...
...and the purchase
of single movie tickets.
And ob-gyn records tell us...
...she's had very little in the way
of sexual relationships recently.
Tell you the truth, I would say
the bulk of her life was her work.
Excuse me, sir. Where are you going?
Apparently, we took out a janitor.
When it all comes down,
all of this will get cleared up.
Well, it ain't coming down
if we don't get Sara.
She'll be here.
I wanna speak to my brother.
We gotta start thinking
about what to do if she doesn't show.
Or if she does.
What if the only reason
this guy's helping us...
...is to get whatever information
Sara has?
What if this is just one giant setup?
Well, good night.
About time you come home.
You out with that Feytek boy again?
- Sasha.
- No!
You may look like me...
...but you take after your mom when
it comes to the boys, now, don't you?
Hopefully with a little better taste.
Damn it, girl,
you are gonna show me some respect.
- I know Sara didn't have many friends.
- She's sort of a loner.
But you were her friend.
I like to think so, yes.
But you have no idea
where she is now?
No.
This is a transcript
of the Scofield-Burrows videotape.
I highlighted the part
where he talks directly to Sara.
Mean anything to you?
No.
You have no idea where
she might meet him, if that's his plan?
No.
Is Brad Bellick
still here in the infirmary?
Yeah. Why?
You must be loving this.
I didn't drive all this way to gloat.
Well, then, what the hell
you come here for?
First, I really gotta tip my cap to you.
You've managed to draw a bead on
the convicts more than my own staff.
Well, thanks for the "attaboy."
But as you can see, the correctional
system doesn't share your gratitude.
I won't take much of your time.
I have a few questions.
- About?
- Sara Tancredi.
She listed you as a reference
on herjob application to work here.
You know her well?
I'd know her a lot better if you can
get my ass moved to ad seg.
I have no influence with the DOC.
You know that.
You want my help, you do.
I'll talk to the warden,
see what I can do.
Right after you give me some answers.
Scofield likes to communicate
with Sara via coded message.
You recognize anything here?
Anything that he may be
trying to tell her?
No. I mean, he's saying he's sorry.
Not that that's gonna do any good
with Dr. Cold Shoulder.
But...
What?
Ad seg.
Yeah.
You see here?
Where it says this stuff about
"another chance" and "safe haven"?
- That's out of the Big Book.
- What big book?
Alcoholics Anonymous.
Sara's in recovery.
Yeah, I'm aware of that.
Those are the names
of some of the chapters...
...in the book they use in AA.
Do you have a copy
of the Alcoholics Anonymous book?
Sara, if you're listening...
...I know I can't ask you
for another chance.
I can only hope by now
you've found your safe haven.
I took advantage of you,
of your commitment to help others.
I put you in a place
that's every doctor's nightmare.
I've considered many ways to apologize,
but I must arrive at one.
- It's getting late.
- I know.
She's not here.
I know that too.
There is a chance
she didn't get the message.
Or maybe she's just sick of all this.
I mean, the girl bailed on you
back in Gila.
What makes you think
she's gonna come running back now?
The same thing that's been keeping us
going for the last three months.
- Faith.
- Yeah, well...
Reality's kicking faith's ass, man.
Michael Crane...
- Look--
- Wait, wait.
- Wait? Man, we can't wait anymore.
- Listen, listen.
Once again, Michael Crane...
...please report to the front desk.
You have a telephone call.
Yeah, Sara Tancredi.
Right, she might be with him.
Just--
Yes. Just call the local police in Akron
and tell them to get everyone they have...
...over to St. Thomas Hospital now.
Um, Michael Crane.
I think you've got a phone call for me.
Here you go.
- Thank you.
- Um-hm.
This is Mr. Crane.
It sounded better than origami.
Even if you got the message,
I wasn't sure you'd respond.
I couldn't get to you in time.
This is the only thing I could think of.
I swore I'd leave you alone...
...but I had to contact you.
Because I have something?
How'd you know?
Michael, back in Gila,
I was coming back to you.
Somebody grabbed me...
...and they, um, told me that my father
had given me something.
Did someone hurt you?
I got away.
Uh...
Michael, I want for this to be over.
That makes two of us.
Do you think that's possible?
With your help, yes.
It's just a question of looking
at whatever it is your father gave you.
It's just...
It's just a key.
Well, we'll figure it out.
Together.
I like the sound of that.
Me too.
Hello, Paul.
Madame President, it's been a while.
I know. I'm calling to apologize.
Okay.
I'm so sorry.
It all just got away from me.
And I ended up hurting the one person
who's always been at my side.
I want you to come home, Paul.
We can fix this together.
But not with those brothers...
...running around the country, tearing
down the very office you helped me build.
Caroline.
I want to make it up to you.
Please bring them in, Paul...
...and everything can go back
to the way it was.
I have to go now. I'll see you soon.
Did you talk to Sara?
In a few days, this should all be over,
one way or the other.
Absolutely.