Ana, look at me. You're gonna be fine.
Ana, listen to me.
You're going to the hospital.
You're gonna be fine. Just hold on, baby.
I need some help here! Help!
I need help!
- What happened to her?
- She was attacked.
- We got a puncture wound here.
- Excuse me, sir. Excuse me.
She's bleeding out. Call up to Surgery.
Tell them we're coming now.
- Is she gonna be okay?
- How long has she been bleeding like this?
- Uh, I don't know.
- How long?
- Uh, half an hour.
- She's crashing.
All right, let's bag her and move.
My wife was brought in. Carrie Hopewell.
I'm so sorry, Mr. Hopewell.
The doctor will give...
You can't tell me anything else?
- Not at this time. I'm sorry.
- All right, thanks.
- She's in surgery.
- They said that you brought her in.
- What happened?
- I don't know. She was attacked.
- Attacked? By who? Where?
- I don't know.
- You don't know who, don't know where.
- Hey, take it easy.
- What exactly do you know?
- Take it easy.
You just happened to be the one
who found her.
Listen, she was outside The Forge.
Okay? That's where I live.
Yeah, I know where you live.
I'm not an idiot, Hood.
Whatever she's caught up in
has got something to do with you.
The shit that's gone on
since you've been here.
- If she doesn't make it...
- She's gonna make it.
- Shut up.
- Mr. Hopewell.
I'm Dr. Granger. Your wife is stable.
She's lost a good deal of blood
and she was bleeding internally...
but there doesn't seem
to be organ damage.
We normally have to report injuries
on this scale to the police, but...
I've already called it in.
- Where is she?
- She's in post-op.
We'll get her moved to her room
in about an hour.
Thanks.
Hood.
This is not over.
Sweet Jesus.
What, you've never seen
a dead body before?
No, I just never had you pegged
as a slumlord.
Would it kill you to slap a coat of paint
on this place?
Maybe get some rattan furniture,
a nice throw rug?
I remember you, motherfucker.
Hi.
Out for a swim?
It's beautiful out here.
I hope you don't mind.
I found it in the closet.
No.
Not at all.
She gonna make it?
Yeah.
Yeah, it looks that way.
I never should have left her with him.
Not for nothing, but she put a lot of holes
in that Ukrainian motherfucker.
Dude was leaking all over the place.
Are you just going to stand there,
or are you going to pour me a drink?
- I'm all out of them little umbrellas.
- Fuck you, Sugar Daddy.
We just buried a body together.
We tight now.
That bad?
Rabbit?
End of days, man.
So, what are you gonna do?
What you should do, what we both should do,
is get the fuck out of Dodge.
I can't.
I can't. I brought him here.
I led him straight to her.
So, then, what do we do?
You don't do anything.
You stay as far away from me as possible.
- Hey, now wait...
- Hey, I mean it. Both of you.
- And you?
- I'm gonna kill him.
I always meant to.
Olek...
was our brother.
Let's go.
Who are you?
What time is it?
- It's not important right now.
- Just tell me.
- It's around 11:30.
- What day?
- Jesus.
- What day is it?
It's Monday.
- The kids.
- Max is in school.
I let Deva have the day off
after everything that she's been through.
- We have to get them.
- You're in no condition to go anywhere.
Carrie, cut it out.
I know how this must seem to you,
and I'm sorry for all of it...
but you have to trust me right now.
Baby, that is a pretty
tall order right now.
- We're all in danger.
- You hit your head.
- You're not thinking straight.
- Listen to me.
We have to get the kids
and get out of Banshee right now.
- Come on.
- You're bleeding, Carrie.
I'm fine. Just drive.
I'll get Deva and be out in a minute.
- Hey, what are you doing?
- I'm going to get Max.
You're in no shape to drive.
Yeah?
Hood,
I need you to take a look at my report...
on that school business
and then sign off on it...
when you get a chance.
There.
What?
You shot and killed two guys,
got Xavier breathing down your neck...
and you better believe this report is
gonna be read as high up as he can take it.
If I was you, I'd wanna read every word.
I trust you.
One thing about our people,
they raise you to respect your elders.
Something the rest of the world
seems to have forgotten.
- I bought you something.
- Really?
Thank you.
Why don't you try it on after you've eaten.
I'd like you to come with me
to a meeting today.
What for?
I need someone I can trust.
You trust Burton, don't you?
I do, completely.
But Burton is, uh, limited.
You, on the other hand, are not.
- Mrs. Hopewell. You're awake.
- How long was I out?
Just a couple of minutes
would be my guess.
You know you're in a hospital gown?
Yeah.
I changed your bandage.
You were bleeding through.
This is the first time I've ever treated
one of the parents.
Oh, I don't think
you should be standing just yet.
- I've called for an ambulance.
- Thank you.
Mrs. Hopewell, I really think you
should wait for the ambulance.
Mrs. Hopewell!
Mrs. Hopewell?
Ms. Lymon, hi.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. I need to get Max.
He's at recess now.
- You're bleeding.
- No, that's from before.
Listen, I'm sorry to barge in like this.
I'm just gonna get Max and go.
No. No, no.
- Max! No! Max!
- Wait... Mrs. Hopewell.
No, get away from him!
He's gonna take him.
- Help me.
- What? What's going on?
He's gonna take him.
Max!
Max! Max!
Max! Where's Max?
Max. My baby. Max!
Max!
Help. Help me!
Okay, so I just need to be clear on this.
You went to the school
before Max was abducted.
His teacher said you saw him
sitting on a bench...
so you knew he was in danger.
- I knew he would come for him.
- Who? Who came for him?
You can't help me.
Carrie, you have to let us try.
Every second counts here.
- Hey.
- What, are you done at the school?
Yeah, the FBI took it over.
Excuse me. Yeah, I just heard from Xavier.
- They're gonna be here any minute.
- Okay. Why is she not in the hospital?
She raised hell when
they tried to take her.
It's the only thing she'd agree to do.
Sorry.
I wasn't in time.
It's all my fault.
She's in shock.
We need to get her back to the hospital.
They're telling me
she never even checked out.
I'm not going back to the hospital.
It's okay, deputy. I'll take it from here.
It just doesn't add up.
Yeah,
just give me a few minutes with her.
Thank you.
- You okay?
- It was Rabbit. He was at the playground.
Hey, hey, hey. He's not gonna hurt him.
- He's not gonna hurt Max.
- You don't know that.
He's using him to get to you and me.
- That's what he wants.
- He's gonna kill us.
He's not gonna kill anyone.
You have no idea what
he will or will not do!
I won't let anything happen
to your family.
I promise. I'll find Rabbit.
You don't have to. He's already found you.
Emmett, will you keep an eye
on Deva for me?
Sure, Gordon.
I mean it.
Do not let her out of your sight.
Understood.
I wanna talk to my wife alone.
Get the fuck out.
Who has our son, Carrie?
My father.
Your father?
You mean the one that died
when you were 13?
That father?
Yes.
Jesus Christ. Sheriff Hood.
What the hell happened to her?
Mrs. Hopewell, she was attacked yesterday.
And now they've grabbed her son.
And she was the one who was assaulted by
those bikers a few weeks ago, wasn't she?
- Yes.
- Has it occurred to anyone else here...
that Mrs. Hopewell is far and away
the unluckiest woman in Pennsylvania?
Obviously she's mixed up in something.
You think?
Did she get a look at whoever took the boy?
She may have. She's still very upset.
But the teacher,
she saw an older man in a dark suit.
I want a sketch artist
here within the hour.
And if they can't get anyone local...
get somebody on a goddamn chopper
from Quantico.
Do you have anything else for me?
- We're just getting into it, so...
- Yeah.
Deputies, could I have
your attention, please?
As of right now,
this is officially a federal investigation.
You will all brief Agent Carlson
and McAvoy...
on any interviews
that you've conducted thus far...
as well as any and all evidence
gathered at the scene.
I've got a team on the way here from D.C.,
but until they arrive...
you will be assisting us
with the legwork.
This is a felony kidnapping.
It is federal by a mile,
so do not fuck with me.
Until the boy is sleeping
in his bed again...
everyone in this room works for me.
Do you understand?
Okay.
I'm gonna go in
and talk to the mother now.
As you can see,
we haven't wasted any time getting to work.
At our current pace,
we're looking at a grand opening...
a month ahead of schedule.
My people are working
with the gaming commission...
to ensure our licensing
is in order by then.
Afternoon, gentlemen.
I hope you like what you see.
Excuse me a minute.
Proctor.
This is coming up nicely.
And ahead of schedule.
Oh, let me introduce my niece.
This is Rebecca Bowman.
She'll be sitting in, learning the
business. And this is Alex Longshadow.
Sorry, this is Chief Alex Longshadow.
He is the leader of the
Kinaho tribal council.
What are you doing here, Proctor?
- I thought you said you had a meeting.
- Oh, we do.
It's just that Alex here
forgot to mention to me...
that he was bringing in a new round
of potential investors for our project.
I don't take that personally.
It's just there's a give-and-take
in every partnership.
We're not partners.
I don't know how to make that any more
clear to you than I already have.
Now I'm gonna ask you one last time
to stay out of the tribe's business...
and then I'm gonna stop being polite.
Listen to his tone.
Look at his posture.
How certain he is
he is the one with all the power here.
Get out now.
Your father and I had a deal, Alex.
You didn't like it, I know that.
But you inherited it
just like you inherited all this.
Now, the smart thing for you to do...
No, the only thing for you to do
is to honor that deal.
- Heh.
- If you continue to think...
you can break your father's promises...
you may cause me
to rethink my own terms.
You know what this is?
It's a whistle.
It's a lesson in power.
Let's go. We're done.
Very nice to meet you.
That was fun.
That was a waste of our time.
I need those workers working.
Then why did you do it?
Because I promised his father
I wouldn't kill him.
Hey, Max. You are okay?
Just let me go home. I wanna see my mom.
Hey.
You don't have to be scared of me.
I would never hurt you.
I just wanna go home.
What is it? What's wrong?
I can't breathe.
I need my nebulizer.
Just calm down. Take a deep breath.
I can't.
I have asthma.
Door was unlocked.
No, it wasn't.
I, uh...
I need your help.
You want my help?
Yeah.
First I have to ask you something.
The Amish girl, Rebecca...
did you fuck her?
- What's that got to do with anything?
- She's my niece.
Small fucking towns.
- So that's a yes.
- Yeah, I didn't know she...
Unh. Hang on.
I said, hang on.
You had enough?
I think I've had enough.
Good.
So, what did you wanna talk about?
There are some men in town.
They came here for me.
Seems to me I'd be better off
letting these men have what they came for.
No. You're too smart for that.
Why's that?
Because I'll owe you one.
Huh.
One thing.
Rebecca, she's off-limits.
- Deal.
- It's not a deal.
It's a fact.
So how long have you had that stuff
buried in our backyard?
There are things
you don't know about me, Gordon.
I'm sorry. Things from my past.
Yeah, but you were holding that gun today.
Gordon, I love you...
but I can't do this now.
Max needs me.
Is anything about us true? About you?
Is Carrie even your real name?
Not now.
Shit.
Ah, here she is.
I bet you didn't know
your mother could handle a gun, did you?
She was just about your age
when I taught her.
Go upstairs, baby.
No. Stay here.
Leave her out of this.
Put the gun down.
Put it down!
Deva...
how old are you?
I'm 15.
- Fifteen.
- Please don't.
Who are you?
- I'm your grandfather.
- My grandfather is dead.
No.
Not yet.
Deva.
Is this him?
- Dad!
- Gordon, no! Gordon!
You tell me where my son is,
you son of a bitch.
Your son is missing for five hours
and you are angry and terrified.
My daughter was gone for 15 years.
Get Deva out of here.
Gordon. Gordon.
If you shoot him,
his men will slit Max's throat.
No!
Is that any way
to greet your father-in-law, Gordon?
Please. Please don't hurt my father.
This is not your father.
Please, don't.
Okay. Please...
can we all just sit down?
Like a family.
- Um, my brother, Max...
- All in good time.
Your mother has told you many lies, Deva.
And I think maybe she lied
to your stepfather too.
I don't know.
Look, you see?
Look at her face. It's true.
- Mom?
- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Deva, your brother has a breathing machine.
- His nebulizer.
- Yes.
- Go get it for me, please.
- Is he having attacks?
He could die.
Then you'd better hurry.
Don't do this. Please.
Let me come with you.
You can do what you want with me...
just let me make sure he's okay.
He's just a little boy.
Anastasia.
Yes, father?
Where is Olek?
You will get no mercy from me.
Let me come with you.
I can take care of him.
You're such a sweet girl.
I will see you again.
Hey.
I'm gonna kill you.
You already have.
- Jeffrey Thompson.
- Yeah?
You're a big fucking guy.
With a big fucking gambling problem.
Rick knows I'm good for the money.
Rick works for me, and it's not his call.
That money belongs to the Kinaho tribe,
and it's my job to safeguard that money.
- Do you understand?
- Yeah.
You're into us for 46 grand.
Yeah, I know.
I made some calls.
Ours is not the only casino you play in.
You're into Fox Valley for 60 grand.
Those guys are some tough bastards.
I don't see that's any concern of yours.
It's not, but we have a working
relationship. See, we do each other favors.
I could wipe your slate clean.
And why would you wanna do that?
Ahem. You used to work
for Kai Proctor, right?
- Yeah.
- What happened?
- Let's just say we parted ways.
- I heard he fired you.
Just when you were
paying off your debt too.
All right, look.
You know you have me,
and I know you have me.
So just tell me what the plan is.
I like where your head's at, Jeffrey.
You look like shit.
Long day.
You know...
sometimes you spend so long
waiting for something...
it simply can't measure up
to your expectations.
So maybe you should just go home, huh?
So you're a pretend policeman now?
Inspired but stupid.
This was always the way with you.
Always in the moment,
blind to the consequences.
You'd make a terrible chess player.
Is this your plan? To insult me to death?
You spent all those years
locked up with animals.
Then you come here...
only to find she's married...
with a family.
Where's the boy, Rabbit?
You can't help him.
You're gonna kill a little boy?
Is that gonna satisfy you?
That's not your concern anymore.
Are you going to shoot me or what?
- I'm considering it.
- Well, decide quickly.
No?
Okay.
What do you want, Rabbit?
I just wanted to look into your eyes
for the last time.
To be the last face you ever saw.
Good-bye.
Oh, shit.