I'm ready to bring him to you.
Finally.
Mr. Proctor.
Hello, Kai.
Hold the work. Clear the room.
I'll call you guys later.
Would you excuse us, Burton?
Last time you spoke to me...
we were pulling yams
in your father's field.
You barely even had that beard yet.
I've come to talk to you about Rebecca.
How is your daughter?
There's no need to pretend.
I know that she talks to you.
She defies every other rule,
so why not that one?
I wouldn't have come if I didn't think...
She is my daughter and I love her.
But she is getting lost.
What happened to you...
has saddened me.
I don't want to lose her.
I understand.
She trusts you.
And because of that...
maybe she would listen to you.
Maybe she would.
Good.
I still pray for you, Kai.
And they were carrots, not yams.
- Don't you got to get going?
- Mm.
I don't think a few kids
in Saturday detention...
will be too crushed
if I'm a little late.
- Hey.
- What's wrong?
Ah, nothing. I'm just distracted.
You've been distracted for the last year,
Dan.
Yeah, well, there's a lot going on at work.
Well, what about what's going on here?
Or not going on, actually.
Well, I'm just a little bit stressed out.
Okay. I've got to go to work.
Four casino guards...
two drivers, and another in the back.
I've studied the photos and the schematics.
And it's like I said, we ain't getting
into that truck once it's closed.
Well, we can't take them
in that loading bay...
if that's what you're thinking.
We'd be dead inside a minute.
You got a better idea?
Yeah, anything but that.
Can we please set you up
with a computer and Quicken or some shit?
Looking at you is like watching
the History Channel.
You of all people should know
that computers are not secure.
Yeah,
there's a million hackers in China just
dying to get their
hands on your financials.
These aren't rent-a-cops. This is
Longshadow's hand-vetted security team.
- They'll die for him.
- So, what then?
We need a friend in the truck.
Lord, I was afraid you were gonna say that.
Hood.
I'll be there.
Oh, for fuck's sake, I know it was her.
I can hear your heart beating from here.
- She says she has a fence for the stones.
- Just like that? Fucking spectacular.
After 15 years,
she just suddenly found someone.
That's what she said, Job.
There is no fence, man. You know it.
Maybe not.
Then why are you going?
- Because it's her.
- She is not her anymore.
And whoever she is,
she's gonna get you killed.
We'll see.
There is pussy-whipped and then there is
that hopeless motherfucker.
Oh, for fuck's sake.
Hey.
Just like old times.
Don't get too attached.
This is just unfinished business.
We got no shortage of that, right?
Where'd you find these guys?
I started putting out feelers
when you came to town.
A guy in Jersey came through.
You trust him?
If I trusted him,
you wouldn't be coming along.
God,
you were always better at this than me.
Fuck!
I'm sorry.
- Ana, what are you doing?
- What I have to do.
Oh, fuck.
I'm sorry.
Fuck.
Well, honey, is there a particular brand
you want? I mean...
Well, how about whichever
one gives us a yes, huh?
All right, baby. Bye.
Fuck my shit.
- Don't fucking move!
- Okay. Just calm down.
Shut the fuck up, cop!
Keep your hands up, motherfucker.
No! Jesus!
Lance, was that fucking necessary?
- He reached for something.
- Please, let me help him.
Get on your fucking knees.
Get on your fucking knees!
Please, no.
- Fuck me.
- Finish him!
Finish him! Let's go!
Fuck me.
The Lord is my shepherd,
I shall not be in want.
Though I walk through the valley
of the shadow of death...
I shall fear no evil,
for thou art with me.
Surely goodness, mercy, and love
will follow me all the days of my life...
and I will dwell in the house
of the Lord forever.
Alma, I've got a robbery in progress.
Shots fired and a civilian down
in the drugstore.
Go, go!
Stop! Hey! Step away from that car!
You should've finished him
in the store, you pussy.
It was a highly charged situation.
And what do you call this?
Killing a cop has ramifications.
Jesus! Fuck!
Sir, are you all right?
Okay, look, stay here.
I'll call an ambulance.
Alma, they're on foot heading towards
the Oak Street parking garage.
Brock, they just crossed Oak Street.
Repeat, they just crossed Oak.
That fucker is still coming.
Suspects heading towards
Banshee High School gymnasium.
I said stop!
- No!
- Come here!
No! No!
- Aah!
- Let her go now!
Ow, fuck!
No!
Do you have any idea
what kind of shitshow you just started?
One of these days we're gonna find you
a functioning set of balls.
Oh, great. Good old BHS.
Shit, more cops.
Help him up!
They ain't gonna come in.
Not when we have us a hostage.
Mrs. Kendall?
- What the fuck is this?
- It's detention.
Get down here now!
Get down from there!
Get up! Move your ass!
Get over here!
Now!
Well, this is new.
I must have gotten the dosage wrong.
You shouldn't have woken up yet.
You called him?
I gave you every chance to leave.
I begged you.
I didn't want to leave.
I would tell you to think
about what you're doing...
but I'm guessing you already have.
I'm protecting my family.
You really think he won't come after you?
That's the deal.
He's gonna torture me to find you.
And you're not gonna tell him.
I'm gonna sing my fucking lungs out.
- Goodbye.
- Hey.
I'll catch up to you.
Anything else?
Yeah, one of them is named Lance.
This place was like church to me.
We were 1983 state champs.
I started at point guard.
You know how many points I averaged
a game, Future Horse?
Twenty points.
Nice.
Goddamn nice.
Get down. Get down.
Any movement in the front?
No, all the doors are
chained up except this one.
- Okay, that'll help us.
- Let me see this.
Fuck.
All the doors
are padlocked shut.
There's no fucking way out of here.
- Lance, can we focus?
- Can you get off my dick?
We've got to get the fuck out of here.
Oh, I forgot.
You hate this place, don't you?
- Hey, look what she's got.
- Hey, hey, hey!
What, are you filming us? Feisty, huh?
Leave her alone. They're just kids.
But you're not, are you?
- You called Hood, right?
- Hood's off today.
He's out of town on personal business.
- Brock, he's the sheriff.
- All right, fine.
Alma, get me the sheriff.
I've been trying him. No answer.
Why am I not surprised?
I just say we go in.
No, we wait.
They've already killed one person.
We're not rushing in.
All right, listen, keep me here,
but let the students go.
Get all their fucking phones.
Give me your phones. Let's go.
Give me your phones!
Siobhan, do another perimeter check,
all right?
Check every window.
Any movement in any room,
you radio in, all right?
She all right?
She's still coming around.
Oh, shit.
Hey! How we doing?
They got fucking TV cameras
set up out there.
This shit's getting out of control.
Time to talk.
Talk to who?
You're on this, huh?
I got the call from Harrisburg.
I was the closest man.
I'm working at scrambling
a SWAT team from Philly.
- All right.
- Where's Hood?
He's out of town on personal business.
We're trying to reach him,
but I can handle this.
- Brock.
- Go for Lotus.
I've got Janie Kendall,
the mayor's wife, on the line.
- She's with the gunmen.
- Put her through.
Janie, this is Brock Lotus. You okay?
Janie?
Tell him it's simple.
He says to tell you it's simple.
We want a car and an easy way out.
They want a car with a way out.
We want it within an hour.
They want it within an hour.
Or bad things will happen in here.
Or bad things will happen.
Janie, is everyone all right in there?
Just tell him to get the fucking car.
Who's with you?
Get the fucking car.
A gangster named Kassin killed my father.
I heard soon after that he'd left Ukraine
and gone to Kunda.
I went there, but I couldn't find him.
Then a few years later...
I was in Yalta on business.
I turned the corner...
and there was Kassin...
carrying a bottle of wine.
We saw each other at the same moment.
It was like two old friends
running into each other.
I gutted him like a fish
right there in the street.
That night I drank his wine with my dinner.
We break from our regular program...
to go live to Banshee, Pennsylvania.
Fuck!
We're here outside Banshee
High School in Banshee, Pennsylvania.
So far what we have to report
is that a pair of armed gunmen...
have taken hostages here
in the school's gymnasium...
after fleeing a robbery gone wrong.
We know at least one person
has been killed at this time.
One hostage posted a video
on her Facebook page...
and we have that footage.
The police confirm
that they have been in contact...
with the gunmen,
but are releasing no information...
regarding the identity of the men...
We are close, no?
Just 15 miles.
These are all the Lances
that Alma could find in our system.
Lance McManus, Lance Hershler...
- Lance Mangan.
- Him. Mangan.
Jesus, I remember him.
He was a point guard back in the day.
- A golden boy.
- Not anymore.
He shot that cashier
like it was target practice.
Brock! Brock!
What's going on?
All right, listen.
I talked to Janie. She's okay.
All right? Gordon, hey.
Deva's inside. She had detention.
- We know.
- Where's the sheriff?
What do we know?
What steps are you taking?
Gordon, come on. Dan, please.
Just stay back.
Stay back behind the barrier.
For your own safety, all right?
Come on, Carrie, pick up.
What?
Wait, what?
What the fuck are you doing?
Are you fucking with her?
- No.
- Yes, you are. You're fucking with her.
Instead of trying to get us out of here,
you're acting like a fucking asshole.
Fuck you.
Why'd you have to shoot
that goddamn cashier?
He was reaching for something.
I said I was sorry.
Yeah, well, are you sorry
for all of this shit, huh?
Because that's on you too.
You know, you don't fucking
think shit through.
Can we focus here?
The police confirm
they have been in contact...
with the gunmen,
but are releasing no
information regarding
the identity of the men...
or the nature of the contact.
But rather were
serving a week of academic detention.
Don't worry.
Fuck.
Oh, fucking spectacular.
How did you find me?
I have a tracker on your phone.
Come on!
Car?
- No!
- Enough of this bullshit, man.
We've got to get the fuck out of here.
Get the fuck out of my way.
- Please.
- You don't need to look at this.
You don't need... Fuck!
Just don't fuck with me. Don't look.
Please.
No, please.
Please don't.
They'll give you what you want.
- I know they will.
- So will you.
You bastard! Goddamn it, stop!
Don't. Don't!
- Yeah?
- Car's here for you now.
I'll call you back.
Come on. We'll pick this up later.
Hey, hey. I've been trying...
Hey, hey, hey! Listen to me. Listen to me.
- Deva's in there? Okay.
- They're doing everything they can.
- Yeah?
- Listen up.
No, you listen.
You're Lance Mangan. I remember you.
Who the fuck are you?
Brock Lotus.
I was a year behind you in school.
Yeah, well, I don't remember you.
Well, I remember you were all-state.
You started at point guard.
You called smart plays.
See if you can call a smart play now.
All right? Your car is here.
You want it moved up there by the door,
I'm gonna need something from you.
Let's get the kids out of there.
I'll send out four kids.
Then you move the car to the door.
All right, it's a deal.
You four in the front, you're leaving.
One, two, three, four. Get up.
- Nathan, bring them to the door.
- Let's go. Come on.
I said four.
Future Horse stays right here.
Whoa, whoa.
She's coming with me.
I'm not leaving without her.
It's okay, Beaty, go.
- What the fuck? Get over here.
- Run!
Get back here! Get back down!
- Watch them!
- Sit down!
- No!
- Get over there, teacher.
Well, especially if they cover this...
Brock, can you please give us an update?
I'd like one too.
What's going on? You going in?
No. I just negotiated
the release of four of the kids.
Great. Where are they?
Um...
- These men are willing to kill.
- You go in there guns blazing...
you're gonna have a handful
of dead children.
Who said anything about guns blazing?
You can't walk in there... Aah!
Don't touch me.
We follow him in, right?
I'm not following him anywhere.
He's insane.
We stay to protocol. We wait out here.
What the fuck?
I'm unarmed.
Don't fucking move!
I came in here to help you work this out.
Fuck you.
You're in some
deep shit here, man.
Lance, get back here!
Where's Lance?
Huh?
Future Horse.
You're not gonna walk out of this.
They won't let you go.
They have to. We have hostages.
That doesn't matter anymore.
That's gone. You killed a man.
I didn't kill anyone!
- It was fucking Lance.
- I believe you.
Lance killed him. What's your name?
You don't need to know my fucking name.
- It's Nathan.
- Shut the fuck up!
- Hey, hey, hey, Nathan.
- Back the fuck up.
- I can help you.
- Lance!
Get the fuck back here! Back up!
Lance can't help you. I can.
Oh, my God! Come on!
Hey!
Don't fucking move.
I will fucking kill you.
- I don't think so.
- Yes, I will.
- No, not you.
- Not you, man.
- I will fucking kill you.
You're no killer, Nathan.
Yes, I am.
- It's Lance.
- No.
Lance, he's the killer.
No, I am a fucking killer.
Shots fired. We're going in!
All of you up. Out, now.
- Hold your fire!
- It's the students.
- Get clear!
- Stay down. Come on. Come on.
- Where's Deva?
- I don't know.
- Where's my daughter?
- She's inside.
Go forward!
Jamie.
It's okay.
Let's... Let's go home, okay?
Get up, Future Horse.
Aah! Nathan, I got them. Nathan.
Nathan. Oh, no, no, no.
No!
Oh, fuck.
- Aah!
- Let her go, Lance.
- Drop your fucking gun.
- Not gonna happen.
Stand down, sheriff.
- I'll fucking kill her!
- Let the girl go.
I'll fucking blow her head off!
- Drop that fucking gun now.
- Drop your weapon!
Get down the fucking stairs right now!
- Drop your weapon.
- Drop your fucking guns!
- Get away! Get back!
- Stand down.
Drop your gun! Drop it!
Put it on the ground now!
Sheriff. Are you injured?
Uh, no.
Good, then you can tell me...
I did what I had to do.
You just endangered the lives
of eight innocent people.
Listen...
I'll give you everything you need...
I promise, in my report.
Welcome to my world.
Hey.
Alma told me I'd find you here.
That guy, the cashier,
he just woke up today and went to work.
He really had no idea that...
Hey, you are an excellent cop
and an excellent man.
If there was something you could have done,
you would have done it.
I'm pregnant.
Police have confirmed
that the two gunmen...
were both killed inside the school,
that the location is secure...
and that all eight of the
former hostages are alive...
and being attended
by medical professionals.
The gunmen were involved
in a botched robbery...
at a drugstore earlier today.
A local police deputy intervened
and pursued them here to the high school...
at which point the gunmen
took eight hostages.
So now you want to tell me
who the hell put the cuffs on you?
Long story.
- Sugar.
- Kai.
Sheriff.
I thought I'd find you here.
Still patching yourself up, I see.
I'll survive.
You did good work today, sheriff.
This town owes you a real debt.
It seems I'm in your debt as well.
The DA formally dropped all charges today.
Apparently the key piece of evidence
disappeared.
Hmm, and a key witness.
This is the first I've heard about that.
Well, congratulations.
You're a free man.
You know, generally,
Banshee is a pretty quiet town.
But after you arrived,
it's been one thing after another.
It's almost as if you
brought it all with you.
"And behold a pale rider...
and his name that sat upon him
was Death.
And hell followed with him."
Revelations 6:8.
Yeah, I've never had much patience
for people who quote scripture.
This is God's country.
You'd better acquire the taste for it.
You have a good night, Sugar.
- Sheriff.
- You too, Kai.
Are you ever gonna tell me that story?
Come on, you and Proctor.
What would we be without our secrets?
Are you gonna shoot me?
I'm sorry.
I'm so, so sorry.
Shh.
Made them all myself.
Strawberry, pecan...
and this one's called triple chocolate.
The dark one.
You're not from around here,
I can tell you that much.
Everyone passes through here
at some point.
And I would have remembered you.
So that accent, where are you from?
I'd rather talk about where I am.