Get out of here!
Come on!
Get up!
Come on, up.
You should have told me.
You and Anastasia...
I could have come
to terms with it.
But you turned her against me.
- I think he knows.
- He doesn't know.
I treated you like family...
and you turned
my daughter against me?
No.
You did that yourself.
You won't tell me where she is?
I don't know where she is.
You gave up your freedom for her.
And now you will die for her.
Yes.
No.
You will not die.
You will suffer.
You will know fear...
and pain and despair...
every single day
you are in here.
This much I promise you.
You're not begging.
You have always been so proud...
so much like me.
I will never be like you.
We'll see.
- Shh.
- Ugh! Ugh!
I know just how deep to go
without killing you.
Every single day.
Now you can go to sleep.
Fifteen minute rest stop, folks.
We'll be in Pittsburgh before noon.
Hey, ladies.
I'm a sinner.
Will you pray for me?
Guess a blow job
would be pushing it, huh?
Huh, fucking bitches.
- I gotta go.
- All right, I'll see you later.
I don't fucking believe it.
Heh. No fucking way.
My father wants a word with him.
Alex tells me
you're still mad at me.
Yes, I am.
I cleared the way for the hotel
with the zoning board.
I got all the permits
fast-tracked.
I made sure the environmental impact report
wasn't an issue...
Burton, get the man a chair.
It was a murder charge.
It's a political vendetta.
It won't amount to anything.
I apologize
if I offended you, friend.
Apology accepted.
How've you been feeling?
Cut the bullshit, paleface.
We all know the spirit horse
is coming for me.
I already heard its hoof beats.
And...
you have concerns.
Your word is
the only bond I need.
But your son...
With all due respect, Benjamin,
he doesn't share our past.
My son will fulfill my promises.
Then I'll treat Alex with the same respect
I've treated you.
I'll consider your promise
his to keep.
But if he breaks it...
it won't be a good day
for the tribe.
I Will talk with Alex.
Now, the landowners
at the site...
I understand there's one
that doesn't want to sell out.
Yeah, it's the reverend.
He's a decent man, stubborn.
He'll sell.
He just doesn't know it yet.
Hello, Deborah.
What do you want?
Is your husband home?
Arthur's around back.
Thank you.
Morning, Reverend Ramsey.
Thought I would've
heard back from you by now.
I want you to taste something.
The pipes in my house, they draw
the water from the aquifer...
but I prefer to drink it
straight from here.
Same well my great-grandfather
drank from.
Same bucket, even.
When my son was born,
the entire congregation...
of First Methodist came out here.
We baptized him with the water...
from that very well.
I understand your attachment,
Mr. Ramsey.
I even admire it.
But you're not
a 19th century homesteader.
You have a Prius, a Facebook page
and a 401 k.
We'll double the payout.
We'll secure you equal acreage
within the district.
You can dig a new well.
I'd be worried that any land
you secured for me...
would involve forcing
someone else out.
Now listen to me, reverend.
You're gonna leave.
You can do it with grace
and some cash in your pocket...
or you can do it broken.
But it's gonna happen.
I'm gonna have to pray on it.
If God was looking out for you...
I wouldn't be
at your door now, would I?
Huh?
Hood.
I've been trying to get you on the radio.
- Where the hell are you?
- Serving the people.
Well, look, I got a guy here
in the cage for shoplifting.
He's got a...
Got a long sheet.
A really long sheet.
Well, I'm sure
you can handle it.
Leonard Vanderwick. Does that mean
anything to you?
- Nope. Why?
- Well, the guy says he knows you...
and he won't talk to anyone else.
What do you mean he knows me?
I don't know.
He just... Get down!
He won't tell me anything else.
I was gonna take him over
to the court for processing...
but he insisted that he use his right
to one phone call to contact you.
- Leonard Vanderwick?
- Yep. What do you want me to do?
You want me
to get him processed?
Yeah, no.
I'll be right over.
I gotta go.
Sounds that way.
Is it okay if I just
stay here and maybe nap?
It's quiet.
The Moody boys becoming
a problem for you?
What, are we going steady now?
I can handle Cole's idiot brothers.
This is Deputy Lotus in Banshee.
I'm just wondering how soon
we'll get the... Yeah.
The file number, it's 00170455.
Can you get it to me today?
Do I know you?
I don't know, sheriff.
Do you?
How you doing there, champ?
You're not up
to solid foods yet, hm?
Come on, let me
get you to sit up.
Leave it.
All right, all right.
I just didn't want it
to go to waste.
Here you go.
Here. Looks like you're having
some trouble there, brother.
Just hold that right there.
I'm Wicks.
You want some water?
Whoa, easy, easy. Easy there.
You won't wanna heal too fast.
The Albino, man...
This and solitary...
the only two places
he can't get to you.
The Albino.
Yeah.
He already put the word out.
You're his property.
I don't know what you did, man...
but your chances of survival
just took a nosedive.
What do I do?
I suggest you get
really good at sucking cock.
I'm serious.
The Albino's
a crazy motherfucker...
but he's also full-on queer.
You're young, good-looking.
You show him some love, maybe
you don't end up in a wheelchair.
It's not gonna happen.
You need to accept
that it will happen, man.
Every single day you are in here.
You got no place to hide.
But how it happens, you might
be able to put a spin on that.
You give it to him
before he takes it...
and curry some fucking favor.
That's your best shot.
Listen, are you gonna
eat that sandwich?
Hm?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome, sheriff.
So, uh, how long you been out?
A little while.
You?
Been out about two years.
Did some work for my sister's husband
down in Florida.
It's nice there.
You could work outdoors
all year round.
But her husband, he didn't like me
being around the kids.
He thought I was poisoning
their minds or some shit.
He said he was letting me go
on account of the economy...
but the fucker
just wanted me gone.
Mmm.
Hey, enough about me, man.
Heh.
How the fuck did you pull off
this little miracle here?
It's complicated.
- No shit, it's complicated.
- And temporary.
What are you gonna have?
Don't know yet.
- You're setting up a job.
- No.
Now, listen, man.
You know you can trust me.
And right now,
I'm what you'd call highly available.
No, Wicks, it's not like that.
Come on, man.
You owe me.
Keep your fucking voice down.
Listen, man, I'm not gonna
fuck this up for you.
But I'm tapped out.
You have no idea.
I'm not living right.
I know what I look like.
I've been sleeping
on the fucking streets, man.
I just need a break.
Or I'm gonna be back
in the cage in a month.
At least I get fed there.
Look, order whatever you want.
I'll be back.
I see you made a new friend.
Yeah, I'm a friendly guy.
- Give me an apple pie.
- Coming right up.
He's wall-to-wall prison tats.
I think you're the last guy who'd want
to be seen keeping that kind of company.
- Mrs. Hopewell, I didn't know you cared.
- Be smart.
What, are you worried about me?
- I'm worried about me.
- No. No, that's not it.
You're worried about me.
Just be smart.
Ow! Ha, ha, ha!
Nice.
Here you go.
A clean bed.
You can take a hot shower.
- Yeah, all right.
- Yeah.
I'll come by tomorrow
with some clean clothes for you.
Then what?
Uh...
we'll talk.
All right.
Hey.
Thank you.
Sure.
None of them will come near you.
But you will?
Well, now...
see, me, I make myself
indispensable.
I'm a purveyor of certain goods,
mostly pharmaceutical.
And the Albino,
he likes his narcotics.
Where is he?
He don't come out in the yard.
You seen his eyes?
Stays out of the sun
like a fucking vampire.
How do I get to see him?
You don't.
What are you,
some kind of masochist?
- He'll find you soon enough.
- Come on.
You see blondie over there
with the football?
- Yeah.
- That's Billy B.
That's the Albino's main squeeze.
If you want in, that's your access.
But I'm telling you...
I wouldn't do that.
You know how to throw a ball.
Yeah, I won
two state championships.
Oh, it's you.
Almost healed up, huh?
What the fuck you want?
I'm sorry, man.
I told him he didn't
have an appointment.
He insisted.
I can always make time
for an old friend.
You see?
Prison can be very liberating.
Billy B here...
he was as straight
as they come on the outside.
Son of a minister,
star quarterback...
fucked the prom queen,
all of that.
Then one day,
he went and got drunk...
ran over some old lady
and her grandson...
and ended up in here.
And now he's in love.
Well, the heart wants
what the heart wants, right?
They did a good job
with you, huh?
I mean, fuck, you were a mess...
What was it, a month ago?
About that.
So you found me
before I could find you.
I appreciate that.
It shows gumption.
I wanna make a deal.
- What kind of deal?
- The kind that keeps me healthy.
Heh, heh, I really can't do that.
See, my deal with Mr. Rabbit
makes that a conflict of interest.
- You understand.
- Rabbit doesn't need to know.
And now you're insulting me.
But I know a way
you can make up for that.
Gotta be honest, uh...
I just don't feel
that close to you yet.
It's gonna happen.
I could make it happen right now,
but I'm not gonna.
Because when you do it...
you're gonna do it willingly...
gratefully.
And while you're
greedily sucking me off...
like a babe suckling
on its mother's tit...
that's when you'll understand...
that I own your ass.
Get him out of here.
And the next time we meet's
gonna be something special.
Mr. Rabbit has requested
a small piece of you...
something to prove to him
that I'm holding up my end.
- So how long are you in for?
- Twenty.
That's a long time to be anyone's bitch.
You know, whatever you're thinking...
you can just forget it.
- You belong to him now.
- We can take him down.
Together.
Fuck you.
You're his bitch now,
just like me.
Stay down! Stay down!
Oh, fuck.
Fighting in the yard...
buys you 30 days in the hole.
The shiv gets you another 90.
Keep it up,
you'll be an old man...
by the time you see
a real bed again.
Yeah, looking sharp!
I feel like a new man.
Fuck, yes.
Mr. Vanderwick is walking tall,
motherfucker.
- You look great.
- I know.
He says he'll take you
to Pittsburgh.
Then you can make
your own way from there.
Here.
That's 2500 bucks.
- Thanks, man.
- All right.
And, uh, thanks
for my new wardrobe.
Yeah.
All right.
- All right.
- Been great, man.
Thanks.
Hey, Wicks.
Don't come back.
Morning, reverend.
No, no, no, no.
Look, you can just turn right around.
I'm not signing.
I've spoken to my lawyer.
He said what you're doing
is considered extortion.
I assure you
that was not the case.
What's this?
This? This is extortion.
This is...
This is not my wife.
Oh? Oh, no, it's her. It's her, all right.
I should know. See?
I never forget a great piece of ass.
Where did you get these?
Oh, I didn't get them.
I took them.
Yeah, I took that one too.
You fucked my wife?!
Of course not.
She wasn't your wife then.
She danced in my clubs for years
before she found you and God.
Or was it God, then you?
I don't know.
Either way, I found her first.
- Arthur...
- Shut up.
- Let me... Listen to me...
- I said shut up!
But my offer still stands.
I'll double the payout.
As far as I'm concerned,
you've earned it.
At least one of you did. Heh, heh.
- I'm so sorry.
- Just sign the papers.
We'll relocate you
and these pictures disappear.
Now, if you don't sign,
tomorrow morning...
they'll be in the in-boxes
of every member of your church...
along with a link to the video.
Video?
Oh, come on, Ramsey.
There's always a video.
- Shut up.
- Dude, you know you like her.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
- Dude, she kisses her dog.
- She does not.
Like, tongue kisses.
Max.
Max!
Mrs. Hopewell!
Mrs. Hopewell! Max. Max.
Come on, baby boy.
It's fine.
Mommy's right here.
Mommy loves you.
- Hey, how is he?
- Where were you?
- I called you over an hour ago.
- I was in court.
They had to come and get me.
I'm... I'm sorry.
- What did the doctor say?
- They haven't said anything yet.
Gordon, Carrie.
He's, uh, stable now.
Can we speak privately
for a minute?
I'm not a child.
Right here's fine, doctor.
We'd been hoping that
the therapies we had Max on...
would keep his lungs going
for a few more years...
until he reached puberty...
at which point surgery
would be a more viable option.
But his asthma is being complicated
by that scarred lung...
and I don't think we can
take that approach anymore.
You're the lucky man.
Oh.
Five hundred, yo.
Yeah! That's what I'm talking about.
I need another fucking drink!
Oh.
Whoo!
- Come on.
- Come on, lucky nine.
Motherfucker!
Yeah, son of a bitch!
Pay me!
Bet is midnight.
Bet is boxcars.
All right, hands off
the layout, please.
The dice are out. Seven.
Craps.
Shit, shit, Shit.
No more bets, please.
- Shit, shit.
- Come on, baby.
- You should really stop.
- No, no, no. I got this.
- You're gonna lose it all.
- Fuck off!
- Hey, man.
- Yeah? Fuck you too.
Where the fuck are you going?
- Come here.
- You're being an asshole.
Take your hands
off the lady now.
Yeah, dickwad,
take your hands off the lady.
- All right, all right.
- Thank you.
Everybody calm down.
It's good, it's good.
Get up, ass-wipe.
Hey, free money!
Who's the ass-wipe now, motherfucker?
Who's the ass-wipe now?
Oh, shit.
Not a fucking word.
So this is the guy who tore up my casino?
It was all a misunderstanding, chief.
Did you really just call me "chief"?
Are you really that fucking dumb?
I... I didn't mean anything by it.
Shut up and listen so there's no
further misunderstandings.
If you ever walk
through my doors again...
we won't bother the Banshee
Sheriff's Department with our troubles.
This is Kinaho land you're standing on...
and we'd be well within
our rights to handle it internally.
Nod if you understand.
He's all yours.
Thanks.
- Here, babe.
- Shit.
- Jesus Christ, Carrie.
- I'm sorry.
- No, no. Leave it, leave it.
- Let me get it.
I got it... I got it, honey.
I got it.
I'm sorry.
It's okay, it's okay.
Max will be okay.
They'll figure this thing out.
They have it figured out.
We just don't want
to believe them.
You know,
the asthma's one thing...
but he's gonna need a new lung.
He had a bad attack.
I know that, but...
You know, so long as we're here
for the night...
why don't we just...
Why don't we just get everything out
on the table?
What are you talking about?
I don't know...
but I know it's something.
- Max is getting worse.
- I'm not talking about Max.
Honey, I'm talking about us.
I'm talking about you.
When I catch you
sitting in the kitchen...
staring out the window,
and the look in your eye...
it's like this look of total despair.
And the kids are picking up on it too.
What do you mean, the kids?
Deva has asked me
more than once...
why you seem so distant.
Did you tell her that
seeing the man who...
tried to rape me,
shot and killed on top of me...
might be a reason for me
to feel a little bit thrown?
- I did. I said exac...
- You just...
Yeah, I said exactly that.
Okay, good.
Tell me about the sheriff.
He got Deva out of that rave
and I'm very grateful.
And that is it.
I need you to let me in, Carrie.
We can beat this thing with Max.
I know we can, but we have to be
operating at full strength.
And... And right now...
You're right. You're right.
Have I done something
to upset you?
- Because if I have, I don't know...
- No, honey, no.
It's all me.
I'm just having...
I've been having a hard time
finding my balance right now.
What can I do for you?
Don't give up on me.
Mm.
Ah.
Thank you, brother.
That is some choice sirloin.
You know your cuts.
- Thank you.
- Mm-mm, thank you.
You got yourself
a sweet setup here.
Most cons I know
can't get minimum wage.
Look at you. Sole proprietor.
What is it about this town?
It's like heaven for cons.
Hey, man!
Where you been?
Well, I had to make sure your mess
was cleaned up properly.
Thanks.
Yeah, look,
I'm real sorry about that, man.
That was my bad.
But in my defense, that hooker
gave me some bad coke.
I told you not to come back.
Yeah, well, you know what?
I believe the power dynamic
here's all fucked up.
Come again?
I mean, knowledge is power, right?
I have some knowledge about you
that nobody else in this town has.
So, the way I see it...
I'm not the one
who should be taking orders.
We had a deal.
Yeah.
And we're renegotiating.
- Wicks...
- Listen.
You got a great situation here.
I'm not looking to fuck it up...
but you better believe
I want a piece.
Been on the road for two years.
And nothing... I mean
nothing has panned out.
You give me some fucking hush money,
send me on my way.
We both know I'm gonna
end up back inside.
And you know what?
I'm not going back.
This is my only play, and I'm making it.
I'm not asking for a handout.
You're gonna give me a chance...
and I'm gonna earn my keep.
And that's how it's gonna be, sheriff.
Man, this is some
fucking grade-A beef.
Well, well, well, look who's back.
Got a special delivery for you.
He's coming for you
tomorrow in the yard.
Watch the yard guards.
When they disappear, it's time.
Why are you helping me?
I consider it an investment.
It's a long stretch in here.
You only get one chance.
The sky is always bluer
than I remember.
I've been waiting
for you, my friend.
What you did to Billy B,
that was uncalled for.
That was a hate crime, man.
Bring him.
Come on, tough guy.
Nice try, smart-ass.
Get on your fucking knees.
Get on your
fucking knees, bitch!
Ask for it.
What?
Whoa.
Okay, so...
I do this...
and we're good?
Fuck, no.
I'll probably still kill you.
But if you show
some serious skills...
you may have a future.
I'd better come quick and hard...
or you won't stand up again.
Now, ask for it.
Okay.
Give it to me.
- What?
- Ah!
Give it to me.
Motherfucker!
Are we good?
Yeah, we're good.
I knew guys like Wicks in prison...
guys that never stop digging graves
for themselves...
and then trading
everything and everyone...
to keep from getting buried.
Hey, Hood, I never saw the paperwork
on that Leonard Vanderwick guy.
That get filed or...?
He wasn't worth the effort.
I sent him packing.
Guys like that don't go down...
without taking everyone close
down with him.
That's their game.
How did he know you anyway?
He didn't.
Not really.
Knew of me, I guess.
And you just, uh, just let him go?
Yeah.
I didn't want to waste
any more time...
on a vagrant who tried
to steal some dinner.
So now you decide which laws
are worth enforcing?
That's why they gave me the badge.
Yeah,
but the rules are different out here.
No. Same rules.
Same rules they had since the first man
picked up the first stick...
and beat the second man's
ass with it.
Mm.
You have an interesting way
of looking at the world.
Yeah, I've lived an interesting life.
Yes?
Tell him it's me.
It's her.
Anastasia.
I'm ready...
to bring him to you.
When?
By the end of this week.
Where?
I'll let you know.
She will bring him.
And just when things finally...
seem to be nice and boring,
you came along.
You're welcome.
I guess I'm just not cut out for...
boring. Heh, heh, heh.
Hey, Dad, uh, it's Jason.
Um...
I got your message.
I know we haven't talked
in a long time...
but I've got some
real trouble here.
I called a few times
and I haven't heard back from you.
I just wish I knew
where the hell you were.
I really need to talk to you.
Anyway, please call me.
Bye.