MAN: Can you describe him for us,
love?
A white man in a white car.
He left tyre tracks.
We find that car,
we find the killer.
It's yours, George.
The whole investigation.
Hobson, Domaille in Bradford.
They all work for you.
Five. Five dead women.
This one, a normal lass from
a good family. Done nothing wrong.
And she is lying there
because you and Dennis, you failed.
I give you my word
that I will catch this animal.
And you have that from me,
Mr MacDonald.
They put everything into Leeds,
so he starts killing in Bradford.
They put everything into Bradford,
he comes back here,
where he started.
He could be watching us right now.
If he can see us,
he should be panicking.
Cos he's looking at the two men
who are gonna catch him.
BIRDSONG
MOTOR WHIRS
George!
Phone. It's Dick Holland.
'Do I want to hear this?
PHONE: 'Bradford again. Aged 42.
'Two gypsy women
found her first thing.'
Have you spoken to David Gee?
No.
Well, call him.
Arrange a postmortem.
'No, no, George.
That... That's why I'm ringing.
'This one's survived.'
Her name's Maureen Long.
Hit with a hammer. Stab wounds
to the body and left for dead.
She's not quite with it.
All she knows is she's been
attacked, and we want a word.
Right. Well, let's keep it that way.
No mention of the Ripper, all right?
Where is she?
Down here.
'You were at the Mecca last night.'
Left just as it was finishing.
That's correct, isn't it, Maureen?
That's what you told the nurse?
Do you remember
where you went after that?
Another drink, or...
Do you remember meeting anybody?
Yes, love.
You do?
Yes, love. A fella.
You met a fella.
And had this fella
been in the Mecca too?
Or any of these pubs
you'd been into?
But you remember him being outside?
Do you remember what he looked like,
Maureen, mm?
Like his build, or...
the colour of his hair, or...
I'm trying to think.
But you spoke to him, right?
Yes, love. In t'car.
Oh, so he had a car?
He drove you in his car?
That's how you got
to the caravan site
where they found you
this morning, hmm?
So, what sort of car were it? Hmm?
What make or colour?
I'm not good with cars.
Had you been drinking?
You know, drinking more than
you should?
How much is more than I should?
You got in the car with him.
So you must've spoke to him.
But these questions are important,
Maureen,
so I need you to think hard.
All right?
The car?
What he sounded like,
what he looked like.
White.
What, the man was white?
No.
The car were white.
Or...
Or were it green?
Wh... Why? What's he done to me?
TV PLAYS
Right.
Oh, thank you, love.
Your dad'd never have worn a beard.
Well, that's the trend these days.
Lot of men my age with beards.
Right, look, there's biscuits there.
Tea in t'pot.
Anything else before I go?
Do you want me changing sides?
No, no, I'll stay on three
until Coronation Street,
and then that'll be me, then.
Right, then. Don't wait up.
Oh, be careful, won't you, love?
Yeah, all right.
Morning.
Morning, Sir. Morning, Sir.
Oh, this is good. Morning.
Morning.
This is what I like to see.
Jim?
Meg, could you bring
some tea through?
Yes, Sir.
Gentlemen. Very sorry to keep you.
Come through.
Donkey wallopers.
Aye. Yeah, I know, lad.
Now, McCann,
Jackson, Richardson.
Then it's Atkinson in Bradford.
Then he makes a mistake,
kills a decent lass.
Jane MacDonald, back in Leeds.
And then... Bradford again.
Maureen Long.
Another prostitute?
We're not sure.
Well, she's in that bracket,
in't she? Out on her own.
Going around pubs and clubs.
Getting in cars with men.
Yeah, men she doesn't know.
Ah, doesn't make her a prostitute.
Prostitute, good time girl,
whatever you wanna call it.
Jim's right. She could just
have been getting a cab home.
Cabbies.
Cabbies are out late at night.
Aye, nobody thinks anything of it.
Look, Dennis and I
looked into cabbies.
Looked at bloody hundreds
of cabbies.
Yeah, well, we'll look at it again.
No, it's a dead end.
No, we need to stay focused
on car tyres.
Tina Atkinson took lots of cabs.
All over Bradford.
We got that from neighbours
in her flats.
Cabbies have a reason to travel,
don't they? Leeds, Bradford.
Both of 'em,
and everywhere in between.
So, this is our focus.
Cabbies in Leeds.
Cabbies in Bradford.
You, you check the drivers,
and Jim, whilst you're at it,
you can check the tyres.
All right? Off you go.
TV: 'He left Miss Long for dead.
'The fact that she survived
is to my advantage and not to his.
'So possibly, you may
have stumbled on a big break, then?
'Well, I sincerely hope so.
'There is a belief amongst this team
that this man,
'the Ripper, as he's become known,
has started to make mistakes.
'And it's when an individual
of this nature makes mistakes
'that the net begins to close.'
Y'all right?
Y'all right, love?
Er, how much to Thornbury?
Only I've, er...
I've not got much on me.
Yeah, don't worry.
We'll get you there.
Come on.
Get in before I change me mind.
Andy! Andy! This one'll take us.
Right.
See you, mate.
You, er... sure you're all right
going all the way to Thornbury?
Yeah, no problem, love.
Hi, I'm calling
from Milgarth Police Station.
We need your help
with a local murder enquiry.
Yeah, we're calling
all cab companies in the area,
not just yours.
OK, well first of all, we need
all cab numbers from 1975. Yep.
Names of all your drivers,
registered and unregistered.
I understand it's confidential,
but you see,
this information is integral
to our murder investigation.
What's going on?
Cabbies.
Yeah, we did cabbies last year.
Yeah, well, we're doing 'em again.
And we're doing 'em properly.
Right. Let's do this in a way
you'll all understand.
I'll have a nice, orderly line
down this side.
When you get to t'front,
you're t'next cabbie to go.
Do you work late at night?
Me? No. I love my beauty sleep.
Says here you were working
the night of June 25th.
I don't think so.
No, no, no, I'm not asking you.
I'm reminding you.
Cos on that night,
a very serious crime took place.
Where do you operate?
Leeds, mainly. Bit of Wakefield.
'Bout Bradford?
Don't bother with Bradford.
Yeah, but you must go there
sometimes.
Hardly ever.
That's what I'm saying.
Other drivers
have got Bradford sewn up.
Ever been to Lumb Lane?
Bradford? Aye.
How about Spencer Place, Leeds?
Yeah.
Roundhay Park?
How about Reginald Terrace?
Reginald Terrace... That's...
Where's that?
Chapeltown.
Right.
There's an adventure playground
there.
A sixteen-year-old lass were found
dead in that playground in March.
Killed with a claw hammer.
Just trying to jog your memory.
I might have been there.
Leeds, Bradford...
Huddersfield, Manchester.
You see, funnily enough,
as a cabbie,
you tend to go all over.
What colour's your cab, Ray?
When?
Look, I went through all this
when you brought me in last year.
I drive a red Cortina.
Up until September just gone,
I've always driven a brown Avenger.
Do you lot not write
this sort of thing down?
You go with prostitutes, Leroy?
HE SNORTS
Nah, man.
I have a girlfriend.
She give me everything I need.
Just don't tell my wife.
HE LAUGHS
We're after The Ripper here, Leroy.
You wanna wipe that stupid smirk
off your face?
You work nights.
You've worked both the nights
we've spoke about.
That's not in any doubt.
Do you ever pick up prostitutes?
You've asked me that before.
Never met you before.
Well, not you personally,
but you lot.
You've had me in here
asking me that before.
So, go on, then.
Do you or don't you?
I pick 'em up,
but only to take 'em
where they need to go.
What, that's all it is?
Their money's as good
as anyone else's.
You always been a cabbie?
Aye.
What colour's your cab?
Why do you ask?
Why not?
White.
And what colour were it
on these dates, nights in question?
White.
It's the exact same car?
Well, I might've changed a tyre
or two, but yeah.
White Cortina.
So, there's a woman from Bradford
who survived the Ripper.
You'll be aware of that, yes?
Yes, Sir.
Maureen Long, Sir.
But she couldn't remember 'owt.
That's right. Well done.
So she's gonna need
her memory jogging.
When she's back from hospital,
recovered of course,
you're taking her out.
Taking her out...?
Saturday night, you and her.
Buying her drinks.
Taking her to all her usual places,
retracing her steps.
Don't worry,
DC Laptew will come with you.
I'll keep an eye on things.
And if anyone starts asking
questions, then Maureen's your mate,
Andrew here's your husband.
SHE SIGHS
I've already got a husband.
Then he's your bit on the side.
Look, the aim here is to see
if it brings anything back.
Details, faces.
So, you make sure
she has a good look round. OK?
That's five attacks in a row now.
All on a Saturday night.
So there's even a chance
you might see the Ripper himself.
His car's white. Now, we all know
Maureen Long's had a skinful,
but that's a definite start.
Add to that the fact
he were in Bradford
the night she were attacked.
He were in Leeds the night of
the MacDonald murder, working late.
He admits to driving all over...
And to changing his tyres.
And we've had him in once before.
But here's the bit I like.
He lives in Drighlington.
Where's that?
It's between Bradford and Leeds.
Now, we don't wanna say
"We're excited, George," but...
But you're "excited, George".
So, what do you say we bring him in,
eh?
Nick him. Get stuck into him.
Does he know we feel like that?
No, no, Sir. We said we'd come back
to him if we had any more questions.
Good. Cos there's not enough.
Not yet.
He doesn't know
that we're onto him,
that gives us more time
to do some digging.
Find out where he goes.
What he's up to.
Good work, though.
We'll get someone on him.
How are you, all right?
Come on, get in.
I've not told you
where I'm going yet.
I've a punter up Potternewton Park,
but he's not got a car.
What do you think? Reckon we can do
the same as last time?
CLEARS THROAT
Yeah, all right. Come on.
So, did he get what he wanted?
SHE SCOFFS
What?
Don't pretend you weren't watching.
So, what about you?
Have you got everything you wanted?
Yeah.
There.
No, no, that's... That's too much.
No, for last time an' all.
Thanks.
See you.
Take care.
POLICE RADIO: 04. On my way.
MUFFLED VOICES OVER RADIO
We've been tracking him for weeks.
Last night he were in Spencer Place,
Leopold Street, Chapeltown Road
until three in t'morning.
And then, last Friday, he was
spotted in Bradford, Church Street.
So he's in all the right areas...
But he's not done anything wrong
since surveillance started.
No, no, Sir,
not since we've been tailing him.
Well, mind you, nor's the Ripper.
So we stay on him.
Right.
Sir, there's a Jack Ridgway for you.
Who?
Central Manchester Police.
Aye, well,
tell him I'll call him back.
Oh, I can't, Sir, he's downstairs.
Right.
Are you Ridgway?
Sorry to come over all this way,
Mr Oldfield,
but I thought it best
done in person, you know?
But it's...
it's this Ripper of yours.
We think he's been over our way.
'Her name's Jean Jordan.'
Two lads found her
up on the allotments in Chorlton.
It's a place where the prostitutes
take the punters, you know?
She'd had a blow on the head
with a blunt object.
Looks like some kind of tool,
she'd been stabbed in the body,
and then she had this long cut.
Right down here, like that,
like length of my tie.
And our pathologist got on the phone
to your chap.
David Gee?
Yeah, that's-that's the one.
And he said with the injuries,
the two weapons, the order that
they're done in, they're identical.
Look, I-I don't wanna
tread on toes here.
Well, that's what you're doing.
So, it's not just Leeds.
It's Bradford,
and now he goes to Manchester
for t'first time.
It might not be his first time.
What, Harrison, you mean?
Mm.
Er... No, we ruled them out.
Harrison?
Joan Harrison.
She were in, er...
Where were it? Preston?
Preston.
Preston, yeah.
Back in, er... '75.
That's right.
Hoban had us look into it
and decided it weren't linked.
Oh, aye? Why?
She were killed indoors.
Well, Atkinson were killed indoors.
Yes, but this was before Atkinson.
And that is why we ruled it out.
Yeah, but why would a man
who's killing prostitutes
in Bradford and Leeds
drive all the way out
to some muddy lane in Chorlton,
just to do the same thing
to some prostitute there?
Apart from anything,
who's got the time
to make that journey, right?
ENGINE RUMBLES
Right, get in there, lads.
BANGING ON DOOR
OFFICER: Excuse me, miss.
Hey!
You!
Hey! On your feet.
You can't go in there.
That the cab?
Yes, Sir.
Right, test it. Outside, inside,
just take it to bits,
and then test it again.
EXHALES
You two with me.
OFFICER: Terence!
Terry?
TERENCE: It's OK, Mam. It's OK, Mam.
He's not nothing.
You can't just take him like this.
What's he done?
You'll hurt my wrists now.
OFFICER: Move!
Agh!
RADIO CHATTER
TERENCE: My mother is 67 years old.
She is frail, she's not all there,
and she did not need to see that.
Worried about her feelings, are we?
The feelings of a vulnerable,
innocent woman?
How were Manchester?
What you on about?
You said you go to Manchester.
Yeah, sometimes.
So how were it? How did it feel?
What are you on about?
Doing a whore over there
last Saturday?
Killing one of theirs?
Nobody watching you over there,
is there? Must be a relief.
No pigs in cars following you about.
Bet you felt like you were on your
fucking holidays, didn't you, fella?
Why is it...?
I'm sorry to bombard you
with questions, by the way.
Why is it that on four occasions
when The Ripper's killed these
women, you are in the same town?
Leeds, Bradford, Leeds.
Every single time. Why?
I mean, I know what I think,
but why don't you go first?
I wasn't in Manchester, Saturday.
Where were you then?
I stopped at home.
And who's gonna vouch for that?
My ma.
Come on!
Your ma?
But your ma's 67.
You can't have it both ways.
Your ma's frail,
your ma's not all there.
We're gonna match it.
D'you understand?
There's mud all around them
allotments where you took her...
where you killed her. Jean Jordan...
Tried to cut off her head.
Well, that mud gets everywhere.
So we're gonna match it
to the mud on your car.
Jim.
Got nothing so far.
Tested his house, tools, clothes.
Did his car last night,
tyres are brand new,
so they won't match
with the Richardson scene.
Right.
What about prints?
One print from any victim,
that's all we need,
or a... single fibre.
So far he's clean as a whistle.
But then maybe that's it, you know.
Maybe that shows
he's got something to hide.
Is Oldfield pressing charges?
He can't.
It's all still circumstantial,
isn't it?
OPENS LIGHTER
DISTANT SHOUTING
DOOR SLAMS,
CUTLERY CLATTERS
I can do all that.
No, I'll-I'll do it.
Needs doing properly.
It-It were all a load of fuss
over nothing.
Marjorie next door
thought she heard the word...
..Ripper.
They think that...
this Ripper's got a white car,
so that's why they wanted
to talk to me,
cos I've got a white car,
you see, so...
Yeah, but lots of people
have got white cars.
Hundreds.
So why did they want to talk to you?
Your dad'd turn in his grave if
he thought you'd been with whores.
I haven't.
Turn in his ruddy grave.
CUTLERY CLATTERS
RADIO: 'The murder
of a Mrs Jean Jordan,
'a known prostitute,
whose remains were found
'by two young men on an allotment
in Greater Manchester
'earlier this month, brings
the total number of murders to six.
'The man referred to
as The Yorkshire Ripper
'has now claimed more lives
than his Victorian namesake.
'Judith Rose spoke to the detective
spear-heading the inquiry,
'George Oldfield.
'It now appears that the Ripper
has struck for a sixth time.
'And yet, after two years,
no suspects, no formal arrests,
'no evidence as far as the public
have been aware.
'Have you made any progress?
'There are a number of suspects
we're keeping a close eye on.
'What I can say is that
'while this individual may be taking
great care to evade us,
'we are making progress, and the net
is closing all the time.'
Come on.
Ugh!
George? Ronald's here.
RONALD: I had the Daily Express
ring me this morning...
wanting the latest.
They just want the gory details,
don't they? That's all they want.
Never does us any good,
all this press, you know?
Nobody cares about dead prostitutes.
They care more about the donkeys
in Blackpool.
I couldn't take their call,
because I had The Sunday People
on the other line
wanting the same thing.
Wondering what the plan was...
how we intend on stopping this man.
I said nothing, of course.
Well, that's quite right.
Because, George, those are not
the questions I can answer.
In truth,
their questions are my questions.
What is the plan?
How exactly are we planning
on stopping this man?
There's a chap who we like...
..cab driver.
Now, his car matches
the witness statement,
and we have him in Leeds,
Bradford, Manchester,
and he has no alibi
for the key dates.
Now, he is right here.
Six murders.
I know.
Six.
I know. Not all on my watch,
but you don't have to tell me.
All I need is a little bit of luck,
you know,
just one more bit of evidence
pointing to him, and we'll have him.
I can feel it.
You won't be disappointed.
No, George. I won't.
Now, this'll create an open channel,
so I'll be able to hear everything.
Just put it somewhere safe.
I would never have had you down
for a Hawaiian shirt, Andrew.
It were a Christmas present
from t'mother in law.
Don't mean to say you have
to wear it, though, does it?
Look, there she is.
OVER RADIO: 'Maureen?
Yeah.
'I'm Meg. I'll be with you tonight.
Right.
'Shall we go in?
OK.'
MUSIC PLAYS
Are they mine?
BARTENDER: Yeah.
Thanks.
Do you know him?
No.
Do you recognise him, though?
So, what's he looking at you
like that for?
Cos that's what men do.
OVER RADIO: 'Look carefully.
'What about that man?'
Could that man be your attacker?
No.
Just... keep looking.
I think we should go.
We need to stay a bit longer.
Is it cos you think people know
you're stood with a copper?
Is that it?
Can I go home, please?
Maureen, you haven't seen him,
have you?
You must tell me.
Nobody knows him, do they?
No.
They don't know who t'Ripper is.
They don't know
what t'Ripper looks like.
No, but they know me.
They've all seen t'papers.
I'm meant to be looking at them,
but they're all looking at me.
They're not.
I can see it on their faces.
They think I'm dirty.
Maureen... A prostitute.
..but you're not.
Mm. That's what they're thinking.
Cos that's what he does.
Everybody knows
t'Ripper attacks prostitutes,
and everybody knows the Ripper
attacked me.
Don't matter if it's not true.
That's me marked.
That's me scarred...
forever.
PHONE RINGING
CHATTERING
And?
Her name's Marilyn Moore,
attacked last night
near Scott Hall Road.
Scott Hall Road.
Wilma McCann.
And Jane MacDonald.
Not only did she survive, but
she remembers what he looked like.
And she reckons he was interrupted.
He was hitting her,
going at her with a hammer,
then he just stopped, drove off.
We had her sit with a sketch artist
before she forgot his face.
SQUEAKING,
ENGINE RUMBLES
DOORS SLAMMING
CHATTERING
BANGING ON DOOR
INDISTINCT SHOUTING
TERENCE: Man, I've told you,
I haven't done anything!
What are you doing to him?
Please help... Ah!
He's after him!
Hey, what you doing!
Eh, all right love, back inside, OK?
You're hurting me!
All right, let's spin this lot
round, get him up to Bishopsgarth.
Bishopsgarth? It's deserted.
Exactly. What we need now is time.
Put the pressure on.
Get a confession.
Can't do that.
Look, he knows he's done it.
We just need to get him to say it.
Now, I promised Wilf MacDonald
I'd nail him,
so that's what we're doing.
It's not just me saying it.
It's not just me and Dick
and my whole team, it's the victims.
The women that you attacked.
Who's that?
Don't know.
I'll tell you who it is.
It's the Ripper.
See, we asked these women
to describe the man
who attacked them.
And then we do a drawing.
And that drawing...
..is you.
So, you're in the same car...
..you're in the same places...
..and now...
..the same face.
How do you explain that?
I can't.
Cos you're the Ripper?
I'm not.
You're the Ripper. No!
You know, I think that
you don't even know that it's you.
Mm. Cos you're confused.
And that's all right.
Mm. Course you are.
Well, don't worry.
Cos I'm here to help you.
Mm?
Cos it's over now, it's done.
Hm. All we need to do
is just talk through it.
Do you want me to tell your mum?
Is that it? I can do that for you,
don't worry.
And I don't have to go
into the details, don't have to...
..tell her all those things
that you did to those women.
Cos I know you didn't mean it.
They were an accident.
I-I didn't.
Don't fucking lie!
Just gonna keep on denying it
till we take him home.
Who said anything
about taking him home?
We'll keep him here overnight.
Can't do that.
Over two nights...
Two nights? George, come on.
Listen. When he'd stopped stabbing
Jane MacDonald
who had that knife on her t-shirt...
So we keep him here.
We keep on keeping him here
till he coughs for it.
Ah!
There he is. Too punctual
for his own good, our Dennis.
There's one for you.
Ah.
You sip on that.
There's just a couple of things
I want to talk to you about. It's...
some ideas I've had.
As long as it's not about the case.
I get enough of that at work.
'Scuse me a minute.
INDISTINCT CHATTER
WOMAN WHISPERING: Calm down.
Don't know.
MAN WHISPERING: The same person
every time. The same person.
People are looking.
What you staring at?
Just wondering if she's all right.
Yeah?
And if she weren't,
what would you be doing about it?
Nothing.
Just leave it, please.
That's what.
Calm down.
This, um, this new lad Botham,
Bo-tham...
Does he get to start
at Trent Bridge, or doesn't he?
Dennis?
You OK?
Still taking your insulin?
Because this is when it starts.
30 years on the job,
all booze and bad eating,
the moment you stop,
that's when it gets you...
..creeps up behind you...
No.
So, what d'you mean "no"?
No, he doesn't start
at Trent Bridge.
He's not got the experience.
Hm.
DICK: Sat exams here once.
Not been back since, thank God.
I did my detective course
in that room.
Margaret were pregnant with Gillian
and...
I got the call to say
she'd gone into labour.
But they wouldn't let me go.
Said, "What type of detective
would I make
"if I went running off to the wife
all the time?"
I said, "Isn't that what you want
from a detectives, eh?
"People who care?"
Otherwise what's he doing it for?
Exactly.
So they let you go?
Did they bollocks?
We can keep you here
as long as we like.
Don't bother us.
So, it don't matter.
The longer you're here,
safer everyone is.
So what about that question
I asked you before, hm?
Why stab Emily Jackson 52 times?
That's more than the others.
What had she done to deserve that,
eh?
Hm?
Come on.
What's going on in there?
I'm...
Go on, you can tell Uncle George.
I'm thinking I'm a bastard.
TERENCE SNIFFLES
I-I don't like myself.
No.
I-I don't know myself.
Go on.
I-I wanna say it...
TERRANCE SNIFFLES
I wanna...
I wanna tell you that it were me,
that...
..I'm this Ripper...
..just so you'll make it
fucking stop.
Well, it's not gonna stop.
DOOR OPENS
FOOTSTEPS
What're you doing here?
There's been another one.
In Huddersfield this time,
a Black lass.
He's dumped her in some wood-yard.
So... your cabbie has an alibi.
An alibi?
Oh, aye, best alibi there is.
He were here...
with you.
Hey, best of luck
telling him that one.
DOOR SLAMS
DOOR CLOSES
HE SNIFFLES
Terry, is that you?
Yeah.
PHONE RINGS
CHATTERING
Mr Gregory rang.
Thank you.
HE COUGHS
PHONE RINGS
Dick! Get in here!
"Dear Sir, I'm sorry I cannot
give my name for obvious reasons.
"I am the Ripper."
SIGHS
"I've been dubbed a maniac
by the press, but not by you,
"you call me clever, and I am,
"but you and your mates
haven't got a clue.
"That photo in the paper
gave me fits,
"and that bit about me
killing myself, not a chance.
"I've got things to do.
"My purpose,
to rid the streets of them sluts.
"My one regret is that young lassie
MacDonald did not know,
"cos I changed my routine
that night.
"Up to number eight, you say seven,
but remember Preston '75."
Preston 75? That's Joan Harrison.
The one Hoban says wasn't linked.
This is it. This is him.
Nobody knows about Harrison.
Subtitles by accessibility@itv.com