Excuse me, waitress?
I'm afraid the teriyaki
chicken's no longer on the menu.
Oh, I'm sorry, that's
what you had last time.
We've never been here before.
I definitely remember you.
No, we never get up north.
We're just up to see a friend of
ours who moved here last summer.
Your hair was lighter,
you had little round glasses.
Sounds like you.
Henry, don't play along,
it's a gimmick for tips.
Could we get some water?
It was last August,
Saturday the 14th.
You were wearing a
blue dress with polka dots,
your eyes were puffy
like you'd been crying.
The 14th is Darren's birthday.
He said he had to
cancel his party
'cause his old
girlfriend showed up.
They got in a huge fight.
Henry...
I knew it. Damn it.
Ever since that ski trip, when
the two of you disappeared...
I'll go get your water.
Are you all right?
Are you okay?
I can't move my legs.
Picture a door, unlocked
with the key of the mind.
Two medical cases, both
more fascinating than the last.
That actually
makes no logical sense.
This is not
a door to logical sense.
Also, shut up.
Case number one:
a 33-year-old woman,
named something
I can't remember,
you'll see
the irony in a second,
presenting with
temporary paralysis,
high CK levels,
and a perfect memory.
How perfect is perfect?
Perfectly perfect.
Hyperthymesia, complete recall
of every moment of
every day since puberty.
All 7,600,049 of them.
That's cool, huh?
One of only a handful
of recorded cases...
So we have two symptoms:
temporary leg paralysis and elevated CK.
Obviously, you're not suffering
from the same condition,
'cause you've already
forgotten my dramatic voice over.
There's a third symptom.
Her memory's unrelated.
Why? It's a strange
medical phenomenon...
Hyperthymesia's known
to manifest in adolescence.
Yeah, in the whole
five documented cases.
To be related, it'd mean
20 years between symptoms.
Plus, I don't know of any
diseases that cause great memory,
only ones that destroy it.
MRIs show no
evidence of a stroke
or tumors, so probably a toxin.
She's a waitress. They're no
strangers to botulism or alcoholism.
We should search the diner
and where she lives.
Or you could search her brain.
You know, where her
memory lives, and save the gas.
You two, check her home, you
two, get a complete patient history.
We'll see who
gets an answer first.
You said there
was a second case.
Oh. Yeah, thanks.
The case of
the 45-year-old doctor
who just failed his pathology
re-certification exam
is going to lose his board
certification and get fired.
How did you fail it? You
spend half your life in the lab.
I was recovering from the flu. I'm
retaking it next week. It's not an issue.
Normally, I'd let
Darwinism run its course
but Cuddy's in a big tizzy about
her poster boy getting canned.
So, how are we gonna get
the short guy off the short bus?
What about a tutor?
I don't need a tutor.
Tutor it is.
Choose your poison.
Chase, if you prefer
pounding Aussie beers
and commiserating over
the suckiness of divorce.
Masters, if you want
nervous energy, flash cards,
and obnoxious
pieces of arcane trivia.
Foreman, if you need to be
berated by a humorless hardass.
- Foreman.
- Interesting.
You must be more
worried than you look.
Need a consult,
Dr. Wilson.
So, call me in a
week if it still itches.
Thank you.
And be sure to give
Sarah a kiss for me.
Will do.
Who's Sarah?
Her granddaughter, I think?
Early stages of dementia.
What's the consult?
I need your medical opinion,
on what bar we're gonna
hit for happy hour tonight
to kick-off the official end to your
three-month pity-party over Sam.
I can't tonight.
Because of Sarah?
Yes, because of my senile patient's
granddaughter, you caught me.
I'm busy.
Who's Sarah?
Wilson's friend?
My computer crashed. Lost my
database of his acquaintances.
Or you're both lying to me.
I know nothing about Wilson
having a friend named Sarah.
Satisfied?
Ooh!
What are the eight
types of vomitus?
I can show you four right now if
you ask me one more review question.
Hey, you picked me and you
said you wanted a hardass.
No, House said that,
and I pretended to agree
to get him off my back.
I picked you because
I wanted the guy
who doesn't like getting involved
in other people's problems.
I guess I thought
you'd want to skip
the massive public
humiliation of getting fired.
By treating me
like I'm an imbecile?
I'm totally fine. I aced
my first pathology boards.
Medicine has come a long way
in the last 100 years.
You know, I heard of
a guy who knew a guy
who could get
the exam ahead of time.
It was something I heard.
Patient's file said she lost
some weight on a new diet, right?
Yeah, she went vegan.
Are laxatives vegan?
- Hello?
- Where are you?
In the parking garage,
searching Wilson's car.
We have an answer,
magnesium poisoning.
We found a pretty
large stash of laxatives.
Abuse can lead
to hypermagnesemia.
I admit, that's impressively
outside-the-box thinking.
House?
You still there, House?
Everything okay?
No. For a second, I thought
Wilson might have a drug problem.
Turns out it's much, much worse.
Okay... So we push fluids
and wait for her kidneys
to clear the hypermagnesemia?
You'll be waiting a long time
since that's not what she has.
Her BP and respiratory
rate are normal.
While you two were so busy
being impressively outside the box,
you missed the actual box.
Chase and Masters done yet?
Two light beers November 16th,
one really bad glass
of Pinot on the 17th,
nothing from the 18th...
Shouldn't you be working
for NASA or something?
You mean,
why am I just a waitress?
No, I didn't mean...
I'm sorry I...
It's okay.
Remembering something is
not the same as understanding it.
I'm not a genius.
I love my job. I'm great at
it. It keeps my mind busy.
Hi, I'm Dr. House,
and you're not pooping.
Question is,
are you also a klutz?
I guess I'm no clumsier
than most people...
What are you guessing for?
You've got a perfect memory.
I was told there'd be
numbers, dates, fireworks.
What do you want to know?
Let's go back to 2008.
How many trips, stumbles,
falls did you have?
Eleven.
This really works. Cool.
How about 2009?
Twelve.
Even cooler.
Last year?
Twenty.
That's a big spike
in dyscoordination.
If you add constipation,
it's early onset Parkinson's.
Give her a full neuro-exam
and start her on levodopa.
I'm so surprised you broke into
my apartment without telling me.
What is this?
An intervention.
Exhibit A:
a baggie filled
with Nepeta cataria,
also known as...
That better not be
what I think it is.
If you mean your new
junkie girlfriend, then yes.
House...
Okay, fine, I got a cat.
Release the Kraken.
I don't think you appreciate
the severity of your situation.
You're rapidly approaching
end-stage male spinsterism.
That cat, that diabetic cat, that
you're shooting up with insulin
and buying dime
bags of catnip for,
that means you've given up
on ever finding anyone.
Don't you think you're
completely overreacting?
If I'm completely overreacting,
why'd you lie to me?
Because I knew you'd
completely overreact.
Its name is Sarah.
Cats aren't named that, women
are. What the Freud is that about?
Look, I didn't name her, my
neighbor did. She died and I felt bad.
Sarah would've been
destroyed at the shelter.
Who wouldn't want
a cat that croaks
if you're not home
twice a day to shoot it up?
It's like having
your own button on Lost.
You know, I'm pretty
sure there's a river nearby.
I'm keeping her.
Okay, shrug your shoulders
and don't let me push them down.
So, I have to ask,
is there a trick you use?
Mnemonics, meditation?
No. No tricks.
I don't even try, really.
It's just there.
Is my memory going to go
away with the Parkinson's?
It's quite possible.
But we still have
a lot of tests to do
before we have
a definitive diagnosis.
Well, here's hoping for cancer.
Nadia?
Your boss called me.
Sorry, I'm Elena,
Nadia's older sister.
You don't have to be here.
But I'd like to pretend you'd
visit me if I were in a hospital.
You brought daisies.
They're your favorite. No,
they're my least favorite.
I was stung in
the face six times by...
Oh, God.
What's wrong?
My heart...
Fast, wide-complex rhythm.
Get the paddles.
Cardiac involvement
rules out Parkinson's.
So we're back to transient paralysis
and high CK, plus arrhythmia.
Masters, when you finally
blossom into a woman,
would you ever sleep
with a man who had a cat?
Sure.
Wrong, the answer is "no."
Slut.
Any of you ever had a cat?
Any of you ever had sex?
I think as your people say,
"Quod erat demonstrandum."
An excess of catecholamine
could set off an arrhythmia.
It's not a pheo,
her blood pressure is fine.
Maybe we're missing the obvious.
The heart could be
behind everything.
If it's not pumping effectively,
the muscles shut down,
CK elevates,
coordination suffers.
Why are you asking about cats?
Curiosity.
Can we focus here?
Her heart problem started
when Nadia saw her sister.
Stress-induced arrhythmia could
be caused by long QT syndrome.
Her sister was barely
in the room five minutes.
She said they'd been estranged for
over six years. That's a lot of tension.
Run a stress test
to confirm long QT.
It'll have to be drug-induced,
a treadmill would
pull her stitches.
Drugs are never the answer.
We want her heart to go crazy,
there's something
simpler and safer.
Use the sister.
You lied to me.
No, I said I didn't
know anything about
Wilson having
a friend named Sarah.
Under House rules,
that's not a lie.
He's lonely.
The cat's a nice way for
him to get some affection.
That's not the kind of puddy tat
he needs to be getting it from.
He needs the puddy tat
he can tap.
Why is this so important to you?
After divorce number two,
he fell into a committed relationship
with a three-legged Siamese,
stopped answering his phone and
redecorated his place like Gray Gardens.
He wasn't able to
come back to humanity
until a window was left,
suspiciously and heroically, open.
How that cat opened the
window, I will never know.
He just needs more time.
Leave him and the cat alone.
I won't if you will.
Sorry about the daisies.
I always get it confused
if you love or hate them.
Do you want to know
exactly how many times
I've told you that I hate them?
I didn't do it on purpose.
Her heart rate isn't moving.
The sister stress
pot needs stirring.
You want me to start a fight?
Just agitate a little.
Use something from the history.
You're not lying to them.
In fact, you'd be
telling the truth
and serving their medical needs.
You haven't seen each
other in a while, huh?
I heard the story about the
time you hit Nadia with the car.
That must have
been pretty scary.
Why would you tell them that?
They asked about broken bones.
I swear that
I checked my mirrors.
You know that's a lie.
You knew I was getting the mail
and you just didn't
care enough to check.
Just like you didn't care that
you ruined my 23rd birthday...
Nadia, don't start.
You started it by coming here
and acting like you give a crap.
Here we go again! I'm such a
monster because I brought daisies!
You need to leave right now.
Is she going to be okay?
Elena, get out!
You said you'd be 10 minutes.
I couldn't decide on the cheese.
When are you getting an
apartment? Or at least a storage room?
I'll get to it.
I like it here.
They have Video on Demand.
I pulled a practice test
I hate practice tests.
Hey, I never saw
The Usual Suspects,
you want to check it
out before we start?
What are you doing?
You've got three days.
Why is everyone's
first assumption
I'm going to fail
this stupid test?
Maybe because you did?
I was recovering from the flu.
I don't care if you
were dying from Ebola,
you shouldn't have
gotten less than a 70.
You're nothing but
excuses and distractions.
Well, it's a nice match with your
condescension and superiority.
Enjoy the movie.
Kevin Spacey is Keyser Söze.
How is she?
We've started her
on a beta blocker,
it should keep her heart
rhythm under control.
She'll be fine
while we run more tests.
Did you hear she
banned me from her room?
I know I'm not perfect,
but she's...
She can be such a bitch.
She never, ever,
ever lets anything go.
Tell Nadia she doesn't need
to worry about seeing me again.
I started the fight.
We needed her heart rate
to rise, so I provoked you.
You can't play
with people like that.
Maybe if I explained to Nadia...
No, it doesn't matter.
It's just one more
fight for her to remember.
Guess you're both bitches.
Masters.
Smell her breath.
Breathe out.
Ammonia.
What is it?
I think your kidneys
are shutting down.
Failing kidneys puts the heart
back on the list as a symptom.
Maybe she went vegan because
she lost the taste for protein.
Could be amyloidosis.
We would have seen a stiff
heart on the nuclear study.
But autoimmune could account for
multiple organ
systems and paralysis.
There are a number that'd fit:
Guillain-Barre, polymyositis...
MS, polyarteritis nodosa... SLE.
Why are you giving me these?
"Cause while they're off
running all these tests,
you'll be submitting
the insurance forms.
There's an entire
department for that.
Exactly, the Foreman Department.
Of which you're
the foreman, Foreman.
I know you've got the time,
since a little wallaby told me
that you recently vacated
your post as Taub's savior.
He asked.
You're worse than Masters.
How's this my fault?
He doesn't need a tutor,
he needs Ritalin
and a babysitter.
Consider the forms incentive.
If Taub doesn't pass,
they will become a
permanent part of your life.
This isn't really about
Cuddy, is it? It's about you.
You don't want to lose me.
I think you care.
You don't think
you can disgust me
into pulling Foreman off you.
Pulse the patient with
steroids for the autoimmune
and start her on dialysis
for the kidney failure.
Treat the Taub with insults
and small slaps for the obstinacy
and start him on studying
for the brain failure.
No, that's not gonna work.
I have a haircut at 4:00.
I'll be in the... I'll be in the
office in about 20 minutes.
Yeah, okay.
You planted something
in my apartment
to make me think
I'm allergic to Sarah.
Paranoia is the first sign
of Toxoplasma gondii,
the parasite linked to
crazy cat lady disease.
I'm not paranoid.
I'm allergic to ragweed and
dandelion. I am not allergic to cats.
You're trying to gaslight me.
Maybe your subconscious
is afraid that you're
gonna die alone,
and it just comes out
as gibberish and sneezing.
Prove that I'm
overreacting. Boy's night out.
Good Time Charlie's.
They just changed
their slogan to
"Where the trashiest
ladies get trashed."
You do see the hypocrisy
in all this, don't you?
Until recently your lifestyle
of choice was self-exile.
But I never had a cat.
Why don't you
pick me up at 8:007?
You're gonna need
another round of steroids.
In the meantime,
we'll start your dialysis.
So I heard Elena
won't be coming back.
You think I was too hard on her?
We all hold our grudges...
It's not a grudge.
It's common sense,
it's simple math.
She's hurt me more
than she's helped me.
Most people edit their memories.
They add small little lies so
they don't have to face the truth.
My memories remain the same.
My truth never changes
because my truth is the truth.
So no one ever gets forgiven?
Sounds like
a lonely way to live.
No, I do forgive, as long as the
good things they do outweigh the...
I can't...
I can't breathe.
Huh.
What?
Nothing.
I just always pictured
your place with shag carpet.
Like kind of a Mod Squad vibe.
Not because of the black thing.
I always thought you
were more of a Pete...
You're limited to this room
and Marcus's old room.
Where's Marcus?
He tells me he's working
with our uncle in Florida.
He tells you?
You don't look at
or touch anything
that doesn't belong
to you, including food.
You will study
and you will sleep.
You will not leave my
sight until the exam.
Great. I'll be back bright and
early tomorrow and we can...
This is no longer just about
your future, it's about mine, too.
You fail, and I will kill you.
Respiratory distress means we
were wrong about autoimmune.
Could be pulmonary
oedema from the renal failure.
Pulmonary oedema
doesn't give you hives.
You think this is
an allergic reaction?
It can't be, we pumped
her full of steroids.
It can be if it was a
really, really bad one.
I have good news and bad news.
Good news is,
I was right about you
having some autoimmune disease.
You're just allergic
to the dialysis.
But if I can't have dialysis
and my kidneys are failing,
won't that mean I'll die?
Well, you figured
out the bad news.
What do we do?
We look for another case.
Even if we're
right about autoimmune,
we now don't have
time to prove it.
The transplant board will
never give her a kidney.
Maybe we could go around them?
Get a relative to donate.
Which relative?
The sister who walked away and
told you she was never coming back?
We caused this, you know.
They were estranged,
but we made it worse.
That relationship was broken
long before we got there.
Nadia literally keeps score.
She tallies everything.
She decided Elena's done
more bad things to her than good.
Doesn't deserve her affection.
I'm sure she's right.
Unlike everybody
else in the world,
her memory seems to
let her keep a pure,
objective view of
people and relationships.
There's no petty emotions or
agendas fogging the windshield.
Why's that so wrong?
Because it's making her die
alone of kidney failure in Room 2057
Not necessarily. Nadia's
sister is not like her.
I'm sure she's got plenty of
subjective emotions we can exploit.
Why don't you go
channel your guilt,
see if you can get her
to cough up a kidney?
Me?
I'm not good at that type of
thing. Someone else should go.
Someone else
didn't screw this up.
I didn't...
You were just
obeying orders, right?
Go fix this.
I didn't mean to
make you hate her.
And now that her
kidneys have failed...
I've always been a book
and equations person.
People are problematic
and random and messy,
and with sisters,
I mean, I had a cousin
who I was close to
and when our
menstrual cycles synched,
it was like gladiator school...
Do you want me to donate
a kidney to my sister?
Yes.
Okay.
Really? It might not
fix your relationship.
Probably shouldn't
have said that.
Your left.
On your left!
Stop whining already.
I was getting a sniper.
Five minutes left in the break.
But the next level is just
past the cooling tanks.
That was the deal. We take
this break, you do a practice test.
I didn't have the flu.
I just choked.
You make life and death
decisions every day.
You work for House.
You're under constant
pressure and you never choke.
I got a perfect score on
my first pathology boards.
I kept thinking
whatever my score is now,
it's going to be
a measure of the distance
between me and
the man I used to be.
You gotta stop
psyching yourself out.
Well, the last test was before
I lost my wife and my home.
So I'm sure the next
one will go much better.
Sometimes I wake up
in the middle of the night,
and I can't sleep
for hours because
I'm worried I got
the diagnosis wrong.
These things work out.
We found a donor.
It's your sister.
Just thought you should know.
Nadia, can you hear me?
You're coming out
of your anesthesia,
you're going to
feel a bit groggy.
You did great.
Everything's looking good.
Nadia? Come on now,
open your eyes.
Get me three milligrams of lorazepam,
and I'm going to need suction.
Seizures mean the
steroids aren't working.
And we got the tests back. We
were wrong, it's not autoimmune.
Could be acute porphyria.
No abdominal pain.
Did the patient
thank her sister?
No, not yet at least.
See if she will.
What are you trying to find out?
If she's telling the truth.
She claims she
objectively sees reality,
weighing the good
and bad in people.
If that's true, I don't
care how many times
her sister borrowed her
scrunchy without asking.
The free kidney ought
to trump all the bad stuff.
And if it doesn't?
Then she sucks
like the rest of us.
We haven't considered her blood.
Clots could hit her leg,
heart, kidney and brain.
Factor V Leiden: easiest
to treat if we're right.
Start her on heparin.
And ask for the thank you.
How did I do?
Great.
Great? How great?
How many did I miss?
It's not about the numbers.
Don't...
Fifty-four percent?
They make the practice tests
harder than the actual exam.
Oh, my God, now I'm
choking in your living room.
This isn't going to work.
Who are you calling?
I found the guy. He can
sell me a copy of the test.
I know it's cheating,
and I suck as a person,
but the test is
tomorrow morning.
It's not about the cheating,
it's about your confidence.
You steal that test and
you'll never get it back.
I can't handle failing at
one more thing in my life.
You're a good doctor.
I've seen what
you're capable of.
You're fast, you're
decisive, and you're bold.
Those are not the qualities of
someone who needs to steal a test.
There's nothing on it
you don't already know,
you just need to
know you know it.
Keep talking.
We need you on the team.
So we're gonna sit here
and take another practice test,
and we're gonna keep taking
them until you've kicked its ass.
You can do this.
You feel me?
Yeah!
I feel like we just buried
a hooker in the desert.
There'll definitely
be another time
to rise up and
turn things around.
You'll come back from it.
Next time.
How're you feeling?
Not any better.
It will take some time
for the clots to resolve.
Your sister's recovering well.
If you're really adding
up the good and bad...
Can I see her?
Too fat.
Too thin. Too desperate.
Not desperate enough.
Come on, you can
insult them, too.
I'd rather not.
If you objectify them now,
you'll feel more comfortable
when you tie them to a
table in your basement later.
Or whatever.
Okay.
Too armpit-fatty?
Whoa. Too hot.
I actually know her. She's the
new barista at my coffee shop.
She's getting her
masters in finance.
Brains and boobs.
The mother lode.
Total moron
as a barista, though.
Every drink I order, ends
up with whipped cream on it.
Even when I say,
"No whip."
Girlfriend, that means
she's into you.
Okay.
"Hi, there.
"Wilson, James Wilson.
"I'm a doctor.
"Hoping that's enough to close,
"but I'm also a social moron.
"And I have a cat."
She said my coffee
is not the only thing
she'd like to put
whipped cream on.
But is she interested?
Oh, my God.
Bartender!
Champagne for everyone!
Hi.
Thank you for saving my life.
I love you, you know.
I was thinking about those times
we went up to Spofford
Lake in the summer.
Whenever we took out the canoe,
you'd tie up my
life vest for me.
And in the afternoons,
you'd sneak me
into the lodge so we
could steal popsicles.
Maybe we could go back.
I could drive us up there.
We could get a cabin,
and maybe rent a canoe.
Wow, I haven't
thought of Spofford in...
Nadia, are you okay?
Elena, I'm sorry.
I can't do this!
Can you stop? Just stop
pushing me for a minute.
I understand now why you
stuck yourself in that diner,
away from friends,
away from family.
You can't forgive anyone.
I don't think
you weigh anything.
I think you're
like a lot of people,
you focus on the bad
memories instead of the good.
I don't have a choice.
Nadia, put your hand
in your lap for a moment.
I'm not doing that.
I know.
It's an involuntary
movement called chorea.
What does it mean?
It means we still don't
know what's wrong with you.
Thank you.
Do you know if that OR
nurse that Wilson liked
ever broke up
with her boyfriend?
I thought your
Wilson fetish was over.
I'm putting together
a second string
in case things don't go well
with the well-breasted barista.
You've got to
let that guy alone.
He's not supposed to be alone.
Is that what this is about?
You feel guilty because Wilson's
the one that's alone and not you?
You still don't
think you deserve this.
Have you met me?
Your happiness
doesn't take his away.
It's okay to enjoy it.
Yeah?
Chorea. Rules out
the clotting disorder.
It means we're
back to square one.
If it's hit her brain, that could
mean she doesn't have long.
So then the question becomes,
"Will the sister show up at the funeral?"
She tried to reconcile.
But the bad memories crowded
out the good and she ran.
Nobody's perfect.
What else?
Come on, the woman has
all the information we need,
she's a bottomless
diagnostic library.
Maybe we're missing something
from the apartment, some lifestyle thing.
Yeah, it's all muscle strain from
doing her hundreds of jigsaw puzzles.
We should do another MRI.
A brain hemorrhage would...
Hey, how many puzzles?
Okay, I was exaggerating dozens.
Do a peripheral blood smear,
look for acanthocytes.
I'll be right in.
Remember me?
Just kidding.
So, jigsaw puzzles.
I find them calming.
You ever left one unfinished?
No, that would drive me crazy.
Speaking of...
Why are you doing that?
More important
question is, why are you?
It's just a habit.
It's a habit that compels you in
an obsessive way that's so bad
it's a disorder.
I don't have OCD.
Each brain with OCD has
its own way of filtering it.
Some people wash their hands
and hoard TV Guides,
you do puzzles
and hoard memories.
So what we thought was a gift,
was just you literally
obsessing over your own life.
That's why I can't stop the
memories even when I try.
But everything else?
My kidneys...
Your memory was a symptom
of a symptom of a larger disease.
You have McLeod's syndrome.
It's a rare genetic disorder
that affects the nervous
system, blood and can cause
OCD.
Am I gonna die?
It can't be cured.
But your various symptoms
can be managed with medication.
Best case scenario, you
can live another 20 years.
If it's any solace,
everybody dies alone.
Probably isn't.
How'd it go?
Well, it's hard to choke when
you have all the answers.
Look at it this way, it's better
to suck at taking one test
than to suck at
saving people's lives.
Wow!
Rachel thought it was too big,
and I can't keep it in my hotel room.
You're giving it to me?
I couldn't stand
the thought of you
having company over
with that other TV.
It's embarrassing.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Hey, look.
I have the room.
You could stay if you wanted to.
Just until you
find your new place.
Who else am I gonna play
SavageScape with?
We could do that online
from separate houses.
Will you shut up?
Okay.
How're you feeling?
Much better.
I don't believe what House said.
I'm not sure even
House believes it anymore.
You said you didn't have a
choice to be the way you are.
Now you do.
These are SSRIs. They've
been effective in treating OCD.
You mean lose my memory?
Not lose it entirely, it'll just
become more like anyone else's.
My memory
is the only thing that has
ever made me special.
Maybe so.
But if you want to be special,
you're going to have to be alone.
Hey!
Hey.
Those are for Sarah.
Are they poisoned?
You and your paranoia.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I really should find a better
place to store my ragweed.
It's a very nice gesture,
but it's still in the apartment.
So, I want to hear all the
dirty, dairy-specific details
of your night
with Java the Slut.
All right.
First of all, all real.
Second, a true connoisseur
of the dark arts of...
I flaked. I walked her to
her car and said good night.
I will get back into it. You just
need to give me a little more time.
I'll give you 10 days.
Fine.
Ew!