Let's hear it for Della Cart.
Dude, your sister
kicks serious ass.
Competed in the boys'
league this year.
Kicked their asses, too.
Nice job, Del. You...
I went faster on the 50-50.
You were right.
All right.
Who wants next?
Yeah, yeah, I'm a little biased.
Custom decks.
Start the bidding at 400 bucks.
Trust me, the kids'll force
their parents to buy them.
You got to see this.
You made a great
event today, hon.
Fast enough for you?
I'm already in a wheelchair,
what are you so afraid of?
All right!
That wasn't what I meant!
Della? You okay?
Mom, Dad!
We got to stop parking like
this. People are gonna talk.
Well, that's why I plan
on doing some talking first.
I want us to formally report our
relationship to Human Resources.
Okay. You get them,
I'll cover everybody else.
I would appreciate it if we could
keep it quiet until we had that meeting.
It's gonna be hard with me
grabbing your ass all day.
Grabbing stops at the threshold.
Of the parking garage.
Handicapped plates.
I get special access.
I just don't want our
relationship affecting our jobs.
Or the other way around.
Why, Dr. Cuddy,
how was your weekend?
I got a call about
a case for you.
14-year-old. EMTs think
her heart stopped while she...
Sounds great.
You haven't seen it yet.
I sense something
fascinating about it.
I'm gonna get us in to
see HR this afternoon.
Think you can hold
your tongue till then?
Mom!
Fine.
People are gonna
know soon enough.
I think I can
hold it till lunch.
I'm seeing Cuddy.
Generally without
her clothes on.
Use your imagination. Hope it's
got a wide-angle lens.
You don't actually need that.
I'm gonna go check my
office for whoopee cushions.
This is not a prank.
This is not me
walking out the door.
Really? You and Cuddy?
For reals.
Foreman can translate.
So, junior miss everything.
Skateboarder, basketballer,
science clubber, seal clubber.
I'm actually guessing
with that last one.
Healthy one day,
heart arrhythmia the next.
Are you sure it's
a good idea to be
yanking on the chain of command?
Way to go, House.
I'm surprised you two
didn't get together sooner.
EKG, echo and head
CT are all spotless.
There's nothing on
her neurological exam.
Interesting. In favor,
indignant, indifferent.
I think I'd like
the female perspective.
Or Thirteen's.
Where is she?
She's gone.
She said was
taking a leave of absence,
wanted us to think it was for
a Huntington's study in Rome.
They've never heard of her.
Cell and home phone
are disconnected,
apartment's
already been vacated.
And what's with
the death's head cane?
They didn't have a
death's ass cane in my size.
I guess we'll just have to wait.
Conditions that cause intermittent
heart arrhythmias. Taub?
Three years you've been trying to
game out Thirteen. Now you don't care?
Sorry, not caring
about Thirteen is not
part of the differential
for heart arrhythmia.
But you do get a home
version of the game.
Patient's brother has severe
congenital muscular dystrophy.
Life expectancy of about 25.
If she's had a latent case of it...
Wouldn't be sudden-onset.
Foreman?
Do you know something
about Thirteen that we don't?
She's entitled to her privacy.
Just as I'm entitled to a diagnosis.
And you're glossing over
Thirteen's departure
because you actually respect
somebody's privacy.
I agree. It's weird
of me not to care.
So either I'm a changed
man because of Cuddy,
or I'm pretending
to be a changed man
because I do know
something about Thirteen
and I'm trying to
throw you off the scent,
or I've just gone nutty-bananas
because I lost a patient.
All of which you are free to
discuss after I get a diagnosis.
If it's long QT syndrome,
any startling stimulus in that skate
park could've triggered the arrhythmia.
Loud noise, flashing lights.
Scare the patient to death
to confirm long QT.
Fine. If you insist, do it in a room
with one of those thingamabobs
that brings people back to life.
Scare test is insane.
The scare test is legitimate,
simulates real-world conditions.
This fling with Cuddy's insane.
Flare gun? Scary enough?
How about just telling her
we're planning this stupid test?
And I'm hoping House and
Cuddy are more than just a fling.
It's clearly mellowed him out.
He didn't even care about Thirteen.
Right, the guy who ordered us to
stop the patient's heart is mellowed out.
It's gonna be horrible,
because it's doomed.
Which is just gonna make
House 50 times more of a crank.
Firecrackers. We can
hide them under
one of those covered food trays.
Find any itching
powder in your hanky?
Any fake poo in
your desk drawer?
Yes, the lack of
dime-store pranks
is proof that you're
actually dating Cuddy
and not just mocking me
for being worried about you.
What do I have to do
to prove this to you?
Tattoo a cane on
her inner thigh?
Tattoo her inner
thigh on my cane?
You told everybody, didn't you?
Repeatedly.
This one's not buying it.
Need a little help.
I'm not selling it.
And it's time for our
meeting at Human Resources.
Human Resources. Now why would
I need to go to Human Resources?
House, you've been
to Human Resources
74 times in the last six weeks.
Never after doing this.
Well, I'm convinced.
Come on, one peck. Just
enough to arouse him a little.
Hey, I'm not even...
I didn't mean you.
If I confirm it, can we leave?
Yes.
It's true.
I've been more passionate
with my great-aunt.
Mabel? Up high.
Are we done here?
She didn't even ask me to cough.
I think you straightened
out my limp a little.
Now, how would you describe
the exact nature of the relationship?
Have you ever seen Wild Kingdom?
Those insects that rip their
partners' heads off after copulating.
It's a sexual relationship.
Go slowly now.
He's writing it down.
I believe that I can still
supervise Dr. House effectively,
but we both want to follow
hospital policy to the letter.
Our concern is to make sure
that there's no conflict of interest,
no liability for the hospital...
You think we're gonna
sue if things go south?
Let me tell you,
she actually does go...
House.
Let him talk.
I know that
you're not going to sue,
because you are both
going to sign love contracts,
consensual
relationship agreements.
Well, obviously
outside counsel will have
to review the crotchless
undies clause.
We'll also need to watch for
any favoritism toward Dr. House.
Does that mean she has
to sleep with everyone?
I promise not to give him a
raise or a promotion of any kind.
There's got to be a joke there
about keeping up with inflation.
Or bias against him.
Are there any supervisory issues
with Dr. House's
current caseload?
Nope. Current case
Is solved.
Patient has long QT,
we're gonna scare her
into a cardiac
arrest to confirm.
No, we're not.
Okay. No, we're not.
See? Everything
is under control.
I know you're still planning
your ridiculous scare test.
But the patient is nowhere near
sick enough to justify the risk.
An angiogram and an EP study
are much safer, and very effective.
Fair point. I'm not
doing the scare test.
I'd invite you to watch me
not doing the test,
but having not done
it many times before,
trust me,
it's pretty not interesting.
House?
Scare test was not approved.
Do an angio and
an EP study instead.
First of all,
that's not as effective as...
How come you're not doing
the more specialized test?
This test is virtually
just as effective.
And Dr. House puts a
premium on patients' safety.
But frequently changes his mind?
Hugo, give him
a break. I'm fine.
You should go
to the bathroom before we go.
We've been hydrating
you for quite a while.
I don't have to pee.
Once we start the test, you won't
be able to move for at least an hour.
I really don't have to pee.
How much fluid
have we given her?
2.5 liters.
When's the last time
you went to the bathroom?
Last night, I guess.
What does that mean?
Your daughter's kidneys
seem to be failing.
So what could cause her heart
to stop, and her urine not to drop?
House, I was expecting
your relationship with Cuddy
to complicate
our work long-term.
I am now concerned it might
be affecting us short-term.
All due respect.
None taken.
I listen to Cuddy all the time. She's
my boss. Also yours, by the way.
You'd listen, then tell her she's being
an idiot, and do whatever you want.
I find I can skip the idiot part
when she's not being an idiot.
And since the scare test
would've led to this same dead end,
she was right to stop it. Which
means your problem's about you.
This should be interesting.
Losers love company.
And if even a misanthrope like
me has a chance at happiness,
it's gonna be pretty
lonely on that landfill
of loser-dom you
call a marriage.
Heart, kidneys, go.
Could be Fabry disease.
Lipid deposition in her tissues.
Dad's history was clean.
What about protein deposits? They
wouldn't show in her parents' history.
Amyloidosis.
Explains both the symptoms.
Marrow transplant to treat.
Her brother's a match.
Confirm and do.
I've been experiencing
fatigue and weakness.
Wouldn't have anything to do with
the fact that you're 102 years old?
Usually he's strong as an ox.
102-year-old ox.
He has tingling in
his feet and his legs.
I want a full battery of tests.
Carbon dating?
I'll pay cash if
it's not covered.
It's nice of you to
float your friend...
He's not my friend, he's my
father. He's 22 years older than me.
Well, if that's true, he's
definitely had his jowls done.
Statistically, if he didn't
have these symptoms,
he'd be like most
people of his age,
dead for the past
several decades.
Do the tests, I'm sick.
You have a bad case
of natural causes.
Do the damn tests.
If the vial fills with sand,
we take that as a bad sign.
Hugo should be here.
Why'd you ask him to leave?
We wanted to be able
to discuss this openly.
But it obviously affects him.
Honey, let the doctor finish.
It's a standard procedure.
We use general anesthesia,
harvest a very small amount of his...
No. I'm not taking
my brother's marrow.
Del, it's... These
harvests are harmless.
With the meds we give,
there's almost no pain,
almost no risk of
infection... Almost?
His life's hard enough as it is.
Small problem
with the treatment.
Patient won't take marrow
from steel wheels?
We're finding another match.
And how do you know?
What other problem could there
be with a problem-free procedure?
Boys' sports, science club.
She's living his life, not hers.
Makes sense she's being
a self-denying moron.
She loves her brother, she's
thinking selflessly. How is that at all...
Moronic? Hmm. If I could only
think of a harm-free medical treatment
she'd turned down lately.
You're right. If everyone
were more selfish,
the world would
be a better place.
See? I can skip the idiot part
when you're not being an idiot.
Yeah, I had that same facial
expression for the first 48 hours.
Had another one, too, but
only for 15 seconds at a time.
I'm happy for you. You're
happy for you. This is huge.
So who's gonna supervise you?
Cuddy.
I guess maybe that can work.
Maybe? Nothing's changed.
You showed up for
clinic hours, voluntarily.
Fine, a little bit has changed.
House, everything's changed.
You're sleeping together.
You want something
from her besides
sign-off on scaring
your patient to death.
You talked to Taub.
He's worried about you.
He's a jerk.
I'm worried, too.
Do I need to say it?
I want this to work.
I'm not doing
anything differently.
She changed my mind
about one diagnostic test.
And she was right.
Even though it's your
emotional default, stop worrying.
I can handle it.
I hear you're a pretty
fierce skateboarder.
I do okay.
All your activities,
don't they seem
like things a 16-year-old
boy would do?
Some people might think
you're trying to live his life for him.
I am.
Sort of.
I got into skateboarding when
some of Hugo's classmates did,
and he realized
he could never do it.
It's the same with a lot of
things. We live through it together.
And you're not worried you're being
selfless to the point of self-denial?
You've never been
inspired by someone?
Why don't you take your pills.
Need some help in here.
Hemothorax, we need
to brooch her now.
Clear an OR. She's
drowning in her own blood.
It's not amyloidosis.
She's bleeding to death,
out of her lung.
I want to fill
a quarter of it with foam.
That'd stop the
bleeding, all right.
Thought it made more sense
than diet and exercise.
And if she doesn't have enough
lung function left, you'll have killed her.
The only alternative is
slowly suturing the lung,
hoping the bleeding
stops in time
and she doesn't die on her own.
But we would walk
away with clean hands.
Except for all the blood.
You're right. Faster and
riskier is better. Foam the lung.
You got a green light?
No. Suture the lung.
Scalpel, rib spreader.
I can't handle it.
What happened?
She said yes, I heard no.
But I didn't actually hear no.
I just was sure
that's what she meant.
The way she tilted her head
and half-arched her eyebrow.
But what do I even
care what she meant?
She said yes,
that's all that matters.
I'm screwing this up.
It's not completely bad, House.
You care enough to pull your
punches. That's not a bad thing.
But you and Cuddy
have got to figure out
a way of avoiding this problem.
Set some ground rules.
Yeah. I have to
avoid this problem.
If I can restrict
our interactions
to places where neither
of us are wearing pants.
Yeah. That's not avoiding the
problem, that's avoiding the issue.
Since avoidance is my plan
for dealing with the issue,
technically,
that's not avoiding it.
Thanks.
No problem.
The stitching worked.
This time.
No guarantee bowing
to Cuddy'll work next time.
Heart arrhythmia, kidney
failure, and now a bleeding lung...
I don't want to criticize
your girlfriend, but...
Hey, you've been on me for
years to respect someone's opinion.
Just because I had to go outside
this group to find one I respect...
Multi-system involvement
centered in the lung. Sarcoidosis.
Doesn't explain the hemothorax.
TB can infect all three organs.
Skin test was negative.
What about Goodpasture's?
Affects the lungs, kidneys.
And autoimmune explains
the out-of-the-blue arrhythmia.
Goodpasture's it is.
Immunosuppressants
and plasmapheresis to treat,
kidney biopsy to confirm.
Dr. House!
Don't tell me.
Your father's hairline is
receding and he needs more tests.
He's 102, his next test
is an autopsy.
Look, I love the old man, but I've
got to get him out of the damn house.
He can't do anything without me.
He needs to be in
a care facility.
So tell him.
He's a big boy now.
I can't.
I'm his whole life. But if
it comes from a doctor...
That's very generous.
When you were 30.
Pretend to run the tests.
And then tell him he
can't live with me anymore.
I didn't run into
you all afternoon.
I missed you.
Busy day.
Maybe we should plan
on lunch tomorrow.
Problem is, at lunch
you tend to wear tops.
This is much better.
Cuddy and I are naked. So
I'm having trouble focusing.
Use small words.
Kidney biopsy was clean,
SO we re-checked a piece
of her lung from the OR.
You lost me. Sorry,
who is this calling again?
It's not Goodpasture's.
There's intimal thickening
of the blood vessels.
And lymphocytic infiltrate.
We tested for LAM, it's positive.
Plus her lung's fried. She
needs a donor lung to live.
Which is the only
treatment for LAM anyway.
Taub's gone to
the transplant committee.
They may have
found a donor lung.
So this call is
purely expositional?
We should really get dressed. I
told the nanny I'd be home by 9:00.
And I slipped the nanny 40
bucks, told her to stay till 10:00.
Really?
Really.
Good news.
Surgery was uneventful.
But the donor lung started
failing about an hour into recovery.
We know we're right about
LAM, tests confirmed it.
Well, that leaves
us with two options.
Her body is
rejecting the new lung,
or we should've
rejected the new lung
because it's infected.
Let's biopsy,
see which one it is.
No guarantee we'd
hit the affected spot.
If we give steroids for rejection,
it'd make an infection worse.
If we give antibiotics for
infection, it'd make rejection worse.
Which worse is worse?
If we treat her for infection and we're
wrong, she'll be dead within hours.
And if we treat for
rejection and we're wrong?
She'll probably
hang on a day or two.
You're assuming her rejection's
hyperacute. Odds are it isn't.
Got to head off
the worst worse first.
I studied under Dr. Seuss.
Start with IV methylprednisolone
for hyperacute rejection.
If that fails, we'll switch her
to broad-spectrum antibiotics,
and hope we're not too late.
Cat got your legs?
We just decided to give meds that
could kill the patient, based on a guess.
You need approval from Cuddy.
And she'll want to
take the safer course.
And you're gonna fold
like an origami crane.
So I'll just wait here until
we get our actual orders.
Fine. You do it.
Tell her she's being an idiot for
always choosing the safer course.
She's sitting on her ample, if
well-formed, bureaucratic ass
while our patient's dying.
We'll see who folds
like an origami shrimp.
You want me to
get Cuddy's approval?
I've gotta be
somewhere important.
Sitting at your desk?
I'm running late.
Forget the tests.
I think junior might have a
few words to say about that.
I love him but he can't let go.
40 bucks says he can.
I can't do anything without
him helping me like I'm senile.
If I go back there,
I'm gonna rip his throat out.
You sure you won't warm up
to him over time?
Skip the blood work.
Tell my son it's grim news, I
need to be in a nursing home.
A private room.
Make it a suite.
It'll be our little secret.
I sit around on
my "bureaucratic ass"?
I was relaying your words.
I said "well-formed."
I said "well-formed"!
What were you...
I needed to be aggressive.
You're an idiot.
She was siding
with Foreman's analysis.
The odds are against it
being hyperacute rejection...
Stop.
I agree with you. That was
our analysis from the start.
If you've got a problem with a
team decision, you come to me.
I'm sorry.
I'll deal with him later.
I said "well-formed."
People who have not seen Cuddy
naked should not throw stones.
She does have great cans.
Cuddy has House on
such a short leash,
she might as well
start giving him chew-toys.
Let's give the antibiotics
at least another hour.
Amazing. And House hasn't
given you one ounce of grief
for your complete lack
of interest in his love life.
Did it ever occur to you
that House is just happy,
and could give a crap about
other people's lives because of it?
Well, that's ironic
and depressing.
And by that logic,
the reason you don't
give a crap is
because you're happy.
Which means you've got
someone new giving you chew-toys.
You're one-fourth right.
Wait. Are you saying...
You're dating four women?
BP's dropping. Means the
antibiotics aren't working.
Put her in Trendelenburg.
Can we save the lung?
Believe it or not,
we've got a better chance now.
This means it's rejection,
not infection.
We'll start her on IV
methylprednisolone right away.
Wow. You hate salad. She's
really got you tied up in knots.
I caved. Through
an intermediary.
I need a plan C.
What you need is a plan that
you actually develop with Cuddy.
Antibiotics didn't work.
And then steroids didn't work.
Her new lung's ruined and
it's not rejection or infection.
The only two options were wrong.
Unless it's not LAM.
It is LAM,
the test was positive.
Then the test had to be wrong.
Deep fryer's working again.
Still working on that?
That was here when I
sat down. I need to think.
I want to make sure you're
trying everything to save my sister.
Everything.
That must be it.
See, I thought you guys
checked the box marked,
"Try every other thing."
I'm the one that's
supposed to die first.
I'm the damaged one, not her.
She never even gets a cold.
Damage has a way of
spreading to everyone around you.
For example, your
obvious emotional damage
is now making me have a
philosophical conversation,
instead of dealing
with your sister.
See how that might be damaging?
Never?
When's the last time
you had a cold?
Any minor aches,
swelling, anything?
It's been years.
She never gets colds.
I didn't ask when's the
last time she mentioned it,
I asked when she had one,
even a tiny one.
It's nothing. Sometimes
my ears ache a little.
So now tell me
the rest of the nothing.
My chest, soreness,
some congestion...
You never said
anything about that.
I barely noticed it until that
skateboarding tournament in Denver.
How long ago?
A year?
Cold's nothing. When I think of
what Hugo goes through every day...
Yeah, we get it. Your brother,
the saint, his sister, the martyr.
Thank God you followed me.
Now you can go back to
the transplant committee
while I get confirmation.
Confirmation of what?
What causes low-level
cold symptoms for a year,
can ruin two lungs,
is immune to drug therapies
and gets worse in cities
nicknamed Mile-High?
A clotting disorder?
She has a nasty case
of sickle cell trait.
Her heart arrhythmia
wasn't sudden at all.
The screwed up blood cells
screwed up the blood vessels,
which gave us the
screwed up positive for LAM.
If she'd told us
about her symptoms sooner,
like, ever,
she might not be dying.
You were right after all.
I never said sickle...
If everyone were more selfish,
the world would be a better place.
So she's gonna die.
Unless we can find...
She burned through
one donor lung,
transplant committee's never
gonna give her a second one.
Well, then, I guess
you're right again.
Unless we don't
need their approval.
You can't advise
your patient's parents
to take marrow and
half a lung from their son.
Guess I could just chat
with them about the weather.
But the blood tests just
confirmed sickle cell trait,
so they might be curious
about the only treatment option.
Though we are having
weird weather lately.
There is a huge reason not to
take lungs from living patients.
So their siblings can die?
Their son has CMD.
As it is, he's gonna die
of respiratory failure by 25.
We could cut whatever
time he has left in half.
That qualifies as a bad reason
for them to reject the idea.
It's a much worse reason
for them not to get the choice.
It's coercive to tell them.
You ever hear of "do no harm"?
That was second year, right?
I had mono all that fall.
Their son's not
even our patient.
Why don't we just
take half a lung from
some guy in the clinic
with a toothache?
It's a great idea. Now I can
give the parents two options.
We don't compromise
one life for another.
Okay.
"Okay"? Seriously?
You made an argument.
If you don't want me to defer
to you, why make it at all?
But are you deferring to me just
because we're seeing each other?
Maybe.
Yeah. I think so.
Look, this is screwing me up.
Why is it not screwing you up?
It is.
I don't know why I okayed
you foaming that lung.
I realized it was wrong
as soon as I said it.
I knew it! I knew when
you tilted your head.
House, we are screwing this up.
I'm gonna call HR.
And find someone else to
supervise you, as soon as they can.
I've got your test results.
You have the metabolism,
blood counts,
liver and kidney function
of a 92-year-old.
Which is great
'cause you're 102.
What's not so great is the
average life expectancy is 78.
It is my recommendation
that you move into a home
with round-the-clock care.
I can't believe it.
Can't my son give me
round-the-clock care?
Not unless you've done
your two-year certification
in Tiburon swab technology.
There must be some other way.
Just because he has
a little tingling,
and some trouble
feeling hot and cold,
and some difficulty...
You can't feel hot and cold?
Not lately.
But at my age...
Show me your teeth.
Dentures. Fairly worn.
I'm guessing 10-years-old.
Show me your denture cream.
Why would he
carry denture cream?
Because he has zinc poisoning.
To get it from denture cream,
he'd have to take so much of it.
Trust me, he never
leaves home without it.
How much do you use, Pop?
About a tube a day.
I buy it online.
So what does this mean?
Bizarrely, this explains
all your symptoms.
Better-fitting dentures,
you'll be fine.
Medically, there's no
reason to go anywhere.
Hospital rebate.
You might want to put it
toward couples therapy.
The transplant committee's
never gonna give
my daughter another
lung, are they?
No.
Are there any other options?
We're looking into it.
Looking into what?
Please.
Tell me, give me
some kind of hope.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
We're talking about my daughter's
life, what can't you tell me?
If there's any chance
you can save her,
anything you can try.
We can take marrow and
half a lung from your son.
It would likely shorten
his life significantly.
He'd never be able to go on
a respirator if he needed to.
Most people with CMD need to as
their respiratory function declines.
How long do we have to decide?
Morning at the latest.
Thank you.
Where are my parents?
They're probably dealing with
committee issues or something.
They were arguing.
I saw my mom crying, looked
like my dad was yelling at her.
They care about you a lot.
Hugo was a marrow match.
We're way past that now.
They want a lung from him,
too. Is that what this is about?
No. It's nothing you
need to worry about.
Everybody's working on getting
you the best care possible.
How do they expect us
to go on from here?
We make a choice,
we live with it.
There's no living with it,
no matter what we decide.
Still cold and clammy,
she had a respiratory arrest.
Oh, my God!
What is she doing here?
She figured out
what was going on.
She's pinking up.
She must have
yanked off her IVs and oxygen.
Came here to die.
By unhooking
herself from everything,
she delivered
a hypoxic insult to her body.
It started a downward spiral.
If you're gonna make a
decision, you're running out of time.
HR can't find you
a new supervisor.
How come?
Because you're
unsupervisable, House.
Two department chairs
threatened to quit.
Well, I guess we're
stuck with each other.
I have no idea why
I'm making this call,
or if it's
the right call to make.
But if you feel
strongly about presenting
the parents your
treatment option,
you can do it.
Thank you. I will.
Several hours ago.
You told them?
I told him.
He came to my office.
I'm sorry.
Well, I should probably
be more mad at you.
Yeah.
Dr. House?
We've decided.
We're not gonna take
the lung from our son.
She's still on the waiting list.
We're gonna do whatever
we can to find her another...
What ginormous crack pipe
have you people been sucking on?
House!
Are you gonna
pretend that you're not
choosing your own
daughter's death?
Our daughter doesn't want it.
Probably doesn't want
to floss her teeth either.
She's a mindless teenybopper.
Don't put this on them.
What do you mean
"put it on"? It is on them.
As much as they may want
to "pass the lung" here...
Of course they do. You're
handing them an impossible choice...
Life has handed them
a crappy choice.
And they're picking
the crappier option.
Trading who-knows-how-many
healthy decades
for four or five years in which
roller-boy will be a limp rag.
Not everything is
a math equation.
You need me to explain the
difference between decade and year?
Their son is a human being.
You know what they are,
right? Intrinsic value.
We don't get to decide...
Come on.
We do it every day.
The two of them
needed the same lung...
He needs to keep
the one he's got.
You don't get to
play God by ripping out...
That train left the station when
we learned to do transplants.
The rest is just paper-pushing.
And of course now, we're
onto your real area of expertise.
I thought we were
moving onto yours,
bullying your patients into
embracing your own lack-of-a-moral...
Hugo, honey...
We didn't mean for
you to hear any of this.
Hugo, please.
I want you to take half my lung.
No.
I am not.
You do so many great things.
I just watch.
I get to watch
and coach and cheer.
But that's not me out there.
Never will be.
If you take this piece
of me, carry it with you,
then I really can share
in everything you do.
This is the great thing
I can do with my life.
Don't make me live without you.
We got lucky.
I did give them
an impossible choice.
The kid took it away from them.
That fight
was the first honest interaction
you and I have had
since we came back to work.
If we're painfully, brutally
honest with each other,
maybe we'll get lucky again.
You've got a big ass.