Darrien?
What the hell happened?
We got to get you to a hospital.
No, no, you're a doctor,
just stitch me up.
It's more complicated
than that. We need to...
The cops will be waiting
for me at the hospital.
They're gonna bust me back
inside just for being with felons.
You stay here, they bust me.
I can't go back, Remy.
Neither can I.
God forbid, you die,
I'm up for manslaughter.
I'll find someone else.
You leave, you bleed out.
You're gonna die. Stop!
Promise me you won't
take me to the hospital.
I promise.
Look at how much
fun she's having.
That's because he has
two functioning legs
capable of supporting
her body weight.
So do I.
You told me most of
your muscle was cut out.
I was going for
the sympathy discount.
Been taking some
experimental medicine.
Yeah, I got a lot of clients
on experimental medicine.
You want proof?
Okay, this amp stack weighs
way more than you do.
See?
Now, even if those implants
were made of adamantium,
I'd still be able to...
Sorry. Cramp.
I'm sure.
I'm not gonna be needing
your services tonight after all.
Bowel's intact.
Inferior vena cava is fine.
Your liver got nicked,
but it feels clotted off.
I don't see any other
signs of internal bleeding.
So I'm okay?
Define "okay".
Just because I don't see
bleeding doesn't mean it's not there.
105 over palp. I'm gonna check
your pressure every two minutes.
If you dip below 90, it means it
is there and we have a problem.
Oh, sorry.
I should get to work.
Wait.
We'll talk more in
the morning. Ruby...
Goodnight, Eric.
You two breaking up?
She's pregnant.
I need a drink.
There was a raid.
Andre needed to do something
to slow the cops down.
He stabbed you as a distraction?
It didn't work.
Cops called an ambulance,
left me lying there.
Come on, give me crap.
I know what I told
you about him,
but it's not his fault
I started using again.
It's mine.
What? According
to this, you're dead.
You have no blood pressure.
You barely have a pulse.
Am I dying? You're
talking and alert,
SO your brain is getting blood.
Pulse in your right arm
is fine, so is your BP.
Hello. THIRTEEN ON
PHONE: Are you busy?
Yeah, I'm about
to go out. Great.
Can you do me a huge favor?
I need you to go to the hospital
and check out a portable
ultrasound machine for me.
Who's the father? I have
a leak in my bathroom,
and my guy won't come take a
look at it till tomorrow morning,
and an emergency plumber
is 200 bucks an hour.
Dr. House.
Dr. Riggin.
Figured you'd be
wrapping up the trial by now.
I just wanted to give
you a hearty mazel tov.
And don't forget the Nobel Prize
for developing an incredibly
expensive rat poison.
What do you mean?
What happened?
Tumors.
Just look at these things.
Any indication the rats
were getting sick?
Just some cramping.
Their legs would stiffen up.
They were having
trouble moving around.
We just thought their bodies were
adjusting to the increase in muscle mass,
but in a day or so,
they just started dying.
Oh, well, get a new compound
to play with next week.
One portable ultrasound,
extra pepperoni.
Thank you so much.
I might be late tomorrow.
Your socks are dry. And
unfortunately, So is your shirt,
which means you either
just changed to greet me,
or you need this
for something medical.
I am a doctor.
She's my friend.
I was in prison.
You killed your own brother?
Yes, it was awful and
devastating, but it wasn't murder.
He was sick and
he wanted to die,
and I promised I would help.
Now please stop pacing
and help me find this thing.
Have you talked to anybody
about it? I mean, are you okay?
No, I may have
an aortic arch aneurysm.
Oh, wait, that's her.
Either help me or leave.
I'm having trouble
getting a clear look.
Try a long axis view
from the suprasternal notch.
Wait! Put on some
gloves, she's got Hep-C.
Wonderful.
I take it you two
were cellmates.
Just friends.
She saved me.
There's a culture in prison.
If you don't have someone to show
you how to get the stuff you need,
or stay away from the stuff
you don't, you're screwed.
Her fingers are turning
blue. Can you move those?
My arm's starting to go numb.
Arch of the aorta's clear,
this can't be an aneurysm.
Maybe the wound threw a clot.
Check in axillary arteries.
Stop. Right there.
Five centimeter gooey mass.
Not a clot, maybe a lipoma?
What the hell is that?
A fat filled sack, probably
aggravated by the stab wound.
You got any syringes
in here? Give me that.
I was stabbed in my
gut, not in my arm.
You lost a lot of blood, gave
the lipoma room to swell.
It's compressing the arteries in
your arm, blocking your blood flow.
Maybe we can suck
some of it out.
You'll be fine.
Little pinch.
That's not a lipoma.
I don't know why she's even
considering having my kid.
She barely knows me.
All she knows is I'm
a short, balding guy.
That doesn't even make
evolutionary sense.
You want her to keep it? No.
'Cause you'd make a crappy dad.
I said, "No."
You're too selfish,
that's why you cheated on your
wife, why your marriage fell apart...
Dude, I said...
I know you.
The only reason you're sitting in
a strip club, ignoring the strip club,
is because you actually
are considering it.
Although, without
crappy dads in the world...
Try moving your fingers again.
Good, means it's almost drained.
Not good enough.
We don't know if
it's gonna come back,
we don't even know what it is.
Drugs, viruses, toxins
from that crack house,
and God knows where
else she's been.
If this were
caused by the drugs,
she'd have kidney failure,
cardiac involvement.
What about her Hep-C?
Could have fried her liver,
loses its synthetic function.
Then her entire body would
be swelling, not just her arm.
Leaves us with toxins.
Where exactly were you
when you were attacked?
You're not doing a home search
in a crack den. That's insane.
Apparently we don't
have much of a choice.
It's a crime scene.
And it's not toxins or viruses,
or anything else you mentioned
because it's not a coincidence.
Her symptoms have to be
related to the stabbing.
What if her body used up
all the clotting factors
dealing with the stab wound?
Explains the bloody mass.
But if you're right, she could
start bleeding anywhere.
Like, in her brain
or in her heart.
Wait, one of those things
could start growing in my brain?
It's time to get you
to the hospital.
No. Remy, you promised.
All we'll do at the hospital
is stick her in a patient bed
and give her IV clotting factor.
We can do that right here.
We could also
embalm her right here.
I'll call the drugs
and you go pick them up.
If I'm right, she'll be fine.
Look, I know you don't know her
and you don't care
about her, but I do.
Please.
Lie down, elevate your shoulder.
You said Andre wasn't
responsible for the drugs. What is?
I don't know.
Yes, you do.
What happened to you?
If you don't deal with
the real problem...
I came here because
you were a doctor,
not a shrink.
Your lap is vibrating.
Oh, sorry.
Ah, it's my boss.
Probably drunk, wants a
ride home. Let him take a cab.
Do you have any kids?
Why? You like moms?
I could be your mommy.
Spank your little ass.
Uh, no, I...
What would you do
if you got pregnant?
Not by me, at all, but by
some hypothetical guy,
who didn't wanna keep
the hypothetical kid,
what would be the least awful
way for him to tell you that?
Don't talk. Just let
mama dance for you.
Should I send flowers?
Maybe write the clinic
appointment on the little card?
"Surprise."
I hate myself!
There's just no good way to...
How long have you had
this mole? It's asymmetrical.
No touching.
Sorry.
Have you been to
see a dermatologist?
Bobby.
Oh. I wasn't touching her.
I was just...
Oh, God.
No.
No, please don't. Please...
Please put the gun down.
Put it down on the
ground and get away.
D?
I'm sorry.
D, what is it?
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Why aren't you in your bed?
I'll give ye splinters in yer
arse, ye mangy bilge rat.
What are you watching?
TV, you bloody scallywag.
Mom...
Someone better be dying.
She hallucinated.
I need you to go back out.
I just called in
more clotting factor.
So, she's bleeding
in her brain now?
We double up the dose,
she'll be fine.
We bring her to the hospital, we
do a CT scan to locate the bleed,
drill a burr hole in her skull,
and maybe she'll be fine.
We can drill a burr hole here.
You're not just risking
our careers here.
You could go back to prison.
I made a promise.
You made a promise?
I will not take her
to the hospital.
Great.
Then I will.
No.
I'm gonna move you, then
I'm gonna pick your friend up,
carry her down to my car,
take her to the hospital,
and try to save her life.
She's staying here.
Move.
Move!
She's going to the hospital.
Sweetie, go wait for Mommy
by the couch, okay? Go on.
I tried calling everyone else.
You were the last one
on the list.
Any reason why 911
wasn't on the list?
It's not an emergency.
Right.
Are you suicidal?
I'm not attempting
bypass surgery.
The tumors are small and
they're close to the surface.
I thought it'd be
like removing a wart.
You couldn't wait till morning,
bring your CT scans
to an actual surgeon?
Surgeons are idiots.
They just hack away at the
muscle till they get worn out.
Or you're just ashamed
you've been injecting a drug
that hasn't even gone
through safety trials.
It's never even been
in the human body.
I got one of the tumors.
The second one is close.
You can use the CT to
help you find the third.
I'm taking you to the hospital.
Just excise the tumor.
Absolutely not!
Elevate her head more.
Don't bother.
The cops are gonna be
waiting at the front door.
I'll go in first.
I'll find a patient on life
support who's just waiting to die.
We'll use that name
on all your tests.
No one will ever
know you're there.
Thanks.
What happened to your leg?
I was trying to make it better.
He was being reckless.
Sit back, honey.
This isn't about making
your leg better.
It's about making
your life better.
Oh, here we go.
Wish I had called 911.
Why else would you risk your
life doing something so stupid?
Well, you know, I've had
a lot of setbacks lately.
Don't blame our
break-up for this.
You're not unhappy because
of me. You're just unhappy.
Unhappy people
do reckless things.
Darrien!
Stop screaming, my head hurts.
I need you to stay
awake, talk to me.
About what?
When you were screaming in my
room, what did you think you saw?
You said, "Put it down on
the ground and get away."
Sounds like a cop.
Old habits, I guess.
You were a cop?
Back when I was a decent person.
How do I not know this?
You knew everything...
Not a good resume when
you're trying to survive in prison.
So who were you talking
to in my bedroom?
Why did you keep apologizing?
Because I'm sorry.
For what?
I killed a kid.
He was 19.
I went in first, saw
him going for his gun.
I tried to talk him down, but...
They told me I was a hero.
So that's when you
started using drugs.
I'm sorry.
Darrien.
Darrien!
She lost consciousness.
There are no cars
coming, just go.
The light is red,
you bloody scallywag.
Stop with the pirate talk.
If you don't want Brownbeard
to end up with two wooden legs,
you should get your ma to
move this ship, ye mangy bilge rat.
Of course.
You showed her
that filthy cartoon.
What kind of idiot lets a
three-year-old watch that?
If you wanna lecture me
on my poor judgment,
there would seem to be
more relevant examples.
There you are.
You were in the VIP room so long
I thought you were gonna
pay off that girl's mortgage.
I got tossed out
by Bobby the Bouncer.
You touched her?
I was looking at her mole.
Genius!
Let's go home.
I wanna wait for the girl,
make sure that mole's okay.
Bobby the Bouncer sees you
standing out here like a stalker,
he's gonna break
open your skull.
It was asymmetrical,
it could be cancerous.
You want to get your
skull cracked open.
You're trying to
punish yourself.
I want to fulfill
my oath as a doctor.
You think you're a screw-up
because you got a girl pregnant
and you deserve
to suffer. You don't.
You just need some sleep
and you'll handle this mess.
Let's get in the car.
She's probably off work soon.
Give me the keys, I'll drive.
I'll get a cab.
Good luck with everything.
You were defending
your friend beyond all rationality,
granting her the right
to die in your bedroom.
Was it really all
because of a promise?
That word means something
to some people.
Not that much.
I don't see the bleed, I'm
moving down to the brain stem.
You promised your brother
you'd euthanize him,
and you think you
won't feel bad about it
as long as you can
blame it on the promise.
That's why you have this twisted
obligation to keep all promises.
Or your carefully constructed defense
mechanism could crumble down.
I saved my brother
from a lot of pain.
Reconstructed image is clear.
There's no bleed
in Darrien's brain.
Image just blurred.
Did she wake up?
She's shivering.
She must have a fever.
Infection? It couldn't
be from the stabbing.
It has to be from the stabbing.
Wait, no, it couldn't
be acting that quickly.
Well then,
what's wrong with her?
Your heart rate's over
120. You're clammy.
I think you're going into shock.
Are you lightheaded?
I'm fine.
Did you see the new
Brownbeard episode?
It was so funny.
No, it was so lame.
A boat full of guy pirates and they
make the girl pirate walk the plank.
She floated.
That's 'cause
she had big boobies.
That's why he
should've kept her.
We gotta get you into
surgery. Where is that nurse?
Rachel, let's go find the nurse.
2:00 a.m. Nice of you
to call me back.
Chase and I are in the
hospital with a patient.
You've completely
run out of ideas
and you're calling
me to bail you out.
I'm touched. Hit me.
Command, please.
Call Ruby.
Would you like to
call Ruby on mobile?
No.
She on any medication
besides crack?
She was taking
interferon in prison,
so I'm guessing she's had
Hep-C for at least 10 years.
Can I guess stuff, too?
'Cause that's gonna make
the diagnosis really easy.
Prison infirmary isn't known
for stellar record keeping.
And we can't exactly
ask the patient.
Yeah, that
would've been pre-coma.
But how could you have known
that it would affect her that way?
We didn't think we had
anything mysterious until...
What about renal cancer
throwing clots?
Urinalysis was
negative. That's too bad.
'Cause that was my
one big idea. Really?
House?
House, you there?
Tell me more about the patient.
What was she doing
before prison?
She was a cop, shot
a kid in self defense,
never got over the guilt, started
taking drugs and got busted.
Way to bury the lead.
How long ago was this shooting?
I'm not sure. Why?
Again, you assumed she's
had Hep-C for 10 years.
But if you find out
when she shot the kid,
you'll find out when
she started taking drugs,
and when she actually
contracted the Hep-C.
And you think this is relevant?
It's more relevant than what
you got now, which is squat.
Three chicks just came
into my bedroom.
I gotta go.
Command, please.
Call Rachel.
Would you like to
call Rachel on mobile?
No.
What the hell?
I really am a doctor.
I just wanted... Cop another
feel? Get away from me.
No, that mole.
I just wanted...
Please don't call Bobby.
Just calm down.
Shut up!
Sick perv.
Get down on your knees.
You think I'm kidding? Turn
around and get down on your knees.
Please don't.
I said shut up!
You think you're the first guy
who thought he was special?
You think you can do
whatever you want?
I am not going
through that again!
Find anything?
Shockingly, a punk kid getting
shot pulling a gun on a cop
did not make national news.
Is your neck okay?
Yeah, it's fine.
I'll get you some ice.
I said it was fine.
I shouldn't have
grabbed you so hard.
You had to.
You were right about everything.
I got something.
Darrien must've had a
different last name then.
She must have been married.
20087 Is that possible?
We never actually talked
about how long she'd been in.
House was right. She could've
only had Hep-C for a few years.
There's no way the prison
would've prescribed interferon,
unless the lab showed
her Hep-C to be chronic.
So, what makes new
Hep-C look like old Hep-C?
What if she got a parasite?
The Hep-C made her susceptible,
and the parasite sped
up the liver damage.
Entamoeba.
Throw in a parasitoma, the stab
wound could have freed them,
sent them coursing through
her bloodstream, wreaking havoc.
A single bag of metronidazole.
If we're right, she could wake
up from the coma in a few hours.
They're ready for you.
Wait.
I want you in there.
I'm not a surgeon.
There's nothing I can do.
Well, you can make sure
that idiot butcher
doesn't cut more
than he needs to.
You already sighed a release.
He's gonna do what
he needs to do.
Yeah,
and if that involves
chopping off my leg,
I want to be sure that
that's damn well necessary.
House...
I don't trust him.
I trust you.
Can you hear me?
Yeah.
You had parasites in your liver.
Probably from a dirty needle,
or prison, or who knows what.
The stabbing made it worse,
but you're gonna be okay.
I'm sorry. We had to.
I told you I couldn't go back.
I shouldn't have trusted you.
I never liked you.
I killed time with you 'cause
I was locked in a cage.
You were a distraction.
Someone to talk to so I
didn't have to think about
everything else.
You're lashing out, I get it.
But in a month, you'll thank me.
Or maybe you won't,
I don't know,
but I know I saved your life.
Is he going to be okay?
He'll be fine.
Close your eyes.
I wish House still
came over to play.
Well,
maybe you should
write him a letter.
Wanna do that?
Okay, let's do it.
Ruby?
You look like hell
and you smell like...
I've been doing
a lot of thinking.
Is that glitter on you?
Just hear me out.
Back when I still
had my practice,
this patient came in, 50-year-old
guy wanting a tummy tuck,
but when we do some prelim work,
we discover that his
stomach is filled with cancer.
So instead of telling him that
he's gonna look great at the beach,
I gotta tell him
that he's dying.
Were you at a
strip club? Please.
The weird part was
I was more upset
about the whole thing
than he was.
He actually had to calm me down.
He said he had great
kids, raised them right,
knew that, because of them, he
was leaving the world a better place.
I thought I might
die last night...
At a strip club?
Yes, I was at a strip club.
And while it was happening,
I kept thinking
about that patient,
and how I wish I was like him.
I wanna have this baby.
Darrien had to shoot that kid.
It was the right thing,
completely justified.
But it didn't matter.
She destroyed her life
trying to forget.
I'm afraid that's
what's gonna happen to me.
You really should
talk to someone.
I've talked to a
therapist. It didn't help.
Maybe you should talk to
someone who isn't a therapist.
Do you really think
you have any idea
what it's like to live
with something like this?
Let's grab a coffee.
Late night?
No.
Just haven't had my coffee yet.
Sympathetic yawn.
Ooh, Amish kid collapsed
while picking up a hooker.
Top that.
I missed a call from
House last night. He in?
You're lucky.
What are you doing here?
You hoping for someone else?
Hot nurse, candy striper,
someone who doesn't
speak English,
speak judgmental.
You've got mail.
"I hope your leg feels better,
"and I hope we can be friends
again soon, you bloody scallywag."
I have to pee.
That's a good sign.
I'm a big boy.
Course you are.
You're an ass.
What? For trying to walk
on a freshly mangled leg?
Or for performing
surgery on myself?
For thinking I can solve my
emotional problems with rat medicine?
If you're gonna nag, at least
have the decency to be specific.
Come on.
Listen to me.
You can't keep going like
this. Something has to change.
Can I pee first?
I know.