Jennifer Williams?
And you are?
Cyrus.
Cyrus Harry? You used to
call me Cy, if it's really you.
I'm trying to find the Jennifer
Williams I knew 23 years ago.
We spent a long weekend
at the Jersey Shore.
She was visiting a friend...
That lasted longer than usual.
That's it for Lansdale.
Pack it up.
Let's move on to Philly.
Seriously, you're
gonna complain?
How many limo drivers
are making six figures?
Cy, you're my little
cousin, and I love you
and you've been
more than generous.
I'm upset because you
are wasting your time
for some faded memory
when there is a world
of pleasure out there.
The kind of cash you got
buys a lot of it.
Come on.
Don't be like that. I've just
been driving around all day.
I'm a little cranky.
Hey!
My leg won't move.
Are you gonna stare
or are you gonna call 9117
Partial paralysis.
Head CT and LP showed nothing.
Spinal MRIs and EMG were clean.
Brain symptom,
and yet nothing seems
to be wrong with his brain.
Refrigerator mechanic, no
family, in and out of work.
He just won 42 million
dollars in the state lottery.
I think I read about this
lucky bastard in the paper.
You sure you don't mean
the lucky bastard
whose grandkids
snorted his winnings
till he drank himself to
death with drain cleaner?
Or the lucky bastard who
was found naked and penniless
in a strip club parking lot
with his winning number
tattooed on both testicles?
Neuro-otological pathology
could've caused loss of balance.
Calorics were normal.
Sure, some people will screw
up anything but some won't.
That kind of cash,
he has a chance
to turn a miserable life around.
Miserable stays miserable,
happy doesn't buy lottery
tickets in the first place.
Our level of happiness
is set. It's in our DNA.
No cash payout's
gonna change that.
It's like there's two of me.
The guy repairs appliances.
He's probably got
toxic brain damage
from years of working
with toxic chemicals.
Or his sudden disease
came from his sudden millions.
He's buying something,
collecting something, ceramics,
precious metals, which gave him
atherosclerosis of
his carotid arteries.
My mother's lawyer called.
She's threatening to sue the
hospital over our mistreatment of her.
Says it slowed her recovery.
I was just thinking how much I
want a relationship with no sex,
but where I still have
to deal with your mother.
Go to the patient's
old workshop,
look for causative
toxic brain damage.
Go take a new history, and
see if there's any lifestyle change
that would explain
the atherosclerosis.
Go.
Medicinal.
I'm expecting a
shooting pain in my ass.
My mom and I got into a fight.
Because of our
replacement hip replacement,
she can barely get
around her own house.
I told her she has to live
with me while she recovers.
I'm starting to
get the connection.
Yeah, she has a house,
my name is House.
You're the doctor
that treated her,
that illegally switched her
meds after she fired you,
that went behind the back
of her actual doctor...
Those beads from Thailand.
If we're listing all the things
that you pressured me into.
The point is, you're the
one who's on the line here,
whose name is
on her hospital records.
Whose name is on her name? Fine.
We're both on the line, but she
won't discuss this with me alone.
She and her lawyer wanna meet
with both of us for settlement talks.
I need you in that meeting,
acting nice and respectful
while I diffuse this stunt.
Yeah, well, I'm not
going to that meeting,
so I'm guessing you're cool if
I'm not nice and respectful, either.
Picked up any new hobbies?
How's a hobby gonna
paralyze my left leg?
If you work on vintage cars, or
you've taken up painting, fumes could...
No cars, no paints.
You're a popular guy.
Popular wallet.
Three years ago, before I had
a dime, I had my appendix out.
Phil was there.
No one else even called.
What about drugs?
No drugs. Look, I've
seen all the documentaries,
I've read all the articles.
I'm not gonna be
a tabloid cliché.
I'm know what I'm
gonna do with my money.
"Find and build a life with the
one woman I ever cared for."
Point is,
nothing's changed.
I live the same life,
I eat the same food...
The same crappy canned food.
How many of your meals
do you eat from a can?
Most of them.
I'm used to it. I order
them by the case, online.
Is that bad?
You're worried about
the trickle-down effect
of Cuddy versus
House versus Cuddy.
You're reading subtext
into my silence?
House gets to you
more than anyone.
House thinks I'm a robot,
you think I'm a wuss?
No. No, no, no.
I think you're repressed.
Well, it's out of your control.
Tough childhood, strained
relations with your family.
Can't be easy trying to
succeed in a white man's world.
First of all, white man, I've
done at least as well as you have.
Second, I didn't think
you'd take House's view
that life sucks and we're stuck.
I think you're stuck.
Last month, I turned my life
around. I'm happier than ever.
Sleeping with 10 women
instead of four?
Mmm.
Try none.
He was cutting metal,
inhaled the dust?
Unless he was
snorting lines of the stuff.
None?
I was having tons of sex and
I was bored, hating myself.
Was never gonna be ready
when something real came along.
So, you're becoming
some kind of super monk,
and I can't change at all.
I challenge you to
go one differential
without House or anyone else
getting under your skin.
Since I say nothing gets to me
and you won't take me at my word,
how am I supposed
to prove you wrong?
I guess you can't.
I hope that doesn't eat at you.
Off-brand solvent from China.
Made of God knows what.
Patient eats cheap
canned goods by the case load.
Could be metal poisoning.
He also worked with
cut-rate chemicals.
Could be inhalation of
the toxic volatile substrate.
Treatment for both is chelation.
Great work.
Alkalinize his urine,
and force diuresis for
heavy metal poisoning.
If that doesn't work, put him
on dialysis for toxic inhalation.
I just said treatment
for both is chelation.
I said force diuresis and try
dialysis. You need a transcript?
You wanna put him on dialysis, risk
infection and hemodynamic swings,
when we can just chelate?
Whoa! Whoa!
Settle down.
If we chelate, we're not gonna
know what disease he had,
which means we're not gonna know
if the problem was
in his lousy, old job
or his still lousy new life,
which, for the purposes of a
metaphorical argument, is very important.
Pointless to argue. He's the
boss, he needs his puzzle solved.
Why bang our
heads against a wall?
When you're done
with the patient,
treat Foreman by banging
his head against a wall.
Where's the dialysis machine?
Who cares, since I
ordered chelation?
We'll flip a coin, tell House it
was one disease or the other.
Worst case, he finds out, and
he's impressed we defied him.
I'm sorry, I asked you to
remove the dialysis equipment,
not the chelation equipment.
And Dr. Cuddy asked me
to remove all equipment.
She de-authorized all treatment.
She won't let us make
a move until you agree to a sit-down
with the Godmother
and her consigliere.
Bitch to king four.
Checkmate. Patient
can't use his leg.
You have to concede.
Or I could just knock all
the pieces onto the floor.
You're discharging me?
We really don't
have a good lie here.
You got caught in some
politics between our boss and his boss,
but you'll be out of
here 20 minutes, tops.
I'm not better,
but you're kicking me out?
Which is why it'll
only be 20 minutes.
See, the Dean of Medicine
acts tough, but she's not, really.
She'll step in, readmit you...
So, you're saying that she
cares more about his treatment
than the doctor who's
actually treating him?
Phil, shut up.
Cyrus.
Jennifer?
It's good to see you.
I read about you in the paper, so I
hopped the first train from Virginia.
So you read that
he struck it rich?
He's right.
It must look weird.
It kind of is weird.
But we're a long way
from the 3rd Street Jetty.
I just wanted to see
you again and say hi.
So, hi.
Hi.
I was starting to
think I'd never find my...
Baby Bear.
Oh, my God.
I'm so sorry.
I don't even feel nauseous.
I don't know why...
Your hand is shaking.
Okay.
You're having a focal seizure.
What does that mean?
It means you're not
getting discharged.
We were right
that it's a brain issue
but wrong about toxic
inhalation and metal poisoning.
Everyone else is waiting.
That was totally
courageous of Khloe
to tweet about her weight gain.
House, we've got a patient
with a seizure disorder
who can't walk.
Another one?
I thought we
kicked out the last one.
Obviously, I'll let you
treat your patient...
What are you doing?
We've got a patient with a
walking disorder who can't seize.
No, wait.
- I'm close, though, right?
- I wasn't finished.
Of course, I'll let you treat your
patient if you meet me halfway.
I guess I'm not finished either.
No clinic hours
for the next quarter.
And three parking spots next to
each other, so I can park diagonally,
and three pairs
of your underwear.
I'm thinking of
taking up sailing.
Forget it.
Treat your patient,
don't treat your patient,
come to the meeting,
don't come to the meeting,
I'm done playing your game.
You realize the game is automatically
over when the loser loses, right?
Neurological Lyme disease
explains the seizures and the paralysis.
But not the fact that Chase
seems to be treating you.
He claims he can
swear off sex indefinitely.
Also claims that I'm a boiling
cauldron of repressed rage.
Your theory is idiotic.
Patient's antibody titers were
negative for Lyme disease.
And I shared a motel room
with your ex-girlfriend.
You make a good point
about the antibody titers.
He's a rock.
How's your brother?
Homeless guy.
Haven't heard
from him in months.
I don't know.
Wish I did.
Postural hypotension,
which could've reduced
the blood supply to his brain.
Then he'd be a miserable wretch.
Actually, the prognosis is...
Oh, I'm sorry. I just meant
his life is gonna unravel.
In fairness, that
applies to any diagnosis.
Why do we do this?
It's not postural hypotension.
He's not orthostatic.
His life may unravel, may not.
He's not chasing
after material things.
Too bad. He might
actually get those.
He's looking for love. Just
tracked down an old girlfriend.
And she'll
never live up to the memory,
and the thrill of
finding her will wear off,
and he won't even be able
to dream about being happy.
Interesting.
The patient may have found
some long-ago nookie,
but it doesn't mean he hasn't
had some in the meantime.
Herpes encephalitis.
Explains the
neurological symptoms.
EEG to confirm,
IV acyclovir to treat.
How's Foreman's BP holding?
- Same.
- That's strange,
since I unplugged the
lead 30 seconds ago.
Admirable effort. And
I'm not just saying that
'cause I'm scared
you might turn green
and rip through
your own clothes.
Down on the patient's romance
because your own life span is
shorter than dinner and a movie?
You're the one who said
miserable stays miserable.
But you keep saying it
several times a day.
I love being back,
having every theory
you and I share
used as proof of
my own personal damage.
I'm afraid we'll need you to
step out when the EEG begins.
The waiting area is
just down the hall.
I gotta catch an early train
in the morning, anyway.
No, don't.
I'll put you up in a nice hotel
or rent you a furnished place.
I came for the night 'cause I
wanted to see how you were,
and maybe get back
in your life a bit.
But if I take your money...
What's wrong with
a nice place to stay?
Unless, of course,
you don't wanna stay.
I guess I could keep my
motel room another night or two.
Need a consult.
Did an EEG on my patient.
Turns out the reason
that prior doctors
thought it wasn't
a neural problem
is because it's
not a neural problem.
The EEG did show signs
of metabolic distress.
Scan his abdomen.
Yeah.
Let's assume we'd already
figured that out on our own,
and found a mass
on the pancreas.
Mass looks solid.
I'd say it's cancer.
Paraneoplastic syndrome would
explain the neurological symptoms.
You need to get a piece of it.
Schedule a CT-guided biopsy.
Yeah. Let's assume we'd
already figured that out on our own.
Then what's this consult?
Why haven't you been yelling
at me about the Cuddy twins?
Because you're
doing the right thing.
We talking about the same issue?
Is there something
I don't know about
that I'm responding to
appropriately?
Cuddy wants you in the
middle of this, so does Arlene,
because they don't wanna
face their own problem.
Somehow, in your
knee-jerk, juvenile way,
you tripped and fell into an
actual adult response to this.
You're right.
That was Cuddy's
strategy all along.
She wanted me to think that she
desperately needed me to be there
so that I wouldn't be there.
Where is Dr. House?
I didn't want him here.
This isn't about her treatment
at Princeton-Plainsboro,
it's about the fight
we had last week.
I'd like a moment with my mother
to try and work
this out on our own.
I'm afraid my client
doesn't want...
It's Mother's Day Sunday.
We can't have five
minutes alone to fix this?
Relax, you can still bill me for
the time standing in the hallway.
I know you're mad at me, but you
can barely make it up those stairs.
How many nights have
you spent on your couch?
This has nothing to
do with our fight.
We're talking about my
home, not a prison camp.
What did I just say? I think it was
something about this not being personal.
You can spend time with
Rachel, I can watch over you.
Win-win.
Maybe I've got a medical thing,
maybe I just think I'm talking
but no one can hear me,
not just my uncaring daughter.
What do you want?
20 grand.
I'll hire help and forget this
nightmare you put me through.
Make it 30.
I'll put in a stair-lift.
If my board even hears about
these threats, let alone a settlement,
they'll investigate
what happened
while you were
here as a patient.
House and I could
both lose our licenses.
I've been assuming
this is personal,
because I don't wanna assume
that that's what my mother wants.
House.
Ex-not-mom-in-law.
You said you weren't
coming. After you said,
"Pretty please,
with sugar on top?"
Problem is, we
only give store credit.
So I say we put your old,
cracked, poisonous hip back in,
here and now.
I saved your life,
happy to un-save it.
He's being an ass.
If I could join you
in suing him...
She's like this in bed, too.
Always scheming to get
the lawyers out of the room.
If House isn't going
to take this seriously,
I know a few judges who will.
Was I supposed to
be the good cop?
I had to rig the monitor.
I had a lot of
salt with breakfast.
You think I'm repressed, too?
I think you're in danger of being
dissolved by your own stomach acids.
But what about Chase?
Do you believe that nonsense
about him being celibate?
Don't know, but I'm rooting
for him. Read the studies.
The fewer partners you have,
the happier you are
with your ultimate partner.
Hmm.
Then you're gonna be miserable.
Those studies, it's important
that they have a control group.
There's the tumor
on his pancreas.
There's one in his kidney,
and one in his colon.
One looks avascular,
one looks vascular,
the third looks calcified.
He has three completely
different cancers at once.
On average,
not so lucky after all.
You had to go all
Wile E. Coyote on her.
You told me that Arlene
wanted me in the middle of it.
I had to show her that
no good would come of that.
Seriously, that's
your rationalization?
How about, you didn't
like that Cuddy tricked you
even though you wanted
the same thing as her?
You didn't like that
she got the best of you.
You've got more anger
toward her than you realize.
I'm happier without her.
So I'm not stupidly expecting
her to make me happy.
I'm happier with my unhappiness.
Do you listen to what you're
saying? Because I have to.
I'm holding a summit meeting to force
you and Cuddy on to the same page
before a lawsuit gets filed.
Three completely
unrelated cancers at once.
A multicancer syndrome,
Von Hippel-Lindau?
Wouldn't have touched his colon.
I hereby certify that
Dr. Foreman has not tampered
with this blood pressure
mechanism in any way.
And after I prove
I'm 100% stress-free,
do I get to strap you
into a chastity belt?
What if the patient's
missing a tumor suppressor gene?
How would we even find it? We
need to blast him with chemo now.
We can't give the patient chemo.
His platelet
count's through the floor.
Even worse,
it'll contain his cancers.
If we wanna know
what they've in common,
we've gotta see
where they spread next.
You wanna wait six months
while the cancer spreads
and his seizures and
paralysis get worse?
Now, that's crazy talk.
But if we pump the patient full of
vascular endothelial growth factor...
Foreman doesn't like that idea.
You want to grow
more and bigger cancers.
We can't figure out what three
small ones have in common,
maybe we can figure out what
eight big ones have in common.
Is this idea real,
or are you just threatening to
kill the patient to screw with me?
This whole thing is idiotic!
What does it matter what's inside
of me if I know how to control it?
Makes no difference to us, but
you may want to make out a will.
Go get lotto boy's consent,
and turn his cancers up to 11.
You, what, found my old yearbook
and got a picture
of my high school boyfriend?
Actually, that would've
been a lot simpler.
I took this 10 minutes ago.
Your high school boyfriend
who dumped you,
leaving you
unable to believe that
anyone can
rekindle an old flame.
He dumped me after I
hooked up with his sister.
Would you mind
letting him down gently?
I might have made promises
that you can't keep.
We're giving you more cancer.
The risks of that
are kind of obvious.
We'll scan you, run your
blood at frequent intervals.
We believe this
is our best chance
at finding the
underlying genetic flaw.
Will you marry me?
Don't be stupid.
If this cancer overwhelms me,
at least I'll die
happy here and now,
instead of hoping for a
future I may never have.
I love you.
No, you don't.
You don't know.
You can't know.
We both need more time.
And I believe
we're gonna have it.
Did you notice she's wearing
different clothes every day?
As opposed to the same
Starfleet-issued tunic?
She said she came for one
night. Why'd she pack for more?
So she stuffed an extra sweatshirt
in her bag or she bought some.
Used? She's here because
an old beau struck gold.
She turned down a proposal. How
long a game do you think she's playing?
I think if she said yes after 14
hours, even he'd be suspicious.
You're lucky you're
hot and smart because...
Well, you're just lucky
you're hot and smart.
I need a hooker.
Not if you can make that work.
How the hell is that
supposed to relax you?
It's not for me, it's for Chase.
I'm saving myself, too.
Maybe you should get a couple.
You're riding me,
why not ride him?
Because I can get
a rise out of your BP,
his pee-pee,
on the other hand...
Forget yoga.
Embrace Zen.
You're a repressed idiot,
he's a horny idiot.
Neither one of you can
do anything about it.
Pretty sure that's Zen.
Thought we were
meeting in Cuddy's office.
And I put one of the radio frequency
tagged sponges from the OR
in your portable television.
However much it hurt, I did
have a right to break up with you.
You just want everything to
have a hidden personal agenda.
You need to get over it instead
of torpedoing our jobs out of spite.
It couldn't just be that
you're a pain professionally...
Stop!
You're both at fault here.
You, for trying to manipulate
House when you used to know better,
and you, for being you,
which is an especially bad
idea under the circumstances.
I had good reasons.
You had lame rationalizations.
If I hadn't played him, he'd
have found out about the meeting
and crashed it anyway.
Yeah, it would've been
a lot more efficient.
Enough! Okay, here's
what's gonna happen.
Tomorrow, I drive
both of you to Arlene's.
You're gonna write her a
personal check for $30,000,
and tell her she can stay in
her own home with your blessing.
You're gonna do this because you
actually give a crap about your job
and this hospital, and your
mother, and possibly even House.
And you're gonna say,
"I'm sorry,"
and not utter one syllable more.
'Cause I'm an idiot?
No, because if you don't,
I'm gonna tell the
pharmacy to stop issuing
Vicodin prescriptions
in my name.
I'm not paying for gas.
Anything look different?
Not yet.
Where's Jennifer?
She's embezzling money
from my Swiss bank account.
That's what you think, isn't it?
I'm being taken for a ride?
I think she wouldn't be here if
you were still fixing refrigerators.
One random set of numbers
doesn't change human nature.
Those sets of numbers
are what kept me going.
Clutching those tickets,
thinking about
the life I could have,
finding Jennifer again.
So you figure if one
long-shot dream came true,
the other one will as well?
You think you're protecting me.
I think you're sad.
Can't stand to
see somebody happy.
Mom, here's a check.
It's a settlement for
all you've been through.
Of course,
you can stay in your home.
It was wrong of me
to suggest otherwise.
I'm sorry
that we saved your life
in the way that we did.
B plus.
I hope this resolves everything.
I can tell you that both your
daughter and Dr. House are deeply...
This is 30 grand.
Which is what you asked for.
This covers pain and suffering.
What about the probate lawyer?
Did you two... I have
to change my will.
Leave everything to Julia so this
one doesn't try more funny business
to get control of my home.
I'm sure we can
toss in another $2,500.
Well, I guess I'll have
to kill you tonight, then.
Mom, I'm not interested in...
You already think you own
my body, why not my home, too?
Everybody, stay calm and...
You have to lash out at
everyone who tries to help you?
Live in your own
kitchen sink, for all I care.
- Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
- Harsh.
I didn't think you
had a case before,
but that is no way
to talk to a patient.
You are right.
Chase has had his eyes
on this one for months.
Meaning, he has eyes?
I paid her $100.
Now, when he hits on her,
might be tonight,
might be next week,
she's gonna slap
him and storm off.
So, your plan is to prove you're
both full of crap all in one move?
First he'll compliment her hair.
That's how he breaks the ice.
Next comes some
kind of joke or story.
He's sharpening his harpoon...
Are my moves this predictable?
She's grabbing his arm,
he's going in for the kill...
Don't let it get to you.
We poured a
lot of gas on the fire.
Ultrasound will give us a
good look at the damage.
A little more gel.
I never made a will.
I wanna provide for you
if I don't...
Stop it, will you?
I'd like you to
hold your breath for a sec.
Your money, there's
charities, causes,
your family.
You gotta ask yourself,
"What's mattered to you most
year in and year out?"
That can't be right.
Is it bad news?
No.
We've been pumping you
with growth factor,
but you don't
have any new cancers.
The tumors you had
all shrank.
Three tumors disappearing means
we were probably wrong about
him missing
a tumor suppressor gene.
How many mulligans
are you gonna ask for?
This test is what
raised my blood pressure.
I'm used to it now.
Go.
If it's autoimmune,
and he created antibodies that
ended up fighting his own tumors...
Growth factor would've made the
underlying autoimmune condition better.
Maybe it was never cancer
in the first place.
Of course, it was
cancer. We biopsied.
It could've been
a false positive.
Amyloidosis? His EKG voltage
has been on the low end of normal.
What if the tumors were
actually protein deposits?
GI biopsy to confirm,
chemo to treat.
She's making that diagnosis
based off a low-normal EKG.
Low-normal's still normal.
That thing cannot be right.
Low-normal is still low.
And that thing does not have
money riding on you being wrong,
like the rest of us do.
Chase, fix this.
Oh, I think you're
confusing Chase and Foreman.
I used to do that all the time.
I know it's rigged!
Because you're Mr. Cool,
nothing could possibly phase...
'Cause I took a beta blocker.
Both times, right?
His platelet count's still low.
Chemo's still a death sentence,
treating for amyloid
with normal EKG
is like doing
heart surgery on a guy
because he's 10 pounds
overweight. It's insane.
We'll do it your way. Go shout
at the patient till he gets better.
GI biopsy to confirm,
chemo to treat.
Here's the dirty little secret.
I just think we are who we are.
And I think
lotteries are stupid.
Janet Hemorrhoid!
That's not my name.
It's why I'm here.
Oh, I see, it goes across.
We better make this fast
'cause I'm about to
lose my medical license
for malpractice.
It's nothing unusual. Head of the
hospital's about to lose hers, too.
I heard Cuddy quadrupled
your clinic hours.
Yeah, but you know what?
I'm flying through patients.
Arlene wants another meeting.
I know. I told my
seconds to tell her seconds
that she gets no second chance.
Technically, it's a third
chance, but I don't have thirds.
Cuddy told her the
same thing, more or less.
So you got us on
the same page, after all.
I've been thinking
about your irrationality,
and I've come up with a
rational explanation for it.
That's quite a challenge.
You don't wanna let go of Cuddy.
So you're clinging to
the negative interaction
because some
small part of you thinks
the bad stuff
beats nothing at all.
Almost making this work.
All you gotta do now
is change reality.
Perhaps if I was
the one suing me.
You didn't start it, but you
had the chance to end it.
And you didn't.
You love her, House.
And it's human to hang on, but
you're blowing up not just your job
but any chance of any kind
of relationship with her again.
Hi.
Hey.
What's that?
It's a check for $10 million.
Uh.
I don't know what to say.
You've already been so generous.
By hiring you? For a whopping
six figures? My own blood?
Best friend I ever had?
Year in, year out?
You're wearing contacts
under your glasses?
I must've forgotten to
take them off when I...
They're tinted. Do you
change your eye color?
Sometimes I like to mix it up.
I don't understand
what you... Wait.
You don't have brown eyes?
Where'd the name
"Baby Bear" come from?
It's so long ago, I don't...
It's a birthmark
on your left breast
in the shape of a bear.
You forgot that?
It's the one thing
I never told you.
That's why she doesn't know.
It's not like that.
I swear.
Get out.
Get out, both of you.
Come on, man.
Get out.
I'm sorry.
Get out!
Both of you!
You were right. I'm
just another lottery fool.
My life sucks.
It'll always suck.
He's crashing.
Everything's shutting down.
Patient had a cardiac arrest,
and his lungs and liver failed
before we even started the chemo.
Brain symptoms that aren't brain
symptoms, tumors that come and go.
It's not amyloidosis.
You're forgetting alopecia.
Oh, I'm sorry. I thought
you were just listing
the things it's not,
alphabetically.
His long-lost love is a fraud.
Thirteen figured that out.
Good for her.
Decades of menial work.
If three cancers couldn't make
him die miserable, she just did.
The truth made him miserable.
It's like there's two of me.
Keep the clinic shut down,
but whatever it is, it's isolated
to the administrative floor.
I'm not gonna
evacuate the whole...
Only way to get the two of you
in the same place
at the same time.
Reopen everything,
readmit everyone, now.
I want you both to know
I'm filing the suit today,
delivering the paperwork
to your counsel's office.
You have to be destructive.
You have to tear things apart.
God forbid you should say what's
really on that twisted mind of yours.
And you're the great peacemaker?
Single mom, can't keep a man
long enough to cook a meal...
You'd be dead if it weren't
for our mistreatment.
And somehow, you'd still
find something to whine about.
We'll let the court decide who's
whining since you're so sure...
We're not getting back together.
What are you talking about?
It's the only explanation.
Why she keeps making threats
without ever filing her stupid,
yet completely valid lawsuit.
Why she ripped up her will,
why she kicked half of the
hospital out on the street.
She wants us united against her.
This is her drawing blood
over the latest of a long
line of imaginary slights.
She doesn't care if anyone
else is happy for a single...
Look at you idiots.
Who else is gonna put up
with either of you?
I asked you to move in.
That meant we
weren't gonna reconcile.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Some things take more
than a common enemy.
And you're an idiot with
impossible standards.
Common enemy.
One way to
trigger brain symptoms
when there's nothing
wrong with your brain.
Have something else turn
your brain into a common enemy.
You have a teratoma,
a usually harmless
congenital growth
which can be filled with
almost any kind of tissue.
And unusually,
not at all harmless.
If I'm right, yours is
filled with primitive cells,
some of which
developed into brain cells.
These foreign cells leaked
into your blood stream.
Now, the body is a little
xenophobic, and it creates antibodies.
The problem is, there's
not much difference
between brain cells
in your abdomen
and brain cells in your brain.
To make matters worse, primitive
cells can become almost anything.
Grow like weeds,
which means they can
turn into tumors,
and destroy whole organ systems.
But the cancer?
It was cancer.
It was just growing so fast, it
collapsed under its own weight.
Am I gonna live?
Cut out the teratoma and
what's left of your cancer,
you should be fine.
Think of it as your
second luckiest day.
It's hard to feel lucky.
The woman I loved was a fraud.
No, actually,
a fraud was a fraud.
You fell for her just the same.
You may stay miserable,
but your long-lost love is
not gonna be the reason why.
It's the real Jennifer.
Or at least
the only one to show up
who actually has the birthmark.
He's renting her an apartment.
It'll end horribly.
Not for him.
She may take all his money,
and he may be a naive idiot,
but he'll always be hopeful.
So he'll always be happy.
You lost your mother,
you euthanized your brother,
you got the life expectancy
of a pretty good sitcom.
If you can
convince yourself that
you'll be miserable
no matter what,
even without all that stuff,
then maybe you don't
have to hate the universe
for dumping a giant turd on you.
Fatalism is your
survival mechanism.
And you?
Dumped by everyone
you've ever loved,
rehab was a bust,
your leg feels like somebody
took a giant bite out of it.
We are who we are.
Lotteries are stupid.