- Howard.
- Morning.
- Delivery for McGill.
- What are you doing here?
It's been a while.
I thought I should check on you.
Did I hear music?
Hm? No, no, I was just--
Let me get that for you. Yup.
- Good to see you, Howard.
- Oh, likewise.
You are sorely missed, my friend.
Don't take that as any undue pressure.
Um.... I'm thinking of maybe coming in
for an hour or two next week.
- Maybe kind of play it by ear.
- Well, if you feel comfortable.
I mean, we certainly would love to have
you. We will take anything we can get.
I'll figure out a day...
...and get Ernesto
to give you a heads up.
That sounds great.
- How's Ernie working out?
- He's been fine, for the most part.
- Excellent.
- Everything on track with Sandpiper?
Moving along.
Davis & Main
are really pulling their weight.
Well, they better. It's a complex case.
- Well, it's definitely not a two-man job.
- No.
Anyone heard from Jimmy?
I have, yes. I've talked to him.
How is he?
He's fine. Doing well.
Speaking of which, I have some news.
He's working at Davis & Main.
Doing what?
Working as an attorney.
- Clifford Main hired Jimmy?
- Mm-hm.
To be fair, he had his doubts,
but he's giving Jimmy a chance.
He had his own people
doing client outreach...
...but every time they'd talk to
a Sandpiper resident...
...Jimmy's name would come up. Yeah.
- Those old folks just--
- They love him.
Yeah, they do.
Plus, I guess,
Cliff thought it would be a good idea...
...for the case to have that sort of...
...you know, continuity.
- Jimmy certainly has a way with people.
- He does.
They're aware of his background
at Davis & Main? His education?
In the spirit of full disclosure,
Cliff did talk to me beforehand.
I didn't pull any punches.
I tried to paint a complete picture.
But I didn't stand in the way.
Of course not. Nor should you.
Truth be told...
...Kim Wexler pushed for this.
Hard.
But I didn't, you know, stand in the way.
Partner track?
I would, uh....
Yeah, assume so.
That's great.
- Good for Jimmy.
- Ha, ha, ha.
- Charlie Hustle, right?
- Yup.
Yup.
Well, I'll get out of your hair.
- Anything else to add to Ernie's list?
- No, all set. All good.
- Thanks for coming by, Howard.
- Any time.
- You truly are missed. No pressure.
- Mm.
Document review...
...will be coordinated through HHM.
To date, the following documents...
...have been requested from Sandpiper
as part of our initial discovery petition.
One, resident lease agreements...
...past and present,
from all Sandpiper locations.
Two, invoices
and transaction documents...
...from all supply companies
used by Sandpiper.
Three, list of all past and present
official Sandpiper vendors.
Four, any and all business agreements
and contracts...
...between Sandpiper and its distributors.
Five, records of residents'
social security cheque receipts.
Six, allowance transaction statements.
Seven, resident invoices
nonrelated to....
I'm loving the new look.
How's Santa Fe?
It's, uh....
It's really....
See? What'd I tell you?
A nice place?
The finest in temporary
corporate housing.
I can't wait to see it.
Maybe I should leave HHM
and get on that cushy D & M train.
It is very cushy.
It's amazing.
Jimmy, I'm so happy for you.
Thanks. You know,
things are really turning around.
I'm even thinking of looking,
you know, for my own place to buy.
- In Santa Fe?
- I'm not sure yet.
Maybe someplace
closer to Albuquerque...
...since I'm going
between the two so much.
- Okay. So halfway points.
- Yeah, I was thinking--
- Oh, wait, what about Corrales?
- Corrales, yeah.
Get a nice little bungalow,
or maybe not so little.
Big open floor plan.
I don't want any walls
disrupting my chi, yeah.
But I'm thinking I definitely want
some decent acreage.
- Get in touch with nature.
- Horses.
Come on, you could get horses.
Man, that would be so amazing.
Too expensive. They-- All the oats, right?
It's oats that they're always eating.
- It's worth it.
- And the horseshoes.
You have to get them shoes
and nail them with a hammer.
It's totally worth it.
Long ride through the country...
...and then a glass of wine
on the back patio at sunset.
Oh. We should get one of those smokers.
We could just barbecue for days.
Yeah, we definitely gotta get a smoker.
All right, well, I gotta go to the salon.
They're delivering my new company car.
- Ugh. Are you serious?
- What?
"Jeez, where's my solid gold blimp?
- No, not that one, the other one."
- Jealous.
Totally.
I forgot, I got you a present.
One sec.
Oh. That's a beautiful wrapping job.
It's a shame to open it.
It's a gift, be grateful.
Just keeping it real.
Come on,
second is still very, very good.
All right.
Thanks. See you tonight?
Maybe, if you play your cards right.
Hello, beautiful.
What do you think, ladies?
Yeah, I know, right?
It's got all leather interior...
...heated seats
for those cold desert mornings.
This must be what heaven looks like.
Hey. Goodbye hug?
No? All right.
We'll forgo the tears and just say
"till we meet again."
Must be metric.
Hey.
What-- What are you doing here?
I work here.
Oh, small world.
So is this the parking lot
for the police station?
- It is.
- You don't know if they validate, do you?
Why don't you pull around over there?
And we'll have a little talk.
Uh, Okay.
Why are you here?
I have business with the police.
And what business might that be?
Well, if you must know, I was robbed.
Somebody broke into my house
and stole my property.
Your drugs?
Yeah, but obviously
I didn't tell the cops that.
I'm not stupid.
You've already spoken to them?
Well, a couple of them
came by my house.
But it's not the drugs that I care about.
I mean, I care.
It's my baseball cards I need back.
Your baseball cards?
Yes. I have a very valuable
collection of baseball cards...
...and someone stole them.
I guess I shouldn't be surprised
I have to tell you this...
...but it's probably a bad idea
that you willingly talked to the police...
...being a criminal and all.
I'm not here as a criminal.
I'm here as a crime victim.
Just because I occasionally
sell some pharmaceuticals...
...I no longer have a right
to protection from crime?
And I was very careful
when I talked to them.
I mean, they have no idea
about my other business.
If you already made your report,
why are you here?
Well, they called me.
They have a few more questions.
They are very dedicated
to finding this thief.
Since you're new to this,
let me explain it to you.
They've invited you on a fishing trip.
What's that, a fishing trip?
Those cops have no interest
in helping you get your cards back.
You're obviously under suspicion.
There was nothing there
for them to see.
I refer you
to our previous conversation...
...and this blinking neon sign
of a vehicle that says drug dealer.
They suspect you.
They will get you in there...
...pretend to be your friend,
lull you into a false sense of security...
...and then they will sweat you.
And you will break.
I don't....
- I disagree.
- Not open for debate. You go home now.
- But I have an appointment.
- Break it.
And if they call you,
do not answer the phone.
But what about my baseball cards?
- Cost of doing business.
- No!
No, no, no! I am getting those back.
I will take the risk.
No, you won't.
Because then you'll be
putting my well-being at risk.
I have to.
I-- I--
Those cards...
...some of them were my dad's.
I am getting them back.
I'm getting them back.
I'll find your cards.
Is-- Is that something you do?
Wow, that's-- That is so generous of you.
Oh, it'll cost you.
Oh.
Okay, we should discuss...
...some sort of financial arrangement,
in which I-- I--
Uh....
Okay, then. Jesus.
Davis & Main, this is Maida.
- Come on in.
- I didn't mean to interrupt.
Not at all,
I was just blowing off some steam.
- You sound good.
- Thank you. Clears the head. You play?
Oh, I tried to learn in high school...
...but then I decided
there were easier ways to get girls.
I hope you've got a way to decompress.
Everybody needs something.
- How are you settling in?
- Great.
It's-- It's quite a step up for me.
Well, we're happy to have you.
Just let us know if there's anything else
you need, Jimmy.
- Thanks, Cliff, I'm happy to be here.
- Great.
- Better get back to it.
- Yeah, me too, I suppose.
Um....
Actually, I might have found something...
- ...in the initial disclosures.
- Oh, yeah?
Schweikart and Cokely keep referring
to the optional allowance programme.
I checked a number
of residents' contracts.
Not a single one has opted out...
...which makes me think it's more
of a mandatory financial arrangement.
You think that's a failure to state a claim
that they filed in their answer?
They keep saying it's optional,
thereby voluntary. We can counter that...
...if opting in
is a requirement for residency...
...which it sure seems to be, well,
their voluntary claims don't hold water.
Might be onto something here.
Nice work, Jimmy.
Thanks, Cliff.
Welcome. How can I help you?
I was hoping to get an estimate,
mi car.
- You do cars?
- Sí, cars, todo el tiempo.
I was hoping
to get my seats reupholstered.
Um....
Take a look?
Yeah, I'm thinking something new.
Give the old girl a little love.
I'm happy for the work...
...but his money might be better spent
on a down payment for a new car.
He said you should save your money
and get a new car.
Yeah? Well, it has a sentimental value.
- Classic car.
- Mm.
What's he looking for?
What material do you want?
Well, I was thinking leather, definitely.
Maybe alligator.
Oh, señor, too much money.
But like I said,
it has a sentimental value.
I think an exotic leather would clash.
Maybe something a little more
consistent with the style of the car.
Convince him.
He says alligator's
gonna look all wrong.
Cheaper might be better.
Well, show me what you'd pick.
Uh....
I'm sorry, señor.
My son, he will help you.
Okay?
Help him pick.
And don't try to upsell him, okay?
Yeah, mucho gusto.
How'd you find me?
- Why are you here?
- Baseball cards.
The way I figure,
you saw that midlife crisis of a vehicle...
...and wisely decided
to cut ties with the man.
And I don't blame you, I did too.
And then you ripped him off.
I'm sure those baseball cards
looked like an easy way...
...to make a few extra bucks off that idiot,
teach him a lesson too.
But you underestimated just
how big an idiot you were dealing with.
- No, I'm pretty aware.
- Well, then, you underestimated...
...how attached the man was
to those cards.
So attached, he called the police
and reported them stolen.
Now they're nosing around.
That sounds like a you problem.
It's very much an us problem.
Yeah, I guess I'll just have
to take my chances...
...but good luck to you.
You know, I was hoping you'd see
our dilemma and do the right thing.
But I think what we have here now
is a carrot-and-stick situation.
Oh, yeah?
This the stick? Hmm?
You coming here
threatening my family?
Huh?
Because you're gonna need
a bigger stick, old man.
I'm not here to threaten your family.
And the name of the stick
is Tuco Salamanca.
Now, you don't play ball, so to speak...
...and Tuco finds out
about your little side business.
That a big enough stick?
However, I'd prefer the carrot.
I think you will too.
And what would that be?
You give me back the baseball cards,
10,000 in cash...
...and you net roughly...
...roughly 60,000.
And how exactly does that work?
Ernesto?
Hey.
Going somewhere?
Yes, we are.
She's a little tricky around the corners.
So-- And you gotta go
with the premium gas.
I know it seems like a scam,
but it makes a huge difference.
And I would get her washed
at least once a week...
...and spring for the hand wax.
You're gonna want that
extra layer of protection for the clearcoat.
She deserves the best.
I'll make sure the boys at the chop shop
are real gentle with her.
Wait, why?
No.
You think I'd be caught dead
driving that thing?
It looks like a school bus
for 6-year-old pimps.
All right, shall we move this along?
Aaron.
Okay, there's Jeter.
All right, okay.
Mantle. Mantle. There's Mantle.
- We good?
- Yeah, that looks like everyone.
Yeah, they're here.
Looks like everyone's here.
And now the other item.
Now our business is concluded.
You know, I can't help thinking
an apology was in order.
It's-- It's the police again.
Sandpiper hasn't responded
to our discovery requests.
They buried us in paperwork...
...but nothing relevant
to the particulars in this case.
No real surprise there.
We may have to subpoena
their bank records. Thank you, Erin.
Jimmy. How are we doing
with client outreach?
While we're waiting
on those subpoenas...
...we should try wrangling some
of this stuff from the clients themselves.
I mean, most of these folks
have hard copies of everything...
...going back to
the Eisenhower administration.
Of course, given some of their
inconsistent organisational practices...
...it's gonna be slow going.
I'm so sorry to interrupt.
Oh, this one lady, um....
She's sweet, but deaf as a doornail.
She keeps all of her paperwork in--
- She keeps it--
- I'm sorry, excuse me, Jimmy.
I'm gonna need everybody's phone,
key fobs and electronics.
Chuck. Welcome.
Please, have a seat.
Don't mind me.
Hey, everybody.
I'm sorry for the interruption.
Just pretend I'm not here.
Happy to have you.
Jimmy, where were we?
Uh.... Yeah.
So I was saying....
Um....
Getting documents
from some of the clients....
We definitely have some pack rats,
God bless them.
I was visiting Mrs. Gusdorff
at the Sandpiper Santa Fe...
...and I spent the whole afternoon...
...sorting through
just a haystack of recipes...
...and half-off coupons for Big Lots.
But now we've got copies
of this woman's monthly statements...
...going back to March, 1997, so....
It might be a little labour-intensive...
...but our clients will always be
our best resource.
Plus, they have ribbon candy.
Jimmy.
Hello?
What are you doing here?
My name is on the building.
So great to have you here.
If you need anything, I'll be in my office.
Why are you here?
To bear witness.
James McGill.
It's Ehrmantraut.
Are you still morally flexible?
If so, I might have a job for you.
Where and when?
Take a seat.
Mr. Wormald,
thank you for coming in and talking to us.
Yeah, of course.
We've been looking at the reports
the officers took at the scene...
...and we have a few
small follow-up questions.
Sorry to waste your time.
Just standard stuff.
There's really no need
for a lawyer here.
I'm here in more of
an advisory capacity.
Dan just wanted a friendly face
next to him.
Well, we're all friendly here.
Look at us. Four friends.
We just wanna get the facts straight so
we can help you get your property for you.
Yeah, you know, it's fine.
Yeah, there's no need to....
No, it's just standard procedure.
You know, officers don't always get
all the information we need in their report.
We just wanna find the guys
who took your baseball cards.
Yeah, that's, uh....
You know, my uncle had
a Ty Cobb tobacco card.
Kept that thing
behind 6 inches of glass.
- Like it was the Mona Lisa or something.
- Wow, Ty Cobb?
Tell him to keep the lights low.
Even artificial lighting...
...has a certain amount
of ultraviolet radiation...
...that can, you know,
over the long term--
Yeah, can you just remind us...
...exactly where you kept your cards
in the house?
Yeah, well, as I was trying to say,
it's no longer an issue.
I found them.
- So you found the cards?
- Yup.
I just wanted to come down and tell you,
you know, in person.
You found them?
Where? Around the house?
No. I hired a private investigator...
...and he tracked them down.
So, yeah.
Really? So where were they?
You know, it's fine. It is.
I really--
I ought to get out of your hair.
- You've wasted enough time on me.
- No, no. It's-- It's okay. It's our job.
We just wanna get the facts right
so we can help close this case for you.
It's done.
Case closed.
I just-- I know how much, you know,
you guys have on your hands.
Like murderers, and robbers...
- ...and gangs and stuff. I--
- Danny, why don't you get some air?
You can have some coffee.
I'll finish up with the detectives here.
Okay, let's get down
to brass tacks here, guys.
I'm guessing your
two fine uniformed officers...
...found Mr. Wormald's little hidey-hole,
and that's why you two...
...are so interested
in "helping" my friend here.
I get it.
A hiding place in the baseboard,
it's gonna make anyone suspicious.
But let me assure you,
there's nothing illegal going on here.
Then why is he so nervous?
Because I must say,
the flop sweat is kind of suspect.
We all have our secrets, don't we?
And who among us is without sin?
But those sins
aren't all of the criminal variety...
...and neither are Mr. Wormald's, okay?
They are, however, very private.
- Private like drug dealer maybe?
- No, no.
He's being evasive
because it's a sensitive subject.
It's very delicate
and of no concern to law enforcement.
You know, as much as we'd love
to take your word for it...
...we'll need a little more than that.
All right, well, this all comes down
to a personal dispute.
That's all. It's between
Mr. Wormald and...
...his art patron.
Art patron?
Yeah, my client has an arrangement
with a wealthy gentleman...
...for whom, ahem,
Mr. Wormald provides art...
...in exchange
for this gentleman's generous....
We'll call it patronage.
Art. Like what, paintings?
It's more like digital media.
Digital media?
- He made videos for the man.
- What kind of videos?
Private videos of an artistic nature.
That's what was in the hiding place,
that's what it's for.
So this art patron stole the videos
and the baseball cards?
Well, there was a misunderstanding.
I mean, call it creative differences.
Artists are volatile creatures.
Guys, this all comes down
to just a lovers' spat. Okay?
Two consenting adults had a falling out,
that happens...
...and the patron stole the videos.
And the baseball cards,
to make a point, I guess.
But the headline here is
it's all settled, hearts have mended...
...and Mr. Wormald
will not be pressing charges.
What was on these videos?
- They were private.
- You said that.
They were videos intended...
...to titillate the senses.
- Okay, so porn.
- Not-- No. Not as such.
Technically, they would be categorised
as fetish videos, but nothing illegal.
Just a man,
a fully clothed man, I might add...
...just all by himself.
Just-- Just Mr. Wormald, fully clothed.
- Yeah, so.
- Yeah.
All right.
So fully clothed, Mr. Wormald...
...by himself.
- Doing what?
- Yeah, come on, man, what?
Squat cobbler.
What's a squat cobbler?
You know what squat cobbler is.
- No, I don't know what a squat cobbler is.
- No, me neither, what is it?
What? You two guys are cops?
Hoboken Squat Cobbler.
Full Moon Moon Pie.
Boston Cream Splat.
Seriously?
Simple Simon, the Ass Man.
Dutch Apple Ass.
Guys, am I not speaking English here?
- What the hell is a squat cobbler?
- It's when a man sits in pie.
He sits in a pie and he--
He wiggles around.
Maybe it's like Hellmann's mayonnaise.
It has a different name
west of the Rockies, I don't know.
But technically
he does a crybaby squat...
...so there's tears,
which makes it more specialised.
Not all pie-sitters cry,
but I'm gonna tell you something.
This guy, he's a regular Julianne Moore
once he gets the waterworks cranked up.
Pies?
- What, like apple?
- I'm not the filmmaker here, all right?
Banana cream, I-- Peach.
Oh, and there is a costume involved.
You got to be shitting us.
Yeah, like I would make this up.
Hey, the world is a rich tapestry,
my friends.
But trust me on this...
...you don't wanna see it.
So, uh, we're good, right?
Yeah, great.
There is, however,
one little, tiny hanging chad.
- What chad?
- You're gonna have to make a video.
Wait, wait.
So he eats the pies or just sits in them?
- Both. Whatever you want.
- Which comes first?
Oh. It's dealer's choice.
- That's where the crying comes in, right?
- That's a safe bet.
How the hell
did you come up with that?
If you give me a million years,
I still would not have come up with that.
The muse. She speaks through me.
I am but a humble vessel.
- And they bought it?
- Yeah.
Wow, I've heard some far-out scenarios
used to sow doubt...
- ...but this definitely takes the cake.
- Kim. Kim. Kim.
- Takes the pie.
- Yeah.
Sorry, I should just
jump off the roof right now.
Yeah, you should feel bad about yourself.
Jesus, can you tell a story.
Well, to be fair...
...I think it was the video that clinched it.
What video?
Wait. Wait, you actually made a video?
I gotta say, in the end,
old Dan really committed.
I believed the tears.
Oh. This is a leftover prop, it was extra.
I wasn't sure how many takes
we would need so I overbought.
But I promise you,
untouched by human buttocks.
- You fabricated evidence?
- I made a video. Not exactly evidence.
You used it to exonerate a client.
You used falsified evidence
to exonerate a client.
- I think you're splitting hairs.
- I'm not splitting hairs.
What if Davis & Main
find out you faked evidence?
It wasn't a Davis & Main client.
It was some nothing
little pro bono thing.
- It was off the clock, totally my own thing.
- Why?
Why would you risk
the best job you've ever had...
...for some pro bono case?
I was doing a favour for a friend.
Risking disbarment? That's--
That's some friend.
It's fine, it worked out.
- Davis & Main are none the wiser.
- Jimmy, you're playing with fire here.
I didn't see you complaining...
...when Ken the douchebag
paid our bar bill the other night.
That was a little bit
of rule-breaking right there...
...and if I remember correctly,
you liked it, a lot.
- That is so not the same thing.
- How? What's the difference?
That had nothing to do with work,
and we were just screwing around.
This, fabricating evidence--
Jimmy, this could really hurt you
if they find out, if you get caught.
- They're never gonna find out.
- Seriously?
You sound like
every dumb criminal out there.
If you keep this up, they will find out.
For what, Jimmy?
What is the point?
I cannot hear about this sort of thing...
...ever again, okay?
I mean it, Jimmy.
You won't.