-[industrial noises]
-WAYNE: Previously on Revival.
-[quiet tense score]
-So, what's your story,
Dead Girl?
-AARON: A ring?
-EM: Your ring.
I woke up and I threw this up.
-That's not mine.
- This is May Tao following up
on the strange occurrences
that shook the citizens
of Wausau last night.
-Can I call you sometime?
-DANA: Okay.
-Did you hear it?
There's something out there.
-MAYOR: You happy now, Wayne?
Locking up the people
you're supposed to protect.
-Oh, what you looking up
the Check Brothers for?
-ANTHONY: I'll take the deal.
-Tell me my family's safe.
-[gunshot]
-Who's ready for a holy war?
-Everyone was really sad
when you died.
-What do all of these mean?
-I don't know.
-DANA: I want to find out
what happened to you.
And I can.
-[quiet tense score]
-[eerie loud score]
-[faint footsteps]
-[score abates]
-Aaron?
-[clattering]
That you?
-[papers crinkling]
-[phone clicks]
-[clattering continues
in background]
-[rasping, quiet thud]
-[score intensifies]
-[choir vocalizes dramatically]
-[eerie loud score]
-[woman gasps sharply]
-[score abates]
-[chair clattering]
-[chair squeaking]
-[loud bang]
-[lock disengages]
-[handle mechanism clangs]
-[door thuds]
-[choir vocalizes dramatically]
-[dramatic urgent score]
-[score abates]
-[ethereal haunting theme]
-[whoosh]
-[theme fades out]
-[distant crow cawing]
-[tense score]
-[dramatic boom, rumble]
-[birds twittering]
-[score fades out]
-[image disk viewer clicks]
-[sparse percussive score]
-You know, maybe let's just go.
-What if those brothers
or the guy you saw on the bridge
come after you again?
We could use your sister's help.
-Who's Lip Ring?
-Dana, I have to
tell you something.
-[zipper scratches]
-All right.
Em, why didn't you tell me
you were sleeping with
your professor?
-Yeah-- [scoffs]
Because I wasn't.
Where-where...?
-Look what Nella found.
-You went through my phone.
-Yeah.
I'm a detective.
I was detecting.
-I thought you were trying
to find out who murdered me.
Not completely violate
my privacy.
-Em, you know the main suspect
is always the ex.
-He wasn't my ex!
He was just a fling.
-None of my business.
You do you, babe.
-Since when do you have flings?
Is he a fling?
-No, I'm Rhodey.
-Rhodey?
-[sucks teeth]
Uh-uh.
-I remember something.
There was somebody on the bridge
that night.
He spoke to me.
-Can you remember who?
Can you, can you describe him?
-He was the same guy
on the news,
the same guy who torched Arlene.
-Blaine Abel?
You're telling me Blaine Abel
was on the bridge
the night that you died?
Okay, well,
that's where I'm headed.
-That's where I'm going, too!
-No!
It's too dangerous.
-I can't just sit here
and do nothing.
-Em, one of us
is a police officer
and one of us is 20. Okay?
Cooper'll be home from school
in a few hours.
Just stay here.
It'll make him
so happy to see you.
Don't fling my sister.
-Cool. Does that mean I get to
hang out with your nephew?
-No.
-[car starts outside]
We're following her.
-[dramatic eerie score]
-[score abates]
I, uh,
need to speak to Mr. Abel.
-Yeah, well,
this is private property
so you better run off
and get a warrant.
-[snorts like a pig]
-That's cute. It's a real
good repartee you got going.
-What's repartee?
-A smart or wise comment,
which is why you don't know it.
-What the hell
are you doing here?
I told you to stay put.
-You can't tell me
what to do, Dad.
-[tense score]
-[fence rattling]
-It's okay, gentlemen.
Guns down.
There's nothing to fear
from the law.
The Lord will judge her,
as all mankind.
If he deems her unworthy,
then he will smite her down.
-Sounds painful.
Where were you
on the night of December 18th?
-We all know where we were
on December 18th.
-I saw you on the bridge
by Bull Falls that night.
-I was called
to tow a vehicle off
Lester Majak's property.
A car had been left in the woods
near the falls.
-So why were you on the bridge?
-Hey, hey, jeez. Quiet.
Why were you on the bridge?
-I was looking for the vehicle.
-So you responded to a call,
you drove to Bull Falls,
got out of your truck and...
you went on foot
to look for the vehicle?
-That is what I said.
-What did you do to me?
-DANA: Hey, hey, hey, hey.
-[tense score continues]
Do you remember seeing her
on the bridge that night?
-Yeah. No, I saw her.
-Well, did you find it weird
to see someone like this
on the bridge that night,
in the dark, in the cold?
-No, I didn't because
she was high. Right?
I could see it in those eyes.
-And then what happened?
-I left.
I found the car
around the bend,
I hitched it up
and took it back to the garage.
-Which lot?
-Alonzo's, on 12th.
-What time did you bring it
back to Alonzo's?
-Whoo. (pondering)
-[laughs]
-Did you see
or speak to her again?
-No. There was something
like an explosion.
You saw it.
-What are you talking about?
-The light!
Happened deep in the woods.
Lit up the night sky in a flash.
You were right there.
You must have seen it.
-All right.
-Personal space, man.
-Okay. Thank you, Mr. Abel.
That'll be all.
-[score abates]
-[makes meek fearful sound]
-[laughs]
-[tense score resumes]
-You run along, little lamb.
The end of days are near.
No, no, no, no. Not now.
Soon,
but not now.
-[rifles rattling]
-DANA: Do you know what
he was talking about?
Some light?
-No, I don't.
I don't remember
anything like that.
What's the next step?
Do we get a warrant?
-Are you kidding?
No! There's no we.
-He knows something! Come on,
you don't really believe
that tow truck excuse, do you?
He was there!
-Em, if Blaine had something
to do with what happened to you,
then there are steps to this
and I,
and I can't mess this up.
Do you understand?
I need to do this right.
I need to make sure I can
put him away for good.
-I get it.
And I trust you.
You'll get him.
I know it.
-Guy's spooky.
-NEWS ANNOUNCER: All revivers
are now required to register
with the county office.
Non-registry will result in
severe penalties,
including incarceration.
-[stamper clicks]
Please be aware that
the sheriff's office may come
to your home or
place of business
to ensure cooperation.
If you suspect someone
of being a reviver,
please alert the authorities
immediately.
I have to let Dana do this
-[score fades out]
and do it right.
When she first became a cop
she was on the Blackdeer case.
-The guy that
killed his daughter?
-[sharp knocking at door]
-Jesus! Dana!
You knock just like...
-[door rattles; hinges creak]
Dad?
-What are you doing here?
-What am I doing here?
I'm with my friend. What are--
What are you doing here?
-I'm alerting
all registered revivers
about the new mandate.
You're dating one of them?
-His name's Rhodey.
-Oh. I'm going to need to see
your ID.
-What? Why?
-Because all revivers
need to have their IDs stamped.
I'm not going to ask you
a second time.
Uh...
-[smack, Velcro ripping]
-[stamper clicks]
-Since when do revivers
need to carry this around?
-Governor's orders.
-[quiet tense score]
-Hm.
-WAYNE: Are you going to be at
your appointment tomorrow?
-What appointment?
-This is why you need to stop
ignoring my phone calls.
I left you a voicemail, too.
-Okay, I'm sorry, Dad,
but why do I have to go to
an appointment?
-Because, Martha, you broke
that woman's nose at Nella's.
You're damn lucky that she
didn't seriously injure you.
-Yeah, but she didn't.
-Yeah, but she did charge you
with assault. Okay?
You're lucky your father's
the sheriff
and I do have
some influence.
Had your punishment reduced;
20 hours of anger management
and the first session
is tomorrow at 9:30,
so do not be late.
-[scoffs]
Light a candle, dude.
Bro.
-Your family is intense.
-[door rattles sharply]
-[door hinges creak]
I kind of think Sheriff Dad
could use some of that
anger management therapy
himself.
-[score fades out]
-[Em inhales sharply, deeply]
-[door thuds open,
slams closed]
♪ Oh, baby,
I'll never let you go ♪
-Marshmallow?
♪ Oh, baby
-[crinkling]
-[girl laughs]
-[Cooper chuckles]
Flip.
♪ Only me
-[static on radio]
-[song cuts in, out]
-[creepy score]
-[wind rustling]
-[distant eerie howling]
-(whisper) Did you hear that?
-[muffled footsteps]
-[creepy score intensifies]
-[footstep]
-[rumbling]
-[chittering]
-[static on radio]
♪ ...me, baby, I love you
-What was that?
-I don't know.
-IBRAHIM: Thanks for letting me
stop by on short notice.
-DANA: No problem.
How's the coffee?
-[coffeemaker clatters]
-Uh, it's good.
Thanks.
-So, what brings you by?
-[Dana grunts]
-Uh, actually, I am, uh,
running into a bit of a problem.
Um, I can't seem to get anywhere
with your sheriff father
and, uh, I'm out of ideas,
so I was wondering
if maybe you could--
-You're looking--
You're looking for advice
from me on how to get along
with Wayne Cypress?
-Well, you're his daughter.
-Aw.
-Thought maybe you could--
-Well, whatever it is,
you're better off talking to JP.
He's the reasonable one.
-Well, unfortunately,
it's the sheriff
who's got Governor Harris' ear
and not JP, so, yeah.
And the CDC
has its own jurisdiction,
but somehow I feel like I got,
uh, red-taped into a corner.
-All right, well, listen,
my dad's pretty simple.
I mean,
he's not easy to deal with,
but he's simple.
He just wants to feel like
he's being helpful.
Yeah.
-Helpful.
-[scoffs]
Treating revivers like
second-class citizens
is helpful?
Marking their IDs is helpful?
Threatening them
with jail time is helpful?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I know, I know he's your father,
but I just, I feel like that's
just a bit ridiculous.
-No, don't apologize.
That was hot.
-[laughs]
I get it.
But in his mind
that's being helpful.
I don't know what you're
up against, but I've never once
successfully got Wayne Cypress
to change his mind, so...
best of luck.
-[door squeaks open]
-[Cooper giggles]
-God.
-[Dana sighs]
-Listen, just let me deal with
the kids and I'll be right back.
-Yep. You gotta do your thing.
-(whisper) Okay.
-He's a scientist who invented
the anti-matter ray.
It would definitely
work on the thing in the woods.
-DANA: All right, guys.
I let you stay up late
in that tent. Time for bed.
Brush your teeth?
-Yes, Mom.
-Let me smell.
-[Cooper exhales loudly]
Very good.
Jordan, are you
going to be comfortable?
Can I get you anything?
-I'm okay.
I don't really sleep anymore.
-[tender score]
It freaked my parents out
so I just pretend.
-Well, you don't have to
pretend here.
And I'm sorry
if anyone made you feel like
you can't be yourself.
-Well, what if they're right?
I feel like there's
something missing in me.
-No.
There is nothing wrong
with you.
You're special
and you are so brave.
And if anyone doesn't think that
you are perfect,
then that's their problem,
not yours.
Right, Coop?
-Yeah.
-You, sir,
do need to get some sleep.
(whisper) You have to make sure
he gets some sleep!
-Yeah.
-[lip smack] Thank you.
-Hey, um...
-[laughs awkwardly]
Can I, um,
can I buy you dinner tomorrow?
-[tender score]
-[knocking on door]
-[score fades out]
-Uh, yeah,
just give me a minute.
-I'll only be a minute.
-What-- Diane.
Did Ken send you here?
-So only the mayor
can speak to
the almighty sheriff of Wausau?
Ken doesn't know I'm here.
-What is it, Di?
-I don't know how else
to say this, so,
I'm a reviver, Wayne.
-I'm so sorry.
-[splutters] I didn't know.
How did it happen? When?
Oh my God.
Diane, you didn't--?
-And now you know, so, um...
-[tense score]
so maybe we can
keep my registry off the books?
-(whisper) Oh, yeah, um...
I can't
just pick and choose who--
-Will you help me or not?
-Look, I have an obligation to
the town.
I have to keep everyone safe.
-Safe from me?
-[Wayne inhales deeply
through nose]
All I'm asking
is for you to be a friend.
Just like I was to you
when you lost Patty.
-(whisper) That's not fair,
Diane.
-We stepped up for you, Wayne.
We looked after your girls
and your house!
Don't act like Ken didn't look
the other way during that time.
And we did it happily
because you needed help.
I need help now, Wayne.
-[sighs]
-[score intensifies]
Please.
-I'm sorry.
Oh my God.
So, what would you like
to accomplish
in our sessions together?
Is there anything
that you feel like discussing?
Honestly, Martha, I'm not about
forcing a dialogue.
If you want to leave,
I'll sign your court forms
and I won't stop you.
How do you think
being a reviver
has impacted your emotions?
Aaron-- Dr. Weimar--
is my husband and he told me.
Your secret is safe with me.
He just wanted to help.
-[scoffs quietly] Does...
doctor-patient confidentiality
cover...
this?
-It does.
I have other clients
who are also revivers.
But Martha, I also think that
you could use some help.
Perhaps your recent
violent outburst
is tied to the fact that you
went through the greatest trauma
anyone can experience.
You died.
Now do you remember
what happened
the night of Revival Day?
-Bits and pieces. I was high.
I was high a lot back then.
-People in pain self-medicate.
Were you self-medicating?
-I guess
you could call it that.
I lost my mom.
-[tender score]
And it was an awful accident
and it might have...
been my fault
and I-I got hurt and I...
-[trembling inhale]
I went there that night...
on her birthday and I just,
I had to get high
to get through it.
-And what were you doing
that you needed to be high for?
-I don't know.
Saying goodbye?
-You were in a
very vulnerable place.
I'm sure that there were
a lot of choices
that felt logical
in that moment--
-Yeah, I know.
My sister thinks I...
killed myself or OD'd,
but I don't...
I don't know. I'm really...
starting to think that
someone hurt me.
-So your sister knows that
you're a reviver?
Who else knows?
With these new mandates
you need to be--
-No, I know.
It's a secret and I'd--
-[sniffles]
really like to keep it that way.
My dad doesn't even know.
-Well, that sounds like
something.
Why not tell your dad?
-I think...
After losing my mom
I just don't know if
he could handle it.
Besides, you've seen how
he's reacted to the whole town
and he's always seen me
as fragile
and I don't know if
knowing I died
would make that worse somehow.
-Sorry, I just find it
surprising that anyone
would see you as fragile.
-To be fair,
I have a condition called O.I.
Brittle bone disease,
so they always
had to be careful with me.
-We do a lot
to protect our loved ones.
But I don't think that
we acknowledge enough
that it hurts when an illness
changes our relationship
with them.
How they see us as weak,
even if it's from
a lens of love.
-I'm, I'm sorry.
My mom had cancer too.
-Oh.
Well, then she must have been
a very strong woman.
-[Nithiya sniffles, exhales,
clears throat]
-[sniffles again]
-[distant dog barking]
-[air drill whines]
-That's right,
Blaine dropped it off
around 10 p.m. '99 Accord.
-Okay, who rented the car
that night?
-Let's take a look.
-[sighs loudly]
-[air drill whines]
-You don't keep your records
on a computer?
-My daughter,
she tried to get me
one of those Macintoshes.
I told her, throw them all away.
IBM, Dell -- doesn't matter.
They all emit, uh, radio waves.
You know what that is?
-Do you know what that is?
-Gives you tumors.
-Sure.
-Gotta take care of the brain.
It's why I do a crossword
every day. Ah!
Here I go: James Anderson.
Paid $75 cash.
I kept the deposit
because he dumped it instead of
bringing it back.
-Where's the driver's licence?
-He ain't got one.
-You rented a car to a guy
without a driver's license?
-No ID, no credit check.
I ask no questions,
you get a car.
And I pay a little more
on my girl's student loan.
-Killing me, Alonzo.
Can I see the car?
-Yeah. For sure.
-[keys jingle]
There you go.
-You're so nice,
but you're so stupid.
-Thanks.
-[bass-heavy rhythmic score]
-[sighs]
-[score fades out]
-Nobody has ever given me
a massage before.
-[chuckles through nose]
-[bones crack softly]
-Like that? Like, are you sure?
It's okay?
-Yeah.
-[laughs through nose]
-I can still press
a little harder.
-Okay, try harder.
-Okay.
-[laughs through nose]
-[tender score]
-[lips smack]
Em, um, we don't have to.
We can just chill or whatever.
-You're not gonna break me.
-[lips smacking]
-[heavy breathing]
-[Em gasps]
-[muffled cries]
-[score intensifies]
-[muffled groaning]
-Are you all right?
Did I hurt you?
-No, Rhodey, I...
I remember on the bridge,
someone grabbed me.
They put a cloth over my face
and I felt woozy
and they knocked me out.
-Blaine?
-EM: No.
No, he left in his truck
and this guy's hands were clean.
There were no scars,
no tattoos but he...
-[dramatic whooshes]
-[bag jangles]
-[score intensifies]
-[paper crinkling]
He was wearing...
-[zipper scratches]
-[paper crinkling]
This!
Knew I wasn't crazy.
The morning I woke up,
I threw this up.
-BLAINE: They smile
with familiar faces.
But do not be fooled.
The dead do not return
without cost.
Their presence is a test
and most have already failed.
I have seen
the truth beneath their skin.
And I say to you now
lock your doors.
Guard your souls
for the deceiver
is within the gates of Wausau.
-Good! And down.
Excellent, Wanda! Excellent!
-[score fades out]
Wanda's our living inspiration
that even death
is no excuse to skip cardio.
Good class, everyone.
And remember:
old age only begins
when you look backward
rather than forward!
See you next week!
-[eerie score]
-[excited chattering]
-It's one of them.
-[man exhales deeply]
-Just let me go.
-MAN: Where? Back to Hell?
-[woman sighs]
-Thank you.
-[footsteps receding]
-The wrath is coming!
-It's really any patient
who would've registered
past 6:47 pm on the 18th.
-[score fades out]
-[indistinct PA announcement]
-[indistinct chatter]
-I have David Kreutz at 6:48.
6:50, Olivia Yazden--
-What about
a James Anderson or...
-[page flipping loudly]
Weimar?
-Oh, yes.
Nithiya Weimar at 6:51.
-Was her husband with her?
-[soft rhythmic score]
-Um, yes,
her husband's always with her.
-So, could you see
what time they left that night?
-Oh, I don't have
an exact time.
Her chemotherapy is usually
scheduled for five hours,
so they probably left
close to 12 midnight or so.
-So if Nithiya was here 'til 12
but the car was dropped off
at ten...
He left.
He's using the chemo sessions
as an alibi.
-Sorry, an alibi for what?
Did something happen to
the Weimars?
-Not yet.
-[dramatic rhythmic score]
-[loud knocking on door]
-[doorbells chiming]
-This is Professor Weimar.
Leave a message.
-Mr. Weimar, this is
Officer Dana Cypress again.
I just came from your office.
They said you were at home.
Now, let me guess,
you're back at the office?
You need to call me back,
ASAP.
-[phone clicks closed]
-[sharp bang]
-[score intensifies]
-[door rattles loudly]
-[security system beeps]
-[sharp bang]
-[door hinges creak]
-[score fades out]
-[door bangs closed]
-We're closing up.
Why don't you try Donaldson's
on Seventh?
-We've been. You're literally
the last pawn shop we're trying.
-ID.
-Uh, shoot, you know, I, uh...
-[zipper rasping]
I forgot mine at home.
-Here.
-What can I get you?
-Do you sell rings here?
-Do I sell rings?
-[clattering]
I sell everything here, hon.
-Sold anything...
-[sharp bang]
...like this recently?
-Uh-huh.
Normally you'd be SOL,
but with this quarantine,
I've only had the one buyer.
-Who'd you sell it to?
-Now, look,
I wasn't officially open
during the 30-day lockdown,
you understand?
I don't need Dillisch siccing
the business lobby on me.
-Come on, man, do we,
do we look like feds?
-Had this gentleman email me
saying he needed to replace
his wife's wedding ring.
-[tense score]
Told him I couldn't order one in
'cause of the quarantine
but he was desperate.
Didn't want his wife to find out
he lost it.
Offered to pay me double.
In cash.
I got one adjusted
from what I had in stock.
-Do you remember
what he looks like, or his name?
-Never met him.
Left an envelope of cash
in the store mailbox.
That's where I dropped off
the ring when it was done.
I do have his email, though.
One second.
-[keyboard clacking]
James dot Anderson
at UWMC dot com.
-James Anderson.
Who the hell is James Anderson?
-Wait, that...
That's Aaron's TA.
-[loud dramatic score hit,
rumbling]
That asshole lied to me.
I got to go speak to him.
-RHODEY: Okay. Wait.
What are you going to do?
-[security system beeping]
-EM: I need to get him alone.
-Em, how?
-I'll follow him.
-[tense score]
-[door hinges creak]
-[drawer rasping]
-[papers rustling]
-Shit, shit, shit!
-[loud rattling]
-[phone keypad clicking]
-[phone line rings, clicks]
I've had enough of this.
I know it was you!
Yeah, or someone you've paid.
What's the difference?
He was in the house
with my wife.
This is going beyond
crossing a line.
Well, I kept up
my end of the deal!
I didn't tell anyone.
Of course not.
Nithiya doesn't suspect a thing.
Don't forget,
I can take you down with me.
-[phone button clicks]
-[loud dramatic staccato score]
-What are you doing?
-Go to bed.
-No. Tell me what's going on.
Why was that officer
at our house?
-Look, it's not good,
but I'm taking care of it.
The last thing I wanted was
for you to worry.
-What do you mean
you're taking care of it, Aaron?
-I'm taking care of it! Just...
Go to bed.
Please!
-[papers rustling]
-[dramatic tense score]
-[score abates]
-[flames crackling]
-EM (echoing): The first
morning birth,
there are no shadows
in the lightness night.
-[woman vocalizing]
And the prey rejoices
as the killers retreat.
-[dramatic boom]
I envy the sleepers,
the never were
-[dramatic boom]
and the long dead,
-[clippers buzzing]
denied this moment.
Each dawn's a question,
the same without you.
-[woman vocalizing angelically]
-[sharp inhale]
Why does the night end
and bring the mourning?
-[high-pitched ringing score]
-[dramatic boom]
-[muffled cries]
-[echoing sobbing]
-[score abates]
-Em,
I don't think
this is such a good idea.
-[Em laughs drily]
-It's the best idea
I've ever had.
-Maybe we just stay back
and think things through.
-No.
I'm done playing it safe.
You with me or not?
-Um...
-[Rhodey breathes nervously]
-I don't need you.
-[footsteps receding]
I don't need anyone.
-[score intensifies
dramatically]
-[knocking at door in
Shave and a Haircut rhythm]
-[score fades out]
-[rapid footsteps descending]
-[door rattles; hinges creak]
-[screen door hinges creak]
-Oh, hey.
Huh. Is, um...
Is your mom ready?
-She's freaking out.
-I am not freaking out!
I just couldn't find
my other earring.
-You, um...
-[short sharp laugh]
You look stunning.
-You look nice.
-Yuck.
-Hey. Told the babysitter
no video games past nine!
-I know, Mom.
-[door closes upstairs]
-[Dana sighs]
-You're still staring.
Is this good staring
or bad staring?
-Oh, no. No, no, no.
Um, just, uh,
don't take this the wrong way,
but part of me thought
when I showed up that
you would still be in uniform.
-[both laugh]
-Well, I always try
to make an effort
when someone's buying me
a lobster.
-Buying a lobster.
Uh, who said anything
about lobster?
I was thinking
the Lick-a-Chicken
down the-the road.
-[door bangs]
-It's Tony.
-[tense dramatic score]
-Hey, brother.
-Got news.
Boss is thrilled with
the new business opportunity
in Wausau and he wants us
to help him run it.
-Yeah? Check Kings, baby.
-Shut the hell up, Andrew.
There's a problem, though.
talked you boys up enough butI
ain't no way in hell
you're running this operation,
so you need to
get me back over the border.
You still play poker with
that piece of shit Irish cop?
-Yeah, he's around.
-Good. Good. Overpay.
Get him back on the line.
That'll get me back in there.
And this is important:
You want Ma to die in that
termite-infested shithole?
'Cause I'd like to see her
in a real house,
one with a painting studio.
-For God's sakes, hurry up!
-Excuse me.
-I'm done waiting.
-What is with the hostility,
brother?
-It's an emergency.
-Oh. It's an emergency?
Yeah, hang on.
-[man cries out]
-[impacts, grunts
and groans over phone]
-[hard smacks]
-[grunting]
-Give Mom my love.
-[phone clatters into cradle]
-[heavy footsteps receding]
-(whisper) You're going to
make sure
my wife is taken care of,
then we're even.
Yeah, well, screw me over
and you'll go down with me.
-Turn left. Turn left up there.
-Yeah, but the GPS
says to take a right ahead.
-GPS doesn't know what I know.
-It knows exponentially more.
-It does not.
Save the insults for tonight.
Come on.
-[phone buzzes]
Whoop, whoop.
Uh, go straight, actually.
Go straight.
-But the GPS says that--
-Oh, this?
-Oh, whoa.
-We don't know what it says.
-Okay
-Yeah.
This is more interesting.
-Okay.
-Where the hell are we going?
-Just...
-[score intensifies]
-[bird chirping]
-[tense score]
-[score intensifies]
-EM: Found you.
-What the hell!?
Have you been following me?
What are you doing?
-Who me?
This is about what you did!
-Look, I already--
-YOU'RE A LIAR!
I know what you did
and you're not going to talk
your way out of it this time!
-This is a really bad time.
-Yeah, it's always
a bad time, Aaron!
I found this in me, so tell me
what the hell you did to me,
you sick freak.
-(shuddering whisper) Look...
Look, I'm sorry.
I-I-I didn't mean to hurt you.
-You?
You killed me.
-[sighs]
-[loud dramatic score]
-[score abates]
-[tires crunching on dirt]
-IBRAHIM: Right there?
-DANA: Yeah.
-All right.
You sure about this?
This is pretty spooky, Dana.
Um... Ah
-[seatbelt lock clicking]
Okay, so, like in the car
is like a thing for you?
I can, um, I can be into that
for sure.
Oh, gross miscalculation
on my part.
Why would you bring a gun
on a date?
-Just wait for me.
Be right back.
-[tense dramatic score]
-[distant bird calls]
-[score intensifies]
-[grunts, groans]
-[Em breathes hard, grunts]
-[choking]
-[heavy gasp; coughing]
-[rasping inhale]
-AARON: You don't understand.
-[coughing]
I didn't kill you.
You're right, I was there.
I took you from the bridge,
but I didn't kill you.
I'm sorry.
You were special and I'm--
-[gunshot; echoes]
-(whispers) Aaron?
-[Em breathing hard]
Aaron!?
-[Em sobbing]
Oh, shit.
-[continues sobbing]
Aaron?
-[Aaron gagging]
-[shuddering breaths]
-[Em pants]
-Em.
-[Em gasping]
-[Em moans, pants]
(whispers) What did you do?
-[gunshot]
-[sharp gasp]
-[gunshot echoes]
-Uh, Dana?
-[emotional score]
-[breathy gasp]
-[score intensifies]
-Oh, Dana!
-[gasps, pants]
Dana. It's okay
-[Dana moaning]
-[Em crying]
-[emotional score]
-[Dana grunts]
-[gunshots]
-[Em breathes hard]
-Dana?
-[score abates]
-[panicked breathing]
SOMEBODY HELP!
-[gasps]
HELP! SOMEBODY HELP!
-[Dana moans softly]
Hey. Look, it's okay.
You're going to be okay.
It's okay. I'm with you.
Dana. Dana?
(whisper) Please.
-[Dana exhales softly]
-[Em sobs]
-[choir vocalizing dramatically]
-[score crescendos, fades out]
-[dramatic alternative score]