Previously
on Revival.
-Oh my God! They're alive!
Open the door! Open it!
The dead
have come back to life!
- Did you not go home at all?
Isn't your dad the sheriff?
-I've been texting, calling.
Emailing.
You're done ignoring me.
-This is reviver tissue.
Okay, so we're doing this.
-Yeah.
-I just don't understand how
panicking people is helping.
Authorize their removal.
Cooper!
No!
Don't tell Dad.
Reports keep
flooding in
as a number of incidents
are rising by the hour.
News coming while we...
Dude!
Dude, the hell have you been?
Are you seeing this shit?
-I don't care. I do not care.
-Em, there are zombies!
This is scary!
-Mm-hm. Yep.
We will watch 28 Days Later...
-Don't! No!
-...tomorrow, okay?
-No! Em!
. ..calm
and let the Mountain Bay...
-28 Weeks Later.
We already saw Days.
Twenty-eight
confirmed cases.
Please remain calm...
Oh, shit!
Hello?
Are you ever going to come out?
Em!
And, yeah.
Yeah, she's here.
Lazy ass never leaves her room.
Okay, talk then.
Dude, what's up with you?
Been, like, three days.
-Oh my God! Get high.
Why isn't this working?
It is now believed
to be a localized situation...
Shit.
-Dude, look,
I'm sorry to leave you 'cause...
...quarantine zone...
-I know you're struggling
and shit
but my parents
are next level freaking and
I guess I gotta wait out
the lockdown at their place.
-No, it's cool.
- I'll probably do the same.
- Mayor Ken Dillisch...
- I left a little nug for you.
- ...Wayne Cypress
continue to
assure the public...
- Hope it helps.
- ...law enforcement
s doing everything possible...i
Okay.
Meanwhile,
we can confirm that
the CDC has entered Wisconsin
and is working
with local authorities
Sheriff,
with the town now quarantined
and residents under lockdown,
what does this move say
about how scared
Wausau residents should be?
Uh, Jesus, May.
We're doing the best we can
with what we know.
What we need now
is for people to stay calm,
tay home and let us do our job.s
But these
revived people
are out there, Sheriff.
What are we to do
if we see one?
Well, that's
a good question.
If anyone out there
suspects anyone of being
one of these revivers,
they should report
their whereabouts immediately
to the authorities.
Don't take any chances.
- Chances.
- Is there a reason
for us to be scared
of revivers?
Look, we're not
trying to panic anyone here.
It's just smart
to take precautions.
But, sir,
can we at least confirm
how many documented cases
there are.
mean, why all of the red tape?I
Jesus Christ, May.
we're doing the best we can
with what we know.
Well, it appears
you know very little, sir.
The town is panicking
and we need answers.
- That's not fair.
- May, I'm trying here.
I assure you that as soon as
I have anything substantial,
you'll be the first to know.
Now, I'm sorry, but that's all
I have to say for now.
- Okay? Thank you.
- Sir, please.
Just answer this:
Are we safe?
-Em, are you okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'm good.
-I don't understand. You...
You're dead? You died?
-No one can know.
-But what happened? How did--?
Car 17 in pursuit.
- Dana, you there?
- Oh. Shit. Okay.
Listen. Listen, no, no, no, no.
Listen, you didn't do this.
I did. You understand?
Okay, Em, look at me. Em?
You, you and I have to be
on the same page
'cause they're coming, okay?
- Dana, come in.
- Okay, wait. Put this on.
- Officer Cypress unresponsive.
- Put this on. Quick.
-What do I say?
-You say that you--
I've got eyes
on her location.
-You were outside
and you heard gunshots.
And you ran inside
but everything was already done.
You didn't touch her -- I did.
Okay?
She went crazy. She killed her--
-Mountain Bay County Police!
- She tried to kill me,
but I cut her.
-Just me and you can know.
Promise?
- Yes, yes, yes!
- Dana! You okay?
-Yeah, it's good.
We're good! It's okay!
It's all right. It's all right.
-Holy smokes. Are you okay?
Wha...
-Her.
-The old lady?
Yeah.
She's stronger than she looks.
But we're okay.
We're okay.
-Hello?
Whoa!
Looking for these?
-Oh. Thanks.
-You're welcome.
What's your name, son?
-I'm not supposed
to talk to strangers.
-Fair enough.
And I'm guessing
you're also not supposed to be
in the woods alone.
-Sorry. I got lost.
-Oh, don't be.
Why don't you run along this way
and be found?
Cooper!
-Papa!
-Dude!
Oh my God! Are you nuts?!
I told you to stay put!
Your mother didn't teach you
not to run off like that?
-Did you hear it?
-Hear what?
There's something out there.
Ma'am? Ma'am?
She's having a panic attack.
Get her out of here.
-How am I supposed to explain
how an 80-year-old woman
ended up with a scalped head?
-She was a hell of a lot more
than just some old woman.
God, what a mess.
We got to keep the press
out of this as much as we can.
-Okay.
I don't even want to know
what my dad's gonna do.
This all needs to die with her.
You talk to Dittman,
assuming he wakes up,
and I'll get Em on board.
-Yeah.
-Where is Em?
-Isn't that Em?
-Oh, shit!
Oh! Ooh. Um.
-Huh.
-Mm.
-We've tested and verified
every known reviver
and, to date,
not a single one has shown
any aggressive tendencies
or abnormalities,
so what is different about you?
Let's do the autopsy here.
Nobody gets
inside this room, okay?
And, uh, I'm going to need
another set of hands.
-Okay.
-Got to put together a kit.
Okay.
-Okay.
-Seems you're fit as a fiddle.
Just a little panic attack.
You're free to go.
-Thanks.
Dude!
-Ooh. I know.
Relax, okay? They don't know.
I just, I passed out, but I--
-You're not okay.
You're not fine!
What happened to you?
-Okay, I'm still working on it.
But the truth is,
is it's all fuzzy.
I wasn't in the best place
and I just, I can't remember.
-Why didn't you come to me?
I mean, you can't just die
and not tell me.
-I will tell you
everything I can remember.
Can we just get out of here?
-Emmy!
-Martha! Tell me you're okay.
-She's good. She's fine.
-Let me look at you.
Are you sure?
They said you came by ambulance!
-I'm fine.
Just a panic attack, seriously.
-She's seriously fine.
Didn't we talk about--
-What were you thinking?
Taking your sister
to a crime scene?
-Okay.
-I raised you
with more sense than that.
-Uh, let me explain
what happened.
How was your day?
-Well, I got lost in the woods.
...for a reason, Dana.
-Is that so?
-I'm just so tired.
-It's okay.
They'll stop soon.
I don't think
I'm above protocol.
- I know.
- Also, I was rethink--
-Bottom line is I don't care!
If you had any inkling
this situation was dangerous.
She's not like us!
You know that!
-Sir, ma'am, if you could--
-Not now!
-Please! Really! You know?
-Whoa, whoa, whoa. Em.
-Let go!
-What are you doing?
You can't grab her like that!
How can you be so careless?
-Careless, Dad? Are you
not the one who lost Coop today?
-What?
What happened with Cooper?
-Nothing. Cooper's fine.
And I'm fine! Okay?
I don't need your help,
your protection, your advice,
your pity -- none of it.
I'm done.
-Martha, honey.
-No!
No, please,
I want to be left alone.
-But you...
-No!
I will figure it out
on my own.
-Okay, well, thanks a lot, Dad.
That was your fault.
-My fault?
Is that what happened to you?
-Yeah, but we're not
unpacking all that right now.
Now tell me what happened--
-I don't even--
-Sheriff, we need to talk.
-Rogers.
Listen, I need you to monitor
who's coming and going.
I want to keep a tight lid
on this whole mess, all right?
Nobody talks to the press.
-Yes, sir.
-All right?
Get Cooper home. Okay?
We'll talk about this later.
-Yeah.
-Yes?
-Uh, yeah, this way.
-Okay, what happened today
with Papa?
-I met a man in the woods.
- You what?
I'm gonna to shove his protocol
right up his ass!
-Mom, language.
-Ma'am, you need to leave.
You can't be here.
-Can I just have one minute?
-Okay, look, you know what?
I'll take care of her.
I know her, so, um,
can you take Coop
up to the cafeteria
and get him, like,
some pudding cups, or something?
-Sure thing.
-Okay, thanks.
I'll see you up there, bud.
-You want to tell me what
actually happened in that barn?
That's the thing.
Strength has as much
to do with the nervous system
as muscle mass and without
the proper pain response the--
Where's the guard?
-Um...
Uh...
-Jesus Christ.
I need everyone
to the first floor!
Everyone to the first floor.
Suspect is on the loose.
It's Arlene. She's alive.
The real joke is
your department thinking that
it can just sweep all this
under the rug. Again.
Tell me the truth.
-All right.
Well, I'll tell you what:
you keep thinking
that you are living
in an episode of The Wire
and the rest of us will just...
- ...keep up.
- Code red.
Emergency department.
First floor.
ode red. Emergency department.C
- Literally.
- Running with scissors.
Hey! Stay!
Jesus Christ.
Oh my God.
- What's going on?
- Ahhh!
-Oh, shit.
-What the hell is happening?
-I've got to get Cooper.
- Go!
- Dana!
-Dad.
-What are you doing here?
Where's Cooper?
-He'll be safe.
But, Dad, be careful.
-Just get out of here!
-Dad, you can't stop her!
Go! Get out of here.
-I'm going.
Troy, check him.
My Terry.
My sweet baby.
-Shh.
Shh. There, there.
-Come on!
Arlene, put the baby down!
Oh, shit.
Where did she go?
There!
Where the hell is she?
Let's spread out.
Stay quiet.
Put your hands up
and turn around.
Put your hands in the air!
What the hell
are you doing here, Blaine?
Oh.
-Where did you get the baby?
Where's Arlene?
-Behold.
And I have given you permission
to tread on the serpents
and the scorpions.
The gates of Hell have opened.
You're worried
about panic?
hat about when people find outW
that there's some super-strong
reviver running around
stealing babies
and throwing nurses
through walls?
-Oh, Wayne.
-I can't police something
that can't be killed!
-Not doing it.
-Look, look. First off
we don't really have
a proud history of
handling people
that are different.
But, that being said, Mayor,
you didn't see her.
This was different,
so, you know,
perhaps until we know
what we're fully dealing with
all options
should remain viable.
-See?
Even the bleeding-heart liberal
agrees with me.
We need to lock them up!
-Oh, no, no, no.
I didn't say that. I--
-Okay, I want to help. I do.
You've been complaining about
a lack of resources
this whole time.
What do you think
it's gonna take
to set up your camp?
And if Arlene's as scary
as y'all say she is,
I suggest that you take
what little resources you have
and you find her.
You do that and then we'll talk.
Em?
You here? We need to talk.
Shit.
-What do you think
you're doing?
-What the hell is this?
-This is your idea
of leaving me alone?
-Hey!
Cut me some slack here, man!
One minute we're talking about
us going to the beach
and then the next
I watch you die!
But then you're alive
because you had already died.
And you don't know
how you died
and now I find out
you're using again
and when Dad finds out
you're dead.
-Is there a question there?
-Seven thousand questions.
But let's start with this:
What the hell!
I thought you were doing better.
-Yeah, I... I was.
And then our accident happened
and that new
instant release shit is hardcore
so it, just, it got bad.
-Are you still on them?
-No.
When I woke up
it stopped working. I...
I sometimes still think
that I need it,
but it doesn't have
the same effect on me anymore
so I'm clean.
-There's like
a thousand pills in here.
How did you even get all this?
-The shady pain clinic.
If you have the money,
they don't really care.
-How did you get the money?
Em, isn't this
all kind of connected?
The drugs, the...
What happened to you could--
-No, I did not overdose.
-Didn't you?
Like, I saw, like...
Like, I just saw
your den of doom
and it's kind of,
I'm vibing, like,
mental health crisis.
-Because ever since I revived
I just can't,
I can't sleep anymore.
-Oh, God, you're emo.
Okay, how about you tell me...
Something? Anything.
So, I, uh...
I went to the bridge
on Mom's birthday
because I just, I...
I'm working through some stuff
and a friend said
it would be a really good idea
to get some closure there
and it just, it got...
a lot and I got really anxious,
so, yes, I got high and then
I woke up in Bull Falls.
-Okay.
You skipped a bunch of details.
Help me out here.
-Like, now?
-Yeah, now.
You have somewhere else to be?
-Um...
Yeah, it was, uh, nine, or...
Nine-thirty.
I think I saw, like,
a car headlight, or something.
-Could it have been
a hit and run?
What kind of car was it?
-I don't know. A normal car?
-Okay, well,
did you smell anything
...or...
...hear anything, or--
- Dana, please. Just stop.
- Or did you...
maybe...
did you hurt yourself?
-You know, I've, uh,
thought about that
a lot recently and, um...
No, no. I wouldn't. I, uh...
I couldn't.
- Shit!
I'm missing morning briefing.
Dad's gonna kill me.
-Mm-hm.
-Well, I guess that's
insensitive now.
I can't say anything.
-Oh, Dana.
Sometimes you are just too much.
Just wait, wait! Come to--
Goddamn it!
Just come to
the station with me, okay?
Just come real quick.
I'll show my stupid face
and look like I'm doing my job
and then you and me,
we'll go to the bridge,
we'll go to where you woke up.
-Dana.
-Okay. Please. I, I...
I want to find out
what happened to you.
And I can.
-Okay.
Yeah, let's go get this
over with.
Okay.
Where should we put
this mountain of drugs?
All right, listen up!
- Great.
Love when he's in a good mood.
- You said this would be quick.
- So be careful!
-I know, I just,
I'm supposed to be helping
with this Arlene insanity.
But I want to be here
for you first.
Give me a second.
Okay.
Okay. Sit. Um...
Grab something
from the vending machine?
Uh, maybe hang out
in the break room for a bit?
I'll be quick.
Get me a chocolate bar.
-What the hell do you want?
Can you tell me about these?
-Where are you
picking your blueberries from?
-I don't have time
for your stupid adages, McCray.
Come on.
-Blues. Oxycodone. IRs.
-I know what they are. How much
would a thousand of these cost?
-Now, see the street value
of it would be--
-No, no. Pain clinic.
-You ain't getting
no G of those
from no pain clinic.
-Well, where am I getting them?
-Ooh. Stealing or dealing.
-For who? From who?
-Well, who are you?
I'm not doing your job for you.
Now, may I please get back
to finding the old lady?
-How many drug-related offenses
do we have?
-Yeah, you shake up the can
be prepared
to deal with the fizz.
Shit.
My sister stole my car.
Is there anything I can snag?
-Uh-oh. Sorry, darling,
everything's gone.
On account of the manhunt
for Arlene.
-Could I borrow yours?
-Uh, no. Lester dropped me off.
-Oh, you could do
so much better than him.
-Well, Lester's a man
of hidden talents.
-What about McCray?
Or your dad, hm?
-Whose is the little hybrid
out front?
-That's Dr. Ramin's.
-You look beautiful.
-Are you sure
you're up for this?
we don't have to go.
-No.
It's important
we keep up appearances.
Let's try the dorms next.
Polos East off campus,
down this way.
Safety continues to
be a concern
as the suspect
is still on the loose.
Authorities have yet
to determine a motive
for the 82-year-old woman's
violent outburst.
Nobody's doing
anything!
I don't care if
they used to be good people.
-Em.
You okay, dear?
-Yeah, I'm fine, Nella.
Shouldn't we, uh,
be searching for Arlene
instead of, uh, your car?
-Shouldn't you be looking
in a microscope
at a... imbiba nucleus?
I don't even think you know
what you're saying.
-It's a tiny record store.
-Oh.
-And, anyway,
we're not looking for a car.
We're looking for my sister
in the car.
-Okay, and why, exactly,
would your sister
commandeer your car?
-She's acting out, that's all.
All right? She's young.
She's had a sheltered life,
sheltered childhood.
She never got to mess around,
be a real teenager, you know?
Make mistakes.
-Hm.
-Hell, I don't think
she's ever even had a boyfriend.
-Aaron.
-Em, what in God's name
are you doing?
My wife is right there!
-What am I doing?
You haven't answered
any of my texts,
calls or emails
for the last month.
I practically had to corner you
in your office
to get you to agree to meet me
and you ghost me!
-Well, Em, what do you
expect me to do?
We agreed to end this.
You know that!
You think this is how
to get back together with me?
-Jesus Christ, Aaron.
You are so full of yourself.
I don't wanna get back together.
Stop dodging me!
I want answers
of what happened near the falls!
-The falls? What? I...
I don't know what you--
A ring?
-Your ring!
Look, something happened to me
that night at Bull Falls.
I woke up and I threw this up,
so now you get to explain to me
how the hell your wedding ring
came out of my mouth?
-Wait. First, that's not mine.
Second, I have no idea
what any of this is about.
If you've been trying
to reach me
I haven't gotten
anything from you
since December 18th.
I had to block you.
You kept texting
and calling that night
and it felt like you were
hell-bent on exposing us
and I couldn't risk it.
So I blocked your number
and email. I had no choice!
-What? Shit.
-And I'm sorry.
Perhaps instead of you
throwing up a ring maybe
you thought you saw something
and found a ring
that had been left there.
People go to those falls often,
Em.
- Shit.
- I don't know.
I don't-
I don't remember sending any
of those texts or calls.
I was really emotional
and I got high and I thought
you'd be the one to tell me
what happened that night.
I thought you'd tell me
what happened to me.
To you?
Wait, Em, did you...
-Mm.
- You died.
You're a reviver.
Holy shit!
I had no idea.
And then...
-Oh, no, that night
those texts were scary
and I knew you were struggling,
but I, I...
I had no idea
you took this so hard.
-I've heard this before.
You think I killed myself?
-I'm sorry, but isn't that
kind of what you're saying?
But, hey, look, look.
You're okay now.
-That's the good news, right?
Like, you get a second chance.
And look at you. You look great.
-Don't, please.
I don't want to hear this.
Do me a favor and don't tell
anyone about me, okay?
-Sure. Yeah. And Em...
I'm so sorry.
-[score intensifies
I'm just worried
about her.
he's going through some stuff.S
And, you know,
it doesn't help that...
that Revival Day
was also our mom's birthday.
Our, our late mom's birthday.
I never get used to saying that.
-I'm sorry to hear that, Dana.
How long ago did that happen?
If you don't mind, uh,
if you want to talk about it,
you don't--
-Two years.
It was an accident.
Em and I were both in the car,
but Em was driving.
-That's awful. Uh...
Losing a parent is very hard,
uh, and I can't imagine,
considering the circumstances,
how traumatic that experience
would have been for both of you.
-Yeah. Thanks.
-So, I'm sorry.
-This is what happens
when we live all like
there's nothing wrong
with zombies.
We're losing our damn way
and for what?
God chose them to die.
Em was always
pretty isolated
because of her condition,
so it was just
always kind of...
tough, but then,
after the accident
and all the brutal rehab
I don't think she's
ver fully dealt with any of it.e
-What the--?
You bitch.
You said
her condition?
Yeah.
She has a disease
where her bones break easily.
-Osteogenesis Imperfecta.
-Yeah. That's the one.
-Yeah?
-Not many people know it.
Type 1. Type 1.
-It's Type 1.
-OI.
-It's still pretty debilitating,
so I understand when you say
that she is acting out.
That makes sense.
nd I, for one, would have a tona
of pent-up frustration...
...and always be, uh,
looking for an outlet.
-That all you got?
- She had it tough.
- She was on a first-name
basis with her doctors and
nurses
by the time she was ten.
But, you know...
no matter what, she always
was able to find levity
in the strangest situations.
It sounds like
her superpower.
How she copes
to get through or push through.
Hm.
Even with how weak she was,
she made it. Yeah.
-She, uh, sounds pretty strong,
actually, Dana.
-Oh, shit. Get out of the way!
Here. I got you.
Sorry
Em! Em!
-I'm okay. I'm good!
She broke
my damn nose.
-Nella?
Em did what where?
Where did she go?
-So, what's your story,
dead girl?
-Cuts. I saw them heal.
Don't worry. Nobody else saw.
Name's Rhodey.
-Em.
You know we can heal?
-And a whole lot more than
a couple of cuts
and broken bones.
But I tend to save
the bigger stuff for my show.
Speaking of, our first show
since lockdown's Saturday.
This place called The Shed.
You should come.
You're a reviver?
-I prefer musician first,
but it's not so bad.
Hell of a lot better
than I was a month ago.
-So...
I, uh, kind of need to
avoid the cops for a variety
of reasons right now.
Do you think you could
get me out of here?
-Yeah. I got you.
-Cool.
I'll just be right back.
And there's my car.
-Okay.
-Well, thank you so much
for the ride.
-Of course.
-Could do it again some time.
-Do, like, what?
Just give you a ride?
-No.
We-- Us. The--
Like this.
Don't worry about it.
-Okay. Awesome. All right, bye.
-Okay.
-Okay, bye.
-I'm still mad.
-What the-- What the hell?
You just can't barge in
like that!
-I can
'cause the door was open, so...
No, don't have reasonable cause.
I'm just gonna...
Listen...
I'm not here for this.
But I can be
if you don't play
your cards right.
Sit down.
-Feel like I'm losing control.
My family.
My job.
This town.
-No. No.
-I just...
-No, no, no, no.
Wayne, you are a good egg.
Your job, this town?
They elected you.
They trust you.
So now you need to
trust yourself.
So you just get on out there
and do what you think is right.
The rest will work itself out.
Okay? All right?
Evening, Governor.
Sorry to bother you so late.
Well, you know, it's uh,
we're handling it, but, uh...
You know,
it's been tough.
And on that note, um,
listen, things have taken
a turn out here and, uh,
you know, you always told me
you owed me one.
You get her this?
- Me?
- Yeah.
-Hell, no!
Who do you think I am?
-I think you got picked up
for possession with intent
last year.
-Oh my God. Okay, okay.
Okay, wait. Look.
Look-look-look. Time out.
Those charges are being dropped.
Look, lady, I just...
I just left her some pot
to help with the pain
and for all I know
that's all she does.
And that's all I do, too.
And maybe molly. I don't know.
-Then explain it to me.
-Look, she-she...
Like, she wasn't good,
all right?
Like she was all strung out
as hell
and she'd been really depressed
and then it got bad.
And so we were just going to
help her get a quick little fix
and then, and then...
-What do you mean a quick fix?
-What? What? What did you do?
-No, no. It's what she did!
Look, I heard you guys talking.
I know Em is a reviver.
And I knew I shouldn't have
taken her there. Shit!
Shit.
-Taken her where?
Hey!
If you got her something
and she OD'd
she's not the only one
who will be dead.
- Okay.
- So this is your one chance
to come clean.
Where did you take her?
What did she take?
Who gave it to her?
-No, no, wait! Lady, stop.
-Stop calling me lady.
I'm barely older than you!
-You're asking
the wrong questions.
I know who killed Em.