Watch your six, ma'am.
John Doe coming through.
You know, people ask me
all the time,
do I think the folks I put in
the old Firebox 5000 feel it?
People ask you that?
I tell them about
old Jerry Bowers.
See, he had this crazy condition
where he couldn't feel no pain.
Like, you could stab him.
Nothing. Sounds great, right?
Well, turns out we actually
need to feel the pain
to stay alive.
Otherwise, might get a hand
stuck in a woodchipper
and not even know it.
Anyway, let's get this puppy up.
Let's go.
Ah! More like John Doughy.
This dude's heavy.
Okay, looking good.
Now, pay attention, Miss Toe.
It's Tao.
You a vegetarian, Miss Tao?
- No.
- 'Cause personally,
I like my chicken oven-roasted.
Do you really think people care
about this kind of stuff?
I find most don't
once the tears dry, you know?
It's a segment on unusual jobs
for people in town, so...
I would say that this qualifies.
What was that?
Is that
supposed to be happening?
Goddamn it, Benny!
Oh my God!
Oh my God! They're alive!
Open the door! Open it!
I'm trying!
I gotta override the system!
I can't!
I can't open the door.
Flames will shoot everywhere!
- Hurry up!
Oh!
Ah!
What's going on?
Oh!
This ain't my fault.
Well, this sure as shit
isn't my fault.
When is it ever, Dad?
What is that supposed to mean?
Of course you're doing this!
You've been running ever since
you fumbled the Blackdeer case.
I'm doing what's best for me
and Cooper!
I need a fresh start.
We all do.
Oh, that's real nice, kid.
Given everything our family
has been through.
Damn it!
What the hell is going on?
Look, I... Just stop.
This one's really cool, Mom!
Oh, yeah.
Wait. What!?
Haven't seen this old relic
in a while.
There's a reason for that.
I can't. I'm with my daughter
and my grandson right now, okay?
I have to go. You handle it.
Still using the family excuse?
What're you gonna do
when Cooper and I are gone?
It's not like
you can just be honest.
Oh, that's rich coming from you.
Hiding all of this.
Taking away my grandson.
Quitting on me. On our town.
On your sister!
- Are you serious?
- I am your boss, too!
Were you even gonna bother
to tell me?
Ugh. Damn it!
Yeah, I guess I forgot
how easy it is to talk to you.
Consider this
my two weeks' notice.
Yes. Randy did what?
What does that even mean?
Oh, wait. Hold on!
What?
Okay, okay. Slow down.
Yeah, look, I got...
What?
Well, where did they go?
How the hell
am I supposed to know?
Yes.
Okay, look, I'll handle it.
You stay put, all right?
The apocalypse start
or something? What's going on?
I'll get the Seeleys
to watch Cooper.
- I need you.
- What?
What is going on, Dad?
I don't know, exactly.
Go see Randy. Find out
what's got him all worked up.
You are still a
Mountain Bay County
police officer
for the next two weeks, right?
All units, please confirm.
We have multiple 10-33s
in progress.
I need someone east...
Forrest. Another at...
Cordova Drive...
Crap.
Jeannie, you there?
Jeannie, come in.
What the hell, man?
Alert! Again, multiple 10-33s.
Units are...
Hey.
Can you help me?
- What's going on?
Hello?
Officer?
- Where the hell am I?
Don't know what's going on.
Is this some kind of a joke?
Oh, why are we here?
Wait! What day is it?
I don't understand.
Miss Cypress?
You, do you know
what's happening?
- Ma'am?
- Can you help me?
Have you seen my mommy?
I... I want my mommy.
- Someone buried me alive.
- Officer!
It's been 35 days
since Revival Day
and after weeks of uncertainty
the lockdown has officially
been lifted.
Mayor Ken Dillisch's
surprise decision
just less than 48 hours ago
allows residents
to leave their homes,
return to work
and reconnect with loved ones.
However, authorities emphasize
that the quarantine
remains in effect
with CDC checkpoints
ensuring no one leaves Wausau
while investigations
nto the revival event continu. I
The Sheriff's
epartment continues to maintanD
a registry of revived citizens
and urges citizens
to report any new cases.
O far, 47 have been identifie, S
all tied to a specific
two-week period...
leading up to Revival Day
on December 18th.
The CDC reassures the public
there is no cause for alarm.
Governor Harris
outlined more detailed
quarantine rules today
at her press conference
stressing that only
vital goods and services
can cross the border
and that approval process
is still being defined.
There is no confirmed date
for this change...
Jesus Christ.
Kay? Are you home?
Kay, what's going on?
Lockdown's over.
Dude, come on.
Did you not go home at all?
Like, isn't your dad
the sheriff?
I've just, uh, I've had
some stuff to deal with.
Liaison who just arrived
You know what blows?
Week this all went down,
I was supposed to be visiting
my brother at Northwestern.
- And?
- And I could've been
in Chicago this whole time.
Not, like,
quarantined in goddamn Wausau
with a bunch of
lame-ass zombies.
I'm sorry?
Well, you know what?
Classes start back up tomorrow
and as excited as I am
to go to school
with a dead person...
Goddamn Shelly should have
stayed that way.
Whatever.
Um, I need to get
the rest of my shit from my car.
And do you think that maybe
we could...
Maybe we could clean this up
a bit?
We could watch a movie after.
Ooh. Oh, ooh, ooh. Sorry.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Ah!
Hold on, hold on,
I think we just dented your car.
- Not mine. Mm.
- Okay. Mm.
Uh, should we leave a note?
Absolutely not.
Is this your vehicle?
- Dude!
- Yeah?
- You talk too much.
- Okay, okay.
Wow. Okay. Huh.
Oh, yeah.
- All right. Oh.
- Okay. Ow!
- Oh, you all right?
- Yeah, I just banged my foot.
- Okay, so we're doing this, huh?
- Yeah.
- Might not be a great idea.
- No, I think it's good.
Okay, you do...
It's really a big coat. Sorry.
- It's so big. Yeah.
- Yeah, look, okay, this is...
Okay, yeah. This is great.
- Yeah.
- It's great but maybe we could
maybe we should talk about
what I do occupationally...
Oh, okay. Wow.
This is happening, huh?
Been a bad month.
This is my good bra.
Don't ruin this.
- All right.
Is that your phone? Okay.
Shit! Shit!
It's... babysitter.
- Babysit...
- Everything okay?
Yes, Coop's in bed.
Where are you?
- Out. What's up?
- It's Lester.
Should I...?
- He's found a dead horse.
- And?
Go check it out.
Figure out whose it is.
I'm not on dead animal cleanup
for some old rich prick.
- Damn it, Dana, not now.
- Don't need this shit from you. - I
- et over there and deal with it.
- G
- That was your babysitter?
- Don't worry about it.
- Okay. I'll go. Yeah, it's okay.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I'm gonna go. No worries.
I'm sorry, I'll go.
- Okay.
- All right. Coat.
- Coat.
- It's cold. Don't forget this.
- Okay. Thanks. Be well.
- Yeah. You, too.
- Okay. All right.
Can I call you sometime?
- Okay.
- Yeah.
All right. Uh...
Get your number next time!
What you think?
Ah! What the hell? Lester!
You trying to give me
a heart attack?
Of course not.
But if you don't cut out
the trans fats
like I been telling you,
you might have one
all on your own.
You not read my books?
- Can we skip the trip
down Majak memory lane please?
- I'll have you know, Officer,
that even at 82,
I believe my best days
are still ahead of me.
In my bestselling book,
A Strong Century, I...
Lester.
Horse.
- What do you think killed it?
I don't know.
Did you talk it to death?
Ha, ha, ha.
Coyotes?
Did you drive your truck here?
Yeah.
I pulled it around the bend.
Then I was getting
some extra steps in.
What are you doing?
Oh, um...
I don't know. I mean, uh,
I tumbled over...
and I had a pain
shooting up my arm...
- Cooper! Come on buddy!
- then everything went dark.
And then bam! I was awake.
All happened in a blink.
- nd hand to God I feel the sam.
- A
And I know that
the sheriff's new task force
has a registry
of every revived citizen.
I also know that it's safe
to leave our homes.
You're gonna be late.
Get your butt in gear!
Visiting
Manning Meats later today
for some of this man's
fine brisket.
Well, I'm not one
to hurt business, Mr. Mayor,
but take it from me:
go light on the red meat.
Cooper! We have got to go!
- Stop yelling, Mom.
- Jesus!
How long have you
been sitting there?
Are you really sure it's okay
for us to go back to school?
Yeah, you heard the guy.
Scientist-approved.
You know nothing happens
in this town
without your grandpa's approval, right?
All right, here you go.
Oh. Okay.
Wait, wait, wait!
Let me see you.
Hat. Coat. Lunch. Okay. Okay.
Okay. Have a good day!
Why do we have to
go to school with the zombies?
Do you think she's going to
eat our brains?
- Eww.
- Hopefully not.
Do you think
she's, like, less smart?
Cool! Look at this.
I don't think I look like that.
- Oh, I know.
- You think so?
I'm glad you're back.
Officer.
Why are we trapped with freaks?
The checkout girl
at Richmonds is one of them.
She wore all black
and was super-pale and had these
crazy dark eyes.
That's Tina.
She just likes The Cure.
There's something
in the woods. I can hear it.
I'm telling you.
I hear you,
Mrs. Shaw, I do.
But if he passed before the 4th,
I don't, uh...
Oh! Morning.
Saved one for you.
Jeannie, you are an angel.
Are we sure?
He passed one day prior.
Just one day.
Maybe he's gonna
come back later?
I just don't know, Mrs. Shaw.
I'm so sorry.
Mm.
You find
your Seabiscuit slayer yet?
Brush your teeth, McCray. God.
Lost my appetite. It's for you.
- Oh, thanks.
- You get me that registry?
He's not budging.
Says task force only.
Nobody tells me anything
around here.
I just want a real case.
Yeah, you'll have to take it up
with your dad.
But, right now,
it's snug on his desk.
He's hanging onto it
like a tick on a hound.
Jesus Christ!
My kid was bullied
at school this morning.
Speak of the devil.
Oh, Lord.
They've been at it all morning.
Yeah, I'd stay out of
the blast zone if I was you.
Feel bad for the new guy.
New guy?
What do you mean new guy?
How do we have a new guy?
CDC folk. This one's
a real cutie patootie.
Oh.
- Yeah.
- Oh.
Let me introduce myself.
Oh, Dana. Dana.
Oh, Wayne, be reasonable!
Reasonable? You're the one
who paraded that man out there
in some ridiculous
publicity stunt
while we're sitting on
a powder keg!
Look at them out there!
- I just don't understand
how panicking people is helping.
If anything, I'm helping you.
You want to help me?
Authorize their removal.
Why can't you see this
as an opportunity?
It is my job to keep
these people...
Our people! safe!
Oh. Why do you have to
make this so hard on yourself?
Because when you die, Ken,
you die!
- I won't send them away.
- We'll see.
You are one stubborn asshole!
You'd know.
- Dana.
- Mayor.
No, Dana, don't go in there.
Come on. No.
- Yeah.
- No.
Yeah.
You know, if you want to
send a message to Dillisch,
Lester's got a dead horse
with a head you can mail.
- Dana.
- Mm-hm?
This is Dr. Ibrahim Ramin,
our new CDC liaison.
This is Officer Dana Cypress.
- Cypress.
- Yeah, it's my daughter.
Okay, yes.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
- And also with you.
- Likewise.
Yeah, okay, let's wrap it up.
Yeah, quickly, sir. I just,
I've only been here for two days
and I need the appropriate time
to catch up
and help us figure out
what caused this
so if we can please
just communicate,
that would be great
for both parties.
What the hell do you think
we're doing now?
Yeah, this is communicating,
isn't it?
- Uh, yes.
- Mm-hm.
- Yes?
- And have you considered
that maybe Revivers
might be dangerous?
Right?
Uh, yes, of course
we've considered that
considering our, our, yes,
our meticulous approach
and extensive testing,
but to be clear,
we have no data to substantiate
that line of thinking.
Uh, all reviver subjects to date
appear normal.
What is going on
between you two right now? Huh?
- What?
All I'm saying, sir, is I need
the appropriate time to
detail findings, observe them
in their environment
not just for the
preservation of this community,
but for the vast potential
of this, this discovery.
So, just, you know,
I don't step on your toes
and you don't step on mine.
Deal, sir?
I've got much bigger shoes
than you do, Doctor.
That'll be all for now.
Thank you.
Thank you, sir.
Okay.
Did you sleep with him?
What?
Dad!
Anyway, moving on.
Did you take care of the horse?
Uh-huh.
Randy's on the necropsy.
We're just figuring out
where it came from.
Finish up quick, okay,
'cause we're stretched
pretty thin as it is.
Myles Miller?
Mm.
Helen, how you doing?
How's Bill and the gang?
Hi, Dana.
Uh, they're great. Yeah.
Do you have a minute?
- Always, for you. Yes.
You know how excited
everyone was to make you
a part of the Paper Street
security team?
Yeah, yeah.
What do you mean "was"?
I'm sorry but we can't
keep holding the position.
I know you're stuck there,
but it's been over a month
and we can't keep waiting.
We have to move to
another candidate
who's available.
I'm really sorry, Dana.
Helen! Hel...
- Howdy-ho, Officer Cypress.
- Jesus.
Forget to put some glitter
in your coffee this morning?
What do you want?
All right, no horsing around.
Uh...
Oh, come on! That was a joke.
'Cause you gave us a horse to...
- Randy!
- Yeah, so the horse, uh...
I lost it.
- What do you mean you lost it?
- All right.
I was minding my own business,
doing my job, right?
And then these CDC folks
swooped in all fast like
and took it!
Was some ET shit.
So, yeah, you might want to
check in with them
if you have the time.
Nothing but time.
You'll be fine.
Unfortunately,
that's the last person
I can meet with today.
Thanks.
I'm sorry.
I'm in a rush
and really don't have ti...
Uh, Miss Cypress.
I really must be on my way.
Nope. No.
- What the hell are you doing?
- I'm doing what I have to do.
- Please just...
- I've been texting. Calling.
Emailing.
You're done ignoring me.
Fine. We'll meet.
Tonight. Our spot.
You'd better be there.
I will. I promise. But Em...
We have to be careful.
You were getting a little scary.
What...
What do you mean, "scary?"
Not now. Not here.
Tonight, seven o'clock.
Okay?
Uh, Dana?
- Hey. There you are.
- Yeah.
What can I, uh,
what can I do for you?
- Can we talk?
- I... Sure.
- Great.
- Yeah. Just step into my, uh...
My office.
Huh. Right?
Yeah, wow. It's so big.
Hey.
We need to, uh,
evacuate the area. Thanks.
Sorry.
She's actually really nice.
She's just... She's here for me.
Let's, let's just
not make this a thing.
I had been stuck inside
for a long time
and lockdown made me...
You know,
it had an effect on my...
Libido.
Gross.
Yeah, can we just keep this...
professional?
Start over,
keep it professional.
So, why would you take my horse?
Oh, just don't...
Yeah. Don't touch that.
That's evidence. Thank you.
Usually, you keep evidence
in a bag.
We found an anomaly
inside the horse.
We found teeth.
Uh, human teeth.
You found yours in the horse?
Mine were just in the snow.
Well, what do you mean mine?
There's more?
Eh. Keep them
in this evidence bag.
Um...
Okay.
Ugh.
Oh my God.
These are identical.
Um, your teeth
and these teeth are identical.
These are a set of right
homologous lateral incisors
and these are superior
right canines,
all with pristine
dental clarity.
And I believe are derived
from the same subject.
What?
Um, okay, if I, uh...
Okay, if I show you something,
you'll keep it
between us. Right?
- Scout's honor.
- Okay, that's, uh...
That's...
That's not what that is. Um...
Okay, this is
reviver tissue, okay?
Look at this.
See?
- Oh my God.
- Yeah.
Okay, now,
this only works post mortem.
Anything pre-existing at
the time of death will remain.
That's why you see
some Revivers with scars,
or some with ailments and more,
but anything new,
their cellular structure
can regenerate.
Granted, wound severity
will dictate
the pace of healing, but...
- So, you're saying
that the teeth healed.
Well, regrew.
Yes. Yes.
Okay. Holy shit.
This makes sense.
It does to you?
Dana.
Lester, what truck do you drive?
Oh, well, I've got the F-150
3-liter Power Stroke V6.
Diesel, of course.
I used to have the 350 7-li...
- Oh, shit.
- That's rude.
Okay, the tracks at the scene
weren't from Lester's truck.
And the coyotes
that tore into the horse?
It was already dead by then.
They wouldn't go after
a living horse.
No! No way.
Someone was hiding the horse?
Someone left the horse
knowing animals would get to it
and cover up
what really happened.
Think about it.
This is someone strong enough
to bite through a horse!
Kill a horse!
And now you're saying
they can heal.
- Yeah.
- Holy shit, man!
I don't know how much experience
you have moving a horse,
but that's like a 1,000 pounds!
So someone went to a lot
of trouble to do this.
But not because
they were hiding a horse.
They were hiding a Reviver.
Oh. Okay.
Okay, um, if this is true,
if there is some rogue,
super-strong, animal-hating
Reviver on our hands
- Shh.
- If that's...
If that's true,
I need to see it.
- Same.
- Yeah. Okay.
All right. I'm on it.
Whatever makes them different
could be the key
to unlocking everything
about what happened here.
- Copy that.
- Oh. Dana, please.
This is still evidence.
- What is it, anyway?
This is a railway spike.
It's a part of the animal trap
that caught your coyote.
I mean, it was all handmade.
It was
a pretty ingenious design.
Um, but this? I don't know.
I doubt it's from
any active track
based on its age.
No, it's probably
from a really old one.
- Yeah.
- Got a train to catch!
Okay.
Huh?
Look, I'll just...
I'm sorry, sir.
There are no exceptions.
Oh, now,
that there's a longshot, Dana.
There were a bunch of these
little D-I-Y traps not far from
where I found the horse.
- Yeah?
Now riddle me this:
there are 47 names
on the reviver registry, right?
On the... Wait.
How did you get the...
You know what? I don't want
to know. I don't want to know.
How do we know
that's all of them?
I mean, the quarantine zone
is, like, 45,000 people.
I mean, someone could've
died in their sleep
and woke up and not even know
they're a Reviver.
I suppose. Yeah.
What about
this Myles Miller guy?
Oh, you think
he's your horse fella?
Well, he's the only Reviver
we know of
with a violent history.
How did he die?
Uh, he was on a life sentence
and he died of a stroke
in prison, I think.
And now he's out
and you can't find him.
If this is your guy, Dana,
please be careful.
Oh, God.
- Goddamn it, Ken.
- Dad?
- Martha?
- No one calls me Martha anymore.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I just...
I'm just, uh...
Where have you been?
I've called you,
like, three times.
Why are you ignoring me?
Did something happen?
- Dad!
Look, we had an agreement, remember?
You can't be out running wild
in your condition.
It's nothing.
I'm fine.
I just wanted to call
to let you know I was all right
and that I'll be better
about calling, okay?
Gotta go.
This is Professor Weimer.
Leave a mess...
Hello! Myles Miller?
Hello?
I ain't going back,
you hear me!?
You're not taking me again!
- Ah!
Ah!
Ah.
- Jesus Christ, lady!
Who's out here with you?
You got a truck?
How'd you move the horse?
A horse?
What the hell
are you talking about, lady?
Ain't nobody out here but me!
Get this off of me, please!
Jeez. Ah. Ah!
Do it for God's sakes!
Myles Miller?
No.
No, I'm not him.
- I think you might be.
No. Goddamn it!
Why can't you all just leave me
the hell alone, huh?
- Two days ago...
- I did my time.
- You were in the forest.
- Did it.
Right over there.
Where the horse was moved.
What!? Lady, I do not know
what the hell
you are talking about, okay?
I ain't with no horse.
- Help with the horse.
- No people. No nothing.
- Moved a horse.
- You got a thing for horses?
Yeah, you do. You horse people
are so damn weird.
Your teeth.
Your teeth
been growing back since...
What?
They look like they've been
growing back to you?
Huh?
No. Come on.
Hey, hey! Wait, hold on.
Hold on, hold on.
You're looking for a truck, right?
See, I saw a truck;
I heard a truck.
Went vroom-vroom few nights past
just like you said.
It was a red truck,
a dually with four wheels on it
and all that.
Yeah, and they had a tarp on it.
I bet they moved your horsey.
I bet that... Hey, wait.
You looking for a horse?
I'll get you a horsey, okay?
I'm a real good tracker,
real good hunter. Yeah.
Whatever horse shit you're into,
I got you.
Great.
Well, you're under arrest.
Dad!
Dad?
- Where's my guy?
- Papa!
There he is! Bring it in.
Oh! Come on.
Nice to see you, pal.
What's wrong with you?
Hey, you're still
not off the hook for that stunt
you pulled last night,
by the way.
You mean catching a criminal
you couldn't even find?
That stunt?
Yeah. So how long
are you going to be?
Couple of the farms
are on the outskirts
of the quarantined zone,
but shouldn't take too long.
All right.
You have fun and how about
you don't load him up
on sugar this time?
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
- Says the person who's going
straight to Friedman's
for a chocolate glazed.
You don't know me.
Mm.
Em!
Em.
- Dana?
What the hell?
Wait.
What the hell
are you doing here?
You know how risky it is for
you to be out here like this!
- I just dozed off.
- You dozed off?
Could you just take me home?
So, um...
we're not going to talk about
you adopting some kind of
vagrant lifestyle, hm?
Should I circle back
and look for your bindle?
What's a bindle?
Em, no one's seen you for weeks.
Dad's been freaking out.
The dead have come back to life!
Can't be finding you out here
sleeping on a bench, man.
Did something happen,
maybe with a guy?
You can tell me.
- Jesus, Dana, please. It's...
Enough with the questions.
I'm just...
I'm fine.
Okay.
'Cause you know your big sister
has a Taser and a gun.
And a low moral bar.
What were you doing
way out there anyway?
I was working a case.
Well, I was trying to.
Anything fun?
For a second there,
I thought so,
but now all I have
is a dead horse and a dead end.
You want some company?
No, I've got to get you
back to the dorm
before you break a femur,
or something.
Sorry.
Can I?
Yes.
Mm.
Remember the weekend
you broke up with Derek?
Mom got us a whole box of these
and then we got sick.
It was the first time I watched
Evil Dead 2.
Oh!
No, yeah, I remember that.
That was the first time
I caught Derek cheating on me.
Asshole.
I swore I was leaving Wausau
for good that time.
I was done. I was out!
Ten years later I'm still here.
Yeah. You always said
you would stay in Myrtle Beach.
You know I did want to go
on that trip with you, right?
It's okay. You got pregnant
with Cooper and...
life had other plans.
Listen, I know we haven't been
as close lately and...
Well, you can say no,
but what if,
after all this craziness end
and they lift the quarantine...
Wait. You want to
go to the beach?
'Cause I've still never been.
Let's go on an adventure
together.
I'd love that.
All right.
Well, let's go plan it.
- Like right now?
- Yeah. Why not?
Well, what about your work?
Who cares?
Farms aren't going anywhere.
Dad's watching Cooper.
Let's do it!
- Perfect.
- Mom usually lets me flip it.
Yeah, well, in my house,
I do all the cooking then
I don't wind up with a big mess.
But our kitchen's
already a mess.
Is that a fact?
The station had better be
in flames.
No flames here,
but I do have a fire
that needs putting out
at Opal Shaw's house.
Neighbors heard yelling
and it seems like
she's not answering the door
or her phone.
Yeah, she's been having
a tough go of it.
They're gonna burn, Grandpa!
Could use
a familiar face, you know?
Stay in the car.
Hello, Officer!
Morning there, Officer.
I'm, uh, Mrs. Dittman.
This is Mr. Dittman.
How can we help you?
- Officer Cypress.
I'm looking for a horse.
A horse?
I can tell you right now
we got no missing horse here.
- Yeah. All accounted for. Yeah.
- Yeah. Accounted for.
Uh, that's nothing.
That's just the animals
knocking about is all.
Uh, wait!
Officer.
- Yeah, Officer?
- Officer!
All right, buddy. You good?
You hang tight. Wait here.
I'll be right back.
Mrs. Shaw! It's the sheriff.
Could you please open the door?
That's a big chain.
Ah! Sorry, Sheriff.
Didn't hear you there.
- Sure.
- What's all the fuss about?
Good morning, Opal.
I'm just doing a wellness check.
We've received a few phone calls
about a disturbance here.
Loud noises and yelling.
From here? Oh, no, no, no, no.
You must be mistaken.
It's not what you think.
She's not all there.
She kept running out.
It's for her own safety!
All right. Stay back.
Would you mind if I
came in and took a look around?
No need for that, Sheriff.
I'm not decent at the moment,
but besides, everything's fine.
Just fine.
If you don't mind
I insist, please.
No! You don't understand.
Please? Please?
It, it's fine.
We're, we're, we're,
we're working it out!
We?
Oh, good Christ!
He, he, he's coming back.
- Mm-hm.
- Just like the others.
Only he's...
he's stubborn as, oh,
all get out.
Get up! Show him!
He, uh...
He passed one day before.
Well, but you knew him!
He was never late!
He was always early. Always!
Isn't that right, Eddie, baby?
I'm gonna need the coroner
at the Shaw house.
Yeah. Listen, we got a...
Sheriff?
Sheriff, are you there?
- Coop?
- Sheriff?
Cooper?
They just keep growing back!
Mom!
I need backup at Dittman's farm.
Stop! Everything's okay!
It's gonna be okay.
No-no-no! Don't go near her!
Holy shit!
Get off of her!
Pudding... Ho!
Em! Move! No!
No!
Em! Em! Em!
- Help me.
- No, no!
Shit!
Don't tell Dad.