Previously on Revival.
- Nice to meet you.
- I need time to detail findings
and observe them
in their environment.
-You want to help me?
Authorize their removal!
Reviver tissue
retains medical issues
present at time of death.
Have you seen my mommy?
Em, isn't this all
kind of connected?
The drugs.
I just saw your den of doom.
Did you hurt yourself?
You're a reviver.
-I prefer musician first.
-Evening, Governor.
Things have taken a turn here.
What the hell
are you doing here, Blaine?
-What did she take?
Who gave it to her?
-I know who killed Em.
- Oh, shit.
- Chill.
-Em, chill?
Uh-huh.
I just want the pills.
-You're saying Em didn't O-D?
You think someone murdered her?
-If she had just
followed my lead
everything would've been fine.
Okay, talk to me about this
because this is
a mother-clucking masterpiece.
-So, this one's dinner.
Mrs. Check
has three series.
Breakfast, lunch, dinner.
And which one you order
determines
what else you get with it.
You catch my drift?
-Yes!
This isn't that complicated.
-Okay.
Can I please use the bathroom?
-Uh, yeah. Sure.
It's just upstairs
around the corner.
Just be quiet up there.
Don't wake my baby.
- Yes.
You have
a thing for cocks.
What is that one?
-Oh, this one's a...
Then, while we're at
the Checks' house,
she goes right upstairs.
While they're sleeping.
Uh, yeah!
- Hey! What're you doing?
- Ah, jeez.
- Grab her!
- Oh my God, oh my God.
Everything okay?
- I'm sorry.
- We got to just--
Get back here,
you little shit!
-Oh my God,
oh my God, oh my God!
This is not being cool, Em!
This is the opposite
of being cool!
-And now, because she stole
from the Checks
you think they killed her?
-I didn't know Em was dead
and a reviver
until I heard you guys talking,
but, yeah.
Yeah, it all makes sense.
-No, it doesn't!
Em's had her issues
but she would never steal
from a drug dealer.
Sounds like you don't know
your sister, lady.
-There you go.
Nice day for a manhunt, right?
-Mm.
-I got a feeling
we're gonna find Arlene today.
Yeah. Oh, what you looking
up the Check Brothers for?
Do you think
they might be hiding Arlene?
-No, it's for another case.
-Must be a doozey.
-Mm.
-Their rap sheets are as long
as McCray's rat tail.
Though they have been
pretty quiet since Revival Day.
-My guess is 'cause
big brother Anthony
hasn't been around
to tell them what to do.
-Hm? Where's he at then?
-He left town
when Revival Day happened
and can't get back in
because of quarantine.
-Well, that's a blessing then,
yeah?
Don't need any more ding dongs
making life difficult in Wausau.
-There's another option.
He did something
so terrible on Revival Day
that he's been in hiding
ever since.
What kind of terrible?
-Murdering someone
that stole from his family.
-Oh, jeez. You think?
-I don't know.
- Oof. I hope not.
Oh.
I got a new picture of my, uh,
new girlfriend.
Just kidding. It's a cat.
-Yeah.
The real Jordan's dead.
She shouldn't be here.
I bet she doesn't even bleed.
-My mom heard on a radio show
that revivers are demons.
-Maybe she is.
-Your mom needs
to turn off the radio.
-I don't know if I'm supposed
to take them down or leave them.
-I think they're nice.
Everyone was really sad
when you died.
-Then why aren't they happy
I'm alive again?
- Watch this.
- Hey, Jordan, show me your hand.
I want to see something.
-Wait! Stop!
Aw!
Ah, God!
What the heck
did you do that for?
You and your reviver freak
are going to pay!
-Come on in! Wipe your feet.
Uh-oh.
Oh! Bless this mess.
Art lover.
-Mrs. Check. Hi. Dana Cypress.
You probably don't remember me.
I went to Durant High
with Andrew.
- Oh. Uh...
Well, judging by that uniform
you got on
you probably got better grades
than he did.
- I'm just kidding.
So, you're in the market
for some folk art?
-No. I'm here to investigate
a series of burglaries.
I was wondering
if you could tell me
did this woman
take anything from you,
or your home?
-Oh, heavens to Betsy.
That is that sweet girl that has
a good eye for great art.
No, no, no, no.
It was her pesky friend.
That girl who went
snooping around my house
and upset my boy.
This woman?
-Oh...
Yeah, ma'am, that is the one.
You can tell
she's got a black heart
by the look in her eye.
-All right, well,
thank you for your time.
-Oh, wait.
Hang on a second here.
Don't I get nothing
for helping you out?
Squid pro quo?
-Seems fair. Yeah.
Let's do a breakfast chicken.
-Okay. Which one?
Surprise me.
-I got one downstairs
I think you're going to love.
You just hang on.
-Can you please hurry?
-Hm.
-Huh.
Hey, Andrew. Long time.
- I haven't seen you
since you were voted
Most Likely to Turn Into A Lez
at graduation.
-What did you win again?
Most Likely to Die in Prison.
That was it.
-Free gift. With purchase.
It's for your little boy.
The hero kills everyone
messing with their family.
Back off my family
or there's going to be
one more dead Cypress.
What do you think?
-Oh, it's good, it's good.
-I know.
I know, it's great, isn't it?
-Your son attacked a boy.
I have no choice
but to suspend him
for the rest of the week.
-What happened?
Why did you attack Noah?
-He was going to hurt Jordan
to see if she would heal
because she's a reviver.
-Excuse me,
but where the hell were you?
Kids have the right
to be safe at school.
It's your job to
make sure that happens.
-You want to talk about safe?
When nobody, not the mayor,
not those CDC scientists,
not even your own father
can convince people
that they're safe
from these revivers.
People are scared
out of their damn trees.
-Oh, oh. Of who?
Of this little, tiny,
little adorable girl?
You can call me
when she starts pulling out
her own teeth,
but until then calm your tits.
-Dana, I am doing my best.
-Your best sucks. Okay?
Come on, Coop.
-What about Jordan?
-Called her parents
an hour ago.
- ...from there.
- People will talk!
But you don't
want her here, right?
Well, don't put this
all on me!
You feel the same way .
Now, come on!
- It's okay.
- They do that a lot.
Want to go play in my room?
-Yeah.
We're not bad people, Dana.
I never said you were.
-We struggled mightily
to have a child.
Scans, tests, procedures.
Doctor said it was
never going to happen for us.
-But we prayed and we prayed
and then, like a miracle
sent from God, she came.
I knew every hair on her head,
every sigh when she slept.
-You're talking about her
like she's dead,
but she's very much alive.
And she needs you now,
more than ever.
-That is not our daughter
up there.
-Can we have some cookies?
-Mm-hm.
Thanks.
-She came back wrong.
And we've prayed over it,
but our Jordan,
the one God sent us,
is dead.
-I think you've had it
too good.
Because if your daughter
had been sick, or troubled...
and you lived every day knowing
that you might lose her
and then you did.
And then, by some miracle,
she came back.
You'd fall to your knees
and weep with joy
instead of
crying over what you'd lost.
And, okay, she might not be
what you wish she was,
but she's, she's worth--
- She's worth loving.
I-I...
I hope you can
find your way to do that.
Please leave your message.
-Hi, Em. It's, uh... It's me.
I, I just
wanted to say
I'm thinking about you and...
I really hope you're okay
and please call me back.
-Can we go for milkshakes?
-Milkshakes? Um...
I'm going to drop you off
at Nella's for a bit.
I have has some stuff
to check out for work, okay?
Go sit.
Riparian Zone.
Nine Mile Forest.
No anomalies
in the local flora or fauna.
Mineral composition of water
and soil samples are normal.
Compounds are unremarkable.
Still no viable hypothesis
on the cause of Revival Day.
-Finally got the toxicology
on our reviver brain specimen.
-She is a person.
Please use her name.
-She used to be a person.
Now she is a reviver
who killed her own daughter
and is still at large.
Hello. You look lovely.
-Thank you
-And I have a hypothesis
about Arlene's psychosis
and I'd love to request
a police escort so that I can go
to the Dittman house
and investigate
my theory further.
-Oh, wow.
-Yeah.
-Okey-dokey, Doc.
-Okay.
-Yeah, the only small problemo
is that, um,
well, with everyone out
searching for Arlene,
it's kind of slim pickings
right now.
-Oh.
-Yeah. I could probably get you
McCray right there.
-Oh, well, what about Dana?
-What about Dana?
-Well--
-You'd prefer her company,
would you, mm-hm?
-No, I just saw
that her car was outside,
so I figured
that she was available
and that I--
-You get me.
-Oh.
-I'll be your escort.
-It's great.
Okay. Okay.
You're on a well system,
correct?
-Wayne, tell Dr. Ramin
that whatever's he's looking for
he's not going to find it here.
-Can I, uh,
check out your bathroom?
Uh, yeah.
-Hey, Bob, why don't we
let the doctor do his work?
Why don't you get me
a cup of coffee, huh?
I'll get the grounds
out of your other freezer.
-Oh. Oh.
-What the hell
do you think you're doing?
-Ah!
Um, hey, I just, um,
I was admiring
the beautiful bay horse.
It's such a,
such a beautiful coat, sir.
-She was my prize horse.
'Til my reviver
bitch mother-in-law killed her
with her bare hands.
-Hey, Bob. Whoa, whoa!
Whoa, whoa!
Calm down, all right?
Let's, uh, let's try to
keep it together, shall we?
Okay, I know you're
burying your wife today,
but, uh, we don't want
to add to the body count.
-He was snooping.
-The CDC has jurisdiction
in Wausau, so...
You best be fixing that,
Wayne.
Unless you want to be
out on your ass next election.
-You almost done here, Doc?
-Yeah.
-Good. Let's, uh,
let's get back to
that coffee, huh, Bob.
Let's go back into
the kitchen, Bob.
You, uh,
you got any other weapons
that I don't know about?
-Oh, da, shit.
Oh, shit.
Shoot. Oh.
Oh, shh...
-Hey, uh, sorry,
I didn't want to wake you.
You seemed like
you really needed the rest.
-Uh, it's been a while
since I've slept.
-I don't sleep much.
The darkness weirds me out.
Kind of feels like
I'm reliving my death.
-Um...
How'd you die if you, uh,
don't mind me asking.
-Did you hear about the guy
that jumped into Sunny Vale Lake
and didn't make it but
still rescued that little girl?
-Holy shit. That was you?
-Yeah.
-Wow.
Nah.
That's the story I want to tell.
The truth is...
I stabbed myself
through the palm
while coring an avocado
and because I was too punk
to go to the doctor
it got infected and killed me.
-Oh ho. Ew.
-This is supposed to be
a safe space!
-I'm sorry, it's just
for someone so cool,
to have died in such a lame way.
Seven days of antibiotics
and I would've been fine,
but instead.
-Oh-ho!
-Yeah.
Okay, quick,
tell me how you died
and make it sound as dumb
as possible!
You don't have to.
-(whispers) Uh...
My sister and my ex
think I, uh...
think I did it to myself.
I don't think I did, but...
I was on the bridge and I was...
high.
And I woke up in Bull Falls,
so...
What if I did? What if...
What if I did jump?
-Lots of people jump
for lots of reasons.
It doesn't make you weak,
or selfish, or a bad person.
-Wait, your...
You got your avocado wound
before you died.
If I had jumped,
all my bones would have broken
before I drowned,
or whatever happened to me.
But when I woke up,
my bones weren't broken.
-So you didn't fall.
-And I didn't jump.
-Okay. Um...
What else do you remember
about that night?
-You know,
you don't have to do this
and, besides,
don't you have, like,
a band rehearsal
to get ready for?
-I have time. We, we have time.
I want to help you with this.
Help you figure out
what happened.
If that's something you want.
What do all these mean?
-I don't know.
Some are fuzzy,
some are clear.
I-I...
I-I-I close my eyes
and really try to focus,
but then they just drift away
and I don't even know
if they're all from the same
place.
What I do know
is I was on the bridge
and something bad happened.
-Terry was
a true-to-life angel.
She even took in
her sick mother,
even when it was a burden
on our marriage.
Even when it made her unable
to take care of my needs,
like a wife ought to.
My Terry
put so much light in the world.
- Terry.
- She was a God-fearing woman
who loved her family,
her friends
and her dear horse, Sebastian.
She didn't deserve to
be taken away from me like that.
-Everybody out!
Arlene, stop!
-...my life.
-Bob!
- Devil woman.
- Get out of the way!
Bob! Get down!
Blaine?
What the hell are you doing?
- They carry our prayers...
- Blaine!
-...up to God's throne...
-Stop there!
-...and lay hands on the beast.
And through my anointed hand
I condemn you.
Oh, my Terry.
-There, in the lake of fire
by your holy soldier, oh, Lord.
Terry.
-It's going to take us a while
to separate the bodies,
but we will make sure
that Arlene's body
is held in a secure room.
-Why? You think she's
going to recover from this?
I thought she was
burned to a crisp?
-Cremains
are already healing, sir.
Slowly, but nonetheless.
-I knew it was
too good to be true.
-Jesus!
Where's Dr. Ramin?
-He said he had
an errand to run this morning.
-Blaine Abel's in lockup.
What are we charging him with?
-Public endangerment
for lighting a fire
but it's not going to stick.
-You got to keep that guy
locked up
as a matter of public safety.
You hear what he's saying
on his radio show?
-Yeah. That he was protecting
the public from Arlene.
That's what he
and everybody else will say.
And, you know, he's not wrong.
He did stop her. I couldn't.
Sheriff's office.
You've got a big gosh-darn mess
and no plans to clean it up.
-With all due respect,
Governor,
the reason I called you
is because there is a plan.
My plan. But I cannot execute it
because I'm being drowned
in red tape
by the CDC and the mayor.
-Oh, going over my head now,
Wayne.
It's a new low for you.
Governor, I think
we can all agree that
stripping the rights
of our citizens is simply not--
-What, not what?
For a violent zombie invasion?
No, that's not
the right thing to do, is it?
-Jesus Christ, Wayne!
-Language!
-I am barely holding back
an angry mob of zealots
screaming for vigilante justice.
I need support.
-Yes? Come in.
-Ah, Governor. Sheriff.
Uh, I'm, uh, Dr. Ibrahim Ramin.
I, uh, found traces of mercury
in Arlene Stankiewicz's
brain matter.
At first I thought
it was from the drinking water
at the Dittman home,
but then I found this.
I believe that after Arlene
moved into the homestead,
Mr. Dittman began poisoning her
with mercuric chloride,
which triggered her psychosis
and, uh, her violent events.
-He got fed up with Terry
taking care of Arlene over him
so he killed his own
mother-in-law?
-When did you
come up with this, anyway,
'cause I was with you
at the Dittman house.
My first time hearing it.
-I'm simply trying to prove
my hypothesis, Governor,
that revivers
aren't inherently violent.
-You got any real science
behind that, Doctor?
Because all I'm hearing
are half-baked theories
and wild accusations
against a man
who can no longer
defend himself.
-Oh, you're so hell-bent
on your camp
you can't even see the truth!
-This camp can't happen.
It can't happen, Governor.
These are people.
They need to be protected.
-We cut the top of her head
off,
we baked her to a crisp
and she's still kicking!
That sound like a person to you?
-Name one time in human history
where camps have been better
instead of horrifically worse.
-All right, all right.
Sit down.
Golly, I am choking on
all the testosterone in here.
Sheriff, considering she wasn't
even on your
little reviver registry,
sounds to me like
you've got a tracking problem.
So how about we start there?
Figure out who really is
and isn't a dead citizen.
Or whatever.
Go door-to-door if you have to.
but you've the authority
to smoke out
every reviver in Wausau
so we can tag and monitor them
and avoid ourselves
another Arlene situation.
-Uh, so we're marking them now?
I'm sorry.
Are we serious about this?
-Governor, no, you can't--
-Tag 'em and track 'em.
It works during Shark Week
and it'll work here.
And to your point, Sheriff,
if any revivers show
signs of aggression or violence,
you have my authority to
remove them to a secure location
of your choosing.
-Oh, wow.
You just legalized
internment camps, Governor.
-I wouldn't use that term.
But big, bold moves
will settle tempers and fears
in this town.
Once people are feeling
safe again
and we have no more
violent outbursts,
we can talk about
lifting measures.
Gentlemen.
Okay.
You happy now, Wayne?
Locking up the citizens
you're supposed to protect.
-Nella, thank you so much
for watching Cooper.
-Ah, you're welcome.
I like the company
before we open.
-What the hell happened here
with Em?
-Your sister seemed fine.
And then, all of a sudden,
she started headbutting Clarice.
-Well, the top of the head
is the hardest bone in the body,
so it's kind of her only move.
Did she come here with anyone,
or talk to anyone
while she was here?
No, no. She was alone.
I mean, she seemed
a little down in the dumps,
but nothing out of the ordinary.
Before I knew it,
Em had hightailed it
out of here.
-By herself?
-Uh, she left with some punk.
-Do you mean
like a shitty dude?
-No, I mean a literal punk.
I think he was in a band.
-Goddamn it!
Told her, no musicians.
-Maybe it's genetic.
I hope not.
Em!
-Cool. Cool look.
-Oh, thanks.
You okay?
-Yeah, I've just never been to
something like this before.
-A punk show?
-No concerts, no clubs.
I've had to avoid any situation
where I could break an arm,
or something.
-Well, you're different now.
Billy Idol once said
punk never dies
and you literally can't, so...
-And with all these
stupid games we play
and all the rules
we need to play them
I forged a blade
for those very rules
And another one to slay them
So keep on talking
with your crooked smile
and your pathetic
search for worth
'Cause in the desert
of my discontent
There's a river of blood
Stop it, clench your fist
The bloodthirsty
bloodthirsty vultures
form circles around my grave
-Holy shit.
Look at what we got here.
-Stop.
Hey, that guy's
messing with my girl!
Get him off her!
Adam, get her!
- Em!
- Move!
- Em, come on.
- Hey, Adam!
-You're a dead woman,
Em Cypress!
-Dana?
-Stop! Police!
-Get out back.
-Okay.
No. No, no, no.
Get off.
Surprise, surprise.
Up we go.
-You're going to regret this,
Cypress.
-I've read your brother's
rap sheet.
This is his third strike.
Looks like he's most likely
to die in prison.
Come on.
You want to join him?
-Do you think
those are the guys who...?
Killed me?
-We are in the middle of
the road.
We should probably...
- Yeah. Yeah.
-You just signed
your own ticket, lady.
I know my rights.
You can't tase me without cause.
You can't search me
without a warrant.
-You verbally threatened
a concert-goer.
And when I searched you
I was looking for weapons
for my own safety.
And it's just dumb luck
that I found a boatload of drugs
that'll keep you in prison
for 25-to-life,
so tell me again
whose ticket got signed?
-My brother's not
going to stand for this!
-Good.
It's what I'm counting on.
Oh!
Hey!
You can't search my phone
without a warrant.
-I don't care
what's on your phone.
Want you to call your brother.
Why don't you call him?
And put it on speakerphone
while you're at it
'cause I'm really gonna enjoy
listening to Andrew
tell you
and your whole stupid family
how dead meat you are.
-You're not calling Andrew.
You're calling Anthony.
Big brother Anthony.
The brains of the operation.
Right?
'Cause if you and Andrew
are going to start a war
with my family you're
going to need his approval.
So, there you go.
Uh, I'm not calling Tony.
He's busy.
In New York.
-Is that it? Or is it
because you're scared?
'Cause he's going to lose
his mind when he finds out
you've been arrested.
My guess is that
he told you two losers
to lay low
while he was stuck
outside the quarantine zone
and, well, here we are.
You call Anthony
and maybe
all of this goes away.
What do you mean?
-No, no. I'm willing to
make a deal with Anthony.
Not with you.
Come on.
Don't forget
to put it on speaker.
- What do you want, grunt?
- Anthony,
This is Deputy Dana Cypress,
Mountain Bay County
Sheriff's Department.
I am here with Adam.
Your brother has two
felony convictions
already on his record
and I just got him on a third.
I can't help but think
of your poor mother.
But I am willing
to release Adam.
Without charges.
I'm willing to give you back
the oxy my sister stole.
But I want a truce.
The Checks stay away from
the Cypresses
and vice versa.
Squid pro quo.
-Take the deal, bro. Come on.
-Anthony, you have no leverage.
I have your brother,
I know your operation
and I know you killed my sister,
you dirty shits!
-Wait.
Your sister's a reviver?
-Oh, you didn't know?
-Of course I didn't know!
-Bullshit. You and your
dirty brothers killed her.
-We didn't even know
who she was before tonight.
-At your house,
your brother said
there is going to be
more than one dead Cypress!
-Um, he was probably talking
about your mom
'cause she died
in that car crash, or whatever.
He's an asshole like that!
- Enough!
I'll take the deal.
Cut Adam loose.
-Tell me my family's safe.
-Stay out of our business,
then no brother
or associate of mine will move
against your family.
-I want your word.
-Cross my heart
and hope to die.
-Come on.
Huh.
-Coop, I'm home.
-Did you lock up
all the bad guys?
-Yeah, I sure did, buddy.
Is this romantic?
Shit, sorry,
do I need to be careful
hugging you, or...
-I'm not that fragile.
I just didn't get
a lot of hugs growing up.
I still got a lot of love
growing up it's just...
with this condition,
everyone looked at me different.
Kind of treated me
like something waiting to break.
Or like they were scared
to touch me.
-That must have been tough.
-It is. It-- It was. Um...
luckily, as I'm getting older,
it's getting better
and the fractures
and breaks happen
a lot less frequently, but,
as a kid, that was different.
-Just because you broke a lot,
doesn't mean you're broken.
-Well, I broke. A lot.
-Mm-hm.
-This is from my
fourth rodding surgery.
They couldn't fix the fracture
so they had to put a plate
in my shin.
Oh.
-I've got pins and screws
and plates all over my body.
Touch it if you want.
It's gross.
Ew. (mock disgust)
-Bet it's a nightmare
at airport security.
- I wouldn't know.
-You've never been on a plane?
-If only we could
fly somewhere right now.
-As soon as
we can get out of here
I'll take you
wherever you want to go.
-I've never been to the beach.
Can we go to the beach,
or is that lame?
-That's really lame.
I'm kidding.
It can't be lame if you've...
It can't be lame if
you've experienced something
that 99.9%
of the rest of the world
will never get to.
-Dying and coming back to life.
-And healing.
That feeling when
your flesh and bones break.
-And regenerate at warp speed.
-It's like lightning
rippling through my entire body.
-The irony is,
at least for me, is that...
I had to die to feel alive.
-Will you do something with me?
What?
You want to jump?
Are you crazy? No!
-Live a little.
Rhodey?
Rhodey?!
Rhodey!!
Whoo! (joyous)
Feels amazing!
You gotta try it, Em! Come on!
Jump! I got you!
Come on! I believe in you!
-Just live a little.
-Stand up. Come on.
You're free to go, Mr. Abel.
Just, uh, know
I'll be watching you.
-Okay.
Hey, you know that you and I
want the same thing, right?
You'll discover that eventually.
-You and I, Blaine,
will never want the same thing.
-Might want to think
about that.
Gentlemen.
Oh. I appreciate
you all coming here.
So...
who's ready for a holy war?
Yeah!!
-Yeah.