KEN: Previously on Revival.
If any revivers show signs
of aggression or violence,
remove them to a secure
location of your choosing.
Your sister's a reviver?
I want a truce.
Tell me my family is safe.
-Cross my heart, hope to die.
You've been running ever since
you fumbled the Blackdeer case.
Did you hear it?
There's something out there.
Whoever shot him shot you.
I even fired back at them.
Lester saw the
shooter. It's a cop.
We found the bullet
that killed Aaron.
And your gun wasn't a match.
You'll never believe whose was.
McCray?
Oh, she's beautiful.
Hey. Say hello to your sister.
-What?
-What's wrong?
What's wrong?
-Why isn't she crying?
Why isn't she crying?
Oh, dude. What a day.
What a night. Jesus.
They got her hooked up
to all these machines.
Now she's in some
incubator thing.
I mean, it's crazy. She's
so tiny, so fragile.
Well, you knew
after Patty's cancer
there was a chance of this.
Complications, underdevelopment.
That was the risk.
But did we really
have to go through
all this hokey crystal,
water-birth bullshit?
I mean, come on! On top of that?
We should've been in the city
at a hospital! This is crazy!
She's all about the nature.
You can't move her off it.
She thinks water's
so goddamn special.
Well, you fell in love
with that flower child.
Hey, just be grateful that
she's okay and that Dana's okay.
Whatever happens
is in God's hands.
Oh, this is for you and Patty.
Thanks, brother. Thank
you for everything.
It's not useless, sweetheart.
You're going to use it someday.
Hey, Doc. How is she?
Oh.
-Hi.
-Be careful.
We need to do some
further tests,
but she's showing signs
of early onset OI.
There.
OI?
What does that mean?
We'll talk more, but
she's very fragile
and likely always will be.
Can I hold her?
Just be extra gentle.
Hold her head.
Yeah, you got her. There
you go. There you go.
You're going to have
to help take care of
your little sister, okay?
She's going to need you.
- Is something wrong with her?
- - No.
Hon, she's perfect.
She's very special.
All right, we don't
got a lot of time.
We gotta flush the stash.
Whoa? Throw Tommy
in the river?
Not literally, numb-nuts.
Now that the cops got McCray,
it's only a matter of time
before they find this place
and everything we
worked for, up in smoke.
But we got a moment
right now, today,
to finally put some
respect on the Check name.
What do we gotta do?
We move the supply.
Today. Right now.
Get them over the
border, out of Wausau.
We set up out east working
for the boss himself.
We need to accelerate
expansion plans.
We need another one.
A female.
Jesus H. Christ,
man. From where?
How the hell we gonna get past
the border without McCray?
We're just gonna bulldoze it
with some reviver chick in tow?
No. No, no, no.
This is why I got the
brains in the family.
You listen to your
older brother.
We're going to kill two
birdies with one stone.
Oh! Oh, I'm sorry.
What the hell's wrong with you
sneaking up on me like that?
Didn't mean to scare you.
I just, you got a visitor.
What the hell?
What's wrong with you? What
if she's my actual killer?
You're not dead.
Starting to wish I was
now that you're here.
Wait. Are these my
Blackdeer files?
Did you steal police property?
You trying to get arrested?
That's all I have. And
I'll be quick, okay?
Do you mind just
giving us some privacy?
Oh, yeah. Excuse me. Yeah.
-No! Brent!
-Yeah?
Stay. I don't trust
her. You kidding?
Okay. Yeah. Yeah. I'll stay.
How did you get these?
What's important
is what's in them.
I know what's in them.
They're my files.
What is happening?
I think the reason
that you were shot is
because you were getting
too close to the truth
about Jesse and about...
I think
you're getting too
close to my face
and it's making me
deeply uncomfortable.
Dana, this is all tied
together. You being shot.
Aaron. The Blackdeer case.
You think McCray had something
to do with the Blackdeer case?
No, I don't think he shot
you. I think he was set up.
There it is! She
thinks he was set up!
-Oh.
-There it is.
Corruption on the police
force, tonight at seven.
Extra, extra!
The rot goes right to the...
The core of the...
Am I the corrupt cop?
-Uh-oh.
-Maybe I shot myself,
and then Aaron.
And then I pinned it
on another corrupt cop.
Oh, bang, bang.
Hard to wrap your head
around why'd you do that.
To cover up for
the Blackdeer case
everyone thinks I
botched two years ago
because I want
everybody off my back!
I just want you to
look at one thing.
No!
Get out of here!
-Okay.
-Yeah, she wants you...
so I think you've
overstayed, even.
My notes are in those files.
Just read them. Please.
Okay. Let's...
No touching.
There you are.
Oh, we got a good
group going here.
Roses, of course.
-Mm-hm.
Classic. But then... boom!
Lilies, all pink and yellow
like a sunset just exploded.
And then we've got
some snapdragons,
those funky ones that look
like little mouths, right?
Oh, and we can't
forget the daisies.
No, don't forget the daisies.
Oh, wait. Do you have any
enhanced mineral flower food?
Do we have any mineral
enhanced flower food?
No, we have none.
Oh! Now, Dana, what
in heavens' name
are you doing with
these other flowers?
They'll wilt, just
like our bodies,
if you don't take care of them.
-You now what?
You should go and
get some immediately
so that nothing wilts.
Yes. Right on it.
Lester.
No. No! No!
What the hell is
wrong with you people?
You all need to stop bringing
in candy and doughnuts!
She's been shot in the
stomach for Christ's sakes.
Sorry.
I'm retiring after this.
Wow. I tried.
-Thank you.
-Uh,
got the stuff you asked for.
How you holding up?
I've been better, but
then they come around
with the 'pterodactyl'
shots and I feel
great. I feel pretty good.
What's up with you?
I, uh, well, you know. Hm.
Seeing you like
this, it's, uh...
You know, it's...
especially, guy was
on my watch, you know?
I mean, you never liked McCray.
And now JP tells me he's
likely working with the Checks.
How'd I not see that?
Don't worry about
it. I don't think
the Checks are a part of this.
I mean, you know those assholes.
If they wanted me dead
they'd knock on my door
and shoot me in the face.
What about the professor?
How's he fit into all
this? He was texting you?
Yeah. I think he had
something to confess
and I just got there too late.
Wrong place, wrong time.
Confess what?
Um, oh, I'm not sure, but I
fired back at the shooter.
I got him in the right arm.
Did McCray have a wound there?
No.
Well, then, it's not him.
He must have been framed.
Well, when we got that
idiot at the checkpoint
he had a trunk full
of reviver parts.
Ugh, Jesus.
Well, he may be an idiot, but
he's an opportunistic one.
Hell, if I was going to
frame someone it'd be him.
You were right to
want out of here.
Town's been holding you back.
What? Dad.
When this is over
and you're, uh,
feeling better, huh?
You want a letter of
recommendation, you got it.
Anything!
Anything you need, I'm not
going to hold you back.
Okay?
I know. I'll take care of it.
Okay? Just...
I bet you I can figure it out.
I'm not the one who's yelling!
You're the one
who's yelling at me!
You're... Oh, nice. Nice.
Bunch of fricking
totally mean...
But... Ow!
Yes!
Oh, yeah.
-Oh, no!
-Oh my God.
Maybe I'll actually
beat you this time.
Thank you.
Ooh.
Okay, go.
Seven. One, two,
three, four, five.
I didn't shoot Dana.
And I sure as shit didn't
shoot that yuppie professor.
I'm a patsy.
What about those reviver
parts in the trunk?
You innocent of that, too?
Where did those come from?
No, no, no, no, no.
I took a criminal justice
class at night school.
I know my rights.
And if some undead freak
wants to sell his body parts
to make a buck around
town to some rich freak,
it's all more the good on them.
I am but a meagre middleman.
Transport. Nothing more.
Who paid you to move them?
You don't pay me
enough to answer that.
I made more last week
than I did all goddamn
last year with you.
I quit!
Gonna go find me a Lambo.
It's not him.
Anything new on the reviver
parts from his trunk?
Well, no match on the DNA,
but it's someone young.
In their 20s, they think.
Yeah.
Not a lot of young
revivers that I'm aware of.
There's one. Well...
you should see something.
I'm so out of touch
with this generation.
I know that kid.
He's dating Martha.
Mr. Cypress.
Please, come on, man.
Hey, listen, Mr. Cypress,
I really don't know anything
about any reviver parts.
-Shut up.
-I swear to...
What is this place?
Welcome to Riverside.
Are you sure?
-Yes!
-Okay.
Get out of here!
Can't you see I don't
want them anymore?!
Take them back where
they came from!
Go!
You hurt yourself.
You were joking?
It was the ending from
Harry and the Hendersons.
John Lithgow has to
be super mean to Harry
'cause he wants to
get him to leave,
but he really doesn't
want him to leave.
I've never seen that.
It's funny 'cause I'm
saying it about doughnuts,
but he was saying
it about Harry.
It's okay.
Okay. I'll see...
-Hey.
-Yeah?
Can you do me a solid
and swing by my house?
Sure. Yeah. Why?
Just check on Em and Cooper.
I tried calling.
I'm sure they're just
playing video games, but...
Okay. Got it.
Thank you.
Take the doughnuts. All right?
-You should watch that movie.
-All right, I will.
I busted a stitch to
try to do that for you.
All right. See you.
-Okay.
Hey! Let me out!
Wait! You can't do this!
Hey!
What the hell is going on?
You can't keep me here!
Shit!
Ain't nothing you can do.
Hello?
Hey. What...
Could you... What's
going on here? Wh-wh...
I'm Rhodey. What's your name?
You ain't no Rhodey.
That shit's gone.
You're whoever they
want you to be now.
But I didn't do anything!
You think that matters?
I served my time. I
paid my debt to society.
Look where it got me, Rhodey.
It's a unilateral decision.
I had more rights as a...
criminal than I do as a reviver.
That's for damn sure.
Hello?
Is anybody in here?
Em? Jordan?
Cooper?
Hey. They okay?
No one's here, Dana, and
the place has been ravaged.
What?
-It's, uh...
It's scary, Dana.
Something's really wrong.
Tell me everything
you see. Describe it.
Uh, yeah.
Hold on, hold on. It's, uh...
There's something on the wall.
What?
There's a...
there's a comic on the wall
with a knife through it.
It's, uh...
There's a girl on
the cover. It says...
It says Hack/Slash.
The Check Brothers
took them. Oh, no.
Dana? Hello?
Okay, no. Seriously?
You need to get back into bed...
I NEED SOMEBODY
IN HERE NOW! Okay.
-Please, they just left...
-Yeah, no.
-No! NO!!
-Thank you.
-NO! NO! They got my family.
-Okay. Sure.
-Sure.
-NO!!
Yep. We'll get you going.
We'll get you going real soon.
There we go.
Th!
Living the dream, are we?
What's that, Tommy?
Do you need a hand?
Nah, he needs two.
I'm sorry.
I can't understand you.
Could you speak more clearly?
Cooper.
Oh, the scrawny kid?
Oh.
The way you shivered when I
put that knife to his throat.
You have nothing to worry
about. He's not going anywhere.
He's only here to keep
you Cypresses in line.
I'm not a savage.
Although that
little reviver girl?
Yeah, she's what they
call collateral damage.
All right. Let's get a move on.
Get her cleaned up
and presentable.
You're going to be
the pretty little face
of our boss's new franchise.
Pull the trucks around.
Oh, oh. You're okay. Relax.
-The Checks, they took them.
-No, we know.
Ibrahim told us.
Dana, why would they
be coming for you?
I don't know. I mean,
we crossed paths, but...
...we made a deal.
You made a deal with
the Check Brothers?
Anthony, actually.
-Oh.
-Shit.
Dana.
Well, that's just super.
What the devil happened?
Wait. Where's my
dad? Does he know?
Where's the hideout, McCray?
Huh?
Okay, I... You
don't understand.
No! You don't understand.
Where is my daughter
and my grandson?
What?! Your family?
I have no idea what
you're talking about, man.
Ah!
No?
What are you going to do?
Shoot me in your own station?
-I don't know! Let's find out.
-Ah!
Where would they keep them?
-Okay, okay, okay.
I know I've done a lot
of bad shit in my life,
but I never laid a
hand on Dana! Okay?
Or your other daughter
or your grandson.
I swear on my pappie's life.
And if it's about the brothers,
then I don't want
anything to do with that.
Why are you so
afraid of the Checks?
It's not them I'm afraid
of! It's who they work for.
-Who do they work for?
-Oh, come on, man!
You might as well just
kill me now! Okay?
Because they're going
to go after my family
and my dog, Newman, and that's
what they're going to do
if I help you out. So, go
ahead, just kill me now.
I'm sorry about your family,
but I gotta protect mine.
Cross my heart and hope to...
-Anthony Check,
I will light up your mother
like a Christmas tree
if you do anything to my family.
Well, it's,
it's good to see that even
stuck bleeding in a hospital bed
you still got your spunk.
We had a deal. What changed?
You're a cop. I'm
a known criminal.
Are you really that surprised?
How do I know my family's safe?
That's fair. Uno momento.
Mom!
It's okay. I'm okay.
Cooper! Cooper,
it's okay, buddy.
Can you just stay on
the phone with Mom?
Your pa's arrest of McCray
has complicated our plans.
All right? My very
unscrupulous boss
has a list of high profile
clients that need their...
Well, fix.
We are in need of an insider
to get our supply
across the border.
You're selling reviver parts?
We're in the midst
of a recession, lady.
Banks are closing. Ma
can't make her payments.
Houses are gone.
My brother's dream
of having a 401k... dashed.
And then Revival Day
gifted us with a second chance.
The Checks are now
the proud proprietors
of a very lucrative
business operation.
I'm not going to let
that go to waste.
Keep your fff...
hands off my sister!
Well, she stole from my family.
I figure it's only fair
I steal from yours.
It's funny. This
is all your doing.
We didn't even know
that tasty teen treat
was a reviver until you told us.
Now the powers that
be have requested
your little sister
and you're the one
that's going to make
sure she gets there.
Oh, you redneck piece of shit.
Sweet cheeks,
I will carve your little boy
up into a 1,000 little pieces.
Just give me a reason.
Or, you do as you're told
and you get your boy back
safe and sound. Tonight.
He might need a
little bit of therapy,
but I saw worse
when I was his age
and look how I turned out.
There's no way to
sugarcoat this part.
Your sister's gone.
But your little
boy you could save.
It's your choice.
I'll take your silence
as compliance.
I'd write this
down, if I were you.
Boomer, give pen.
-First truck...
will be at the Eastern
Checkpoint at 4:35.
Second truck, Southern
Checkpoint at 4:45.
Licence plates are RJM
1-9-9-0 and VRD 7-4...
4-6.
My men will call me once they're
safely across the border.
And listen up: if I
get so much as a whiff
of your boys in blue,
or my men don't make
that phone call,
every last Cypress alive gets
thrown into a wood chipper.
You get it?
Cypress trees? Wood chipper?
All jokes aside, I'm
serious as your ma's cancer.
Tell me you understand.
Understand.
-Great!
Toodles!
Pull the car around.
They've taken Em.
Oh, uh, all right. I thought
they already took her?
-PULL THE CAR AROUND! NOW!
-Okay. Yeah. Ow. Yeah.
NURSE! I NEED A 'PTERODACTYL!'
-Okay, sweetheart.
-NURSE!
Let's get you back into bed.
I need the
'pterodactyl' shot now.
-We can't just give you...
-Nurse!
-...a Toradol shot.
-Please?! Please.
Please, it's police business.
My family's in danger. Please.
-Okay. Okay. Okay.
-Thank you.
Dana. Hey.
-Dad, where are you?
-I'm at the police station.
What's going on?
-Okay, good. You're close.
Dad, I need you to head
to the Eastern Checkpoint.
Why?
-Brent and I are headed
to the Southern Checkpoint.
Dad, there are two trucks.
Em is on one of them.
Dana, what the hell is going on?
Call me when you
get to the border.
The driver will know
where they came from
and get you a location and
then we have to call Anthony.
Slow down.
Please.
Dad, this is for Cooper and Em.
I need you to trust me.
I'll explain everything
later. There's no time now.
Just trust me. Please.
Okay.
I'm heading to the
Eastern Checkpoint.
-Got it.
-Okay.
Hit me. Hit me.
All right.
And here we go...
Oh, that's the shit.
Okay.
Thank you.
Yeah, okay. Okay, whoa, whoa.
Good to go.
Oh.
Uh...
Well
Shit.
Why would you shoot...?
Buddy, come on.
Who put you up to this?
You don't have to do this.
For once in your goddamn life
shut that trap of yours.
♪ Never surrender ♪
This has to happen, Dana.
Nothing you can do, so...
On the bed.
-What?
-I'M SERIOUS DANA. ON THE BED!
I'M NOT MUCKING AROUND.
WHAT THE FUCK?
All right.
Ah! Don't throw piss on me!
Now get on the bed!
Gotta shut you up.
Okay, Dana, say goodnight.
♪ When they try... ♪
♪ ...to break you down ♪
Ah!
♪ That don't shake you ♪
♪ When your back's
against the wall ♪
♪ The thrill of the fight's
got ya standin' tall ♪
Where are you going?
♪ Never surrender ♪
♪ The will to survive ♪
Why...
...won't you just die, Dana?
I have the vehicle
in my sights. Licence
plate VRD 7-4-4-6.
Blue truck. Engaging now.
Officer requiring
assistance on Route 51.
Blue transport vehicle...
Iicence plate VRD 7-4-4-6.
OFFICER: Five minutes from
the Eastern Checkpoint.
Be on the lookout for
RJM 1-9-9-0, blue truck.
Get your hands up!
Get out of the truck.
Get to the back.
Open it.
Cuff yourself to the bar.
Em. Em, I'm here.
Em, I'm here.
Oh, God.
-Hey.
-Hey. You can't go past here.
What's going on here?
Where is Dana? Is she okay?
-Dana left.
-Dana left?
Where did you load this truck?
Nueces Street.
The old warehouse.
Call Anthony right now.
You tell him you made
it past the checkpoint.
Everything went really well.
Dana been shot. Why
would she just leave?
I'm not sure.
Who did this?
She did.
-What is going on here?
-Dad.
Em's not on this
truck. She's on yours.
What about a location on Cooper?
Yeah.
It's a refrigeration
warehouse. The Carbone.
Nueces. I'm on my way there now.
Be careful. Did you
hear about Brent?
Dad, Brent's dead! Brent's
the one who shot me.
What? Jesus!
Listen, you're on the
other side of town.
I'm closer. We gotta get there
before something happens
to Cooper and Jordan.
Damn it! Don't engage
until we arrive.
I'll head there once I get Em.
All units be advised:
Possible 1-3-4 at
Ninth and Nueces.
Proceed with caution.
Okay, Ninth, Ninth.
That's, uh, that's close.
Is that the Check
brothers' warehouse?
I think so.
Okay. Okay.
Dad, do you have her?
No! The truck's
still not here.
What do you mean? It
should be there by now.
Where the hell is it?
What is going on?
Check down there.
Adam, you okay, brother?
Adam?
Adam.
Ooh!
Ah!
Oh! Hey! Hey! Jordan.
Where's Dana and Cooper?
I don't know.
Okay, okay. Let's get
you out of here, okay?
Come on. Are you okay? You okay?
-Yeah.
Okay. I got you.
I got you, okay?
Come on. Let's get out of here.
Watch your step. All right.
Coop.
Cooper.
Mom, I'm here!
MOM!
Guns are so...
...messy.
Mom?
Look at me.
Look at me!
Never go against the family!
You get in. Get in.
You're okay. You're okay.
I can help. I'm a reviver.
No, no, no, no, no.
You're just a kid. Okay?
You stay here. You
stay safe, all right?
What about Cooper?
Okay, Coop. Uh...
Stay safe in here.
Stay in there.
-Hey, Coop. Hey, buddy.
-Auntie Em!
Hey, I need you to
listen to me, okay?
I need you to go
around that corner
and I need you to
get out of here
as soon as possible, okay?
Okay, buddy? Go, go,
go, go, please! Please.
Jordan, what are you doing?
It's okay.
It's for me.
Jordan!
Be careful!
Come on. Come on.
Dana, fight. Fight!
Please? Come on.
I need you to fight. Please!
You can't give
up! Please. Dana.
Thank you all for
being so kind to me.
You're going to be okay.
What's happening?
You're going to be
okay. I got you.