Previously on revival.
Are these my black deer
files? How did you get these?
The reason you were
shot is because you were
- getting too close to the truth.
- When she first became a cop
she was on the black deer case.
The guy that killed his daughter?
My gut says Aaron was
working with the person
who killed em, but Brent
was working for them.
Let's follow the evidence
instead of your gut.
Stop throwing the
black deer case in my face!
- Hi, Dana.
- Jesse black deer?
I think the real question is
why do we have the
same murder board?
Drinking it only gave
you temporary relief.
- Where's Ibrahim?
- Back at Moore creek.
I couldn't bring him with me.
- Why not?
- It wasn't up to me.
Martha is being hunted
and my soldiers will find her.
There's another way to draw her out.
Families intertwined
and so are our stories.
Whoever killed me and my
Rose, they killed you, too.
Come on, you actually know dad.
He's gonna freak out
even though it's literally
a 15-minute bus ride away.
Your father knows how
important college is to you.
I think if you just break it to him gently,
he won't overreact.
Much.
Well, it's more than college.
Mom, it's about getting out of the house.
I need this and I really don't want to
have to worry about dad
just showing up on campus
and dragging me out of the dorms
because something went wrong.
He just worries about you.
Do you worry about me?
No.
No, you're my little miracle, em.
You are the strongest,
most amazing person I know.
Dad, I'm working.
Can we talk about this later? Please?
Apparently you've had months
to tell me. There is no later.
I shouldn't have to
hear from your uncle Don
that you're leaving.
God, I can't believe uncle told on me.
How come you could tell
him about it, but not me?
I wanted to tell you,
but I knew this was going to happen.
- It's not a big deal.
- It is a big deal - to me.
Rose, after your mom,
you're all I got left.
That's not fair! This isn't about mom.
There's just nothing for me to do here.
This is about your mom, though.
If you leave, her land rights
go back to the government.
I know.
Uncle told me.
But maybe it's time to let that go.
Okay, mom doesn't live
through a stupid land contract.
What your mother left you isn't stupid!
- This is important! We need to...
- Dad!
Please, just go.
Okay, we'll talk about this later.
I promise.
I just wish he didn't
take it so personally.
I've always had to walk on eggshells
when it came to my mom.
He's never really gotten over it.
I don't really care
where we are, you know?
I mean, even this place is not that bad
'cause you're with me.
No, we're still going.
Sure.
But you want to give
your dad some time to, like,
cool down a bit. I mean,
there's no need to rush.
Tomorrow, I'm on the train to Chicago.
Okay, but what about all your stuff?
It's stuff.
We both loved that place.
Okay, it's perfect for us.
And if I don't go now and lock us in,
someone else is going
to come and rent it.
And that'll just give us
another reason not to do this.
And next thing you know, we'll be
stuck here until we're 50.
I just... I need to take this step.
You, me, a shitty cat.
In the windy city.
I can smell the smog and the deep dish.
Deal?
Deal.
You knew we always had a deal.
God.
Hey!
Rose?
Where you going?
Rose.
Hey, what are you doing way out here?
Just passing through.
Where you headed?
The train station. Chicago bound!
You want a lift?
Officer cypress?
I see her. Don't worry. Hey, Dana.
- Sir.
- Just wanna talk to her.
Hey, stop.
- What are you doing?
- No.
Why aren't you guys looking
for my daughter? Dana.
- It's okay.
- No, no, no. No. Okay.
Brent, let him go.
Stay outta my way.
Please.
It's been 72 hours. Three days!
I know. This is bad.
We've alerted the authorities in Chicago
and at her first stop in Milwaukee.
Big city cops don't
care about a missing girl.
Especially one off the reservation.
- No one ever cares.
- That's not true. I care.
Jesse, you know that,
right? I'm your friend.
I'm-i'm... I'm not giving up on this.
Okay? I promise.
Dana, I'm telling you,
something happened to her.
I just.
I just feel it.
And every day and
every minute we waste,
we're not going to find her.
Dana, please. Please.
I'm not giving up.
Don't tell my dentist.
How'd you get it unstuck
from the spinny thingy?
I just gave it a little...!
You know? Fell right out.
I got them hip movements
down from the, from the bowling.
Good tip.
Let me know if you
want a square of this?
You know, if I eat the whole thing,
you don't want to see that.
Did you talk to the manager?
Yeah.
Yeah, so, you know how the neighbour
heard yelling and a
tussle, you know, that night.
Well, turns out the night before
Jesse came to see her at work
and he was yelling
right in front of everyone
about her going away and,
turns out Rose did buy a
ticket to Chicago, but she,
she never got on the bus.
And that ticket?
Never scanned.
Shit.
Hey, Brent, meet me at
the bus shelter off stetton.
I think our missing person
case just became a homicide.
- Hey.
- Hey, Jesse.
We're going to need
to search the premises.
All right, yeah...
Take you to her trailer.
We need to search the whole house.
And I'm going to need
you to wait out here
with the deputy while we do.
Dana, what's going on?
I'm sorry, Jesse.
Dana, you might want to see this.
What am I looking at?
It's a land ownership contract.
It's in the safe back there.
It's Rose's.
Why are you showing this to me?
This says that Rose's
land ownership rights
revert if she establishes
permanent residency
outside tribal lands.
Yeah, right, that's why I'm
so adamant about her staying.
I don't want her to lose this.
Yeah, or maybe you
don't want to lose this?
If she leaves, the land rights
revert to the government,
not you.
What are you saying?
It's motive, Jesse.
Hey, there, elder Don
George. Do you have a second?
You find her yet?
No, no yet.
I was told Rose notified the council
of her intent to relocate.
Well, she came to see
me a couple weeks back.
Why do you think she
kept it from her father?
Why do we all keep secrets
from our family, deputy?
Jesse is a proud man.
Protective of his family and our ways.
Was it all protective?
Doesn't he stand to lose a lot
if the land ownership defaults?
Jesse only did what's best for Rose.
That much I know.
You're a parent, no?
What would you give up for your child?
No, don't talk like that, ma. Okay?
No, you're going to be all right.
Yeah.
No, I gotta go, though.
I'm at work. Bye now.
How is she?
She's,
she's holding up best
she can, you know?
But my, but my little brother, it's,
hitting him something fierce.
Little brother? He's your twin.
I'm at least a movie
lengths older than him, Dana,
so that's gotta count
for something, right?
He's, he's trying to
pitch in with medical bills
right now and it's,
you know, my salary here
doesn't make it any easier.
So, did you find anything in the letters?
The, the bear letters. Yeah. Yeah.
What does that mean?
Well, they're all addressed to
this individual named bear, so,
sort of taken to calling them that.
Who the hell is bear?
Jeez!
You want to tell me what the hell that is?
It's an endangered form of print media
known as a newspaper.
You told the wausau chronicle
that Jesse black deer
is no longer a suspect.
Yeah. He's not. He's still
just a person of interest.
I mean, there's no physical
evidence tying him to this.
Really?
He was the last person to see her alive
and they had a public altercation.
Now, we're trying to
make a case here, Dana,
and you contradicting yourself
week to week in the press
is not helping anyone, okay?
So, if it's not him, then
who the hell is the suspect?
Well, I'm looking into
this person called bear.
No one seems to know who they are,
but they had been writing these
long rambling letters to Rose
for years. Look at this.
And-and the last one
was about her leaving
and something about them
seeing each other one more time.
It could be, a love thing.
So your suspect is the pen pal?
Where is the evidence?
I'm investigating, but
dad, my gut is telling me.
Jesse's not our guy.
Right now, all he's guilty of
is fighting with his daughter.
Does that sound familiar?
Despite your gut, we're
doing another search
of the black deer property tomorrow.
No. Come on, we've put
him through enough, dad.
Talk to Brent. He'll
tell you the same thing.
I did talk to Brent, by the
way, who agreed with me.
He said another search couldn't hurt.
Or, more properly,
couldn't hurt a tick on a fly.
Whatever the hell that means.
This...
Mountain bay county
sheriff's department.
Officer.
Where were you on November 5th?
Okay. So much for pleasantries?
November 5th.
I believe I was travelling.
Yeah. You travel a lot, officer...?
- Cypress.
- Cypress?
No! Come on.
Answer the question, Abel. Thanks.
Like I said, I was travelling, you know?
Collecting new experiences,
new perspectives. Getting out of the
where were you travelling?
Myrtle beach.
All right? I like to get out
of here when it gets cold.
Do you have proof?
Well, yeah, I'm sure I've got a receipt
of the plane ticket somewhere,
but you know, more importantly,
what are you even doing
here 'cause I can chat all day,
but chatting with a cypress?
Not really my thing.
So when I look up this receipt,
do I search for Blaine or bear?
And why would you say that?
I'm not the only one, am I?
Rose black deer.
She gave you that necklace, right?
A bear claw for her bear.
What did you give her?
Rose is special to me.
I'll bet.
No, no, no. Don't you do that, okay?
It is nothing like that.
She's one of the only
people that actually sees me,
who cares what I have to say.
You are twice her age and
you expect me to believe
that all you cared about was her writing?
I respect her. It's not like that.
What's it like?
Dana, you there? Over.
One minute, Jeannie.
Sorry, Dana, but this is urgent.
They found something
at the black deer home.
You're going to want to see this.
Copy.
I'll be back. We'll talk again.
Yeah.
Anytime.
I don't know how that got in there.
Dana, you gotta believe me.
What the hell's going on?
It's over, Dana. Move on.
Dae... It's not good. It's Rose's shirt.
We'll take it for testing,
but, it was in the furnace.
Must've fallen down the side
when he, burned the body.
What? No! That doesn't make sense.
Brent, how-how could we
have missed something like that?
I'm sorry.
Hey.
I want a lawyer.
Jesse, I'm trying to help you.
Really? 'Cause this is
where your help's got me.
You want me in there?
- No. Absolutely not.
- Dana.
- Get out.
- I think I should, you know.
Brent, I got this.
I got this. I'll let you
know if I need help.
All right.
These are too tight. I'm so sorry.
This is how you treat a murderer.
- Let me see if I can...
- no, I don't want
- anything else from you.
- Jesse.
No.
I shouldn't have trusted
you in the first place.
This entire department
is rotten to its core
and you know it!
He was your friend! He trusted you!
Jesus. Okay. What? Is
there a question here?
Yeah. Was it your dad who
planted the evidence or you?
How desperate are you for a headline?
Question is how desperate
were all of you to close the case?
Just pin it on the native
man. No one will blink an eye.
Some things never change!
Let's get you in here.
He was taking him to county
and got jumped in the car.
Blackdeer?
He's on the run.
Shit.
What's the status on the
north quadrant search?
Negative on contact.
Shifting east into denser cover.
- Will advise if we spot any thin.
- Copy that.
No update yet on deputies
cypress and Rogers.
This is Rogers.
Dana has eyes on
black deer and is in pursuit.
Returning to her position now.
Jesse! Jesse! Stop!
Please! You know I didn't do this!
Jesse, get your hands up!
No. I'm not going with you.
Come on, don't do this.
You're going to have to shoot me.
Jesse!
My Rose is gone.
Let me go, too.
Thank you.
Dana!
You let him go?
Visual confirmed, but he evaded.
We lost him.
Pinsconsin pride.
12-year regional champions.
And we've been to nationals twice.
I've been the team
captain for seven years.
Seven years? Wow.
And what about the rest of your team?
I mean, have they
always been the same.
We've got, Doreen, Paulie,
zeb, Brent and myself.
And that would be deputy Brent?
Yeah. He's our top striker.
We would've won nothing without him.
I mean, honestly, we'd be
celebrating a seven-year run
if he hadn't missed the
championship two years ago.
Two years ago? Was that common?
I mean, did he ever
miss any other matches or
no. No. He is dedicated to the cause.
I mean, yeah, even when he was
sick as a dog that time he showed up.
And are the championships
the same time every year?
Yes, ma'am. Third week of November.
Bowlers' Christmas.
Third week of November. The only game
Brent ever missed
was on November 17th.
Which was one night
before he found Rose's shirt.
I don't follow.
He said he had food
poisoning and he had to sit out,
but this was the first and only time
he's ever done that.
This is the same guy who
won regionals the year prior
while running a fever of 102.
And Jesse's neighbours
said that they saw an officer
at 8 P.M. at the time, but
they didn't think anything of it.
But why didn't Jesse see them then?
It was a Thursday at around 8 P.M.
He was at the tribal meeting.
And he knew that.
He had one window of
opportunity to plant the evidence
and he took it.
He framed him.
I need to get to Jesse. Please.
See you later, Justin.
Goodnight.
Jesse black deer?
It's okay. You're okay.
You shouldn't be here.
Jesse, or I can call you
Justin, if that's preferred.
You're that wausau reporter.
Look, I ain't got nothing to say to you.
Please leave. Just leave me alone.
I'm not here for you. I'm here for Rose.
Here.
We were friends.
And you're right. I am a reporter.
But I'm not here for a
story. At least, not yet.
I've been looking into Rose's case.
I know you didn't do it.
And I know that two
years ago you were framed.
How'd you find me?
Uncle Don. He helped me.
I don't understand.
Why would he help you?
I was in love with your daughter, Jesse.
We were going to go
together to Chicago.
Do you know who took my Rose?
Not entirely, but I'm close.
Deputy Brent?
No. No, I'm not.
No applause needed.
I think he was involved.
I think that he planted
evidence in your house,
but I don't think he was
the one who took Rose.
Look, his mother was ill.
They had medical bills piling up
then I found this.
Four days after the second
search of your property,
after he found her torn
shirt in your basement,
he just walks into wausau
general memorial hospital
and completes the payment
for his mother's treatment in full.
It's nearly $10,000.
So, somebody paid
him to plant evidence.
He was desperate and
they took advantage.
So who's he working for?
That's what I'm trying to figure out.
Wait, where are you going?
To handle business.
You can't just waltz
back in there. I mean,
if anybody sees you
I appreciate you coming to see me, may,
but there isn't a second that goes by
that I don't think about
what they took from me.
But this needs to end.
There needs to be some answers.
Where the hell did you go?
My god!
Open the door! Open it!
This was Rose's.
She was wearing
these the night she left.
And this
we found recently.
This is em's. Where did you get this?
Moore creek. Same
place we found the earring.
The sacred place.
Well, that could just be a coincidence.
How do we know Moore
creek has real significance.
Because that's where I was murdered.
Remember how mom had this
thing with the water being special?
She was right.
That is where Ibrahim
took me and the water...
That's what healed me,
but when I went fully under,
a memory came back of this person
in an animal mask holding me down and
he had this, this symbol
carved on his chest.
This symbol has been
haunting me since revival day.
And I'm assuming Aaron didn't
have any carvings on his chest?
No. Look,
after I died,
they must have just left my
body to wash down the river
and into bull falls.
And when we found that,
I followed em, which led me to Aaron.
Who was also shot by Brent.
Is all of this enough of
a coincidence for you?
When we searched
Brent's phone records,
there was a text between him and Aaron
sent around the time Rose went missing.
It was a model of a car.
A dark blue cutlass supreme.
The USB drive that we
took from Aaron's house,
it had a text file on
it, but all it read was,
"dark blue cutlass
supreme." I mean, could
could that be bear's car?
Think you mean Blaine's car.
Wait, like the crazy radio dude?
Blaine had one of Rose's
necklaces, a bear claw.
He said they were friends.
Do you have any
reason to suspect Blaine?
Our tribe's had land disputes
with the abels for decades.
His father offered a lot
of money for our land.
That creeps how. I
knew he was not there
just towing a car. And
he was there that night.
Wait, Blaine was there
the night you died?
- Yes!
- Then it's time to go.
Jesse... Jesse, wait.
Jesse, where are you going?
Wait, wait, wait! Where are you going?
I'm going to get the man
that killed my daughter and your sister.
The last time you did this,
it didn't end well for you.
- Let them try that again.
- Reviver or not, last I checked,
- Blaine had a small militia.
- That's why I'm going with him.
Em, there are mercenaries
everywhere looking for you!
I think you know by now
I can handle myself fine.
Getting shot and
having you heal me again
is not part of my fricking
priorities right now, okay?
So please stay here.
Please, please? No. Stop.
Dana, let me go.
We don't even know if it's him.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm not saying it's not.
I'm just saying we need to be sure.
Let me get jp to help.
We all trust him, right?
I can get a warrant.
I can search the premises
and get what we need
to make a proper arrest.
I'm ready to end this.
We are all ready to end this.
Your vengeance is not
going to bring our Rose peace.
Jesse,
I didn't come through for you last time.
I know.
Let me do it for you this time, okay?
It's not going to happen again.
Please?
What are you writing?
Just some poetry.
May I?
It's-it's not really good.
I'm sure it's very good.
Every path finds its edge.
Silent crossing over dark
we mistake the silence for peace
forget that longing can
echo louder than rage
and the path we choose, a pit.
A stream, an icy river
is sometimes a return to what we were,
to what we left behind.
We cross, dimly aware
of the depths beneath
but these quiet Bridges
carry us beyond the dark.
Still, something yearns beneath the ice,
a voice not spoken, but known.
It pulls, not with force,
but with a promise.
But what was lost still waits.
Like a memory of warmth
in a body grown cold.
Unaware, we pass
over shadows waiting
below on an icy river.
It's still a work in
progress. I'm really rusty.
Rose also gave up writing.
Couple of years before.
I'm really sorry
about Rose.
Blue cutlass.
You really loved her?
I really did.
You ever had anyone like that?
Yeah.
Yeah, maybe.
Rhodey?
Em?
Holy shit. Are you-are you okay?
Rhodey... my god.
My god.
I've been so worried.
I've called so many times.
- Are you safe?
- I am now. I managed to escape.
It's crazy. Listen, em,
we can't talk for long.
You called just in time.
I'm getting out of here.
Come with me. - What?
Rhodey, no, I don't-i don't think I can.
I'm with my sister and we
are so close to figuring this out.
Like, I know who killed me.
Em, listen to me, you can't stay.
They've got some drug that
really messes with revivers.
You gotta get out.
Come with me.
What's going on?
What is it?
It's okay. Look,
can we at least say goodbye?
Okay. Okay, yeah.
Yeah, just meet me past
the camp at unity drive.
Okay.
Mr. Abel.
- What?
- It's the angel, sir.
- It's gone!
What?
Tyler!
What? What did you say?
Em?
Em!
Have you seen my sister?
I'm sorry. I didn't see her go.
I guess she snuck out.
Shit. Shit.
Is...?
No!
You were right, uncle.
I knew you'd bring her back.
No! Let me go!
Please. No!
I've got her.
I've got her. I'll meet you at Moore creek.
What was that?
It's calling me.
And I'm ready to go.
I'm ready now.
Our Rose can move on.
It's time for us to go, too.
Rhodey?
Em.
Hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
Don't cry. It's okay.
Look, I really gotta finish this,
but then I can come meet you wherever.
Like, Austin, or Nashville.
Or no, no, no! You,
you said we're going to the ocean, right?
What's wrong?
I'm so sorry, em.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
- What is this?
- So sorry.
Copy.
Target is acquired.
Moving her to a secure location.
Team 3, team 4, proceed with caution.
Northwest Ridge. Target is acquired.
Target is acquired.