[inspirational fanfare]
Previously on Revival.
She thinks water's
so goddamn special.
For now, my theory
remains Moore Creek
is ground zero for Revival Day.
How do you think
being a reviver's
impacted your emotions?
-EM: It's a secret and I'd
really like to keep it that
wa. My dad doesn't even know.
You've got a big gosh darn mess.
And no plans to clean it up.
We need to lock them
up. I'm doing this
for your own good, Ken.
She's a reviver.
-And my wife!
-[burning man grunts, groans]
-[exclaims]
[skin sizzling]
DANA: Are these my
Blackdeer files?
Did you steal police property?
Wanda's our inspiration
that even death is no
excuse to skip cardio.
It's time for you
to get branded.
Become one of the flock.
That is not our
daughter up there.
DANA: You're talking
about her like she's dead,
but she's very much alive.
-It's okay.
-[sizzling]
It's for me.
-[high-pitched trilling]
-[downward swoop]
[man grunts, groans]
-[gunshot]
-[body thuds]
-[knife squelches in back]
-[Dana groans]
-[thud]
-[score slows, descends out]
-[Em gasps]
-EM (crying): Come on, fight!
Fight, Dana, fight!
-[tense emotional score]
[Em sobbing]
No! No!
[Em continues crying] Oh my God.
[warbling tone]
[Em sobbing]
You're going to be okay.
[female singer vocalizing]
[gasping sobs]
[dramatic boom]
[score intensifies]
[score abates]
Em? Hey, Em? Em?
-[loud bang]
-Help!
-IBRAHIM; Hey. Hey. Hey.
-DANA: Where's Cooper?
He's in the car. He's
going to be okay.
-DANA: What about Jordan?
-Uh, she's going to be okay.
[Em groans] Hey, what happened?
She healed me and now, I
don't know, there's something
wrong with her.
-Hey, Em?
Her pulse is weakening,
Dana. I think she's dying.
But that's impossible.
Revivers can't die, right?
-[distant approaching sirens]
-What? Reviver?
(whisper) Oh my God. Nobody
can know Em was here.
Nobody can know what
she did to the Checks.
[splutters] Nobody can know.
I will hide her and
I will find a way
to fix her, okay?
-How?
-I think I know a way.
-[score intensifies]
-[rumbling]
-[rumbling abates]
-[quiet tender score]
I don't understand. Are
you sure you're okay?
[sighs]
Yeah.
Mm-hm. I'm okay.
Are you okay?
I'm a little scared, Mom.
What's scaring you?
I don't know.
You got shot and Auntie
Em's really sick.
And Jordan touched this big
glowy thing then poofed away
and now everyone's
gonna find out
what Auntie Em did
to those people
and then Grandpa's
gonna put her in a camp.
Yeah, so, that's a lot.
It's a lot for an
awesome kid like you
to have to deal with.
It's not fair.
But I'm going to take
care of everything.
I promise.
And, Coop, I, uh...
uh, I'm good.
How?
Um, I don't know. I
really don't know,
but that's what I'm going
to work on figuring out.
All right?
So you're going to be
with Jeannie for a bit
and I'm gonna go make
sure that Em is safe
and that Grandpa doesn't
do anything dumb.
And then you and I are
going to go find Jordan.
No, Jordan's gone.
She's not coming back.
But I think it was good for her.
♪
Okay.
Mr. Ibrahim saw it too.
Mom, do you not believe me?
Coop, I don't understand
it, but I believe you, okay?
Hey.
I believe you.
I'm really, really
sorry about Jordan.
I know she was your friend.
Listen, when this is all over,
you, me and Auntie Em
are going to go on
a big, fat vacation.
Can Grandpa come?
Um, we'll see.
Hey! Come on, Cooper! You
go, sweetie. I got him.
Thank you. All right, buddy.
BLAINE: This is our future.
This is your future.
-[score turns darker]
Tyler, power does not come
from worldly weapons or force.
It comes from influence.
How we inspire others.
In this holy place, we will
close the gates of Hades
and build this church anew.
WAYNE: Is this the footage
from the Check factory?
Yeah, you're going
to want to see this.
You should know the
governor has this, too.
[dramatic score]
She's in all the footage, Wayne.
TYLER: Go make disciples
of all nations.
Yes.
Hey, but first,
we must show the people
the power that God
has bestowed on us.
Wayne, is Martha a reviver?
[score intensifies]
TYLER: How do we
do that, Mr. Abel?
By using our avenging angel
to send those
demons back to Hell,
one by one.
[score abates]
[ethereal opening theme]
-[ringing whoosh]
-[opening theme fades out]
Why didn't you tell
me Martha died?
[door slams]
-[water running]
-[distant dog barking]
[distant birds singing]
Hey.
Wait a minute.
You-you you were stabbed and
you were in the ICU and
now you're standing here.
Oh my God.
Don't tell me you're
a reviver, too?
No.
Em healed me.
Em healed you? What the hell?
What do you mean she healed you?
She healed me. Dad,
I-I don't know.
I've never seen
anything like it.
I don't think this is a
regular reviver thing.
But this is Em. She...
She's special, Dad. I, I mean,
is she Jehovah-level
special? I don't know.
But she pulled off some
pretty biblical shit.
-[quiet tense score]
-Listen to me, okay?
You need to tell me
everything you know about
what happened to Martha.
But you need to stay calm.
-Calm? I'm calm.
-Yeah.
Okay, I'm her father, Dana!
I could've done something.
I could've helped!
Well, you did. You helped...
You turned the town
against revivers.
You called in the governor and
ripped them from their home
and stuck them in camps.
Everything has been
happening so fast.
Revivers needed your
protection, too, Dad!
So, I mean, it's no wonder
the Check brothers thought
they could kidnap them and
chop off their body parts.
I get it. Okay?
Now you gotta tell me
what happened to Martha.
Did, ah, I mean,
was it an accident?
Uh, how did she die?
I've been trying
to figure that out
ever since Arlene in the barn.
I'm trying to figure
out who murdered her.
Murdered? She was murdered?!
KEN: Wayne Cypress,
get your ass out here!
Ken, I don't have time
for this right now!
What is this all about?
-[score fades out]
-[crow caws]
-[quiet tense score]
-[hard smack]
-DANA: Oh!
-What the hell?
-WAYNE: It's okay.
I had to do that
again before I left.
What do you mean "again"?
What the hell, Dillisch?
I just got a call
from the governor
and this shit is completely
out of his control,
like everything else he touches!
-Ken, we need to leave now!
-A minute!
-What? You're splitting town?
-We have no choice!
And I don't care if I have
to ram through a blockade.
I'm getting Diane out of here.
Whatever happens next,
Wayne, it's on your head.
DANA: Diane's a reviver?
What did the governor do?
Shit.
[score intensifies]
Who the hell are you?
General Louise Cale.
On the order of Governor Harris,
Wausau, Wisconsin is
now under martial law.
That wasn't the deal.
The circumstances
have changed, Sheriff.
What?
GENERAL: Take the reviver.
-No. No!
-KEN: Take your hands off her!
-No! No, get off me!
-Diane!
-DIANE: Ken!
-[thud]
-DANA: Ken!
-SOLDIER: Let's go. Move!
-Ken!
-Hey! Hey!
♪
[Dana sighs]
[score fades out]
NEWSWOMAN: A city-wide
manhunt is on for the reviver
who murdered three brothers
at a south side
warehouse last night.
This brutal act
prompted Governor Harris
to call the military into
Wausu where containment efforts
will be spearheaded by
General Louise Cale,
a decorated two-star general
who made a name for herself
in the controversial
Ignant Riots in Dublin.
[Em breathes raggedly]
Governor Harris further outlind
that Cale and her men will
be taking into custody
every reviver in Wausau until
the suspect is apprehended.
[gunshot] And now reporting live
from the Cordoba
Nursing Home is May Tao.
[grunts; efforts]
May, I understand
you've spoken with
some of the families impacted.
Thank you, Katie. Yes, I
have. But I want to mention
in addition to the
reviver in question,
they are also actively
searching for an elderly woman,
IBRAHIM (whisper) Hey.
-Wanda Peterson,
as well a young child,
Jordan Borchardt.
-Gentle, okay. I'm sorry. Sorry.
-[Em groans]
MAN ON TV: They kicked
in the door and took her.
They treated her like an anima.
I mean, this is my grandmother.
We were so happy
to have her back.
What did she ever do to
anyone to deserve this?
I just want my
family back together.
Is that too much to ask?
NEWSWOMAN: This aggressive
and controversial decision...
-[loud thud]
-Hey, hey! Ooh, ooh, ooh.
[Em loudly gasping] Hey,
hey, hey. It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. I got you.
[Em loudly gasping]
I got you. I got you.
As always, stay
tuned to Channel 8
for your latest breaking
news in the Wausau takeover.
This is May Tao reporting in H.
[laser zaps on TV] ♪
Manning's Meats on Main ♪
Come on down to
Manning's Meats on Main
where family always comes first.
From Sunday dinners
to backyard cookouts,
we've got everything you need
to make mealtime memories.
Our meats are neat, but there's
nothing as special as family.
MYLES: No, no, no, no.
Please, I can't take anymore.
-[quiet tense score]
Please, you don't know
what this shit does to me.
-SOLDIER: Shut the hell up.
-[thuds]
No more lip.
You know the routine.
-Hey, I been good, ain't I?
-[clicking; ratcheting]
I done everything you
asked, all your damn tests.
-[loud click]
-[quieter clicks]
You ain't like them,
Doc. I know you aren't.
I said shut your trap
or I'll shut it for you.
RHODEY: Myles,
buddy, you got this.
Rhodey.
RHODEY: We'll make it
through this okay. Okay?
Don't let them break
you. It's you and me.
I don't know.
No, come on, man.
Don't say that.
FEMALE SCIENTIST:
Mr. Miller, please come here.
[Myles screaming in distance]
GENERAL: What a
mess. Nineteen dead,
three revivers missing.
You're governor
isn't happy, Wayne.
So she sent you to fix it, huh?
It is my specialty.
[loud grinding]
-[grinder spins down]
-[distant yelling voices]
Oh my God.
What is that for?
[distant loud buzzer]
That murderous reviver.
You have any
information on them?
Oh my God. Kenny.
It's amazing what
people will share
when you promise them safety.
You told them about Martha?
They got her on video.
Just a matter of time
before they put it together.
YOU SON OF A BITCH!
You didn't care about my family,
why should I care about yours?
You hurt her and I'll kill you!
I'll kill you. I'll kill you!
[score fades out]
[loud crinkling]
-[clattering]
-[loud bang]
-[paper crinkling]
-[quiet melodic score]
I was born in a Wausau
that was decent and free.
Under the eye of a righteous
mn who kept his house in order.
[Dana inhales, sighs]
And when I strayed from
the path he'd paved,
he collected me
with a stern hand.
[crinkling]
But I have awoken in a
far different Wausau.
We have been betrayed by
those we chose to protect u.
And that betrayal comes
with a steep price.
But rest assured, the Father
and His avenging
angels are coming
for the demons and the damned.
Their days walking
amongst us are numbered.
And through me, He
will collect his flock,
for I am now the door which
our Father has opened.
This is Redeemer Radio
and you've been listening to
the Reverend Blaine Gospel Hou.
-[headphones softly click]
-[spiritual music plays]
-[clicks music off]
-[knocking at door]
[quiet score]
-[door rattles]
-[door hinges creak]
Hi.
-Inspiring words, sir.
-Thank you.
Um...
isn't it time for our ascension?
It's just, I'm ready, sir.
Respectfully.
Tyler, my son, you
are indeed ready.
-[score intensifies]
-[dramatic whoosh]
Like it or not, Martha
is being hunted right now
and my soldiers will find her.
I've known a few
generals in my time.
They were smart, respected,
fair leaders. You're no general.
This general can offer you
the same deal as the mayor,
leniency, if you help
us bring her in safely.
[Wayne laughs]
Yeah,
[round chambered into
pistol] I didn't think so.
There's another way
to draw her out.
Where's your daughter, Wayne?
Do it. Go ahead.
You'd be doing me a favour.
Martha never told
me what she was
and I had no idea
until I saw that video.
So I don't know where she is,
or what she's capable of,
because she's never trusted
me enough to tell me.
Both my daughters hate me
because I failed them.
So go ahead.
[exhales]
She won't come. She'll
be glad I'm gone.
[score intensifies]
[score fades out]
-[quiet tense score]
-[sirens wailing in distance]
[inhales, sighs]
[phone clicks]
Where are you?
[helicopter rotors thumping]
[sharp sigh]
Hey. Em, Em, Em, Em.
We gotta go. Come
on. They're coming.
They're all coming now.
Oh, shit. Aw, shit!
Uh... Ah, shit! Hey-hey.
The soldiers are coming
down the road. Hey!
Hey, I need you to
listen to me, Em. Em.
drink this, okay?
This is from the water
sample from Moore Creek.
This is my Hail Mary, Em. I
need you to drink this, okay?
-[Ibrahim panting]
-(weakly) Okay.
-This is all I got.
-[pounding on doors in hallway]
[indistinct voices
in hall] Okay.
-[knocking in hall continues]
-[Ibrahim continues panting]
-Mm-hm.
-Okay. Okay. Okay.
Yeah.
-Okay, come on.
-You should go.
-We should go. Yes.
No, no, no. No.
[knocking on doors closer]
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
I'm with you,
okay? I'm with you.
Em, I'm with you.
[knocking on doors even closer]
[Em softly moans]
Hey, hey. Yeah. Hey.
You're sitting up.
-Yeah.
-Yeah. Okay.
Let's check your eyes, okay?
I'm going to check your pupils.
-Okay.
-Look at me. Okay.
[flashlight button
clicks] Yes. Yeah.
-Okay.
-[both loudly breathing]
-Hey! Hey!
-Yeah.
Hey, hey. You feeling better?
-Uh-huh.
-Okay. Hey.
[voices, pounding on
doors continue in hallway]
We gotta move. Okay.
Ah, shit. That worked.
I'm going to surrender myself
so that you stay safe, Ibrahim.
No. No. Hey.
I'm getting all your stuff and
we're getting out of here, Em.
[loud banging in hallway]
Okay? Okay. Okay.
Where are we going to go?
Hey, hey, listen, I got you.
I got you, okay? All right?
-Where? Where?
I told Dana I'd take
care of you, so I will.
Okay?
-Okay.
Okay. We got to
get to Moore Creek.
And I got you. We're
going to go together.
-Okay.
-We gotta get you to this water.
Okay? We gotta get
you to this water.
-[score abates]
-[scratching]
-[tap]
-[paper crinkling]
[sharp taps]
[distant dog barking]
[quiet tense score]
-[door lock clicks]
-[clattering]
-[cocks pistol]
-[door hinges creak]
[door bangs closed]
-Whoa.
-[relieved breaths, sigh]
-Jeez.
-[calming exhale]
What happened to you?
They let me go.
There's two of them
out there watching me.
Probably hoping I
lead 'em to Martha.
They know?
Yeah, that piece of
shit, Dillisch, told 'em.
[pistol bangs onto table]
If they're following you,
why'd you lead them here?
-[glass thuds on counter]
-I needed a drink
and your house is closer.
[cork pops]
If they don't have
Em yet, that's good.
That means Ibrahim's
keeping her safe.
[alcohol sloshing]
You told him before you told me?
Yeah, well, technically,
he figured it out.
And technically,
I didn't tell you.
But I have faith in him, Dad.
Yeah? Well, that's
one of us, I guess.
I just hope he can
keep her hidden.
[distant dog barking]
What's going on here?
-[deep sigh]
-This is everything
I've collected on Em's case.
You know, Dana, when you're
investigating a crime
there's a process.
We need to treat this
like a real case.
Proper case? Dad, Em's alive.
She's a murder
victim who's alive.
This case was jacked
from the beginning.
Walk me through
what we have here.
[glass thuds onto counter]
All right.
No, I don't think Blaine
was working with Aaron.
My instincts say it
was a coincidence
Blaine was on that bridge.
-[score fades out]
Let's not forget where your
instincts took us last time.
Well, let's not forget that
you hired two deputies.
One who tried to traffic Em
and one who tried to kill me.
Okay, are we pointing fingers
or are we working the case?
No, I'm good at both.
I can multitask.
[quiet tense score]
You walk me through what
you're thinking and...
-[bottle clinks on glass]
-[liquid sloshing]
I'll have a drink.
-Okay.
-[bottle thuds onto table]
[Dana sighs]
Why did Brent shoot
Aaron and then me?
Because one of us
knew who killed Em
and the other was
close to finding out.
So, then, the next
obvious question is,
then, did Brent kill Martha?
Or was he a hired gun?
'Cause my gut is that Aaron
was working with the person
who killed Em, but Brent
was working for them.
Let's follow the evidence,
okay, instead of your gut.
Can you st... stop throwing
the Blackdeer case in my face?
I'm not throwing the
Blackdeer case in your face.
I'm trying to teach
you something, Dana.
You had the guy in your
grasp and you let him go.
You know why I let him go?
Because I know a dedicated,
loving father when I see one,
no thanks to you, shithead!
[alcohol sloshing]
Wow. Okay, yeah. Well,
no flies on you, right?
[thud] You know what?
You make it goddamn
hard sometimes, too.
Why? How?
Because I got in
trouble as a kid?
Because I picked the wrong
guy and got knocked up
and gave you a
beautiful grandson?
Or the real kicker:
it's my fault that mom died.
I have never said that. Okay?
That's in your head and I don't
want to talk about that night.
You don't wanna talk about Mom,
or whatever happened
with you and Dillisch.
Because talking doesn't
bring back the dead.
♪
I know you think I'm a
rotten son of a bitch.
I don't...
I don't know what you
are. That's the problem.
Well, you know
what? Whatever I am,
I'm here right now, okay?
I'm not perfect. I know that.
I've made mistakes. I own it.
But everything I've ever done
has only been with your
best interest at heart.
That's a fact.
[soft tapping on glass]
♪
[pen clatters onto
desk] You know what?
Why don't you...
-[clattering]
chase down Brent's financials,
see if they lead to
him being a hitman
and I'll try to figure
out where the hell he was
the night Martha was killed.
All right?
-It's a good plan.
[distant dog barking]
[score fades out]
Why are you doing this to me?
BLAINE: We are doing nothing.
It is our angel
who will judge you.
Angel? What are
you talking about?
That's Wanda.
The reviver from Lester's
class. We took her?
MAN ON TV: Make
room for the angel!
That is who we took, but
that is not her name.
MAN ON TV: Behold.
She's perished.
-MAN (TV):  Bring it closer.
-Replaced by...
-MAN ON TV: Stay back!
-...something vile.
[strange trilling moan]
-[electricity crackles on TV]
-[Wanda moans, cries out]
WANDA: What the
hell is that thing?
Get it away from me!
[Wanda sobs] It's,
it's not mine.
[strange trilling moan]
It's... No, no, no...
No, no, no.
-[loud trumpeting]
-(crying) NO! NO!
This isn't mine!
[Wanda's scream interspersed
with brief moments of silence]
-[dramatic score]
-[Wanda continues screaming]
[loud trumpeting]
-[loud static]
-[Wanda screams]
[loud trumpeting]
MAN ON TV: Holy shit. It worked!
[other man on TV laughs]
She's back in Hell
where she belongs!
BLAINE: This is the start of
our holy war, my brethren.
What was that, Mr. Abel?
FOLLOWERS ON TV: Our
rock, our fortress...
That is how we are
going to cleanse Wausau.
...our fortress, Grant
us everlasting light.
[drum hit on TV]
-Our rock...
And restore my good name.
...everlasting light.
Our rock, our fortress,
Grant us everlasting light.
[score fades out]
WAYNE: How did you
manage to steal
Brent's police
notebooks, anyway?
Uh, didn't steal it.
I asked JP to steal it.
[breathy laugh]
He's good at that.
You know, his
writing is atrocious.
I can't make heads or
tails of where he was
on Revival Night from these.
Just check the GPS records
from his squad car.
That'll tell you where he was.
-Yeah.
Well, I mean, I
was gonna do that.
Yeah.
Looks like he was named on an
old LLC called Spare O'Clock.
Some... There's not much here.
There's no other
managing members.
Call the patent and
the trademark offices.
When I get off of this, you
can check the TESS database.
-I was about to... do that.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
-Huh.
[quiet dramatic drum hit]
You know what?
[quiet tense score]
Why the hell was he...
at Randy's Crematorium
while he was on duty?
That's where he was
on Revival Night?
Not in the woods or
near the stone bridge?
That's what his car GPS says.
Well, sounds like we need
to pay ol' Randy a visit.
The only problem with that is
Randy's basically 60% water,
40% conspiracy theories
and if we show up with
the military in tow,
he's going to bolt the doors
and head for the hills.
Right. Well, one of us
needs to create a diversion
so the other can
slip out to Randy's.
Right.
You decide who.
Sorry?
You decide.
Uh, I think this is the
part where you say, uh,
"you should do it 'cause
I suck at my job."
You take the lead. You go and...
I mean, Em chose
you to protect her
and you've been right, you know?
You were right.
You decide this.
Okay?
[score abates]
-I have a plan.
-[exciting percussive score]
I'M SICK AND TIRED
OF YOUR BULLSHIT!
WAYNE: I'M SICK
WELL, THAT'S ENOUGH!
I'M GONNA KICK YOUR ASS,
...OLD MAN!
-MAKE YOUR MOVE, BITCH!
-(sotto) Bitch?
-[Wayne scoffs]
Jesus.
I HATE YOU!
[loud smash] Not on the floor!
-Don't worry about the floors!
-Chip the fricking tiles!
-Just say the next thing.
-I'm not saying that again.
I WISH YOU WERE NEVER BORN!
-Jesus.
-Listen, I don't mean it.
That's going to
come out in therapy.
-I don't do therapy.
-Yeah, no shit!
You go ahead.
[score abates]
-Should we do something?
-No.
We're just supposed
to follow them.
You ready for the grand finale?
-Grand finale?
-Yeah.
Oh! Don't shoot the
roof. Point it down.
-Okay.
-[cocks pistol]
[Dana gasps] DAD, NOOO!
NOOO!
-[gunshot]
-[loud exciting score]
-Inside now! Move, move, move!
[door clatters]
Shit!
-Surprise, shithead.
-[electrical crackling]
-[first soldier groans]
-[body thuds]
[second soldier's body thuds]
Go! Dana, go!
Hey, Dad! We make a good team.
-I know.
-Yeah.
-[dramatic boom]
-[score fades out]
-[frogs, toads croaking]
-IBRAHIM: You've know, I've, uh,
I've never been
much of a Boy Scout,
but look at me now, huh?
[Em weakly laughs] Huh?
Hey, you okay?
-Yeah.
-All right.
You know what? You
should take a rest here.
Come on. Come. This is perfect.
Here, you sit, you sit.
-[Em groans]
Okay, just take it easy, okay?
[Em sighs, sniffles]
Earlier, um,
when you were sick
you were having these
vivid dreams.
Flashes.
To the warehouse and what I did.
To the Checks?
And what I did to me.
There was, like,
electricity running
through my body,
glacier water through
my veins. Me...
but not me.
Em, it's, uh,
I've tested many, many,
many revivers, Em.
Biologically, they are
all still themselves.
Their cells just act
a little different,
that's all.
This is more than that.
I don't know who I am anymore.
I used to be timid
and fragile and I...
didn't necessarily like
myself all the time,
but I knew who I was
and now I have...
[scoffs]
...no idea. I have...
no concept of the
world around me
and what happened
last night? You...
You said that Jordan combined
with some glowing creature
and then vanished and what
if that happens to me?
What does that even...
What does that even mean?
-Hey, hey.
Hey, you're living an
unprecedented life, Em.
It's okay.
It's bound to do your head in
from time to time. Okay? Hey.
-[Em sniffles]
-(whisper) Okay.
When I feel unsettled,
I try to focus on
what I know for sure.
Yeah, that must be
the scientist in you.
-[chuckles]
-Yeah, it must be.
But what I saw last night,
I observed, was this:
Jordan, she didn't look
scared of the creature.
She, she didn't cry
out. She didn't falter.
In the face of this
large, haunting,
alien-like creature, being,
whatever you want to call it,
she went toward
it. She chose it.
Instead of us. So maybe...
-Maybe...
Maybe not all monsters are bad.
Yeah.
If you could go back to
the old you, would you?
If you created a
cure, would I take it?
Yeah. Yeah.
This...
this version of me saved
Cooper and Jordan and
stopped my sister from dying.
[Em laughs]
Who would turn
their back on that?
Somebody who wanted
to be normal?
[score intensifies]
Screw normal.
[Ibrahim groans]
All right. Come on.
[score intensifies]
-[score fades out]
-[song playing faintly on radio]
RANDY: Oh, sure. Brent
was here that night.
He wanted to discuss some
fella chilling in the morgue.
Ya know, chilling?
Yeah, I got it. Tell
me about the guy.
Yeah, right. So,
Deputy Brent said
that the fella had
taken his own life
and his poor family just
wanted him cremated right away
so as to not make a fuss
and, you know, upset folks.
It's a shame, really,
is what it is.
You know, a lotta fellas our age
don't prioritize mental health
as much as they should.
It's an epidemic, honestly,
is what it is. That's
why I myself have
a therapist and a life coach.
Think power!
-[laughs softly]
You know what I'm saying?
[song plays faintly on radio]
The guy?
Well, - [sighs]
for starters, it
was on Revival Day.
Jeez, if that night
doesn't haunt me
every time I close my eyes.
What happened?
The poor guy revived right
as he went in the fire.
-[whoosh]
-[exclaims]
Then he burst out the retort
and ran right past us
like a flaming Cheeto.
-[whooshing]
-[burning man yelling]
DANA: Us? Who? You and Brent?
No. Me and Miss Toe.
Tao? May Tao?
-Yeah, yeah. May Tao. Yeah.
-What was May Tao doing here?
She said she was
working on a story
on account that she's a
journalist, or whatever,
and, uh, she wanted to
interview little old me,
which I thought was pretty dope.
-[inhales sharply]
But turns out all she really
wanted to talk about was
the soon-to-be-burnt John
Doe that Brent brought in.
If the family
identified the body
why did the tag say John Doe?
I don't know. I just figured
it was his real name.
What was the story
May was working on?
She said she was
working on a special.
On the most interesting
jobs in Wausau.
Can you beat that?
I have one of the
most interesting jobs
in all of Wausau.
May Tao was here
at 9 p.m. at night
to work on a story about
quirky little townie jobs?
Not quirky little townie jobs.
The most interesting jobs
and it happens to be me.
[dramatic rumbling]
[rumbling intensifies]
-[distant crow cawing]
-IBRAHIM: It's going to be okay.
All right?
-[Em coughs, gasps]
One step at a time.
Right, Em? I got you.
[Em coughing] I got you.
-[water burbling]
-Is this the super water?
Yes. Yes.
Drinking it only gave
you temporary relief.
I think you're going to need
to get into it, Em. All right?
But I'm going to be
with you, all right?
-[Em groans]
-I'm going to be with you.
-(whisper) Okay.
-All right. Okay?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
-[crow calls]
-[quiet tense score]
-[Em groans]
-(weakly) Okay.
Slowly. You're okay. Okay.
Watch your step.
-[Em grunts]
Okay.
-[Em shivers from cold]
All right.
-[water sloshing]
[Em shivers]
[Em gasps] Careful.
Watch your step.
[score intensifies]
There you go.
[water sloshing]
[soft exhales]
[breathing loudly]
[score intensifies]
[water splashing]
[muffled water burbling]
[intense high-pitched tones]
-[dramatic boom]
-[intense high-pitched tones]
(muffled) Em!
[dramatic boom] EM!
[cacophony of loud
intense sounds]
[intensifying whoosh]
I remember! This is it!
This is where I died!
Ibrahim?
[dramatic boom]
[score intensifies]
-[score abates]
-[Em breathes raggedly]
[score fades out]
[woman yawns]
[woman yelps]
I'm sorry. I snuck
into your house.
I'm kind of on the run,
so be quiet, be cool.
Dana, what the hell are
you doing in my house?
[sighs]
Cute PJs.
I think the real question
is why do we have
the same murder board?
[pensive score]
The Blackdeer files.
So you looked at my notes?
How did you know
Brent was my shooter?
And why didn't you tell me?
He was right there!
And I didn't know for
sure, but I had a hunch.
He tried to kill me
again an hour later!
Yeah. I came to you
to help you and you said
to your actual killer
watch out for me.
What is all this?
Are you looking into
my sister's murder too?
Your sister was murdered?
Wait, so Em is a reviver?
Yes. Catch up, woman.
I don't know anything
about that, okay?
I've just been
looking for justice
for Rose and for Jesse.
We both know he didn't do it.
-Yeah, of course not.
[crunching]
But what does that have
to do with Brent and me?
Brent killed Jesse.
No. [scoffs]
Jesse escaped.
-I think you're missing a few...
And what were you really doing
at Randy's on Revival Night?
I was there.
I saw Brent leaving
the crematorium.
He dropped off a body
on Revival Night.
A John Doe.
Well, who's the John Doe?
Is he connected to all this?
[score abates]
You want to ask him yourself?
-[dramatic boom]
-[helicopter approaching]
[tense dramatic score]
-[loud door release buzzer]
-[metal clanging]
You see nothing,
you say nothing.
Shifts are on the wall.
Phones are left at the door.
Understand?
[loud metallic bang]
[tense score abates]
-[leaves rustling]
-[birds chirping]
[score fades out]
So, uh, this eye mask,
like a sex thing, or what?
You wish.
It's to protect my friends.
-From what?
From you. Can you
just wait a second?
It will all make
sense very shortly.
[quiet tender score]
What was the deal
with you and Rose?
Have you ever looked
up the word patience
in a dictionary?
-Gosh, you're charming.
No wonder you're single.
[clattering] Ah! Shit!
Sorry. I didn't see that one.
How much further?
May?
-[stirring score]
-[Em gasps, pants]
[both breath emotionally]
[tender score]
You're okay? You're better?
He figured out how to fix you?
He did!
Where is he? Where's Ibrahim.
Back at Moore Creek. I
couldn't bring him with me.
What? Why not?
It wasn't up to me.
Someone else brought me here.
-[door handle clatters]
-[door hinges loudly squeak]
[feet clunk on steps]
Hi, Dana.
[stirring dramatic score]
Jesse Blackdeer?
-[deep sigh]
-[score abates]
I don't understand.
I let you go. I thought
you made it out.
I did.
On the run for two years.
Trying to mourn my Rose in
peace, but no peace came.
So I returned here to
Wausau to find answers
and find my Rose.
I'm done running.
Whoever killed Rose made sure
that they were waiting for him.
And since I've been reborn
I've been hiding here.
And thanks to Uncle
Don, I've been safe
and been able to work close
with May to find the answers.
I wish I could
welcome you, Dana,
But I don't wish to have
Cypress troubles on tribal land.
Respectfully, Uncle,
their woes belong to us.
The families intertwined
and so are our stories.
What... what do you mean?
Whoever killed me and my Rose,
[dramatic score]
They killed you, too.
-[score intensifies]
-[dramatic boom]
[rhythmic dramatic score]