Previously on Revival.
I lost my mom and
it was an awful accident.
- Take your hands off her!
- No! Ken!
It's amazing what
people will share
when you promise them safety.
Rose is special to me.
You're giving him snake venom?
It dramatically
slows down reviver healing.
- Moore Creek.
- Please.
I never ever hurt anyone.
-What was that, Mr. Abel?
That is how we are
going to cleanse Wausau.
Where is he?
Where's Ibrahim?
- Back at Moore Creek.
- I couldn't bring him with me.
I'm so sorry, Em.
Help!
You're awake.
Lovely.
Here. Here, here.
There you go.
You're lucky my men were
scouring that area.
I heard all about you, preacher.
Should have just...
You should have just left me
at the creek where you found me.
For the soldiers to find you?
In the state you're in?
No, no, no. You're the
great doctor, after all.
He who studies revivers.
I read your notes and, uh,
you're hiding something, Doctor.
Why don't you tell me
what started Revival Day.
We can help each other.
Don't you already have
all the answers?
Huh?
Or are you just pretending
for all your followers?
I have some pieces.
But I want to know
the origins of the evil, right?
So I can better fight it.
You know,
ensure it never happens again.
You are a hate-monger.
I'm not helping you.
You know, on Revival Night
I was called to tow a car.
And then I felt this
blast of energy
come through the forest and
I saw a light
shine from the sky
and I ran to that light
to find the origin,
but it was already too late.
You know why?
The gates of Hell had opened.
The demons were free.
Hm.
Bet you've been
waiting a long time
for something like this
to happen, huh?
Huh? So you could continue to do
your little radio show,
stoking fear and hate, huh?
Pretending to be chosen by God.
Shame on you.
No, people may think a lot
of different things about me,
but one thing I am not
is a fraud.
And I'm going to prove it.
-You actually...
You actually believe
what you're selling, huh?
Maybe you should, too.
-The last thing you want
is to turn Blaine
into a martyr for his cause.
He's killed your girlfriend
and my sister
and now she's missing
and I know he has her.
Martyr's still dead...
and that's good enough for me.
-We have the element of surprise
so let's use it.
- And the general?
- We approach from the woods.
- She doesn't care about us.
- We take out the guards.
- Quietly, individually.
- She just wants Em.
Then we go after Blaine.
Good.
JP is right. So listen up:
We need to be smart
and tactical about this, right?
I want this son of a bitch
as much as anybody, but, uh,
we don't want to start a
full-blown war with his militia.
Let's do it.-
So when did you
lose your faith, Dr. Ramin?
I haven't.
I just don't let it cloud
my reason.
My angel
would have opened your heart.
Your angel?
I lost her
but she'll come back to me.
Through the woods,
like she did last time,
just a beacon of light.
-A yellow light?
Did your, um,
did your angel call out with a,
a pained moaning sound, too?
I think I've said enough.
It's your turn to share.
I'm not helping
you hurt them, Blaine.
You know we want
the same thing, Doctor.
I can see it in your eyes.
The same fire I have in mine.
To know. To understand.
We came here for a reason.
Kullu nafsin dha'iqatul mawt.
Every soul shall taste death.
Police!
Keep your hands where
I can see them, Blaine.
- Ah, yeah.
- Stand up slowly.
It's okay.
- Why are you here?
- Move over there.
- Yeah, yeah. I got him.
- Fitzy! Cuff him.
- Where's Em?
- Pat him down.
I don't know.-
Fitzy: He's clear.-
Why does she require
such extreme measures?
She needs triple the dose.
Her body heals faster.
She fights back
when others don't.
And she's demonstrated
an unmatched threshold
for violence.
Doctor, the clock is ticking
and I must account for control
and remove all the revivers.
I'll find the revivers,
but I need you for
the control part.
She's experiencing some form of
hysterical psychosis.
She's not fit to be moved.
So fix her.-
Martha.
You're going to be okay.
Mom?
Lester Majak asked me
to tow a car.
A car rented by Aaron Weimar,
who you then had killed.
-Okay, so, hypothetically,
let me indulge here
with this theory.
So, what would I have to pay
Deputy Brent
to kill the professor?
- You paid $10,000.
- Ha!
Ten thousand dollars?! Yeah?
And does it look like
I have $10,000?
I mean, I am a tow truck driver
living in a junkyard, so...
You had enough money
to try and buy your father's
land back from Blackdeer.
You see, I gave that away
before your sister was killed.
Wow! Who'd you give it to?
That's my business
- and only God can judge me.
- Oh, I'm so sick of this
Chosen One bullshit.
You know,
when I saw your sister
on the bridge that night,
cold, alone, -
messed up,
I couldn't help but wonder
who in her family
failed her so miserably
that she ended up
a murdered junkie.
Hm?
You? You?
I can't imagine
how you must have felt
losing everything,
so publicly, so shamefully.
And then to have your mother
run out on you
immediately thereafter.
And then your father
gets killed.
So, then you find these
two young, innocent women,
with their whole lives
ahead of them and you...
you're just angry and you just
want to punish them.
So you get Aaron Weimar
to find them,
befriend them,
lure them into the woods
so that you're not
seen with them
the night they're murdered.
And you decide to play God
and use them
to fulfil your sick fantasy
of being chosen.
- No.
- That's why you murdered Rose
- and my sister!
- No.
- I did not murder your sister.
- Okay?
And I did not murder Rose!
She was my friend.
You know,
we finally found her body.
In the trunk of one of
the wrecked cars on your lot.
-That's bullshit!
That's bullshit!
You reviver lovers,
just setting me up.
You just want to destroy me
like you did my father.
I would've left
your father alone, Blaine,
except he was swindling people
out of their life savings,
conning them into believing
you had stigmata
by sticking nails in your hands.
-This was my father preparing me
for the day I was chosen.
- You know what?
- We don't need your confession.
We know what you did
and we know why you did it.
I just hope to hell
your redneck militia
can handle the news that
you're a fraud
'cause your father's flock
sure as hell couldn't.
-Please.
He truly believes
he's been chosen by God,
so how does murdering
Rose and Em help his mission?
He was probably
offering them as sacrifices
to prove how worthy he was
of being chosen.
Yeah, but why team up with a
Humanities professor to do that?
If it was to
keep his hands clean,
why would he choose Rose,
someone he had
a direct connection to?
You auditioning
to be his defence attorney?
- No. No.
- No, he's-he's crazy. Sure.
But he's curious.
His threats are
only directed towards revivers,
not young women,
so I'm just struggling to find
a motive that fits.
Is he in there?
- Yeah, yeah. It's okay.
- We got him.
Listen,
I need your help.-
You're a better investigator
than most of our deputies.
Most?
Find out
where Blaine's money went.
Hurry up.
Hey, Em. It's me, Rhodey.
They said you were sick and
I wanted to see you,
make sure you're okay.
So this is the boy you've
been seeing?
What's he like?
-Em, I...
I never meant
for this to happen.
They threatened my family.
They tortured me.
And...
I wasn't strong enough.
There's one thing
I've learned in my day:
men will say anything
to get you to take them back,
but as soon as you do
they will break your heart
all over again.
I have to wonder, Martha,
what made you choose a boy
who could do something like this
to you?
You think you'll ever
be able to forgive me?
You don't need him, lovebug.
You have me now.
Hm.
Let me out!
Please! She's not okay!
Please don't leave me again.
I don't know
what else to tell you.
Just get her under control.
There's a problem at security.
Some old reviver-loving townie
causing trouble.
- Deal with it!
- And set an example.
The sooner we get them to
Ember Point, the better.
-Uh, Ember Point?
Above your pay grade, Doctor.
Ken, you have to
get me out of here.
This place is awful.
They're doing something to
the other revivers.
All day long
it's just screaming.
They done anything to you?
No, they haven't touched me.
But I am so afraid
at any moment they're going to.
I can't stand it.
- They won't, they won't.
- I promise.
We made a deal.
A deal?
Mm-hm.-
It's complicated.
Remember,
we made a promise to each other.
No more secrets.
The general asked me
to identify a reviver
on a surveillance video.
It was Martha Cypress.-
You're the reason
they caught Martha?
Oh, Ken.
She's a child.
- I know.
- I know, I know.
Listen, listen...
I heard the general
talk to a soldier.
I think they want to move us.
Move?
Wait a second.
I saw all these transport trucks
and, uh,
shipping containers outside
that weren't there before.
She's getting ready
to do something. And soon.
I promise I'll get
you out of here, okay?
Hey, don't worry.
Well, if Ibrahim is right,
then we're back at square one.
I mean anybody in Wausau
could've killed Rose
and your sister.
Believe me, I know.-
Do we have any whiskey
for this coffee?
Look, we have a guy in lockup
right now
who had the means, opportunity
and pathology
to commit these murders.
I'm not saying
we should let Blaine go.
I'm just saying
we need to be sure.
Otherwise, Em and
every other young woman
in Wausau's not safe.
All right.
We hang on to him
as long as we can.
We continue to investigate until
we find evidence that
points one way or the other,
but my money's on Blaine.
- Wayne!
- You son of a bitch.
Oh! Oh!
That's for narcing on my sister!
- I tried to stop him.
- Thanks, Fitzy. It's okay.
- Oh.
- What the hell do you want?
I deserve that.
But you gotta listen.
The general found Martha.
- What? How?
- Where?
-We got bigger problems.
Diane overheard
the general talking.
They're moving all the revivers,
including Martha.
We gotta bust them out,
or we'll never see them again.
Because it has
the best tactical security
of any of the empty facilities
in Wausau.
It has a single entrance
leading to a set of stairs
down into the basement.
It's a choke point.
It's the only way to save Em.
How does us getting blasted
to pieces help your sister?
How does sitting on our asses
save her?
Focus, please!
All right, if the general
is planning a mass move
of revivers, she's not going to
take any chances.
So, JP, call Paul Blake at the
department of transportation.
Tell him that I need to know
if they've cleared any highways,
rail lines,
or flight paths out of Wausau.
- All right. You got it, chief.
- Let's go.
- Hey, Sheriff!
- I need a hand here!
They're nothing but cowards!
Nothing but bullies
hiding behind army fatigues.
I've seen it a hundred times.
- What happened?
- What's going on?
He went to Riverside
to find his friend
and they pistol whipped him
and then dumped him near my bar!
So much death and destruction
and what do we have
to show for it?
It's the reason I left the army
to focus on life
instead of death!
Lester, calm down. You're going
to give yourself a coronary.
Wanda didn't ask to
come back from the dead,
but she was doing
the best that she could.
Even after losing
her social security.
I did what I could to help her,
but you couldn't care less,
Sheriff!
You all overlook us
because of our age!
We still have good years
ahead of us!
- Oh.
- Uh, let me get you some ice
for that eye.
- Don't bother.
- It's a badge of honour.
See if you can convince him
to go to the hospital.
That looks nasty.
He needs to get checked out.
No, no, no. That is the cost
for standing up for
the people in this town.
Something that you
couldn't be bothered to do
until you realized
that Martha was one of them.
That's not leadership.
That's cowardice.
Just like the man that
did that to Lester.
Any revivers get free,
you send them to me.
I can get them out of Wausau
through the old bootlegging
tunnels under the bar.
Okay, so Blaine
was telling the truth.
He gave away his money.
- To who?
- To you.
Well, originally,
to the department
as a reward
for finding Rose's killer.
Wait, Blaine was behind
the anonymous reward for Rose?
- That was...
- Fifty thousand dollars. Yeah.
- Well, we never got that money.
- They pulled it when Jesse ran.
-Then it went to
the Missing and Murdered
Indigenous Women's Fund.
I guess he could've donated it
out of guilt.
I don't think he did.
-Dana, he can't go free.
You have to find something
to make this stick.
Finish what you started.
- I'm taking off.
- Ah.
Hey, I'm a journalist.
I'll take my info
from any reliable source.
- Yeah, well, I'm a scientist.
- I shouldn't be
looking for answers
in religious texts.
Says who?
The dead have risen, Doc.
Pretty sure there are no rules.
You know,
Rose and I always used to say
that whoever died first would
come back
- and haunt the other.
- Hm.
Just to prove
there was an afterlife.
Like, uh,
Harry Houdini and his mother.
-Exactly.
Have you,
have you heard from her?
-Not yet.
But I'm keeping
my fingers crossed.
Good luck with
your soul-searching.
Hm.
Dana, I don't even know
what I'm looking for here.
It's all just his plans for
storming the gates of Riverside.
And it's not too hot
of a plan, if you ask me.
There must be something here
about Rose, or my sister.
Oh.
Oh. He wouldn't be
the first murderer
to record his crimes.
Get it away from me.
This isn't mine.
Jesus.
So that's how
Wanda Peterson died.
He's found a way to
kill revivers.
Seems like that light
is the thing that killed her.
No. No, it's...
I've seen the source of light.
It's a creature, or a being.
Tall, thin, like, -
like an apparition,
but it wouldn't kill.
- What are you saying?
- Like an alien?
I don't know, Sheriff,
I don't know.
But I saw it touch
Cooper's friend, Jordan,
and that's not what happened.
She went toward it peacefully
and then she just,
she disappeared.
Yeah, that's what Cooper said,
but it doesn't make sense
'cause if what happened to Wanda
is what happened to Jordan...
It's not, Dana. Trust me.
People just
don't disappear, Doctor.
And that's not what
happened in that video.
Well, maybe
the thing that you saw
is different from
the thing in the video?
- Maybe.
- Certainly had a presence.
Something beyond words. I...
You're supposed to
be giving us answers,
not add aliens to the mix.
-I know, I know, I know.
And don't you think I feel like
I've failed you all every day.
That maybe Em and Diane
and Wanda would all be safe
if I just figured out
what happened on Revival Day?
That maybe you'd all be
better off
if I hadn't insisted on heading
the CDC efforts here in Wausau?
-Well, regardless,
clock is ticking and
we now have two problems.
Blaine's going to
break into Riverside.
He wants to use that thing
to kill all the revivers.
He called it his angel,
but he told me he lost it.
Well, that sounds like
a good thing, doesn't it?
I know what the general's up to.
Tomorrow at 1700 hours
the Department of Transportation
has shut down a lane
of Highway 51 North
to Fox Valley rail line.
There's a defunct line
that goes all the way to
the docks at Lake Superior.
So, she's going to truck
the revivers to a rail line
and put them on a ship to
Christ knows where.
Diane had mentioned to me that
she had the suspicion
that they were going to
move the revivers and soon.
And now that we know
what she's up to,
all we need to do is stop her.
No.
We force her into a new plan.
One that works for us.
Hello, Martha.
I understand you're having
a difficult time right now.
-Now who do we have here?
I'm just here to talk.
I won't touch you, or hurt you.
Have an affair
with a married man
while his wife was going through
cancer treatment.
Martha, I raised you
better than that.
I'm sorry. I'm so...
so sorry.
Can you tell me
what's going on around you?
Maybe that's why
you were murdered.
As punishment for
ruining the home life
of a sick, fragile woman.
- Don't say that.
It's a good thing
I died in that crash.
If I'd lived long enough to see
you turned into a home-wrecker,
- I might've killed myself.
- Mom!
Patricia Cypress.
But everyone called her Patty,
right?
Can you see her too?
Martha, is your mother
in the room?
Yeah.
You're experiencing
a break with reality.
Likely it's stress-induced.
But, look,
I'm here to help you, okay?
Do you know
what happened to her?
No.
Would you like to tell me?
Dana got into a fight
at Nella's bar because
some townie was heckling her
for the Blackdeer case and...
- Stop it, Martha!
- That story is for our family.
- Then...
- Just our family.
-And my mom called my dad
because she didn't like
to drive in winter,
- but he didn't pick up.
- Stop it!
- Martha, look at me.
- Talk to me, okay?
- So I drove.
- Martha, stop.
- And when I was driving...
- No.
- A deer just...
- No!
- Came out of nowhere.
- NOOO!
It was all my fault!
And it was all my fault!
It was all my fault!
- I'm so sorry, Mom.
- Time's up.
- What do you mean?
- She's in a state of distress.
She's coherent enough
to follow directions.
- She's still in a very fragile...
- That's all I need.
Martha, no!
No! Martha! This isn't you.
Martha...
I know that you've felt
so much loss in your life,
but this will only make
those feelings worse.
Please.
Let him go.
See, Mom?
I am the Martha you raised.
I did the right thing.
Mom?
General Cale!
I have an urgent message
for General Cale.
Whoa, whoa.
There's a local militia...
There's a local militia
that's going to attack
- Riverside tomorrow!
- We got it.
And they've found a way to
kill revivers!
- Get out of here. Go!
- Listen to what I'm saying!
They're going to kill revivers.
Carla.
Ibrahim. Where have you been?
I need you to tell me
what time the general
is planning on moving
the revivers.
I don't want to get involved.
-You're already involved.
This is not
what we came here to do.
I know. That's why I'm trying
to make it right
and why I'm giving you a chance
to make it right.
She heard about Blaine's plan.
She's moving them at sunrise.
And, Ibrahim,
they're moving them to
some secret facility.
No, they're not.
I need you to
give the revivers this.
What's in these vials?
It's just water.-
If we can pull this off,
JP and Nella are gonna need
all the help they can get
getting over the border,
so, here you go.
Always aim for centre mass.
Y'know, when I became a doctor
I never imagined I'd be
solving murders
and planning extractions.
-Listen,
you saved my sister's life, so,
that may not be why
you came here but,
to me, it's what matters most.
Thanks. Uh...
- Okay, so...
- I'll be at Nella's.
Yeah.
This is all the pyro
we have at the station, okay?
So we're going to use the woods
and the cover of night
to get set up outside.
JP and Rogers will set up on
the north perimeter.
They're going to
set all this off at once
so the general thinks
Blaine's militia is attacking.
Dana, you, Ken and I
will be on the other side.
We're going to enter
from the back lot,
take care of business.
Look, I know I screwed up when
it came to protecting this town
and I own that.
This is my chance
to make it right.
So, let's do it, uh?
Let's go save
the people that we love.
All right, I'm on it.
The angel! Look!
- Yeah, yeah.
- See, Mr. Abel was right.
Another one's coming.-
Man your stations!
It's beautiful.-
Whoa!
- Oh.
- I, uh, I brought you this.
- A sandwich.
Thank you. That's...
That's kind. I kind of assumed
everyone had just left me here.
Yeah, well, uh, I have
more questions for you, Blaine.
- Um...
- Okay.
You said that, uh,
on the night of Revival Night,
that Lester Majak called you
to tow a car
the same night
you saw that yellow light
shoot up into the sky
and the same night
that you saw Em Cypress
on the bridge.
I saw Em on the bridge before.
Right? I went to tow the car,
- I saw the light...
- Yes.
And then when I went back,
the light was gone,
but Em was no longer on
the bridge. Just her stuff.
-Em wasn't at the bridge.
Em Cypress was not there
when the yellow light
shot up into the sky.
You see, I've been studying
that water at Moore Creek.
It has special properties
specifically designed to
heal revivers.
It helps revivers,
specifically Em Cypress.
I've literally seen it
bring her back to life
and if that's the case,
if Em Cypress
is connected to the water,
that means that
she was murdered.
Which means that
Em's death caused Revival Day.
- She what?
- Oh!
- I'm sorry, brother, okay?
- Hey.
- This is for the greater good.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
- All right, now, hey!
- I'm walking out of here!
No! Go back!
Anyone moves, the doctor dies.
Rise and shine.
You're taking your medicine
early today
because we're going on
a little field trip.
I'm not going anywhere
or taking anything until
I can see Em Cypress
and make sure she's okay.-
So now you're in charge?
Hey, hey! Back off.
Let me talk to him.
I said I got this.
Give us some space.
This is going to feel different,
but you have to act the same.
Okay?
It's the only way to save Em.
Hurry up!
Now, you're going to behave,
right?
Help is coming.
Spread the word.
All right,
you know the drill! Let's go!
Single file, no talking,
as you were told.
- Where are they taking us?
- What are they going to do?
We're taking out
the guards at my cue. Pass it.
- We're going to take them.
- Wait for my cue.
- Up the ramp.
- Around the corner.
Up the ramp, in the truck. Move.
Single file.
Let's go, let's go.-
What the hell?
Everybody in the truck!
Get 'em in the truck!
Hey! You two! Go set up an
observation point. Now!
Command, this is Alpha 2.
Priority red.
I repeat: priority red.
We have an incoming
hostile force.
Small militia approaching from
the northeast. Over.
Let's go! Move!
Now! Fight!
Go! Go! Get 'em! Yes.-
You so much as twitch
and your skull is gonna have
a skylight.
Who are you?
Your sister sent me.
We have to go now.
The guards are coming.
Come on.
Where's Em?
- She's not here.
- She's still inside.
We gotta go back in and get her!
No time! They're coming out
the door any second!
We can't just leave her here!
We need to figure out how
to get her out of there.
-Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
We're getting the hell
out of here. Let's go.
- Dillisch!
- Where the hell are you going?
The only reason she's in there
is because of you!
You're the one
who called the governor.
Ken.
You're the one who
had my wife locked up.
You're the one who put all this
shit in motion, Wayne, not me.
- No, Dad! Jesus Christ!
- You two were best friends
and now you're at
each other's throats when
we need each other the most.
What the hell happened?!
What the hell happened
is that Wayne Cypress
is a goddamn home wrecker.
Ken, please.
-When Patty died,
ask him why he missed the call
from Nella at the bar.
Why he didn't come and
pick you up.
Ask him where he was!
I'm so sorry, Dana.
Dana.
-Save it for your memoir.
- Guys, we need to move now!
- We gotta go!
Get the revivers to Nella's bar.
- What about Em?
- I can't leave here without her.
I will take care of Em.
But they need you right now.
We need your help. Go.
Go!
- Dana.
- No!
- Not now.
- Clear!
We gotta go! We gotta go!
Look, Dana, your mother and I
were separated.
- I don't want to...
- I don't want... Just, mm-mm.
How could you not tell me?
Yeah, what would the point
have been?
Telling you?
I spent the last two years...-
beating myself up about Mom.
Em has spent the last two years
blaming herself for the accident
and you wanna know the po...?
Honey, me being with Diane
did not cause a deer to
run in front of you.
Should've been you.
Who the hell keeps calling?
It's Lester.
We need to focus on finding Em.
We need a plan.
JP and Nella are at the,
at the border
getting revivers out and, um,
Cale will be monitoring comms
so even if I knew who
I could trust anymore,
we can't call them.
So what do we do?
Well, just answer it. Answer it.
You just said the general
will be monitoring our comms.
Lester's just calling to
whine about something.
Who gives a shit?
What do you want, Lester?
Well, sure.
Now, I'm just minding
my own business
out in this nice brisk air
on my own property,
and wouldn't you know it,
we got some trespassers
that need taking care of.
- Trespassers? Really?
- I don't have time for this.
- No, no, no, sir.
- No, this isn't just someone
wandering around.
They have guns!
I think they might be
domestic terrorists.
Then call the station.
I already called them.
Well, then I'm sure
they're on it, okay? Goodbye.
No, no, no! Don't hang up!
They have a girl!
What do you mean a girl?
I don't know, but they keep
saying something about
the girl and
what do with the girl and...
Where are you?
I'm out on Route 13,
by the old church.
Stay put. We're on our way.
Where are we going?
- The old Abel church.
- Blaine has Em?
Don't know, but we better get
there before the general.
Where are we?
Ibrahim? What is...
going on?
Behold!
Martha Cypress,
you are the Mother of Babylon,
the serpent
who opened the gates of Hell.
And I
aim to send you right back.