- Previously on revival.
- Em healed me.
What do you mean she healed you?
- She's special, dad.
- I'm working through some stuff
and a friend said it'd be a
good idea to get closure.
Patricia cypress.
Can you see her, too? It was all my fault!
Anyone moves, the doctor dies.
He's found a way to kill revivers.
This isn't mine!
- Wanna go to the beach.
- On an adventure together.
- They have a girl!
- Where are you?
I'm out on route 13, by the old church.
In these dark weeks
we have heard over and
over this term: Revival.
A sacred word meant to
represent spiritual renewal.
That word has been hijacked and defiled
by a plague of revenants,
of revivers who now walk amongst us.
In revelations, John speaks
of the ancient serpent,
who, when he's cast out, the demons
are cast out with him.
And now I want you all
to bear witness as I cast out this demon
and end Satan's reign within wausau!
You couldn't keep me dead the first time.
You're not going to keep
me dead this time, either.
I never laid a hand on you.
But now my angel will.
You do know that my
father foretold this, right?
An angel of the lord
would reveal itself to me
and the day after revival
day it did, in the woods.
And it was
it was beautiful.
I'd never seen anything like it.
And then the angel...
Spoke to me.
In pained agony
it said Rose's name.
That's not an angel, Blaine.
That's confirmation bias.
You could put that on your radio show.
You see this?
The celestial cannot be
touched by human flesh.
I watched it obliterate a reviver
and send it back to the depths of hell.
Yeah. Yeah, I saw one, too.
But what I saw was it
connect with a reviver,
not in an act of damnation,
but in an act of reunion.
You so badly want your father to be right
that you're willing to
kill people to prove it.
I don't know if that's a
leap of faith or fear, Blaine.
Doug.
Clarice? Come in.
Anybody? What's the status?
What's going on over there?
Doug, come in.
The angel was supposed
to be here by now.
Get down to the creek
and find out what's going on!
Yes, sir!
The reviver woman.
The one you tortured.
You mean the one I exterminated.
What was her name?
Her name, doctor,
died when she did.
What came out of that
grave, that was a vessel of evil.
I saw the video, Blaine.
What did Wanda say?
What did she say before you killed her?
It's not mine.
She said, "it's not mine" over and over.
What does that mean?
See, in islam we believe
that when a person dies,
their soul is separated from their body.
And it enters an intermediate state.
A transitional barrier between
this world and the next.
That light that you saw on
revival night, that was em.
What if somehow her
death broke that barrier?
I mean, that's a...
A bold and spiritual
hypothesis for a man of science.
Well, science, it's about
being open to change
when presented with new evidence.
You see, you witnessed
something you can't explain, Blaine,
and you've assigned it a
variable based on conjecture.
Now, see, I would say
that I am a man of conviction
who's not going to stand idly by
as the gates of hell are at my doorstep.
Over here! Took you long enough.
Hey! Don't move!
Drop your weapons!
Sorry.
My god. Martha!
- Dad!
- Are you okay, baby?
Whoa, whoa. Hey! Right there is good.
You harm one hair on her
head, you son of a bitch,
I'll rip your lungs out, so help me
god? Is that what you were going to say?
So help me god? How poetic.
Coming from the man who
ran my father out of town,
destroyed our church.
Now you're going to be
here to witness firsthand
as my angel sends
this demon back to hell.
Wait!
She healed me.
Like, she healed you?
Yeah.
Just like Christ with the guy in the...
The walking problem.
- The guy with the skin!
- The leper.
The leper.
I was shot and I was stabbed
and she put her hands
over me and healed me.
So,
I mean, I guess that makes her...
Special, right?
Yes.
No!
Damn. Shit.
Dad. Dad.
- Now she can prove it.
- Dad.
Dad.
Damn it!
What?
- No.
- Did you give her the serum!?
I did! She must need a larger dose.
It's going to be okay.
Em, just stay calm.
Please, just stay calm. Please.
Yeah.
Okay. You can do this.
Just breathe, okay? You have to focus.
You have to breathe, em. Breathe.
I don't know why it's not working!
- Who's the charlatan now?
- Shut up, Blaine!
Take your sister and go.
Dad, stop, please! I think...
I think I just need to focus, okay?
So, what are you? Are you a healer?
You the oppressor? Do you even know?
I love you both.
I'm sorry. For everything.
You coward!
I love you both so much.
Em!
Em. Em, look.
You did it.
Em! Someone help. Em!
Blaine, I can save her.
Hey. I have a vial in my
pocket that can help her.
- What's wrong with her?
- Is she dying?
You say you're not a killer.
This is your time to prove it.
Free me and let me save her.
Sorry. I can't take that risk.
Put it down!
Hey, hey! Let's go! Let's go!
Release the reviver immediately!
Drop your weapons!
Put them down!
You've got nowhere to go, Blaine.
Your flock is dead.
Can you get these off?
Second team, prepare to breach.
All right, listen: This will help.
This will help but you have
to get her to Moore creek
and get her in the water, okay?
- We'll sneak out the basement.
- There you go.
Time to surrender, Blaine.
This is over!
This is our battle.
Do not surrender!
They have our angel!
Send her with me. I've got a place
right around the bend. It's the grist mill
downstream from the creek.
- Could-could that water help?
- Yes, yes, yes, maybe.
I'll get her to Lester's. See
if she gets her power back.
We need to get her to
nella and jp at the tunnels.
Go, go!
Drop your weapons!
I'll deal with the general.
She's my problem.
You get Cooper, get your sister well,
- then get the hell out of wausau.
- Okay.
- Dad, you need to be careful.
- I'll go to jp and nella.
- Go! Just go.
- Let's go! Let's go!
Come on.
Nobody gets out of here.
Where is she?!
How much further?
It's just up this way to the mill.
Do you need help getting her up?
Nah.
Strong as an ox.
Here. Keys to my truck.
Thank you. Hey.
Get your strength back, okay?
I'm going to go get Cooper
and then we're out of here.
Together.
Can we stop and split a doughnut
- from Friedman's on the way?
- You know it.
Go.
No, ma'am. Let me explain. Ye
yes, ma'am. I understand. I
yes. Right away.
We can still get them,
ma'am. Our mission is not over.
Delayed. Not over. Now go.
So, let me get this straight:
You lose all the revivers
and in an effort to get them back,
you mow down 12 civilians at a church.
And you're the one
who cleans up messes?
Command, this is bravo.
There's something you need to see.
What is it?
I think we found one.
Here, drink this.
Good.
Now, you just rest up.
I'm going to go check to
make sure nobody followed us.
Okay.
He's been like this ever
since I picked him up.
Just not talking, like,
like the joy's just gone
right out of him, you know?
He's been through so much.
I can't imagine what's going
- through his head.
- I know. I know.
Thank you so much for looking after him.
Are you kidding? Anytime.
He's a sweetie.
- Thanks. Just one sec.
- Yeah.
- Lester, how's em?
- She's okay.
Pretty worn down, but I
think the water helped some.
Might not be as potent
as what the doc has
but she's taken to it.
Okay. I'm grabbing
Cooper and I'll be right over.
Well, now, you might
want to hold off there.
There still seem to be a bunch of soldiers
just down by the creek. But, don't worry.
Em is safe and sound right here.
Okay, well, call me as
soon as the coast is clear.
Will do, deputy cypress. Will do.
- What happened?
- It's how we found it.
We think it's Wanda Peterson's.
Alert Alpha.
Our exit timeline just got accelerated.
And the sheriff?
Let him go.
We don't need him anymore.
We won't be going home
empty-handed after all.
Aw, Coop and I had so much fun, Dana.
We watched cartoons and he
showed me his comic drawings.
My goodness!
They are so good. He could
be a professional artist someday.
Jesus.
We even watched the bucks game.
But they lost to the pacers again.
But, listen:
I will look after him anytime.
Well, okey-dokey, smokey.
I think I got everything here for you.
Where did you get this?
What? That old snoozer?
I thought it was going to be
a rip-roaring romance novel,
but no such luck.
It's just a boring old book
about water, you know.
But people seem to
like it. He even did this
mind-numbing speech about it.
Hang on. You've seen
an Aaron weimer lecture?
Yeah.
Well, it's actually on a tape
around here somewhere.
Can I see it?
Many adherents see the river as
the earthly manifestation
of the goddess gang a.
They regularly attribute healing
and transformative powers
- to its flow.
- And why do you have this?
- This is all Lester's stuff.
- Wait, what?
Millions performing ritual Lester.
- What is he doing?
- Nothing!
You don't want to see this.
- I'm so sorry.
- Could you stop it?
Yeah, yeah. Oops, that's pause.
- Christ, Jeannie! Give me that!
- Is it coming out?
What? What? What?
What are you doing?
What, what? That?
My god. I hate that thing. It's...
He's Irish. It's Celtic,
or something like that.
Gives me the creeps.
Hello, Martha.
It was you?
You killed me?
Now, now, dear, just hold on.
It wasn't me. It was your professor.
Although that's a bit of a technicality.
No, no, no. I...
I saw the mask. You-you
knocked out Aaron
and you tried to kill me.
I should return the goddamn favour.
Wait!
Look... You could kill me,
but then you'll never know the truth.
You're weak, Martha.
But the water from the
creek helps you, no?
It makes sense.
It's one of a few places on the earth
where the membrane
between oblivion and awareness
is thinnest.
And it flows right through this very mill.
Please,
let me help you.
Why the hell would I trust you?
Because I need you.
The world needs you.
Why did I have to die?
You were never part of
my plan. That was all Aaron.
His infidelity and his wife's cancer
could both be solved by your death.
So, he picked you.
Tried to make it look like a suicide.
He was my partner at first, I admit,
but he was a sloppy, sloppy man
and he parked a car on my property.
And when I called Blaine to tow it,
I realized he was trying to cut me out
and steal our discovery
for himself and his wife.
But his poor choices
created, well, a mess.
I can take you down with me.
So be it.
I did my best to clean it up,
tie up Aaron's loose ends.
I bet you I could figure it out.
There was, unfortunately,
some collateral damage
of which I'm so regretful.
But I had to see this through
not just for me, but
for the world, Martha!
And try to do what?
What we are all trying to do. Live.
For as long as we possibly can.
So that's
what this was all for?
So that your old ass
doesn't have to die?
Not just me.
Can you imagine what it would be like
to give the gift of eternal life?
You didn't give life. You took it!
And not just from me, but from Rose.
Someone who had her
whole life ahead of her.
People loved her and
you stole that from her!
You killed two innocent
women. You-you killed me!
All for some power trip
that, given what happened,
you, you clearly...
There, there. Save your energy.
We didn't know what would work.
But we needed a vessel.
A young woman capable of creating life.
Rose was the first.
- And through her death...
- I've got her. -It would
allow us to open the door.
But then we saw the light
coming out from within her.
It was working!
And in a flash, it was over.
But it was enough to let
us know that we were right.
All those years, all the searching.
The research!
It was all finally within my grasp.
And that's why I bought
the mill and built all of this.
To do it right!
No one would laugh at me now.
Then your petulant ex-lover
decided he wanted to
try and steal it for himself!
This was supposed to be a sacred ritual
that demanded our
respect and Patience!
But he was so cocky and
thought he could just scoop it up
and take it home to his wife.
I couldn't allow it.
I would not be undermined by such a
pusillanimous mendicant!
Forgive me.
I don't normally lose my temper.
The irony of life is that it is lived forward,
but understood backward.
Listen to me, Martha. Look around you.
Rose's death, your death, led to life.
We have reunited families.
You did that.
Because you are so very special.
I'm not special.
You used me, just like Aaron and Blaine.
No, you are special.
You see, in order to unlock
the door to immortality,
you need a key and that key was you.
Something in you, Martha
cypress, caused all of this.
You weren't just a key,
you were a detonator
that blew the door right off!
You started revival day!
I am done with this and
with you. I will make sure
- you rot in prison.
- Don't you want to see it?
Behind those doors lies a part of you.
I couldn't let Blaine take
this one. He confused its purpose.
It's not his.
It's yours.
And if you open
yourself to it, it will come.
You've felt something missing
ever since you woke up, no?
Well, this will make you whole.
But you have to be willing.
The decision is yours.
What is it?
It's your soul, Martha.
Follow it to the water, Martha.
Let it fill the void inside of you.
I know this a lot to take in, Martha.
But you are special.
And if you venture into
the water, I'll prove it.
Mom?
Martha, come here.
It's okay. I'm here now.
I forgive you. Here's my
Martha. We can be together.
It's not your fault. There's my Martha.
- It'll be okay. I forgive you.
- I'm so sorry.
It'll be okay.
There's my Martha.
Put all this behind you.
Come with me and heal.
It's not your fault.
I forgive you. I forgive
you. We can be together.
I forgive you. My baby.
My perfect little miracle baby.
There you go.
Lester!
Something's wrong.
What's happening?! Em!
What's happening?! Em?
I... Don't... Know!
I don't know what to do.
It's okay.
It's o... it's okay.
We finally
got to have that adventure together.
Em. Em, em.
Em, em, no.
Em, please. No.
Say it. Say it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
No.
Em! Em!
Em!!
No. God.
She's over here!
Jesus.
Shut it down.
Dana. Dana.
Sheriff, no sign of Martha in here.
Are you okay? Where's Martha?
Where's Martha?
With revivers still among us,
how can we be sure that
history will not repeat itself?
Jamie, I'm going to nip this in the bud.
Revivers were not the problem then
and they're certainly
not the problem now.
As you may know, my wife is a reviver.
It's a fact that we had to, keep hidden
for the safety of our family.
But no one should be made
to feel unsafe or unwelcome
because of who they are.
Which is why the governor
is spearheading efforts to,
pass this new bill now
that ensures the rights of
all revitalized citizens.
I think there's still a lot of anxiety...
Coop, come on, buddy!
Confusion surrounding
the military's presence
and their sudden disappearance.
Well, I've been assured by
the governor herself that the,
whoa.
Cale's operation was unsanctioned
and that a special committee
has been established
to investigate the matter in full.
But I'm here to say, plain
as day, wausau is safe.
- Okay, all right, come on.
- Welcome back.
Cooper, we've got to go!
- Stop yelling, mom.
- Jesus!
You're really good at
sneaking up on me in here.
Sure you're ready for school?
I really miss em.
Yeah, I know. I know.
After school we're going to
go talk to Dr. Park again, okay?
You like Dr. Park? She's nice, right?
Then, tonight after school,
we finally finish unpacking your room.
I already packed it once.
Shouldn't you be the one
to unpack it now that we're staying here?
Sometimes life's not fair, Coop.
All right. Go catch the bus.
Off you go.
How you holding up?
Yeah.
About as good as can
be expected, I guess.
Well, look, maybe a little
time off will do you good.
Go fishing every morning.
I'm just glad it's you taking over.
You're exactly what the
town needs right now.
Interim. We'll see how things go
with the run-off election. I mean,
I'm not that good at politics
and all that baby-kissing shit.
And I was?
What's going on with
the ladder, anyway?
That's my first order of business.
You know that leak that Dana
was complaining about all this time?
Yeah, well, turns out
that it actually starts here
in your office.
Now, Jean Paul,
this is yours now.
You're the right man for the job, brother.
I'll see you down the road?
All right, bro.
Hello.
Hey, I, I come bearing gifts.
You should have.
I accept.
Well, how do I look? No big coat.
And me.
You look good.
You ready for your first day, professor?
Yeah, not a professor.
Just a short-term residency.
Yeah.
That's a relief. The last
cypress professor thing
didn't end well.
Yeah. I'm sorry about that.
But it does keep me
closer to Moore creek
so that I can continue my studies. So...
Is that the only thing
you want to stay close to?
Algae?
I-I better get going. I don't want to be late
- on my first day. It's no good.
- No.
- Ibrahim!
- Yeah? Yeah?
We should do it again sometime.
Do, do what exactly?
Dent a car and not leave a note.
Yeah, we should.
Sometime. I'll see you around.
[The past is never dead.
We stood on two legs;
and raised our heads
above golden grass;
he was there.
We sharpened stone and
steel; Used tools to harvest grass,
beast and brother;
he was there.
We clustered together; In brick and mud,
swarming with rats and plague.
He was there.
We built nations and mistrust;
our fingers hovered over the red button.
He smiled.
But still we build to rise
above the golden grass;
away from the reach of his scythe.
For a day
when he will harvest no more.
You had everything else.
There's just that one box left.
It really hit me going through her things.
I mean...
I miss her.
I do too.
I wish you hadn't told her
to go to the bridge that night.
Excuse me?
To get closure, or whatever.
Since she wouldn't have been taken
and revival day wouldn't have happened.
What are you talking about?
Em said a friend told
her to go the bridge.
You're her only friend. I did the math
and that sums up to you.
Okay, no. No, look, we-we became cool.
We became cool, but back
then we were just roomies.
It was probably one of
those online friends of hers
from live journal or
that o1, oi forum thing.
She was always chatting with them.
Hi, may. I need a favour.
Coop! Time for bed! Brush your teeth!
I know!
- Hey, dad. - Hey!
I was wondering if, you know,
maybe I could watch Cooper soon?
Dad, I-I don't think that's a good idea.
He's still...
Broken up about losing
em and he blames you for it.
I'm sorry.
We're navigating
everything with a therapist
and it's a lot right now
and I think we just all need a bit of time.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I get it.
Sure. Okay.
I should get him to bed.
All right. Okay.
Dad.
If you want to talk, you
know, just you and me,
we could talk.
You know...
All right. We'll chat soon, then.
Yeah. Okay. I guess so.
May, did you get my lead?
- You sitting down?
- Nope.
So, those message boards
you had me look into?
You'll never guess where
the ip address was from.
- The weimar house.
- Yeah, that tracks.
Aaron needed her on the
bridge to push the self-harm play
so he lured her there.
Well, what do you know about his wife?
Nithiya? Why?
She was the court-appointed
therapist for em, right?
Well, turns out she
wasn't assigned em's case.
She asked for it. In fact,
she went out of her way
to make sure she
would get em as a client.
Mrs. Weimar!