To all of our customers:
Management was
obligated to open your units.
Restitution will be made. Apologies.
Hola, señor.
Me llamo...
Hola, yo soy Carol sturka.
Estoy de los… United States...
leave me alone, you sons of bitches!
Fuck your mother, asshole!
Hi, Carol.
Can you hear us?
If you feel like responding,
all you have to do is pick up
the handset and speak into it.
It's got a push-to-talk button on the side.
Hey, Carol!
Works just like on Adam-12. Remember
how you used to love that show?
What?
Hi, Carol.
You left the hospital kind of
quickly. Is everything okay?
- Yep. Yes.
- Hey, Carol!
Just… just headed home.
Would you be more
comfortable in your range rover?
We can deliver it to you.
Also, we're happy to remove
the alcohol interlock device.
No.
Hey, Carol.
What are you doing here?
You're in my house? What the
hell are you doing inside my house?
Patching shrapnel holes.
Plus, there was a lot of
broken glass to clean up.
Well, who gave you
permission to be in my house?
You did.
Remember? When you were
riding with us in the ambulance
and we were applying a
pressure bandage to zosia's back.
And we asked you if you'd like
us to tidy up your house a little bit
and you sort of nodded absently.
Okay. Jesus, fine. Whatever.
Is everyone out now?
Yes. And we're almost done here, Carol.
But we could leave the finishing touches
for later and clear out now if you'd like.
Give you some space.
Do I know you?
Hi.
You're the fucking mayor.
Thank you for your vote.
I need a volunteer.
Not a politician.
You. Shorty.
Rest of you just take a… coffee
break, or whatever floats your boat.
Come with me.
Happy to.
Have a seat… what's your name?
Your name?
Well…
This individual went
by Lawrence j. Kless.
Or Larry to his friends,
of which he had many.
Whatever. Just… have a seat.
Do you like my books?
We love your books.
What do you love about them?
Everything. Your books are an
expression of you. And we love you.
Need you to be more specific.
Character arcs. Plot turns.
Yes. Yes. We love the
character arcs and the plot turns.
Which ones?
All of them.
No offense, Larry, but I
think you're bullshitting me.
Sounds to me like you haven't
even actually read my work.
But we have.
Gosh, where do we even begin?
In your first novel,
we greatly admire the description
of lucasia's gown on page two.
"Gossamer threads of the finest
shang silk shimmered like spun gold,
as if the sun itself were
showering lucasia's shoulders
"with resplendent kisses."
That made quite a few of us tingle.
Okay.
Ha.
How would you say my work
compares to… Shakespeare?
Equally. Equally wonderful.
You love my books as much as…
Macbeth?
Or much ado?
Yes. And Henry vi,
parts one, two and three.
Well, I mean, what about a
crowd-pleaser? Romeo and Juliet?
Wonderful. Have you read
the first quarto of 1597?
No, you haven't, but you
must. We'll bring you the original.
So, Larry, you are telling me
that you love the wycaro series
as much as the most famous
English language play of all time?
Carol.
When we think about a passage
from one of your wonderful...
stop using that word.
From one of your books.
We experience it through
many eyes. Many hearts.
Do you remember a woman
named moira McAllister?
Crazy moira from Kansas City that
sends me these dumb crocheted hats?
Right, of course. She's one of you now.
Yes.
Before she found your books,
moira was deeply depressed.
In fact, she was going to…
You gave her something to live for.
You made her life better.
That's how we see your work,
and you. Through moira's eyes.
What did Helen think of my books?
Tell me.
Helen loved you very much.
Not what I asked, Larry.
Spit it out. What did Helen
think of the wycaro books?
Carol, you expressly told
us that Helen is off-limits.
Yeah, but you know what?
Special dispensation this one time.
What did Helen think
of my wycaro books?
Larry?
She thought they were… harmless.
Harmless?
"Cotton candy" was the phrase
she used in her mind. Mostly.
Cotton candy.
Yes.
And as you know,
Helen loved cotton candy.
I don't actually recall Helen
ever eating cotton candy.
No. She consumed it four
times in her life, and each ti…
Yeah. You weren't there. But really…
Helen thought you knew
how to please your audience.
And she was so grateful for the
beautiful life the two of you shared,
that wycaro provided.
She was so proud of you.
What did Helen think of
my unpublished novel?
Bitter chrysalis.
What did she think?
Carol. This line of inquiry isn't…
- Can we talk about something else?
- I wanna know.
If you tell me, it'll make me happy.
Helen thought it was fine.
Fine as in good?
Or fine as in…
"Meh"?
Yeah, "meh."
What about the last 200 pages?
Helen stopped on page
137, paragraph three.
It's 489 pages long.
She read the last two pages.
Thought it wrapped up nice.
- If she hated it so much…
- she didn't hate it.
If she hated it so much, why
did she tell me to publish it?
Because she talked to val, and they
agreed that it wouldn't hurt your career.
And it would make you happy.
Out.
Hi, Carol.
Here.
Thank you.
You want this?
Do you like your police car?
Sure.
Fun fact, the police officer
who drove that vehicle,
his son's third-grade
teacher's husband's sister
was a chartered member
of the wycaro fan club.
Wow. Chills.
Listen, about the…
It wouldn't have happened if I had
had the foresight to understand that
you people are… generous enough to
give me actual explosives, and I regret it.
Please don't.
Well, I'm sorry you got hurt.
Are you up for answering
some questions?
Certainly.
About a week ago, the
undersecretary of ag…
Well, I mean you. I know
you're all one. I get the basics.
Anyway, all of you, in the
form of the undersecretary of…
You told me that you don't really
understand how all this works.
This joining. So my question
is, do you understand it now?
We have quite a bit more
insight into it now, yes.
So… is there a way to reverse it?
The joining?
Is there not a way to reverse it?
Zosia?
We want so much to
please you, Carol, but we…
We can't answer questions like that.
Right. Except your
non answer is my answer.
'Cause I don't think you can lie to me.
I don't think it's something you can do.
But you would definitely
tell me if the answer was no.
- We're sorry you're so troubled by this.
- Do I seem troubled?
This is me happy.
I mean, congratulations. You did it.
Soon enough you'll
understand everything.
And you will feel so much better.
Freedom falls.
You know what that means, don't you?
Of course you do. You know everything.
Tell me about it. Tell me about
camp fucking freedom falls.
You were sixteen. Beginning to understand
yourself. And your mother, she sent…
Yeah, go on. What'd she do?
She sent you to… a conversion
therapy camp in Covington, Tennessee.
Camp freedom falls.
You never forgave her.
Well… it was a terrible
experience for you.
The counselors there were some...
some of the worst
people I have ever known.
And they smiled all
the time. Just like you.
We're sorry, Carol. As for us, we
love and accept all beings equally.
Okay. If you're so accepting, then what
about what you're trying to do to me now?
Make me just like you. Even
though you know I do not want that.
You want to change us too, don't you?
Didn't you just ask if it's possible?
There is something else to consider.
We know what it feels like to be you.
To be alone. To suffer. We've been you.
But you've never been us.
- Everything all right, Carol?
- Yeah.
Can we help you find something?
Do you have any heroin?
Are you sure that's a good
idea? Remember last time?
What can I say?
Sophomore year was tough.
Course it doesn't hold
a candle to this shit.
Carol, you should know. We
have a whole wing of bodies here
recovering from physical addiction.
Some might not make it.
Just… food for thought.
What are you, my Nana?
Yesterday, you people
gave me a hand grenade.
Are you seriously gonna
begrudge me some h?
Unfortunately, this hospital
doesn't stock heroin.
We have other opioids.
Ones that were manufactured
under more regulated conditions.
Would oxycodone suffice?
The closest unadulterated
heroin is eight miles from here.
It's on its way.
See? Put your mind to it, and
you guys are better than domino's.
Where are the hypodermic needles?
Might we suggest
snorting the heroin instead?
It's been quite a number of
years since you've injected.
No. In for a penny, in for a pound.
I'm gonna sid vicious this shit
like it's the Chelsea fucking hotel.
It's just…
It's absolutely ineffectious.
- Ineffecti…
- what?
This just… this shit does not work.
I'm on my own.
I miss you. I miss you.
"'Don't', it said.
Dark slips and falling from
his clothing, a shadowy figure."
I think this could be a movie.
"She slowly turned to
face the raspy voice."
Listen. I'm not that bad.
And that fuckin'…
lady… lady pirate they sent?
Raban. I'm… I'm sorry. I mean zosia.
It's zosia. You didn't catch her
name because I knew her name. Zosia.
You're a fucking idiot.
Whatever.
How annoying is that chick.
Very, very fucking annoying. All smiley.
"Hey. Hi. Hey, Carol, we just…
we just wanna make you happy.
Blah, blah, blah."
She's like. "We're the whole
wide world, and we're stoked."
It's just life is one big, long
sunshiny walk in the park
"when you're one of us. Whoo."
No way. Nobody sane is that
happy. I call bullshit on that.
And why she gotta be
so goddamn fuckable?
We have a winner.
Hey, Carol.
Carol.
Hey.
You look…
Yeah.
Got a lot more color in your face.
Thank you.
We feel much better today.
Good. That's good. How
about some fresh air?
How was the heroin?
I threw it away.
Yeah. I wasn't in the mood.
Well, chickened out, actually.
Maybe for the best.
So…
When do they let you out of here?
I mean, when do you let you out of here?
Probably in a day or two.
Sooner if we need an extra bed.
That's great.
Hey, you know everything.
Whatever happened
to music in elevators?
- When did they stop doing that?
- Would you like some?
Sure.
Nice day.
It is. Thank you for bringing us outside.
Well, I know how much it
sucks being in hospitals.
Better out here, right? Little…
little sunshine?
Really, really nice.
What do you think the
temperature is? About…
80?
Well, it's currently
27.778 degrees celsius,
or 82 degrees fahrenheit.
The winds are three
kilometers per hour from…
From where?
From south… south-east…
Any chance of precipitation?
Percec…
Zosia, you with me? I need you to
answer some more questions, okay?
How do I reverse all this?
How do I reverse the joining?
No.
Zosia, how do I end this thing?
You… you already told me it's possible.
- We… no.
- Yes.
- Yes. Yes. You did. You pretty much did.
- No. No.
So, the hard part's over, right?
Now, all you have to do is tell me how to
put things back the way they used to be.
Come on. Tell me, tell
me. Come on, zosia.
Is it making you sad not
giving me what I want?
Is this making you sad? Don't be sad.
Tell me what I want to know.
Yeah.
Zosia, zosia.
Is there something I can do? Is
it something one person can do?
No, stop! Stop! Let go of her.
You can't touch me.
I have agency!
I have agency, and you can not interfere!
Back away from us!
Zosia, zosia. What is it?
Zosia, tell me what it… is it…
is it some kind of chemical?
Some kind of medicine?
Zosia, tell me what it is!
Please, Carol. Please,
Carol. Please, Carol. Please…
Zosia, tell me.
Tell me!
What is it? Tell me.
Tell me what it is.
Tell me. Tell me!
What… what's happening?
She's dying, Carol.
She's in cardiac arrest.
May we save her?
Yeah.
Excuse us, Carol.
Analyzing. Analyzing.
Shock advised. Stay clear of pa…