(FILM CREW CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY)
-CREW 1: Press play here.
-Okay.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
And that's the same songs
that we had?
-CREW 1: It is, yeah...
-Okay.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(PAPER RUSTLING)
OSCAR ISAAC: Hey,
can I talk to you for a second?
HAGAI LEVI: Yeah, sure.
What's going on?
-OSCAR: I was looking
at the original.
-HAGAI: Mm-hmm.
-In two, right?
-HAGAI: Yeah.
-OSCAR: And Marianne
in that one...
-HAGAI: Yeah.
She does have kind of
a different energy
at the beginning of the...
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
OSCAR: There's this great moment
where she goes into
the refrigerator and--
Like the equivalent
or something,
like a version of...
CREW 2: Right, here we go.
And go ahead.
-CREW 3: Do you
want the door open?
-(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(BELL RINGING)
CREW 4: All right.
Stand by to roll, guys.
-Let's get slate in. Okay.
-CREW 5: Ten seconds...
CREW 6: Marker.
DIRECTOR: And action.
-(RAIN PATTERING)
-♪ (MUSIC PLAYING ON EARBUDS) ♪
AVA LEVY: Daddy!
-Why can't I just call Mommy?
-(RAIN PATTERING)
JONATHAN LEVY: (GROANS)
Because, sweetie,
you already said good night
to Mommy.
You talked to her already,
remember?
But I forgot to show her
the picture I drew
in the kitchen.
Yeah, well...
she'll be here tomorrow
when you get home from school,
and you can show her then, okay?
-(RAIN PATTERING)
-(BIRD CHIRPING)
How do you know
she's gonna be here?
How do I know?
Because she is coming at noon.
Her train gets in
at twelve o'clock.
Close your eyes, kiddo.
(RUSTLING)
(EXHALES)
♪ (PIANO MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(HUMMING)
(SIGHS)
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(RATTLING)
-Hi. You're awake.
-Yeah, you know.
So, you made it out of there?
-Ah, yeah!
-JONATHAN: That's great!
I ended up taking
the nine o'clock.
JONATHAN: Fantastic!
Ava's gonna be thrilled.
I told her she wouldn't see you
until after school tomorrow.
Oh, yeah.
How's she been sleeping?
You'll do pick-up
in the morning? Yeah?
Uh, she's sleeping great.
That rain app you got is genius.
-MIRA LEVY: Good.
-She doesn't wake up anymore.
MIRA: That's great.
JONATHAN: So, how was the train?
Did you sleep?
MIRA: Uh... yeah.
Um, not really,
I-- I did some work, I read.
-It's...
-Good.
You just ditched the dinner
last minute?
Yeah. I told Ackerman
Ava was sick.
He was bummed,
but he really couldn't do
-anything about it.
-(JONATHAN CHUCKLES)
-Don't use that one too often.
-MIRA: Hmm.
(MIRA EXHALES)
So, you didn't eat.
You must be hungry.
You want a little something
to eat?
-MIRA: No, I'm not hungry.
-There's some pasta left over
from Ava's dinner.
It's not gonna win any awards,
-but, uh--
-MIRA: No, thanks.
JONATHAN: Okay.
Do we have a bottle of wine
open, by chance?
JONATHAN:
I don't know, let's see.
Yes.
MIRA: Thanks.
(PHONE CHIMES)
It's, uh...
Kate. She thinks I'm in-- Oh!
-West Coast for some reason.
-JONATHAN: Right.
How are she and Peter?
They doing okay?
Everything all right over there?
MIRA: Yeah, I think so.
Usual drama, nothing new.
-Why?
-(WINE POURING)
No, 'cause I tried to get, uh,
lunch with Peter the other day.
I had some free time, and just,
I feel like he's avoiding me.
He's just been blowing me off
the last couple months.
Did you ask him why?
I tried to.
He just mumbled something
about it being a busy time.
It's not like him,
he's usually really excited
to brag about
his latest adventures.
Well, maybe he's just
stressed at work.
Yeah.
You still mad at me?
(CHUCKLES) What? About what?
JONATHAN: You were pretty pissed
on the phone last night.
Oh, no, that was nothing. No.
JONATHAN: I texted you after,
but you were probably asleep.
Yeah. I was really wiped.
Anyway, sorry about what I said.
MIRA: Yeah, that's--
Really, please. It's nothing.
Just forget it.
It's not a big deal.
JONATHAN: Do you know
what I'm talking about?
You mean the renovation, right?
JONATHAN: Yeah. In the attic.
So, anyway, I-- (SIGHS)
I was just trying to say,
it was that...
I get that
it's a really busy time
-for you right now,
with all the acquisitions...
-Yes.
...and all that, which is fine,
but the thing is that...
you know, you left it mid...
-MIRA: Mm-hmm.
-So when the desk's upstairs,
but my books and all my papers
are downstairs,
-I can't really, you know...
-I know. You're right.
You're right, you're right.
-(JONATHAN CHUCKLING)
-And, as I said on the phone,
um, it's your office,
so you decide what you want.
Yeah. But I don't--
Mira, it was your idea,
the whole renovation's
your vision.
-I know. Yeah.
-It just doesn't make sense
that you suddenly don't care
what part of the house is like--
I'm sorry, I'm doing it again,
I'm blaming you.
-It's okay, you can.
-JONATHAN: No, no, no. I...
All I'm saying is that
it is fine for me
to come back downstairs, okay?
I will move the desk myself...
and that's fine, that's it.
And then you just finish it up
whenever you have the time,
and that's okay.
And I'm not being
passive-aggressive.
I really mean it.
I'm-- I'm happy to do that.
-Okay?
-Okay, fine.
(CHUCKLES)
Okay. Cool.
Cool. Then it's settled.
Oh, man, watching you eat that
is making me so hungry,
I'm gonna polish off that pasta.
(SNIFFS)
(FRIDGE CLATTERING)
(CLEARS THROAT)
What?
I didn't say anything.
Everything okay?
Mira, what's the matter?
I, um...
I came back tonight
because I needed to talk to you
about something.
Okay.
I'm here.
I fell in love with someone.
It sounds stupid.
It's so stupid.
(SIGHS) Maybe,
maybe it's stupid. I don't know.
I met him in September,
uh, in, uh, San Francisco.
He's the CEO
of an Israeli startup
that we're buying out.
He-- he's...
Israeli, from Tel Aviv.
He will be relocating out here
at some point. I mean, not...
exactly here, it'll probably be
the New York office,
but I don't-- I don't know
which city it's going to be,
but either way, he will be...
(CLEARS THROAT)
...moving to the States.
He's not someone you would think
too highly of, I bet.
He's not really an intellectual.
You'd probably, I don't know...
make fun of him.
(EXHALES HEAVILY)
I don't know how it happened,
it just-- it happened.
I felt terrible about it.
But it was good for me.
(CLEARS THROAT)
It was-- it was really good.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
Please, say something. Please.
What do you want me to say?
MIRA: I know it's unforgivable
that I didn't tell you
about it earlier.
I mean, I just-- I couldn't.
And, um...
I didn't know
what was gonna happen.
I guess I thought
that you would find out
on your own at some point.
How was I supposed to find out?
MIRA: I don't know.
You didn't...
(CLEARS THROAT)
Haven't...
You didn't feel anything?
No.
Well, that right there might be
a sign of something, I guess.
Right? (CHUCKLES)
-(COUGHS)
-(GLASS CLINKS)
-Sorry.
-You okay?
-(COUGHS)
-Here.
-Here, let me...
-(SNIFFS)
(WATER POURING)
Here, just drink this, okay?
Okay, please?
So, what am I supposed to do
with this information here?
I don't know. I...
I thought that it would pass,
but it hasn't.
(SIGHS)
So it's still...
it's still going on?
Like, right now?
Yeah.
And you're gonna keep doing it?
I don't know.
Yes.
Yeah.
So why are you telling me
right now?
MIRA: I don't--
I thought you should know.
JONATHAN:
Why are you telling me tonight?
-Why--
-I'm going to Tel Aviv,
uh, with him, tomorrow night.
-JONATHAN: What--
-I have to go. I have to go.
Just for a little bit. I don't
know for how long, and...
I'm gonna talk to Ava
in the morning,
and I'm gonna tell her that,
um, I have to go away for work,
which is true. I...
Someone has to oversee
the transition.
(SIGHS) Ackerman and I spoke,
and we both agreed
that I would go-- I would do it.
So I am leaving tomorrow night
at 10:00 p.m. from JFK.
What do you-- why does Ackerman
need you to leave tomorrow?
MIRA: No, it's not Ack--
It's not about him.
It's because Poli's go--
What?
That's his name. It's, um...
short for Poliakov,
his first name's Saul,
but everyone
just calls him Poli.
He's going tomorrow.
I'm gonna go with him, so...
(SIGHS)
You already bought a ticket?
Yeah.
I mean, now that I'm talking
to you,
now that I'm in this house,
it's, uh...
it seems crazy. (CHUCKLES)
Nothing could be crazier.
It's just...
it's really surreal. It's...
But at least now you know.
Now you know.
-That's a relief, I guess.
-I don't know anything.
I don't know
what's going on here.
I told you what's going on.
I don't...
I don't know what else
that I can say. It's...
Okay.
(DISHES CLATTERING)
Go ahead, I'll be right up.
(PHONE CHIMES)
♪ (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
♪ (TUNE PLAYING ON IPAD) ♪
JONATHAN: You have marks
on your back.
What?
Sorry.
MIRA: Uh, I need
some things for the...
Did you have a chance
to pick up the dry cleaning?
-No, no, I didn't.
-MIRA: That's okay.
You can pick it up yourself
in the morning.
Yeah. I'm not sure
I'll have time.
I wanna be with Ava until
I drop her off at preschool,
and then I have to run
to a meeting,
but it's okay. Never mind.
How long are you going for?
MIRA: I don't know. It depends.
JONATHAN: On-- on what?
Is it something that you're...
-still trying to figure out?
-Three months.
JONATHAN: I see.
Okay.
And, uh...
What about Ava?
Have you thought about...
I'll see her
every other weekend.
-Got it in the contract.
-JONATHAN: You will?
It'll be a long weekend,
Friday to Sunday, so...
Flight's 11 hours,
not the end of the world.
I'll get a hotel nearby
and she can stay with me.
And then there's Skype
and there's FaceTime,
I mean, we--
I could talk to her every night.
It's a seven-hour
time difference,
so when she gets home
from preschool,
I'll be home from work.
People do this.
I won't be the first,
or the last.
Men do it all the time,
and then, you know, it's not
really a big deal, so...
JONATHAN: Okay. As long
as you've convinced yourself.
I don't care
if I'm convincing anyone.
I don't give a shit.
You can think I'm a monster,
think whatever the fuck
you want, I don't care!
(RAIN PATTERING)
This can't-- I just--
I can't do this right now.
Let's talk about this later.
I can't-- I just--
-I can't do it right now.
-When's later?
MIRA: When I get back.
-So in four months?
-MIRA: When I get back,
we will, you know,
set something up in advance
with a couples therapist
or a mediator,
and we'll-- we'll start
some sort of process.
JONATHAN: A process of what?
MIRA: Of detachment.
Detachment?
What the fuck is detachment?
It's a separation.
You want a divorce?
Maybe. I think so.
But we don't have to do it
right away. I think it's best...
that it's gradual,
-so that Ava isn't...
-(JONATHAN SCOFFS)
Yeah. Gradual, gradual.
You're leaving her overnight.
-I'm not leaving her.
-JONATHAN: Really gradual.
Don't say that. I'm leaving you.
I'm not leaving her.
Yeah.
Try explaining that to her.
MIRA: I will. I'm gonna tell her
that I'll see her in less than
two weeks from today,
and-- and, you know,
when I'm back from this trip,
we're gonna be together a lot,
you know, all the time.
(CHUCKLES) All the time.
I mean, maybe the three of us
can start this process,
you know, over Skype
with a family counselor--
I'm not really interested in
going along with your process.
MIRA: Okay, fine.
-We won't do it.
-Good.
Whatever you want.
I mean, I can't force you
to do anything, so...
I'm just gonna take
some clothes.
That's all I need.
And of course, I'll pay
for all of the help
that you need, obviously.
-Okay. Thank you.
-MIRA: You don't need to worry
-about anything.
-Sounds great.
MIRA: When I get back,
we can talk about the rest,
but I'm sure we'll work it out.
I don't wanna fight you,
Jonathan. I just wanna leave.
Okay. Well, you know what,
if it's really that urgent,
why don't you just leave
right now? Go ahead.
Leave if it's so urgent for you,
just-- you can leave right now.
Urgent? Do you know how long
I've wanted to leave?
JONATHAN: I'm not really
interested in knowing.
Every day for eight months,
every morning,
I've woken up with the knowledge
that I cannot be here anymore.
That I have to go.
But I didn't go. I stayed.
So don't talk to me
about urgent.
I fought this for months.
You were so busy
with your own anger,
you didn't even notice.
What? What-- what--
what did I not notice?
That I was miserable.
(PANTS)
And we never even
talked about it.
The abortion? We...
we talked about it for days.
We...
-It's what you wanted.
-I know.
I thought that it was going
to protect what we had.
It was for us.
And then Kate saw
that I was in bad shape,
so she took me to dinner,
she set me straight.
She was like,
"Who has an abortion
to save their marriage?
What kind of marriage needs
an abortion to save it?"
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
MIRA: She's right, though.
It was the other way around.
I was terrified
that if I had another kid...
then I could never leave.
(SCOFFS)
(SIGHS)
Why didn't you talk to me
about it?
MIRA: I couldn't.
You couldn't either.
-I couldn't?
-MIRA: No.
You were so angry at me,
you couldn't even admit
that you were angry.
How were we supposed to talk
about anything?
Okay.
Let's talk about it right now.
-MIRA: No.
-Let's talk.
-It's too late.
-JONATHAN: Come on, let's talk.
Jonathan, it's too late.
It's too late.
JONATHAN: Mira.
Mira, I know that I've...
I've made my fair share
of mistakes, okay? And I take
-responsibility for that.
-No.
No. No, no, don't go there.
-On this position, I--
-MIRA: You don't have
any responsibility.
You didn't make any mistakes,
and I didn't any mistakes,
and...
(SIGHS) ...we're not gonna get
into blame because if...
we do that, I will go crazy.
So this isn't anyone's fault.
It's just the way that it is.
This is the way that it is?
-What the fuck is that?
-MIRA: Yeah, it's the way
that it is.
It happens to everyone.
It's so predictable,
it's practically a cliché.
I mean, so let's not get
into the blame game
or where we went wrong
and all that,
-because it's not about that.
-What is it about?
I'm trying to explain to you,
but you keep trying
to figure out
where you went wrong,
what this has to do with you,
but it's not about you.
-JONATHAN: Okay.
-It's not.
Well then, tell me.
What is it? What is it about?
MIRA: I don't know how.
I mean, can you understand
what it means to feel like...
like I'm lying here at night
and I...
just feeling like I'm...
I had a crazy thought
the other night where I just...
I thought of checking
my own pulse
to see if I was still alive.
Can you understand that?
Like there's no oxygen,
like you can't breathe.
-Do you under--
-Yeah, yeah. That I--
-That I can understand.
-Yeah, well, yeah.
Of course you can. So imagine
like a constant asthma attack.
Entire days...
where you just feel...
suffocated,
and the whole time,
I'm just thinking...
"Is this it?" It's like...
Is this all I'm gonna have?
Just like...
this?
Without any...
feeling?
Without feeling?
When you're in this house,
you don't--
-No.
-You don't feel anything?
That's not what I meant.
I love Ava so much, and I...
I love you.
I didn't even know
what the problem was
until this happened, and...
then I remembered what
it was like, and now I...
I can't go back.
You can go back.
You can,
-you just don't want to.
-No, I can't.
I can't.
I tried a hundred times.
Believe me, I tried.
Over and over. I can't do it.
I know you think I'm spoiled
and I'm pathetic.
Look, I don't think that.
I don't know why you--
Well, maybe I do.
(SIGHS)
I thought I was better than this
but I guess I'm not.
Mira, please, this is bullshit
and you know it.
-No, I don't.
-(SIGHS)
I mean, you've known me forever.
How long did you think
that we could just, like...
go on like this? Just...
living without any...
JONATHAN: What? Without what?
I don't know, just...
-Passion.
-JONATHAN: Uh-huh.
-I hate that word. It's--
-Right.
It's-- it's really--
it's embarrassing,
it sounds pathetic,
but, you know...
that's, uh...
-Who is he?
-(EXHALES)
What?
JONATHAN: The guy.
I wanna hear about him.
Why? What good would that do?
I wanna know.
Why? Why do you wanna
torture yourself?
Do you have a picture of him?
Of course you do.
-Can I see it?
-Jonathan, no.
-Please, let's not do this.
-Please?
-Not right now. Don't--
-Yes, yes, right now. Right now.
I'm asking to see a picture.
Okay.
(SNIFFLES)
(JONATHAN SNIFFLES)
This is recent?
MIRA: About a month ago.
How old is he?
Twenty-nine.
JONATHAN: What does he do?
-I told you, he runs a startup.
-JONATHAN: Right, right, right.
He's tall?
MIRA: Yeah.
Is he married?
No. Single.
(RAIN PATTERING)
So, um...
how'd you meet?
At that party on the boat
after we...
-closed the deal. Yeah.
-JONATHAN: Right, right.
Yeah, yeah.
I remember that party.
So, how did it happen?
What do you wanna know?
JONATHAN: How it happened.
He walked up to me and...
he told me that he liked
the way that I was dancing.
JONATHAN:
Since when do you dance?
I haven't in a long time.
But there was, uh...
I'd had a lot to drink,
and there--
and there was
a lot of coke there. So, yeah.
(INHALES)
I was dancing and, um,
he came over.
Mm-hmm. And?
And...
he said that I was the first...
American woman he had met
who wasn't constantly trying
to please everyone,
who didn't need to be liked.
JONATHAN: Hmm.
MIRA: And then we talked
until 2:00 in the morning.
And then what?
And...
then we kissed.
And then, um...
(SIGHS)
...we went up to the room.
His room?
MIRA: No, my room.
Your room, okay.
And then what?
-Honey.
-JONATHAN: Just tell me.
It was mostly funny at first.
-It was funny?
-MIRA: Yeah.
Um, I was just--
I was laughing hysterically.
It was really awkward,
and... (SIGHS)
But it was also liberating...
to laugh like that.
JONATHAN: Mm-hmm.
MIRA: And then we didn't leave
the room for two days.
I told, uh, everyone I was sick.
I-- I told you that too.
And then I came back and I...
prayed that you couldn't see it
on me, but you were...
you were just so happy
to see me happy again,
and calm, and...
We started having sex again too.
Yeah.
-JONATHAN: Does he know that?
-No.
Every day, I told myself
it had to stop, every day.
I couldn't do it.
(SNIFFLES) And I even told him,
I told him I wanted out, but...
I couldn't go through with it.
He wouldn't let me go.
(SNIFFLES)
-JONATHAN: You can still end it.
-Uh-uh.
-JONATHAN:
You just don't want to, Mira.
-I can't.
-JONATHAN: You can.
-I can't. I'm in love with him.
-You're in love with him.
You're in love with him.
-MIRA: I'm happy with him.
-Yeah. I'm in love with him.
-Okay.
And he's good for me.
I am-- I'm happy again.
You've seen that. I mean,
even people at the office
have said
that I'm finally
like myself again.
I'm so vibrant, and...
even Ava. I'm--
I mean, you saw
how we got-- we got so close,
and it's like suddenly I--
I had so much patience for her.
I'm not-- Honey, I'm not
saying this to try to hurt you.
I'm just trying to explain,
like, why I can't give it up.
If I-- I'm gonna go
out of my mind
-if I don't leave right now.
-Right now?
-Like, right this second?
-MIRA: Yeah.
If I don't leave right now,
I know I'm never going to.
(BREATHING SHAKILY) So...
I just-- I wish you could like
listen to yourself for a second
'cause if you could,
you'd think you're nuts.
No, don't patronize me.
-It's crazy.
I'm not trying to patronize you,
I'm not.
I'm just telling you
that this is not you.
-MIRA: It is me.
-You don't talk like this.
-It's absolutely me.
-JONATHAN: It's not you.
You're not this person.
You don't do shit like this.
Just without thinking.
It's insanity,
what you're doing.
-It's not insanity. It's me.
-It's gonna leave you--
It's me! If you think it isn't,
you haven't been listening
to me all this time.
I'm listening. I'm listening,
and I'm trying to understand.
-I'm trying. Believe me.
I'm trying to understand, okay?
-MIRA: No, you understand.
You understand. You're just
trying to convince me to stay,
-and I don't wanna be convinced.
-All I'm asking for you
-is to postpone the trip...
-No.
-...for a few weeks.
-I can't.
Just-- Yes, you can, you can.
It's more than reasonable
for me to ask you to do that.
If it's really meant to be
with this guy,
a few weeks is not gonna
make any difference.
You need to think
about Ava for a second,
if not about me.
-Don't say that. Please don't.
-JONATHAN: What?
What exactly do you think
is gonna happen here
every day and every night
while you're gone?
Have you thought about that?
-Will you think about that?
-MIRA: I think that you...
are the best dad in the world,
and I think that I'm...
(SOBS) I just...
(BREATHES SHAKILY)
It's gonna be the best
for her too.
JONATHAN: How could you--
how could you possibly say that?
MIRA: (SOBS) Because it's true.
(CRYING)
(CRYING CONTINUES)
JONATHAN: Sweetie.
(MIRA SNIFFLES)
JONATHAN: Honey.
We can survive this.
We can get through it.
We can talk. We know
how to talk to each other.
MIRA: You'll never forgive me.
(SNIFFLES)
I think I can.
We can...
I think we can...
we can get through it together.
We can...
go to therapy. We'll, you know,
maybe it'll bring us
closer together.
(SNIFFLES)
JONATHAN: We have something
so real between us,
something so big.
You've been so good
for me, honey,
and I know that I've been good
for you.
-I know I have.
-You have.
Then let's not just blow it
all up in an instant.
Okay? Just think about that.
-It won't work.
-JONATHAN: Why? Why--
How-- how can you be so sure?
Because it ended so long ago.
Okay. You-- Listen,
you have to give me
a chance here.
You have to give me a chance.
You can't just...
This is cruel,
doing it like this overnight.
You know, I...
-I don't deserve this.
-No, you deserve so much more.
I'm telling you, honey,
I really think
that this is gonna be
the best for you too.
-What?
-Yeah. You...
you think that you're gonna
be lonely
like you were before,
but I'm telling you,
honey, you're not
that guy anymore.
You have Ava now
and it's really--
it's gonna be good for you.
I mean, you're not happy
with me like this.
You haven't been
for a long time.
I mean, there's no way
you haven't felt that.
-(CRIES)
-Don't-- don't--
don't tell me what I feel.
I thought everything was okay.
Don't put that on me.
-I'm not-- I'm not--
-That-- Yes. Yes.
I think you are.
You're putting that on me.
Honey, please. Let's just talk
in the morning, okay?
It's just not helping.
It's so painful.
It's like everything
we're saying
is just more and more pain.
(MIRA SIGHS)
(CLEARS THROAT, SNIFFS)
(SNIFFS, CLEARS THROAT)
(COUGHS)
-(SNIFFS)
-(MIRA SOBBING)
(CRYING)
(RAIN PATTERING)
I'm so ashamed.
(CRYING)
(BLANKETS RUSTLING)
♪ (VIOLIN MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
(WIND HOWLING)
(CLOCK TICKING)
(BIRD CHIRPING)
(MIRA SIGHS)
MIRA: Hmm.
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(WATER RUNNING)
(JONATHAN COUGHS)
(MIRA GRUNTS, SIGHS)
Could you hand me
my towel, please?
Thanks.
(TOOTHBRUSH WHIRRING)
(SPITS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
(SNIFFS, CLEARS THROAT)
MIRA: (GRUNTS)
I'm taking the Bric,
I'm gonna leave
the small suitcase here.
(GROANS)
(MIRA MUTTERING INDISTINCTLY)
(CONTINUES MUTTERING)
(SIGHS)
(CLEARS THROAT) Okay.
(MUTTERING)
Okay... (CONTINUES MUTTERING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Okay.
-(GRUNTS)
-Just let me do it.
-No, I got it.
-Let me help you.
Okay. I'll take some stuff out,
it's fine.
Let me do it. Let me do it.
It'll just take a second.
It'll just take a minute.
(SIGHS)
(CLATTERING)
Let's just move this.
MIRA: Okay. That's good.
That's enough.
Jonathan, please don't--
-Just-- It'll take a minute.
-Don't do this.
It's gonna just take a minute,
you're gonna rip it.
-Give me one second.
-Let-- Okay, stop it.
-No! I don't want you--
-JONATHAN: Stop.
It'll just be a minute.
(CLEARS THROAT, SNIFFS)
(CLEARING THROAT)
(CLEARS THROAT)
(SNIFFS)
♪ (TUNE PLAYING ON IPAD) ♪
(CRYING)
♪ (SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
-(JONATHAN COUGHS)
-(COFFEE MAKER WHIRRING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
JONATHAN: You want a coffee?
Yes, please.
Thanks.
(COFFEE MAKER WHIRRING)
I can't do it.
I can't wake her up.
(POURING)
Well, let's just get through
the morning and...
we'll see, you know, maybe...
we could talk to her together.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Just-- just do everything
gradually. (CLEARS THROAT)
(EXHALES SHARPLY, COUGHS)
(COUGHING)
-(COUGHS)
-MIRA: Oh.
(COUGHING)
-(COUGHS)
-I'm not doing it. Whatever.
-(INHALER CLATTERS)
-(MIRA MUTTERING)
-(EXHALES SHARPLY)
-(FOOTSTEPS RECEDING)
(LUGGAGE THUMPING)
Calm down, calm down...
Have you seen my, uh...
the carry-on
that I came back with?
JONATHAN: Mira, will you
just sit down for a second?
You know, I'm gonna pick--
pick her up today after school.
Um, yeah, I'll have time
before the flight.
I could-- I'll take her
to Vaniglia,
maybe I'll talk to her there,
and then you could meet us
-to take her home.
-JONATHAN: Veronica's already
planning to pick her up
from school today.
It's okay, I'll call her.
I'll tell her everything
-so that way you don't have to--
-Where are you going?
-It's 7:00 in the morning.
-MIRA: Uh, to the office.
I called a car.
It's-- The office
is still closed.
MIRA: Well, I've got a key.
Will you please just listen
for a second?
(SIGHS) What?
JONATHAN: This is, uh,
it's just surreal.
-It's delusional.
-Yeah, I know.
Then, no. No, I don't accept it.
We're gonna sit here
and we're gonna talk
as long as it takes, okay?
-MIRA: We talked last night.
-No. No, we yelled at each other
for an hour, that was--
that's not the same thing.
MIRA: It's not gonna do
any good. I mean--
It's not gonna do any--
What is this? What is this thing
-where we can't talk
to each other, Mira?
-(PHONE BUZZES)
I want to talk to you, and
-you don't want to talk to me.
-No, you don't want to talk
to me.
-What kind of cruelty is that?
-You want to keep me here
at all costs.
I want to talk to you.
I want to...
I want to sit here 'till there's
smoke coming out of our ears
and we've--
we've gone through all of--
all of the angles and figure out
where we went wrong
and how we can fix it.
I'm not attracted
to you anymore.
How do you fix that?
(JONATHAN SIGHS)
Mira.
Jonathan, please,
let me go, please.
(CRIES) Please.
(MIRA SNIFFLES)
(SOBS) Let me go.
(CRYING)
Let me go.
Jonathan.
(BOTH SOB)
MIRA: I'll text you
when I'm with Ava.
♪ (MUSIC INTENSIFIES) ♪
-(LUGGAGE CLATTERING)
-(JONATHAN SOBS)
Ready to go?
Let me get that for you.
♪ (MUSIC STOPS) ♪
(JONATHAN SIGHS)
♪ (TUNE PLAYING ON IPAD) ♪
(BREATHES SHAKILY)
(PHONE RINGING)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
The number you have dialed
is not available.
Please leave a message
after the--
(PHONE RINGING)
PETER: Hey, Jonathan.
-Hey, Peter.
-PETER: Hey!
How's it going?
Um, can you put Kate on
for a moment?
She's not answering the phone.
PETER: Sure. Is anything wrong?
No, I'll talk to you
in a second, just--
Could you--
could you put her on?
PETER: Uh, sure.
Uh, just a second.
-Thanks.
-PETER: Hold on.
-KATE: Good morning.
-Kate, hey, good morning.
KATE: Good morning.
Hey, so, listen, um,
look, I-- I know that, um,
-that you know...
-KATE: Know what?
...about the whole thing
with Mira.
KATE: Oh.
-Kate?
-KATE: Um, I'm sorry, Jonathan.
No, no, Kate, Kate, hey,
hey, it's-- it's okay.
I-- I understand, I know
that you couldn't, and, um...
look, I just, uh-- (SIGHS)
So, basically, Mira just left.
-KATE: How do you mean? Like...
-She, um...
She got in last night,
and she just left
for the office,
and she's going to fly out
to Tel Aviv...
tonight. Yes. And, uh...
KATE: I'm sorry,
but if you two--
No, I-- I-- I--
I know that you don't wanna
be put in the middle of this,
and I just-- I just need you
to talk to her,
and-- and convince her
that she needs
to postpone this trip
just for a little bit,
-you know? (CHUCKLES)
-KATE: Postpone...
Yeah, just for like a couple
of weeks
so that we can talk
about this calmly,
and, you know,
maybe go to therapy,
and it's just-- it's insanity
doing it like this overnight.
KATE: Well,
she's not doing this...
Did-- did you try to talk
to her?
KATE: Yes, I tried. But she
wasn't really listening...
Then why didn't you
tell me about it
before this thing turned into
a fucking shit show?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Kate, Kate, I need--
I need you to--
(CLATTERING)
-PETER: Hey, Jon.
-Hey, Peter.
PETER: Why don't we come over
and then--
No, I don't-- I don't need you--
I don't need you to come over...
PETER: I can be there--
...because it's not gonna help
at all.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Yeah, yeah, it is. It is.
By the way, how long
have you known about this?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Fucking--
And it did not occur to you
to let me know about this,
with all your
"honesty" bullshit?
PETER: Look,
Kate's the problem--
No, don't-- don't blame this
on Kate. Don't blame it--
I-- I called you yesterday, man.
PETER: I didn't wanna hurt you.
You didn't wanna hurt me?
Fuck you!
Fuck you! Fuck the both of you!
You're both pathetic!
You--
(SCREAMS)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
-(SNIFFLES)
-(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(JONATHAN SIGHS)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
♪ (SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
-(SNOW SETTLING)
-(BIRDS CALLING)
♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪