And who might you be?
- Who are you?
- I already told you.
I wanted to let Jesus Christ
into my life.
I have a feeling you'll be meeting
Jesus quite soon.
The only question is
how much it'll hurt before you do.
What the fuck kind of priest are you?
Please watch your language.
Fuck you, motherfucker.
There's no call for profanity.
Spend some time
with our confused friend.
See if you can show him the light.
Well, I thought he'd never leave.
See, now, that won't be necessary.
Shut your mouth.
- Fuck me.
- Down!
Get him! I need him alive!
Fuck!
Ah!
Like that.
Good morning, everybody.
- Hey, Mom.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- That's sick! I love it.
- That's pretty cool.
- How did you sleep?
Good.
- Do you like it?
- Yeah.
Me, too. It's awesome.
Hey, you know what?
Let's go outside and try it out.
- You gonna do an awesome trick?
- Oh, yeah.
I think you are.
I miss this.
I missed you.
Do you think
we could ever get it back?
I don't know.
Probably not this,
but maybe something different.
Something better?
I'm sorry I lied to you.
I know.
Sometimes when you live
with a lie for long enough,
it starts to feel like the truth.
- Hey, Alma.
- Hey.
Proctor arrest. You up for it?
Sure looks like a lot of paperwork.
How much is it gonna cost me?
Are you kidding me?
- It's Proctor. It's on the house.
- Thanks.
Besides, we both know
you would just screw it up.
- Hey, Emmett.
- Sheriff.
- You come for these?
- No.
- I don't deserve that badge.
- Come on.
No one deserves it more than you.
Have you heard back
from the D.A.'s office?
You let me worry
about the D.A., okay?
- Listen, what I did to those men...
- They had it coming.
- Not from me.
- Well, if not from you...
Listen, Emmett, there are rules,
- and then there's what's right.
- And then there's God.
Yeah, God kind of takes all the fun
out of the argument.
This job is doing something to me.
I can't risk becoming the man
I was last night.
- So, what are you gonna do?
- Meg's sister lives down in Florida.
We're gonna head down there
for a while.
See what it feels like.
I hate to lose you.
You know,
you may have everyone else fooled,
not me.
How's that?
I know you're a good man.
It's been an honor
to work with you.
You, too.
Dr. Hadman to E.R. Bay 13.
Hey, man,
give me some fuckin' morphine.
I'm dyin' here.
I've been ringing this bell
for a fuckin' hour already.
Where the fuck do you people go?
Oh, shit.
- That's right.
- You gotta tell Proctor
I didn't tell them anything.
By the time they came to me,
they knew all about it.
What the fuck are you doing?
That's my fuckin' morphine drip!
You won't be needing that anymore.
You were paid to transport
Mr. Proctor's merchandise
and keep your mouth shut.
You chose to speak to
the authorities.
As such, Mr. Proctor
has asked me to inform you
that your services
will no longer be required.
Get the fuck away from me...
What are you doing here, Sugar?
You came to see me
when I was inside.
I'm just returning the favor.
Seeing if there's anything you need.
Yeah?
And where was your friendship
while Hood was making his plans?
A simple warning
is all I would have needed.
Hood, he doesn't consult with me.
Yeah?
Would you have told me
if he had?
Kai...
I've known you
since you were a kid.
We may not be friends,
but in some way,
we're still family.
We're not family. Not anymore.
You made your choice.
And don't come back.
Kai, it doesn't have to be this way.
Yes, it does.
I forgave what I could,
given the years you lost for me.
But when I get out of here,
and I will get out of here,
I'll be coming for Hood.
And if you're standing between us,
I'll cut you down,
without a second thought.
You shouldn't have come here.
Hey, boss, we might have a glitch
with Proctor's case.
Just get your son and go.
You can't ever come back here.
Why are you helping me?
I know what it feels like
to be trapped in your own life.
I went to check on Juliet.
She missed her shift at the Savoy.
- And what about you?
- I made my choice.
- Thank you.
- Just go.
I swung by the day care center.
Apparently, she pulled her son out
in the middle of the day.
The director there had a feeling
she's not coming back.
Smart girl.
What about your case
against Proctor?
She was never gonna testify.
Anyway, we've got a stronger case
with Longshadow.
Hi.
He has a list of people
Proctor extorted to clear the land
for the new casino.
And you think Longshadow's gonna
see that through?
He wants Proctor out of his hair
for good.
The charges against my uncle
will soon be dropped.
You've nothing to worry about.
But I am worried, Rebecca.
I don't doubt for a moment
Proctor's lawyers
will buy his way
out of a few gun charges.
The cops have papers
linking him to the Kinaho Moon
and I can't have that.
That sounds like something
you should talk to him about
when he gets out.
- Why now?
- What?
Proctor. Why now?
That's why I'm here, isn't it?
I don't know why you're here.
I've been trying to
pinpoint in my mind
what it is about you.
Procedure, protocols, laws,
you just don't have patience
for any of it.
Rebecca,
your uncle has had a long run...
But his luck's about to run out.
I don't think that they're gonna
take him down for this,
I know it,
because I'm gonna help them do it.
Why are you telling me this?
It's time for you to make a choice.
Why me?
I like you.
The warrant is specific
to the basement
and excludes any and all other rooms
of the house.
So, it could be argued
that the subbasement
in which the contraband was found
wasn't on the warrant and is,
therefore, inadmissible.
- Would that work?
- 50/50.
Depends on the judge.
And meanwhile,
I'm pushing for a new bail hearing.
The ADA is arguing flight risk.
But all the new ones do that,
so I will push it through.
It'll just take a day or two.
What about Longshadow?
Well,
that's a whole 'nother ball of wax.
You sure he's gonna
go through with it?
He seemed very sure.
Yeah. Well, we'll have to see
what he's got.
Until then, my number one priority
is to get you out of here.
So I will call you
as soon as I have anything new.
Thank you.
Rebecca,
I will wait for you outside.
What is it?
It never rains, but it pours.
You're worried about Alex?
Well, he picked a hell of a time
to grow some balls.
Well, can't Sperling
do anything about that?
Maybe.
Uncle?
Just go home, Rebecca.
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
Okay.
You've got another visitor.
Mother.
Hello, Kai.
You look tired.
I'm not tired.
Just older.
Why are you here?
A mother hears her son is alone
and in trouble.
Well...
I've been alone
for many years, Mother...
For my entire adult life.
As have I.
Does my father know you're here?
Your father demands contrition
from everyone except himself.
As I get older,
I have far less patience
for arrogance
disguised as righteousness.
- And yet you stay.
- And yet I stay.
I was not raised to think
there was another way.
By the time I came to it on my own,
I was an old lady.
I failed you, Kai.
I let the dogma of small-minded men
determine your fate
when I should have been
protecting you...
The way any other mother
in the world
would have protected her young.
And now I see you in here,
and I know
that we put you here...
Your father and I.
Your crimes,
whatever they may be,
are my crimes.
May I come see you again?
Yeah.
Can I help you?
Captain Julius Bonner, NYPD.
So you are not here to pray?
No.
Just doing a little legwork
for the FBI.
- Where is Agent Racine?
- They don't seem to know.
Maybe that's why
they asked me to drop by,
to see if maybe you knew.
I haven't seen Agent Racine
in a while.
He was not a healthy man.
But he did come in here
from time to time.
Yes. He was looking
for my brother.
I take it you haven't heard from him,
either.
If I had,
do you think I would tell you?
No, I guess you wouldn't.
I don't suppose you'd allow me
to search the place.
Yes, of course,
as soon as you show me your warrant.
Why all this interest?
Surely you have more pressing cases.
Oh, yes.
But you never seem to forget
the one that got away.
I almost nailed him
a long time ago.
I picked up this kid
doing a job for him.
Diamonds.
It's for you.
Turns out
it was Rabbit who tipped us off.
I tried to turn the kid,
but he was,
you know, committed.
Everyone must live or die
by their own code.
Of course.
Well, you have a good day, Father.
Have a good day.
They're closing in...
The intruder last night,
now this cop.
They will be here soon.
I had hoped to be a bit stronger
when I faced them.
It was a mistake
sending the assassin after them.
We should have waited
until you were healthy.
The only mistake was her failure.
You could not have foreseen that.
- Who the fuck are you
- I'm a nurse, man.
What about this intruder?
He proved more resourceful
than we imagined.
There are only
so many hospitals in the city.
We will find him.
- Which one?
- New York Presbyterian.
- Was I shot?
- No, dude. You got hit by a car.
We have to assume
he will get word to them.
He was badly hurt.
He may not get word to anyone.
How long have I been here?
I don't know.
My shift started at noon.
- Are the cops here?
- Why would the cops be here?
I have called everyone in.
We will be ready for them.
Wait, what the hell are you doing?
No, you can't get out of bed.
Tell me where
my fucking clothes are.
You can't go anywhere.
- They're gonna fucking kill me, man.
- No one's gonna kill you.
They're gonna fucking kill me.
You have a serious concussion.
You can't go anywhere.
- The fuck I can't.
- Please just get back in the bed!
- I need some help in here!
- Get the fuck off me!
Hey, sorry to keep you waiting.
It's all right. I just got here.
Hey, Laura,
can I get a cup of coffee?
A few days ago,
that building blew up.
Word is it was an ecstasy lab.
Proctor?
Well, not that we can prove,
but, yeah.
Thanks.
I've requested a forensics team
from the DEA,
but first they gotta
find us on a map.
So I'm guessing
this is not a defective gas line.
Mm-mm, truck went through a wall
and then the place went sky-high.
Is that it?
I mean, why are you showing me this?
Because the day before this happened,
I was out there with Hood and Emmett.
We shook down some guys.
We found out this is where
they're making the drugs.
And Hood desperately
wanted to tie it to Proctor,
but we couldn't.
And then it blows up.
Just like that.
And then he busts Proctor
on a warrant
based on information
from a confidential informant.
Exactly. And I wouldn't bet
the farm on that warrant.
Shit.
What the hell is he up to?
George.
Long day?
The only kind I seem to
be having these days.
Drink?
That was some stunt
you pulled with the council.
Oh, George, don't be a sore loser.
Men voted their consciences.
Well, I'm sure you've heard
that your good friend Proctor
has once again been incarcerated.
Proctor's no friend of mine.
As a matter of fact,
I'm taking measures to make sure
he goes down for the count.
Maybe I underestimated you.
But maybe you underestimated me, too.
This dagger
belonged to my great-grandfather.
It's handed down as a totem
to the first-born male
of each generation
when he comes of age.
So far, every man in my family
who has carried this knife
has had occasion to use it.
Of course, I have no sons.
Is this your occasion, George?
Is that why you're here?
I didn't think so.
It's hard to know
when I realized it.
Little girls love their fathers.
And mine was so loving,
so attentive.
And he kept me in this little world,
and I had no other reality
to compare it to.
So what changed?
Kids in school.
They started to tease me.
And you know how kids can be.
Then this one day,
I was walking home from school...
And I passed by a newsstand.
And my father's picture
was on the front page of every paper.
So I bought a copy and I read it.
And I didn't understand much,
I was about 11,
but I understood enough.
They were saying that my father
had had people killed.
So I took the paper
and I put it on his pillow...
And I went to sleep.
And then the next morning,
he was sitting in my room
in an old rocking chair
I had in the corner,
just rocking back and forth,
staring at me.
And for the first time in my life,
I was scared of him.
Jesus, Carrie.
But then he picked me up...
Put me in his lap,
and I was barely awake...
Kissed me on my head,
and just rocked me back and forth
and I almost fell asleep again.
He was my daddy.
Hey.
That's enough.
You'll have plenty of time
to tell me the rest of it.
- Yeah, I should get going.
- No, no, no. Shh.
No.
No, you shouldn't.
You okay?
Yeah. I'm just thinking about Emmett.
Yeah.
I just can't believe
he lost it like that.
Well, I don't think he did lose it.
I think he made a conscious choice.
They hurt his family...
- He needed to make 'em pay.
- We would have made them pay.
Yeah, but he needed it
to come from him.
Think of it like you and Breece.
Look, there is a point at which
any one of us will do
exactly what Emmett did.
It's just a question
of what puts us in that situation
where the circumstances
outweigh the consequences.
We go to the Cadi every day
and we're supposed to be
dealing in justice,
but...
All we're really doing
is enforcing a set of rules.
But justice,
real justice...
Is personal.
Sometimes the only way to get it
is with your own two hands.
You scare the shit out of me
when you say things like that.
You're the one that wanted me
to talk more.
Yeah, I'm starting to
have second thoughts.
You're the only sheriff
that doesn't answer his phone.
What?
You need to get your ass
to New York now.
Job?
I'm in deep shit here, man.
Whoa, slow down, slow down.
Where are you?
In the hospital is where I am.
New York Presbyterian, room 307.
And if Rabbit get here first,
I'll be...
You found him?
Yeah, I found him.
Now he gonna find me.
I'm on my way.
- What? What's wrong?
- I have to go.
What, just like that?
You don't think I'm entitled to
more of an explanation than that?
Yeah, you are,
but right now I just don't have time.
Well, are you coming back?
- Not tonight.
- How about ever?
I don't know.
- Then don't go.
- I have to.
I don't think I can do this anymore.
I mean,
I don't even know who you are.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Hello, Brock.
Shit. Sorry about that.
- It's fine.
- Wasn't expecting anyone, clearly.
Don't worry about it.
What the hell are you doing here?
I got the night shift.
I have to leave town tonight.
- Where are you going?
- It's not important.
- For how long?
- I don't know.
You're in charge.
Yeah, because that worked out
so well last time.
Hood.
Who the hell are you?
You're a good man, Brock.
Take care.
Are you expecting anyone?
It's okay. I got it.
Are you expecting somebody?
Hood, what the hell is this?
- Carrie here?
- Are you serious?
If she's here,
I need to see her now.
- Go fuck yourself.
- Gordon, it's okay.
- Yeah, the hell it is.
- What is it?
- What?
- Job found Rabbit.
- Oh, my God. Where?
- New York.
Job's hurt. I'm going now.
- I'm coming.
- What?
- Give us a minute.
- We have to go, now.
Give us a minute.
Gordon, honey...
Look, this is your first night
back in this house.
- I know, but if Rabbit's in New York
- None of this shit makes any sense.
I know it doesn't.
But I have to do this,
to protect us, to protect our family.
- If we're gonna have a chance...
- And how are we gonna have a chance
when he keeps showing up here?
What is it with you?
Why is any of this your problem?
Don't look at her,
I'm the one talking to you.
I don't have time for this shit.
You can stay here if you want.
- I gotta go.
- Hey, stop fucking talking to her.
- Don't you turn your back on me.
- Gordon, stop it!
- Fuck you!
- Jesus Christ!
Now, how many times
are you gonna ruin our lives?
- This has nothing to do with you.
- Gordon, put the gun down.
- You don't understand.
- What, are you protecting him?
- No.
- What the hell is this?
Are you fucking him?
Is that what this is?
- No, it isn't.
- Then what the hell is it, then?!
If he doesn't get that gun
out of my fucking face,
- I'm gonna fuckin' kill him.
- Stop it.
You're gonna kill me?
I don't think so.
I don't give a fuck what you think.
You show up at my house
- looking for my wife...
- You don't know what's going on,
- so back off!
- I will blow your fucking head off!
- Last chance!
- He's Deva's father!
What?
What did you say?
Gordon...
Gordon?
I will tell you everything.
But right now I have to go.
I have to go.
Why?
Because I have to kill him.
Or die trying.
I meant what I said.
Either he dies or we do.
Nothing less.
I couldn't agree more.
Is that any way
to greet an old friend?
- Asshole.
- Can you move?
- Barely.
- Come on, let's get you...
Oh! Fuck!
Shots fired on the third floor.
Request police backup.
Drop your weapon!
Help!
Drop it! Drop the gun now.
Come out and drop the gun now.
I'll kill her.
No, you won't.
What took you so long?
- He had a friend.
- How about a little less talk
and a little more
getting the fuck out of here?
Shit.
Let's move.
I want men in all four stairwells.
And be careful. The shooter
might still be in the building.
You two, with me.
I want you to head down there,
make a loop.
We'll meet back up at ICU.
Son of a bitch!
Move, move, move!
So what the hell were you thinking,
trying to take him out on your own?
I saw an opening and I took it.
Would have finished him right there
if it hadn't been
for that psycho priest.
- Priest?
- Yulish.
- What, you know him?
- He's my uncle.
I never met him,
but my father used to talk about him.
I always got the feeling
that he was scared of him.
Are there any members
of your family
who aren't homicidal maniacs?
- We'll go in tomorrow.
- I know the layout.
- I should come with you.
- You can't even stand, Job.
It's just a concussion, man.
You get them every day.
The inside of your head
must look like a Jackson Pollock.
Can't have you slowing us down, okay?
It's not exactly an arsenal.
Yeah, we had to leave
in a bit of a hurry.
Hey, Pony still dealing guns
in these parts?
Only dealing Pony's doing
is blowjobs in Sing Sing.
But you know who is still around?
You think?
I'd have heard
if someone took him out.
Who?
An old friend.
He's using a very liberal definition
of the word friend.
Think he'd remember me?
The question is,
do you want him to?
Your men?
They are dead.
Then they have come.
Yes.
I spent 15 years
searching for my daughter.
And now she hunts me.
Tell me, Yulish.
Do you really believe in God?
I do, yes.
To me...
God always felt
like something men made up
to feel less alone.
And now...
I am more alone
than I have ever been.
I don't trust you.
I don't give a shit.
And instead of wishing for God...
I am praying...
That He does not exist.
Because if He does...
Dead or alive...
There will be no peace for me.
My sins will follow me
beyond the grave.