I've been thinking.
It's probably time
for me to be moving on.
Where would you go?
What would you do?
Best thing I can do
for you is to leave.
Bad shit happens to people
standing too close to you.
The rules are different out here.
No, same rules.
Same rules they had since the first
man picked up the first stick
and beat the second man's ass
with it.
People like you and me,
we don't need bars.
We build our own cells.
Every time I think
I know the way forward,
something just kicks me
back on my ass.
I don't know what's coming next,
but it's coming.
Who the hell left this here?
It's not from around here,
I can tell you that.
Big shot thinks
he's got a fancy freakin' car
and he can block the pump.
It's like he's telling
the world he's hot shit.
Ooh-whee.
This is one fine-ass machine.
- I have to piss.
- Do it quickly.
We're on a schedule.
Must have cost a fucking fortune.
What's the matter?
It ain't gonna bite you.
My apologies, gentlemen.
I'll just get that out of your way.
Oh, shit. It's 007.
Nah, it's Austin Powers.
Well, 00-homo,
why don't you take your ride
and get back to
your own fucking country?
You know,
you shouldn't be smoking
at a petrol station.
Safety first, fun later.
Who the fuck do you think you are?
Fuck!
Alex Longshadow.
What brings you around?
Anything you want to say,
you can say in front of her.
George Hunter wants me out as chief.
And?
And they have the votes to unseat me.
Sounds to me you have
a real problem there.
If Hunter becomes chief, you can kiss
any piece of that casino good-bye.
Hunter won't let you near it.
Yeah, well, you always said
that you wouldn't either.
I'm young,
as you so enjoy pointing out.
My mind can change.
- Get me the list.
- List? What list?
Of the council members
who will vote against you.
- They meet next week.
- That's plenty of time.
- Okay. Thank you.
- No, don't thank me.
After all, we're partners.
Partners, yeah.
Hey.
The new you.
Passports, credit cards,
IDs, the works.
- Buddy, buddy, buddy!
- All right, all right.
Oh, man.
Just keep it safe, okay?
This is great.
- Don't fuck around with it.
- Thanks, man.
Don't thank me. Thank Job.
Sorry, friend.
We don't open till noon.
Gentlemen, I'll have
what my young friend Jason is having.
Hello, Jason.
Um, I said we're not open.
Where's the money, Jason?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
- You know who I am, right?
- Yeah.
Then you know I mean it
when I tell you
this is the last time
I'm going to ask.
Where's the fucking money?
Hey, Sugar.
Don't you have some sort
of house rule about guns?
- Yeah, no guns.
- Right.
You hear that, Clover?
No guns allowed.
Well, then,
I think we might have a problem.
Hey, Hood!
- You all right?
- Yeah.
What money?
Why is the casino
so important to you?
I mean, you've got
all these other businesses.
Just seems like a lot of trouble.
I have no illusions about what I am.
These other businesses,
they'll either kill me
or I die with them.
Either way, I leave nothing behind.
And since I have no children...
So the casino, being protected from
local law enforcement,
offers me the shelter I need
to do something legitimate.
You know, something that
will live on when I'm gone.
Now do you understand?
Yeah.
Go on.
Sheriff Hood and I
were having coffee
when this one guy chases
the other guy through the door.
Have you ever seen
either one of them before?
Never. They were arguing
with each other.
Deputy.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
See, the one guy,
he had a thick British accent.
Who fired first?
You know, you really got to start
taking better care of yourself.
I'm still in one piece.
But the day's just started
and the shooter's still out there.
Hey, I'm fine.
Okay?
We got an alert out for his car.
A red Jag, right?
Yeah. Yeah, should be
easy enough to spot.
Holy shit.
Uh-huh.
Is it just me,
or does it seem like every scumbag
with an automatic weapon
comes to Banshee to shoot you?
- No, it's just you.
- Huh.
You all right?
Yeah, thanks for asking.
Did you get a good look
at him, Sheriff?
- Good enough.
- Yeah, 'cause you just
happened to be here
when the shooting started, right?
- Yeah, I live here.
- Yeah, I guess that much is true.
What?
Maybe now's not the best time
to give the sheriff a hard time.
- I mean, he just got shot at.
- Come on, Emmett.
You don't wonder why this shit
keeps happening with him?
Sure, I do.
But you know he's still the boss.
So you don't question
anything that he does, huh?
Maybe that's the difference
between us.
No, the difference between us is
you still haven't wrapped your mind
around the fact that he's in charge.
What I want to know is
who's gonna pay for this stuff?
- Who's the English guy?
- His name's Quentin.
Quentin, he's an enforcer
for Brantley.
Brantley? That's the guy
you stole the money off, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Dude, I've only seen
Quentin once before, okay?
But the guy's a fucking legend.
They sent four guys for him once...
Wow, great story. What did you take?
It was like a drug payment
or something. I don't know.
Brantley's into a lot of shit, man.
Look, I was just supposed
to pick up the money
from some guy in Eugene
and run it back.
- But you ran off with it instead.
- Yeah, because I had to.
Look, I saw some shit
I wasn't supposed to see.
Brantley...
Brantley's a paranoid fuck.
Look, I knew I was getting sent on
some sort of errand that I wasn't...
- supposed to come back from.
- Shut up. Shut up.
How much are we talking?
62K.
- Jesus Christ.
- Yeah, I know.
- I fucking panicked, man.
- Shut up.
Where is it now?
I figured, like,
if I got far enough away,
they'd have to forget about it.
Forget about it?
They're never gonna forget about it.
These guys have rules.
There's only 49 here.
You're 13 short.
- Where is it?
- I spent some.
I've been using it to live off
since I left Oregon.
You must have lived
pretty fucking well.
God damn it.
- I've got to get out of here, man.
- And go where?
- He's still out there, though.
- Go where?
Where are you gonna go?
He followed you across the country.
He's gonna find you.
What are you gonna do?
I'm so fucked.
There's no way out of this.
All right, hey, hey, hey.
Listen to me. Hey.
Jason, listen to me.
I'll figure something out, okay?
Just calm down.
In the meantime,
you don't leave this room.
- Say it.
- I stay in the room.
Good.
- Maybe clean it up.
- Yeah.
Eyes forward.
Watch your position.
She's such a freak.
And her mother
is a total whack job.
Hi, baby.
You can't be here. You know that.
I couldn't help it.
I wanted to see you.
Mom, no.
Deva, watch your speed.
You can't keep doing this.
Sneaking into the house
and leaving me little toys.
It's creepy.
Deva, slow down right now.
I'm sorry I lied to you.
I was only trying to keep you safe.
Deva, brake!
I didn't have a mother
to keep me safe.
Please slow down. Slow down!
Brake!
Pull over right now!
Honey, it's me.
Deva, please slow down! Please!
I don't know who that is.
Hey, Sugar.
How you doing, Brock?
Uh, pretty good, you know.
Just trying to track down Hood.
Thought you had radios for that.
Yeah, well, you know Hood.
He never keeps his on.
And I was just passing by, so I...
Man, that was something yesterday.
How you holding up?
I didn't get a belly full of lead.
Yeah, well, I've got to head back.
So, good to see you.
Yeah, I'll tell Hood
you were looking for him.
All right, thanks.
- Are you all right?
- I'm okay.
We were screaming at her...
- What the hell happened, Deva?
- Nothing. It was an accident.
That's crap.
You could have hurt someone.
You could have killed someone.
What are you thinking?
They were talking shit about Mom.
She freaked out.
She started going super fast.
- She almost killed us.
- I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
You could have killed those girls.
Hey, you talk to me.
Your freak show of a kid
put my daughter in danger.
You say another fucking
word about my daughter
and I'll feed you your fucking lungs.
Got me, you piece of shit?
- Mom.
- Max.
Come here. Oh.
I didn't know you were coming.
You didn't? Didn't Daddy tell you?
I mean, he said you were coming,
but he didn't say when.
I'm here now. Come here. Mwah.
- How are you?
- I'm so happy to see you.
- Deva's not home.
- Know what, buddy?
This time, I came just to see you.
Go show me that trick again.
- Let me see.
- All right.
- You found this in his apartment?
- Yep.
Why would the sheriff have
a picture of your family?
I have no idea.
And what about these guys
that shot at him yesterday?
Well, we haven't ID'd the stiff yet
and one of them got away,
so we don't have much to go on there.
Gordon, you all right?
Yeah, sure, Brock. I'm great.
On top of the fucking world.
Hey.
You asked me, remember?
Look, I'm sorry. I'm just...
I'm not at my best these days.
Listen,
you let me worry about Hood,
all right?
I feel like things might be starting
to break there a little bit.
We just got to be patient,
wait for them to break a little more.
- All right?
- Yeah, all right. Thanks.
Nice spot.
Sheriff Hood.
Myself, I stopped drinking
some years ago.
I didn't make a very good drunk.
Some might say
I made an excellent one.
Either way,
I now feed booze to the birds.
For some reason it soothes me.
You're not exactly
keeping a low profile.
And you don't fight
like a small-town sheriff.
You, my friend,
have the sort of skills
that can't be taught, only acquired.
We were all something else
once upon a time, eh?
Guess so.
Men like us,
we've every reason
to appreciate a day like this.
Men like us?
Fighters.
Killers.
Armies of one.
I don't know anything about you,
but I know everything
I need to know.
The way we live our lives,
we know every day could be our last.
Sooner or later, it will be.
The sooner, most likely.
Maybe, but right now
let's talk about the money.
When I figure I'll have to stay
in a place for a bit,
I like to check out
the local law enforcement.
It's a practice I've developed
for some years.
A little due diligence.
Well, when I discovered
the sheriff's name was Hood...
that complicates things.
How so?
In any other case,
you and I might be able to
work out some kind
of professional courtesies.
But a father's not gonna
give up his son.
You're not leaving town without him.
No.
I have a strict mandate
to bring the boy
and the money back to Brantley.
He likes to deal with this sort
of thing up close and personal.
So...
So, one of us
is gonna have to kill the other.
Which is a shame, really,
since neither one of us
made this mess.
You know, in my experience...
there's usually a deal to be made.
I have a similar experience,
but in this case,
I don't really see...
50 on top of the 62 the boy owes.
So you're offering me a bribe?
Not a bribe, a token.
I'd give you more if I had it.
50,000, you go back,
you tell them he's dead.
You and me...
we both get to live
another day in the sun.
- What's that?
- That's the 13
to go with the 49,
make up the 62 you owe.
Wait, you're giving me your money?
No, I'm giving it
to Quentin, and this.
- What are you doing?
- We have an agreement.
I mean, I can't let you do this.
Really? Come on, cut the shit.
When do we bring him the cash?
Not we. Me.
- What do I do?
- You get on a train, go to Canada.
Live your life.
112,000, all in.
- Don't want to count it?
- Just make sure you keep your end.
I will.
My condolences, then.
What for?
You just lost a son.
- Yes, I did.
- Let's hope so.
For all our sakes.
Why are you helping me?
You're not the first guy
to make a mistake.
Things happen.
Mr. Procter.
Juliet,
I told you many times before,
call me Kai.
You're here for your money?
- If that's okay.
- Of course.
- I'm sorry.
- No, no, no.
Don't ever apologize for
asking for what you're owed.
It's just that sometimes I get
a little behind on the rent, so...
It's fine. It's all fine.
Payroll is next door.
Why don't you come with me?
Uh, actually,
I need to go pick up my son
from the babysitter soon.
So I should probably
just get out of here.
Just stay a little while.
Fuck!
Hello, Jason.
Get your knickers on.
So it went smoothly?
I guess so.
- And now you're broke.
- Temporarily.
That's a lot of money
to give a stranger.
Why the kid?
It's not like you owe him anything.
No.
But maybe I owe his old man.
Hmm.
Got rats in the basement.
Fumigated a few weeks ago.
Thought they were gone.
Turns out they only wanted me
to think they were gone.
So now I'm bringing out
the big guns.
Played by a bunch of rodents.
Hey! Hello!
Now I thought we had a deal.
If you thought that,
you wouldn't have followed me, eh?
True. I guess we're both
full of shit, huh?
I suppose so.
The kid in the trunk?
Yeah.
- Hello!
- You all right, kid?
You know,
you could have been
a long way away by now.
I couldn't do it.
Professional pride fucking with me.
Fair enough.
So what now?
You're no small-town sheriff.
Nope.
- Hello!
- Hey.
Let's go.
Dad.
Dad, you're drunk.
No, I just had some drinks.
Come on.
We're almost there. Two more steps.
I've got it.
Two more steps.
Back to bed, Max.
Now.
Are you okay, Dad?
I'm good, Max. Just go to bed, okay?
- It's okay.
- Dad's okay.
It's good.
Dad.
I'm sorry.
I took this off your father
before I buried him.
I don't know why I kept it.
Just didn't feel right
to throw it away.
I thought you should have it.
Yeah.
There's a train,
leaves tomorrow at 10:00.
I'll be by at 9:30 to pick you up.
You get on the train, you go north.
You go all the way to Canada.
Even you can't fuck that up.
Okay, yeah, I got it.
Uh-huh.
What about you?
Who knows?
Maybe one of these days,
I'll be getting on
one of those trains myself.
Huh. Not yet?
- Not yet.
- Hey...
Thank you.
Just remember,
you only get one second chance.
I know.
Here's your toast.
Sure I can't get you anything else?
No, thank you.
I haven't seen you before.
Are you new?
Uh, I just moved from New York.
Most people go
in the other direction.
What, do you got family
in Michigan?
Just needed a change.
What can I get you, Mr. Marine?
My name's Gordon Hopewell.
Carrie.
I know.
Don't say anything.
What can I get you?
I'll take blueberry pancakes
and some syrup.
You got it, honey.
When did you first figure out
your father was a criminal?
I heard you were on
the way out of here.
Not without saying good-bye.
So you put the pieces back together?
Yeah, just about.
Be nice to keep it that way.
I'm just here to thank you.
Well, then, one for the road.
Hey.
Nobody needs to know your plans.
It's my last night in town.
I'm just trying to make it count.
You don't want to go there.
See, that one's
more trouble than you know.
It's the good kind
of trouble, all right?
What?
Nothing.
This is nice.
Yeah.
What are you thinking about?
I don't know.
I was thinking about something
someone said to me the other day.
I mean, you get used to
a certain way of being
and, uh...
Do you think we are who we are?
Or do you think we can change?
What, you mean people like you?
Well, me, you,
people in general.
I don't know if anyone
ever changes, really.
But we can evolve, right?
I mean, that's what
we're trying to do, isn't it?
Just become better versions
of ourselves.
So you think we evolve?
I'm counting on it.
You're either with me
or you're not.
Do you understand?
You okay?
I'm fine.
Long day?
You have no idea.
Hmm, you know,
my mother used to say
even a train got to stop sometime.
I'm gonna make you
my Last Call cocktail.
Why don't you make it a double?
No, I'll make it
any damn way I want to.
Here.
- Nice.
- Where's mine?
Hey, Job.
How was New York?
I see you got your ass kicked again
while I was gone.
It's starting to be a thing.
Every man needs a hobby.
Do I even want to know?
Probably not. How'd it go?
How'd it go?
You couldn't get rid of them?
There was a wrinkle.
I should have found out everything
there was to know
about those diamonds
before you went in.
Where they came from.
Rabbit fucked you.
He fucked you hard.
You served 15 years
for stealing a handful of glass.