I thought you said
you disabled the alarm.
I did, both of them.
But I didn't think you'd take so long
to open the goddamn safe.
Are you gonna bitch about that now?
Ana, what the fuck?
Go. Get out of here.
Hood! Hey!
- Yeah?
- You got 'em?
- No, no one came this way.
- They ran right towards you.
Shit, they must have doubled back.
Come on.
So when did you two become a duo?
- I needed the money.
- Yeah, we all need money.
That's why we work together.
It wasn't that kind of a job.
Oh.
Oh, okay.
Not that kind of job.
You need to tell me
when you're out there.
- I don't need your permission.
- You do around here.
What if it had been
one of my deputies that found you?
- Your deputies?
- Yeah.
Jesus. Do you hear yourself?
It was a big risk for a small take.
- It was fucking stupid.
- I needed the money for Max.
Look, I could have helped.
I've already agreed
to using your vendors
and your administrative fee,
but 5% of the floor, that's out...
That is the figure
your father and I agreed on.
If you don't think I'm earning it,
we can rethink it.
I don't know how I'm gonna hide
something like that in the books.
We'll figure something out.
You'll find me to be very flexible.
Well, you're gonna have to be.
We should schedule a weekly meeting.
Okay.
You were saying about the warehouse?
Cell phone detonator. Homemade.
- And the shipment?
- No.
Sorry.
Our associates in Philadelphia...
Rebecca, come in. Sit down.
Are expecting delivery today.
You call them and tell them
we'll make it up to them.
What happened?
An explosion
at our manufacturing facility.
- Someone planted a bomb.
- Who would do that?
It was Hood.
He's making a statement.
What are you gonna do?
Nothing for now.
- There's something else.
- What?
The slaughterhouse
lost power over the weekend.
- We have a backup generator.
- It was disabled.
All of the meat has gone bad.
How's that possible?
I spoke to the electric company.
Someone hacked their server
and shut down that particular grid.
He's got to be fucking kidding me.
You know, there's a saying
in the restaurant business.
Don't buy your meat
where you buy your bread and butter.
Trying to say don't shit
where you eat?
Yeah.
Why didn't you just say that, then?
It lacks poetry.
Morning, Kai.
The club I can understand.
If my employees were involved
in illicit activities,
you are compelled to act, sure.
- Even the warehouse.
- Yeah, I heard about that.
Explosion or something, right?
Now I've got a slaughterhouse
filled with rotten product.
Are you accusing me of something?
What can you possibly gain
by fucking with my meat?
What the hell are you doing?
Are you here to report a crime?
'Cause if not, I'm kind of busy.
- What the hell are you doing?
- Kai.
Easy.
You and I have a very complicated
relationship...
No.
I'm a cop, you're a criminal.
You disappoint me, Sugar.
You should be keeping better company.
Being your friend,
it should come with hazard pay.
You know, he's right about one thing.
All I'm doing is harassing him.
Well, before you decide
to kick it up a notch,
give me plenty of warning.
Oh, crap.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Doctor said for you
to take it easy, remember?
- I'm okay.
- Yeah?
Now, what is this?
- Well, I think it's pretty cool.
- Thanks.
I mean, that's major architecture.
Good morning.
- Don't forget your inhaler.
- Got it.
You're not going to work?
Took a couple of days off.
What are you up to?
Just gonna go
cast my Father of the Year ballot.
Deva, I know you're mad
and I'm sorry
I haven't been around enough.
It was worse when you were.
Yeah, and there's no excuse for it.
You just need to be around, Dad.
I know.
And it wasn't...
Look, it wasn't fair for me
to put you in that position,
but I am very sorry, baby.
I'm gonna do better, I promise.
I was gonna pick it up after work.
I'll get it after my shift.
Em, I'm pregnant, not an invalid.
The package could weigh
20 or 30 pounds for all I know.
Let a man do his wife a solid.
I think we can handle it.
Fuck me.
Hey, you want to have some fun?
He's gonna be the first Yawners
to make it to the NFL.
Oh, really?
What if he likes to
paint or dance ballet?
He'll be a Renaissance man.
I should get back.
Okay.
We need to talk.
You said
you were going to arrest Proctor.
- I'm working on that.
- Jesus.
Every day I think that he knows
I'm the one
who told you about the warehouse.
Hey, there's no way
he could know that was you.
But right now
I need something more.
I need something that
directly connects to him.
I don't know anything else.
You said you see him
three or four times a week.
He fucks me.
There's no pillow talk in that.
Come on,
it doesn't have to be illegal.
Just something unusual. Anything.
One night I was leaving
his house really late
and I saw all these guys moving
a bunch of crates into his basement.
- What was in the crates?
- I don't know.
Did you see in the basement?
He doesn't let me wander around.
I need to know
what's in that basement.
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- We don't want you to do anything
that puts you in danger.
Just talking to you
puts me in danger.
Just leave.
Please.
You pushed her too hard.
Right now she's all we've got.
Fuck.
No one wants to see Proctor go down
more than her.
Well, moving crates into
a basement isn't a crime.
- Depends on what's in the crates.
- That's not enough for a warrant.
And without a warrant,
you can't go in there.
- Boss.
- What? I know.
- Do you?
- Yes.
Here's his ditzy bitch.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Can I ask you a quick question?
- Sure.
When did you become
a traitor to your race?
Get out of my way.
- Oh, no. Oh, no, look at that.
- Excuse me, guys.
Don't tell me
this is a half coon baby in here.
Ooh!
What the fuck are you doing, man?
Come on, let's go.
- Somebody call 911.
- Hurry.
Come in.
That boy at the motel,
did he tell you his name?
- He just said Jason.
- Jason.
He didn't say anything about himself,
did he?
No.
It's just because
I don't understand why...
Hood cares so much about
what happened to him.
I mean, it's, well...
What are you going to do?
- About Hood?
- Yeah.
He's acting out of desperation
because he has nothing
and he's trying to provoke
an equally desperate response.
What about all that money you lost?
You know, I'm taking a longer view.
Those losses are nothing compared to
what we'll make with Longshadow.
And I can’t jeopardize
that arrangement
over a personal vendetta with Hood.
No matter how much I'd like to.
And I can't believe you have
so much restraint.
Dr. Irvin to Orthopedics.
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Excuse me.
- Megan, honey. It's Emmett. I'm here.
- Sir.
- It hurts.
What's happening?
Where are you taking her?
- Doctor's right here.
- I'm Dr. Holland.
She's bleeding internally.
We're prepping her for surgery.
Okay, honey.
Baby, tell me what happened.
There were these guys.
They had shaved heads.
Tattoos.
- They know you.
- You need to stay here, sir.
Emmett, I'm scared.
Okay, all right. Okay, look,
I'm gonna be right here.
- Emmett, I'm scared. I'm scared.
- Sir, I need you to stay here.
It's gonna be okay.
I'm gonna be here.
Sir, we have to go.
- Emmett.
Hey, what happened?
Meg, they're taking her into surgery.
It's the driver
we shook down the other day.
- Sharp.
- The skinheads?
Son of a bitch.
I guess he wanted to
get some payback.
- Fuck.
- Whoa, whoa. Where are you going?
- To get Sharp.
- No, no, you stay here. We'll go.
- Get the hell out of my way, Brock.
- Listen, Em.
Emmett, Emmett.
Look at me. Look at me.
Meg needs you here, okay?
- She needs you.
- Hey, we'll find them.
I promise.
We're gonna find them.
Okay?
It's gonna be okay.
- Who's your informant?
- It's confidential.
- Will he testify?
- No.
How do you know
you can trust him?
Let's just say he has a good reason
to want to see Proctor put away.
As long as that reason
wasn't your gun in his face.
I think you got the wrong idea
about me, Ms. Medding.
You are hardly the first cowboy cop
I've ever dealt with.
You all smile, play the game,
but you'd really
rather just shoot first
and ask questions never.
And here I was thinking we were just
starting to hit it off.
From what I understand,
you've been down this road
before with Kai Proctor.
If I'm gonna get a search warrant,
it needs to be bulletproof.
No judge will issue one on hearsay.
My informant saw the guns being moved
into the basement.
- She's got soft hands.
- Shut your mouth.
What's going on?
Meg's in the hospital.
- What?
- They were getting even with Emmett.
- She assaulted me, Sheriff.
- Yeah, I witnessed it.
I was defenseless.
Is she okay?
She was in surgery.
We've been looking for
these assholes all night.
- I sure hope she's okay.
- Shut the fuck up!
Shut it!
We were gonna head
to the hospital after this.
It's gonna have to wait.
I need you both
after you're done booking them.
Why? What's up?
Got a warrant to search Proctor's.
Fuck!
I want to go over
potential sites for a new lab.
- I'll call you back.
- Kai Proctor.
We have a warrant
to search these premises.
- On what grounds?
- It's all in here.
Maybe I didn't make myself clear.
Oh, no, no. You made yourself
perfectly clear.
You got anything
you want to say to me?
I'll make sure the DA's office
takes your cooperation into account.
I don't know what it is
you hope to find, Sheriff.
So that's a no?
Okay. You mind if I look around?
Thanks.
Wait a minute. What's that?
What's that sound like?
See, to me...
That sounds like...
A door.
- Bastard! I'll fucking kill you!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I'm going to fucking kill you!
Easy, Kai.
This is not changing anything.
I think it might.
- Wow.
- What's in there?
I'm guessing this wasn't
on the original floor plan, right?
You have permits
for all these illegal guns?
He asked you a question.
Fuck you.
- Take that as a no.
- I'll fucking kill you.
Kai Proctor, you're under arrest.
- You have the right...
- I know my fucking rights!
Yeah, okay, but let me
have my moment, all right?
Kai Proctor, you are under arrest.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you do say can and will be
used against you in a court of law.
Now, you have the right
to an attorney.
If you can't afford an attorney,
the court,
they'll appoint one for you.
- You're fucking dead.
- Take him away.
All right,
let's get the guns and anything else.
Sure.
Well, the internal bleeding
was a lot worse than we thought.
But she's gonna be okay?
We're gonna watch her,
make sure that her pressure
doesn't drop again,
but, yes, she's going to be okay.
But the trauma was too great
for the fetus.
What?
We'll run down the guns.
If we're lucky, one of them
has been used in a major crime.
- If not?
- None of the guns are registered.
We've already got him
on illegal possession.
That is a major offense,
especially
if there was gun trafficking.
How long can you keep him in county?
Long enough to try and make a case.
I want to go over
the warrant again.
We've been over that already.
Well, now you're gonna
go over it with me.
If you're gonna be late to the party,
Gordon...
Did you not get the fucking memo?
I'm still your boss.
Proctor's not gonna
beat the warrant, end of story.
I've faced Proctor in court.
- He's got a good lawyer.
- Yeah, now so do we.
You want to fuck with me on this?
Do I step out
so you can measure your dicks?
The feds will be by
to pick up the guns
first thing in the morning.
Until then, thank you
for your time, Sheriff.
Guess everyone needs a hobby, huh?
Stamps, that's a hobby.
This is psychotic.
So, how'd it go with the ADA?
Good.
She thinks we have a strong case.
Well, hopefully
it'll hold up this time.
Hey, I wanted to ask you.
Who tipped you off on the guns?
Confidential informant, Brock.
Not that I don't trust you.
Any word on Emmett?
I left a couple messages.
Okay, I'm gonna head over
to the hospital, check in.
Great.
You know what we haven't talked about
in a while?
- What's that?
- Him.
Sheriff Lucas Hood.
When he first got here,
he did whatever the hell he wanted.
We were all so shocked.
And now, all of a sudden,
he's Mr. Johnny By-the-book.
I guess better late than never, huh?
I guess.
He tell you who his informant is?
Why would he tell me and not you?
I don't know.
You two seem pretty close.
I'm sorry?
No, I'm...
Come on, Siobhan. I'm not blind.
I see things, you know?
I'm assuming you two are probably
sleeping together at this point.
You want to tell me about it?
There's nothing to talk about, Brock.
Oh, fuck.
Go fish.
Hey, you want a burger
or a hot dog?
- Uh, both.
- Okay.
- How about you, Deva?
- I'll take a burger, please.
Hey, yo! Stop. You're cheating.
Put that back.
That's not how we play. Come on.
Goddammit.
Carrie.
If you want to know, I'll tell you.
But you really don't want to know.
Carrie, wait.
Look, why don't you stay for dinner?
The problem is
this new ADA Medding.
She's smart.
And from everything I've heard,
she is not open for business.
Everyone has a price.
You want to add attempted bribery
on top of the gun charges?
Everyone has a weakness.
Anyway, our best shot is
to attack the search warrant.
We attack the veracity of their
confidential informant's claim.
Which was?
Their CI claims to have seen guns
in your basement.
That was the basis
for obtaining a warrant.
- Impossible.
- Is it?
No one knew about that room.
No one could have possibly seen
what was inside of it.
Rebecca and Burton
are the only other people
with access to my home.
- Is there anyone else?
- No.
Think. If we knew who the CI is,
maybe we can discount the warrant.
Juliet.
Who's Juliet?
I'm going to step outside
for a minute.
Take care of the girl.
How is she?
Doctor says she's gonna be fine.
That's good.
Siobhan and Brock,
they got Sharp and his buddies.
They're in holding right now.
They're not gonna
get away with this.
Okay.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Yeah, we also arrested Proctor.
For what?
Assault weapons, but...
It doesn't really matter right now.
Emmett.
- Hi.
Doctor says you're gonna be fine.
I lost the baby.
It's gonna be okay.
Okay?
You just need to get some rest.
It's gonna be all right.
Emmett.
What are you doing here?
Shouldn't you be at the hospital?
- Meg is sleeping.
- How is she?
- She's gonna be fine.
- Thank God.
You can't still be on duty
tonight.
No, I already called Brock
to cover.
This is a test. That's all.
You're right.
Okay, well, I'll wait for Brock.
You get back to Meg.
He's gonna be here in,
like, five minutes.
It's fine.
Just try to get some rest,
sweetheart.
It's gonna be okay.
Promise.
- All right.
- Well, you have a good night.
- You, too.
And you tell Meg that
I will be praying for her.
I will.
- All right.
- Thank you.
Just a test.
Cheryl, I'm going to need
the other thing as well.
I think she must have stepped out.
Sheriff Hood.
How can I help you?
Well, I don't know if you heard,
but we arrested
Kai Proctor last night.
Possession of illegal firearms.
- What does that have to do with me?
- Nothing I know of.
But I am curious
why Proctor would have so much
information on the Kinaho casino.
I mean, that is a lot of information
to have about
someone else's business.
Don't you think?
So I started wondering,
maybe everything going on
between you and him lately,
maybe you have a little more to do
with him than I know.
Do I need to call my lawyer?
I know you'd never intentionally
risk the well-being
of your tribe by getting in bed
with someone like Proctor.
So I'd like to help you
get him out of your business.
And why would you do that, Sheriff?
We have a case against him
with these guns.
It might stick.
But if it doesn't,
I want some insurance.
And what do I get out of it?
Same thing I get.
Same thing this whole town gets.
My father had certain
dealings with Kai Proctor.
Extortion rackets for land grabs.
I inherited those along with
everything else
when my father passed.
He was a revered leader,
so I hope you can understand
why I didn't want to
bring these things to light.
Of course.
I understand that.
But I think we've all
been living in the dark long enough.
Yeah.
I think so, too.
I've been wondering when you'd
come around to pay us a visit.
Look at him, boys.
That is one angry black man.
I guess we're lucky the bald guy
and the dyke caught us first.
- You think so?
- Hey, I like the dyke.
Do you know what I love
about this country?
The same laws
that protect people from me,
protect me from you.
You sound like my father.
I think that was an insult.
You see, my father believed
that the law spoke for all men,
even a black janitor.
You just have to have faith
in the system.
And he did.
One day his boss cheats him
out of some wages,
so he takes the guy to court.
The judge says, "Boy, don't bite
the hand that feeds you."
- Pops gets fired.
- That's some judge.
Couple years later
he buys his first car.
It gets stolen.
So like any law-abiding citizen,
he goes to the police.
They say, "Boy, don't you know
we got better things to do
than to chase after
some nigger's car?"
The point is, my father died
without ever having
anyone to speak for him.
That's touching.
I never wanted to be a cop.
Just wanted to play football.
That didn't work out.
Now, you guys got me realizing
the real reason I'm here
is to speak for people
who can't speak for themselves.
People like my father.
And my baby boy
who you killed today.
Fuck you, man.
I ain't scared of you.
What the hell is this?
Relax.
He ain't gonna do shit.
There's no one else here.
You get past me...
And you're home free.
Oh, I'm gonna fuck you up, spook.
Help him, asshole!
Take him out, Curtis.
Nighty-night.
Come on,
he's going down. You got him.
Go night-night.
- You got him.
- Night-night.
He's going down.
He's had enough.
What did you say?
I said he's had enough!
You know how you feel right now?
That rage that you're feeling?
That keeps building inside you
because somebody touched
someone you love.
I feel that rage every day...
When I see you and your people...
Overrunning this country.
It makes people feel better
to say we're ignorant,
but I see exactly what's going on.
I'm not ignorant.
And I'm not sorry.
Same deal.
You get past me,
you're home free.
You know,
if you're gonna be here this late,
feel free to pick up
a mop and a broom.
Tables can never be too clean.
Shit.
I got you, motherfucker.
What?
- Got who?
- Rabbit.
- I got him.
- How?
FBI followed protocol and digitized
all of Agent Racine's files.
It was a shot in the dark,
but I found an old exploit
from a legacy system.
I used the computer.
Yeah, right.
Racine found Rabbit?
Yes, he did.
He just didn't know it.
But I do.
Kind of wish you didn't.
Hey.
- I was hoping you'd still be up.
- I'm up.
Listen, I just wanted to explain...
What, about the fact that
you got an illegal search warrant
for Proctor's arrest?
I wouldn't put it quite like that, but...
Juliet never said
anything about those guns.
- You lied to get that warrant.
- But I ended up being right...
- Look, that is not the point.
- What's the point, then?
That's not the point.
You know what Proctor's capable of.
You put that woman's life
on the line.
Oh, come on.
Not to mention my career.
But that's nothing new for you.
- Hey, I didn't ask you for anything.
- You already did.
The second you got that warrant,
you made me complicit in your lie.
Yeah, but Proctor...
I don't give a fuck about Proctor,
okay,
or how you got him, but if you think
that sleeping with me
gets you my
unquestioning loyalty...
- You know that's not what I think.
- How do I know?
How do I know?
You never tell me anything.
I'll answer
any question you have.
Right now.
It's Brock.
Oh, my God.
Hey, Hood, over here.
- Did you call for an ambulance?
- Yeah, they're on their way.
Fuck.
They're alive.
I need more bandages.
Hey, Emmett, you want the EMT
to take a look at you?
No.
Two of the guys are mostly okay.
A lot of broken bones
and concussions,
but the one guy...
Sharp, he's...
He's pretty bad.
Listen, Emmett...
I think we need to
get your story straight
- before we call you a lawyer.
- Hey, Brock.
You leave us alone for a minute?
Yeah.
Hey, we're gonna figure this out.
There's nothing to figure out.
You were in an emotional state.
Your wife, your baby.
They taunted you, you snapped.
You didn't know what you were doing.
I knew exactly what I was doing.
I've been dealing with guys
like Sharp my whole life.
Maybe not as extreme as him,
but it's always something.
A look, a comment.
Something.
You know,
you get real good at burying it
and hiding it behind a smile.
This, I couldn't let it go.
I didn't want to.
I've been following
His teachings for years.
Been turning the other cheek.
The thing about it
is if I could go back,
I'd do the same thing
to those pieces of shit again.
I'd do the same thing again and again,
even though I know it's a sin.
So what kind of Christian
does that make me?
You know, when Meg first told me
she was pregnant...
My first thought...
Was "How can we raise a kid here?"
I mean, this town.
It's like everything that's good
just gets swallowed up by the bad.
It's like a never-ending
cycle of shit.
Guys like Sharp feel like they can
do whatever they want
to whoever they want.
And we're supposed to be
part of the solution.
We're supposed to hold that line.
But there is no line.
Not here.
The Bible says,
"See that no one
repays evil for evil."
Sometimes repaying it
is all you've got.
I got no problem with that.
Hood.