Hey, sweetie.
Yeah. No, I'm sorry. The
meeting's running a little late.
Well, you know Matheson,
guy loves to hear himself talk.
Yeah, yeah, I'll meet
you at the restaurant.
Hey, we're going over the contracts
now. I got to get back in there.
I love you, too.
You're getting
paid to clean, not window shop, Vesky.
You calling me a thief?
Take it easy, I'm just
yanking your chain.
Damn, it's freezing in here.
Better the cold than the smell.
I used to think my job sucked.
How much you make an
hour anyway? Not enough.
The difference is, this job
is just a temporary setback.
You, on the other hand,
will always be a schmuck.
Yeah. A schmuck with a
guaranteed pension and benefits.
I'll take it.
Sorry I'm late.
No talking about
real estate tonight.
I really want you to
just enjoy yourself.
Seeing you in that dress,
I'd say mission accomplished.
It gets a little better. Wait till
you see what's on underneath.
Fresh tako
with lemon. Enjoy.
I ordered the appetizer special.
Oh, I thought tako was a kind
of tuna. We're so not eating this.
Well, we should at least try it.
Please. It's moving, Bert.
That's so gross.
Actually, it's not that bad.
Really?
I'm not eating it.
To us, on our third anniversary.
The day I met you was...
Was...
Bert?
Bert? What is it? What...
Honey, what's wrong?
Oh, God. Someone,
please, call 911!
Can you breathe?
House!
I assume you're avoiding
me because of the charity gala.
This Friday? It must have
completely slipped my mind.
So you'll be there.
No, I meant
it slipped my mind to
tell you I'm not going.
What do you think
it'll look like
if you don't show up
when I get an award?
Like I don't give a crap about
awards, charities, what it looks like.
If you ever want... I
RSVP'd two days ago.
What, you think
I'm a complete ass?
If you were already
going, why did you...
Foreplay.
What?
Are you wearing my tie?
I saw it in your closet, and it
happened to match my shirt.
Why were you in my closet?
Looking for a tie.
What's the big deal?
Obviously he wants you out
of the closet for some reason.
I suspect marriage,
but I'm liberal that way.
Now tell me how someone
can have an allergic reaction
when all of their tests were
negative for known allergens.
Environmental. File says
he's a real estate developer.
He could have been exposed to
something visiting a construction site.
He's lying.
He's not an executive.
I saw his hands.
They're covered with
calluses and little cuts.
He works with them, a lot.
Stand up.
Our little girl is
finally growing up.
I mean, you dream of this day,
but when it finally happens...
So, what did Mr. Meat Hooks
say when you called him a liar?
Uh...
I didn't.
Baby steps. Go
down there and do it.
Um...
But what if I'm wrong?
I'll just end up offending him.
Consider that part a bonus.
All right, I'll send along one
of your big brothers to help.
You want scary,
smarmy or shorty?
We need to ask you
a few questions.
Alone, if you don't mind.
Uh, they tend to be
personal in nature...
I'm his wife.
I can probably answer
them better than he can.
They're about his job.
Well, what does that matter?
He sits in an office all day.
Honey, take a break.
No!
It's okay.
Seriously, if there's something
really wrong with him,
I want to know about it.
It's not...
Our questions are about
what he eats for lunch at work
and what comes out at the end.
Bowel movements mostly.
Color, texture, smell.
Okay...
Pretty sure you
can't help with that.
Maybe I could use a break.
Thank you for your honesty.
You're welcome.
I can't let my wife find out about
this. You have to promise me.
That depends on if
it's considered...
We promise.
I lost everything
because of the recession.
My entire real estate company.
And she has no idea.
So what do you do
for a living now?
I used to be a janitor
when I was in college,
and now I'm almost 40 and doing
it for the people I built homes for.
Why?
Why do you think?
Because I need the money.
No, I mean, why lie
to your wife about it?
None of our business, really.
What kind of cleaning?
Industrial jobs.
Crime-scene clean-up,
septic tank repair,
mold removal.
It's physically killing me.
It's the holy grail
of potential diseases.
Caustic cleaning chemicals,
raw sewage,
mold spores, fungal infections.
Not to mention cleaning up
blood and other body fluids
from a homicide yesterday.
We should check
out the crime scene.
He might have picked up a bacterial
infection from the victim's blood.
The place has been
cleaned and sanitized by our patient.
We sent for the autopsy report,
probably take a week to get it.
When he's not working, where
does he go all day to hide out?
His old real estate office?
Treat for bacterial infection.
Meantime, Bert, take Ernie and
check his office for environmentals.
I'll talk to Cuddy about getting
the autopsy results faster.
You're Bert.
He's Ernie.
And they're both roommates.
That was a good one.
Well, at least the Alzheimer's
patient in room 202
won't remember she only
got half a ham sandwich.
I'm doing her a favor.
You're really going
to the charity gala?
Why?
I wanna do something
nice for my girlfriend.
You never do anything
unless it stands to benefit you.
I realize that three
failed marriages
can leave a man
twisted and bitter inside.
But in a good relationship, people
sometimes do things for each other.
A hundred says
you don't show up.
You're giving me an
incentive to actually show up?
A personal, selfish incentive.
I'm just making easy money.
Two hundred.
How high did Cuddy
authorize you to go?
She... She...
Three.
She really wants you there.
Why do people believe that I'm
incapable of doing anything nice?
Experience.
It's a tie.
I'm not wearing your underwear.
I said I was sorry.
You want the tie back?
Can we get to work?
I can't tell if you're
being passive-aggressive
or if this is just your regular
fun-loving personality.
Both. And you
can keep the tie.
It went out of style
five years ago.
Vicodin, and he doesn't
have a prescription.
We didn't test for an
allergic reaction to narcotics.
Or it's the obvious.
Take a look at this.
We think you're suffering
from boric acid exposure.
Which is causing the rash.
We need to
decontaminate your skin
and hope you didn't
inhale it into your lungs.
I feel like I'm...
Never seen a fever
spike this fast before.
Acid exposure burns, literally,
it shouldn't be causing this.
What's happening to him?
Bert? Honey,
are you all right?
We have to get his
fever down right now.
If it gets any higher, it could
cause permanent brain damage.
We used cooling
blankets to get his temperature down.
He stabilized at 102.
Problem's not boric acid. We
found no traces of it on his skin.
Infection from
the murder victim's blood?
Autopsy report was negative
for communicable disease.
Cause of death was an
overly stabbey girlfriend.
We found Vicodin in his office.
Give it to me.
It might look like Vicodin,
but be something else.
It's real.
Unfortunately.
Because Vicodin doesn't
cause rash, fever and joint pain.
It does make Taub considerably
less annoying, though.
Maybe we're thinking too
far outside the box here.
Just because he
could have picked up
any one of a hundred
exotic diseases
from his job,
doesn't mean he did.
Taub's life partner has a point.
We started treatment with
antibiotics and he got worse.
The simple answer begins
with "M," ends with a "Mia."
Meningococcemia?
That works, too.
Confirm with a lumbar puncture.
And on the off
chance we're wrong,
find out what else
he's been lying about,
besides his job
and his drug use.
You sure do hide
a lot from your wife.
Your job, your
drug use, what else?
What does it matter?
We can't help you unless
you're completely honest with us.
I was doing manual labor.
If I came home
barely able to move,
Diane would know something's up.
That's why I take the
Vicodin, to hide the pain.
I'm not an addict.
Is that all you're hiding?
I didn't just lose my job.
I mean, that's how it started,
but I figured it'd just
last a couple of months.
I maxed out our credit cards,
took a double mortgage
on the house
and I sold all of
our investments.
Who'd have thought the
recession would last this long?
So it's Obama's fault
you're lying to your wife?
Look, I screwed up,
but it's too late now.
I need you to roll over on
your left side for the procedure.
Haven't you ever done
something in a relationship
you wish you could take back?
Maybe.
How'd you handle it?
I told the truth, eventually.
How'd that work out?
Not well.
I need some Intel on this
charity event on Friday night.
If I go, do I have to actually
give money to charity?
I'm going.
I just don't want it to suck.
There has to be a
way to make this fun.
Show up and behave.
Problem solved.
Your problem solved.
Don't you think she
deserves more than a plaque
and a round of applause for
15 years of running this dump?
It's a watch, not a plaque.
It's a cliché.
I want to make
things more exciting.
Something she'll remember
for more than 10 minutes.
Okay. By fun and exciting, you
mean screwing this up for Cuddy
so she won't even dream of
asking you to go to one again.
You really can't stand
seeing me happy, can you?
Gram stains are negative
in the first CSF samples.
One down, three to go.
I'm starving.
You want to get a bite...
Already have plans.
A date?
What difference does it make?
We're roommates,
not a married couple.
We don't have to eat
every night together.
So you're saying it's a date?
Yeah, it's a date.
I don't have plans.
Ooh. Shocking.
Are you mad
because I picked you?
You're stuck actually
doing your job?
A little hazing never
hurt a med student.
I doubt it ever helped either.
I'm sorry that I
think our patient
shouldn't be lying to his wife.
I'm a woman, I guess I just
have a different perspective.
You're sharing this unique
insight that women don't like lying?
No, I'm sharing my unique insight
that you don't respect women.
You sleep with a different
one every few days.
Or maybe you find meaning
in meaningless relationships?
At least I have relationships.
I'm seeing a high lymphocyte
count in the CSF sample.
And that couldn't wait until they
finished mocking each other?
Means it's not meningococcemia.
He's getting worse. He
can barely move his legs.
I can't feel them.
I can't feel my feet!
What is it?
What is happening to him?
Luckily,
he didn't lose his feet.
We were able to
restore his circulation
before any serious
damage set in.
It's not meningococcemia.
CSF was negative for bacteria.
But high on lymphocytes.
It's some kind of viral infection.
Serum sickness fits everything.
There'd have to be a cause,
some drug he's been exposed to.
In rare cases, a tick or
spider bite could set it off.
Show of hands.
Who's going to this
charity thing Friday night?
Already got a date.
Cuddy's getting an award.
I think we should all be
there, show our support.
I assume you're
planning on screwing it up,
SO you want to
maximize the witnesses.
Why does everyone go to that?
Experience.
Shut up. How about go or
work the clinic all weekend?
I hear it's Genital
Herpes Awareness Month.
Serum sickness fits.
Take him off the antibiotics,
start him on corticosteroids.
If we're right, he'll
be better by morning.
Canceled date, huh?
You're bugging my cell phone?
No, I just noticed
you're not wearing it.
What?
Your first-date shirt.
You're tracking my wardrobe?
I'm just observant.
It's why I'm good at my job.
It's also the reason you're
starting to annoy the crap out of me.
Forgive me for trying to
connect a little with my roommate.
I just found out that Rachel is now
officially more than just emotional
with her online friend.
You're getting divorced,
what'd you expect?
I know. You're right.
Just thinking about it kind of
makes me want to throw up.
You still want to
get something to eat?
I could cook.
- That had to hurt.
- You suck.
Not as bad as you, and you
just missed a free upgrade.
You just did it again.
You ran past a power up.
Double damn.
Are you just letting me win?
Of course I'm not letting you...
Okay, maybe a little.
You're having fun, right?
Not anymore.
I used to think
the whole brooding thing
was just part of
your work persona,
but now I live with you.
You need to lighten up, Bert.
And you think I need you to show
me what? How to have fun? Relax?
It was working
until you flipped out.
If I was going to take
advice on how to live my life,
it would not be from you.
You're broke, you
ruined your marriage,
and yet you act like
you're the victim here.
Like somehow we're all
supposed to feel sorry for you.
You screwed up your life,
not some emotional friend
your wife met on the...
What's wrong?
My stomach.
You poisoned me!
I ate the same thing you did.
How come I'm not... Oh! Oh.
Oh, dear God.
Open the door, Bert.
Please. Baby, talk to me!
He locked himself inside.
He went crazy. He hit me.
Bert.
Open the door, Bert.
Bert, talk to us.
- Bert?
- Open the door, Bert.
I can't get out!
Why? I can't get out.
No, no!
God! No!
Why can't I get out?
The skin rash is gone.
But whatever it is, it
obviously moved into his brain.
Or not. MARTHA: He
had a psychotic break.
I'd say that usually indicates
neurological involvement.
Usually, not always.
The hallucinations
stopped once the steroids
we gave him cleared his system.
I think...
I think we caused this.
What happened to you?
Taub tried to
kill me last night.
The steroids probably
did clear up the rash,
but the rest of his
symptoms are the same.
And now bilateral
conjunctivitis.
Excuse me, I'll be back.
I better go check on him.
Swollen joints, high
white count, fever, conjunctivitis.
Anyone?
- Seriously?
What, you two can't think
and poop at the same time?
There's a life at stake here.
Could be Familial
Mediterranean fever.
Not likely, that almost always
presents with abdominal
pain or diarrhea.
Given his job, the skin
and eye involvement,
it's more likely a
systemic fungal infection.
We would have seen
it in his blood work.
Unless the saline used to recover
and store the tissue samples
has been shown in
recent studies...
Get new blood and CSF samples
using formaldehyde
instead of saline.
And start him and his wife
on triple antifungal therapy.
His wife?
Well, if he's really
trying to keep her happy,
I assume they've
shared bodily fluids.
I hate you.
You could have picked
it up from your job.
The real one, not the fake one.
If you would've been
more honest about...
How is that relevant?
If his wife knew about his job,
they both might have been
more alert to the early symptoms.
We could have caught it earlier.
That's ridiculous.
Oh, my God, sweetheart.
I'm so sorry.
Whatever you're doing,
it's obviously not working.
We think he has a
systemic fungal infection.
We're starting him on a
parenteral antifungal regimen.
It can be transferred
through bodily fluids,
so we have to start you
on the treatment as well.
A fungus?
Where would he...
Could be from anywhere. The
spores can become airborne.
But why would he
be the only one?
No one in our neighborhood,
no one in his office building.
Sometimes it just happens
that way. It's hard to explain.
No, it's not.
I need to talk to my wife
in private for a moment.
Your numbers
indicate the medication
isn't helping with
your cholesterol...
Hey!
Huh?
What are you doing?
What's it look like I'm doing?
I'm auditioning
a band for Friday night.
So you're trying to ruin
Cuddy's moment in the spotlight.
Ruin? These guys recorded
with Juan Gabriel.
They're gonna cost me two grand.
This is not a prank.
These guys are the beginning
of Cuddy's evening to remember,
which in turn will
make my evening...
I think if you do this,
your evening will end with you
in your apartment
alone with a sock.
This is all for the best.
Yeah. Either that
or the opposite.
If it means anything,
I think he's
honestly just trying
to protect you
and keep you happy.
Oh, God!
Of course.
He would tell a bunch of
strangers before he would tell me.
I mean, why not? I'm just
a stupid housewife, right?
You know, I have something
you can share with him. It's over.
He's a liar, and I never
want to hear from him again.
You may want to go check
on him, his fever's back.
But I'm done worrying about him.
She was right, he's at 101.
Diane?
We're gonna have
to get your fever down.
What's wrong?
What are you saying?
I can't hear you!
I can't hear anything.
Why can't I hear anything?
His hearing's
almost completely gone.
The new blood and CSF tests
were negative for spores and fungus.
Tumor necrosis factor syndrome?
Fits the conjunctivitis and
painful swelling in his joints.
Except it's never been documented
to cause hearing loss. Ever.
Oh, no, she didn't.
This isn't the classroom.
In the real world,
real doctors know
that patients can have more
than one thing wrong with them.
Zing. CHASE: He
was taking Vicodin.
Extreme abusers can
experience hearing loss.
Except his drug levels never
got into the ototoxic zone.
You have a better idea?
Ugh!
I do.
Only in the sense that you're
wasting my time with a bad idea,
and she's wasting
my time with no idea.
Maybe we should hear
from silent and silenter.
It's probably neurological.
Brain tumor?
Or a viral infection
that's reached his brain.
I say we go with Ernie on
this one. Get an MRI. Find it.
I'm gonna move out next week.
I'd rather stay friends
than be roommates.
Just make sure
I get my keys back.
It's not my fault.
I cooked it thoroughly!
Looking forward to Friday night?
Yes and no.
Yes, because it's a great honor.
And, no, because... Well,
you know the because.
You think House is
gonna embarrass you?
Well, not intentionally.
Maybe intentionally.
I know what you mean.
I picture him
doing something stupid,
like hiring a mariachi
band or something.
Actually, I could
get behind that.
I tried to hire one last year,
but the board wouldn't let me
because they thought
it was too expensive.
I'm freezing.
Is Diane coming back?
Mmm-mmm.
Bedside 101.
When a patient IS near
death, try to be nice.
She's not coming back.
I'm not gonna lie to him.
Stop. What? You
heard what she said.
He's seizing. We got
to get him out of there.
Both his kidneys are fried.
He's in a coma. He
has maybe a few days left.
We could try and get him on the
transplant list, but in his condition
and without a diagnosis, I
don't see him getting selected.
He wouldn't survive the surgery.
Hence my previous comment.
What do you want
us to do, House?
If it's a tumor, we start chemo,
bombard his head with radiation.
Which will probably
kill him in this state.
And without an MRI, we
don't even know if he has one.
He's definitely dead
if we do nothing.
If I'm wrong, all we do
is shave a few hours off.
We'll need his wife's consent.
Masters will get it.
Probably not a good idea.
- Uh, he's right.
- No, he's not.
Consider this me officially
booting you out of the nest.
Just wanted to watch.
Do you even like me?
Why?
I put making friends and
having relationships on hold
so I could
concentrate on studying.
I always thought there'll be
plenty of time for that in the future.
But now, when I do want them...
I can't even get a date
to this charity event.
If I can't establish
relationships in my personal life,
how will I ever do
it with a patient?
Be honest with her.
But if it comes down to a choice
between the brutal
truth and hope,
side with hope.
He's in a coma.
We think it's a brain tumor. We need
your permission to start treatment.
Due to his current
condition, the risk factor...
You mean it could kill him?
It's possible,
but there is still hope.
Can he hear me?
They say that people in
comas can still do that.
Sometimes, but your
husband's hearing
is fine.
I didn't mean any of
those awful things I said.
I'm so sorry.
I love you, Bert.
I've always loved you.
I also kept a secret from you.
I was going to tell
you at the restaurant,
but you got sick.
Then I wanted to wait
until you felt better.
I'm pregnant, sweetheart.
You're going to be a daddy.
Why rash again?
It went away, it needs
a reason to come back.
We know it's not
an allergic reaction
so we must have done
something to set it off again.
What?
We put him on dialysis?
Moved him to the ICU?
We also did a partial MRI.
Two hours before the rash
came back. They're not connected.
What was he doing two hours
before he broke out the first time?
Cleaning a crime scene.
A crime scene and an MRI.
Still not seeing the connection.
We've been missing
connections this entire case.
Did he say anything? Did he show
any signs of stress in the MRI room?
He said he was cold, but
it's always freezing in there.
Cold then rash.
Cold urticaria causes rash,
but it's almost instantaneous,
not time delayed.
And it wouldn't
explain his other symptoms.
That's what we did.
We made him cold.
CAPS.
A genetic disorder
caused by a mutation
in the cold-induced
auto-inflammatory syndrome 1 gene.
Muckle-Wells syndrome?
There's only been a couple of
thousand documented cases in the US.
Well, now there's a
couple thousand and one.
Fits every symptom there.
We're idiots for
not seeing it before.
Treat with rilonacept.
He'll live a long
and healthy life
filled with lies to his
wife and future child.
You okay?
Why wouldn't I be?
I solved my case.
But your patient died.
I didn't say in time.
It happens,
we can't save everyone.
I just came to apologize.
You're right, I am turning
bitter and cynical inside.
You're finally
putting the cat down.
She loves mariachi, I told you.
Go home and change,
the party's in a few hours.
You don't have to move out,
if you don't want to.
I realize you might
have had a point.
I've been alone a long time,
and I don't want
to end up like House.
What you said about
me and my marriage...
I was being an ass.
True.
But you were right.
I needed to hear it.
So we're good?
You know, I have
a couple tickets to...
Don't push it.
Taub and Foreman done?
I'm hitching a ride with them.
Me, too.
You're not picking up your date?
No, going solo.
All those meaningless relationships
tend to wear a guy out after a while.
We've got 15
minutes to get there
if we want to
see the board freak
when House's mariachi
band marches in.
All of them are gone, Wilson.
They're all dead,
because I'm screwed up.
You lost one patient,
and it wasn't your fault.
What about that mom
who gave her baby cancer?
If I'd figured that one out
quicker, she'd still be a mom, alive.
She refused treatment
when it was offered.
How is that your fault?
Then there was that guy I spent
a day trapped in isolation with.
I was five feet
away the whole time.
Just watched him die,
like an idiot.
Yeah.
You've lost patients before,
and you'll lose patients again.
Exactly. Why?
Because love and happiness are
nothing but distractions.
The only thing my
relationship with Cuddy
has done for me is
make me a worse doctor.
Right, the great Dr. House
doesn't deserve to be happy.
You know it's not true.
My happiness is being paid
for with other people's lives.
How is she?
She's worried. She's upset
that you didn't show up tonight.
I got to tell her
the truth, Wilson.
First... First, you're
not driving anywhere.
And second,
you're definitely not
talking to Cuddy like this.
Okay.
Then I'm gonna walk.
We really, really need to talk.
You're drunk and you
screwed up big time.
Go home!
You completely
disappeared on me.
You wouldn't even
answer your cell phone.
You're gonna want
to sit down for this.
Go ahead.
Sit, sit, sit, sit, sit.
I've made a decision.
Being happy and
being in love with you
makes me a crappy doctor.
Shut up!
You're too drunk to
end this relationship.
I am drunk, but I'm also right.
You have made me a worse doctor,
and people are going
to die because of that.
And
you
are totally worth it.
If I had to choose between
saving everyone
or loving you, being happy,
I choose you.
I choose being happy with you.
I will always choose you.
My head's on your vagina.
Go to sleep, House.
Yeah, I am kind of tired.