To your knowledge,
did the Departed drink
more than two
alcoholic beverages daily?
Yes.
To your knowledge,
was the Departed born in a hospital?
I think so.
To your knowledge, did the Departed
ever attempt suicide?
I don't know.
I understand you want to protect
your husband's privacy
but the more questions
you answer honestly,
the better chance your claim
will be processed.
He told me...
He took some pills once
in high school.
So is that a "yes"?
Yes.
- Hello?
- Hello. Angel?
I'd like to make an appointment.
Hey. I'm Angel.
I'm Nora. Come on in.
Have a seat.
- Can I get you something to drink?
- No. Thanks. I'm good.
Nice mattress.
That for us?
That's for me.
You want me to watch you?
No, I want you to shoot me.
No way. No fucking way.
Just...
Two thousand dollars
for two seconds.
Your ad specifically said,
"Nothing is forbidden."
Lady, I fuck people.
I don't kill them.
If I wanted to die,
I wouldn't need you.
I'll talk you through it.
It's Kevlar.
All you have to do
is aim right here.
Just above the stomach,
just below my heart.
You've done this before?
Yes.
Why didn't you just get the person
that shot you last time?
She said she wouldn't do it again.
I need another thousand.
Okay.
Go ahead.
What if I miss?
You won't.
What happened to you?
Hold it up. Two hands.
All right? Okay?
Aim right here!
Just pull the trigger, okay?
On three.
One...
...two, three!
- Do it.
- Just wait!
- Just do it.
- I can't!
- Just do it!
Do it now!
Nora Jamison Durst,
you have provided
the appropriate documentation,
certifying the respondents' status
as "Departed"?
Yes, I have.
And you wish to dissolve
the marriage
between yourself, the plaintiff
and the respondent,
"Douglas Isaac Durst"?
I do.
And is there any matter of custody
or removal of children,
here named "Jeremy" and "Erin,"
to be resolved
within this application?
My children are also Departed,
Your Honor.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Should the Departed respondent
return,
this will remain binding.
Do you still want to proceed?
My husband was sleeping
with our kids' preschool teacher.
Yes, I'd like to proceed.
All right.
The court hereby grants
a Judgment of Divorce.
While you're here,
would you like to legally revert
to your maiden name?
- It's just another form...
- No, thank you.
I'd like to remain Nora Durst.
Hey.
If that's a traffic ticket,
I can get you out of it.
Divorce.
I just got myself out of it.
Whoa. Small world.
Me, too.
You're joking.
No, I should have got the hint
when she joined the Guilty Remnant.
- Oh, you're not joking.
- No. I don't know how to joke.
- Do you wanna go to Miami?
- What?
I was supposed to go
to this work conference
in Manhattan on Friday
but it's gonna be terrible
and I was thinking
maybe Miami instead.
Oh, uh...
I live with my daughter, so I...
Fuck your daughter.
I'm sorry. That--
I am so sorry.
Look...
- Hi, Tracy. Is he in?
- Yes, he is.
Okay, thank you.
Hey.
Come in.
Ma'am, the benefits aren't determ--
Right, but our office has nothing
to say about--
Hello? Ma'am?
I feel like I have
the same conversation
- 80 fucking times a day.
- I have no idea what you mean.
Sit.
So, you ready for your panel,
whatever, at DROP?
Yes, sir. They put me on day two,
along with Rhode Island
and Connecticut.
Just don't let them bully you
into taking questions
about the data. All right?
They gave us a pass
last year
but they're gonna want answers
this time.
"I'm sorry, sir or madam,
I'm not qualified to analyze
the data from our questionnaires.
I don't even have access to it
before it goes
to our statisticians in Annapolis."
Oh, shit.
Annapolis. Speaking of.
- What are you doing on 121?
- What?
I just got this email.
"Please inquire ID 42ECN
as to the manner by which
he/she presents Question 121."
What are you doing?
I'm not doing anything.
It says here
you're 100 percent affirmative.
Every single one of your applicants
answers 121 "yes."
Isn't that what we're supposed
to be looking for, a pattern?
Everyone else who asks the questions
get plenty of "no's".
It's only a pattern for you.
Maybe you're...
...mentioning what happened to you.
Hm?
You know, before you roll,
just to get people comfortable?
I would never do that.
Okay. Sure.
No, I know.
I'll talk to Annapolis.
Well, enjoy the conference, okay?
Hey.
When you took it...
when they asked you 121,
what'd you answer?
I said yes, all three times.
Hello. You've reached
the Durst residence.
Please leave a message.
Hi, Nora.
It's Rick Carson.
Just wanted to thank you again
for being a panelist
at this year's
Departure-Related Occupations
and Practices conference.
Your unique perspective
is really valuable to us.
And a heads-up. We're expecting
a big crowd this year,
so register early.
I'm really looking forward
to meeting you in person.
Look in the Bible.
Look right now. Look today!
They're poisoning us!
Have you seen this?
He's still here.
He's hiding in a basement in Sicily.
Don't trust the Vatican.
The Pope is still here.
Any fucking time now!
Fuck you!
Sons of bitches!
You can't do this to us!
Ms. Durst.
You are staying with us
for two nights?
Mm-hm.
So what's up
with all the people outside?
There's a lot more than last year.
Well, you know, anything about
the Departure for some people.
Can't let it go.
This is the hotel's code of conduct.
Please read carefully and sign.
We had some issues
with your conference last year.
Better cancel the kegger.
Registration is on the third floor.
Enjoy your stay.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
- There you go.
- Hi.
- Nora Durst.
- "Durst." Great.
Here's your welcome bag.
Let me look up your badge.
Hey, you want a good cry, read that.
He lost four people on the 14th.
- That's terrible.
- Isn't it?
Looks like somebody
already picked up your badge.
What? I just got here.
Well, somebody
must have picked it up by mistake.
No worries.
This'll get you in
to all the events.
Sorry for the confusion, okay?
Next person?
Hi. Your name, please?
Williams.
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
I need my badge.
I'm a panelist tomorrow.
I work for the Department
of Sudden Departure
and I'm a legacy.
I'm sorry for your loss.
I'd like to give you a legacy decal
to go on your guest badge
but we don't have any left.
No, of course. Thank you.
But you understand
that if somebody took my badge...
Well, I'm sure
it was just an innocent mistake.
Why don't you go into the mixer?
Everyone is in there.
I'm sure your badge
is in there, too.
Yes. Next person, please.
They can deny it all they want.
North Korea lost people.
We can't ignore the possibility.
Ooh!
God.
Hey there, easy...
"Guest"?
What's up? Marcus.
I have the most interesting job
at the conference.
And I don't believe in name tags.
If you want to know what I do,
just ask me.
It's a fucking madhouse this year.
You might wanna watch out
for baldy over there.
He's working the room,
asking people,
"Do you really wanna feel this way?"
It's a great fucking pitch.
I give him that.
I mean, who the fuck wants
to feel this way?
I have to go.
It was nice meeting you.
Hey, hey, hey, Guest.
So you're seriously
not gonna ask me what I do?
Okay, what do you do?
- You don't wanna know what I do.
- Okay.
We can't deny
the rising instances
of Post-Departure Delusion Disorder.
Or some pundits
have cheekily taken
to calling it
"The Prophet's Dilemma."
For most of humankind's existence,
certain individuals have come forth
as self-professed interpreters
of the world's mysteries.
But what happens when those
conversations with God go wrong?
Following a catastrophic event
or circumstance,
let alone one
that defies scientific explanation,
the incidence of prophetic delusion
rise dramatically.
And this isn't just megalomaniacs
who make the news for a week.
This is happening to our friends,
our neighbors, our own families.
This belief that a higher power
is speaking to us,
whether through dreams or signs,
even voices,
is a powerful coping mechanism,
and if left unchecked,
it is a very dangerous one.
I can wait as long as you want.
I am so sorry.
I thought you were somebody else.
You don't remember me, do you?
No.
Last year, you called me
a heartless bitch
at the farewell party.
I don't know--
No, that wasn't me.
Yes, it was.
Your name is Nora.
You lost your husband and kids.
- You work for Linden-Bix?
- I do.
You said my kids disappeared
because I gave them Frosted Flakes.
No, I mentioned a correlation
between eating cereals high in sugar
and pre-adolescent Departures
in a cocktail conversation.
And then you made me cry
in front of a roomful of people.
I am sorry.
Last year I didn't... I...
I was having a really hard time.
You're doing so much better now.
May I have
your attention, please?
The breakout session
of the Brandenburg Carousel
has been moved to Room 6-B.
6-B in ten minutes
for the Brandenburg Carousel.
Thank you.
I'll take the next one.
Holy shit. It's Guest.
Get your ass in here.
- She's crazy, this one.
- I was just going.
No, no, you're not.
You're going up the elevator.
Get this, get this.
I gave this young lady my best
"you don't wanna know,"
and she still refused to ask me
what I do.
I like her.
Well, guess what, Guest?
We got you now.
You're coming up
to the hospitality suite for drinks.
Thanks, but I have a panel tomorrow,
so I...
- Fuck, Marcus.
- No, no, no.
You have a choice, Guest.
You can play by the rules of this
fucking depressing conference
like everybody else,
or you can go
down the rabbit hole with us.
So what's it gonna be?
You want to spend the next two days
of your life dying,
one panel at a time,
or do you want to live?
Oh, ho, ho! Yes!
Poor Patrick Johansen.
It's a fucking tragedy,
what happened to him, yeah.
- Four! He lost four!
- Did you read the book?
I try not to read anything
that comes in a fucking tote.
Leave that shit to the oranges.
- What's an orange?
- The badges.
You know, some people
have the orange stickers?
The legacies?
Legacies, orphans, survivors.
Whatever they wanna be called
this year.
- It's awful.
- It's a fucking tragedy.
It's like I'm supposed to treat
them better than anyone else?
How many times am I supposed
to say I'm sorry, right?
Right, right.
- You pregnant, Guest?
- What?
Any suicidal thoughts,
history of heart problems?
No.
What is this?
Don't worry.
FDA's gonna approve them next year.
Have fun.
Yo, Guest. Guest!
Why the fuck would you work
for the DSD?
- I like giving people money.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
All those questions you ask,
seriously.
So you really think
you're gonna find out why them?
You're gonna crack the case?
I'm sorry, sir or madam.
I'm not qualified to analyze
the data from our questionnaires.
I don't even have access to it
before it goes to our statisticians
in Annapolis.
It's a fucking scam.
The insurance companies
won't pay out on the Departures
because they're technically
not dead
and then your department
created this little questionnaire
so that people won't wanna collect
on their benefits.
Hey, look, if your fucking dad
died in a jet ski accident, right,
would you have to answer
150 yes or no questions
about what food he liked
or whether he had anal sex?
We do not ask questions
about anal sex.
He's fucking with you, Guest.
He's fucking with you.
- You do an important job.
- No, we don't.
We all do an important job,
all of us.
- Okay. Marcus?
- Yes?
What do you do?
You don't wanna know!
You know that's my line.
That's my line.
I say that.
That's my pickup line.
Open.
You sell these?
Forty grand a pop.
Our basic models are cheaper
but they're less convincing.
- It looks exactly like you.
- Down to the appendectomy scar.
We take photos of the Departed
and home videos,
whatever they give us,
and then we slowly generate
every little thing
that made them, them.
You know, scars, tattoos,
piercings, body hair.
Then, four to six weeks later,
voila.
They got their loved one back.
You make people pay
$40,000 for this?
Oh...
You think I'm soulless?
You think I'm taking advantage
of these poor, grieving people.
But no, no, no, no.
They're coming to us, you know?
And, look at this.
One hundred forty million
bodies disappeared.
That's demand.
We are simply providing the supply.
It's pretty amazing,
helping someone rebuild
the person they lost, bit by bit.
This, they can bury in the ground.
This is here, this, this.
This is real.
I want them to have that.
I want them to have something real.
It's a pretty good pitch.
I'll give you that.
So tell me, Guest, am I soulless?
No.
You have a soul.
Can I kiss you?
I wanna kiss you.
- You're married.
- I am married.
But I still want to kiss you
and I believe
you want to kiss me.
Okay.
What?
What are you doing?
You go, girl.
Check this out.
Really?
You're making me jealous.
This is horrible, horrible.
Don't look at this.
Guest! Guest! Guest!
- Nora Durst?
- Yes?
Security. Open up.
- Open this door now.
- I'm coming.
Open up.
- Yes?
- Nora Durst?
- You need to pack up your things.
- We're escorting you from the hotel.
- What?
- I don't understand.
- You destroyed hotel property.
- The mirror in the bar?
- I wasn't in the bar.
- Let's go, Ms. Durst.
- Wait! Stop!
You-- Listen to me.
I wasn't in the bar last night.
Someone took my badge.
They're pretending to be me.
See? The conference,
they gave me this
because my badge was stolen.
That's the person
you should be looking for.
They're impersonating me.
I'm not with your conference.
I'm with the hotel.
You signed the code of conduct.
You broke it.
We want you out.
Let's go.
You can't do this.
I didn't do anything wrong.
I have a panel in a few hours.
If we see you
on these premises again,
we're gonna call the police.
Morning.
Thanks for printing those out.
I lost my ID at a conference.
I have to get back for a panel
I'm on.
I work for the Department
of Sudden Departures.
This is good.
So, Nora Durst,
what are you doing back in my hotel
- with a fake credential and a gun?
- That's not for--
I forgot I had that with me.
I am supposed to be on a panel
this morning.
So, why did you throw a bottle
at the mirror behind the hotel bar?
I wasn't in the bar.
Someone is impersonating me.
No offense, but who would
wanna pretend to be you?
I don't know. There are a lot
of sick people out there.
Maybe somebody's doing it
for attention. I...
My husband and two children
are Departed,
and that sort of thing,
it gets a lot of sympathy.
Jesus, your whole family?
What are the odds?
One in 128,000.
Okay, let's try this on for size.
I know how these conferences can be.
Away from home, new people.
So maybe things got out of hand,
one drink too many--
- No.
- No, no...
- Listen to me.
- Maybe...
...you did go down to that bar
and things got out of control.
Maybe you've been under
a lot of stress and you just...
...lost your grip on things.
- Is that possible?
- No, that is not possible.
Please, just...
She is probably on my panel
right now.
The other panelists don't know me.
She could walk onstage
with my badge
and nobody would stop her,
so please.
All right.
If I walk you down
to that conference room
and there's no one there
pretending to be you,
then you leave this hotel
and I never see your face again.
- Deal?
- Deal.
I'm sorry.
The session's already started.
We're just gonna be a minute.
Next we have Marquee Jackson
from Vermont.
Beside him,
we have Olivia Livingstone
from the Rhode Island branch
of the DSD,
which has
the highest participation rate
in the benefit program
in the country.
Next, we have Jonathan Van Meter,
also from Vermont,
and beside him,
Nora Durst from New York.
Mrs. Durst
is also a triple legacy.
Well, fuck.
I need two guys
to the Waterloo Room right now.
...liaison with the Canadian
Departure Census,
and he'll talk about
how they collect
their data up north.
And finally, Daniel McCallum
from Connecticut.
Daniel served
on the Review Committee...
Excuse me.
I have a question.
- We haven't started the panel yet.
- I have a question for Nora Durst.
We will open the floor
to questions--
I am not Nora Durst.
I have been watching you people
for the last two days,
listening to you
and you are all blind.
- Puppets.
- Ma'am.
The Department
of the Sudden Departure
is an elaborate smokescreen
to give the public the illusion
of progress. Excuse me.
Their questionnaires
are sent to incinerators
- outside of Tallahassee, Florida.
- Shut this off!
Their benefit payments
are a way to silence us all.
In 2005, the Israeli Mossad
was experimenting with a plasma ray
that could target all human matter
and leave almost no residue.
Where are your experts
and panels on that?
- Another martini, dirty.
- Thank you.
Let me give you my card.
You can keep it open.
Manager says whatever you need,
it's on the house.
What'd they do,
if the drinks are on them
because you've been
seriously wronged?
Maybe they're just rewarding me
for being a loyal customer.
- Nah.
- Nah?
Isn't the way the world works.
Indeed it is not.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
Would you mind signing this for me?
Absolutely.
Should I make it out to anyone?
- To Gail.
- "To Gail." Sure.
- Please.
- No problem.
- God Bless.
- Thank you.
Take care.
What?
I hear it's amazing, your book.
The writing's so-so.
People respond to the idea.
Why no question mark?
"What's Next," period.
I mean, no offense,
but it's not like
you know what's next.
Exactly.
No one knows.
But we can't spend our lives
waiting around
for something that may never come.
Back.
- Sorry?
- Something that may never come back.
You lost someone?
I did.
You know, my daughter,
about a year ago,
she was out in our backyard,
chasing around some of her friends
and she was laughing.
Then she saw me watching her
and she looked guilty,
like she wasn't sure
if it was okay to be happy.
But this, what we've experienced...
...it isn't grief.
It's never-ending.
Ambiguous loss.
If my eight-year-old can find
happiness again...
...why can't the rest of us?
Bullshit.
- I'm sorry?
- No, you're not sorry.
Sorry people
don't write fucking books.
Wait a minute. Ma'am,
if I've offended you in any way,
- that was not my--
- "Ambiguous loss"?
What is ambiguous
about your family being gone?
Well, and you must know
because you lost what, four?
You count your parents in that?
What were they, in their 70s?
You sit there and tell me a story
about your daughter.
I lost everyone.
I lost everything.
You fucking fraud.
You fucking liar!
You're not in pain.
Because if you were in pain,
you would know
there is no moving on.
There is no happiness.
"What's next"?
What's fucking next?
Nothing is next!
Nothing!
Evening.
Excuse me.
Excuse me. Miss, miss, miss.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I saw you back in the bar
and I heard what you said.
And I just wanted to ask you,
do you wanna feel this way?
Yeah, I want to feel this way.
Fuck off.
You're right, you know,
about Johansen.
What? Excuse me.
He's not in pain.
He's a fraud, just like you said,
and I can prove it.
How?
Come on.
This is Ray.
He'll take your payment information.
Payment for what?
Last year Patrick Johansen,
he walked through doorways
just like that.
If you want to know what happened,
it's $1000.
What do you mean,
"What happened"?
You on PayPal?
If not, I can get you set up.
- I have an account.
- Go ahead and pull it up.
You authorize the amount.
Thank you.
Now right this way.
Go ahead.
Come on.
This is Wayne.
Holy Wayne.
I don't think
she's heard of me.
No, she's here about
Patrick Johansen.
Who?
The one who came to you
just before you left for the ranch?
Lost most of his family?
- He ended up writing a book?
- Oh, right.
Right. I didn't read it.
I assume he didn't mention me.
Why would he mention you?
Because I took his pain from him.
What are you doing?
What's your name, love?
- Nora.
Nora, I don't give a shit about you.
I've already got your money
and I'm fucking exhausted.
You've lost someone, yes?
Someones.
And you believe
that you will always feel that pain.
And if it starts to slip away,
you...
...you seek it out again, don't you?
You won't let it kill you
but you won't...
...kill yourself.
For whoever is joined
with all of the living,
there is hope.
Surely, a live dog is better
than a dead lion.
Hope.
It's your weakness.
You want it gone
because you don't deserve it.
Nora...
...you do deserve hope.
I've seen my own death
and it's coming upon me very soon,
so this is your one chance,
your only chance,
and the question remains the same.
Do you want to feel this way?
- No.
Then let me take it from you.
Will I forget them?
Never.
- You have a rewards card with us?
- Sure, I got it right here.
- Thanks.
- All right.
Hello, you've reached
the Durst residence.
Please leave a message.
Nora. Hi, it's Matt.
I know I keep calling.
I should just...
I don't know how many
different ways I can apologize. I...
I've made some changes in my life.
I see things more clearly now.
We're family. I love you.
Message saved.
Hey.
- Hi.
- I looked up your address.
Actually easier to get
than your phone number,
believe it or not.
Did you want to come in or...
No, actually, I'm on duty.
I...
...just wanted to stop by
and tell you
I don't take it personally.
You know, when you said,
"Fuck your daughter."
I was having an off day.
- Divorces will do that to you.
- They will.
Anyway, I just wanted you to know
that I wanna get out here
all the time, just go,
but when you said that
about Miami,
it sounded pretty good.
Maybe we should do dinner
or something first sometime?
- I would love that.
- Good.
All right. But you should know,
though, I'm a fucking mess.
- Thanks for the heads-up.
- All right.
- Bye.
To your knowledge,
did the Departed
regularly use aerosol hair spray
and/or deodorant?
Yeah, I think so.
In your opinion, was the Departed
a charitable person?
Yes.
In your opinion,
was the Departed a religious person?
Yes.
In your opinion, do you believe
the Departed is in a better place?
No.