.
- Previously
on "Good Girls"...
- I got fired from tutoring.
They said I took
their stupid pen.
- She's not me.
- I tried to seduce
my therapist.
He straight up rejected me.
- You have a storied history
of pursuing inaccessible men,
which is a defense mechanism
to protect you from rejection.
- You're gonna like her.
She has birds.
- [baby voice] Good night.
- So we wanted to talk to you
about doing some
custom work for us.
Casino night.
- If it got into
the wrong hands,
it's kinda, like, counterfeit.
- That did not even occur
to me.
- He's alive.
I'm dead!
- Word is, you do
the best work.
I'd like to see how it's done.
[suspenseful music]
- What do you think?
- I think I need you alive.
♪
[upbeat percussive music]
- Customer's here for you.
- Who is it?
- Lewis baby shower.
- I'll be right there.
♪
Congratulations, Mr. Lewis.
Everything in order?
- You'll know if it isn't.
♪
- Yo.
- Welcome to
the Paper Porcupine.
- Here for the Shapiro
bris announcements.
- Of course, Mr. Shapiro.
Back to school night, right?
- Northfield Christian Academy.
- Back in a jiffy.
♪
- Morning, sunshine.
Wow, they don't build them
like this anymore.
- Pickup's not today.
- Is this where the ink goes?
[camera shutter snapping]
- Oil.
Can I help you with something?
Please--
[mechanical clicking]
Please don't do that.
- Okay, my bad.
What tension do you set
the rollers at?
- Why?
- Just curious.
- 'Cause I'm a curious guy.
- Well, you could look
at the manual,
but there isn't one because
this is older than the Bible.
- [chuckles]
See you soon.
- Eww.
- They didn't give me a knife.
- I don't want your grubby-ass
house key on my BMT.
- Gym locker key.
- Gross.
- I barely use it.
- Why didn't you just get
two six-inch?
- Because the foot-long comes
with chips and a drink.
- All good, thanks.
- You know, I would love
to be rolling in six-inchers,
but instead I am working
my ass off for nothing.
- Yeah, 'cause I just love
being homey's
indentured servant.
- Coming home covered in ink
and self-loathing.
- Where is she?
- Voilà.
- Thanks.
- Lock the doors.
- What?
- Hit the locks.
- But they don't work.
They're broken.
- What's going on?
- Take this home
and hide it somewhere.
- Why?
- And only take it out
when we're printing.
- What is happening right now?
- This is insurance.
- For what?
- Anyone can run a printer,
right?
But you need these plates
to make our money,
so if one of us disappears...
- Why would we disappear?
- When he's done with us.
- Jesus.
- Yeah.
- Oy.
- You guys get me
a sandwich?
- Yeah.
[sighs]
[laughter]
[Stan speaking indistinctly]
- Oh, my God, Sara.
What--what are you doing?
Two fingers?
Really?
- So much cream cheese.
- Yeah, it's a lot of cream--
it's a lot--it's a lot--
it's a lot of cream cheese.
- What's all this?
- Hey, baby.
Got you poppy seed.
- They have chocolate
cream cheese.
- I'm sorry, did you just
put that with your lox?
[groans]
Eww!
Oh.
- How long you guys been awake?
- Uh, baby girl wanted to go
to the early-morning service.
- She did, did she?
- Yeah, I didn't
wanna wake you.
- Daddy said you worked late.
- Now...
Lil' Money, he still
in there sawing logs.
I went in there with
his video game music,
put it to the boy's ear--
nothing.
- You could have woke me up.
- Where's that chocolate stuff?
- I put it in the fridge.
- Okay, I see what you doing.
Trying to keep your own stash.
[both laugh]
Okay, now, I'm gonna put
this stuff under his nose,
and if this sugar shock
doesn't wake that boy up,
nothing will.
- [chuckles]
- Oh, Harry!
- So you just found God?
- What?
- Game recognize game, peanut.
I'm just saying.
- Nope, that didn't work.
Okay.
Oh, time to pull out
the big guns.
[water running]
[Raphael Lake & Lily Marly's
"Through a Trap Door" playing]
- ♪ I forget what it's about
♪
♪ Living in my head
♪ I hurt my own heart best
♪ But who cares anyway
♪ What should I worry
myself for ♪
♪ Myself for
♪ Turn the blame away
[items clattering]
- [moaning]
[both breathing heavily]
- Break's over.
- Go again?
- You can do that?
- Yeah.
I'm like a chick.
- Let's just leave it
on a high note.
- Hey, uh, can I...
And I'm not complaining,
but, uh...
what's happening here?
- I'm getting over someone
by getting in front
of someone else.
Cool?
- Happy to help.
- Good man.
- Hey, uh, do you mind if we
just do it at your place
next time?
- I have a kid.
- Yeah, and I have this,
like, back thing,
and tiles just--
- Okay.
So we'll go to your place.
- We already did that.
You live in your car.
- [sighs]
That's kinda how I got
this back thing.
- You're homeless.
- I'm experiencing
homelessness.
- Got it.
- You mind if I take
a shower here?
- We don't have a shower.
- Sink?
- [sighs]
[soft dramatic music]
♪
- Thank you.
[lock clicking]
- [sighs]
♪
- Wake--wake up.
- What?
What is it?
- It's a massacre.
- What did you do?
- I killed them all.
- How much did you feed them?
- Too much.
Well...
not enough.
I--I ju--I don't know.
- They're not ready for this.
[water sloshing]
- I read about this thing.
They can get an STD.
- Eww, gross.
- No, it's called
sudden tank death.
- It's gotta be the water.
- Yeah, I tested it with those
little strip thingies.
One, two, three, up.
[groans]
Easy.
- [sighs]
We'll just tell them
they were sick and we took them
to the fish doctor.
- I'll grab towels.
- And pick up some new ones
on the way home from work.
- They're gonna know.
- They're goldfish, Dean.
They all look the same.
- What's this?
- Nothing.
- Doesn't look like nothing.
- It's for work.
- Then why is it hidden
in the laundry room?
- Where are those towels?
- Is this what you're doing?
- Will you flush these?
- Are you making money?
- Could I get that back?
- No.
- What do you mean, no?
- He didn't waste much time,
did he?
[drawers rattling]
- Dean--
- How do you not see
what's happening here again?
- It's different this time.
- You're like the damn fish
with a castle
thinking it's new.
- You don't understand, okay?
- Oh, look, a castle.
Oh, look, another castle.
- Give it back to me!
- No!
- [gasps]
Don't.
- We can't go back.
- He's gonna kill me.
- You don't kill
something you love.
[metal clattering]
- [exhales heavily]
.
[machines whirring]
- Hey, Beth?
Customer's here for you.
- Mm-hmm.
[machines banging]
[banging loudens, echoes]
There's been a bit
of a snafu.
- You don't say.
- Press needed to be serviced.
- Mm-hmm.
- So we couldn't make
your invitations.
- It's more than a snafu.
- Well, you'll get them.
It'll just be a little bit
of a delay.
- See, here's the thing.
- I get it.
- We don't do delays.
- I know.
- And if that's what
I'm looking at here,
then my boss has been pretty
clear on how to handle it.
- What if I made it up to you?
Like...
not him but you?
- [exhales sharply]
You mean if I wanted
my own invitations?
- No event's too big.
- It'd be a huge order.
- Try me.
- 100,000.
- Easy peasy.
- I'll hold him off
as long as I can.
- Thanks again
for your understanding.
- Which kind?
The super absorbent ones?
- Uh, maybe just get
the variety pack.
- It only gives you
eight of each.
- Yeah, that should be fine.
- How heavy is your flow?
- Like, medium.
- I'll get you options.
What about pain relief?
How are your cramps?
- Babe, I'm fine.
- Oh, I'll pick up some Midol,
just to take off the edge.
- Thank you.
That's very sweet.
- Mm, oh, bubble bath
when I get back?
- Only if you join me.
both: Mm!
[both giggle]
- Isn't he awesome?
- Like nothing I've ever seen.
- Quite a catch.
- So, um, remember that project
you did for us a while back?
- Mm-hmm.
- Well, you did
such a great job
that we wanted
to hire you again.
- Uh, what's the project
this time?
- You're not gonna believe it.
- It's another casino night.
[chuckles]
- Uh, I can't.
[birds chirping]
- We'll pay you more.
- That's not it.
- I can cover you at work if
it's time that's an issue or--
- I'm not comfortable doing
what you're asking me to do.
- It's for a really good cause.
- Gambling addicts, right?
- I'm so sorry
I brought you into this.
- Why did you?
- Okay, well, let me
lay it out for you, Lucy.
That piece of paper that you
found in the dumpster,
shredded,
that's gonna be us.
- Yeah, except you
won't be able
to tape us back together again.
- Hey, babe, I'm gonna
pick you up some pads too,
'cause I know you hate leaving
those things in overnight.
- I'll come with you.
- Oh, awesome.
- Lucy.
Please.
- Just go.
[birds chirping]
[laughter]
[indistinct dialogue over TV]
- He's so happy.
- Why aren't you in bed?
- Shh. It's the finale.
- Why isn't she in bed?
- Shh. America's voting.
- She has school, Stan.
- It's just one night, baby.
Um, tiny country guy
with the glasses?
- No, old lady who raps.
- [laughs]
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, my God.
You should see
this old geezer rhyme.
- Mom!
- Woman!
- Bed--now.
- What the hell's
got into you?
- Close the door, Stanley.
- You know, she finished
all her homework.
- Oh, I know.
Little heifer's
on the honor roll.
She loves animals.
She pops out of bed
for church.
You know what else
our little angel does?
She takes pens--
expensive ones.
Yeah, she did it.
- [sighs]
I know.
- You know what?
- She told me.
- When?
- A while back.
- And you're just cool with it?
- No, I'm not cool.
- You're not not cool.
- You know what I am?
I'm relieved.
- The staying up late
and the cream cheese?
- At least she was too guilty
to live with it.
- What are you trying to say,
Stan?
- [chuckles]
Come on, Ruby.
[chuckles]
- Wait, you're mad at me now?
- When you lie,
you sleep like a queen.
We're just lucky
she knows the difference.
- [sighs]
This is so wrong.
- We gave her a chance.
- She doesn't deserve this.
- Well, we tried asking nicely,
so now it's either this
or the funeral home.
[suspenseful music]
- I want to make it very clear
that we have hit a new low,
even for us,
and once you cross over,
you don't come back the same.
- Do it already.
We've done worse.
[door clicks open]
[door slams]
♪
- What's it gonna be,
baby girl?
♪
- [sighs]
Go.
.
[Juniore's "A Bah D'accord"]
♪
- [singing in French]
[clattering]
♪
- What if she kills him?
- She can't.
- Oh, believe me, she can.
- He's no good to us dead.
- I meant by accident.
How much time do we have left?
- I don't know.
- What do you mean?
- I hit lap timer.
- What's a lap timer?
- I don't know.
♪
[singing in French]
- [sighs]
♪
[bird chirping]
- What if we add up
all the laps?
- I'm afraid to stop it.
- Lucy said he only power walks
for ten minutes.
- [sighing]
Oh, God, I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
It'll be fine.
- No, it's not.
Stan's gonna leave me.
♪
- [singing in French]
[bird chirping]
♪
[bird shrieks]
- Come on.
Why?
- This.
Literally this.
- Birds?
- Birds.
Bodies.
Robberies.
It's ruining our marriage.
- He loves you.
He will get over it.
He always does.
♪
- That's the thing.
He's okay with it.
This is who he thinks I am now.
Oh, God.
- It'll be okay.
- No, he's back.
♪
- Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- Come on, girl.
Get out of there.
Let's go, Annie.
Come on.
- Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on.
- Oh, goodness. Where is she?
Where is she? Where is she?
- Does she have it?
- Drive.
- Why didn't you take
the cage, Annie?
- Just drive.
[engine turning over]
[shushing]
[gears shifting]
[bird chirping]
- Uh, there are matching
envelopes in the back,
if you need them.
Hi there.
Welcome to the Paper Porcupine.
I like your tattoo.
- Oh, thank you.
- What does it mean?
- Well, it's, uh, sort of
for this club that I'm in.
- Cool.
Super cool.
- [laughs]
- I used to sling ink
to pay for art school.
- Hmm.
- Slung ink. Slang?
- I think it's slang.
[laughs]
That's cool.
So you're an artist?
- Yeah, I do all
the work design stuff here.
Uh, custom orders,
stuff like that.
- Oh.
Wait, so you mean,
like,
if someone wanted
something special printed,
you would draw it?
- But you'd pick the paper,
the colors.
- Yeah, but you'd draw it?
- Yeah, and then we'd make
an engraver's plate
and print it all on-site.
- Cool.
- Yeah.
- Cool, cool, cool.
- Yeah, uh, one-stop shop.
- Yeah.
You know, that's good,
'cause I'm, um--
I'd really like to get rid
of the person I'm using now.
- Really?
- Yeah, not so reliable.
- Well, won't happen
on my watch.
Just let me know if I can help.
- Actually, Lucy,
I think you can.
[door clicks open]
[door clicks shut]
- Hey.
How was school?
That good, huh?
- You're mental.
- What?
Oh, wait, hey, uh, wait.
Uh, hey, dah-dah-dah!
Don't go in there!
- I can't go in the bathroom?
- You can, but--
- Your boyfriend just asked me
for toilet paper.
- Who?
- Chris, Kevin?
- Ugh, Kevin.
- He's outside in his car.
- Oh, God.
- He said he wants
to live closer to you
now that you guys are dating.
- We are not dating.
- He's living on our curb.
- He's going through something.
- You said you were done
with this.
- He's homeless!
- You're an addict!
- Ben, Ben!
- We study people like you
in psych class.
- Ben, Ben, Ben!
[bird chirping]
- What the hell?
- [sighs]
It's not mine.
[door clicks open]
[bird chirping]
- I don't understand anything
that's going on here.
[bird chirping]
- His name's Au Jus.
- Give this to your boyfriend.
[door slams]
- Oh, my God.
- Damn.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I tried to get one
with his head
actually in the disposal, but--
- Oh, Jesus.
- I didn't do it.
He freaked out every time
I turned him upside down.
- How'd you even take these?
- Ben's selfie stick.
- Are we supposed
to show all of these
or just choose the best one?
- The one
with the carving knife.
- See, I don't buy that one.
- Well, sorry,
Ansel Adams.
- What don't you buy?
- I don't know.
Maybe if it was, like,
scissors or something.
It's just not believable.
- [exhales heavily]
Well, here,
just scroll to the end.
I did, like, a whole thing
with the microwave and tinfoil.
- Let's just stick
with the disposal.
She's gonna cave.
- Okay.
- If you hold the phone,
then I can do the talking.
That's all I'm saying.
- It's your phone.
- How am I gonna hold the phone
and do the talking--
- I already had to kidnap
a freaking bird.
I'm not doing it.
[tense music]
♪
- What's up, ladies?
.
[dramatic music]
♪
- How we doing, champ?
- My hand keeps shaking.
- Yeah?
It's okay.
Just take your time.
There's no rush.
- She doesn't need
to be involved.
- Oh, 'cause you can do this?
How about you two?
- No.
- I have the software.
- No?
All this time, I thought you
were the one doing
the heavy lifting.
- Just let her go.
- And here you are
stealing my girl's thunder.
[chuckles]
Ain't bitches supposed
to be, like,
lifting each other up
these days?
- So much for feminism.
- [laughs]
♪
Maybe you don't need
to be involved.
♪
[door bell jingles]
- Hello! Lucy!
- It's Mrs. Harris.
I told her I'd stay late
so she could pick up her order.
- Go tell Mrs. Harris
that we're closed, okay?
- Okay.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
- Go with her.
[door clicks open]
[door clicks shut]
Oh, and...be smart, yeah?
[door clicks open]
- Oh, my God.
They're almost too beautiful
to send.
- Wish Henry
a happy retirement for us.
- Now, what do you have
in the way of place cards?
- Uh, we're all out, actually.
- What are these?
It says place cards.
Oh, boy.
What do you think
would go best?
- Blue plaid.
- Okay, but the invitations
are red.
Should we--
- Uh, red gingham.
Right here.
- Oh!
These are perfect!
All right, now, should I just
give you the guest list?
- Uh-huh.
- Yep.
- Okay, great.
Um, definitely
the entire office.
We'll start there.
Uh, Bob,
uh, George,
uh, Troy,
Stanley...
Richard, Ellen, Hakim...
- All right,
I love you, babe.
Good night, sweetie pie.
Good night, bug.
I'll see you in the morning,
okay?
- Daddy?
- Yeah?
- When do Reddy, Bluey,
and Greeny
get back
from the fish hospital?
- Hmm.
W--
It turns out...
that...
The fish doctors discovered
they have superpowers.
- Really?
- Yeah, and they were accepted
at a very special
fish magic school.
It's half "X-Men,"
half "Harry Potter,"
but it's top secret,
so we can't see them
or visit
for a really long time.
- Kenny said you flushed them.
- Huh.
- He saw you do it.
- Well, yeah, that's how
you get to the fish school.
The toilet is the portal.
- Can we get a different pet?
- Fish smell.
- Yolanda, Javier, Esme...
Hannah, and Tom.
Should I just wait for these?
- Friday.
- Friday. Perfect.
[chuckles] Thank you.
[door clicks open and shut]
- You cannot finish that plate.
- He said he'd let me go.
- He won't.
Trust me.
- Can I ask you a question?
Like, as a friend?
How could you take Au Jus?
- I am in
a real situation here.
But I promise you,
I would never,
ever hurt him.
- Why would I believe
anything you say anymore?
[sighs]
All done.
Um, feel free
to email me any questions,
but it's all on there.
- Cool.
- Uh, GraphicFarts89@gmail.
I, um--I spelt it wrong
and then, uh,
got stuck with it.
- Come on.
We'll give you a ride.
- We can walk.
- We have a car.
- Let's go.
All right, rock star.
We'll drop you off
wherever you want.
Least we could do.
- Lucy, don't.
- [exhales heavily]
Here's the thing.
I've been doing this
a long time.
The only way someone like you
gets hurt is if you talk.
You're not gonna talk, right?
- No.
- I got your word?
- Cross my heart.
- Then you'll never
see me again.
Unless I got questions
about that plate, yeah?
- GraphicFarts89@gmail.
- Ah.
[laughs]
My girl.
All right, who's next?
- Wait.
Wait!
What kind of packing are you
gonna put on the plates?
- What?
- What if the press
gets too hot?
- Not your problem
anymore, is it?
- How you gonna stop
ghost marks on the rollers?
What happens if you get slur
with the half tones?
It means your ink's too thin.
So even with a perfect plate,
it's gonna look like
your son made it.
How long did it take you
to get the security glow?
- Um, a while.
- You think they sell
that color at Home Depot?
What if you add too much water
to the mulch?
- Starch builds up.
- And why don't we like that?
Why don't we like that?
- Because the paper
won't feel right.
You wouldn't even be able
to pass it off at a bodega.
- Just because she gave you
a cookbook
to a five-star restaurant
doesn't mean you
can make the dishes.
You need the chef.
You need us.
You need all of us.
- Nah.
- No?
- Not all of you.
[gunshots]
[engine turning over]
[engine revving]
[all breathing erratically]
.
[The Langley Schools
Music Project's "In My Room"]
♪
- ♪ There's a world where
♪ I can go and
♪ Tell my secrets to
♪ In my room
♪ In this world I lock out
♪ All my worries
♪ And my cares
♪ In my room
♪
♪ Do my scheming
♪ And my dreaming
♪ Lie awake and pray
♪ Do my crying
♪ And my sighing
♪ Laugh at yesterday
- Get up.
- What?
- We gotta do this.
- Now?
- Get up.
- All right.
I'm up.
- I'm not a lost cause.
- What are you talking about?
- When you look at me,
I don't know
who you see anymore.
- I see my wife.
- You can't leave me.
- She's acting crazy
in the middle of the night.
- That's how it happens,
you know?
It--it's not any big thing.
You just wake up one day
and you stop caring
that I don't put the remote
back in the same spot
'cause you just got used
to looking for it.
- Well, who says
I'm used to it?
I couldn't watch
anything tonight.
- Marriages don't end, Stanley.
They fade little by little.
- Okay, come here.
- You don't even
see it happening...
[sniffles]
Until it's over.
- Get in here.
- [crying]
- [groans]
Mm, tell me
where that remote is,
and we're good forever.
- Just don't give up on me.
[soft dramatic music]
♪
[door clicks open]
[door clicks shut]
- Mm.
- What are you doing?
- [sighs]
Can I sleep with you?
- Aren't I kinda old for this?
- Please?
- Jordan called an Uber
from the mall
and Chris-Kevin picked her up.
- Oh, no.
- She rode home
in his living room.
- [sighs]
I'll get rid of him.
- I'm still mad at you.
- Don't be.
Not tonight.
- Can we get rid
of the bird too?
It's nesting in the bath mat.
[bird chirping]
- Who's that little guy?
- Meet Dorito Boland.
- [laughs]
When did you buy a bird?
[clicking tongue]
- He's a rescue.
- You tell the kids yet?
[cage rattling]
- I thought we could
surprise them
together after school today.
[bird chirping]
- I wasn't trying
to make things worse.
- I know.
- I just--I really hate you
being around that guy again.
- Me too.
- Really?
So what happened?
Was he pissed?
- Yeah.
- I told you he won't
kill something he loves.
- It's not me, though.
- What is it?
- Money.
- Mm.
How long's this guy
gonna be around?
[bird chirping]
- Um...about 50 years.
We'll have to put him
in our will.
- [chuckles]
He's cute.
[funky music]
♪
[singers vocalizing]
[door bell jingles]
- Beth?
- Hey.
- Have you heard from Lucy?
- She's off today.
Why?
- Uh, she didn't
come home last night.
- What?
- Yeah, cops say it's too early
to do anything.
[scoffs]
I--
- Maybe she's with friends.
- Oh, she didn't
really have friends.
Except for you.
- Well, keep trying her.
I'm sure she's fine.
- [sighs]
[cell phone buzzing]
If you hear from her
or anything like--
- Of course.
♪
- [sighs]
[door bell jingles]
♪
- [singing indistinctly]
♪ Again and again
♪ Sank like a ship
♪ That will never be found