.
- Previously
on "Good Girls"...
[tires squeal]
- [grunts]
- It was an accident.
- He ran behind the car.
- Well, then I moved the body.
- What are we supposed to do
with this?
- We get rid of it.
- What do you want?
- Is there any way you could
take her for the night?
- So you can bone some other
pregnant lady's husband?
- Yeah, she knows.
- Yeah, I'm aware. Thank you.
- So I think it's pretty much
game over.
- Do you think
I could make it in LA?
- We'll put the vroom, vroom,
vroom, back in your--
- Here's what's
going to happen.
You're going to quit your job
and my husband.
This is 5 grand.
Enough for a plane ticket
and a little
to get you started in LA.
I have a few ideas.
If we start catering more
towards women,
I think we could really
increase our sales.
- We both have our own,
you know, superpower.
Why would you want
to wreck that?
[sultry rock music]
♪
- You didn't tell him yet?
- Tell me what?
- We're partners now.
- We threw a man away.
all: One...two... three!
- Tell me again.
- It's kind of late.
- Which part?
- Where you chopped
the dude up.
And you stuck him
in the freezer.
- She did that.
- Where'd you dump the body?
- Downtown.
- Where?
- Hill and Snelling.
- There's a lot of homeless
around there.
- No one saw us.
- That you know.
[sighs]
Tell me again.
[mellow music]
♪
You throw away his shoes?
- Yes.
- Are you sure?
- We threw out everything.
- Okay, whose car did you take?
- Beth's.
- Did you cover
the license plate?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Okay, what about people
with their dogs?
- It was pretty late.
- You don't think dogs like
to whiz late at night?
- No one saw us, Stan.
- That's what everybody says,
and they all get caught.
Tell me again.
- ♪ Looking for love
♪ Looking for love
♪ I'm still
♪
♪ Still looking
♪ Looking for love
♪
♪ I'm still
♪ Still looking
- Why'd you tell me?
- You said no more lies.
- I'm an idiot.
- Kids will be up soon.
You want breakfast or...
Where are you going?
- Get ahead of it.
[vibrator buzzing]
[ceramic shattering echoes]
[vibrating continues]
[knocking]
- Beth?
[door creaks]
Hey. Morning.
Kids want French toast.
- Okay?
- What's the egg-to-milk ratio?
- I usually just eyeball it.
- Hmm.
- I'll be right out.
- Thanks.
- Morning, handsome.
- [groans]
- [laughs]
- Go away.
- Hey, you are gonna miss
these moments
when you go to college.
- That's why I'm going
to college.
- Will you take me with you?
Please?
- Or I could just get
an alarm clock.
- Yeah, but alarm clocks
don't have morning breath.
- This is child abuse.
- [laughs]
All right.
It's time to get up.
- Do I have to go to Dad's
this weekend?
- Is she being cray?
- Yeah.
- Well, you know her hormones
are probably,
like, out of control.
- He cheated on her.
- What?
With who?
- I think a friend of theirs.
- Wow. No way.
- Why would he do that?
- Well...
You know...
marriage is really hard.
- Or he's just a dick.
- Well...
- Whoever he banged
is an even bigger dick.
- Okay, you know...
it's probably really,
really, complicated.
- Or they're both just
king-sized bags of dicks.
- Okay, time to brush
your teeth.
Go on. Get out.
Thank you.
[cell phone chiming]
What?
- Stan said there's a witness.
- What does that even mean?
- It means someone saw us.
- Like a camera?
- There were no cameras.
We checked.
- Like a person?
- No, a damn robot.
I don't know.
- What did he say, exactly?
- He was asking around at work,
and that is what he heard.
- Oh, my God.
- Well, I mean, a witness
could mean anything.
- Someone saw someone
do something.
- Exactly.
- We just threw out
a bag of trash.
- That's literally all it was
from, like,
a purely visual standpoint.
- There's only three bitches
in the world
who know what we did.
- Yeah.
- And they're right here.
- Correct.
- Four.
Four bitches.
- This isn't gonna work.
I mean, we can't--
we can't stay here.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
Were you expecting
the Four Seasons?
- I mean, there's no crib,
there's no tub.
The boys have school.
- I don't think
you're in any position
to make demands right now.
- Mommy! They have Nick Jr.!
- Oh, that's--that's--
that's good.
- Let's go over there
right now.
- Yeah, and rough her up.
Like, verbally.
- Not if she's talking
to the cops.
- What is this
shady trick's game?
- She's just as guilty
as we are.
- Uh, yeah, except guiltier.
She did it!
♪
- So how'd they do it?
[recorder beeps]
- I mean, you know,
I already told you, so.
- Tell the world.
- Can we have some chips?
- Yeah, just not
too many, okay?
This place is way too small.
- You ever been in a jail cell?
- No?
- Real tight.
- All right, so like
I told you, um...
they ran him...
O-V-E-R.
You know, a bunch of times.
And then they, um...
They C-H-O-P-P-E-D up
his B-O-D-Y
into tiny little pieces.
With an M-A-S-H--
mm...
M-A-S-H-I...
M... ma--
- A mashi?
What the hell is that?
- No, um, no,
you know, like a, um,
like a giant--
like a giant K-N-I-F-E.
An A-X-E?
- No, I know
how to spell A-X-E.
Like a big--like a big,
you know, like a big, um...
S-W-O-R-D.
Like... [vocalizes]
- A cleaver?
- No. No.
- Oh, um, you know, they had
them in R-A-W-A-N-D-A.
You know? Oh, with that
terrible uprising.
- Rwanda?
- Yes, but can you--
- Machete!
- Shh!
- [whispers]
Machete?
- Yes.
- Jesus.
- Yes. I know.
[upbeat children's music
playing]
Can you just, like,
go arrest them now or--
- Mm-mm, I need to find
the B-O-D-Y first.
- Oh, yeah.
How's that going?
- We're getting there.
- Yeah, that's good.
- We need you to make it...
go away.
- Without, you know,
making her go away.
- Unless push comes to shove.
[indistinct chatter]
Yes, I know. She's a mother.
Yes, I know she has four kids.
But we have, like, seven
between us.
- What did I say about
your rotten egg?
- So what do you want, a medal?
- Yeah, maybe I do.
- Can you somehow shut it down?
- I can try.
- Just to be crystal clear,
we need
the situation that we're in
to go away,
not the rotten egg
who caused the situation.
- Yeah, I'm gonna need
200 G's. Fresh.
- What?
- Shutting things down
ain't cheap.
- On top of what we're
already washing for you?
- Jesus.
How much to just smoke her?
- We don't have time
to sell that many cars.
- It is what it is.
You need time to think it over?
Maybe a quick bathroom break?
[rock music playing
over stereo]
No?
- No.
We're good.
- Really? Are we?
.
- [chuckling]
Hey. Have you seen
this Fluff Challenge?
The dog thinks the owner
actually disappears.
It's hilarious.
- How many cars would we
have to sell to make 200 grand?
Ball park?
- Uh...
[chuckles]
Like, you know, 20 or 30.
It just kind of depends
on the model.
- How about the Vettes?
- Ooh, that takes
the right kind of customer.
- Well, it needs
to happen quick.
- Well that's--that's not
really how it works.
Plus we don't have that kind
of inventory right now.
- How do we get
that kind of inventory?
- Oh, man.
That guy.
What a--what a punk.
I mean, he's already got
60% of the business.
- It's not for him.
- I am not gonna be
his little bitch.
If he wanted an ATM,
he should have knocked over
a 7/11.
I'm trying to run
a business here.
- It's for me.
I need it.
- Why?
- Can you get the cars?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- Maybe.
- Is there a problem?
- No, there's no problem,
per se.
It's just--it's just more of,
uh, you know...
a thing.
- Oh, what a feelin',
We're wheelin' and dealin'
at the Eastern Michigan
Auto Auction!
Wholesalers, retailers,
come on down.
We've got over 250
pre-owned vehicles
with prices starting
at just $800.
I'll be waiting for your call.
Can you feel the deals?
[cheesy new wave music]
- I mean...
- I know.
- Wow.
- I thought she moved to LA.
- I bought her the ticket.
- Looks like she did
for a hot minute.
- Let's see,
she was Dead Girl on Pier
on "NCIS Los Angeles."
- I'm sorry, is she acting like
she works at the car auction
or does she
actually work there?
- Oh, she's like
the gatekeeper.
And she's got Dean
on permanent waiting list.
- She's blackballing him?
- Yeah, I mean,
can you blame her?
- Ooh,
also Mutilated Corpse in Woods
on "Criminal Minds."
And...
Well, that's it.
- So, we go down there,
we kiss her bony ass
and tell her the cars
are for us and not Dean.
- And by "we," we mean not you.
- Yeah, you don't go anywhere
near her bony ass.
- No, no.
We will take care of it.
- You guys, I'm fine.
It was a long time ago.
People make mistakes.
- I told myself, "Amber,
you give it six months,"
and if acting is not
in the cards, then go home.
I really wanted to be realistic
about my prospects, you know?
I'm not saying I needed
to be Anne Hathaway famous,
but I definitely
should have been
John Krasinski's wife level.
- Emily Blunt?
- I don't know what that means.
- What about the 5 grand
I gave you?
- Acting classes
are so expensive.
- Got any left?
- Sorry.
- I bet it goes fast out there.
And I didn't want to take
a day job, you know?
Like, I moved out there to act.
Not wait tables, so...
Mrs. Boland... I seriously
can't believe you're here.
- I'm here.
- I really owe you one.
- How about 20?
As in motor vehicles.
- Yeah.
- What do you say?
- For him, right?
- For me.
- And we can pay cash.
Look at that.
- Mm-hmm.
- Cash... money.
- I don't care about the money.
- Look.
What he did to both of us
is completely terrible
and I can't excuse what he did.
- Did you forgive him?
- You know what?
I think I did.
- Well.
You're a better person than me.
I don't know, I just--
I don't think I could just
forget all those times...
- And when you say
all those times, Amber...
- Nuh-uh.
- Do you mean all those times
with one woman or...
One time with all those women?
- Or... all those times
with all those women.
- [whispering]
There's no good answer here.
- [scoffs]
I'm so confused.
- How many women did my husband
cheat on me with?
- Um...
Lifetime or per year?
- It's not the damn census.
- Oy vey.
[pounding]
- Well, the good news is,
we got the cars.
- Yay.
- I mean, if you--
if you know someone
is already... a cheater...
- Does it make it
that much worse?
- I don't know,
I'm just asking.
- And it's not a love affair,
right?
I mean, it's like a--
a preexisting condition.
- And... is two worse than one?
And is three worse than two?
Again, I have no clue.
I'm here for you.
You don't have to answer.
- It was just a warm body.
Anyone but me.
That makes it way worse.
- Okay.
- Now we know.
[phone buzzing]
[whispering]
Stan.
Hey.
- Hey. Yeah, uh...
I'm not gonna make it
to dinner.
They tracked his phone.
- That's a good thing, right?
- Yeah, it took us--took us
to the lake just like you said.
Then forensics backtracked us
to the Dumpster
and that came up empty too.
- Good, that's good.
- [mouthing words]
- What's up with the dogs?
[dogs barking]
♪
- We were so close.
I mean, we were almost
out of there,
but then they picked up
a scent.
- [mouthing words]
[melancholy vocal music]
- Where are you, Stan?
- And once they do that,
they don't stop, you know?
♪
They don't stop
until they find a body.
♪
.
[Broadcast's
"You and Me in Time"]
♪
- ♪ You and me
♪ In time
♪ You and me
♪ The river flows down
♪ The flower grows up
♪ The snow makes no sound
on the mountaintop ♪
♪ You and me in time
- Hey! You did it.
How many?
- You tell me, Dean.
- Including Amber?
- Why not?
- Four.
- Wow.
- I love you.
I was pregnant.
I mean, I must have been.
- With one of them.
I think. I don't remember.
- Which one?
- Why does it matter?
- Because it matters.
- [sighs]
Patty.
- The flat-chested one
with no ass?
- Yes.
- She looks like a little boy.
- I don't know
how to respond to that.
- Does that turn you on?
- No.
- Did you bring one home?
- What do you mean?
- Did you do it here?
- Of course not.
- Why not?
- I don't know.
It's disrespectful.
- How was the sex?
- What is the point--
- Was it good?
- What does it matter?
- Was it better?
- I don't know.
It was...
It was different.
- Hmm.
Hot.
- Things weren't good
between us.
- Apparently not.
- Since Jane, it was like you--
- Don't even.
- You did not want me around.
- You're gonna turn this around
on me?
- No, I'm trying to explain it.
- It's called depression.
- I know that.
- It's hormonal, you dick.
- We hadn't had sex
in two years.
- That's not true!
- It is true!
It is.
What did you expect
would happen?
- I'm gonna go feed the kids.
[door closes]
- You going in early again?
- Mm-hmm.
First light.
- How do we play this?
- They're bringing in...
officers from the eighth
and ninth to pitch in.
- Jesus, Stan.
What are we gonna do?
- [sighs]
Put on "Below Deck Med."
- What?
- Yeah, I'm behind.
- You want to watch TV
right now?
- Yeah, I want to see
if our boy Conrad
is still with Hannah.
You know, last time,
they were running
a little hot and cold, so...
[sighs]
- This isn't a grocery store.
- I know.
- Or a bunch of fake cash.
- There is a body,
and they're going to find it.
- I-I-I know!
I-I know.
I know.
I just can't.
Not--not tonight.
I just can't. Okay?
I cannot.
- Well...
You're not gonna believe
what Hannah did to our boy.
- Yeah?
- I don't play favorites.
What I do reward
is initiative.
- Morning.
- In light of your
excellent work habits...
- Yes.
- Excuse me.
Excuse me?
Ma'am?
- You can't do that in here.
- Oh, man.
I was hoping you would rob
the place.
- Guess I wasn't in the mood.
- [laughs]
I used to put vodka
in those in college.
- Can I help you
with something?
- Yeah, uh, do you bowl?
- What?
Bowl. You know, the sport
with the funny shoes.
- No.
- Hmm.
Zumba?
Maybe you garden.
- I like to stay
out of the sun.
- Ah.
Well, there's something
there for everyone.
- Where?
- Crystal Falls Correctional.
- You won't even know
you're in prison.
It's like
an all-inclusive cruise.
- If you came here
to freak me out,
I've already had a night.
- No, I came here
to offer you a deal.
I got a hundred guys
looking for a body
with your name on it.
- I have no idea
what you're talking about.
- Mm.
My source says you do.
- Are you charging me
with something?
- Not tonight.
- Then I'd like to go home.
- When they find
the body, though,
the bougie prison
will be taken off the table.
It'll be Ionia Max,
which is... way less fun.
- I don't know
who your source is,
but they have no idea
what they're talking about.
- No?
- Lot of crazy out there.
- Yeah, right?
[melancholy music]
♪
.
- Where we at?
- Well, I did a deep dive
last night.
Not prepared to label it,
but I ordered a bunch of stuff
about sex addiction
to my Kindle.
- I'm talking about
the cars, Dean.
- Oh.
- How many were sold?
- With...
Rick's Lincoln
and Linda unloading
the Hyundai last night,
we're at--
we're at two.
- We have to sell
the rest today.
- I can't move 20 cars
in a day.
- We have to.
- We both can't steer the ship.
You don't understand
the business.
I mean, I know you think
you do, but it's--
- They're gonna find a body.
- Did you kill someone?
- Not really.
- Jesus, Beth.
- But they're gonna pin it
on me.
I don't have
any more time, Dean.
- I would literally
have to give them away.
- Okay, let's do that.
[upbeat music]
♪
- This is a $50,000 car.
- ♪ One
♪ Two
- ♪ I'm a--I'm a--I'm a--
I'm a big girl ♪
♪ Don't need no help
♪ I'm a--I'm a big girl
♪ I'm a big girl,
I don't need your help ♪
♪ Don't get me wrong,
I can do it myself ♪
♪ My back never broke,
my feet never dragged ♪
♪ So I'm guessing I could
make a run without you ♪
♪ I'm a big girl,
I'm a big girl ♪
♪
♪ I'm a big girl,
I'm a big girl ♪
♪
♪ I'm a big girl,
I'm a big girl ♪
♪
♪ I'm a big girl,
I'm a big girl ♪
♪
- ♪ One, two
- ♪ I'm a big girl
- ♪ Don't need no help
- ♪ One, two
- ♪ I'm a big girl
♪ Don't need no help
♪ I'm a big girl,
don't need no help ♪
♪
♪ I'm a big girl,
don't need no help ♪
♪ I'm a big girl
♪
♪ I'm a big girl,
I'm a big girl ♪
- What?
- What's up with your hair?
- Nothing.
- It looks different.
- Yeah, it's like, fluffy.
- Bouncy, even.
- It's called shampoo, guys.
I washed it.
- [whistles]
Okay.
- Shampoo.
- Yo.
- What are you gonna do?
- Uh, take care of it.
- Buy off a cop
or a judge or something?
- Yeah, you don't really
have to sweat the details.
- Well, how will we know
if it worked?
- If you don't get arrested,
it probably worked.
- It's not really a plan.
[indistinct chatter]
- You trust me?
- God, no.
- That's good.
- What?
- Oh... my... God.
- Oh, I think you know.
- I don't need this
from you right now.
- Oh-ho!
I think you do.
Hey, so just riddle me
this one.
- You don't get to judge.
- Picture if it was me,
'cause you'd be so far
up my ass
about the responsible choice
and keeping it in my pants
and all that bull.
- Dean slept
with half of Detroit.
- Dude, I'm not saying that
you don't deserve to get some
because you obviously do, but,
like, this isn't just some guy.
Why would you drop
that steamy of a deuce, like,
right where you eat?
- What has gotten into you two?
- Oh, I'll tell you
what's gotten into her.
- Oh, come on, shut up.
- Gang friend.
- Don't look at me like that.
- You know what?
It actually makes
perfect sense.
- I'm sorry.
What?
- It's why he gave you
the money.
- That was before.
- Yeah, and you've been, like,
big-timing us for weeks.
- Come on.
- You're on a total power trip.
- I am not!
- Yeah.
You think you're like
the big boss now
'cause your vagina got woke.
- I mean...
[whispering]
How was it?
- You know what, Beth?
You're actually a total liar.
- And you're a truth teller?
- Was it good?
- What's that supposed to mean?
- It means you're screwing
a guy with a pregnant wife.
- I ended that.
- When? Yesterday?
- You know what?
Bone whoever you want.
But I'm telling you right now,
this is gonna end bad.
For all of us.
.
[synth pop music]
♪
[horn honks]
- Chill, dawg!
- I gotta go.
- Yeah, oh, hey.
Um, I made you these,
like, really weird
sandwich kabob thingies
that I saw on Pinterest, so...
- You were on Pinterest?
- Correct.
It's kind of my jam now.
- Weird, but thanks.
[horn honking]
- Cool it!
- I'm gonna be late.
- Okay, uh, uh, well,
don't--don't forget,
um, you have debate
after school.
- I know.
- Uh...
And, oh, I thought maybe later,
we could binge that documentary
about the guy who pushed
his wife down the stairs.
- [laughs]
Can I have my bag?
- What's going on?
Well...
I am the dick
who slept with your dad.
- What?
- I couldn't lie to you, like,
for one more second, you know?
So...
Look, I know this is--
it's really messed up.
And it's really crazy, and I--
I wish I could explain it
to you better,
you know, but... it's just so--
so complicated.
And believe me, I am not proud,
at all, you know?
I totally admit that I am the--
I am the king-size one.
Of the... dicks from earlier.
[horn honking]
Honey, please say something.
- I have to go to school.
- Something else?
- I want to stay
with Nancy tonight.
- Okay.
[horn honking]
Oh, suck it!
Suck it!
[mellow music]
♪
- Just got rid of
half my sales force.
- There's nothing to sell,
anyway.
- Burnt the whole thing
to the ground.
- We did.
- Is everything okay now?
- I think so.
- Well, then, I would do it
all over again.
♪
So now what?
- We start over.
♪
I've been working
on your calendar.
Emma has ballet Tuesday.
Thursday is swim.
Cub Scouts is on Monday.
It's all here.
Oh, and Friday
is early dismissal.
You have to be there
exactly at noon.
If you're even, like,
ten minutes late
they charge you for aftercare.
- Mm. Okay.
So wait.
So you need me
to do all of that?
- I do.
- Where are you gonna be?
- Here, at work.
♪
We can't both steer the ship.
- What's your favorite donut?
- A free one.
- Rotary club
forgot their glazed.
Is that "Nemo" again?
I cannot watch that movie
one more time.
And when they get scared
at the same part,
that's all you, okay?
I'm so sick of that damn fish.
- There's no body.
- What?
- We searched every inch
of that dump.
- That's impossible.
- It's over.
They called it.
- We threw that boy away, Stan.
- Well...
Then we got somebody
looking after us.
- Yeah, we do.
[thumping]
[kids screaming]
[man speaking indistinctly
on TV]
- Call now
before this deal expires.
- You enjoying this?
Is this fun for you?
- What're you talking about?
- Having a hundred guys sift
through a bunch of garbage.
"They C-H-O-P-P'ed him up."
- They did.
- With a machete, no less.
Where do you buy
those from now, huh?
Walmart?
- I saw them, okay?
- In your home, right?
- Yeah.
- In your freezer.
Maybe you did it.
♪
- I just need to, like, shower
and sleep for a hundred years.
♪
- I want you out.
No more staying ahead of it.
No more pen caps.
I want you to stay clean of it
from now on.
- Ruby.
- There's no saving my soul.
I'm already going to hell.
Someone's gotta stay here
and raise these kids.
- Don't you get it, boo?
- You're done.
You hear me?
- Wherever you go, I go too.
- It's the scary part!
- Damn sharks.
- I'm not playing
with you, okay?
- I don't know
what you want from me.
- Give me something I can use.
- I told you everything I know!
- Then why isn't there a body?
- I don't know!
Okay, maybe your guys
missed it or--
or--or maybe someone took it.
- How do you think somebody
even takes a body?
How does that even happen?
- I don't know!
- Maybe Jesus came down.
Or the tooth fairy.
It's a landfill, all right?
It's guarded 24/7.
You know what?
Pack your kids up.
I'm booking you tonight.
♪
- One of them's married
to a cop.
♪
- Check out this ride, baby.
The paint sparkles
like your eyes.
[upbeat music]
- Ladies, are you tired
of being hit on, lied to,
or ignored every time
you try and buy a car?
Then come on down to the new
and improved Boland motors,
where we have on-site daycare
while you shop.
Imported teas and coffees
from around the world.
Free car seat installation.
But most important,
our flexible hours
will suit any woman's schedule,
whether you're stuck at home
or stuck in the boardroom.
We'll make time for you.
Our team of specialists
can't wait
to meet your family's needs.
So come visit us,
and we'll put the vroom,
vroom, vroom
back in your engine.
- Come on, now.
It matches your hair.
- Hit the road, Jack.
♪
- Cut.
Let's take five, everyone.
- I don't know what to do
with my hands.
- Mrs. Boland, I think
your business partner is here.
- Thank you.
You can't tell people
you're my business partner.
- No? What do you want
to call this, then?
- Let's just not
label it, okay?
- Yeah, yeah, you're right.
It is kind of early, huh?
So I got your trash bag
for you.
- Where'd you dump it?
- Nowhere.
Yeah, I figured I'd hold on
to it for a bit.
Just to be safe.
One man's trash...
- Who are you protecting?
You or me?
- Let's just see
how all this goes, yeah?
- Ready, Mrs. Boland?
- "Ready, Mrs. Boland?"
You'll do great, just, um,
picture everybody naked.
- ♪ Oh!
[upbeat music]
♪ Oh!
♪ Na, na, na, na
♪ Yeah, we do it like this
[woman rapping]
- ♪ We coming through, yeah
♪ Getting it
while we do it in style ♪
♪ We be making
that engine vroom ♪
♪ Let me do it like that
♪ Do it, do it, yeah
♪ Let me do it,
do it like that ♪
♪ Do it, do it, uh-huh,
let me do it ♪
♪ Do it like that
♪ Let 'em talk, talk
♪ They know what you got
♪ You touch it,
it turn to gold ♪
♪ Yeah, keep your head up,
you spreadin' that love ♪
♪ Stay lettin'
the whole world know ♪
♪ Let me do it like that
♪
♪ Whoo!
♪ Na, na, na, na,
yeah, we do it like that ♪
♪
♪ Na, na, na, na,
yeah, we do it like that ♪