.
- Previously on
"Good Girls"...
- That's your homie, right?
He's talking to the Feds now.
So, I'm gonna need you
to handle that.
- All right.
Let me see it.
[whistles]
- Am I the only one
who doesn't wanna do this?
- No.
- He's a rapist.
- No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no.
Hang on.
- Don't let him talk.
Just do it.
- You are not going to give
that deposition.
- Because she's gonna kill you.
- How much?
Come on, everyone's
got a number.
But you gotta disappear
for good.
[tense music]
- Well, that's twice now.
- They got to me.
There were, like,
three or four of them.
I mean--
- It won't happen again.
If I have to take you to
the courthouse myself, I will.
- I am just so tired.
I can't kill somebody.
- I'm gonna teach you.
♪
[dramatic percussive music]
- I booked a hotel room.
For the alibi or whatever.
♪
- Girls' night.
- We'll just put her
in the bathtub.
- Yeah.
With a fat glass of wine,
she loves that.
- I got Tylenol PM for after.
Just in case she can't--
- That's good.
She's gonna be fine.
♪
We're all gonna be fine.
Here we go.
That's not him.
- You said he takes
the trash out--
- He does! He always does.
♪
Hang on, hang on.
Oh, my God.
- Call her.
- Okay, I'm calling her.
I'm calling her.
♪
She's not answering.
It must be on silent.
♪
No, no, no, no, no.
[horn blaring]
- Tyler!
- Annie?
- [exhales deeply]
[gun clicks]
[bullet clatters]
- Hey, Annie.
- Hey yo.
- Hi.
What--what are you doing?
You don't close ever.
- Oh, well, now that I'm
the acting manager, I do.
- What about Boomer?
- Oh, he never showed up
for his shift the other day,
so I sort of stepped in.
Hey, did you change your hair?
- The Feds got him tucked away.
- What does that mean?
- Probably protective custody
or whatnot.
Someone got a whiff
of something.
- How do you even know that?
- Home court advantage.
What's up, bud?
- I wanna go on
the monkey bars.
- You wanna go on
the monkey bars?
It looks like someone's
on it though.
- But I wanna--
- No, I know what
you wanna do, okay?
But when that kid's done,
you'll get your turn.
Okay?
All right, come on.
We all gotta tough it out
sometimes.
Have fun.
Playground don't get easier,
right?
Might as well learn now.
- So, you'll take it
from here then?
- Excuse me?
- I mean, if he's in custody
and we can't get to him,
it's over.
- No.
It's over when you finish it.
- How?
- Be a boss bitch.
- I don't know.
Root him out.
He on Facebook?
[upbeat music]
♪
- That's way too many
bathroom selfies.
[chuckles]
- You know Diandra?
- Diandra.
No.
- You know, Diandra-Diandra.
She gave me the fireworks
on my nails for the Fourth,
turkeys for Thanksgiving.
- Yep, yep, yep.
- Her crazy ass boyfriend
is gone.
- What do you mean "gone?"
- Just up and disappeared
a few days ago.
- He ran out on her?
- I mean, she doesn't know.
- Just ghosted, huh?
- Poor girl is losing her mind
trying to find him.
- Ah, well, tell her
to call me.
- Nah, she's too embarrassed.
- She's gonna need to file
a missing person's.
- So, what kinda stuff
would y'all do to root him out?
- Um...
Track the cell,
try family.
You know, he's been talking to
somebody,
you just gotta knock on
the right doors.
- Yeah, right.
- I need the internet
for my report.
- Okay, I'm gonna need you
to check all of that.
- Please?
- What's it on?
- Where our garbage goes.
- Ew.
All right. I'll get off.
- Suspect.
- No way.
Get out of town.
You go here?
- I get my hair done
every Friday.
- You're kidding me.
That is so crazy.
- What a small world.
- Yeah.
It really is.
While I have you, um,
is everything okay with Leslie?
- Oh, why wouldn't it be?
- Well, he just hasn't
showed up for work
in a few days, so you know.
- He hasn't mentioned
being sick.
- Oh, good, but you have
talked to him then?
- Every single night
before bed.
[laughs]
You tell me any grandson
who would do that.
- There are not too many.
- Yeah, the rest of the bunch,
I could take or leave.
But Leslie's a true gentleman.
- Hmm.
He is definitely something.
- It's rare to find a boy
his age so thoughtful.
- Yeah. You don't know
where he is, do ya?
- Well, probably
with his fiancée.
He is so sweet with her.
[gentle music on TV]
♪
- They're all related?
I'm out.
[music stops]
[phone ringtone bleeping]
[clears throat]
Hi, Beetle.
- Where are you?
- Mmm.
I can't say.
- Why not?
- Well, I'm kind of on
a special assignment.
- What the hell, Leslie?
- Look, this is very
high level stuff, okay?
And I might've just
jeopardized your life
by telling you that much.
- Well, you didn't even
leave a note.
- Well, I didn't think
you'd care.
- Yeah, well, I do,
and the kids are worried, so...
- I'm sorry.
- You can't just come and go
out of their lives
like that, you know?
I mean, they don't get it,
so they miss you.
- Seriously?
- Yeah, Benji wanted you
to read him
his bedtime story last night.
- Ah, well...
You tell that little turd
we'll FaceTime.
Okay?
- It's not just him though.
I mean, I...
- What do you mean?
- I mean, I guess
I miss you, too.
So...
Oh, my God.
Mary Pat, just shut up.
- I miss you.
A lot.
Tell you what,
grab a pen and paper.
- Okay.
All right.
Mm-hmm.
I understand.
I promise.
Yeah, I will.
Okay.
I'll see you soon.
He's at the Simple Stay
over on Grand River.
- Ew.
- Oy.
- Gross.
Thank you.
- What are you gonna do?
I mean, when you find him.
- We're gonna make sure
he can't ever bully us again.
- You know what?
I think you should kill him.
.
[distant sirens wailing]
- Someone's been smoked here
before for sure.
- Hold up.
- Okay, we've got ten minutes
till he's back.
- All right.
What are you doing?
- I'm gonna do it.
- Give me the gun.
- It should be me.
- Why?
- Well, you've taken a couple
swings now,
champ, and you did great.
But it's time to bring in
the A-Team.
- Just give me the gun.
- Will you jump in here,
please?
- I got brothers, I don't--
- What if there's a witness?
- Come on.
- Anyone--a maid.
- There has never been
a maid here.
- I can't have this on you.
- Hey, I have done
a few things. Okay?
- I'm the one who got us here,
I did this.
- Hey, he did this.
Son of a bitch
tried to rape me.
- You keep your head down.
- Okay.
Knock and shoot.
- And don't forget to drop
the gun--
- I got it.
I got it.
[exhales]
- It doesn't matter.
It's on all of us.
- ♪ The city of stone
♪
♪ It's so cold and lonely
♪ No love of my own
♪ I can just only
♪ Cry in the night
♪ 'Cause nothing goes right
♪ When you're alone
♪ So I'm alone
♪ In the city of stone
♪
♪ No one to talk to
- What are you doing here?
- I should ask you
the same thing.
- ♪ No one to care
♪ Strangers won't listen
♪
- I was on my way, but--
- Oh, I've heard that before.
My sitter fell through
and then the kids were--
so, I was gonna call.
- I thought you missed me.
Hmm?
- You know, I really don't
like it when you drink though.
- ♪ Alone in the city
of stone ♪
♪
♪ Yeah I got nobody
to talk to ♪
♪ In the city of stone
- Where are you going?
- Will you stop?
The boys are sleeping.
- We booked the reception hall.
- I think you should go.
- We made the guest list.
We spoke to the pastor.
You picked the cake.
- Oh my God, you are so drunk.
- Nana is so pumped.
She has been waiting
her whole life for this.
- Lower your voice.
- We are getting married.
- No, we're not.
- Why would you say that?
- I don't love you.
- You're a terrible person.
- Well don't say that.
- You are.
I hate you.
- I do.
- Stop it.
- God, I hate you.
I hate you so much.
- I said shut up.
When you say things like that,
see, that's what gets me mad.
Okay?
- I want you to leave.
- I'm gonna make you so happy.
- [exhales]
- Where is this guy?
- Probably at a strip club.
- What if he brings one back?
- Please.
They're professionals,
they're not just gonna
go home with anybody.
- 'Cause there's
a code of conduct?
[rustling]
- Something bit me.
- [groans]
This place is nasty.
- What do you think a room
like this goes for?
- 29.99.
- Come on, Beth.
No way.
- It's disgusting.
- Yeah, but you got, like,
you know, Greektown,
and the Renaissance Center,
and--
- Comerica Park, Ford Field.
- It's no more than 40.
- Look it up.
- You look it up.
- You look it up,
I'm holding a gun.
- Like we need to know.
It's 150.
- A night?
- Told you.
[Warpaint's "Billie Holiday"]
♪
[door next door opens, closes]
- ♪ B-I-L-L-I-E
♪ H-O-L-I-D-A-Y
- Mommy?
Mom?
Mommy?
Mommy, I called
but you didn't come.
- Hi--shh.
Come here.
It's okay.
I'm sorry.
What's up?
- I'm hungry.
- You are?
Okay.
Do you wanna go get
some pancakes?
Do you know where Mommy
keeps her purse?
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
So, you're gonna go get
my keys, okay?
And I'm gonna get
your brothers, all right?
But here's the thing, we need
to be super, super quiet.
Okay?
[sniffles]
- What about him?
You know what?
I think we should just let him
sleep a little bit.
Okay?
Okay.
Okay, but you gotta
be quiet.
♪ Tear me away
from my guy ♪
♪
♪ Nothing you can do
♪ 'Cause I'm stuck like glue
to my guy ♪
♪
- [crying]
- I know, bubba.
I know, we're gonna get
that diaper changed
as soon as we can, okay?
Just give me just a second,
all right?
I promise.
Okay.
- What are you doing?
- Hey.
Hey, what the hell?
Hey, open the damn door.
Hey.
Open up.
Where do you think
you're going, huh?
[engine turns over]
Stupid bitch.
Open the damn door.
Let's go.
Where do you think
you're going, huh?
[engine revving]
[Peter Cetera's
Glory of Love"]
- ♪ We'll live forever
♪ Knowing together
♪ That we did it all
♪ For the glory of love
♪
.
- It was an accident.
- We gotta call the cops.
- Uh, she's gotta call
the cops.
We gotta go.
- Just tell them it was
an accident.
- It was.
- Yeah, I mean he--he ran
behind the car.
- He was kinda asking for it.
- Yeah.
I mean, except, um...
Well, then I moved the body.
- Okay.
- I mean, I didn't want
the kids to see it, so...
- I mean, nobody's gonna
argue with that.
Right?
- Mm-mmm.
Where did you, um, put it?
- I didn't want it to smell...
- Okay.
I mean, it's supposed to be
so hot today, so...
- A real scorcher.
- Yeah.
And Jeff used to hunt,
so we have, um,
we have a meat freezer.
- Well, that still makes sense.
- Yeah, except he just got
so bloated.
I think that's because,
you know,
all the gases that
get trapped inside?
So, then he--then he
wouldn't fit.
- What do you mean?
- I mean there was just
like,
like, too much of him to...
You know, at first.
- Oh, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no.
- You know those, um,
those electric knives
like you use at like,
at Thanksgiving?
- [gasps]
- Mommy?
We're hungry.
- Okay, who wants waffles?
- That's a meat locker, huh?
- Dude, we should just leave.
- Don't hold much meat.
- What are you talking about?
- We should go, and the cops
will do their job.
And she'll take the fall,
and we'll be totally clean.
- What are you even
talking about?
- She murdered him, Beth.
- We were about to do
the same thing.
- Yeah, but we didn't,
and we sure as hell
weren't gonna chop him up.
- Small game maybe.
Like, real small.
- Listen, we were the first
call she made.
If she's going down,
we are going down.
- Like a pheasant.
- Do you understand that
she is like
a literal mental patient,
right?
- We made her call him.
- Or a grouse.
- Okay, so, what are we
supposed to do with this then?
Anyone?
- I don't know.
We get rid of it.
- Where?
Well, we wait until it's dark
and then...
And then we'll figure it out.
- [scoffs]
- Be easier to carry
if he's all thawed out.
- Oh, my God.
I am so sorry.
It's just been kind
of a mess of a day.
What did I miss?
- They caught Kenny
in the teachers' lounge.
- Okay.
Not the biggest crime
in the world, so--
- He--he ate somebody's
retirement cake.
- So, we're here because
Kenny had a slice of cake?
- He ate more than a slice.
- He ate the entire cake.
- Well, how many people
was it for?
- Everyone who works here.
Mm-hmm.
Look, in my experience,
behavior like this
is often a cry for help.
Is there anything unusual
going on at home?
- We need to be more present,
put the phone down
once in a while.
- It's not about the phone.
- I heard a thing on NPR
that said phone--
- Maybe it has something
to do with the fact that
some psycho gang banger
shot his dad,
and now his shady ass mom's
running around
doing God knows what.
I mean, where--where were you
last night?
- Book club.
All night long?
- Can we be at a point now
where we just know what
"book club" means?
- You're about to put bleach
in with the colors.
- You wanna do laundry?
We will find someone who deals
with this kinda thing.
- We can't afford a shrink.
Okay, fine.
No phones at dinner.
[solemn music]
♪
- The landfills import enough
solid waste each year
to fill over one million
garbage trucks.
- Hey.
- If you lined those trucks up,
they'd stretch from
New York City
to San Francisco
and back again.
- You okay?
- Long day.
- All right.
Well, look alive
or lose a finger.
- Dirty diapers,
plastic bottles, plastic bags,
coffee cups,
rubber-soled shoes,
dead animals...
- What is she doing in there?
- Her working on her report
about landfills.
- It'd take two hours
just to walk
from one side of it
to the other.
That's almost thirty
square miles of trash.
All dumped right here
in Eastern Michigan.
At this rate...
What?
- Where'd you say
this trash was?
[acoustic music]
♪
- Hey.
- You're kidding me, right?
- How was work?
Sadie's in the car.
- What do you want?
- Is there any way you could
take her for the night?
- So you can bone some other
pregnant lady's husband?
- I have to take
a little road trip.
- Now?
- Yeah, well, a friend
suddenly passed away, so...
- Oh, I'm so sorry.
- You'd be doing it for her,
not me.
- I love her.
- I know.
- I don't love you.
- Hey, Sades.
Sleepover.
[thumping, squelching]
[thumping]
- Can we turn something on?
- With our thinly-shaved
beef carpaccio.
Then zesty ragu made from
from our fresh ground chop
butchered in house.
[thumping and squelching]
.
- Oh
- [grunts]
- Jesus.
- Okay.
Try and lift with your legs.
- You can do it.
- Okay.
[grunting]
[heavy breathing]
- No.
- I don't wanna ask.
So don't.
- We need help.
- We need those
strong sauce arms.
- I would if I could,
but I am telling you I can't.
I can't.
- Ruby, look here.
Look here.
What is tomorrow?
- Trash day.
- So, when do we have
to do this?
- [crying]
Mother--
Forgive me my sins, O Lord.
Forgive me the sins of my youth
and the sins of my age.
- It's okay. It's okay.
We're almost there.
- Forgive me the sins
of my body
and the sins of my soul.
Forgive me the sins
that I have done
to please myself
and to please others.
- Oh, God, oh, God, oh, God.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Let me get my arm under there.
- Got it.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, sweet Lord.
- What's Harry doing in school?
- He's, uh, dinosaurs.
- Oh.
What's his favorite?
- I'm gonna pass out.
- Hey, hey, come on.
Give me a dinosaur.
Come on.
- I don't know.
- What about a Triceratops?
With--
- Oh, uh, no.
- Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
- Pterodactyl?
- T--T-rex.
T-rex, T-rex.
- Danny likes that one, too.
- Kenny, too, right?
He likes...
- Yeah.
What is it with boys
and T-rex?
- Yeah, they're killers.
- [gasps] Oh, my God.
[sobbing]
- I didn't mean--I didn't
mean...
I didn't mean that--Oh, God.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
- We're gonna have to swing
it in.
- Okay.
- Come this way.
- Come on.
Okay.
- Let's do it on three.
- Wait, on three or like,
one, two, three, toss?
- On three.
- So, one, two, three, swing?
- No, see, that's what
I'm saying, that's on four.
Is it on four or is it--
- One, two, swing.
- So, one three.
Final answer.
- Okay.
together: One...
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
together: Two...three.
- Okay, let's just go.
[phone ringtone bleeping]
- Did you check his pockets?
- How would I have checked
his pockets?
[phone ringtone continues]
It's fine, right?
Let's just go, please.
- We can't just leave it.
- But--
- They'll track it to the body.
[phone ringtone bleeping]
Mother--
- Hey, will you stop it?
Boys, will you cut it out?
Hey.
Will you--you know,
someone's going to arrest you
if you keep doing that.
You're not supposed to be--
- Boys, boys.
Or I cold rustle up
a public disobedience charge
if that'll help.
Hi, sorry, I don't...
I didn't wanna bother you,
I just didn't--I didn't--
boys, will you sit down, okay?
Go sit down.
I just I didn't--I didn't know
who else I could talk to, so...
- What's going on?
- I'm--I'm worried
about Leslie.
- Why's that?
- I think something
bad happened.
- Let's talk in my office.
- Okay, boys, follow
the nice man
into his office, okay?
And don't touch anything
while you're in there.
Take--yes.
Take the--thank you.
- Well, this should keep 'em
busy for a while.
- Let's just get it over with.
[phone ringtone bleeps]
Who keeps calling this dude?
- It's Marion.
She's called him, like,
seven times.
- Don't.
Annie.
Don't.
- What time you coming
tonight, honey?
I need to know when
to put the roast in the oven.
Oh, you're really gonna
tease me.
I mean, guess what I forgot
to pick up?
The roast.
[chuckles]
[somber music]
♪
Don't worry about dinner,
you're probably out
having a good time.
I hope you're wearing
some of that nice cologne
we bought.
- Stop.
- Well, I'm turning in.
I'm sure I'll hear
from you tomorrow.
You be a good boy.
If you would just give me
a quick ring when you get in,
even if it's late.
It's the funniest thing,
I just can't get to sleep.
- [ragged breathing]
.
[Hannah Georgas's "Walls"]
♪
- ♪ It's too easy
♪ To give in these days
♪
♪ It's too easy
♪ To blend into the grey
♪
♪ When I build these walls
♪ I build them so high
I build them so high ♪
♪
♪ It's too easy
- I'm sorry I ate the cake.
♪
- ♪ To walk away
- It's not your fault.
♪
- ♪ So you could leave me
- Hey.
How late did you work?
- I did something really bad.
- Hey.
What'd you do?
- [sniffles]
I took a payday loan.
I used your check as collateral
and forged your name.
- Why?
- Insurance was taking forever,
I had bills.
I don't know,
I just walked in--
- All right, all right.
It's okay.
It's no biggie.
We'll figure it out.
- Morning.
- What's the worst thing
you've ever done?
- What?
- Like, the worst.
Like, the all-time worst
possible thing.
- It's kinda early...
- Come on, Sadie.
- Um...I cheated on
an English test.
- W--how do you even do that?
- We had to write
original poems,
and I couldn't come up
with anything good,
so I just used Miley Cyrus.
- What song?
- "Wrecking Ball."
- That's a great song.
- Am I in trouble now?
- I mean, yeah, maybe.
- But you asked.
- All right.
We'll make a deal.
You're off the hook if you
swear to cap it right there.
- What do you mean?
- Promise me that
you won't ever, ever
do anything worse than that,
okay?
- Okay.
- No, Sadie, I mean it.
Look me in the eyes
and promise me right now.
- Promise.
Can I go shower?
I have school.
- Yeah.
Go--go get clean.
[upbeat music]
♪
- Good match, counselor
- Huh.
Their key witness missed
the deposition again.
- See, you worry too much.
- Anything I need to know?
- Nope.
- Client-attorney privilege.
- All good.
- Are you being careful?
- Always.
- Did you go for a run?
- If by "run" you mean
a sad old man shuffle,
then yes.
- Good for you.
- Yeah, PT's starting
to pay off.
- I found a therapist.
- I thought you said
we couldn't afford one.
- He's a grad student
at Wayne State.
They need the hours,
so he's cheap.
- Nice, how soon can he start?
- I think this week.
- I just want Kenny
to feel safe again, you know?
- Me too.
- Hey what do you
think about Krav Maga?
- Huh?
- It's this badass Israeli
like, fighting style.
My PT guy says it'll make him
feel more in control.
- Yeah, sure.
- Cool.
You okay?
- Yeah, I've just had--had
too much coffee.
- Slow down, tiger.
I am going to go do abs.
[upbeat French music]
♪