.
- Previously
on "Good Girls"...
- So I got
your trash bag for you.
Yeah, I figured
I'll hold on to it for a bit.
- Who are you protecting,
you or me?
- I want you done.
- It's over.
- Which part?
- All of it.
Bring the children home, okay?
- How did they even know
about the pills?
- Or exactly where
to look for them?
- Someone said something.
- Did you remove a pen cap
from the evidence locker?
- You're not going away
for this.
We'll get you a real lawyer.
- You know how much that costs?
- So how we gonna do this?
[funky music]
- I took it all out.
- Oh, my God.
You left our payday
in a trash can?
- You do whatever you want
whenever you want...
- I take risks, Ruby.
- Without thinking about
anyone else but yourself.
- What are you doing here?
- I tried calling.
- I blocked your number.
- You don't gotta know
about this, then.
- Where are the books?
- Uh, they--
they're in accounting.
- Not those books,
the book club books.
- FBI!
- Everybody down.
Where is she?
Mrs. Boland,
we're gonna need you
to come out now.
♪
Lot's clean.
- They knew we were coming.
♪
[man singing in French]
- Kenny, now!
♪
- How'd you know
they were coming?
♪
- I didn't.
I just stopped in
to go over promos with Linda
and I saw all those cars,
like, a block away--
all those FBI guys.
- That is some Spidey sense.
- Or lucky, like you said.
- Yeah.
♪
[clears throat]
So...
did he call or text?
♪
- Check my phone.
- It's weird, 'cause...
Janey saw you
in the park with him.
♪
You said you were done.
- He did us a favor.
- Are you kidding me?
We wouldn't be here
if it wasn't for him.
That dealership,
do you know how long
it's been in my family?
'Cause it's gone now.
- Can we do this another time?
- Hey, honey?
Give this to your mom.
- Thank you.
- We had a deal, Beth.
- We still do.
[door clicks]
- My slime kit came!
- You're gonna be late
for school.
- Can you open it?
Please, please.
- Okay, but then I want you
in the car.
I'm serious. And, you guys,
grab your backpacks.
♪
- Can I see?
Can I see?
♪
- We're gonna do slime later.
- Kenny, I got your backpack!
Let's go!
♪
Come on. Chop-chop.
[indistinct chatter]
Let's go.
[door slams]
- And you get 10% off
your next purchase.
- Well, thank you.
- Yay, you.
- Here you go.
- Thank you very much.
[cheerful music playing
over speakers]
[woman singing indistinctly]
- Hey, uh, can you cover
for me?
- Where you going?
- Home. I don't feel well.
- Oh, I would,
but, uh,
I gotta organize
the meat freezer.
It's getting crowded again.
Hunting season.
- [sighs]
Since when do we hunt
our own meat, anyway?
What is it, like,
a weird farm-to-table thing?
- No, um, it's a service
we offer the community.
Anyone can store
their meat in there for a fee.
And if you want,
Karl will butcher it.
No charge.
- Good to know.
That's totally disgusting.
[man over P.A. system]
Coffee filters are 25% off
until 10:00 tomorrow.
- Hmm.
Hey.
- Hey, pal.
How--how are you?
- Oh, hey!
- Hi.
Are you okay?
- Fine, yeah.
Fine.
- Need a break?
- Not really.
- You want to tell me
what's going on?
- Nothing.
- You've been avoiding me.
- [sighs]
♪
I don't know
if I can do this.
- Well, that's not nothing.
- Well, I-I didn't know
how to tell you.
- So you--you just waited
for me to take the hint?
- I'm sorry.
I'm not good at breaking up.
- Wait, we're breaking up?
- Well, I don't know.
I...
- Well, that's not nothing.
♪
- I just need
to figure some things out.
♪
- I think I just got dumped.
- What'd she say?
- That she has
to figure stuff out.
- Yeah, brother,
you got dumped.
- [sighs]
What is that?
- Mrs. Boland left a page
from her ledger.
- [sighs]
- Okay, here's what
you're gonna do.
You're gonna buy yourself
a pint,
something shameful like Oreo
or cookie dough.
- Go to hell, man.
- Then you're gonna watch
"Fault in Our Stars."
- Oh, I already
read the book.
- Anything to get
the tears flowing, okay?
- Mm.
- Then you just gotta
flush her out.
- You're a dick.
[grunts]
- And maybe if you stopped
thinking with yours,
we'd have more to go off of
than a scrap of paper.
[faint indistinct chatter]
We still need her.
- I'm cool with her kid.
- Then do that.
And do this too.
- You're paying
for the ice cream.
- Gladly.
- We should be okay
until tomorrow.
- Yeah.
[light music]
♪
- Coffee?
- Oh--
- Sure.
- Thanks.
- Starbucks, Great Lakes,
or Astro?
- Just, uh, tap.
- I'm sorry?
- Oh, you know,
from the pot's fine.
- We have a runner who will
get you anything you want.
- Um...
- Uh...
- Cappuccino's fine.
- PSL.
- This is a joke, right?
- Well, I'm sorry
to waste your time.
- No, no, no, no, no, no,
it's this case.
[laughs]
This is hilarious.
This thing ought to have
its own set
down at the Comedy Castle.
I mean, they haven't offered
one single argument here
that isn't laughable.
- W-we didn't
find it funny.
- Okay.
So they're charging you
with evidence tampering, right?
You ever heard of something
called chain of custody?
- Um, yeah.
- Is that good or bad?
- Good, 'cause this pen cap
that they're saying
you took?
It's been through
so many undocumented hands,
you're just as guilty as
anybody else in that station.
- So you think
you can get him off?
- I can and I will get him off.
Happy birthday.
[laughs]
So all we'll need
is a signed letter
of engagement
and we will deliver some pain.
- It says here, um,
you require a retainer
before service?
- Yes, yes.
We bill our time against it.
It's just to streamline
our accounting.
But as soon
as we get the check,
we'll get started.
- And, um, how much
is that retainer?
- Ten grand.
- Hmm, okay.
♪
- Didn't know
if you wanted whip on the PSL,
so you got both.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
♪
[woman vocalizing]
- [groaning]
- Ew.
- [yelps]
Okay.
- That's a white boy's thumb.
- Could be a toe.
- That's not a toe.
- 'Cause I suggested it?
- Because it has hair on it.
- Yeah, like a big toe.
- Guys.
- You have hair on your toe?
- Like you don't.
- I am not a hobbit.
- It's evolutionary.
People have to have
a tiny bit of fur left from--
- Whatever, Frodo.
- Guys.
It's Boomer.
I mean, it has to be, right?
- I don't know.
Don't look at me; I don't know
what his toe looks like.
- You know what his thumb
looks like?
- Well, it's clearly personal.
He wants me back.
- I mean, there's nicer ways
of saying it, gang friend.
- I blocked his number.
- Greeting card,
I mean, e-card,
an edible arrangement.
- So what are you gonna do?
- [sighs]
[finger thuds]
He needs to get over it.
[garbage disposal whirring]
[Sam The Sham & The Pharaohs'
"Li'l Red Riding Hood"]
- ♪ Who's that I see
walking in these woods? ♪
[garbage disposal grinding]
♪ Why, it's
Li'l Red Riding Hood ♪
♪ Hey there,
♪ You sure are looking good
♪ You're everything
a big bad wolf could want ♪
[garbage disposal grinding]
♪ Listen to me
♪ Li'l Red Riding Hood
♪ I don't think
little big girls should ♪
♪ Go walking in these
spooky old woods alone ♪
[howls]
♪ What big eyes you have
♪ The kind of eyes
that drive wolves mad ♪
♪ So just to see
that you don't get chased ♪
♪ I think I ought
to walk with you for a ways ♪
♪ What full lips you have
♪ They're sure
to lure someone bad ♪
♪ So until you get
to Grandma's place ♪
♪ I think you ought to walk
with me and be safe ♪
♪ I'm gonna keep
my sheep suit on ♪
♪ Until I'm sure
that you've been shown ♪
[garbage disposal grinding]
♪ That I can be trusted
- [coughing, gagging]
- ♪ Walking with you alone
♪
[howls]
♪ Li'l Red Riding Hood
[garbage disposal grinding]
♪ I'd like to hold you
if I could ♪
♪ But you might think
I'm a big bad wolf ♪
♪ So I won't
[garbage disposal grinding]
[howls]
♪ Li'l Red Riding Hood
♪ You sure are looking good
♪ You're everything that
a big bad wolf could want ♪
- All right, what do you want?
- Thought you'd never ask.
.
- Wait.
- Yeah.
- W-why do you have--
- Because now we have
to work off a debt.
Apparently,
two budding entrepreneurs
took it upon themselves
to go on a pill run
but didn't deliver the pills.
- Guess whose fault that was.
- Don't even start with me.
- So you went behind my back...
again.
- To be fair--
- We needed the money.
- And you said you were out.
- You know how much
a real lawyer costs?
Like, 11,000 doughnuts.
- Have you ever had
a lemon rind
stuck in your garbage disposal?
It goes round and round
and jacks up all the blades.
Turns out, so does an ear.
- Jesus.
I mean, how much
of him is left?
- Enough to send to the cops
if we don't, as he put it,
"Do what you do."
- But I mean--
I mean, what about the FBI?
- What about the FBI?
- Well, I mean,
what if they're watching us?
I mean, I don't know that
they're literally watching us,
but, you know,
after what happened
with the raid,
they--they could be
watching some of us...
or one of us...
or none of us.
Let's move on.
- How does he expect us
to wash this much cash
without the cars or Costco?
- What do common criminals do?
You know what I mean.
[Matias Aguayo's "Rrrrr"]
♪
- ♪ What you looking
is my language ♪
♪ Very different
that I speak ♪
♪
♪ Am I waiting for my pears
under an olmo o algo así ♪
♪
♪ I've been doing a request,
it took me más que una night ♪
♪
♪ And you look
si como un porro ♪
♪ Ya te puso super high
♪
♪ Tenés que decir, "Rrrrr"
- Hi there.
♪
- ♪ Rrrrr
- ♪ Repitelo decí, "Rrrrr"
♪
- ♪ Rrrrr
- ♪ You were doing
all your best ♪
♪ Is what you told me
just así ♪
♪
♪ Y lo que no querias hacer
eso me lo dejaste a mí ♪
♪
♪ Si quieres estar conmigo ya
es too late, I say good-bye ♪
♪
- It's all I have.
- ♪ I am giving
a respuesta, girl ♪
♪ Just make me feel alive
- ♪ Rrrrr
- ♪ Tenés que decir, "Rrrrr"
♪
- ♪ Rrrrr
- ♪ Repitelo decí, "Rrrrr"
♪
- [sighs]
Hey.
- Hey.
- Do you, uh,
want to order a pizza?
I'm too tired to cook.
- You don't cook.
- Well, then can you call?
Because I'm too tired to dial.
- Sure.
- Ugh.
[indistinct chatter on phone]
[laughs]
- [laughs]
- What's so funny?
- Someone taught a parrot
to burp.
- I mean, is it
actually burping,
or is it just imitating
a human burp?
- I'll ask Noah.
- Wait, what?
- He tagged me on the parrot.
- What do you mean,
he tagged you on the parrot?
- I mean he DM'd me.
- Wait, when are you guys
DM buddies?
- Why do you care?
- I just don't want you
DM'ing him.
- Fine, I'll text.
- Hey, I don't want you
anything-ing him, okay?
- What did you do?
- What do you mean?
- You always do this.
- Sadie, no--
- Whenever you find
someone normal--
which is never--you mess it up.
- Look, it's not--
it's not like that, okay?
- He's cool.
- [sighs]
Well, I'll find someone cooler.
- I like him.
- Well, I'm sorry,
but that can't always
be enough.
- Why?
- Because.
You know, he may not be
as normal as we think he is.
- Well, now we'll never know.
[dynamic music]
♪
[women vocalizing]
[coins jingling]
♪
- Slime kit came.
- Oh.
Good.
- Where have you been?
- Just running errands.
Man, I hate these ties.
It breaks every single time.
- Beth.
- Huh?
- I don't know
what to do anymore.
- I'm really trying.
- Are you?
- I mean, it's not
the kind of job
you can just go to HR
and give your notice.
- But maybe you don't
want to quit.
- I do.
- Then I don't think you can.
[sighs]
I want to make it as easy
as possible for the kids.
I don't want
to get lawyers involved
unless, of course, you do,
but we can't really
afford them, so...
I gotta protect my family.
- But I'm gonna get out.
- Yeah.
Me too.
.
[birds chirping]
- Did you knock?
- No, I usually case the joint
before I knock.
- Do you wake up every day...
[knocking]
With this much attitude,
or is it just for me?
- Just you.
- You want me
to say I'm sorry?
I'm sorry, okay?
You want me
to say it in Spanish?
- I want you to say it
like you mean it.
[door clicks]
[gasps] Janey!
- Hi!
- Hey, uh, where's Mommy?
- He'll definitely
get the kids.
- Hey, you don't know that.
- And the house
and the cars, this bed.
- He said it won't get ugly.
- It always gets ugly.
- Well, that's true.
- How'd you guys do?
- Uh, slowish start.
- I washed $400 in quarters.
- Ugh.
Yeah, no, I totally quit.
- We're never gonna
pay it down.
- If he didn't have that body,
he couldn't hold it over us.
- But he does.
- What if he didn't?
- I'm sorry,
you want it back now?
- Be hard to find.
- Would it?
- I don't know
where he keeps his bodies,
and I don't want to know.
- That guy loves
a storage facility.
- You'd--you'd need
to get in first.
- I need his key.
- You don't even know
where he lives.
- But I know where he drinks.
[Broadcast's
"Forget Every Time"]
♪
- ♪ If I were a candle
♪ I would dance for you
♪ Maybe I'd move the shadows
♪ In your room
♪ And if you wanted to
♪ We could be together
♪ I think we should
♪ Ah-ah-ah
♪ Forget every time
♪ My words cursed
♪ You never turned dirt
♪ Let's dig ourselves out
♪ Of this world
♪ Ah
♪ Ah-ah-ah
♪ Ah-ah
♪
- Uh, hi.
So this is
really embarrassing.
Um...
I had a little sleepover
with your neighbor last night.
- Mm, Brian?
- Um, the other one.
- Uh, Christopher, 3B?
- The one with the little boy
and the--
- Okay, Christopher.
- Right.
We didn't really get to names.
[laughs]
Um, but he left,
and I went out in the hall
to make a phone call
because I couldn't
get reception inside,
and then the door locked
behind me, so...
do you happen to have a key
to Christopher's apartment?
- No, sorry.
- Okay.
Is there, like,
a super or something?
'Cause I've just--
I've gotta go back in there
and get my clothes
and my, you know,
morning-after pill.
- This is
my girlfriend's place.
I don't even know.
- Okay.
Thanks.
[laughs]
- You could try
the fire escape.
These windows never shut.
[distant sirens wailing]
[dramatic music]
♪
- Find what you're looking for?
- No.
- You want to tell me
what it is?
- No.
- Hmm.
All right.
[sighs]
Let's play a game, yeah?
20 Questions.
I'll start.
Why'd you follow me around
all day?
- Was that your ex-wife?
- 18.
- That's not an answer,
Christopher.
- [chuckles]
Why are you here?
- 17.
- Oh, that's not an answer,
Elizabeth.
- Is this some sport to you
or some twisted hobby?
- 15.
- What am I supposed
to do here,
buy that body back
for the rest of my life?
Piece by piece, limb by limb?
How much for an elbow?
Any eyeball?
- 8.
- You're supposed to answer,
though, aren't you?
Why aren't you answering?
- Why are you
talking so much?
- It'll take a lifetime
to wash all that money.
- Yeah, that's kind of
the point.
- Why are you doing this?
- I mean, you came to me
way back when, right?
Asking to be a part of it.
Now you a part of it.
- When does it end?
- [sniffs]
One question left.
You want it?
Would you please
leave my house now?
.
- What's that?
- Oh, one of those
"choose the ending" books.
- How about you choose
your homework?
- My hot air balloon's on fire.
- What are your options?
- "Stay and try to put it out"
or "jump with my dog
into the unknown below."
- You don't know
what's down there.
Crocodiles, clowns.
- The extinguisher is empty.
We exploded
into a billion pieces.
- Sorry.
All right, homework, baby girl.
[clears throat]
- So Daddy's going away
for a long time, huh?
- Who's talking to you
like that?
- Daddy.
- Oh.
- He said I needed
to help you out more.
- What else did he say?
- That it was wrong
but he'd do it again.
- He said that?
- If he didn't
do something bad,
something worse
would have happened.
- Go back and see what happens
if you jump.
[cheerful music]
♪
[man and woman vocalizing]
Afternoon, Tara.
Starbucks, please.
Chai tea latte,
oat milk, no foam,
extra hot, dash of cinnamon.
- Right away, Mrs. Hill.
♪
- So what'd you do
to get this much cash?
Because I'm betting
that it's way worse
than stealing a pen cap.
- You said you needed
a retainer.
- Mrs. Hill, we pride ourselves
on our reputation here.
- I got you the retainer.
- I can't risk
losing everything
that I put into this firm.
- So it's like that, then.
- 20 grand to cover the risk
and another ten
for our reputation.
- Tell Tara
to make it a grande.
- Will do.
[bittersweet music]
♪
- You're right.
- About what?
- I can't quit.
- Why?
- [sighs]
It feels good...
to be really good
at something.
- You're good
at the dealership too.
It's not enough, is it?
Does he, like...
listen to you more or...
you know, encourage you
in ways that I don't?
- I just really like
having sex with him.
Yeah.
- ♪ Tell me, did the wind
sweep you off your feet ♪
♪ Did you finally
get the chance to dance ♪
- What is happening
right now?
- Oh, now you want
to bring Train into this?
- Can you turn it down?
- ♪ Did Venus
blow your mind? ♪
- A really, really
thoughtfully written song.
[music loudens]
- Can you please?
[music softens]
Give me some of that.
[music playing softly
over stereo]
♪
- [sighs]
- So...
you hear from Beth?
- She couldn't find the body.
♪
Did you come all the way here
to ask me that?
♪
- I'm sorry.
Lo siento.
- French.
- Je suis désolée.
- German?
- Eine un Wiener schnitzel.
♪
- That's not real.
- But I mean every word.
♪
I got Stan a lawyer.
- How?
- I'm a disaster.
- What did you do?
- I used
the counterfeit money.
- Oh, Jesus.
- [sighs] I'm like
that oil spill in the Gulf
where they're still
cleaning up the pelicans.
♪
I'm the mess, not you.
- Oh, believe me,
I've destroyed
my fair share
of ecosystems.
- But I shouldn't
have said it.
You're a good person.
You always have our backs--
- Noah's FBI.
I told him stuff.
- What stuff?
- Like, a lot.
Do I win?
- It's real close.
.
- Hey, when does Noah's
shift start?
- In, like, 20 minutes.
Why?
- 'Cause that's what time
I'm gonna get the puke flu
and go home.
- Yo, Tyler, I just left it
out on the loading dock.
- Cool, I'll hang it up
for you.
What'd you bag this time?
- Six-point buck.
- Oh, hell yeah.
- [laughing] Yeah.
- [chuckles]
That guy.
- So people pay you
to store the meat?
- Oh, no, I'm just
holding on to it for Boomer.
He set the whole thing up
before he went AWOL.
- [scoffs]
That sketchy little weasel
would take kickback
from anyone.
- Literally anyone.
[laughs]
[man over P.A. system]
Cleanup on aisle two.
- Wait...
what do you mean,
literally anyone?
- That, I'm not
at liberty to say.
- It's not just hunters, is it?
And...
it's not just deer meat, is it?
- I'm not really allowed
to ask what it is.
[Drinks' "Blue From the Dark"]
- ♪ Buildings
♪ Climbing a tree
♪ How're you gonna take
the blue from the dark ♪
♪
♪ Cold shin
♪ Out on a limb
♪ How're you gonna take
the blue from the dark ♪
♪
- [sighs]
At least he's ours now.
- This cannot be
his final resting place.
- Why not?
- 'Cause he's not a hamster.
- Do you want
to throw him away again?
- Do not start.
- Okay, we will take a minute
and we're just gonna decide
the best way
to dispose of him properly.
- And respectfully.
- I wish there was a toilet
big enough to flush this turd.
All due respect.
- So all this is going on
right under
your boyfriend's nose?
- How many bodies
are in there?
- [sighs]
I only saw ours...
and a pit bull somebody's
probably getting stuffed.
- Ew.
- Gross.
- And he's not
my boyfriend anymore, FYI.
- Maybe he should be.
- No.
- You could hand-feed him.
- It would get him
off our trail.
- With my vagina?
- If we could use
somebody else's, we would.
- I really liked him.
- I know.
- Sadie, like, loves him.
[mellow music]
♪
- Are you ready for this?
- Uh, hit me.
- You not ready for this.
Mama, you ready for this?
- Play the damn song already.
- [laughs]
- Okay, watch this.
[playing Scott Joplin's
"The Entertainer"]
Okay, now you do it.
♪
Oh...
Mm.
[smooching]
♪
[humming]
- Okay.
- What?
Can't love up on my wife?
- Get the spoons, Casanova.
- Mm, spoons.
Got it.
[humming]
- I like this mood on you.
- I like having
my daughter back.
- Me too.
- I also like having
a good lawyer.
- Me too.
- What I don't like
is how we're paying for it.
- If I didn't do something bad,
something worse
would have happened.
- Who--who said that, now?
- Daddy!
- Keep it going, baby.
I'm coming.
♪
[silverware clattering]
- So what am I
looking at here?
- It's not a VIN.
It's not a bank account.
It's not a street address.
- Okay.
- That...
is a serial number.
- She keeps records
of her cash?
- Oh, yeah.
'Cause it's not real.
Forensics tracked these
back to three different sources
in the area, okay?
The paper's all totally legit,
but the bills are all
in sequence, man.
- That's as good as it gets.
- Yes.
They're counterfeiters.
The pills are just the tip.
Who knows how big
this thing goes?
So...
I mean, don't hold back.
I'm awesome.
- Here's the thing:
she's a mother of four.
She volunteers, crafts,
bakes for the neighborhood.
- Okay.
- We jump on this now,
she'll get Martha Stewart time.
If we dig deeper--
just a little deeper--
connect the dots...
- You get motive
for the murder too.
- I want everything.
- Question...
Does your boyfriend know how
much you think about this shit?
- Shut up, man.
- Here's what we're gonna do.
We're gonna go out,
get a pint, okay?
Something real bad like, uh--
like cookie dough.
Does this sound familiar?
- You want to know what it is?
- Yes, please.
- She's a terrible human being.
And she thinks
because she lives
in this clean little bubble
that no one's gonna notice.
- So...
mint chip?
- Get out.
- Mm-hmm.
- And I'm tired of getting
all the carrots back.
I'm spending money.
You guys have to eat
a vegetable.
- Yeah, just dip them
in ketchup.
Pretend they're French fries.
- Here you go.
- Hyah!
[children chattering
indistinctly]
- I'll pick them up later.
- Hey, uh...
thank you.
- I mean, it is my turn.
- No.
For, you know,
finally being honest.
- I signed the papers.
They're on your desk.
- Look, I'm not gonna try
to take anything.
Like, I don't want
the house or--
- What about the kids?
[door clicks]
- Mommy, come here!
- One second.
- The Coopers' dog
is eating your new flowers!
[dramatic music]
♪
- Oh, my God!
Macy, Macy, Macy!
Get out of here!
[dog growling]
Get out of there!
Come on, come on, come on!
Go home!
♪
[woman and man vocalizing]
[bag tears]
♪
[metallic clattering]
- So what's going on?
- What ya making there, B?
- What color was Boomer's hair?