.
[bright tones]
- Previously,
on "Good Girls"...
- Did you come to steal my baby
like you stole my husband?
- We can do this.
Let's meet this little guy.
- Are you in love with your ex?
- Kind of.
- So do I even have
a shot here?
[moaning]
- How's it going
with the sister?
- I'm out of the friend zone.
- Already?
- Yeah.
- You didn't tell him yet?
- Tell me what?
- We're partners now.
- What's homeboy look like?
- That's him.
- [gasping]
- Can you guys kill him or not?
- Half up front,
the rest after we dust him.
- Oh, my God!
Oh, no, no, no!
- First thing that you did
was to check on your money.
- He left me,
and he took my kids.
- It'll be worse for him
when they find out he took
the pen cap.
So you let me know
how you want to play it.
- You took this from my house
while my daughter was missing.
Are you gonna give it to him?
- No.
- I would never even
think about it.
- Did you remove a pen cap
from the evidence locker?
- I did not.
I failed.
- Like, inconclusive or--
- Capital "F".
Failed.
Feds, they opened up
an IA deal or whatever.
- I have literally no idea--
- Internal Affairs, okay?
They investigate dirty cops.
- You might want to pack up
an umbrella today.
- I'm done.
- You quit?
- You get them up.
I'm so over it.
- [laughs]
You pull the covers off?
- "Covers"?
I threw water in their faces.
There's a full-on
insubordination at this point.
And then when we're
30 minutes late for drop-off,
who's gonna get the call?
- You get the call.
- I get the call.
- All right, I got this.
Drink that.
- Thank you.
[TV plays indistinctly]
[playing Bach's
Toccata and Fugue]
[eerie music continues]
- Oh, that's nasty.
- Right?
- [laughs]
- Daddy!
- Stop it, Daddy!
- You're gonna
give us nightmares.
- Then don't be sleeping.
- Okay, cereal's on the table.
- I want hotcakes.
- Hotcakes?
You must still be dreaming
if you think
you're gonna get hotcakes.
[knocking]
- You expecting somebody?
- No.
- Hmm.
- You need a haircut, buddy.
- Morning.
Morning, all.
Mind if we come in?
- What's going on?
What's up, Mike?
- You guys go get dressed.
- What's happening?
- You mind if we not do this
in front of them?
- I need you
to turn around, buddy.
- Let's just talk
about this, okay?
- Mm-mm, been there, done that.
- You have the right
to remain silent.
- I know the drill, Mike.
- Go to your rooms.
- Hey, hey, listen.
Listen to your mommy, okay?
Daddy's gonna be fine, okay?
You go to school and I'm gonna
call you when I can, okay?
[both mouthing words]
- This didn't have to happen.
[door shuts]
- [inhales shakily]
[children laughing distantly]
[woman singing
in foreign language]
[children repeating singing
♪
[children yelling]
- Hey, Mommy!
- We're making panca--
[music, voices stop]
- You can't just
take them away.
- Is this where you meet?
- Who says that?
- "Mommy's friend with
the drawings on his neck."
[children chattering,
laughing]
- I keep them far away.
- Jane says he's got
a little boy about her age.
- What do you want?
- I want you done.
- It's not that simple.
- I want my family safe.
- How do you think
we pay for things?
- Who cares?
- We could lose our house.
- So we'll get an apartment.
- With four children?
- Probably sleep better.
- It's not just
the house, Dean.
It's braces, it's college,
it's the clothes
on their backs.
- At least the park
would be a park again.
- Wait!
Will you just wait?
- What about Emma's birthday?
- We're doing it at my mom's.
Kids would love to see you.
[knocking on door]
[TV plays indistinctly]
- Pajamas?
It's almost lunch.
- Gee, thanks for the update,
Father Time.
Excuse me.
- Hey.
- Great, come on in.
- Um...
I just wanted to say thank you
for delivering my son.
- Starbucks.
You shouldn't have.
- Look, it'd be weird
if I got you, like,
a tennis bracelet
or a massage or--
I just didn't want
to be creepy.
- So you went with what you get
your postman on Christmas.
- Everybody loves a latte.
- Hey, um, thanks so much
for putting absolutely
no thought into this.
I have to get to work, so maybe
we could talk another time.
- Hey, where are my pants?
Hey.
- Hey.
- I'm Noah.
- He's my friend.
- I've heard really great
things about you.
- Um...
you move fast.
- I work with him.
- Of course you do.
- He's my boss.
- Ah, of course he is.
[shower running]
Well, enjoy your lattes.
[muffled chatter]
- Next.
- Hey, how you doing?
- Well, look who it is.
- Can we just do this?
- I knew you'd be back.
How much this time?
- 35.
- Hundred?
- Thousand.
- Do I look like
a genie to you?
- I've brought my pay stubs.
- For $500.
- So?
- So you must be
tripping, girl.
Your wish is denied.
Next.
- I am in real trouble, okay?
- Well, you wouldn't be here
if you weren't.
- I need to post bail.
- Aww, bunny.
For who?
- My husband.
- Mm-hmm.
- What's that?
- What's what?
- "Mm-hmm."
- I'm just wondering
how it feels.
- How what feels?
- Being no better
than the rest of us.
Next.
- There's no security.
It's basically just him,
the safe,
and his bitch-ass judgment.
- What if he recognizes you?
- I'll drive getaway.
- Isn't he behind glass?
- We wait till it closes,
he comes out to lock up.
You hold the gun,
B hits the safe.
- We're gonna need new masks.
- My treat.
- Can I pick them?
- Sure.
- Then I'm down.
- I'm gonna lose my kids.
- Stan is in a jail cell.
- Because of us.
- I just need to get him out.
- I know.
- I mean, how else
am I gonna get the money?
- I need 35 grand.
- Yeah, I'm not Merril Lynch.
- Well, then can I get
some fake cash
so I can move cars?
- [laughs]
Uh, how's my cut coming?
[moody pop music
playing through speakers]
- Slow.
- And why's that?
- You know why.
- So those stoner kids
didn't feel bad
and put all your money back?
- You'll get your cut.
- And when you do,
you'll get more money.
That's how this all works.
- You know what would be
so nice?
- Hmm?
- Is if you gave me a break
just once.
- Rough week?
- My husband took my children.
♪
- I know it's lonely
at the top.
- [scoffs]
- Will you set her up for me.
On my tab, please.
- I'll have another.
[knocking at door]
♪
- So here's the thing.
- Are you trashed right now?
- He's in jail because I'm not.
- You are bombed.
- So if we're gonna
do this thing,
I would like
to choose the masks.
- Okay.
- And also, can I stay
the night here?
Because it's really weird
without my kids.
- It's really weird
without Stan, too.
♪
.
- Only three
stuffed animals, all right?
Last time your suitcase
looked like Noah's damn ark.
Poor Grammy was picking up fuzz
for a week.
Hustle.
She's making you spaghetti.
- How's Daddy gonna eat?
- They'll feed him.
- Where does he go
to the bathroom?
- You know, in a bathroom.
- There's a toilet in the cell.
- What's a cell?
- Okay, you know what?
Daddy's gonna come home
real soon.
But right now
we gotta motor,
or Grammy's gonna eat
all your spaghetti.
- No!
- Go get your animals then, go.
And not that giant thing
you won at the fair.
Go find your retainer, please.
- Did he do it?
- It's complicated.
- Did he do
what they said he did?
- Yes.
- Then he should stay in jail.
[knocking on door]
both: Hey.
- Wanna do something?
- Uh--
- Look, I know you're supposed
to wait two days or whatever
to not seem like a psycho,
but it's tomorrow in India
and I ordered a pizza.
- To here?
- And wings.
- Huh.
- Yeah, and then I felt gross,
so I ordered a salad
and some green juice.
- Wow.
- And then I didn't want
to come off like one
of those health nuts,
so I ordered Chinese.
- Mm.
Well, I--
I have to go do something
with my sister.
Her husband left, so it's
kind of like a whole thing.
- Oh.
I'd love to meet her.
- You know, you--
you just met my ex.
I feel like that's enough.
- Mm. That's a lot.
- Okay, I tell you what.
Why don't you stay here, okay?
- Okay.
- Eat till you barf.
I'll be back.
- Right.
[quirky piano music]
♪
[woman singing
in foreign language]
♪
[microwave door shuts]
- I'm starving.
- Why do you even
eat those things?
- They take three minutes
to heat in the microwave.
- That's a plus?
- They're ten for ten bucks
at Kroger.
- Yeah, 'cause you gotta eat
like four of them
to make one regular meal.
- You know what else
is a lean cuisine?
- Hmm?
- Ordering a Big Mac
and taking one bite.
- Mm.
Or having, like, three fries,
and it tastes way better.
- Okay.
- Or one bite of pizza.
- All the toppings you want.
- Boom!
- Mm-hmm.
We should market this.
- Why are we in crime?
- You guys, 10:00.
That's how you use
the clock thing, FYI.
- [clicks tongue]
- So cute.
- I know.
I found cute colors.
- I was gonna
tie-dye mine, but...
[devious music]
Don't move!
- We're closed, y'all.
- This'll be quick.
- Come on!
- Go, move!
- Okay, okay.
I'm moving, I'm moving.
All right.
- Hurry up!
- I'm moving, I'm moving.
- Open the safe!
- I'm opening it.
[safe beeping]
- Come on!
- It's not gonna open.
- What do you mean?
- It's on a timer.
It won't open again
till morning.
- What?
- I mean, I'm happy
to do this all night,
but someone gonna see
your asses in the window
and call the cops, so...
- What do we do?
- Why don't y'all just
come back in the morning?
I'll bring the croissants.
At some point,
I'm gonna need a burrito.
And a big old cup
to urinate in.
.
- Oh, my God.
- It's the only way
to get the money.
- What else were
we supposed to do?
- How about anything?
- Oh, I'm sorry, should we have
left him there?
- He would have had the cops
waiting with donuts
when we came back.
- Croissants, but...
- I can't believe y'all
kidnapped a guy.
Again.
- He's like a baby bird,
you know?
You--you can't touch it
and then just put it back.
- That is not a baby bird.
That is a grown-ass man
duct taped to a booster seat.
We have to feed him
and care for his bodily needs.
- So, a baby bird.
- Oh!
Emma's birthday!
- Hey.
Hey!
Hey, yo!
Yo, anyone out there?
- Yeah, we're back here.
- Hey, you got my food?
- We're working on it.
- Hey, and, uh, can somebody
fire up my next playlist?
- What do you, uh,
want to hear?
- Phillatio.
That's "P-H."
Straight up Phil Collins.
- Can I help you?
- [sighs]
Hey.
Yeah, uh...
I was just looking
for a towel.
- Hall closet.
- Okay, see, your mom
just said "closet."
Whoa, these are dope.
- They used to be my grandpa's.
- Oh, yeah?
You know how to do a Windsor?
- Is that the big one?
- It's the power knot.
- I don't know any of them.
- Oh.
Well, I'll show you.
But first you have
to help me take down
all those wings out there.
- Yeah, my mom said
you went crazy.
- Mm, I like having options,
so... [clears throat]
- You can smell it
from the hall.
- Yeah, it's a real
clash of cultures, isn't it?
[mellow music]
♪
- You figure out how
to take a dump
with ten guys watching you yet?
No matter how long
you're in there
you never learn how
to wipe with dignity.
[sighs]
- What's your angle, here, man?
- That's a fair question.
Um, you go on record saying
you saw
Leslie Peterson's murder.
How Beth Boland
chopped him up,
put him in a freezer,
and threw away his body.
- I didn't say any of that.
- Well, I didn't see you
take that pen cap, but...
I know you did.
- How's that?
- I got a guy who saw you.
- Who?
- I haven't found him yet.
But there's always someone
out there that...
needs to save
his own ass, right?
- Well, you know...
I'm not that kind of cop.
- I can also find a guy to say
he saw you take
that missing cash
from the Linwood bust.
- I guess you'd know the type.
- Listen, man,
you do what you gotta do
to get to the letter
of the law.
Think about it, okay?
- You know what I was
thinking about?
How you say at my table
and you pretended
like we were the same.
- Not so much, huh?
- Not at all.
Brother.
Not at all.
[overlapping chatter]
[playful hollering]
- [sighs]
[children laughing]
- [imitating chomping noises]
I'm gonna eat you!
[goofy growling]
Oh, oh, oh!
- Mommy!
- Hey!
Happy birthday!
Hey, sweetie.
[smooches]
I missed you.
Thank you so much
for doing this.
- Happy to.
- I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean
to be so late.
- Yeah, what, uh--
what happened?
- That nest in the front yard,
a baby bird
just fell right out.
- Hmm.
- Hit me up with another one,
will ya?
- [sighs]
- I need some salsa.
- I just dipped you.
- But I'm gonna need it
on every bite, girl.
Look, the chip
is just a vehicle
to get the salsa to my mouth.
Okay, yeah.
Mm-hmm.
En fuego.
- [scoffs]
Okay, you know what?
We're out of chips.
- Can I have my burrito then?
- You do know that
there's still a gun
pointed to your head, right?
- Second one this month.
- Seriously?
- And you know what?
I'm no gun rights person,
but honestly,
if you don't shoot me
and I get a burrito out of it,
it's a hell of a lot better
than getting yelled at
by a bunch of trash people
who think that
their money problems
are somehow my fault
when they just need
to get off they dumb asses
and get they lives right.
So, what's up?
Where my burrito at?
- I forgot it.
- No you didn't.
- Yes, I did.
- [sniffs]
I smell the chorizo.
[mumbles indistinctly]
How 'bout you dig up that guac
you also forgot?
[children chattering]
- [gasps]
Oh, oh, oh.
I put a knife in the freezer
for that.
Then it doesn't stick
to the frosting.
- Oh, I just ran it
under hot water.
- Does that work as well?
- Better.
- Hmm.
I'll have to try it next time.
[cheerful music playing
through speakers]
Now, if John were here,
he'd be six scotches in
by now.
- Dean said he loved a party.
- Oh, he was the life
of the party.
He was Santa at Christmas,
had a pie-eating contest
every Thanksgiving.
On July 4th he'd take Dean
down to Indiana
and fill the car
with illegal fireworks.
- Dean does that with Kenny.
- Does he?
- He's a good dad.
- So was John.
[sniffs]
Not much of a husband, though.
He dipped his pen in
the company inkwell many times.
- How many?
- I stopped counting.
- Dean's never said a word.
- Well, the kids want
to remember Santa,
and pies, and skyrockets.
And the crazy thing is,
in the end...
it's that matters.
Would you grab the ice cream?
And run the scoop
under hot water.
- Judith?
Did Dean tell you
what's going on?
- He told me why he left.
- What'd he say?
- That he's too much
like his father.
- [groaning]
- You got this, you got this!
You got this!
Go!
- [grunting]
[muffled speech]
- Now I'm gonna barf.
[knocking on door]
- [grunts, laughs]
- [scoffs]
Fail!
- Oh, well.
Someone's at the door
- Hey.
I've been waiting downstairs
for like 20 minutes.
- Oh--oh, my gosh.
Uh, I forgot.
- Did you pack a bag?
- We were watching a movie.
- We can do that at the hotel.
[TV playing indistinctly]
- Sorry. Do they have "Top Gun"
at the hotel, though?
'Cause he's never seen it,
so...
- Do you, like,
live here now?
- No, Annie and I had plans
and then she had to go, so...
- All right,
'cause you're here, like...
a lot.
- I would have
brought Sadie down.
I didn't know--
- No, no, no.
It's fine, it's fine.
- Um...
Annie probably just forgot
that you were coming.
- Yeah, well,
she is kind of a mess.
- I don't know about that.
- Mm, I know her pretty well.
[epic music plays on TV]
Look, uh, I wouldn't get
too comfortable here.
- What does that mean?
- Well, I just don't think
she really knows
what she wants.
- Well, I think she knows
what she doesn't want.
- Ready.
- See you, Goose.
- Later, Mav.
It's a classic.
- I know.
[mellow music]
♪
- What time is it?
- Almost go time.
- Hey, wake up.
- [groans]
God, I got the worst taste
in my mouth. Ugh.
- Let's just do this.
- I'm coming in.
- You have to drive.
- There's something
I need to do.
- [spits]
- Just wake him up.
- Come on, sunshine.
[clears throat]
It's time to make
those donuts.
[devious music]
- Okay, great.
Now get down on the floor.
- Okay.
- But easy, easy.
Head down. Now count.
- How high?
- I don't know, a million.
- That--that's impossible.
- List all
the Phil Collins songs.
- Uh...
Su-Su-Sussudio...
- I got it, let's go.
- [stammering]
"Against All Odds"...
- Come on. We gotta go.
- "In the Air Tonight."
- Hold up,
I'm looking for something.
- Uh, that was a good one.
"In the Air Tonight."
Do y'all remember
"In the Air Tonight"?
- Where are the contracts
everyone signs?
- Contracts for what?
- What are you doing?
- The ones with
the nasty fine print.
- Red cabinet.
- Head down!
- Okay, uh, uh,
"A Groovy Kind of Love"...
- Dude!
- What are you doing?
- I need another bag.
- I only brought this one.
- Okay, take as many
as you can.
- Okay, why?
- 'Cause no one
should feel like trash.
- We gotta go, now!
Now! Down.
- Ooh!
"I Wish It Would Rain Down."
That was a good one.
Hey, bunny.
I knew you'd be back.
.
[introspective music]
♪
- ♪ We can run away
♪ But we can't hide
for long ♪
♪
♪ I don't know
why I can't change ♪
♪ I will always
stay this way ♪
♪ And thinking of you
♪
♪ Thinking of you
[music fades]
- So how'd you do it?
- I robbed a Qwik Cash
with the girls.
- Which one?
- Six mile.
- Good.
That guy's a dick.
- So you're just
cool with it now?
- You did what you had to.
[sighs]
- You're a cop, Stanley.
- I don't even know
what that means.
Just don't get caught.
Got the keys?
- My mom, uh, got her makeup.
- Are you kidding me?
- Full-on Texas pageant
glitter action.
- All you want to do
is keep them off the pole.
- Mama Boland's got
different plans.
- Why didn't you tell her
the truth?
- I did.
I cheated on you.
- Well, that's not the reason
I got into...
book club.
- Isn't it?
Getting cheated on
makes you do...
crazy things.
Like hire teenage hitmen.
- How'd you know?
- I'm not a total idiot.
- It's over.
- Which part?
- All of it.
Bring the children home, okay?
[knocking on door]
- Ugh. Why are you always here?
- Why are you always sleeping?
- I had a night.
- I bet.
[clears throat]
- What did Sadie forget?
- Uh...
What's with this dude?
- What do you mean?
- I mean, you've known him
for like a second
and all of a sudden
he's Sadie's wingman?
- So?
- So it's not normal.
- What, that--that he likes me?
- No, not--
- That somebody
would actually want
to stick around
after boning me, or--?
- No, just the fact
that he's so far up your ass
after, I don't know, a week?
- Okay, I'm sorry,
don't you have
a new family to deal with?
- It's shady.
- Yeah.
- Why don't you go ahead
and give
Idaho
a little skin-to-skin?
- His name is Dakota.
[long exhale]
I'm a D-bag, okay?
So I know when I see one.
Just...
Be careful.
[moody music playing
through speakers]
[man singing indistinctly]
♪
- [grunts]
- I'll have another.
And he'll have a Chardonnay.
- No, I won't.
- Whatever you want.
Your tab's still open.
- [laughs]
You're starting early, huh?
[clears throat]
- The one perk
to losing your kids...
- What's that?
- Day drinking.
- Thanks, man.
- Thank you.
- Cheers.
♪
Dean's bringing them
home tonight.
- That's good.
- And I have your cut.
- Even better.
- I don't have it here.
Sorry.
Didn't get a chance to...
Can I get you
something to eat?
- Yeah, what you got?
- I could make you a sandwich.
- Yeah, I'm not really much
of a sandwich guy.
- I'm out of bread anyway.
- [chuckles]
What am I doing here,
Elizabeth?
- It's just habit.
[both breathing heavily]
- [moans softly]
.
- My kids will be home soon.
Here's your cut.
- I thought you left it
at home?
- Guess not.
- [chuckles]
All right, swing by tomorrow.
I'll hook you up
with the funny money.
- I don't need it.
- Yeah, but how you--
- I'm not.
I'm done.
- Is that right?
- No more cash,
no more pills.
I'm gonna take a shower.
You should go.
It's over.
- Next?
[keyboard clacking]
Welcome to Qwik Cash.
How may I assist you today?
- Why didn't you tell the cops?
- We offer many different types
of loans.
- I know when
I'm being hustled.
- Did you mother teach you
those manners?
How 'bout a "thank you"?
- If you want a cut
of the money,
it's already gone.
- Yeah, I didn't think it went
into your 401K.
- Okay, you know what?
You might think I'm trash,
but I work really hard
for what I have.
And I've got a 12-hour shift
ahead of me--
my second double of the week--
and it's barely gonna cover
my groceries
let alone the roof
over my head--
which I only have, by the way,
because my mother--
who wrote the book on manners,
I'll have you know--died.
God rest her soul.
- I want your address.
- Don't you have it
in your system?
- No, I need it
for your school district.
- You can get your GED online.
- I majored in finance
at MSU, bitch.
- Then who's it for?
- My nephew.
He's smart.
Or I--I could go to the cops.
- Fine.
- Little nerd just needs
a leg up.
- We all do.
[women vocalizing]
[bittersweet music]
♪ Save it for the sake
of the fight ♪
♪
♪ Copy/paste
the child inside ♪
♪ You used to smile,
but now you are staged ♪
♪ I hate to watch you
walk away ♪
♪ I hate
to watch you walk away ♪
♪
♪ Is this how we're
gonna grow old? ♪
♪ Is this how
we're gonna grow old? ♪
♪
♪ Is this how
we're gonna grow old? ♪
♪ Is this how we're
gonna grow old? ♪
♪ Is this how
we're gonna grow old? ♪
[indistinct chatter]
♪ I hate to watch you
walk away ♪
- Thank you, baby.
♪ I hate to watch you
walk away ♪
♪
♪ I hate to watch you
walk away ♪
♪
children: Mommy!
- Oh, my goodness, hi!
[overlapping chatter]
♪
- [mouths "Thank you"]
[peppy pop music playing
through speakers]
[billiard balls thudding]
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Noah, right?
It's Noah?
both: Yeah.
- Oops.
- Mm-hmm.
- Um, so I had an epiphany.
Why are we, as a company, not
making, uh,
bite-sized... treats?
- I think we should
slow things down.
With us.
- Oh.
- Yeah, I just...
you know, I have--
I have a kid,
so I--I gotta be careful.
You know?
- Yeah, right.
- I don't even really know
anything about you, you know?
- What do you want to know?
- Just that...
you're not a total D-bag.
♪
- [mumbles indistinctly]
Here's the thing...
uh, I kinda am.
- Seriously?
- Yeah, I'm so sorry.
- Oh, my God.
What--why do I always do this?
- I'm not just a...
grocery store manager.
♪
I'm...
on probation.
- For what?
- Well, I stole
from my last job,
and then I had to lie
to get this one.
- What did you steal?
- Money.
Lots of it over
a long period of time
and then, uh--
I mean, it was, uh--
they didn't notice at first
and then it got easier.
Listen, I'm not--this is not
something I'm proud of.
- [laughs]
Noah.
- What?
- Sweet, sweet Noah.
[inhales]
- What?
- Okay, we're gonna need
some shots
for this conversation,
because we are
so much more alike
then you could ever know.
[woman singing
in foreign language]
[mellow music]
♪
[woman vocalizing]
[woman singing
in foreign language]
♪