.
- Previously, on "Good Girls."
- He left me,
and he took my kids.
What do you want?
- I want you done.
I want my family safe.
- How's it going
with the sister?
- I'm out of the friend zone.
- Already?
- Do you, like, live here now?
Because you're here,
like, a lot.
I'm a D-bag, so I know
when I see one.
- Well, I stole
from my last job.
- What did you steal?
- Money. Lots of it.
- We are so much more alike
that you could ever know.
- Feds, they opened up an IA
deal or whatever.
- I literally have no idea
what you're saying.
- Internal Affairs, okay?
They investigate dirty cops.
- Did you remove a pen cap
from the evidence locker?
- I failed.
- Like, inconclusive?
- Capital F, failed.
- Did he do
what they said he did?
- Yes.
- Then he should stay in jail.
- It's over. They got me.
I'm out on leave.
[tense music]
- I'm done.
- Is that right?
- No more cash. No more pills.
It's over.
- Which part?
- All of it.
Bring the children home, okay?
[kids laughing]
[sighs]
It's cost me everything
at this point.
But my...
rock bottom or whatever, um...
was when I lost my family.
[slowly building music]
♪
- [clears throat]
[engine sputters]
- The thing is, you have
no idea how far you've fallen
until you get some distance.
[dark, groovy music]
♪
I've had cops in my kitchen.
I've...
♪
Taken my kids to a crack house.
I've lied. I've cheated.
I've stolen.
[machine whirring]
I've had a gun to my head
so many times
that it doesn't even
scare me anymore.
A full clip adds a pound.
It's like...
why do I know that?
I shouldn't know that.
♪
[haunting vocalizations]
♪ Oh, Lord, I've lost it now
♪
[door clicks shut]
- I just have to stop.
I want to be normal.
♪
And I can't lose my kids again.
My name is Beth.
And I am an addict.
all: Hi, Beth.
- I'm going to need one of
you here and one of you here,
and I'll hold down the middle
over here with the goodies.
Who's on masks?
- Uh, how about a big leaf?
- Or a fluffy turkey?
- Ooh, Indian headdress.
- Not cool,
- Why not?
- It's cultural appropriation.
both: Oh.
- Mm-hmm.
- Why don't we
avoid any land mines
and just keep this fall themed?
- Oh, thank God you're back.
- Right?
- Where's our homegirl been?
- Life got a little crazy
for a second.
- All I got to say
is Carol filled in for you.
- Oh, do not.
- She didn't want to do themes.
- For the parties?
- It was nuts.
- Oh, speaking of which.
[both gasp]
Okay, so we have
acorn thumbprints,
and see, the Hershey kiss
is the little acorn.
- Oh, that's so cute.
- And we got turkey cake pops.
We've got little squirrely
sweet treats,
and I cannot with
this pretzel tail.
- Stop!
- Beth!
- Can you even?
And then, we've got
Gobble Gobble Maple Crumble.
- Oh, wait.
- Uh--
- What?
- Um, those look like
walnuts on top.
- So?
- Oh, walnuts are nuts.
- Well, they're not peanuts.
- Nut family.
- Well, who in
our class is allergic?
- Uh, Cooper doesn't like them.
- Right.
- Well, that's not an allergy.
And you know what else?
All of this...
filled with gluten.
- Oh, my God.
- I mean, where are the
gluten issues in Africa?
Or Brazil?
Or anywhere except for here?
Right?
- Oh, you're bad.
- What happened to you?
- I like it.
- Let's live a little.
- [laughing] Okay!
- Annie Marks,
please report to produce.
[both panting]
- We can never
sell this lettuce.
- Hey, question.
- What do you think is worse?
The sex or the pesticides?
- Um, does our insurance
cover puberty blockers?
- [laughs]
I think that ship has sailed.
- Has it?
- Yeah, honey,
you're a woman now.
- Mm, it's for my kid.
It's kind of, like the next
step, and he's really stoked.
- Uh-huh.
- So, you know.
- Look, well, I'll check,
but we are Fine and Frugal.
- Mm-hmm.
- Emphasis on the "frugal."
- Mm, right.
- Yeah.
- But you know,
I could pick up extra shifts
or I could--you know,
I'd mop the butcher floor
or unclog toilets, or--
you know, whatever.
I'm just saying,
something to think about.
- Mm-hmm.
- Well, come on,
I'm still down.
- Yeah, blood, bathrooms,
your child's trans journey--
it's, uh--
- It's a lot of imagery.
- Yeah.
I can--I can look
at the schedule.
- Thanks, boss.
- Okay?
Uh--
[exhales]
Hey, uh...
what about your
extracurriculars?
- Oh. [sighs]
Those are over.
- Huh. Why?
- It's--it's, like,
a whole thing with my sister.
- That sucks.
How bad do you need the money?
- [sighs]
Kale.
- Hmm.
[exhales]
- Guilty?
- That's what he wants.
- Why?
- I'm--I'm just another file
in his stack, Ruby.
I mean, you should
see this guy.
He'd rather go play
racquetball or golf.
- The court-appointed ones
can't afford golf.
- Well, that's what it is.
- Then we'll get you
a real lawyer.
- You know how much that costs?
- Stan, you're not
pleading guilty.
- Babe, do you want to eat
or keep the lights on?
Because that's where
we are this month.
Okay, I got no paycheck
coming in.
I can't even get my old job
back at the mall
because they think
I'm a fel--
That better not be a phone.
Hey, you got your ears on,
Journey Scout?
- Excuse you, miss.
Your father is speaking to you.
- Hey.
No phones
during homework, baby.
- And no pop after dinner.
- [snarkily] Oh, my bad.
I didn't think we still
followed rules around here.
- Oh, you're gonna have
your hands full.
- What are you talking about?
- When I go away.
[soda tab pops]
[soft music]
♪
- It's cheating.
- It's fine.
- It's an affair.
- Oh, come on.
- What do you call it?
- It's maybe
an emotional affair,
which is, like,
barely even a thing.
- Hoda says that's worse.
- Oh.
You know, we're doing Beth
a favor.
- How's that?
- You don't take
an alcoholic to a bar.
[groovy music]
- How's this even
going to work?
- We just keep
the trains running.
- Without the dealership?
- Well, I'm kicking around
some ideas.
♪
- You are?
- I am.
- Well, as long
as it doesn't involve
shoving anything up our--
- Sara needs her badges, right?
- Oh, hell, no!
- Okay, will you just chill?
- I'm not going to let you
shove things up my child's--
- Bus!
- What?
- Customs is never
going to search
a bus full of Journey Scouts.
I mean, they're
practically nuns.
- Jesus.
- Oh, I'm sorry,
what was your idea again?
Because I'm open.
- I don't know.
- Mm, shocking.
- That was Beth's thing.
- Or...
- Or?
- Or we locate
a travelling circus
and we find the elephants
or whatever
the largest mammals are
we can find
and we cram the pills
up one of their--
- Hey, ladies.
[exhales]
♪
So how are we
going to do this?
.
- So it's about a dead girl?
- No, she gets in an accident,
and when she wakes up,
she has no memory and she has
to sort of start her life over.
- So it's a medical
mystery thing?
- More like she has to sort of
figure out who she wants to be.
- Do you actually
see the accident?
Because I am not
good with blood.
- Mm, probably
can't see anything
because it's a book.
- Oh, thank you, professor.
- Hey, is it on Netflix?
- Hey, you guys wash up.
We're going to eat.
[kids squeal]
- So you're totally okay
with all this?
- What?
- You know...actual book club?
- I mean...
what about you guys?
- Well, kind of miss the money.
- Not going to lie.
- Yeah, how's Stan's lawyer?
- Super. Real shark.
- Well, maybe when
the dealership
gets back on its feet,
I could pitch in and--
- Hey, we'll get by.
- How do you think
he's going to do it?
Without us?
- Oh, I don't know.
There's always some idiot
willing to do
something stupid for money.
- So, do you guys want to
come to book club or not?
- Ooh, gee, we would but...
we kind of have, like, a thing.
- Oh.
- Otherwise,
I would totally love
to pretend to have read it.
- All right, you guys.
Come and get it.
- You want your service badge
or not?
- Why do we have to
go to Canada?
- Because that's where
the nursing home is.
- Can't we visit one here?
- Old people
are lonelier there.
- Because of
socialized medicine?
- Yeah.
- Wait, that makes no sense.
- Okay, you know what?
Bed time.
Daddy will be in for prayers.
- No thanks.
- To Daddy or prayers?
- Both.
- Excuse you.
- We're just going to act
like we're good people now?
- We are good people.
- He stole, you lied,
and I still can't borrow
the neighbor's Internet.
- Sara Louise Hill--
- It makes about as much sense
as going to Canada
to get my service badge.
[groovy music]
[Superorganism's "Something
For Your M.I.N.D."]
♪
- Green for grass
or blue for sky?
- What about red?
- For what?
Like a sunset?
- I mean, it's a balloon.
We don't have to
be literal, right?
- Let's do green.
- For grass.
- Leaves or pumpkins?
- Leaves.
- Maple or oak?
- Oak.
- Brown or tan?
- [exhales]
- Turkeys or corn stalks?
- ♪ I know you think
I'm a psychopath ♪
- Beth?
- ♪ A Democrat lurking
in the dark ♪
- What?
- Turkeys or corn stalks?
- ♪ Cirque du trash,
I kept the stash ♪
- Turkey.
- Mm.
- Corn stalks.
- ♪ Cocoa candy
♪ Straight from Japan
- Are they too sexual?
- Oh, yeah, that's, uh--
- ♪ I know you know
what I need to get by ♪
- You know what
the sixth grade started?
- What?
- Mom's night out.
- ♪ Mind
- They watched "Magic Mike."
- No!
- ♪ Something for your
- What, with the kids there?
- ♪ Mind
- No, they were at Brooke's.
- We have to do that.
Throw in some margaritas.
Let's get loose!
- ♪ Mind
- ♪ Something
for your mind ♪
♪ Mind
- [speaking Korean]
- ♪ Mind, mind
♪ Something for your
- [speaking Korean]
- ♪ Mind
♪ Mind, mind
♪ Something for your,
for your ♪
[drink slurps]
- ♪ M-I, M-I,
M-I ♪
♪ M-I-N-D
- ♪ For us, the bourgeoisie
♪ So carefree
♪ Remember when we?
♪ I don't know what
you need to get by ♪
♪ Something for your mind
- ♪ Mind
♪ Something for your
[music slows]
♪ Mind, mind, mind
[music falters]
[tense music]
♪
- Beth?
- Are you coming?
- ♪ Mind
- ♪ I-N-D
- Boy, once again,
I am really sorry.
I--you know, we don't have
a lot of control
over what happens
to these things
once they're put
on the shelves,
but if you head over
to customer service,
they'll give you a full refund.
And you have
a fine and frugal day.
You know, these people
need to lighten up.
She just got a half
a cigarette for free.
[both laugh]
That's actionable.
- Mm.
[laughs]
Hey, um...
is there any way I can have
the day off tomorrow?
- Everything okay?
- Yeah, I, uh--
took your advice,
and I have an extracurricular.
- Model UN?
- Something like that.
- Yeah, you go, Kofi.
- Did you just make
a Kofi Annan reference?
- I did.
- [laughs] I love you.
When you make...
references to former
world leaders.
- Mm-hmm.
- Also, he's dead.
I'm gonna dip.
- Hey.
I love...
I love that you
said his name right.
- There's just so much
to love about Kofi.
- Well, he redefined the UN.
- I'm going to go.
- Go.
The pills come across the
border right here in Detroit.
There is a wide range,
some of them controlled,
all of them prescription-grade.
They distro through a
sophisticated street network.
- How you want to play it?
- I think it's go time.
We hit them fast,
hit them hard.
- Ladies and gentlemen,
you heard the man.
Let's get this party started.
- You hanging in?
- Yeah, I just want it over.
- Burritos on you
tomorrow night.
- Great.
.
- [singing powerfully] ♪ This
is the song that never ends ♪
♪ It will go on and on,
my friend ♪
♪ Some people started singing
it ♪
♪ Not knowing what it was
♪ And they'll continue singing
it forever just because... ♪
- Who is that?
- One of my mom's friends.
- Come on!
♪ It will go on and on--
And we can do it in a round,
so you go--
♪ It will go on and on my--
and then, you go
♪ It will go on and on
♪ My friends
[sighs]
[quietly]
♪ Started singing it
♪ Not knowing what it was
♪ And they'll continue
singing it forever, just-- ♪
- How about you stop now?
- How about you chill out?
- We're not at camp.
- Doesn't mean
we can't have fun.
- Let's just do this
without getting...
[whispers]
arrested.
- Okay.
- Can I get a juice box?
- Well, I don't know, can you?
[scoffs] Yes, you may.
Have a juice box.
Enjoy.
- So why are you here?
- Are you kidding me?
I was big in all that.
- What badges did you get?
- Like, almost every
single one.
I only had to drop out
because I got knocked up.
[indistinct chatter]
- Seriously?
- Well, actually, I only
made it to Brown Birds.
But Beth, she went all the way.
[humming]
♪ Song that never--
[timer dings]
- You, uh--you okay?
- Fall festival and book club.
Book-club book club.
- Yes, got it.
- Careful, they're hot.
- So you want to
stop by work tomorrow
and check out the new promo?
- Can you take Kenny to swim?
- Sure.
- Yeah, you can tell Linda
that I'll stop by.
- I will.
So, do you miss it?
- I don't need
to be there every day.
- I'm not talking about
the dealership.
- Would it matter if I did?
- This is delicious.
[soft music]
♪
- ♪ This land
is your land ♪
♪ This land is my land
♪ From California
♪ To the New York island
♪ From the Redwood Forest
♪ To the Gulf Stream waters
♪ This land was made
for you and me ♪
♪
- I'm looking for
a Beth Boland.
♪
- You found her.
- ♪ I saw below me
♪ That golden valley
♪ This land was made
for you and me ♪
♪ When the sun came shining
♪ And I was strolling
♪ And the wheat fields waving
and the dust clouds rolling ♪
♪ And the fog was lifting
♪ A voice was chanting
♪ This land was made
for you and me ♪
♪ As I went walking
♪ I saw a sign there
♪ And on the sign it
said "no trespassing" ♪
♪ But on the other side
♪ It didn't say nothing
♪ That side was made
for you and me ♪
♪ In the shadow
of the steeple ♪
♪ I saw my people
♪ By the relief office,
I've seen my people ♪
♪ As they stood there hungry
♪ I stood there asking
♪ Is this land made
for you and me? ♪
♪ Nobody living
♪ Can ever stop me
♪ As I go walking
♪ That freedom highway
♪ Nobody living
♪ Can ever
make me turn back ♪
♪ This land was made
for you and me ♪
- And I'm thankful for waffles
and Missy, my doll.
And that my mom doesn't
go to work as much
so she can play with me.
[applause]
- These are the moments
you just can't miss, right?
- Right.
[laughter]
- Oh, I didn't even go there.
- Oh, God.
But you know what?
She is so great.
- Sorry to interrupt.
- Oh, my God.
Jane was the most adorable
thing I've ever seen.
- Yeah, she's hilarious.
What happened to
all the stuff I made?
The cupcakes and the crumble?
- Oh, um...
- Oh.
- Right.
- Beth, we just got
a little nervous
about the nut thing.
- Yeah, and not to mention
all that gluten.
- Yeah, so we had Trish
run out to Kroger
just to be safe.
- They were gorgeous, though.
And we had them all wrapped up
so you can take them home.
[tense music]
- So, um, I was thinking.
How about a mom night
in early January?
- Well, actually,
February might be better
because of the winter carnival.
- That work for you, Beth?
Beth?
♪
[distorted singing]
- [sobs]
♪
[distorted radio chatter]
- We're good?
- Locked and loaded.
- Uh, hey, guys.
Here, pass these out
for me, would you?
Thank you.
All right, I think I'm
going to pee again.
I really like the toilets here.
They're so high up.
- What's your secret?
- Sorry?
- When mine was their age,
she was already smoking dope
and stealing cars.
- Well, give her a minute.
- Mm-mm, I don't think so.
Not that one.
She taught me Snapchat.
- I am so sorry.
- She's patient.
- Well, she just
came out like that.
- That's not
how it works, honey.
I had eight.
- No wonder you're in a chair.
- [laughs]
Well, whatever you're doing,
it's working.
Bye.
- Passports.
- Here you go.
- Quick trip today?
- Oh, yeah.
You know, just keeping up
international relations.
- They just earned
their service badge
at Mallard Pond Senior Center.
- Would you like some water?
- Thanks for
your service, girls.
- See?
Piece of cake.
- I took it all out.
.
- Back on the bus in ten.
- Stick with your buddies.
That goes for you, too, Karen.
- I panicked, okay?
- No.
- I couldn't do it.
- No, no, no, no, no!
- We're supposed to be making
them better people, not this.
- What did you do with them?
- In the garbage at the place.
- Oh, my God, you left
our payday in a trash can?
- We could have gotten caught.
- But we didn't.
- With a bunch of drugs
in front of Sara.
- It was the perfect plan.
You know if Beth
had suggested this,
you would have been all in.
- Like I'm some kind
of yes-man?
- "Hey, Ruby, want to rob
a grocery store?"
"Sure, Beth."
"Hey, Ruby.
Want to drink some gasoline?"
"Yeah, sounds yum, Beth.
Pour it in my mouth."
- Okay, you know what--
- But of course, when I come up
with a sound solution--
- Oh, you mean this
or up an elephant ass?
- Yes, I put two viable options
on the table,
and all you had to do
was choose one.
- You know what?
You're right.
You're not Beth.
You never will be.
You know what you are?
- Please.
- You're a child.
You do whatever you want
whenever you want.
- I take risks, Ruby.
- Without thinking about
anyone else but yourself.
- Just because I didn't choose
some safe-ass,
boring-ass life
like my sister--
- You know why she did that?
Because she had to.
She didn't have anyone to
clean up after her like you do.
- That's not true.
- She has been
mopping up your messes
since the day I met you.
- I'm really glad that I can be
such a convenient excuse
for everyone.
- What does that even mean?
- Well, now when Stan
goes to jail,
you'll have someone else
to blame.
- Anyone want dibs
on a Slim Jim?
The machine gave me two.
- You sang songs
and braided hair?
- Ugh, it's, like,
a troop thing.
- That's terrifying.
- ♪ This is the song
that never ends ♪
- Stop.
- ♪ It will go on and on
♪ My friend
- Oh, my God.
- Go on, open the drawer.
Come on.
- Okay, okay.
- You like-y?
- Why?
- Well, I mean, you needed
new ones anyway.
- They look expensive.
- Nah, they came
in a three-pack.
- They're dope.
- The, um...
The medicine
might have to wait.
It's just--
it costs so much more
than I have right now,
you know?
- Okay.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm going to get something
to drink.
- Hey, um...
am I a mess?
I just mean, like,
relative to the other moms.
- Medium.
- Seriously?
- [clicks tongue]
Here's the thing:
most private school kids
think their parents
are perfect.
They're going to be
majorly freaked out
when they realize they're not.
- Hm.
- But with you, I already
know what I'm dealing with.
So I'm, like, not that damaged.
- Thanks.
- Want anything to drink?
- I'm okay.
[soft elevator music]
♪
- That bad, huh?
So they suck your soul out yet
or what?
- What are you doing here?
- I tried calling.
- I blocked your number.
- [laughs]
Damn, that's cold.
- I'm sure you'll get over it.
- I just wanted to make sure
you were in the loop
about stuff.
- Well don't, okay?
- Okay.
So you're all good, then?
- I'm good.
I'm great.
- All right, then, yeah.
You don't--you don't got
to know about this, then.
- Know what?
What?
Where are they?
- What?
- The books, Dean.
They're not in the cabinet.
- What's going on?
- Where are the books?
- Uh, they're--
they're in accounting.
- Not those books.
The book club books.
- Why?
[sirens wail]
- ♪ The night
would never end ♪
♪ In your sleep,
you called me Natalie ♪
♪ It was the nicest
thing you said ♪
- Everybody down on the ground.
- FBI!
♪
- Don't move!
- Where is she?
- Who?
- Sir!
- ♪ You said I live
for tragedy ♪
- Don't hurt her!
- ♪ So I threw the keys
at your head ♪
- Mrs. Boland, are you decent?
[knocks on door]
Mrs. Boland, we're gonna
need you to come out now.
♪
.
- You have to open
the door, Mrs. Boland.
Or we'll open it for you.
- I'm going to come out.
I need to know that
I'm not going to be hurt.
- No one's going to hurt you.
- Or my staff.
Nate has a heart condition.
- Nate's fine.
♪
All right, Mrs. Boland.
[groovy music]
Time's up.
♪
- Hello, James.
Wow, you brought
the whole team.
Oh, if any of you
are in the market,
we do give special discounts
to government employees.
- I think you'll be
shut down for a while.
- Take all the time you need.
- What's this?
- Shirt, pants, underwear.
- [exhales]
I'm good.
- No, you're not.
You're going to get up,
you're going to hose off
that self-pity and depression,
because I'm tired
of looking at it.
- Oh, is that so?
- It is.
And once it starts
swirling down the drain,
you're going to get dressed.
You're going to shave off
that nasty-ass face fungus,
and we're going to go out
and celebrate, do it up right.
- What's there
to celebrate, Ruby?
- You getting a proper lawyer.
- What are you talking about?
- You're not
going away for this.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm going to take care of it.
- How?
- I got you, boo.
Now please, wash your ass.
- [grunts]
[laughter plays on television]
- Drink up, baby.
- Oh, thanks for mine.
- She's had a day.
- Haven't we all?
- God, it was really--
- Terrifying, I'm sure.
- You would have had to
change my diaper.
- But it was almost--
- I bet Deansie lost it.
- Fun.
It was fun.
- Here's a question.
- Yeah?
- How did they even know
about the pills?
- Or exactly
where to look for them.
- And just for the record--
- You don't have to go there.
- I didn't say a word.
- No one's accusing you.
- But I mean,
someone said something.
- Hey, have you seen Noah?
- He didn't
come in yesterday.
- Why not?
- Oh, nasty stuff's
going around.
You know, last week,
I had conjunctivitis.
You probably know it
as pink eye.
It's super contagious.
I didn't want to
miss work, though.
You probably didn't notice,
but that's why
I was wearing those shades.
They're new.
I found them in
the parking lot.
Don't tell Noah, though.
Because, um...
[tense music]
♪
- ♪ There must be something
else to do ♪
I didn't want to show anybody,
because it's real nasty.
You ever had it?
♪
- Hey, take a look at this.
What do you think?
I'll be done in
about five minutes.
♪
- Sometimes I think maybe
I don't want to get better.
Because at least if I use,
I know who I am.
♪
I feel like myself.
- Anyone else want to share?
♪
- ♪ There must be something
else to do ♪
[engine starts]
♪ There must be something
we can do ♪
♪
- Lot's clean.
- They knew we were coming.