.
- Previously on
"Good Girls"...
[tense music]
- Take off your pants.
- What?
- Just do it.
Come on.
- This guys is a real bad news,
huh?
- I need him to go away.
- Let's say I have a friend.
He takes care of your problem.
- We're out of cinnamon,
so...
- What do you want?
- Is there any way you could
take her for the night?
- So you can bone some other
pregnant lady's husband?
- I'm Noah.
- Hey, Noah,
- I'm the new manager.
- You opened up a thing.
- What's a thing?
- Internal Affairs, okay?
They investigate dirty cops.
- For what?
- The pen cap!
- What do you want?
- Her.
- Whatever you need to know,
but he has to stay out of it.
- Do Sara and Harry have
grandparents?
- What do you mean?
- When you and your husband
go away.
- I did every single thing
you asked.
- And still, I got nothing.
- Can you meet me right now?
["Freedom! '90"
by George Michael]
♪
- ♪ I won't let you down
♪ I will not give you up
♪ Gotta have some faith
in the sound ♪
♪ It's the one good thing
I've got ♪
[tires screeching]
♪ I won't let you down
♪ So please don't give me up
- Oh, no, oh, no,
no, no, no, no--
♪
- Are you okay?
- Son of a bitch.
♪
- Have you ever driven before?
- Duh.
- How old are you?
- Where are you going?
- To get groceries.
- Can't your mom do it?
- She's in bed.
- Is she sick or something?
- She just really
likes it there.
- Thanks.
- My uncle taught me once
in a parking lot.
- Yeah?
It's harder than it looks.
- I want to drive.
- Shut up.
- I call next.
- Shut up, Annie.
- Okay.
- ♪ You've got to give
for what you take ♪
♪ Freedom
♪ Hold on to my freedom
[tires screeching]
- [squeals]
- ♪ You've got to give
for what you take ♪
♪
- So...
I love you, I mean, obvs.
Whatever you--
it's not half as bad
as how I feel, okay?
I'm as low as it gets.
I'm disgusting.
I'm sewage.
You know how they drain it
for fertilizer or whatever?
I'm what they can't use.
I'm the sewage so rancid
they have to bury it
100 miles in the earth
and hope that nobody
ever finds it.
I'm that garbage.
Please, just say something.
- You took this from my house
while my daughter was missing.
- He's got us over a barrel.
- When I was frantic
and searching.
- He's got Stan for
the pen cap.
- Some of those neighbors--
God, I don't even know
their names.
- And me on like
everything else.
- They were looking for Jane
while you were looking
for this.
Are you gonna give it to them?
- No.
- But you thought about it.
- But I couldn't do it.
- I would never even think
about it.
[door slams]
- Hey, do you...
do you get along with your ex?
- Sure.
- Things aren't weird
or anything?
- What are you doing?
- Well, I'm inquiring about
your life.
- Please, stop.
- I just want to get
to know you.
- [sighs]
You know, I'm gonna have to
teach you how to dirty talk
because this is not doing
it for me.
- I feel like a cheap slut.
- Mm, that's better.
- Take me to dinner.
- [groans]
- Treat me like a human.
- What's so wrong with me
liking you?
- [sighs]
The more the know, the less
you're gonna like, kay.
Just trust me.
- What does that even mean?
- Okay, yes.
I get along with my ex.
Mm-hmm, yeah, and--and
his wife and I are real tight.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, we team parent.
You know, it's all very chill.
- Uh-huh.
- And I was almost a nurse.
- Seriously?
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I was like one class shy.
- No way, that'--
where'd you go to school?
- Detroit Nurse School.
- I don't know it.
- Really?
- I don't.
- God, it's like the Harvard
of the 313.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
- Nurses are hot.
- Right?
- Comfortable?
- Doing great.
- Need some water?
- No, all good.
Thanks.
- We won't keep you too long.
- I got no place to be.
- Hmm.
Have you ever stolen anything,
Officer Hill?
- No, I have not.
That's not true.
Signed Dennis Rodman
rookie card,
swiped it off my friend,
school bus, sixth grade,
- So you switched shifted
with Officer Peters
to work the evidence locker?
- That's right.
- Why'd you do that?
- I needed to get home to pick
my children up from school.
- Can their school
corroborate that?
- Sure.
- Have you ever taken
any evidence
from the locker unauthorized?
- I have not.
- Were you aware of a pen cap
tagged in the evidence locker?
- I was not.
- Are you aware
a pen cap went missing
from the evidence locker?
- I am not.
[keys clacking]
- Did you remove a pen cap
from the evidence locker?
- I did not.
[keys clacking]
I failed.
- Like, inconclusive--
- Capital F, failed.
With flying colors.
- Are you sure?
- Apparently, I don't even know
my own damn name.
- So he just told you
the results, like,
right there on the spot?
- Yeah, it's not the SAT, Ruby.
You know, you don't have
to wait three to five weeks.
- Well, what did he say?
- He said that Internal Affairs
are gonna reach out
and that--
I'm out on leave.
- Like...
- I'm done.
It's over.
They got me.
- I'm so sorry.
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
It's not you.
- Yo.
- Hey, what's cracking?
- What's for dinner?
- Oh, my God.
What time is it?
- Like, way past starving.
- I didn't make anything
all day. I was just--
- Pizza night.
- Hare Bear,
we're getting pizza.
- It's okay, baby.
- I'm sorry.
- No, no.
- Nico explained to you
the job, right?
- Yeah, he said homeboy messed
you up good.
- That's why I'm here.
- Did you, like, walk in on him
sticking it to her?
- What?
- This dude and your girl,
you saw them boning?
- No, I didn't see them--
- I'd go mental seeming him all
freaky all over her.
- I feel for you, bro.
- Thank you.
- Look,
here's what I'm thinking--
- Your girl say anything about
how he stacked up?
You know, down there?
- No, she didn't share details.
- I bet homeboy had
some package.
- Big fat pumpkin, right?
- Put in the patch.
[both laughing]
- Can you guys kill him or not?
- Yo, chill.
You gotta keep your head, man.
- I just--
I need this to be over.
- You gotta be cool, man,
- All right, look, I'm cool.
Look at me.
I'm cool.
- What's homeboy look like?
- That's him.
- Damn, dog, Eastside.
- Nico didn't say anything
about a banger.
- Does that matter?
- It's gonna cost extra.
- I'll pay whatever.
- 50% down.
The rest after we dust him.
- Okay.
Yeah.
Deal.
What?
- We're gonna need
to see some cash.
- Wait, tonight?
- You want the job done or not?
- I mean, I don't--
I don't have it on me
right now.
- Thanks for the frap, man.
- Wait, no, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait,
just sit down, please.
Please.
Look, I can get you whatever
you need.
- Right now?
- All right, let's go.
- Okay.
["Time In My Mind"
by Emilie Mover]
♪
- ♪ I need time
in my mind ♪
- [muffled grunting]
- ♪ To forget about the pain
in my heart ♪
♪
♪ I need time in my mind
♪ To forget about
the pain in my heart ♪
- [muffled grunts]
- Oh, my God.
Are you--
- ♪ Time like the wind
♪ Time like a season
- Oh, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no
- [muffled yell]
- No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no.
♪
Son of a bitch.
- [laughing]
They put your panties
in his mouth?
- Don't say panties.
- Oh, please, don't tell me
you call them underwear.
- None of this is funny.
- [laughing]
- Damn, that Dean's
a trip, man.
- They took every cent
I've made.
- Oh, relax, I'll take care
of it for you.
- And get it back?
- What'd I just say?
- But how?
- Again, not your department,
is it?
- They're just kids.
- Who stole.
You need to set limits, mama.
You know that.
- Is that your solution
to everything?
What happens when your son
wets the bed?
You gonna cap his ass?
- Yeah, I'm gonna cap his ass.
- Well,
you can't solve every problem
by shooting someone
in the face.
- All right, look.
Here's your problem, okay?
That dumbass husband of yours
in there gave 'em a taste.
- What does that mean?
- They know you make money.
They know you can't put it
in a bank.
So the next time they
come knocking, and they will,
'cause they know where you live
and they know what you do,
they're just gonna want
a cut of the action.
And they're just gonna
keep taking and taking
till you got nothing left
but a good old fashioned
turf war on your hands.
- Or they're just kids.
- You better hope
they play nice then.
- Jesus, what is in this thing?
- They know where I live.
I can't afford to lose
anything else.
- God.
Ow.
- Careful,
this is Nana's china.
- Hold up, how did you get
Nana's china?
- Oh, I'll tell you how.
- Here we go.
- After she gave you
a certain wedding ring
that turned into
two nights at the Bellagio.
- First of all, it was one.
- Okay, well,
I think from now on
I get all the heirlooms.
- And second of all,
it was the Flamingo, so...
Have you called her yet?
- No.
- Are you gonna?
- She's talking to the FBI.
- They were gonna lock Stan up.
They were gonna take her kids.
I mean, she's obviously,
like, sick about it.
- Yeah, she should be.
She almost turned us in.
- Yeah, almost.
- So you're just gonna
trust her?
- We've known her for,
like, 10,000 years.
- Exactly.
- Well, you don't just throw
that away over almost.
- Seriously?
- Yeah, I know.
I reported them stolen for
the insurance money, though.
- Why don't you just have
a yard sale?
- And then I'm gonna have
a yard sale.
So how do we get
our dough back?
- They're children.
We set limits.
- This is unacceptable
behavior.
Breaking and entering, theft,
assault of the first degree.
- All the degrees, really.
- When I turn you
into the cops,
they're gonna lock you up
and throw away the keys.
- What do you want to be
when you grow up?
- Club DJ.
- You?
- Festival DJ.
- Hmm. Well,
that's never gonna happen.
Because what you did will ruin
the rest of your lives.
- The system is gonna chew you
up and spit your ass out.
- But you know what?
At the end of the day,
you are children.
So if you give me
my money back,
I will give you
a second chance.
- Where do I know you from?
- Yeah, she looks super
familiar.
- Right, like, it's killing me.
- Do you work at the vape shop
down on Cass?
- No.
- Dude, it's the car chick.
You know, from those
cheesy commercials.
- Yes.
- Hey, costs a lot of money
to make those.
- Can we have a car?
- No.
- We want a car, bitch.
- One of those fly rides
from the commercials.
- Excuse me,
no one's getting a car.
- Can I get another cake pop?
- Do you want me to turn you
into the police?
Because I will.
Right now.
- No, you won't.
- Yeah, I will.
- Okay, we'll go together.
- Fine, let's go.
- Let's do it.
- We got something
to tell 'em too.
[cell phone beeps]
- Can you guys kill him
or not?
I need this to be over.
I'll pay whatever.
- 50% down.
The rest after we dust him.
- Deal.
- We'll give you a car.
- We will?
- Fully loaded.
- [laughing]
- Yeah, dog.
That's what I'm talking about.
- So how long?
- I don't know.
- Yeah, you do.
- 25 years.
- Damn.
- We grew up together.
- That's amazing.
- Our kids grew up together.
- Yeah.
- Every Christmas,
every birthday.
- I get it.
- When I went into labor
with Sarah,
I called her before
I called Stan.
- She's family.
- My ride or die.
Will you go easy on her?
- No.
But you will get to keep
your husband.
- It all goes away, right?
- You want me to take
a lie detector?
Too soon?
- It's an orange Charger,
fully loaded.
Here's the VIN.
- She will be there?
- Mm-hmm.
You did good.
[soft blues music]
[door shuts]
[cell phone rings]
- Hey, how'd it go?
- Tell her I made it right.
- Don't you want
to tell her yourself?
- [no audible dialogue]
- Just tell her he bought it.
- She had to pick up her kids.
♪
.
- [roars]
[roars]
- That fool has a death wish.
- She's charging kids 50 cents
to jump off our back porch.
[both chuckle]
[children grunting]
- She got any game?
- Half the neighborhood thinks
they can fly.
- Yeah!
- You don't want to go in?
- No.
- Okay.
- I can't.
- It's gonna be weird.
- He was your dad.
[children grunting]
- Where you going?
You look like a cat burglar.
- I have to get our money back.
- He's wrecking our lives.
- You're not helping.
- [scoffs]
Okay.
Do you want to talk about it?
- What?
- The first thing you did
was check on your money.
- I knew the kids were
with your mom.
- That's not
who I'm talking about.
- You're drunk.
- I'm working on it.
- Why don't you go to bed?
[door shuts]
- You know,
after a while I was like,
"Dude, I miss technology,
you know."
I mean,
not that feeding Ebola orphans
wasn't gratifying, obviously.
It was in its own way,
but eventually I was like,
"Jesus, give me a phone that
can send a text, you know."
- Uh-huh.
- And--oh, are your fries cold?
- Yeah.
- Here,
let's heat up our buffet.
- So clever.
- I know.
- [laughs]
- So, yeah, you know,
then I jetted to Osaka
and I joined
the movement there.
You know, what they're doing
with those dolphins
is criminal.
- Where's your daughter
in all of this?
- Right there next to me
on the surfboard,
facing down the fishing boats.
- Doesn't she have school?
- No, this was mostly
over Thanksgiving--
Hey, I thought we
could retire to the boudoir?
- I'm--I'm still eating.
- It's just I kind of have
somewhere I have to go.
- Did you double book me?
You did.
- I can come back,
but I thought we could pre-game
a little, okay?
- Wait, so who gets
to play the actual game?
- Don't get all sensy.
I have a thing with my sister,
'kay?
- Okay.
[cell phone rings]
- Please hold.
- Yeah, yeah. Technology.
+- Hey.
Seriously?
Right now?
- Uh-oh.
Dolphin alert?
- It's worse.
Hey.
How is she?
- Did you come
to steal my baby
like you stole my husband?
- We're only at a three.
- Oh, my God.
Are you serious?
I feel like it's a ten.
- You're doing great.
- I hate you.
Where is your dad?
- She wouldn't let me call him.
She's just pooping
and screaming.
- Shouldn't she be
at a hospital?
- It's a home birth.
It's a rich people thing.
- Who's he?
- Oh, that's Noah.
He's my colleague.
Well, my boss.
- [laughs]
- My colleague boss.
- I'm gonna call a Lyft.
- No, no.
I'll drive you.
- You have to stay here.
What? Me?
- She's all alone.
She has no one.
- But she has, the, the lady.
- Her name is Harvest
and she smells like patchouli.
You have to stay.
- Okay, all right, fine,
I'll stay.
- Promise?
- Yes, I promise.
You just go home
and try to bury this memory
as deep as you can.
- So nice to meet you.
Can I share her Lyft.
- No, that's really weird.
Just go wait outside.
I'll be right there.
- Okay.
- Go, go.
[cell phone buzzing]
Yeah?
- I can't do this without you.
- Well, what do you want me
to say?
It's not my fault.
- I've heard that before.
- I didn't plan this baby,
okay?
- I've heard that before.
- Okay.
- How am I supposed to get it
all out by myself?
- You're not.
- I'm not?
- I got you covered, boo.
- You're the worst.
- Love ya.
- Yo.
- Hey.
.
- Hey, got some fresh ice
and towels for you.
- God, get out of here.
I don't want her here.
- Clean up some
of that goo coming out.
Any progress?
- We're gonna have to go
to the hospital soon, honey.
- That's a great idea.
Hospitals are great.
They have doctors with degrees.
- Why are you here?
Why?
- Well, I promised Sadie,
you know, she--
- You know,
and you brought a guy over.
- Well, we were--
- You nail my husband,
and then you bring
your boyfriend over, like,
while I'm sitting in this
freaking stew.
- Okay, well...
Yeah, I just didn't want you
to be alone, you know--
- You know what?
Your vagina's probably
way more destroyed then mine
and I am, like,
in active labor.
[breathing heavily]
- I...
what do you want from me?
- I want you to go blind.
- Nancy, I told you
I feel so bad,
and I'm really sorry, and
if there's anything I can do
I would do it.
- Oh, my goddess.
She's at a seven.
- And then I want you lit
on fire,
and I want your ashes
stuffed up a--
[screams]
- It's helping.
- Where do you want
'em stuffed?
- I don't know.
Somewhere gross.
- Like up an ass?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah,
like, like, way up.
- Yeah, well, whose ass?
Come on, whose ass?
- I don't have anyone.
I can't do this.
I need you off my hair now.
- Hey, you can do this, okay?
Just give me an ass.
Any old ass.
- I can't.
I can't.
I can't do it alone.
I can't do it.
[soft pop music]
♪
- What are you doing?
[crying]
I hate you so much.
- I know.
- I hate that he thinks
you're funny.
- I'm not.
♪
- Yay, almost 8.
- I can't believe you're just
sitting in my juices.
- That's nothing, I think
your mucus plug is on my arm.
- [laughs]
- Okay, my love.
It's time, it's ready to push.
- Oh, God.
Oh, my God. It hurts so much.
It hurts so much.
- You got this, Nancy.
Come on.
We can do this.
Let's meet this little guy.
- [screams]
[muffled hip-hop music]
[indistinct chatter]
- You said they
wouldn't be home.
- They're not supposed to be.
♪
[gunfire on TV]
- Smells shady.
- You'd know.
[hip-hop music playing]
♪
[gunfire on TV]
[music stops abruptly]
- All right!
Come on.
Let's go. Move it out.
School night!
Let's go!
- I'm sorry.
Who are you?
- She's his mom.
- PJ's mom?
- Who else would she be?
- Okay, guys, come on.
Get out.
Go to Mike's.
Get up.
Get out.
[indistinct chatter]
- Where is my son?
- I don't know.
- When's he gonna be back?
- When he gets back.
- [groans]
I don't know how you guys live
like this.
It's disgusting.
- Well, I'm gonna shower.
There's beer in the fridge
or Ensure.
Whatever you guys drink.
- Ensure?
- I am not old enough
to be his mother,
- Oh, you're gonna get on
my jock about that now?
- Just start looking.
- Hey.
- What are you still
doing here?
- You said to wait.
- Yeah, but that was,
like, 100 years ago.
[grunting]
[sighs]
- So I heard...
that you're kind of
a mess down there.
- She's just hormonal.
- Hmm.
Well, good thing you guys
team parent.
- It takes a village.
- Sure, yeah.
Like, like, the one in Ghana
where you fed
the Ebola orphans.
Your daughter has
no recollection of that,
by the way.
- She was very young.
- Yeah.
You didn't go to nursing
school either, did you?
- No, and after
what happened in there,
I am so glad.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
[both laugh]
- Are you in love with your ex?
- Kind of.
- [sighs]
So do I even have a shot here?
- Kind of.
Are you mad?
- [clears throat]
Kind of.
- Still like me?
- Kind of.
What is this on your arm?
- You don't want to know.
["Panique" by Juniore]
[singing in French]
♪
- Go ahead.
What?
- Why me?
- Why not?
- What address
did you give Turner?
- The one you told me to.
- Or did you give them
this one?
- Why would I do that?
- Because I'm about
to walk out there
with a ton of laundered money.
[tense music]
♪
- Fine, I'll go.
- No, wait.
So, what, you can go
give them the signal?
- What signal?
- The ones that gets me
alone in here
with a bunch of drugs and guns.
- So, what, you want me
to carry you out
like Costner
in "The Bodyguard"?
- I want you to be honest
for once.
- Okay.
We're doing this.
♪
Stan got put on leave, okay?
We are totally screwed.
You have no idea the hell
we've been going through.
- I don't know?
- He was in my house
breathing down my neck.
- How many times
was that man in my kitchen?
- He threatened
to cart my kids off.
- And I would never think
to save my own ass.
- Again, you are mad at me
for something I did not do.
- Because I would choose you
every time.
♪
- Who the hell are
these clowns?
[indistinct radio chatter]
- Sir.
♪
- Oh, Come on.
- Not what you wanted?
- Not even close.
- I'm sorry.
- Let's just get out of here.
[gun cocks]
- Put down the bags.
- Oh, no, PJ asked me to take
these for him--
- You're not his mom.
Get out.
Let's go.
- Told you I was too young
to be his mom.
.
- If we see the 5:15,
we can just stay through
for the 7:45.
- Sounds good.
- I mean, we don't have to.
- No, I want to.
- Well, I mean,
we've seen it like five times.
How about "My Girl?"
- It's not the movie.
It's prom.
- You want to go to prom.
- I don't know.
- I don't even have a dress.
- No, I mean, someone asked me.
- Oh.
- But I don't have to go.
- Who?
- Let's just go see the movie.
- Beth.
- Just some senior.
- A senior?
- His dad owns
a car dealership.
- [laughs]
["Can I Kick It?" by
A Tribe Called Quest]
♪
You should go.
- I don't even wanna.
- Well, I'm gonna be busy,
so...
- Doing what?
- Not going to the movies.
- Hate you.
- Hate your face.
♪
- Say I had tickets
to Beyoncé,
but I only had two tickets
and both you and Stan
wanted to go.
- Is this like a Destiny's
Child reunion situation,
or is this Bae by herself?
- With Jay-Z.
- That's dark.
- I'd pick...
you and Stan,
and I'd stay home.
- No, you wouldn't.
- I would.
Honestly, this whole thing
makes me want to puke.
- If it's Jay-Z,
I guess you take him.
- I mean, I got to, right?
- Hate you.
- I hate your face.
- Hey, you're up late.
- Whoa.
- Yeah,
you made the right call.
- What'd she go with?
- Dakota.
- Better than Mackinaw.
- Ew, that was a contender?
- It's where they boned.
- Jesus.
Okay, I'm gonna go shower,
and then shower again.
Yay, it's a boy.
- Mom.
So am I.
- Did you tell your dad?
- You're first.
- You okay?
- Are you?
- I was always wanted a boy.
[both laugh]
- You smell super bad.
- [laughs]
Meet your new baby brother.
Come here.
- Oh, my God. Ew.
- Come on.
Get in there.
[laughter]
- You want some hot
or mild sauce?
- They got that habanero?
- That stuff's napalm.
- No, no, no,
see you eat it fast enough,
the burn never hits.
Little trick.
- Yeah, okay.
- [laughs]
- So she's not gonna
give her friend up.
- There's only so much pressure
you can put on a person.
- How's it going
with the sister?
- I'm out of the friend zone.
- Already?
- Yeah, man.
You can't turn this down.
- Dude.
Dude.
[both laugh]
- Let me run with it
for a while.
- All right.
- We'll see what turns up.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Hook me up with another
spice bomb.
- You're an animal.
- [laughs]
["After The Fall"
by Chelsea Wolfe]
♪
- ♪ Nothing
♪ Keep us apart
♪
♪ I said nothing
♪ Keep us apart
♪
♪ I know that
you'll find me there ♪
♪
♪ After the fall
♪ I know that you're waiting
♪
- You might as well get
a pool now.
You're already halfway there.
- Ooh, yeah, should
put in a pool.
- [scoffs]
Like I could afford it.
- It would be fun though.
- Should we go in?
- It's too quiet in there.
- 'Kay.
♪
- He left me.
- ♪ Nothing
♪
- [sighs]
- ♪ Keep us apart
- And he took my kids.
♪
- I know.
♪ I know that you're waiting
♪
♪ I know that
you'll find me there ♪
♪
♪ After the fall
♪ I know that you're waiting
♪