Previously on Dexter...
You still don't remember
anything from before?
Before we took you in?
No.
What are you doing?
I'll talk to you through
a relaxation technique.
It might bring some things to the surface.
It was a match.
Joe Driscoll was your bio dad.
And this is Rudy.
- Dexter.
- Hey.
I have waited a long time to meet you.
Why the different nail polishes?
What's this guy thinking?
The real king is still out there.
Hungry.
Ready.
He'll kill again.
It's just a matter of time.
Dex, Rudy's different.
I feel safe with him. I think...
I'm falling for him.
Divorce papers.
Sign them and I'll agree
to supervised visits twice a week.
You think you can make me back down?
Are you fucking my wife?
Kids are settled at Colleen's.
You can visit them when we get back.
I just wish he'd go away. Why can't he
just go away and disappear forever?
- No.
- Fuck you, whore.
Come on, buckaroos. It's Monday.
Can't be late on Monday.
Throws the whole week off.
What about breakfast?
Made and eaten.
- The kids' lunches?
- Packed. Ready to go.
Did you tell the locksmith?
Yeah, new locks on every door,
reinforced strike plates,
seven-pin keyways.
Here you go, buddy.
Go wait in my car.
I want to talk to your mom for a sec.
- Are you gonna make out?
- None of your business.
- Are you?
- Astor.
You don't have to do this.
Getting attacked
by your ex-husband merits a day off.
I'm fine.
I won't let Paul control my life anymore.
Those days are over.
It will be OK.
The police have been notified. They'll find him.
What if they don't?
I got you some pepper spray.
Aim for the eyes.
You want some? It's Kirk Bliloc's cake.
I had some at Kirk's birthday. Ten days ago.
Having lunch every day with your boyfriend,
you miss some things around here.
Cake's still good. It's mocha, I think.
It started out vanilla.
Guys, you should look at this.
Put that thing down.
- It was addressed to Homicide.
- Put it down!
Jesus, is that blood?
Morgan, get your ass over here.
Ass en route.
You're the blood expert. What is this shit?
It's a little watery for jam.
Maybe you should open it.
What if there's an airborne toxin
in here waiting to be released?
I got to wash my hands.
So gullible.
What is it?
It's definitely blood.
There's something in here.
Marina View hotel.
It's a key.
Maybe a promotional gag.
Stay the weekend, get a jar of blood.
Show-and-tell's over.
Let's try and find out who sent this.
Grab Batista and get over to that hotel.
He's working on the explosion
at the smack lab.
Morgan, put the cake down. You're with me.
A jar of blood. Dramatic, cryptic, playful.
Could it be him?
Got an extra key from the manager.
Said the same thing as the front-desk clerk.
The guy who checked into 103
was white and normal-looking.
I haven't seen a security
camera since we came here.
It's likely he scouted hotels
and chose one with lax security.
Be ready to cancel your lunch.
Police. Open up.
Oh, my God! Jesus.
Get back in your room.
Metro dispatch, this is 3 Henry 88
out of the Marina View hotel.
I need uniformed backup, forensics.
Fuck it. Just send everybody out.
It's been a while
since we went prophylactic.
- Not me. Last night I met this chick...
- I'll stop you there, Vince.
They tell you anything about what's inside?
- No one's been inside. Too much blood.
- Dexter.
Just a heads-up. It's bad in there.
- I'm serious.
- OK.
She's not kidding.
It's your wet dream in there.
You're going in first alone.
Get a sense of what we're dealing with.
Give me a report. Don't fuck up.
Now I'm really curious.
He's been gone so long.
He had to be planning a splashy return.
But a crime scene just for me?
Mommy!
Tell me you found something.
I talked to the guests in 105.
They didn't see anyone go in or out.
- Across the hall?
- German tourists.
Got their head up their lederhosen.
They heard a whirring sound
but thought someone was mixing
margaritas or vacuuming.
Oh, my God! Are you OK?
I'm just a little queasy. I fell down in there.
Never should have skipped breakfast.
You're shaking. What happened up there?
No, I'm OK. I just need a little air.
Something finally got to you.
You're human after all.
Cut him some slack, all right?
I hate to disappoint you,
I think it's low blood sugar.
Tell us what you saw, Dex.
- How many dead?
- A lot.
But no bodies, just blood. 50, 60 liters.
Maybe half a dozen dead. I don't know.
There was a mass murder in there,
but they took the bodies?
How is that possible?
There's one elevator, stairs with alarms.
Someone would have seen
corpses coming out.
I don't fucking know.
- Hey, Dexter, you all right?
- I can't go back in there.
You don't have to.
Fine, just get yourself cleaned up
and work from the hallway or something.
You're in room 422.
Elevators are to your right,
and Bobby will see to your bags.
Excuse me.
Dade County, Sheriff's Department.
I'm looking for Rita Bennett.
That's me. Did you find Paul?
I'm sorry?
Paul Bennett.
My ex-husband attacked me last night.
My boyfriend filed a police report.
We only have the report Mr. Bennett filed.
What? Wait.
- Paul filed a police report? For what?
- Assault.
Your ex-husband was just released
from Baptist Memorial Hospital.
He's pressing charges against you.
- He attacked me!
- Not according to him.
All right. Can we talk about this later?
We need a formal statement.
You have to come with us
right now to the station.
Fine.
Make sure you label the section of the grid
each blood sample came from.
All right?
Sweet.
You should really get in here, Dex.
I never seen anything like this.
Wait till you see a few more
Columbian drug busts.
I got misting up the walls,
across the ceiling,
but no tissue. Come see.
Photos, Vince.
Why the blood's not clotting?
The blood's not clotting?
Genuine medical mystery.
Just keep getting samples.
I'll test it at the lab.
Hello? Don't hang up.
Dexter, I'm at the Sheriff's station.
Paul's pressing
assault charges against me.
How's it possible? I was defending myself.
Just stay calm. I know a lawyer.
I'll straighten it out.
I am calm. They're the hysterical ones.
They're charging me with
a Class Two felony.
Hello, Dexter? Are you there?
I'm right here.
This is ridiculous.
I could lose my job. I could lose my kids.
I won't let that happen.
- I'm glad you're so confident.
- Rita, just trust me.
I know how the system works.
I'm at a crime scene now,
I have to go.
I'll talk to my lawyer friend right away.
You're OK?
Yeah, I'm OK.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
Is there a wall socket there? Check it out.
- What? A wall socket?
- Yeah.
Of course there's a wall socket.
There's lots of wall...
You're right.
There was something plugged in here.
Probably a power tool to cut them up.
Come take a look.
Photos, Vince.
Lots and lots of photos.
Open Sesame.
Blood samples for the fridge.
Make room. There's a lot more coming.
Shooters at the Bel Canto tonight. You're in?
I'm not in the mood.
Angel, you're on the market,
and the Bel Canto is hottie central.
Look at this.
They were for Nina's birthday.
- Backstage passes to Neil Diamond.
- You're in worse shape than I thought.
- Oh, hi.
- Hi.
Masuka was looking for you.
Something about drinks at the Bel Canto.
I told him I had a yeast infection.
A bit of an overshare.
You want to talk about
what happened today?
Already did.
The last time I saw you
like that was when Dad died.
You can talk to me. You've just
got to open your mouth and move it.
I'll tell Rudy I'll be late.
Deb, seriously.
I puked.
I'm fine. I know you want to help,
but unless you have breath mints,
there's nothing to do.
- Why do you always do this?
- Do what?
You shut me out.
Like your birth father
that lived up the highway your whole life
and never contacted you.
I still don't know how that makes you feel.
If some random emotion strikes me
in the middle of the night,
you'll be the first one I'll call.
Fine.
Whatever.
- Did Paul force his way into the house?
- No.
Did you ask him to leave?
Yes, and he refused.
But in your statement,
it says you invited your
ex-husband into your bedroom.
He was drunk and the kids were asleep,
and I knew exactly where this was heading.
Cracked ribs and a broken jaw.
And you didn't want it to escalate.
I understand that.
But we can't prove intent.
Your ex-husband
has the injuries here, not you.
Paul has a record of spousal abuse.
Spousal abuse can be mutual.
It was never mutual.
But the man is a model parolee.
His drug tests are clean.
He's got glowing reports from
the court-appointed supervisor.
Corrections will want to see
this guy transition.
I don't care.
He's not going near my children.
Do you understand?
Rita, if you deny him visitation,
you could lose your children.
Now, you have deposition in two days.
Do not give him any more
ammunition than he already has.
Damn. Just blood?
What happened to the bodies?
Hell if I know. I don't want to know.
Blood was bad enough.
No wonder you seem so amped.
Your brother must have loved it.
- Fuck no. He freaked.
- Really?
I thought blood was his thing.
What happened?
I don't know. He shut me out like usual.
Did he say anything?
Let's not talk about Dex right now.
Was it like a panic attack?
I don't know. He's not really big into sharing his
feelings, in case you hadn't noticed.
Kiss me.
What's the matter?
You don't even have wood.
- You're the one who wanted to talk.
- Yeah, but not now. I'm horny.
Maybe I should call him.
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- What? We bonded last weekend.
Isn't that what boyfriends
are supposed to do?
Show some interest in the family?
Yeah, but not when his girlfriend's
trying to get into his pants.
Deb, that's not fair.
You take me out on a couples' weekend
to get to know your brother,
and then you punish me for giving a damn?
I mean, your issues don't have to be mine.
You know what?
Forget it. Let's just go to sleep.
OK. I'm gonna go watch TV.
She loved him so goddamn much,
She took every one of his CDs
in the separation.
She wouldn't even give me Greatest Hits.
Nina loved Neil Diamond.
Song Sung Blue.
September Morn.
Oh, my God, Kentucky Woman.
You got to love that shit.
That's like the fourth chick you've driven off.
Waitress! Is there a waitress?
I need a drink. Waitress!
Bro, you're a train wreck.
- You got to stop talking about the divorce.
- I ain't ashamed.
Yeah, I think that's clear, but it's pathetic.
Look, don't talk about
the divorce unless they ask.
Oh, and eighty-six the ring.
I have to take a squirt.
She's gonna fuck me silly.
My sister's right.
I don't share my problems with her
or with anybody.
Harry taught me that.
Secrecy, self-reliance,
and a well-stocked cupboard of Hefty bags.
Fortunately, I've never met
a problem I can't manage.
Until that boy in the blood.
He scares me. I want him to go away.
You awake?
What?
Are you sure you locked the door?
Yeah, I'm positive. Bolt and chain.
What am I gonna do?
Don't worry. I'll figure it out.
And I will.
I can always see other people's problems
more clearly than my own.
Fortunately, Rita's has a name.
Everyone who set foot on the bloody
carpet in room 103 left a footprint,
and since we do shoe molds
of everyone on personnel,
that leaves only one
set of footprints unaccounted for.
The killer's.
This shows everywhere he went in the room.
The question is why.
Hold on. Aren't we missing something?
Where are the victims' footprints?
Give that lady a lollipop.
Are you suggesting there were
never any bodies in room 103?
Why would a guy stage a massacre
and not have any bodies?
And where'd he get the blood?
I've just got a preliminary blood report.
The blood in that room came from
at least five different bodies.
Possibly more.
My fellow traveler had five victims.
- Ice-truck killer had five victims.
- Five bloodless victims.
I always wondered
what he did with the blood.
Wait. The ice-truck killer
did not horde his victims' blood
just to have a party at the Marina View hotel.
Why would he do that?
To chase me down the rabbit hole.
What was that, Morgan?
I didn't say anything.
I'll remind you people.
We arrested the ice-truck killer.
His name is Neil Perry,
and he's awaiting trial in County.
Bullshit.
Neil Perry recanted his confession.
He's a fraud.
- Try telling that to the Captain.
- I did.
Do we have any more evidence
to support this theory?
When Masuka noticed
the blood wasn't clotting,
I ran some tests,
and it was loaded with coumadin and heparin.
One's an anticoagulant.
The other's a preservative.
It means the blood's old.
Plus the blood spatter's all impact and castoff.
There are no hand transfers or swipe patterns
to indicate the presence of any actual victims.
Run the DNA on all five vics
and see if it matches
the ice-truck killer's victims.
You two get out to the Marina View hotel.
Retrace his steps. Maybe it'll tell us something.
And not a word to anyone
about the ice-truck killer.
Astor, just stand up straight.
Do you have
the emergency phone number list?
It's in my backpack.
Do I have to show it to you again?
Just promise me you won't let
your brother out of your sight.
- You're scaring them.
- Well, they should be.
I didn't tell them what Paul did the other night.
What'd you say when you dragged
them to the neighbors'?
I smelled gas.
I should have just thrown them in the car
and headed out of state,
gone back to Michigan.
Remember what the lawyer said.
You don't want to do anything rash.
Just relax. The court supervisor
will be there the whole time.
Hey, buddy. Come on.
Where's the love? Come on.
Daddy, what happened?
Nothing, buddy. Just a little bump on the head.
We're going to the circus,
'cause Daddy always keeps
his promises, remember?
Good. All right. Ready?
Got your stuff?
Let's go.
You OK? Come on.
I prefer the enchanting Rita
over the worried one.
If I can find a way to make
her ex-husband my problem,
I can help her sleep much easier tonight.
All I need is a little proof
of his inner monster.
Harry would have insisted on that.
Harry didn't believe in preemptive killing,
but maybe I can bend the rules, just this once.
After all, Harry wasn't perfect.
He lied about my birth father.
The trifecta. Weapon, ammo,
and impaired judgment.
Throw in a little domestic violence,
and you have the perfect recipe
for a family slaughter.
Mommy!
Close your eyes, Dexter. Close your eyes.
So, after he soaked the room in blood,
he crossed to the desk
and then over to the bedside table.
There's a clock radio
and some smeared blood.
Maybe he turned it on.
No, we're missing something.
Let's go over it again.
We've been over it three times.
Maybe the map's wrong. Call your brother.
What?
Why is everybody's first move
to call Dexter?
You don't even like him.
What'd the freak do this time,
boil your goldfish?
No, it's just...
It's Rudy. We had our first fight.
Tiff. I don't know. Whatever you want to call it.
I thought we were talking about your brother.
We were.
And we'll be back with
Billy Joel, the Eurythmics
and Devo on 103 FM, hits from the '80s.
Turn that off.
No, wait. I want to hear it.
It's Devo. Turn that shit off.
He said 103 FM. This is room 103.
Leviticus 10:3.
10:3. 103.
Son of a bitch.
You think he's trying
to tell us something?
"I will be sanctified in them
that come nigh me,
"and before all people, I will be glorified."
Hey.
Deb's pissed at me. I need advice.
So you came here?
You know her better than anyone.
Come on. I got two Porterhouses
and a sixer of Microbrew.
Well, one minute we're talking about her day,
you know, the whole bloodbath thing.
Right.
And the next, she wants to jump my bones.
I mean, Deb's hot and all,
but sprinkle in a little conversation
once in a while, you know?
No, she's my sister. I don't know.
Can I help you find something?
You wouldn't happen to have
a good meat knife?
Thanks.
Anyway, the other half
of the argument was about you.
Me?
Yeah. It was already tense enough,
but when I brought your name, she lost it.
So, what do I do?
Tell her it's all your fault.
- Seriously?
- You will eventually.
Deb has a way of wearing you down.
Just start from there. It's easier.
I got to take this.
You mind if I...
Where are you?
Still at work, chasing a lead.
Let me guess. The bloodbath case.
I don't want to talk shop right now.
Baby, I am so sorry.
You were totally right.
I was mad at Dexter,
and I took it out on you.
My shift's almost done.
You want to come over and talk?
I'd love to, babe, but I'm about
to eat dinner with Dexter.
Well, after.
Yeah, but here's the thing.
I think I'm gonna sleep at my place tonight.
I mean, it's closer,
and I'm drinking, you know.
You understand, right?
Yeah.
I'll call you tomorrow.
- Care to dance?
- You dance to this?
A bit.
What about your wife?
Tan line on your ring finger.
Well, um...
I'm not gonna talk about that tonight.
Divorced? I get it.
Mine was just finalized.
Let's go.
Will you excuse me? Excuse me.
Police. I need to talk to you.
I'm not a hooker anymore.
I work for a legitimate escort service now.
I'm not here to bust anyone.
I just need to know why
you paint your nails the way you do.
- He was a real good client.
- You want to spend the night in a cell?
All right. About a year ago, there was this guy.
Guy or client?
A john, OK?
That's when I worked Calle Ocho.
Anyway, he started getting all
rough with me until he saw this.
Then what?
Then he changed his tune, got all turned on.
Told me to take my fake hand off.
He started doing some kinky, weird stuff,
like he was worshipping it.
To cap it off, he takes all my nail polish
and paints each nail a different color.
I liked it, so I kept doing it.
You know that guy they arrested
for the ice-truck killings?
Yeah, the one who stuffs roadkill?
- Is that the guy?
- No way.
My trick, he's sexy. A freak, but sexy.
From the beginning and with more detail.
Well, thanks for the hospitality.
Thanks for the steaks.
You know, I didn't get a chance to ask.
Deb mentioned that you had
a little incident at the crime scene.
Did she?
Most of my prosthetic
clients are pretty traumatized
by the time they get to me.
Anyway, I'm a good listener
if you ever want to talk.
Thanks, but unless you know
an expert in repressed memories...
For real?
You know something about it?
More than I ever wanted to.
When I was in high school,
I started having these dreams
of a woman hit by a truck.
Who was she?
I didn't know.
Then one day I stopped by a mailbox,
and it all came crashing back.
My mom getting out to mail a letter,
me still in the car.
I watched her die.
How old were you?
Four.
I didn't remember anything
till I went and mailed a letter.
Walked right into the belly
of the beast without knowing it.
What kind of memories
are you having?
They're still a little vague.
Right.
Well, you're gonna have to face it eventually.
Maybe next time.
When you see Deb, go with white roses.
They're her favorite.
That's a good tip.
It's funny how life brings people together.
Rudy misunderstands my problem.
I want the boy and blood to go away,
not come crashing back.
Fortunately, I have other people's
problems to focus on right now
like forgotten cellphones.
What you got?
So far we're chasing a ghost.
Couple of employees helped with the sketch,
but it's pretty generic.
Only real lead we have is a couple
of numbers at the crime scene.
Screw the numbers. Who was killed?
Where are the bodies?
I heard some pretty wild theories out there.
Just theories. We're still
waiting for full blood results.
Damn it, Maria, you're stalling.
I'm just trying to avoid speculation.
You got to give me something and soon.
This department can't afford
another public relations disaster.
Well, maybe you should tell
the DA to let Neil Perry go.
He's not the ice-truck killer.
Are you still hung up...
I can't believe this.
Jesus, Maria, that's not gonna happen.
The DA takes his cues from us.
If you just tell him you made a mistake...
Not going to happen.
Now let it go.
First break in this case,
you come straight to me.
This may be a shot in the dark,
but I met this hooker last night.
Going with a pro.
Now, that's how you get over the ex.
No, that's not what I mean.
So you didn't fuck her. But she blew you, right?
Would you shut up?
- It was a lead.
- On what?
I'll let you know if it pans out,
but what do you know
about amputee fetishes?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, it's called acrotomophilia.
But don't let them hear you call it that.
It sounds like a disease.
No, they prefer to be known as devotees.
I knew you were the man to ask.
Not really.
I prefer a girl with a kung fu grip.
You know who you should talk to?
What's-his-face, Deb's boyfriend.
Prosthetics guys deal
with devotees all the time.
Thanks.
No memory flashes here.
No little lost boy in blood.
Maybe he went back to hiding in the dormant
reaches of my cerebral cortex.
Here's to hoping.
Yo, Dex.
So, this is what you do for a living?
I'm trying to match castoff
patterns from a crime scene.
A power tool was used.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
Circular saw.
Seems like there'd be an easier
way to make a mess like this.
Yeah, trust me. I know.
I've been in here for hours.
In my line of work,
you hear all sorts of horror stories.
Boat propellers, garbage disposals.
It seems like something
you'd see with a chainsaw.
Yeah, I hear that but this power tool
was plugged into a socket.
Guess you haven't heard
of an electric chainsaw.
Come on, people.
We're coming up empty.
Those numbers mean something. 1-0-3.
We need to find the connection,
and until we do,
you need to go over every page
of every police report you wrote
in the last six months.
Think. 1-0-3.
103.
Bus station locker, piece of a bank account,
area code, partial license plate.
What is it? I want answers.
What are you doing here?
How do you always do it?
Do what?
Make me feel like
I'm six years old all the time.
If this is about Rudy, he was
just picking up his cellphone.
Where'd he leave it?
- My apartment.
- What was he doing there?
- Eating steaks.
- And?
I don't know. Drinking beer.
And?
- Debra...
- And?
- Talking?
- Talking. You talked.
You opened your mouth,
and sounds came out.
On the same night that I wanted
to talk to you, but you shut me out.
Yeah, "oh."
You don't talk to me, Dex.
You've spent our entire lives
keeping me at a distance.
But my boyfriend shows up
on your doorstep with a couple of T-bones...
They were Porterhouses.
Porterhouses.
And you end up tossing beers back
into the middle of the night.
You are all the family
that I have, and I barely know you.
So, if you're gonna eat steaks
with somebody after a rough day,
if somebody's gonna break
through your walls, I think it should be me.
I think I have earned it.
I'm late for Rita's deposition.
Deb, it's hard for me. You know that.
You Rudy Cooper?
Angel Batista.
I work with your girlfriend, Debra.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
I'd like to ask you a few questions,
if you don't mind.
Sure. Let me just grab the door.
So, does this have to do with a case?
You could say that.
Well, fire away.
I ran into this lady with a prosthetic hand,
call girl, actually.
Said she had a very unique client,
an amputee devotee.
You have a lead on this client?
That's the bitch of it.
I don't have a goddamned clue,
except for the freaky sex stuff.
I was hoping that you could steer me
toward some of those weirdos.
I'm afraid I got into this business
to help people get better,
not help people get off.
I'm sure Debra will be happy to hear that.
But I can talk to some of my colleagues,
see if I can draw up a list of contacts for you.
That'd be great.
How often does someone get a chance
to help catch a bad guy?
- You in a rush for this information?
- No, no, I'm good.
I'm chasing a long shot, really.
Well, just give me a call at the station
when you got something.
Will do.
Good to meet you.
Last question.
According to your ex-husband,
you left town with
your boyfriend last weekend.
That's right. His father died.
Did your ex-husband
have a scheduled visitation
with his children during that time?
I told Paul I'd make it up to him.
So, then he gave you permission?
No.
I'm the one that gave him
visitation in the first place.
I'm the custodial parent.
I didn't have to do that.
Could you give us a second?
Yes, of course.
Why didn't you tell me you broke
your visitation agreement?
I didn't know it was a big deal.
I think she's answered that last question,
so unless there's something else...
No, that's fine.
If I missed anything, we'll get to it
at the psychiatric evaluation next Wednesday.
Nobody told me about
any psychiatric evaluation.
It's mandatory in these cases.
The psych test determines
if there's a competency hearing.
For me? But he's the ex-con.
It's standard. You should be fine.
Should be?
You mean she could actually lose this?
Guys,
I'm handcuffed here.
You violated a custody agreement.
You struck your ex-husband in your bedroom.
He has a case.
Mama, look at my henna tattoo.
- So, how much candy have you had?
- Lots.
Thanks, now she'll never get to sleep.
She'll come down soon.
This one's already crashed.
Mom, can my dad read me a story?
I don't think so, honey.
Please?
OK. Butjust one.
Put your duds on, buddy,
Spider-man ones I bought you.
I'll get him ready.
You've got 20 minutes left.
Thanks, Betty. Thank you.
It doesn't have to be this way.
I mean, we can make this easier
on each other, right?
I could drop the charges if you agree
to unsupervised visitation.
Fuck you.
Hey, Dexy.
I don't think your girlfriend
appreciates the gravity of the situation.
If she loses that case,
she could lose the kids.
- That won't happen.
- Never say "won't."
We live in a world of wills,
wills and wonders.
That's what I'm trying
to teach my children.
And they are my children, too,
something she seems to forget.
OK, so I made some mistakes,
but I learned from it, right?
I'm sober.
Look, no needle marks.
I got the Alaskan pipeline
running through these veins,
and all because of those two little glowsticks
of love in the next room.
My heart beats for those two kids.
So if you or that skinny bitch
try to screw with what's mine,
I swear to God, I don't care
who I have to hurt...
Harry's first rule was,
"Don't get emotionally involved."
I think this is why.
Astor, go brush your teeth.
Someone once said
it's easier dealing with other people's
problems than your own.
They were wrong.
- Where were you?
- Taking out the trash.
Did you see Paul?
When I was in the side yard,
I heard the front door open.
My dad's car is gone!
Let's face it, Paul. You've been a problem.
It's time for you to go away.
The ice-truck killer case
has been reopened. Officially.
We have new forensic evidence
that shows that the DNA
from the blood at the Marina View hotel
matches the DNA from his victims.
What about Neil Perry?
Isn't he supposed to be the ice-truck killer?
All those questions should be
directed to Captain Matthews.
He's been personally handling the Perry case.
Oh, shit. I hope she told the Captain.
- Where is he going?
- Thank you so much.
Who knew?
Who knew about this?
This is the first we're hearing about it, Captain.
The ice-truck killer is still at large.
Sure.
I'll call you back.
You overplayed your hand, Maria.
I gave you a chance to make it right.
- I told you...
- You don't tell me shit!
This is my department.
I made you lieutenant. Me.
You were just another spic detective.
Nice, Tom. Real nice.
Your true colors finally come out.
Oh, no.
No, you haven't seen
my true colors, Maria.
But you're about to.
Enjoy this office while it's still yours.
What happened? What's wrong?
It's Paul.
I don't know all the details,
but he violated Florida's three strikes law.
The cops picked him up
totally strung out on heroin.
He's back in jail.
It is truly amazing the things you can do
when you put your mind to it.
What's so funny, Mom?
Yeah, why are you laughing?
No problem is insurmountable,
not when you have
the most accessible
evidence locker in Miami.
The equipment that the navy has
is state-of-the-art.
Paul did need to go away.
This is the police.
But death wasn't the answer.
Police. Open up.
We're coming in, Mr. Bennett.
Life in prison will do just fine.
They train you to be the best,
and they expect you to be the best.
For now, at least, the code
of Harry remains unbroken.
Get over here. You're part of this family, too.
I need an ambulance at 1228 Caldon Street.
A guy's been stabbed.
Stay with us.
Just breathe, man. Don't try to get up.
Just hang in there, OK? Keep looking at us.
Heard they're dropping
murder charges on Perry.
Yeah, I'm sure he'll be filing
a lawsuit any minute now.
More shit for us to deal with.
Speaking of which, watch out
for reporters out there.
They're still waiting on
a comment from the Captain.
So, things still rocky at home?
With Rudy?
Yeah. I'm not calling until he apologizes.
I'm done being second choice.
Good for you, Morgan.
If you're not doing anything tonight,
Masuka's invited us to the Bel Canto.
- For you.
- It's too late. You blew it.
This is the first chance I've had to talk.
I'm too tired to talk.
Well, let's go home,
fall into bed.
Why, Rudy? I mean, fucking why?
You didn't want to fall into bed
the other night
when I laid my heart out on the phone.
- You wanted to talk to my brother.
- I was confused.
I'm not confused. I know what I want.
I was confused because I love you.
What I want is very simple
and uncomplicated.
What did you say?
I love you.
Don't try to...
- Fuck.
- What?
I love you, too.
What happened to your lip?
Incident with a tool at the workshop.
Let's get you home and take care of it.
So, this is doom.
I've been the architect of so much of it.
It's only fair I should know
what the fuss is all about.
He left me this room for a reason.
Five women gave their blood,
their lives for this moment.
There's only one way to find out why.
Close your eyes, Dexter.
I want Mama.
No!
No! Not in front of my baby!
Please don't cry. It's gonna be OK.
Not in front of my baby!
Don't you dare! Not in front of my baby!
Close your eyes, Dexter. Don't look.
Dexter, close your eyes.
I want Mama!
Mommy loves you, Dexter.