Previously on Dexter...
What happened changed
something inside you, Dex.
It got into you too early.
Your urge to kill is only gonna get stronger.
I wanna catch him
before he kills another one of my girls.
What can I do to help?
No blood.
What a beautiful idea.
Refrigerated truck.
He wants a cold environment
to slow the flow of blood.
I suppose I should be upset,
even feel violated,
but I'm not.
I think this is a friendly message,
kind of like, "Hey, wanna play?"
Finding that truck is your
golden ticket into Homicide.
So Miami's the haystack,
and the ice truck's the needle.
I just found the fucking needle.
This is seriously fucked-up.
I think he's trying to impress me.
And it's working.
The captain wants you
reassigned from Vice to Homicide.
Thank you, sir.
Rita is, in her own way,
as damaged as me.
- Are you gonna kiss him?
- Actually, yes.
We just got an ID on the body
from under the causeway.
His name is Ricky Simmons.
He was a cop.
Ricky Simmons was under deep cover
in Carlos Guerrero's family.
Guerrero's crossing a whole new line.
Now he's pissed off
the entire Miami Police Department.
It's me. It's James, OK? It's OK.
Was Kara sleeping with someone
other than Ricky?
Was it you?
James, she died.
Miami's full of good cops,
a lot of them here today.
But no offense, I wouldn't want
any of you hitting on my sister.
Ricky was different.
He was the kind of guy
you hoped your sister would fall for.
Most people have a hard time
dealing with death,
but I'm not most people.
It's the grief
that makes me uncomfortable.
Not because I'm a killer, really.
I just don't understand all that emotion,
which makes it tough to fake.
In those cases, shades come in handy.
Mac.
- I'm sorry, man.
- Thanks, man.
It's a fucking travesty.
You going after Guerrero?
Guerrero ordered these hits.
I'm gonna make something stick
to that Cartel cocksucker.
I didn't know
you and Ricky were so tight.
It ain't about that. Fuck with a cop,
you lose the privilege to walk the streets.
You're right.
...tragic loss of our fellow officer
but we praise his courage.
Ricky knew no fear.
Can you believe LaGuerta?
She didn't even know Simmons.
She knew he was a cop.
Wait. Did you tell her?
Proud of you for coming, bro.
I know you hate funerals.
- How you holding up?
- I'm managing.
I'm not. Keeping my face pinched in sorrow for
two hours straight is a real chore.
A whole life reduced to ashes.
For Ricky Simmons, it's over.
But sometimes,
you get a second chance.
Florida prisons kick free
25,000 inmates a year.
They don't do that for me,
but it feels like it.
I search for the ones who think
they've beat the system.
They're not hard to find,
like Jeremy Downs.
Jeremy got off easy.
Four years in a juvenile facility
for manslaughter.
To the coroner, the knife strokes
looked random, impulsive,
but I saw the work of a young virtuoso.
Too many major arteries were severed -
femoral, brachial, carotid.
Today Jeremy is just another
piece of trash on the street,
but four years ago,
he was the toast of Miami.
It was a gruesome scene today -
the bloody body of a teenage boy
found stabbed to death
inside this south Miami park.
Police haven't released
the name of the victim yet
but investigators are holding
a 15-year-old suspect in custody.
We're hearing that the suspect
lured the older boy
to the pond to spot alligators,
but once they were alone,
the victim was robbed
and repeatedly stabbed.
But I knew what he was
and what he'd do again.
All I had to do was circle
my calendar and wait.
Lemonade for my sweaty workers?
What do you say, crew?
Anybody parched?
What's parched?
When we put in the new lemon tree,
we'll be able to make our own
fresh-squeezed lemonade.
Can we have a lemonade stand?
I'll apply for a business license
first thing in the morning.
Thank you for doing this, Dexter.
I moved here from Michigan
with dreams of fruit trees in my yard.
But they keep dying.
I can't help it. I kill things.
That must be awful.
Fortunately, I have a green thumb.
The key to happy citrus is a fertilizer.
Bone meal works the best.
Hey, Rita.
Paul doesn't live here anymore.
No shit. He's in jail, but...
See, he still owes me
for two ounces of blow,
which means you owe me.
Don't get involved.
I never know in these situations.
- I don't have money.
- You got a car.
You want my car?
Yeah. The keys in it?
You know my dad?
I sure do, little man.
And you want to know something?
You look just like him.
I'm gonna tell him you said hi, OK?
Look, if you want,
I could go in the house,
throw your furniture around,
make a real mess,
but what kind of message
would that send to the little ones?
Just give me the fucking car.
You go inside and get the keys.
I'll wait with our friend.
Come on, kids, let's go inside.
What?
You think you can take me
with your little red shovel?
Everything OK in there?
Yeah.
You need toilet paper?
No.
The guy had no idea
who he was dealing with.
I'll file a report.
We'll get your car back.
No, no reports, Dexter.
Thank you, but Paul's out of my life.
I filed for divorce.
I just want my past to go away.
Well, it went away in your Rav 4.
Whatever it takes.
I can give you a ride to work
until you get another car.
Or I could take the bus
like millions of other people.
Come on, let's go outside
and enjoy this beautiful day.
Come on, kids.
What did they use, an ax?
It's blunt force.
See the way the head's caved in?
You guys check out the new hottie McGotass
in Dispatch yet?
She's a butter face.
What's a butter face?
You know, she's got a hot body,
but her face...
How great would it be
to pull a bronco on her?
Yeah.
Yeah?
You do it doggy-style, right?
And just when she's getting into it,
you grab her by the hips
and you yell another woman's name.
You're riding her like a bronco
cos she's trying to buck you off.
Often in life I feel like I'm missing
some essential piece of the human puzzle.
This is one of them.
What are you doing?
Oh, the bronco.
See? She knows.
I just got my first official Homicide call.
He's back.
- Who? The ice-truck killer?
- That's right.
You won't believe
where he left the body.
I knew he'd be back.
It feels like Christmas morning.
Look at that - a miracle on ice.
Stunning.
You all right, Dexter?
This is like a dream.
Standing on the home ice
of the Miami Blades.
I never pegged you for a hockey fan.
Yeah, there's something
about standing in a big, cool hole
I find very relaxing.
So, what do we know?
Same as the others. No blood.
So far, I don't see any hesitation cuts,
no bones flayed.
I think our boy's got his confidence back.
He never lost it.
He was just getting bored.
What do you think he's trying to tell us?
That hockey's a violent sport.
What else?
He's escalating the thrill.
Posing his victim
in the middle of a 20,000-seat arena
for all Miami to see,
to show them - to show us -
what he's capable of doing.
What did I miss?
Relax. You didn't miss anything.
Yeah, but she is - fingertips.
This body belongs to the frozen fingertips
we found in the truck.
Sherry Taylor.
It's another prostitute.
No blood, no need for me.
Come up to the command center.
We may have a suspect.
Is there really a suspect?
I'll let you know when I get back from
my first official homicide investigation...
I know her.
- Sherry?
- Yeah, she called herself Cherry.
We worked the same corner
when I was undercover.
You were, like, friends?
Yes.
Do you want a hug?
Fuck off.
A surveillance tape is missing
from the security office.
Let me guess -
the one covering the ice.
They said you were good.
I got the press knocking
on the door outside.
Somebody who was here last night
saw something.
Rent-a-badge, cleaning crew,
crack whore in the men's room?
- Come on, work with me.
- We can't find the night watchman.
Then he's a suspect.
Unless the ice-truck killer abducted him
to gain entry into the arena.
Your brother help you with that logic?
He could have just been
at the wrong place at the wrong time.
We need to get to his apartment
to see what we can find.
I was hoping I could hit Kiocho,
talk to my old contacts.
I thought you wanted to get out of Vice.
Isn't that why you cried to the captain?
Yeah, I mean... I didn't cry.
Listen, my girls know this victim, OK?
Their information could help us.
No, I want you to work with Doakes.
Maria, she has contacts.
- You still got your tube top?
- And my nipple clamps.
Don't come back without any information.
Everyone moves to Miami to die,
which means we have more junk
than any city in America.
A skilled bargain hunter
can find real treasure here,
but that's not my idea of hunting.
I prefer a stalk-and-ambush approach.
My instincts are impeccable,
but I have to be sure of my prey.
We're all adrenaline rats, you know?
Kill it till it dies.
We all meat hunters,
just out looking for dinner.
What you looking for?
- Can I see that one?
- Good eye.
It's a fixed-blade skinning knife.
Stainless steel.
Real time-saver for the hunter who likes
to do his own butchering in the field.
See the way that blade curves like that?
It's like the talon of an eagle.
15 bucks, and she's yours.
- I'll take it.
- Hell, yeah. Why would you not?
I'll get your change.
Easy, kid.
What the fuck are you doing, boy?
I didn't see him.
- You all right, mister?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Honest mistake. No harm.
You be careful with that thing, huh?
Sorry about that, boss. I only sell 'em.
So, what you hunt -
trophies or meat?
What do you think today, Dex?
The Winchester?
What about the 9mm?
A handgun?
Not exactly the weapon of choice
for pheasants.
You need a wide spread
to bring them down.
Did you ever shoot anybody, Dad?
Afraid so.
- Any of them die?
- Just one.
How did it feel to kill a guy?
Not so great, Dex.
When you take a man's life,
you're not just killing him,
you're snuffing out
all the things he'll ever become.
As a cop, I only fire my weapon
to save a life.
That's a code I live by.
Killing must serve a purpose.
Otherwise it's murder.
- You understand?
- Yeah.
I changed my mind.
I think we'll take the Ruger.
Rifle? I thought that shotguns
were best for pheasants.
We're not gonna hunt pheasants.
- It's a big one.
- Yeah.
This deer will put meat on our table tonight.
It's still alive.
For now, this is how we'll control
the urges you feel.
Channel them.
Why don't you go ahead, son?
Really?
Put the poor animal out of its misery.
I'm very proud of you.
You worked hard for this.
Thank you, Bishop.
Hi, Rose. Congratulations
on your confirmation.
Thank you. Do I know you?
My name's James Doakes.
Miami Metro PD.
I'm investigating the murder
of an undercover cop and his wife.
Oh, that's terrible.
Were they members of the church?
No, Rose, they weren't.
I don't understand.
Have you ever seen this man before?
I don't know.
Why are you asking me?
Get away from my daughter.
It's OK.
At my church?
In front of my family?
Ricky and Kara had a family, too.
You just opened a dangerous door.
No, man, you did...
When you murdered a cop
and an innocent lady.
What is he talking about, Daddy?
- Come on, honey. Let's go!
- Daddy!
You don't play by the rules.
Why should I?
You've got five minutes, Bizach, OK?
Yo, look who's back.
Who'd you fuck -
Dolce or Gabbana?
I let them both pull a train, OK?
Listen, I got a confession to make.
I'm not who you think I am. I'm a cop.
Bridgett, get back. I'm not gonna bust...
You're not a cop. You're a whore.
- I'm not a fucking whore.
- What's wrong with being a whore?
We trusted you, Brandy.
My name's Debra, OK?
And I'm not here to bust you.
He hit again, the ice-truck killer.
He got Cherry.
Cherry?
Shit.
This shit's crazy. I'm out.
I got a sister who lives in Ohio,
runs a fashion-boutique store.
I'm on the bus tomorrow.
I ain't closing my shop
for no sick, psycho bitch.
Fucking woman-hater.
I was on the street before him. Fuck it.
I can get him, you guys.
You just got to give me something.
Did any of you all see Cherry
with anyone the night before last?
Well, I saw her last night,
and then she got into a car
and never came back.
I was working all night, so...
- Do you know the driver?
- No.
The car was, like,
one of those old station wagons
that have wood panels on the side.
This is good. This is good. This is a lead.
- I should go get LaGuerta to listen.
- Who's LaGuerta?
My lieutenant. She hates me.
I'm close with the Captain. I'll talk to him.
What?
Never piss off your pimp.
LaGuerta's not my pimp.
Is that right?
Bitch tell you what to do?
Is your pussy taking all the risk?
Does she steal everything you earn?
Yeah, she definitely does that.
She's your pimp, baby,
And she will mess you up
if you play her.
I told you, I'm not a fucking whore.
What's wrong with being a fucking whore?
Hey.
Bought you a present to celebrate
your first official homicide case.
Seriously?
It's a cactus.
You only have to water it
three times a year.
You didn't have to go out of your way.
I didn't. I was at the swap meet.
So, any news on our frosty friend?
One of my contacts saw Cherry getting
in a station wagon the night she died.
- Did you check the DMV database?
- As we speak.
There are thousands of registered
station-wagon owners in Miami-Dade,
but guess who's not on the list?
The night watchman.
I knew LaGuerta had her head up her ass.
She doesn't have shit on the ice-truck killer.
Good.
Why good?
It's good for you.
You're gonna be the one to apprehend
that heinous murderer, not her.
Heinous.
All right. Good night, sister.
Don't stay up too late.
OK.
Thanks for stopping by.
- Hello?
- Hi.
Are you...?
Is this a bad time? It's Rita.
No, it's fine. Hi.
I was just reading a sad story.
Is everything OK?
Yes, I'm...
Look, the thing is...
You need me to pick up Cody?
No. Colleen's gonna take him
to karate with Hudson.
- What about Astor's piano?
- Jen's got that covered.
It's Social Services.
There's a caseworker coming by
the house this afternoon.
I should be home by 4:00,
but with the buses...
I'll be there. Don't worry about a thing.
Thank you, Dexter.
As you all know, a night watchman
from the hockey arena is missing.
Till now, we presumed he was abducted
or murdered by the ice-truck killer.
We searched his apartment
and found a stolen surveillance tape
from the night of the murder.
Chief of security at
the hockey arena confirmed it.
The man you're looking at
is Tony Tucci,
the missing night watchman.
And here's the best part -
Tucci has a record.
He pulled a knife at a party in '97.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I give you Tony Tucci, the ice-truck killer.
Bullshit.
Captain Matthews is coordinating
with the FDLE
to launch a manhunt
as soon as we get clearances.
- Does he drive a station wagon?
- Excuse me?
What kind of car does he drive?
The last known victim was seen
getting in a station wagon.
I don't recall asking for any questions.
Now, from this moment on,
all our resources go to finding this man.
Your individual assignments
will be coming shortly. That's all for now.
Doesn't make sense.
After being so careful for so long,
why would he leave evidence?
Of course I agree with my sister,
but unlike her, I'm not upset.
He's still out there, and I'm waiting...
breathless.
- You sure we can't get you anything?
- I'm fine.
Rita's usually home in time for the kids.
I'm just backup. Her bus must be late.
My files say Ms. Bennett
has personal transportation.
She did and will again very soon,
probably next week.
I just have to make a note of it.
She's doing an exemplary job.
I wish all my home visits were this lovely.
So why do you keep coming around, then?
Routine follow-up for
all domestic-violence cases
to ensure a stable home environment exists.
It's a good thing.
The system does work from time to time.
I was actually taken in
by a wonderful family.
No abuse.
In fact, my foster father understood
I had special needs.
Without him...
You're lucky.
Lucky.
I'm here!
Hey, everyone, I'm here.
Thank you.
- Sorry.
- It's OK.
I am lucky.
What do I know about abuse?
Without the code of Harry,
I'm sure I would have committed
a senseless murder in my youth
just to watch the blood flow.
Just try and keep him comfortable.
It's about all we can do for him now.
I don't understand. A week ago,
the doctor said he was getting better.
He is getting better, sweetie.
A body cannot suffer in sweet repose.
What does that mean?
What the hell does that mean?
She's weird.
Listen, you two,
I'm not gonna be around much longer.
Dad, don't say that.
You can make it through this if you fight.
When I'm gone,
I won't be able to stop you
from being who you are.
Sooner or later,
you'll need to do it.
Do what?
Just remember our lessons.
What lessons?
What are you talking about?
- I can't make it without you.
- Yes, you can.
If you feel like you're slipping,
lean on your sister.
She'll keep you connected.
Fucking Forensics report.
- What did they find?
- Tucci's hair and fiber.
Of course Tucci's hair
and fibers are on the body.
He's hauling her around
with his pork hands.
Any word from the chem lab?
Same as the other murders.
The killer used liquid nitrogen
to preserve the tissue,
give it that bleached look.
You know how unstable liquid nitrogen is?
You'd have to be a lab rat
just to mess around with that shit.
Tucci didn't even pass
high-school chemistry.
Watch carefully.
Right there. See?
Right before he repositioned the torso.
- He turned his head.
- Like someone's giving him directions.
Someone like the ice-truck killer
holding a motherfucking gun to his back.
- The killer's framing Tucci.
- It looks that way.
LaGuerta's gonna lose her
sheep shit when she finds out.
She'll have to cancel her press conference.
And you know how LaGuerta
loves her press conferences.
Can I borrow this tape?
Bingo.
I know what happens next
in this gruesome little scenario.
Jeremy is trying to recreate his first kill,
ritualize it.
You ready?
I don't know if I want to do this, man.
I thought you wanted to see an alligator.
- I do.
- Come on. It's in the marsh up here.
Wait. Are you a pussy?
No.
OK.
Let's go.
It's right up here.
Come on, Jer.
What are you talking about?
Don't be a bitch.
Here we are.
I don't see it.
It's right there.
See its eyes sticking out?
You have to get closer.
I still don't see it.
Really?
Maybe I was wrong.
There's no gator here, is there?
I don't know, Lucas.
Is there?
Anyone see a Frisbee? It flew in here.
Oh, shit.
Let's get the fuck out of here.
What am I doing out here?
Fuck! Fuck!
Fuck!
All I had to do was drive home,
have a taco, plan my attack.
Instead, I tried to act human,
like it's my job to save lives.
The code of Harry never covered this.
At least I know what Jeremy is
and what I need to do.
Don't let her.
OK, my brave little soldier.
Let's get this nasty shot out of the way.
No! Wait!
- What is it, honey?
- He doesn't want the shot.
Your father's very sick.
He's in a lot of pain. He needs a shot.
- No, I want pain.
- He wants pain.
I'll have to tell the doctor.
He's not going to be happy
you're refusing your medication.
You can tell.
About the nurse? Yeah.
She's...
like me.
How could you tell?
She gives too much morphine.
It's something else.
It's making me worse.
She's drugging you.
She's killing you by overdose.
Not just me. Others, too.
Stop her.
What do you mean, stop her?
It's time.
Before she hurts anyone else.
See the look on his face,
like he's scared?
Like he has a gun pointed at him?
I don't know, Debra.
It's not much - a look off-camera.
There's more. One of my Vice contacts,
Gabrielle - I trust her -
she saw the victim get in a wood-paneled
wagon the night of her death.
That was the last time anyone saw her.
Did a background report on Tucci.
He doesn't even own a car.
There's no fucking way this guy
can be the ice-truck killer. Sir.
What does Lieutenant LaGuerta
say about all this?
- I came straight to you, Captain.
- You went around her back?
- LaGuerta doesn't listen to me.
- You don't violate the chain of command.
You just don't.
Now, listen, Debra,
I gave you a shot in Homicide
because I think you can make
a decent detective.
But if I find you can't swim in these waters,
I'll put you right back on the street.
- You got it?
- Yes, sir.
Your father never would have pulled
the kind of shit you just did.
Did you know that one
of your officers has information
that casts some doubt
on this manhunt of yours?
Who, Morgan?
I realize you're something of
a folk hero around here, Maria,
but it would be a mistake
to ignore the work of a promising officer
just to further your political career.
Is that what you think I'm doing?
You were a middle-of-the-pack detective
before the press got ahold of you.
- Thanks for the vote of confidence.
- It's a reality check, and you need it.
And I got it.
Let's cut to the chase.
Are you telling me to call off my manhunt?
I will remind you that Jeb Bush himself
signed off on it.
No, no. You go ahead
and hold your press conference, Maria.
People of this city need to know
we're doing something about this mess.
But don't expect me to bail you out
if that night watchman
turns out to be a dead end.
A state-wide manhunt is under way
right now in Florida.
According to police,
a night watchman is on the run
after the dismembered body parts
of a young South Beach woman
were found Tuesday,
stacked on the home ice
of the Miami Blades.
The woman is believed
to be the latest victim
of the notorious ice-truck killer,
now responsible for five deaths
in the Greater Miami area.
These terrible attacks have to stop.
And we have to stop them.
With Tony Tucci
now linked to the murders,
it's our mission to find him.
Fucking joke.
Hey, going out tonight with the guys,
blow off a little steam. You in?
- Hey, man, sounds good.
- I'll pick you up at 8:00.
Elevator's around the corner and to your left.
Enjoy your stay with us.
Hello?
Rita, this is Mr. Curtis.
Are you coming to pick up Astor?
Oh, no, a friend of mine is - Denise.
Is she not there?
I'm afraid not, but your daughter is.
She's the last kid left here at school.
I don't have a car. Is she OK?
Yeah, she's just fine,
but we can't keep her here much longer.
OK.
OK, I'll work something out.
Do it again!
Shh. Let's not wake up Cody.
Now, let's see about that splinter.
That's a deep one.
This might sting a bit.
But the magical splinter fairy
will soon make you forget all about it.
- Who's the magical splinter fairy?
- Second cousin to the tooth fairy.
She brings candy if you put your splinter
under your pillow at night.
The tooth fairy is make-believe,
just like the bogeyman.
Hi, guys.
Ooh, you're right, Astor.
There's no such thing
as the bogeyman.
But the splinter fairy,
she's the real deal.
Will the splinter fairy come if I cry?
Thanks for picking her up.
If I had a heart,
it might be breaking right now.
Oh, sorry.
Who we picking up now, man?
He sure ain't sitting on my lap.
We're not picking up anybody, bro.
What we doing in the Gables?
I told you.
We're blowing off some steam.
This is it.
What the hell is this?
It's a disguise.
One of Guerrero's top lieutenants lives here
and we're gonna fuck him up.
Hold up, Mac. I thought you said
you wanted to go out and get shit-faced.
I am shit-faced.
How do I look?
Man, I'm all for sending the message,
but this ain't the way.
Why the hell not?
The guy's scum.
Mac, listen. I've got to talk to you.
Mac, Mac!
Hey, listen up, man.
I showed my face to Guerrero.
They gonna think I'm behind this shit.
- That's part of the plan.
- What plan?
You fucked my sister.
You fucked a cop's wife.
Now you're just fucked, buddy.
Open the door!
Shit.
Motherfucker!
Fuck.
Quit fucking around. Turn on the lights.
Come on, man,
turn on the fucking lights!
You're mine now.
- What do you want?
- Silence.
You gonna fuck me, faggot?
I killed the last guy who raped me.
What guy?
He raped you?
The guy you killed when you were 15?
Why didn't you tell anybody?
Would you?
He fucked me, and I killed him,
and if you try, I'll kill you, too.
I understand now.
Why didn't I see it before?
Jeremy didn't murder that boy
four years ago.
He was taking out the garbage.
Just like I do.
I don't want to cancel all my credit cards,
and I hate waiting in line at the DMV,
so give me back the wallet
you stole from my car,
or I'll break your fucking neck.
It's in my backpack.
Wait, is that all?
You want more?
That boy who raped you four years ago,
did he deserve to die?
Yeah, he did.
Well, the boy the other day didn't.
Remember that.
It could save your life one day.
Mr. Tinker?
Mr. Tinker, where are you?
Are you trapped behind the couch again,
Mr. Tinker-stinker?
The nurse was my first playmate.
I'll always be grateful to her
for opening up so many
magnificent new doors for me.
Things were a little messy in the beginning.
Hey, perfecting a new craft takes time.
But I was trained well.
Those who witnessed my early stumbles
never had a chance to tell.
I've just been looking
through your photo album.
I hope you don't mind.
Are all your victims in here?
I'm sorry. Let me help you with that.
Scream and lose a tongue.
I helped them...
all of them.
I took their pain away.
I understand.
Now it's time to take away your pain.
It was messier than I anticipated,
but it was still a special day.
But, of course, it was really Harry
who paved the road to my salvation.
With the nurse put down,
Harry lived another year
before hardening arteries
squeezed the last bit of life from him,
but his lessons have never failed me.
Harry taught me that death isn't the end.
It's the beginning of a chain reaction
that will catch you if you're not careful.
He taught me that none of us
are who we appear to be on the outside...
...but we must maintain
appearances to survive.
But there was something
Harry didn't teach me,
something he didn't know,
couldn't possibly know.
The wilfull taking of life represents
the ultimate disconnect from humanity.
It leaves you an outsider,
forever looking in,
searching for company to keep.
- Sweet ride!
- Is it yours?
It's yours, until your mom
can get a new one.
I borrowed it from an impound
right before auction.
- Dexter...
- Can we get in?
You better.
All you can do is play along at life
and hope that sometimes you get it right.
Thank you.
Score one for the little wooden boy.