Previously on Dexter...
I got here as fast as I could.
What are we looking at?
Female victim cut up into pieces.
The ice-truck killer? So soon?
This is what he wanted me to find all along.
Laura Moser...
My mother.
Laura Moser and three others
found chopped up with a chainsaw.
Your father was a decent man
and an honest cop,
but what he saw in that
cargo container changed him.
You think it's the attacker's blood?
We know Batista fought back.
The samples were a match.
They're from the same person.
So if you or that bitch
try to screw with what's mine,
I swear to God,
I don't care who I have to hurt.
Let's face it, Paul.
You've been a problem.
I need you to explain
to them why you're here.
I have no fucking idea
why I'm in this place.
You really don't want to do this.
Effective immediately,
you will no longer serve as my Lieutenant.
This isn't fucking over, Tom!
Debra Morgan...
will you marry me?
Yes, yes, yes.
Where's my sister?
Took her Code 12.
Left about an hour ago.
She wasn't supposed to go anywhere.
You made it easy.
So desperate to fall in love.
Where the fuck are you?
I'm at work and you're not.
I need to talk to you.
Do not see Rudy until you find me.
I've lived in darkness a long time.
Over the years, my eyes adjusted
until the dark became my world
and I could see.
But then Rudy turned on the light.
He flooded my memory, and now I'm blind.
I don't have much time.
To be more accurate,
my sister doesn't have much time.
He wants me to find him,
but where do I look?
I can't think. It's too bright.
Let me know if the tape's too tight.
There's no need for you to be uncomfortable.
Why are you doing this?
Who am I to spoil the surprise?
Oh, God! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
I'm just checking the supplies, OK?
Things are moving faster
than I had planned.
- This isn't you.
- Pretty sure it is.
No.
I know there's more. I've seen it.
I never wanted to hurt you.
I know. I know.
Does this make it easier for you?
'Cause I can keep going.
Oh, God. Oh, Jesus.
Oh, Jesus Christ!
There's nothing to be ashamed of, Deb.
You're not the only one who bought it.
Your name isn't even fucking
Rudy Cooper, is it?
- Nope. But he died for a good cause.
- Yeah, well, so will you.
You kidnapped a cop this time, you know?
Not some invisible hooker.
You kidnapped a cop.
It's all part of the plan.
Jesus.
It's hard to believe
it's almost come to fruition.
I mean, this is a lot of years
in the making.
We're only hours away.
He wouldn't have taken Deb
unless he left me everything
a clever monster would need
in order to find them.
Seems I have a new screen saver.
I knew he wouldn't leave me stranded,
but Born Free?
Of course.
Thanks to Rudy, now I know
where dearly disturbed Dexter was born.
Born free of all that's human.
That's where I'll find him.
She knows.
She knows. She knows.
All fucking night with that.
She knows.
Listen, we need your help.
Masuka says you were following up a lead
on the ice-truck killer
when you were attacked.
A hooker with a prosthetic hand.
John painted her nails different colors,
but it didn't go nowhere.
Except she was just cut up
by the ice-truck killer.
Holy shit. Monique was a victim?
We're operating on the theory
that he found out you were on his trail.
If we're right, that means
you got stabbed for a reason.
No one knew what I was doing
except Masuka.
Someone else had to know. Think.
I consulted with Rudy, Debra's boyfriend,
the prosthetics guy.
But that's crazy, right?
She's been AWOL
since she went to meet him.
She was supposed to come back
and help me canvass,
but she never made it.
That's not like her. Angel, we got to go.
Go. Just go.
There are about 5,000 cargo containers
in the port of Miami.
Finding the one where my mother
was butchered took a bit of magic.
Presto.
Shit.
Just a second!
I told you he was here.
There some reason you're not
answering your damn phone?
Ambien.
What happened here, Dexter?
I couldn't find the remote.
Where's your sister?
She didn't come to work,
and she's not at her apartment.
I honestly don't know, Sergeant.
Dexter, we think her boyfriend
is connected to the ice-truck killer.
We're working on getting
a search warrant to search his home.
Oh, my. No, wow.
Cut the crap.
- You know something. What?
- James.
I saw him last night, skulking in the lab,
ordering secret blood tests.
What kind of tests?
I was looking for a match
on the blood on Batista's collar.
And whose was it?
Rudy's.
Motherfucker.
Knock it off!
He knew all along!
Rudy lied about a cut on his lip.
Angel headbutted his attacker in the face.
- It was just a hunch.
- Why didn't you tell us?
I couldn't destroy
Deb's love life on a hunch.
I had to get the facts.
Here are the facts. If he kills her, it's your fault.
What else do you know?
That's it.
He's lying.
Give him a break, James.
It's his sister, all right?
If he knows what's good for her,
he'll stay home
and answer the fucking phone when it rings.
Call if you hear anything.
Hello?
Please don't hang up.
Paul?
The kids don't want to talk to you, OK?
Give them more time.
This isn't about them.
It's about how I was arrested.
Yeah, with a needle in your arm.
I know all about it.
Well, I don't.
I take responsibility for all the shit I pull,
but Rita, I was in the program.
I kicked the hard stuff.
Well, apparently not.
I was clean. I swear on my kids' lives.
It's been driving me nuts.
How I got from your house one minute
to the motel room the next,
completely out of my mind on junk.
- It's called a blackout.
- It's called a set-up.
Last thing I remember,
was standing
in the kitchen, talking to Dexter.
Maybe he smacked me on the head
and dragged me out of the house,
through the backyard.
You're a piece of work.
I'm telling you,
Dexter is not who you think he is.
Hello?
Make sure it's distributed to everyone, OK?
OK, his name is Rudy Cooper.
Some of you may have met him.
He was dating Officer Morgan.
She was last seen 16 hours ago,
driving to meet him
at the Miami Beach marina.
We need to canvass the entire area.
Check boat rentals. You guys know the drill.
I've sent a team
to his prosthetics lab at the hospital.
The judge just signed off on
the warrant for Cooper's apartment.
Let's tear that place apart.
Jake, Sergio, Kim, you guys are with me.
Your attention, please.
I want to introduce you to
our new lieutenant, Esmé Pascal.
She agreed to put her vacation on hold,
to provide us with much-needed leadership
at this critical time.
Lieutenant, you're on.
I understand we have a new suspect
in the ice-truck killer case.
We're on our way over now
to search his place.
And you are...
Maria LaGuerta.
An officer is missing,
so we need to move fast.
I thought that Sergeant Doakes
was running that investigation.
- He's out following a lead.
- What lead?
He said he'd let me know
if it came to anything.
I'll take it over from here. Thank you, Maria.
Who can get me up to speed on the way over?
I can, I guess.
You're driving.
Feel free to join us
when you locate your partner.
Would you like to come with us, Captain?
You seem to have everything under control.
Let's go, people.
It's in there somewhere, my birthplace.
Now what?
No cameras, no patrols, no dogs.
With billions spent on homeland security,
it can't be as easy as a couple of snips.
So much for the war on terror.
Finding a needle in a haystack isn't hard when
every straw is computerized.
Reefer yard, plug 4-3-6.
I don't like this place.
Something nameless was born here...
Something that lives
in the deepest, darkest hole
of the thing called Dexter.
Get in there!
Somebody else, get in there now!
It's all right, little guy. You're safe now.
Nothing will hurt you. I promise.
OK, Deb...
Don't be dead.
Shit.
Surprise, motherfucker.
- Are you following me now?
- You better have a reason for being here.
- I'm looking for my sister.
- In a cargo box?
Yeah, I'm kind of working on a theory.
You forget you work for the cops?
We love theories.
Spin me a story, asshole.
- What I do on my time is my business.
- Me too, and I'm on my time now.
There's no lieutenant here to save your ass, so
don't fuck with me, Morgan!
All right, you got me.
I ordered some furniture from Thailand.
I was waiting for it to be delivered.
Lab geek my ass.
What the hell's going on?
Security, I need somebody
down here right now.
Miami Metro PD.
Is this guy under arrest?
That's a good question.
You're connected to this.
I don't know how, but I'm gonna find out,
and what I find is gonna stick to you.
Let me out of here, asshole!
Let me out! Let me out!
Let me out, you piece of shit!
Let me out of here, you fucker!
Fuck! Let me out!
Sorry, but you were drowning out Fred's radio,
and he was kind enough to lend us his wheels.
Don't do it!
Bye!
His happy place,
where he kills more than time.
This is where he'd leave me a clue.
Dexter, better bundle up.
I like the cold.
You know, hypothermia
can easily sneak up on you.
So can hypochondria.
A home like this
would take years to put together.
He must have hated leaving it behind.
What are you looking for?
A clue. A signature or a calling card.
Anything that might give us
a sense of where he went.
I don't think he was
thinking about us when he did this.
I mean, look at this place.
You were right about the victim.
He rushed his work.
He killed that girl to keep us
busy so he could escape,
but he wouldn't go without
leaving a message.
We just need to find it.
Check this out.
This is where he played with his meat.
Pretty whacked out.
I can think of 101 uses for this table.
Know what I mean?
He has my sister, Vince.
Right. I didn't mean... I'm sorry.
Shit.
You're Karen, right?
That's right.
You're in charge of evidence.
This entire room, evidence.
Take photos of every item
in its original position.
Show me the inventory list
when you're done.
Is he in charge?
Guess he is now.
Hi. I'm Bob Hicks.
Can I help you?
I guess Paul never mentioned me.
I'm his Narcotics Anonymous sponsor.
Right.
So, having your sponsor do your dirty work,
which step is that?
He's just concerned for the kids.
No, he's concerned for himself. Excuse me...
I thought he was lying, too,
until I saw the proof.
What proof?
Well, the X-rays the prison
doctor took of Paul's head.
They showed a skull fracture.
Yeah, which I deservedly gave him.
No. You didn't.
After you struck him,
the hospital took X-rays, no fracture.
But in prison, a fracture.
If you know Paul,
he'd bash his head against the wall
to get what he wants.
I do know Paul. I think I know him pretty well.
No, listen, if Paul was attacked,
the way that it happened,
that takes expertise, skill.
No first-timer is gonna be able to pull that off.
Which is why his accusations are ludicrous.
Dexter spends all his time
in a laboratory, for God's sake.
So you've been there?
You seem like a nice man,
but this is none of your goddamn business.
OK. Got it.
We traced the social of Rudy Cooper
to a New Jersey plumber
who mysteriously died in '98.
You got to be kidding.
We still don't have an ID on this guy?
Rudy isn't his real name?
- You trying to be smart?
- Not trying, no.
If you know his name...
Whatever it is going on
between you two, it ends now.
What did you find in there?
Other than the obvious,
a lot of trace bloodstains.
It's probably where he killed them all.
I'd like to look at the rest of the apartment.
Yeah, OK.
- You mind if I...
- Be my guest.
It's perfect. Right out in the open.
At least he's consistent.
Was there anything else near this?
Yeah, a fucking doll sitting on top.
"Home sweet home."
Is he taking me back before the blood,
to a place where a boy was born?
Home sweet home, but which home?
Down on the floor, please.
It's kind of foolish, Deb.
I don't usually work this way.
Call it an homage to a fellow
traveler I greatly admire.
Laura Moser.
Addict, dealer.
My mother.
Arrested in '69, again in '71.
Same address listed both times.
1235 Mangrove Drive.
They say home is where the heart is.
Maybe this is where I left mine.
Surprise.
What are you doing here?
White-chocolate mocha. Your favorite.
I'm gonna have to drink it on the road.
I've never even been here before.
I'd love a tour sometime.
Sometime that's not now.
Dexter, what's going on?
It's Deb, OK? She's in trouble.
God. Is it serious?
Yeah, actually, it's very serious,
but I just can't worry
about you, too, right now.
She knows.
The notorious ice-truck killer,
whose been leaving a trail of dead bodies.
Authorities say their big break came
when they found a video of his latest victim.
If she knows, you yapping
about it ain't gonna change it.
The suspect is operating
under an alias, "Rudy Cooper."
We didn't have his fingerprints
in our database,
so his identity is still unclear to us.
She knows.
So sorry, Mr. Batista.
We had to take the psych
overflow from County,
but this one's harmless.
Don't be so sure.
We never take the violent ones.
They have the arsonists, the rapists,
the psycho killers over there.
I tell you, those people belong in prison.
Do they fingerprint
psych patients at County?
Yes, of course.
Half of them don't know their own names.
Got to ID them somehow.
That should take care of him.
Enjoy the peace and quiet.
ID Tech.
It's Batista. Can you do me a favor?
I need you to run Rudy Cooper's prints
against psych, mental, and institution records.
Where are you, you silly little bear?
I'm going to find you!
Where can you be?
You silly little goose.
I'm gonna find you!
You silly bear. Where is my baby?
Where is my Dexter? Where are you?
- Where's my Dexter?
- Here!
Oh, my goodness, yes!
You surprised me, you stinky little bear.
Hey, where could your brother be hiding?
Bynie's right there.
Hey, Bynie.
You weren't supposed to tell her.
You remember now?
Bynie.
You always had trouble saying Brian.
I have a brother.
A real brother.
None of this foster bullshit.
We're blood brothers, through birth and death.
Watching mom die,
it's amazing that we survived that, isn't it?
The chainsaw, the flying body parts,
the blood.
You were there, too.
Two days sitting in blood
before they found us,
but you were young enough to block it out.
I've never forgotten the day that we were...
Born.
Exactly.
Where's Deb?
I waited for you before we got started.
- Debra!
- She's not in here.
This is not the way
I envisioned our family reunion.
Come on, let's just sit down
and have a beer.
That was the best wipeout.
You didn't even cry.
Next time you try my skateboard,
bend your knees, OK?
Hi.
Look out!
I didn't want to do it this way.
OK, let's run his description
against Interpol's fugitive list,
in case he isn't American.
Rudy Cooper? His real name is Brian Moser.
What the hell are you doing here?
I got a hit on his prints
from a Tampa mental hospital
where he grew up.
He was institutionalized for
antisocial personality disorder.
At 21, they said he was cured.
They released him.
Run the name Brian Moser
for credit cards, bank accounts,
anything that might tell us
where he's got Morgan.
We've triangulated
Officer Morgan's cellphone.
Last known location,
20 miles off the coast,
which means he's got her on a boat.
We have his real name.
We're digging into his records.
His name's not gonna help us
find him in open water.
Coordinated search with the coast guard.
- Waste of time.
- Chain of command.
Flyovers, helicopters, whatever it takes.
That signal died last night.
By now, he has most likely taken
her to his final location.
Noted.
Let's get busy, people.
Flyovers look good to the press,
but they won't find Morgan.
You think the press matters to me?
It matters to Captain Matthews,
and he calls the shots.
I know you need to define yourself here
and putting me in my place
is one way to do that,
but one of our own is missing,
and we shouldn't waste our time
pissing on trees.
I agree.
I can also see why you were reassigned,
and it has nothing to do
with incompetence
and everything to do with
the Captain trying to save his job.
OK.
Now, I was hired with the directive
to not make your life easy.
So you're gonna ignore the lead?
You don't know me very well,
but luckily for Officer Morgan,
neither does the Captain.
Nothing personal.
I just wanted to have a beer
with you before we got started.
You made that kind of difficult.
Sorry.
You don't ever have
to apologize to me, Dexter.
Not for who you are or anything you do.
Looks just like it used to, doesn't it?
Who does it belong to?
Me.
I got it for you, actually.
I'm really more an apartment person.
You're trapped in a lie, little brother,
the same lie they tried forcing me into.
They?
You know...
Doctors, therapists, group leaders.
What a family they were.
You were never put up for adoption.
Afraid not.
You were three, a little bird with a broken wing.
First cop on the scene, Harry Morgan.
He wanted to make you all better.
But me... I could see it in his eyes.
All he saw was a fucked-up kid.
They all did.
So they locked me up.
I didn't even know you existed.
Of course you didn't.
Harry wanted to keep you all to himself.
And while you were being raised
by the Morgan family,
I only had the memory of a family.
Me.
Mom always told me to look after you.
Imagine how I felt when I tracked you down
and found out you were exactly like me.
I don't have to imagine.
I know what you've been going
through all these years.
The isolation, the otherness,
a hunger that's never satisfied.
Well, you're not alone anymore, Dexter.
You can be yourself with me.
Your real, genuine self.
Takes the breath away, doesn't it?
I think we're ready for Debra.
I've prepared her just the way you like.
This time, we'll do it together.
Does it have to be Deb?
It's the only way.
But she's my...
Fake sister. I know.
Tell me something...
Your victims, are they all killers?
Yes.
Harry teach you that?
He taught me a code...
to survive.
Like an absurd avenger?
That's not why I kill.
You can be yourself around me.
Who am I?
A killer...
without reason or regret.
You're free.
You can be that way, too.
What about the code?
You don't have a code.
Harry did.
And he's been dead ten years.
You can't keep him sitting
on your shoulder like Jiminy fucking Cricket.
You need to embrace who you are now.
I don't know who I am.
Of course you don't.
You've been away from
your family since you were three,
but I'm here now. I can help you.
We can take this journey together.
I can't.
Not Deb.
Don't say that.
I'm very...
fond of her.
You can't be a killer and a hero.
It doesn't work that way!
Cover the yard! We're going into the house!
Fuck.
In the garage!
Through that door!
It's locked. Fuck! Cover this door!
Cover the door!
Come on. Stay with me.
Shit.
Maria, stay on the door.
He's trapped inside. I'm breaking in.
Cover me, man.
Get in.
Shit.
Chopper 1 to command,
we're broadening the search
to a five-mile radius.
Any headache, dizziness?
I'm fine. I just want to go home.
I'm afraid we have to take you
you to the hospital.
Standard procedure.
You're saying Rudy called you?
Why would he do that?
Maybe he wanted me to try to talk him down.
He was having second
thoughts about killing Deb.
He seemed to feel like we have
some kind of connection.
He's not the only one.
He said he'd kill Deb
if I didn't show up alone.
Well, you almost fucking got her killed.
I'm gonna request an immediate
suspension when we get back.
You're gonna what?
Morgan, you shouldn't be out here.
Are you questioning Dexter?
Back the fuck off my brother!
He just saved my life! He's a fucking hero!
Want each of you to treat him
that way, God damn it!
Way to go, Deb.
I thought you were gonna burst
a frontal lobe out there.
Assholes.
Stop. You're gonna dislocate it.
Get it off me. I'm gonna be sick.
Relax.
Here.
He's still out there.
Yeah.
And he didn't get what he wanted.
No.
Think he'll try it again?
Maybe.
I'll talk to Captain Matthews
about getting us an officer stationed
outside your hospital room.
No, I'm not staying in a fucking hospital.
There's nothing fucking wrong with me.
Well, you're not staying at home.
Well, I'll just crash with you.
Let's just wait and see what
the doctor says, all right?
Yeah.
Why me, Dex?
Why'd he choose me?
You're just lucky, I guess.
I was so scared. I was so scared.
- I know.
- Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Dad would be so proud.
It's me.
Paul, this is harassment.
Just tell me if he's acting weird.
Who?
Dexter. He hasn't been
himself lately, has he?
How could he be, after what he did to me?
That's it. I'm done.
Call again and you can forget
about ever seeing the kids.
I am not gonna subject them to your insanity.
Fine, if that's what it takes
for you to listen to me.
- I want to know that they're safe.
- Why are you doing this?
You want me to be
miserable and alone like you?
All I want is for you to look for a shoe.
A shoe?
Could be in the kitchen or in the backyard.
It's missing.
I checked, and it wasn't in
the items that they got when I was arrested.
Why would it be here?
I was trying to figure out
why my ankle was so bruised.
Now I'm thinking it got banged
when he dragged me out,
when my shoe was knocked off.
Good night, Paul.
Night.
Screw you.
What did I just do?
I drove away a brother
who accepts me, sees me,
for an adopted sister
who'd reject me if she knew
and a foster father who betrayed me.
That's what it was, a betrayal.
The most important single fact about me.
I'm not alone. And Harry kept it from me.
What do I really owe him after that?
Mr. Morgan?
- Mr. Morgan?
- That's me.
Your sister has some bruises,
but no major injuries.
Still, you should keep an eye on her.
I'll write a prescription for a mild sedative.
But she's OK, right?
She can go home with you tonight,
or we can keep her here at the hospital.
It's your choice.
Don't worry. The sheets are clean.
We aim to please here at Chez Dex.
I'll be sleeping on the couch
with a spring in my side
just to make sure
you're safe tonight, but...
we're gonna have to talk
tomorrow about a long-term plan,
after you get a good night's sleep.
Good night, sister.
I stopped by your prosthetics lab
after I left Deb at the hospital.
Your work's so good, you even fooled yourself.
Sweet dreams, Bynie.
Hey.
You weren't supposed to wake up.
I guess not.
Sorry.
Police recorded all your knives as evidence.
Took a while to find your dinner flatware.
Sterling.
I keep it for special occasions.
Which you are.
I can give you more tranquilizer if you want.
It's a service I don't usually offer.
What am I, one of your victims now?
You going to collect a sample
of Bynie's blood for your collection?
No, you're not a trophy...
but you need to be put down.
Why? Because of your code?
And the safety of my sister.
She's not your real sister.
She's a stranger to you,
and she'll always be one.
I tried to help you by killing her.
I know that!
You should know this isn't easy for me.
You've done more to deserve
my knife than anyone.
You're the only one
I ever wanted to set free.
You're the one that needs
setting free, little brother.
Your life is a lie.
You'll never be what you...
Sorry.
I can't hear any more...
'cause you're right.
How did you know he was here?
A neighbor saw the door open.
We got his fingerprints on
the knife, a note on the fridge,
and a single incised wound to the neck.
Slight upward angle.
Even a stigmata of hesitation in the stroke.
Looks like a clear suicide.
He does himself the same way
he did the hookers. Poetic.
Retarded. Look at him. He's dead.
The ice-truck killer always flaunted
his kills as if he was untouchable.
By taking his own life,
he's preventing us from ever catching him.
I don't care why he did it.
I'm just glad he did.
Decaf mochaccino, non-fat, no whip.
Your favorite.
I got your message.
How's Debra?
She has all her limbs.
Thank God she's alive.
That poor thing must be a mess.
Falling for a serial killer.
What are the odds?
- What about you?
- What about me?
Are you all right?
Yeah.
No.
I've been through a lot lately.
I could use a little more time
with you and the kids.
We could, too.
I'm sorry I've been so...
Next time, could you just
let me know what's going on?
When you didn't return my calls,
I started to get a little paranoid.
I can be better about that.
Good.
Who knows?
You might even find I can handle the truth.
I wish that was the case.
The reality is, there's nobody left alive
who can handle my truth.
Doakes always sensed
I was hiding something.
Now he knows.
My devil danced with his demon,
and the fiddler's tune isn't over.
I wonder what it would be like
for everything inside me
that's denied and unknown to be revealed.
But I'll never know.
I live my life in hiding.
My survival depends on it.
Dearly damaged Debra,
she's here to face what's left of the monster,
spit on his carcass, mourn him.
She's in hiding now, too.
Harry's daughter won't let anyone see
what she's suffering inside.
That's her tragedy.
My tragedy is that I killed
the one person I didn't have to hide from.
And I'm the only one who mourns him.
Everyone would probably thank me
if they knew I was the one
who drained him of his life.
Good job. You sliced him up good.
In fact, I'm sure
they'd appreciate a lot of my work.
Way to take out the trash. Thanks, man.
All right, Dexter, protecting our children!
This is what it must feel like
to walk in full sunlight,
my darkness revealed,
my shadow self embraced.
Yeah, they see me.
I'm one of them...
In their darkest dreams