Previously on Prison Break.
Did you see the guy in the viewing room?
No.
It was Dad.
I know that guy.
What is it?
It was fused into Michael Scofield's skin.
- Where'd it come from?
- As far as I can tell, a guard's uniform.
What's wrong?
The blueprints,
the ones we need to get
from the psych ward to the infirmary,
they're gone.
Hey, that's looking good.
You're making some real progress.
The plaster adds a lot of weight.
I may have to add reinforcements.
Whatever it takes, as long as you get done
in time for the anniversary.
It'll be done. Hold this.
You know, the Shah loved his Taj so much
that he built another temple
just like it on the other side of the river.
It was an absolute mirror image.
Except it was darker,
it was like a black Taj Mahal.
Never heard of it.
Well, that's 'cause it was never completed.
He was overthrown by his favorite son
before he could finish it.
- Sounds like a myth.
- No, it's 100% true.
I think.
Excuse me, Warden.
Dr. Tancredi is here to see you.
Thank you.
Adams, please escort Mr. Scofield
back to his cell.
- Doctor, what can I do for you?
- Actually, it's about Scofield, sir.
Come in.
- What about Scofield?
- The burn on his back is fairly serious.
He seems to be recovering.
At first, I assumed
he was being assaulted by another inmate,
but I found this embedded
in the skin on his back.
- What's this?
- It's fabric.
Came from a guard's uniform.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to remember those blueprints,
what we lost to the burn.
- Any luck?
- No.
I spent a lot of time
studying those blueprints,
tracing them night after night,
considering every possible route
to the infirmary.
It's like trying to take a test
you studied for 10 years ago.
PI!
- How do they get like that, I got no idea.
- I do.
- Tugging on too many pockets.
- She tug on your pocket?
I may be social, but that's
the boundary line even I won't cross.
So how about it, Fish?
When we rolling out?
- One hiccup left, but I'm working on it.
- Yeah, and what is that?
Our road map's
a little incomplete at the moment.
I don't get it.
Why not just go down there again?
'Cause, one, I don't have
the guard's uniform anymore,
which means I can't get across the yard
or past the orderly.
And two, even if I did,
it's a mess down there.
I need this.
- You think you're gonna remember it?
- Not with you hounding me.
Time to wrap it up.
We're going to
have you start exterminating.
- We're not done in here.
- Well, you look done to me.
No, CO,
we still got the carpet to do, man.
No, Bellick is going to bring
professionals in to do that.
Wants the job done right.
- When's that going to happen?
- Tomorrow.
We got a real problem
on our hands, don't we?
Rug monkeys gonna come
in here, tear up that carpet
and that hole's gonna
be smiling up at them.
- We'll have to fill it in.
- We just dug that bitch.
All we need is a piece of plywood
and a couple inches of that
fast-setting concrete on top of it.
The carpet guys will never know
there's anything beneath it.
And the night we break out,
we'll just smash through
with a sledgehammer.
Well, okay. Let's get on it.
We've only got a couple hours
to get this thing done.
Hey, Tweener. You met Avocado?
Yo, what's up?
Lookit. She's just a baby.
Hit road.
Have a seat.
So...
Scofield.
What's the 911?
It's 411, and I don't know, man.
I ain't up in his car.
You know, Avocado's looking for a new cellie.
Boss, come on, man,
I'm trying to break bread with the man,
but I can't get jack
unless I can get to the table.
You know what I'm saying?
Scofield got his own peeps up in PI.
He don't need me.
- How long this stuff take to dry?
- One, two hours.
Fire on the line.
This place is sweet.
I heard we're getting satellite.
- Yeah, all the porn you can watch, boss.
- Good, good.
You know, you girls
have done such a good job,
I thought you could use
an extra pair of hands on the crew.
What's up?
Hey, man, look at my brush.
It's all sticking together.
Somebody needs to go clean them out.
According to rank, that would be you.
What do I gotta do?
There's a hose out by the shed in the yard.
You can use that.
Clean those, too.
All right.
Sorry I busted up the party, yo.
Who is he?
For your purposes, all you need to know
is that man in the photo
used to work for the Company.
He went rogue.
And how's he involved in this situation?
He's Burrows' father.
Wait, wait, wait.
You picked the son of a Company man
to be our patsy? Did the Company know?
The Company did know.
That was the whole point.
How about you elaborate on that?
How about you
stop with all the questions?
You are a glorified bodyguard, that's it.
Your job's to be seen, not to be heard.
Is that understood?
- How close are we?
- Oh, we're good to go, baby.
Got another badge.
What is this, happy hour?
Scofield? Pope wants to see you.
The rest of you round up,
you're done in here.
Hey, CO Patterson said
we had till the end of the day to finish up.
And I say you're done.
There's a couple hours of work
I want done in the yard before sundown.
Come on, let's go.
- We're dead.
- We're not. I'll get it done.
- It's gotta be done tonight.
- I said I'll get it done.
Scofield, Pope's waiting.
Hey, Linc.
You going to let me out?
No, Linc, just came to let you know
they set a new date.
DOC refiled all the paperwork.
Execution's a week from Friday
at midnight.
You going to let me out in the yard
or what?
Unless I hear it from the Pope himself,
I can't do it. I'm sorry.
Come on, man, 10 minutes.
That's all I'm asking.
Ten minutes.
I'm sorry.
Some guy just walks into the courtroom,
drops off some medical records,
Lincoln gets a stay of execution,
then "poof," he disappears into the cold.
Who do you think it could be,
some anti-death penalty fanatic?
Oh, come on, in this case, I doubt it.
But without a name or a paper trail,
we got no way of getting to him.
So once again we have nothing.
I wouldn't exactly call
a two-week stay nothing, okay?
It's more than we had yesterday.
Can I ask you a question?
Do you really think that
you're going to get to the bottom of this?
That they'll let you
get to the bottom of this?
These guys don't exist.
You go after them with the law,
and they'll just use it against you.
We're doing the best we can, okay?
Law's the only way we're going
to bring them to justice, LJ.
They gunned my mother down, man.
You think I give a damn about justice?
I want them.
I wanna do to them what they did to me.
Come on, LJ.
It's for the courts to decide, not us.
Look, they're going to slip up, okay?
They're going to leave a piece of evidence
that can't be refuted.
And we're going to be waiting
to nail them when they do.
Maybe they already slipped up.
Up at the cabin, at the well.
Quinn.
- Somebody covered it up.
- They must have come and gotten him.
There's only one way to find out.
Look, there's his cell phone.
Easy.
Okay, a little lower!
A little more.
Okay, I got it.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Pull me up.
Would you give us a minute, Gary?
Michael, I want you to be
absolutely honest with me.
Dr. Tancredi found this
embedded in your flesh
when she was treating you.
Apparently, it came
from a guard's uniform.
Have you been assaulted by an officer?
Michael, Michael,
I need an answer.
This is not about
sticking to the inmates' code anymore.
This is about officer misconduct.
That's my responsibility.
You wouldn't want to see me
lose my job now, would you?
No, of course not. You have been
very good to me and my brother.
Then I need to know
where you got that burn. Right now.
Otherwise, your ass is going to solitary.
You understand?
It's your choice.
Don't... Hey, please, listen to me.
- Cool down!
- Listen to me, don't do this!
Don't do this!
Michael!
No!
Michael?
- Linc?
- What the hell are you doing in here?
Linc, we're in a lot of trouble now.
What happened?
The Pope asked some questions
that I couldn't answer.
About what?
He's got proof that I was
where I wasn't supposed to be.
He doesn't know it, but sooner or later
he's going to put the whole thing together.
There's no way out of this.
Yeah, there is.
- You just got to keep the faith.
- No.
I put my blood into this,
and it's coming apart.
Listen to me.
The whole point of solitary is to break you,
make you crazy.
You got to keep strong, you hear me?
Don't let them break you.
I put my blood into this.
Look, baby, I'm so sorry it took me so long
to get back to you.
Turns out that our division is not
getting mobilized for a couple more days.
When I didn't hear from you,
I didn't know what to think, baby.
I got so worried. I started
watching the news, looking for casualties.
I'm so sorry about all this.
You gotta believe that.
I started calling
the rear detachment office,
asking if there was some sort of problem
with the 117th.
No.
There's not a problem with the 117th.
We're coming back. It's a snafu, that's all.
A couple more days,
and we'll be on those hops, baby.
That's not what
the rear detachment officer said.
He said the 117th wasn't coming home
for another six months.
What? No. That can't be right.
That's what he said.
You know what it is?
It's because we're transpo.
You know, technically
we're on a loan-out from the 140th.
I mean, that's why he said that.
- The 140th?
- Yeah, yeah.
It's just a few more days.
That's all. I mean,
you don't need to go calling anyone.
I'll be back, okay?
I will call you
as soon as I know the exact date.
Okay?
- I love you.
- Michael's in the SHU.
- Oh, God, the hits just keep coming!
Last thing we wanna do now
is panic, fellas.
Oh, it's panic time, old head.
We got an unfinished hole
in that room over there
that Scofield was supposed to fill tonight.
Come tomorrow 8:00 a.m.,
they rip up that carpet, our game is over.
Unless someone else fills it.
That's right, papi.
You're the only one
with a toilet open to the outside world.
You're saying
I go out there by myself tonight?
- That's exactly what we're saying.
- Are you kidding? That's impossible.
Look, I don't wanna hear impossible
from you right now!
I got people waiting on me,
people that I'm gonna lose,
unless you man up
and get some cojones, comprende?
That's easy for you to say, pendejo.
It ain't your ass on the line.
All of our asses are on the line.
And you're the only cat
that can do something about it.
Yeah, maybe I can get out of my cell.
And maybe
I can get into the guards' room.
But even if I do, and I fill that hole in,
I'll still be in that room.
I'll be sealed in. There's no way out.
- Scofield must've had a way.
- He did.
The grate at the sally port.
Oh, that's right. The one out there
in the middle of the open?
Yeah, so you better lace up, amigo,
'cause you're gonna have to
make a run for it.
That's 10 years on my bid if I get caught.
Then you better figure out a way
not to get caught.
Line it up!
Tonight, primo. It's gotta be tonight.
Michael. You okay?
What you doing?
I'm trying to remember
what's beneath psych ward.
You're thinking about the wrong thing.
You got to think about
how to get out of here.
Michael.
Man, come on. Talk to me.
Uh-uh.
Absolutely not.
If I'm gonna be the one doing that running,
you gotta do some lifting, too.
I mean, you know
what you're asking of me?
You gotta do it for the team.
Hey, sister. Your bloomers are showing.
They aren't showing, baby,
they're flying. Proudly.
I take it you are a party girl.
- LJ? Come on, we're leaving.
- Okay.
We get Quinn's phone powered up and
it could be a gold mine of information.
- No. Doesn't fit.
- We just need to find the right adapter.
What about Quinn?
Are we just gonna leave him here?
You mean the guy
who shot me in the back?
Yeah, we're just gonna leave him here.
You tell anyone about this, and I...
Capitol Hill saw
its first deadlock of the term
on the Senate floor this morning.
The hotly contested energy bill
ended up in a 50-50 tie.
That means it will now be up to
Vice President Reynolds
to cast the deciding vote.
I know I sound like a broken record,
but you work too hard.
You need to get out,
hang out with your friends more.
What about men?
If this is your exposé on my social life,
it's about to be a real sad one.
I...
I've had some bad luck
when it comes to relationships.
You had bad luck or you had bad boys?
I think I've managed to have
a little of both.
Yeah, you know, you're right.
I don't tend to go for the nice guys.
I like the ones
with the deep-seated emotional issues
I can internalize and make my own.
Mmm-hmm. Like Scofield?
- Nope, not like Scofield.
- Don't lie to me.
Every time he comes in for his shot,
you spend 20 minutes
rolling up his sleeve.
You know what? I think he's interesting.
And I think he's attractive,
but he's still an inmate.
I can promise you one thing.
And that's that you will never see
anything happen
between me and an inmate.
Michael.
I put my blood into this.
What? What'd you say?
- Stop! Freeze right there!
- Get down on your knees!
- Please don't shoot! Don't shoot!
- Freeze right there!
You know the state of Illinois
doesn't look too kindly upon prisoners
who try to escape.
Charges are filed,
you get sent back to county
for three months.
Come back here with 10 more years
added to your bid.
- I wasn't trying to escape.
- Sure you weren't.
You were just out there
howling at the moon.
If I were you,
I'd better start talking, mano.
I stayed out after yard today.
I waited under the bleachers
until it got dark.
Something was gonna come
over the walls.
Drugs is almost as bad as escape.
Last guy had heroin slingshot
over the wall
got a nickel added to his bid.
- It wasn't drugs.
- Then what the hell was it?
Frisk him!
What do we have here?
A pair of grunds?
You risked going to the SHU
for a pair of grunds?
Hell, you risked adding extra time
to your bid, all for a pair of panties?
My girl just wanted me to know
she was thinking about me, boss.
You got a real beefer on your hands,
don't you?
I know, boss.
It's the dumbest thing I've ever done.
I'm just scared that being here,
I'm gonna lose her.
- He did it for love.
- Then you understand.
Yeah, sure, Sucre. I understand.
Don't let me catch you alone
next time, okay?
- Sucre!
- Sink?
Sucre.
- Where's Michael?
- Other side of you.
Michael! Michael!
Michael!
Michael, come on.
Badge!
Yeah?
Check out my brother.
He's not responding.
- What?
- Scofield. Check him out.
He's not responding. Please.
Scofield.
- I need a medic in 12 now. I repeat, now.
- What?
There's an electronics store
on Eighth Avenue. Grab his phone.
We'll be back in 10 minutes.
Stay on the couch.
Hi, you've reached Owen Kravecki.
I can't come to the phone right now.
You really think you're gonna get
to four buttons before I get to one?
Leave a message, and I'll return your call.
Thanks. Have a great day.
Light on 12.
Would you wait outside, please?
Michael?
Okay, you're going to feel my fingers
on your wrist.
Come on, I need your eyes.
I'm going to take a look at that hand.
You're going to be okay.
- Sucre got...
- I heard.
Papi better had did us right, man.
Hope he had enough time.
Looks like we're about to find out.
Make it fast.
I thought we picked
Lincoln Burrows off the street
because he was some lowlife
who couldn't defend himself.
Now I learn it's all about his father,
some old spook
that the Company's
trying to settle a score with?
Well, fortunately for us,
the Company's agenda and our agenda
have the same endgame.
Caroline, I've been doing this for 15 years,
and it's never been about anything
other than you, your family,
and most importantly, this country.
Now, I need to know
who I'm working for here.
You are working for me.
Promise me that.
I promise you, Paul. I got to go now.
And to what do I owe this honor?
To the vote on the Senate floor
this afternoon.
Look, I get it.
The vote comes down to me, I vote "no."
Lt'll get done.
Well, actually, we are going to need you
to vote "yes" on this one.
I want to make sure I heard you straight.
You want me to vote
on the environmentalists' side?
This isn't about a vote.
This is about you
and how you look to voters.
Now, we have a nation that is growing
increasingly hungry for alternate energy.
So if you come across as more centrist,
you'll appeal to the broader swath
of the electorate,
the very people
who will get you elected next year.
Besides, once that bill
hits the President's desk, he'll veto it.
Then we'll get precisely what
we always wanted anyway, won't we?
You probably don't have
a hair on your body, do you?
Just back your punk ass up.
Hey, Tweener! Get over here.
Looks like Avocado
has taken a shine to you.
- I could set you up as cellies if you want.
- Stop it, all right?
I got something for you this time.
Scofield and his boys,
they're up to something.
How about being a little more specific?
Whatever it is, it's got to do
with that room they're fixing.
Something to do with the carpet.
Excuse me, fellas.
Out of the way!
Michael!
Michael! Michael!
He's totally non-responsive,
so start him on chlorpromazine.
And I believe he's in danger
of a psychotic break.
I want you to notify me immediately
if and when that happens.
- All right.
- Thank you.
Come on.
Come this way.
Come on. Here you go.
Watch your step.
Clean him up.
You scared me.
Put it down. You're not a killer.
You don't want to make
any rash mistakes here, LJ.
- Don't move!
- Go easy, go easy...
Shut up!
LJ, there's other ways out of this,
you know, okay?
I can help you beat this rap,
but if you pull that trigger,
you really will be a killer,
and then I can't help you, okay?
I'm government, LJ.
There's a lot of things I can do for you.
The only thing you can do for me is die!
Drop your weapon!
I said drop your weapon!
Guess you're going to have to take
a rain check on that one, huh?
Drop the gun now!
No. I did what you said.
- You brought me a pile of crap.
- There was nothing there.
Boss, come on, man.
I just need some more time.
You had your time.
You're a waste of my fries.
Open on 88!
Boss, come on, man!
Dude, just give me another try.
Close on 88!
Have at it.
Boss.
Boss!
- You're lucky.
- Kid's got a warrant for double homicide.
- Oh, dear. Are you serious?
- Did you have any prior contact with him?
- Any idea why he chose your house?
- No, none.
I mean, he was screaming something like,
"You killed my mom,"
and going on
about me being a government agent, and...
I don't know, it just seemed like that kid
was on drugs or something.
What do you do for a living, Mr. Kravecki?
I'm a regional sales manager
for a dehydrated meat distributor.
- What, you mean like jerky?
- Yes.
- You a fan?
- What kind?
Buffalo.
Have some. Really.
I'm swimming in the stuff.
One hour till lunch.
So, what's the problem?
You're looking at it.
- What, Haywire?
- Yep. He's my new cellmate.
They think I have schizoaffective disorder
with bipolar tendencies.
Your tattoos.
What about them?
- What are they of?
- They're just tattoos.
The man's got a maze on his skin.
Why would he do that?
Why would he put a maze on his skin?
It's a pathway.
Where does it lead?
Hello, roomie.
You were right about my tattoo.
It is a path, just like you thought.
And I need you to remember
when you saw it, Haywire.
I need you to remember
what it looked like.
Do you think you can do that for me?
Who are you?