Rough night?
I got your message. What's the problem?
Lost my keys.
- Where'd you find them?
- Four feet that way.
Must've dropped them.
How you doing? It's been a while.
Fine. How are you?
Cold.
Man, I...
I need to talk to you about something.
- Grab some lunch at Fascetti's?
- I have to get back to work.
Speaking of which,
I heard you got fired a few weeks ago.
What was it this time?
You really want to know?
Or are you just enjoying the view
from your high horse?
You know what I want?
To not have to be the older brother
to my older brother.
What you doing here, Crab?
Long time no see, Mr. Linc.
Where you been?
- Here and there.
- Mmm-hmm.
I'm gonna get your 90 grand, all right?
Oh, relax, man,
that debt already been paid.
- By who?
- Someone who likes to do people favors.
I don't know what it is
you think you're getting,
but let's be clear about something.
It's gonna be a few days
before I get the money lined up.
Let's not kid ourselves.
You can't get anywhere
near that kind of money.
So let's talk about
what you can do for me.
REYNOLDS. ;  Allies are like family.
We have disagreements,
but we always seem to
smooth things out by Thanksgiving.
Okay, if you had to choose,
Vice President Reynolds or Kathy in HR?
- I'll take door number three.
- Come on. If you had to choose.
That chick in HR.
Michael never cared much for blondes.
- V.
- How you doing, Michael?
Good. I'm good. How are you?
I'm okay.
You know, I'm over at Glazer and Ross.
Lawyer number 97. Benefits are good.
How's Lincoln?
How is he?
He's...
He's Linc.
I don't care who the guy is.
I ain't killing no one.
I must have missed the part
where I gave you a choice.
Black leather jacket.
Two buttons down the front,
three on each sleeve.
One missing on his right... No, left arm.
Jeans. Faded.
Stain on the left knee.
He does bad things to good people.
Think of this as a $90,000 bullet.
You start fresh,
and you keep me from finding out
if there's someone in your life
you will do something for.
Oh, I should call you a cab.
You know how you can tell God is a man?
Shoes.
Easy.
I'm sorry.
What?
It's...
You gonna answer it?
He'll leave a message.
He always does.
Michael, it's Linc.
I need your help, bro.
I'm in something real bad.
I can't get out of it.
- I need you to straighten me out.
- My head is all messed up and...
Anyway, it's real important, bro.
You gotta call me.
You gotta call me now.
I can't do this.
I know.
I'll call you a cab.
- Did we get him?
- I believe we did, partner.
Are you kidding me?
Nando, we should've
whooped that guy's ass.
Please. Only time I seen you
whoop some ass
is when that old man
cut in front of you at Arby's.
Yeah,
and he was like 102 and blind.
With a plastic hip.
Oh, my God.
What?
WOMAN. ;  Dr. Davis, telephone,
please. Dr. Davis, telephone, please.
- Hey, they're waiting for you in 4B.
- Oh, pull his film.
- I'll be there in a minute.
- Okay.
Sergeant Franklin,
you never cease to amaze me.
Is there anything you can't get here?
All right, a deal's a deal.
Prison guard duty. Away from the front.
Safest place you could be.
Thank you.
And my wife and daughter
back home thank you too, sir.
These coal seams are pretty significant.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Would you give us a minute? Thanks.
Have you been watching the news?
- Why?
- It's Lincoln.
- I didn't do it.
- Terrence Steadman.
The Vice President's brother.
Do you have any idea
what they're gonna do to you?
I didn't do it, man. It was a setup.
I didn't do it.
You knew him.
- Who?
- Steadman.
No.
- You worked for his company.
- So what?
From which you were fired
a few weeks ago.
I loaded containers in the warehouse.
Never met the guy. What the hell, Mike?
You sound like
one of the damn detectives.
- I'm just saying.
- You think I did it?
I heard you owe someone 90 grand.
- Who told you that?
- People talk.
And I know Steadman had a lot of money.
I may be a lot of things,
but I'm not a murderer.
Then what were you doing
in that garage last night?
You admitted to the police you were there.
Honestly, Linc,
I don't know how it's come to this.
And you can't keep
blaming Mom for dying
and Dad for leaving,
because I was there, too.
Difference is, I got out.
Mom had life insurance.
I took my half, put myself through school.
What did you do with your half, Linc?
Everything's not how it looks, Michael.
I hope for your sake that's true.
Here...
- Here is where we want the turn to anger.
- Trust me, that won't be a problem.
Now remember to stress his record
as a repeat offender.
We need the public behind us
if we want the death penalty.
And where are we
with Governor Tancredi?
He has aspirations. He won't be a problem.
Thirty seconds,
Madam Vice President.
The papers
have already crucified him.
The police say they got a phone call
right after the murder
from someone claiming they saw Lincoln
running from the parking garage.
He was into someone for 90 grand.
What do you need that kind of money for?
Drugs, bribes?
Forget about what you want to be true.
Let's look at this objectively.
- Maybe you should too.
- I am.
All right, you know what?
I promised I wouldn't say anything,
but I'm getting tired of you
talking about him
like he's some guy from the neighborhood
that you used to know.
- He's your brother.
- I know.
And I know he helped you out
with your dad back in the day,
but you should see
the kind of person he is now,
the kind of people he keeps friends with.
You want to know
what the 90 grand was for?
- I think I do.
- You.
What do you mean?
The money you got
when you were 18 years old
from your mother's life insurance?
The money that paid for your degree,
that got you this job,
that bought you your loft?
Your mother never had life insurance.
That money came from Lincoln.
- How?
- He borrowed it.
He knew it would be tough to pay back,
but that didn't matter,
because he thought you deserved it.
He also knew you'd never accept it
if you knew it came from him.
Michael, you are where you are
because of your brother.
You're telling me
he is where he is because of me?
Why?
Why didn't you tell me about the money?
- No need to.
- Oh, Linc.
Who told you? Veronica?
What did she make of all this? About me?
- I don't know.
- Glad she got out when she did, huh?
You know how she feels about you.
It's been the same way
ever since we were kids.
Yeah.
Linc,
- I owe you an apology.
- For what?
The night you called.
If we'd talked,
- maybe I could have stopped you.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
This ain't your fault.
Then who's is it?
Listen up. You need to forget about this.
Move on. Work hard. Do what you do.
I can't do that.
Oh, yes, you can. And you will.
Here's the part I don't understand.
All the evidence is lining up
in a path that leads directly to you.
They say they have you on tape.
Pulling the trigger.
If you didn't kill Terrence Steadman,
how the hell did someone
make it look like you did?
Perfect.
Perfect's a strong word, coz.
- I got strong feelings, bro.
- I'm telling you, she might be the one.
- She from the block?
- Nope. Uptown. Pill Hill.
You think you could hold on
to a girl from the PH?
I want to take her out to dinner.
You'll see. Someplace real nice.
Come on, Fernando.
How are you going to afford
a place like that?
- Open the drawer!
- Hey, hey, okay!
- Open the drawer, coño!
- Okay, okay!
- Quick! Quick!
- All right, okay!
- Now!
- Here.
Actually, this is all I need.
Okay.
C- NOTE. ; I appreciate your business, man.
I'll have that in here for you
about next week.
I brought you a gift from the hospital.
I'm telling you, it is like Christmas.
And you work at the North Pole.
If the North Pole had gunshot wounds
and cancer patients...
Seriously, I don't know
how you work there.
What do you mean?
I like to help people.
You like helping yourself.
And you like helping your friends.
Oh, my God.
Can you hear us? Are you okay?
- Help, somebody!
- Who's got a telephone? Call 911!
Oh, my God! Can anybody help...
Call 911! Help!
Are you a doctor?
Can you help him?
Well, do something!
At ease.
The whiskey that you ordered, sir,
will be here in a couple of days.
That's fine. I actually brought you here
to talk to you about something else.
- Prisoner-abuse report you filed?
- Yes, sir.
I need to know how far
you're willing to go with this.
Whatever it takes, sir.
I particularly have no love
for the desert donkeys,
but I do have some
for the Geneva Convention.
Something like this gets out,
it might open up our boys
- to similar treatment from the enemy.
- I understand that, sir.
But I'm not planning
on calling a press conference.
What I'm saying is,
what I saw was wrong,
and someone
needs to take responsibility for it, sir.
All right.
Please take Mr. Franklin into custody.
Yes, sir.
What? What the hell is going on, sir?
Sergeant Franklin,
I'm hereby recommending
that you be dishonorably discharged
from the United States Army.
- What? For what?
- For engaging in illegal black-market...
- You asked me to get that stuff, man!
- I kept it to myself.
Maybe you should learn to do the same.
You can't do this.
You can't do this! You cannot do this!
Has the jury reached a verdict?
- We have, Your Honor.
- What say you?
In the matter of The People
of the State of Illinois vs. Lincoln Burrows,
on the count of murder in the first degree,
we find the defendant guilty.
The defendant will remain in custody
until one week from today,
when we commence the penalty phase.
Lincoln.
I'm so sorry, Linc.
Don't be. It's not your fault.
Know what I like?
How after we make love,
you get this little puddle of water
in your belly button.
Fernando, that's sweat.
And get out of there! It's disgusting there!
I think it's beautiful.
I think you're beautiful.
What do you want, Fernando?
Oh, you got to give me
a few more minutes...
Stop.
From the future.
What do you want from the future?
Would you run if I said "you"?
Would you chase me if I did?
DARIUS. ; I don't get it.
All these commercials show brothers
learning computer skills,
new technologies.
Uncle Sam didn't teach me nothing
but cadence and kill.
- You check over at the Price-Mart?
- Ain't hiring.
Especially with a brother
with a dishonorable discharge.
Goes right to the bottom of the pile, man.
How long you think you can keep this up?
Until somebody gives me a job.
No, I'm talking about lying to Kaycee.
Your unit's been on leave
for a long damn time now.
Pretty soon they gonna stop thinking
you're lucky,
and she's gonna start asking questions.
Yeah, well, then I need to start
finding some answers.
Look, I happen to know
of an employment opportunity.
Come on, man, you know
I don't get down like that.
- It's just driving a truck.
- Yeah.
A to B. That's it.
Uncle Sam taught you
how to drive trucks, didn't he?
Yeah. And he also taught me
to look inside.
It might be illegal, but it's also rent.
A to B, your call.
Yeah.
- They didn't even let her testify.
- Who?
Leticia Barris.
And that cop?
- Changed his story a dozen times.
- What part of "move on" don't you get?
After Mom died,
when it was just you and me,
I remember having trouble sleeping.
Never knowing where you were.
But when I'd wake up in the morning,
there'd be this paper bird,
an origami crane, sitting next to my bed.
And I never knew what it meant exactly,
but I figured it was your way
of letting me know
you were checking in on me.
Anyway,
I looked it up.
The crane.
It stands for familial obligation.
Watching out for your own.
Maybe it's my turn to watch out for you.
So same time tomorrow.
No, man,
they're transferring me to a prison
where I'll wait until they execute me.
- Can I still visit?
- Yeah.
It ain't that far. Place called Fox River.
- Fox River?
- Yeah.
Why?
Nothing.
How come there's four?
Well, Mommy's new friend
is coming over for dinner again.
Again? He just came over last night.
- I like him.
- Well, I do, too.
And I want you both to be extra polite,
because he's stopping by Malarkey's
on his way home from work,
and he's bringing us a really good meal.
In fact, you two go wash your hands.
Evening, Mrs. Hollander.
Don't you look lovely this evening.
I'm gonna do it.
Do what?
I'm gonna propose to Maricruz.
Are you serious?
When?
As soon as I can afford the ring.
So what, like 10, 20 years?
What's your problem, man?
Why can't you just be happy for me?
I'm just trying to protect you.
What, you think you can give her
everything she wants?
Takes more than money to do that.
You know I love you, coz.
Just think
you should look at the reality here.
Seriously, primo,
how are you gonna afford
a ring for a girl like that, huh?
- Open the door!
- Hey, okay, okay!
Oye, coño, now!
Hey, this fine?
Actually, I'm gonna need
a little bit more this time.
Okay, okay.
Here you go.
- I'm sorry.
- Okay.
- Anyone asking questions?
- Not loud enough to hear.
God,
I can't remember the last time
I was this much of a nervous wreck.
School board, second term, 1992?
Secluded, no real access roads,
perfect for what you're looking for.
Only one problem.
- What's that?
- It's over $2 million.
Well, didn't my poor brother, Terrence,
leave something for me in his will?
You'd have to ask
your accountants, ma'am.
Tell them to use that money.
I'm paying for his mistake.
He can pay for the damn house.
And I've been clean for 18 months now.
I'll tell you, I've never been happier.
That actually might be the wrong word.
I'll be honest,
there were times I was using,
I felt pretty damn happy.
But what I feel is different now. I feel...
I feel joy.
So here I am. I know that
all I can do every day
is the next right thing.
And I think for me right now,
that means going back to work.
I...
I don't know, maybe counseling.
I want to help people
get from where I've been to where I am.
Hey, Sara.
You used to be a doctor, right?
- I still am, in theory. Why?
- Well, I was just thinking,
I might know of a job opening
where I work.
Really? Where's that?
- You ever heard of Fox River?
- The prison?
Yeah. I know it sounds like a strange idea.
Maybe...
Maybe you and I could...
Maybe we could talk about it over dinner.
I got a gift card to the Red Lobster
over off the interstate.
Oh, my God.
Thank you. Really.
I...
Tonight's kind of my night
to work on my resume.
Yeah.
- Of course.
- Sorry, I...
But thank you, really, for the referral.
Fox River.
Yeah.
You know,
math was never my best subject, either.
But I got through it
by learning some new tricks.
- You want to learn some tricks, Gracey?
- Like what?
Like your nine-times tables.
Ready? Nine times one is...
Nine.
- Nine times two is...
- Eighteen.
Nine times three is...
Twenty-seven!
Exactly. You got it. Now keep on going.
Mommy, Mommy,
did you see what Teddy taught me?
Yes. That's great, honey.
Go show your brother.
- Zack, look. Nine times one...
- Thank you.
Nine?
- Nine times two?
- Eighteen.
Nine times three?
Nine times four?
MAN. ;  Welcome back to
America's Most Wanted.
Right, right, left, left, right, right.
Right, right, left, left.
Left.
Left, left, right, left right, boiler room,
left, left, left, right.
Left, left...
- There you go.
- Hey. Thank you.
Let me get your change.
Do you want your change?
Keep it.
And this is his.
Love it. That's different.
- Hey.
- Daddy!
- Hey, sweetheart.
- Come here.
- Hey, there.
Hey.
You know I got...
I got to tell you something,
and it's gonna be really hard to hear.
Okay.
What?
Well, the thing is,
I'm being shipped back off.
- What?
- Yeah.
My unit just got called back
for another tour, baby.
I can't believe it.
Deployment orders just came down.
You know, with the Italians
pulling out and everything.
Tell them no, Daddy.
- Yo, B.
- Come here.
Can you give me a hand
with something out back?
Okay.
That's my sister you lied to in there.
Which is why I know you're going to
take care of them when I'm gone.
This is crazy.
Maybe. But so is the way
I got kicked out of the Army.
So is the way
I got busted for driving that truck.
And so is the way
I feel about that woman up in there.
She married a military man
who knows
how to take care of his business.
Now if I look like one of these thugs, now,
what do think she's going to do? Huh?
How long do you think
she's going to wait for me
while I'm inside?
I don't know, man.
You owe me this, man.
Don't you ever let her know where I am.
Do you feel me?
Usually, I do this the other way.
- Why do you want to...
- I want what I want.
You show this to anyone else,
I am calling the whole thing off.
My therapist said...
She said that I'm holding too much in
and that I need to confront you
to let you know how betrayed I feel.
I let you into my life,
my home,
my God, I let you near my children!
- I never touched them.
- You should have told me what you were.
You think that you're the only one
who feels betrayed?
I loved you, Susan.
Real love.
For the first time in my life.
And then to have you do me like that,
to just throw me out to the dogs,
just toss me out the back door...
- You're a murderer, Teddy!
- That's enough!
I have sinned in the past,
but when I met you,
that person, the one that did
all those terrible things, he died.
And I was reborn.
By the grace of your love, I was a...
A new man. A better man.
No.
That doesn't just erase the man
who killed six students in Alabama.
I guess that's where you're right.
Because when you sent me here
to this place, with these people,
it brought that old dirty bastard
right back home.
In fact, there was a candle
in the window
just waiting for me
to walk up them front steps.
You know, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna get out of here someday.
And when I do,
don't think I won't remember
what your front steps look like, Susan.
It's almost over.
Burrows will be dead soon
and then things will start
getting back to normal.
I know that you've been through a lot,
but I promise you
the worst is now behind us.
My dear sister,
you have no idea what I've been through.
Good night, Terrence.