Previously on Prison Break:
Hey, John, you know,
actually about Jesus,
say hi to him for me, will you?
It's him.
- Did you see him?
- Who?
- The guy in the viewing room.
- No.
It was Dad.
- Where's your girl?
- She'll be at my place in about an hour.
Pretty soon, we're gonna call in our favor.
Have at it.
Boss!
The Department of Corrections
is allowing you a one-hour visit
with your son.
I'll make the travel arrangements,
but I don't want any problems.
You know,
I used to have a Great Dane, big and loyal.
But when she was 12, she got cancer,
so we had to put her down.
And you'd think it would be this
big, dramatic event, but,
it was very peaceful.
One minute she was breathing,
the next she wasn't.
Hey!
Everything okay? Need me to call 911?
No, no, I got it.
That engine's smoking pretty bad,
looks like it could go up any second.
We'll be okay, actually.
- You think?
- Yeah.
- All right, if you say so.
- Fine. I think it's going to be fine.
Fernando Sucre
released from Ad Seg.
Cuz!
You're out.
It's good to see you, buddy.
You all can sign each other's
yearbooks later. Where are we at?
The map is complete. I got what I needed.
- Then we're ready.
- Almost.
I know which pipes we need to take
beneath Psych Ward now.
Which means our way
to the Infirmary is clear.
With our new route, we're gonna come
up on the far end of that building.
Which means we gotta walk down
30 feet of hallway to get to
the doctor's office, our exit point.
Which means there's only one piece left
to this whole thing.
The key to that room.
It's not that easy.
Only the medical staff have those keys.
How're you fixing
on getting it then, pretty?
Carefully.
No more surprises this time, right?
Right.
Jesus, Mary, and Joseph.
- Hello, John.
- Michael.
How are you?
Any day above ground is a blessing.
Thanks be to God.
Do you mind? Please.
Thank you.
Lot of rumors going around.
Yeah.
I'm glad you're back.
I'm surprised you're still here.
I thought you'd be gone by now.
Well, we had a few setbacks.
Still planning on it?
That depends.
How does the idea of escaping
sit with the new you?
Oh, the old sinner
who was confined to these walls,
he's dead.
The new soul deserves to be free.
Well, the old sinner was gonna have
a jet ready for us.
Is the new soul gonna be able
to pull that off?
Noah had his Ark, did he not?
Let's pray.
I'm gonna need a blade.
Pronto.
- Hit and run?
- Yes, sir.
- And Burrows is gone?
- That's right.
- The officers?
- Two are dead, one is in critical.
Do you realize what the media's gonna
say when they get ahold of this?
We'll get him back, sir.
40 years in corrections, and this is
how they're gonna remember me.
This is Kane County.
Sheriff Ballard's a good friend of mine.
- He hasn't said a word to anyone yet.
- Yeah, well...
Give us four, five hours, we'll find him.
If I don't report this
to the D.O.C. Right now...
They don't have to know.
You've always been
a by-the-book guy, boss,
but this time,
the book's gonna get us all fired.
Find him.
The records of every phone call
made to and from every contact
in Quinn's cell phone.
Well, we have our haystack.
Any idea what the needle might look like?
There must be thousands of calls here.
But to who? To where?
You know, it's gonna take us forever
to go through all of these.
And what if these have nothing to do
with Lincoln and Steadman, huh?
What if we're just burning time?
We're just that
much closer to the execution.
What's going on with you, Nick?
I mean, it's almost like you want to quit.
I don't want to quit.
Then let's get to it.
Dr. Tancredi will be right in.
- Morning.
How're you feeling today?
- Better.
- Good.
We got checkpoints up at 171 by Lemont,
at Sage Bridge and at the river going
towards Romeoville.
According to our witness over there,
this new perp was driving an '06 Mustang,
black, dark blue, maybe.
We're not gonna be able
to sit on this thing very long, Brad.
This is me, Nate. I need this.
All right. You go back to Fox River.
I'll be in constant contact.
You mind if I...
How're you doing, Mr...
- Roy Hawkings.
- Hi.
Where are you going?
I'd like to get going if I could.
I'm late for a meeting in Aurora.
- Where you coming from?
- Chicago.
Kind of an indirect route to get to Aurora.
I'm not from around here.
2006 Mustang, black. No ID on the plates.
If any of you get so much as a whiff
of anything,
I want to know about it immediately.
Makes two of us, pal.
What do you want from me, Michael?
Sara...
I need you to do something for me.
What?
Wait for me.
It won't always be like this.
In this room, in this place.
Until then, I can't.
We can't.
Damn it.
I can't.
And I gotta go.
Doors closing!
Hey, squirt.
Avocado.
How many times I gotta say it?
You address me formal-like.
- Mr. Balls-Johnson.
- That's better.
I think maybe you and I
can work something out.
- Really?
- Check it, I got this homie on the outside
and he can put a hundie into your
commissary account each month.
It was nice of you to think of me like that,
but you only got one thing I need.
I need you to get something for me.
Do your bump and swipe thing.
- Like I did with the watch?
- Exactly.
Yeah, that did me a lot of good.
Guards found out and they stuck me into
a cell with Avocado.
So if you want something glommed,
you need to do something for me.
Kill that son of a bitch.
That's not something I can do.
Screw Honus Wagner.
What was that?
This kid in my neighborhood,
his dad had a baseball card collection.
So I figured, you know, I'd swipe it.
I could get some party cash, you know?
And there was one card in there.
A 1910 Honus Wagner.
Doesn't mean nothing to me, you know.
Hoops is my sport.
This card, it was worth $300,000.
So they slapped me with grand larceny.
That's why I'm here.
That's why I'm sitting on a nickel
getting turned out like a little bitch.
A baseball card.
Dad?
What are you doing here?
As soon as I heard they granted you
a visit with your son,
I knew they'd make a move on you.
I mean what are you doing here?
I've got a car about 20 miles from here.
We'll switch out. After that,
gonna make sure you disappear.
Then this business will just be
between me and them.
Can you move?
What are you talking about?
They're after me, not you.
It's not as simple as that, trust me.
I worked for them.
You worked for them?
You're an alcoholic...
Is that what you remember
or is that what you were told?
Why'd you leave?
I took a position with a group
of multinationals we call The Company.
They call every shot this country takes,
what laws to pass, what judges
to appoint, what wars to fight.
Thing is, if you wanted to rise in the ranks
like I did,
you had to commit to leaving
everything you know behind.
Because then you start to get access
to the real information.
Information people would do
a lot of things to get their hands on,
- like harm your family.
- You expect me to believe that?
Why didn't you reach out to us?
Why didn't you call us?
I regretted it every day,
but I didn't have a choice.
Lincoln, the day I left The Company,
I took all that information with me.
That's why they're doing this to you.
All of it, to stop me.
You have to trust me.
Then you'll have to tell me
what's going on.
I can't do that.
Then I can't help.
Look, I did what you ask. Green card
for credit card, that was the deal.
Then, we'll make a new deal.
- Michael, if somebody find out...
- Believe me,
- I'll be in more trouble than you will.
- I know,
and this is why I won't help you.
Look, Nika, I promise you...
Look, I don't know what's going on.
I don't know why you're in there,
but if there's one thing those guys
that brought me here taught me,
is that if you fight, if you struggle,
you only make things worse.
Stop fighting, Michael.
- Just think about it, okay?
- I'm sorry.
There it is again, the 406 number.
It's on every listing.
406.
Yeah, there's
over 200 businesses, another 100
residences in 17 different countries.
- And they're all calling the same number.
- 406.
Montana.
- Can you check the prefixes?
- This doesn't make sense.
All these people from all over the
world are calling this place
in the middle of nowhere with a
population of 42.
Blackfoot, Montana.
I thought you understood, Terrence.
If you wanna talk, we set up a meeting,
at home, in person.
I saw the latest tracking.
Your polls are headed south.
Maybe the Burrows thing is finally starting
to gain some traction with the swings.
It could hurt.
- Goodbye, Terrence.
- You said it was almost over.
It is.
Are we talking about Lincoln Burrows
or your candidacy?
The only reason that you are still alive
- is because I won't let them kill you.
- Yeah.
I'm pretty clear on that.
But the thing I can't quite figure is,
with the crap storm this thing's become,
why they haven't killed you.
Figure out how you're gonna
get the key to the Infirmary yet?
Not quite.
You working a game on her, or what?
I don't know.
Hey man! Get out of my way!
I've had time to think.
Not that you tried to kill me,
but about how Jesus saved me.
I didn't come here, Theodore,
to inflict any more pain.
Take my hand
so we can put this behind us. Please.
Show me the palm of your other hand.
Don't insult me. After all that you've done,
the least I ask is that you don't insult me.
Does not a warm hand
feel better than a cold shank?
You got a point there, John. Yeah.
Truce?
You got it. Truce.
Son of a bitch.
It's been two and a half hours
and you're telling me that
sheriff has got nothing?
I'm telling you the roads are blocked off.
That Mustang's got to be somewhere
within those 10 square miles.
All right, listen,
you got two hours to find him.
After that, I have got to talk to the press.
Hey, but there's an escaped killer
outside our walls
and there are some things
that are more important than career.
Now you find him!
Hey, Captain.
I don't have time.
He says he really needs to talk.
You have something for me
or do you need something?
'Cause if it's the latter,
you just wasted my time.
That cellie you stuck me with, Avocado...
Do you have something or do you need
something? Last time I'm gonna ask.
I'm asking you
to just, please, get me out of that cell.
Boss, please. Boss!
Let's go.
You need to start relaxing.
It'll hurt a lot less.
- Can we go on your bunk?
- Sure, squirt.
Let me make it
a wee bit more comfortable.
Now we're talking.
- Are you the doctor from the prison?
- Yeah. Can, I...
Do you know a prisoner
named Michael Scofield?
I do.
- You're his wife, right?
- I need to talk to you.
I think Michael has got himself
in some trouble.
And I think he's planning on doing
something dangerous to get out of it.
Thanks.
- So what is it that you...
- Michael has a deep need to help people.
So I've come to understand.
That's actually how we met.
There were these men
that brought me here.
Told me I'd have good job,
but that was just a lie.
They were going to sell me.
And until they did, I...
Michael paid them off for my freedom.
And not to keep me for himself,
like I've heard from other girls,
but to give me an opportunity.
He's a good man.
Yes, he is.
Nika, I wanna do
whatever I can to help Michael.
To do that, I need you to tell me
what it is you think he's mixed up in.
- I think this is a mistake.
- No, no, it's not at all.
- Lf you can just tell me what it is...
- Please, just keep an eye on him.
God, I'm sorry. Thanks.
Listen, could I just have a contact number
for you in case I see something wrong.
I don't think that's a good idea.
Please don't tell him that we met.
I... I...
Something I don't get.
How could killing me stop you?
'Cause I'm the one who leaked
the information about Ecofield.
They could've covered up the scandal
a thousand different ways,
but they chose to fake
Terrence Steadman's death.
And they chose you
'cause they knew it would flush me out.
They knew that any man with a son
on death row who was innocent
would have to come forward.
But you didn't.
We had a cause, Linc.
We have a cause.
Their wars can be averted
and millions of lives can be saved.
So you were willing to sacrifice one.
Yeah.
At least I thought.
But I couldn't watch you die.
You know what you've done?
The mother of my child is dead.
- I know.
- Do you?
Then I'm guessing you know
Michael's in Fox River
- and LJ's rotting in some jail.
- I know all of it.
- Lf you think for a second...
- You don't have a choice right now.
This is all on you. All of it.
Yeah, I know. That's why I'm here.
'Cause there's still a chance
we can make it right.
That man in there
is our transportation out of here,
which means that, you go after him,
and that messes with my chances
of me seeing my family.
So I ain't gonna let that happen.
So why don't you just hand me
that shank you're holding, huh?
Good.
- Hey, Sara.
- Hey, Rick.
You all right?
Yeah. I can't find my keys.
Would you let me in?
Oh, sure.
- I'm surprised to see you here.
- That makes both of us.
Look.
You were right and I'm sorry.
I should never have gotten you
involved in this.
- Oh, it's okay.
- No, it's not.
If anyone knew what I asked...
I'm not even sure why I did it.
Thank you.
Now we're even.
- You didn't owe me anything.
- Yes, I did.
I owed you everything,
but that's over now.
Goodbye.
The lady doctor, she cares for you.
Bellick. It's the sheriff.
I think he's got something.
Go, for Bellick.
We just got a call from Steve
Schimek up at the junkyard.
- Our Mustang is on the premises.
- He seen Burrows?
Yep, I got a couple of units
five, 10 minutes away, tops.
Good, I'm right behind you.
Here. You ready to travel?
Place is gonna be crawling with cops.
You know that, right?
There's an unimproved road
down by the river.
There's a chance
they haven't blocked it off yet.
We got trouble.
Come on. Through here.
Come on.
Hey!
Get out of here.
Go.
Turn around.
Bellick!
Bellick, don't shoot! Don't shoot!
- All right on your knees!
- Right there! Right there!
On your knees! Hands up! Let's see them!
Take him down!
Get down! Get down!
You thought you'd go
for a little stroll, did you?
Did you hear about Avocado?
Got his salchicha sliced.
- How?
- Tweener.
But Avocado's saying
it got caught on the frame
while he was hopping
down off his bunk, yeah.
Why did he lie?
He doesn't want Tweener to go to
the SHU 'cause he can't get him in there.
All I have to say is, as soon as
Avocado gets out of the infirmary,
Tweener is a dead man.
How's that key coming?
What about your car?
You know, sometimes...
I just checked.
Your apartment?
No, 'cause I had them this morning.
Well, then, they gotta be here.
Just retrace your steps.
When did you first notice they were gone?
When I came back from lunch...
Hey, Kev, I need to take a look
at that visitation log.
Thanks.
Michael?
I need to know where he is.
- Who?
- Fibonacci.
You see, my conversion requires
that I not only seek forgiveness,
but provide forgiveness,
even to my greatest transgressors.
Don't look at me like that,
like I'm the same old man I used to be.
I'm not.
Trust me,
I need to reach out to
Fibonacci, so we can heal.
That's a good story, but the answer is no.
I understand.
I'll be patient.
- Hello.
- Hey, you're officially now on standby.
And you'll have her there.
Do you understand?
- Yeah. I'll do my best.
- Hey, I said, do you understand?
- Yeah. Loud and clear.
- Good.
Goose Park airstrip.
You can find it on a map. As soon as I call,
you have that bitch there
ready and waiting.
Hey.
You still want me to swipe the thing
you were asking about?
'Cause I'm having
a going-out-of-business sale.
Why don't you get yourself to Ad Seg?
For that to happen, I'd have to admit
what I did to Avocado.
That'd get me what, 20 years?
I'm dead no matter what.
There may be another way out of here.
Yeah, in a body bag.
I need to know if I can trust you.
I'm as straight up as they come,
you know?
No, I mean really trust you.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- How are you?
- I'm fine. You?
Fine.
Can I have your hand, please?
- Here they are.
- Here what are?
Your keys,
they were right over there by your inbox.
Well, you got a maintenance guy
waiting outside here,
says you wanted him to change the locks.
Want me to call him off?
No, send him in.
Is it okay if I...
Yeah. We're about done here.
Is there something wrong?
No.
Unless you want to talk about
what happened this morning.
I think I have a pretty good idea.
We're done here.
I want him under 24-hour surveillance.
- He doesn't sneeze without my knowing it.
- What the hell for? What did I do?
Someone tried to kill me.
Finding you in a junkyard eight miles
from here makes me think different.
Who was your accomplice?
- What accomplice?
- 24-hour surveillance.
Boss.
I heard Avocado
cut his hose on your bunk.
Must have been some serious gymnastics
going on.
I got something for you this time, Boss,
but I want guaranteed protection
from Avocado,
- and I want time cut off my bid.
- Anything else?
Couple of big-canned whores
available to you 24/7?
Believe me, what I got is worth it.
So, are you gonna step up or what?
This is your last chance, Tweener.
You blow smoke again, they'll be
scraping you off the heel of my boot.
Scofield and his whole PI crew,
they're escaping.