Previously on "Prison Break":
I find it incumbent that you
see the inside of a prison cell.
- Why do you want to see Burrows?
- Because he's my brother.
So you get yourself
tossed into Fox River with him?
To what? Save him?
And whoever it was that set me up wants me
in the ground as quickly as possible.
The closer it gets, the more I'm worried that
the bottom will fall out of this whole thing.
That son of a bitch fingered Abruzzi.
- Someone found Fibonacci.
- Who was this someone?
- Why'd you hire him?
- Keep your friends close,
and your enemies closer.
- They come at me, I'm coming after you.
- I doubt it.
I'm getting you out of here.
- It's impossible.
- Not if you designed the place it isn't.
- You've seen the blueprints.
- Better than that.
I've got 'em on me.
You're anticipating every one of my moves
three moves in advance.
You're a hell of a strategist, fish.
You ever think about Boston?
Think you'll ever see it again?
I'm a 60-year-old man with 60 years left
on my ticket. What do you think?
- I'm thinking about going.
- Well, there's going and there's going.
Which one do you mean?
The one you think I mean.
Three days inside and he's already
thinking about turning rabbit.
It'll pass. It always does. Got bigger things
to worry about at the moment.
I've been in here long enough
to know it when I see it.
The calm before the storm.
Whites and blacks are going at each other
real soon here.
Everybody chooses sides
and a lot of guys bleed.
There a reason?
Same reason you don't put
cats and dogs in the same cage.
They don't get along.
- Hm.
- What?
- Toilet won't flush.
- So?
- Means only one thing, fish.
- Shakedown!
You can't flush your contraband.
- We got nothing to worry about.
- Says who?
Under the table, conjo.
- What the hell is this?
- It's insurance, white boy. Now dump it.
Open it.
So, tooling up for the race riot, are we?
- Which side are you on, anyhow, fish?
- That would be neither, boss.
Maybe you're gonna go extracurricular
with it, then. Stick a CO, maybe.
- Is there a problem here, deputy?
- Got a shank in here.
Is this yours?
You're not a good liar.
Come on, Sucre. You're going to the SHU.
- Move along.
- I'm not done shaking this cell down yet.
I said move along.
In the old man's back pocket, are you?
Well, I got news for you, fish.
He may run this place during the day,
but I run it during the night.
What the hell
were you thinking, Michael?
- How are we doing it?
- The infirmary.
Infirmary.
It's the weakest link in the security chain.
If I get that PUGNAc,
I'll get all the access I need.
- What the hell's a PUGNAc?
- It lowers my insulin levels.
As long as the good doctor
thinks I'm diabetic,
- I'll have time there to do what I need to do.
- Which is?
A little work. A little prep for your arrival.
- That's the idea, anyway.
- The idea?
There's a little hitch in getting the PUGNAc.
They don't exactly stock it at the commissary.
- This thing's riding on a bunch of pills?
- Someone's working on it as we speak.
- Now's not the time to trust a black inmate.
- Our relationship transcends race.
Nothing transcends race in here.
Good behaviour,
you're outta here in three years.
- Gonna be a whole lot sooner then that.
- It can't be done.
No one's ever broken out of Fox River.
Every step's already been mapped out.
Every contingency.
You may have the blueprints to this place but
there's one thing those plans can't show you.
Guys like Abruzzi. You so much as look at
these guys the wrong way, they'll cut you up.
As far as these guys are concerned, I'm just
a con doing his time, staying out of trouble.
- You don't gotta look for trouble. It finds you.
- And when it does, we'll be long gone.
This is madness. You can't get outta your cell.
- Not true.
- What, you got a key?
Something like that.
Wrong piece of real estate,
fish. Belongs to T-Bag.
Who?
Speak with respect, fish. Man kidnapped
half a dozen boys and girls down in 'Bama.
Raped and killed 'em.
Wasn't always in that order either.
- Does T-Bag have a real name?
- That is my real name.
No, no, no. Please, sit.
So, you're the new one I've been hearing
all the rave reviews about.
Scofield.
One thing's for sure.
You're just as pretty as advertised.
Prettier, even.
- Rugheads got you scared, do they?
- Sorry?
I assume that's why you're over here. A few
days on the inside, any white man realises
the correctional system's got a lean
toward the African-American persuasion.
- I hadn't noticed.
- They got the numbers, all right.
We got one thing they don't. Surprise.
We gonna take the ball game
to them real soon.
It's gonna be nasty for a first-timer like you.
We'll protect you. I'll protect you.
All you gotta do is...
take this pocket right here
and your life'll be all peaches and cream.
I walk, you walk with me.
I'll keep you real close
so no one up in here can hurt you.
Looks to me you already got a girlfriend.
I got a whole 'nother pocket over here.
I'll pass.
I don't protect you, them rugheads
are gonna gobble you up like a plate of peas.
- I said no.
- Then you'd best move, then.
Now.
You come around these bleachers again, it's
gonna be more than words we're exchanging.
Know what I'm saying?
Are you the Tim Giles
that represented Lincoln Burrows?
- If you're a reporter...
- I'm not a reporter. I know the defendant.
- Oh. You family?
- Not exactly.
We were in a relationship a few years back.
Ma'am, I... I don't know what to tell you.
The man was guilty.
- The prosecution's case was a slam dunk.
- The victim was the vice president's brother.
If you're suggesting the government
rammed this through, I take offence.
- I fought for that guy.
- That's not what I meant.
The evidence was there.
Lincoln worked for Steadman's company.
He gets into a public altercation with the guy,
so he gets fired. Steadman's shot dead.
The weapon's found in Lincoln's house,
the blood on his clothes.
Trust me. There are cases you lose sleep over
but this isn't one of 'em.
What about Crab Simmons?
Lincoln said he could exonerate him.
The man's a five-time felon, all right?
He had no credibility.
- So you wouldn't mind if I paid him a visit?
- Be my guest.
But I don't think it'll do you any good.
Strange feeling. Don't know how to explain it.
You know, um, usually my whole life
it's always been crazy and noisy.
Maddening, you know, in my head.
But now it's quiet.
It's perfect.
I'm glad you came back.
I thought about you the whole time.
You know, I made a lot of mistakes in my life.
I know that.
- I'm gonna make it right.
- I know you will.
- What are you doing?
- I want to remember this.
- No.
- Oh, come on. Come on, Vi, please. Just one.
OK.
- Easy.
- How are we doing on the PUGNAc?
- Hey, I'm working on it.
- Well, work faster. I need that stuff tonight.
What's up there in that infirmary
that you need so bad?
You get me that PUGNAc
and maybe I'll tell you.
Uh-uh-uh.
Thought we had an understanding.
This here's for the family.
You made it pretty clear you ain't blood.
How about you hand that over?
Nice-Iookin' piece of steel. Bit of work.
You could do some serious damage with it.
Question is,
who is it you was planning on damaging?
I seen you with the Negroes, you know.
Well, maybe you're one of them
milk chickens, all confused, like.
White on the outside,
black as tar on the inside.
Maybe we oughta take a look at them insides
and find out.
Girl Scouts, is there a problem over there?
I think we'll just hang onto this
if that's OK with you.
Hey! I'm not gonna ask you again.
Let's break up the party, ladies.
You heard the man, little doggie.
Get along.
What's it take to shake down another inmate?
Get something he's taken from you?
- It would take Fibonacci.
- Well, I'll give you Fibonacci.
I promise you that.
- When the time is right.
- The time is right now.
No, when you and I are both standing
outside those walls.
You're on life without parole.
You'll never stand outside those walls.
Not unless you knew someone,
someone who knew a way out.
- What do you say, John?
- I say I've heard nothing but blabber.
Philly Falzone.
It's an honour. What are you doing here?
Well, I, uh, just thought we'd,
you know, fraternise.
- He looks like it, doesn't he?
- Looks what?
Like everybody's been saying.
You got no sack. You've been neutered.
You shouldn't talk to me like that.
- You used to pick up my laundry.
- Not any more.
Word is someone knows where Fibonacci is
and you're not doing anything about it.
- I'm working on it.
- Not fast enough.
Apparently Fibonacci's
coming up for air again.
Next month, a congressional hearing.
Now, if he testifies at that hearing
a lot of people are going down, including me.
Now, I've known you a long time.
Our wives are friends.
Our kids go to the same Catholic school.
It would be a shame if anything happened to
your kids. I know my kids would miss them.
- You don't need to do this.
- I do.
I'll get this guy. We'll get Fibonacci.
- For everyone's sake, I hope you're right.
- I am.
Be well, John.
Thank you.
Yo, badge, I gotta use the phone.
- Sure. You want a pizza and a pedicure too?
- I gotta call my girl. She's expecting my call.
- Put a sock in it. You got nothing coming.
- No, no, no, man! No, man!
Hey, pull up the manifest.
Is there an Allen Schweitzer in gen pop?
- No.
- How about the SHU?
No. Why you asking?
Curious, that's all.
You hear the trumpets, fish?
I know you can. That's Judgment Day.
It's coming. Real soon.
Yo, Curly! Come on, May Tag.
What you doing in my cell?
I want in.
I'm not sure I heard that.
Did you say you're in?
- That's right.
- In for an inch, in for a mile.
You want me to fight, I'll fight.
The bolt from the bleachers was for that.
Well, you wanna fight,
you're gonna get your chance. Next count.
- Tonight?
- Problem with that?
We goin' straight at 'em. You better catch a
square, fish. We're undermanned in a big way.
- All I need's a weapon.
- You want a weapon, bitch?
- There you go.
- All prisoners, return to your cells.
You have to prove yourself
before we trust you with the heavy artillery.
Gates closing!
- I'm sorry for being so short with you before.
- No problem.
Closer it gets to an execution,
the harder it becomes.
That's why I wanted to give you this.
It's the surveillance tape
of the garage that night.
It was a closed trial
so no one outside the courtroom saw it.
- It could help you out.
- With what?
Closure.
Allen Schweitzer.
That name mean anything to you?
- Should it?
- I don't know. You tell me.
- Never heard of the guy.
- Are you sure?
Positive.
Ah, what's up, snowflake?
Do you think I'm a fool?
- What are you talking about?
- I see you up there with the Hitler Youth.
I got a good mind
to slash you open right now.
It's not what you think.
They've got something I need.
Now, see, that's funny,
because I got something you need too.
You want your PUGNAc, fish? Huh?
I hate 'em, baby. So will you.
Listen, white boy. Your luckjust ran out.
You chose the wrong side.
Man, it's great to see your face.
I think it's time you quit the charade,
don't you?
- What?
- It's starting to ruin people's lives.
Michael's in here
cos he thinks you're innocent.
- What's he told you?
- He hasn't told me anything, but I know.
I know what he's planning.
Call him off. If you love him, call him off.
- I saw the tape.
- That's not how it went down.
- I know what I saw.
- I know what I saw. I was there, remember?
I got high that night. I had to.
It was the only way I could go through with it.
I never pulled the trigger.
The guy was already dead.
- I know. You told me a thou...
- Listen! I was set up.
I went there to clear a debt. Crab Simmons
was on my ass for the 90 grand I owed him.
Told me the mark was some drug dealer
and if I took it we'd be clean.
I never pulled the trigger. Somebody wanted
me in the same garage as Steadman.
Why would somebody wanna set you up?
It wasn't about me. It was about him.
- Steadman?
- Yes.
The guy was a saint. All the charity work, the
environmental progress his company made.
About the only person in this entire country
who had motive to kill him was you.
You came all the way down here
to tell me how guilty I am?
I don't know why I came here.
You have your life now. I know that.
But if what we had before meant anything
to you, you'd find out the truth.
Maybe all this is the truth.
Maybe they got it right.
- Badge! Badge, open up! Badge!
- You talking again?
It's my girl's birthday. Please. I'll give you
$1 million if you let me use the phone.
I've seen your kick. You got something
like 40 cents to your name.
Please! No! No! No!
All right, Maricruz.
What are you doing? Come on.
- It's OK, Hector. You go ahead.
- What are you talking about?
- I think I'm just gonna take a cab.
- What do you mean? You just got here.
He didn't call you, did he?
Look. I love Fernando to death,
but the guy's a deadbeat.
You gotta move on with your life.
- Mr Giles, we'd like a word with you.
- I really don't...
I'm afraid we're going to have to insist.
It's come to our attention that you made
a FOIL request on the Burrows case.
- Yeah. So?
- You made a dupe off the surveillance tape.
That's right.
- Mind us asking why?
- It was for one of Burrows' old girlfriends.
She thought the guy was innocent.
I figured it'd help her with closure.
She's in possession of the tape now?
Don't pull that card with me.
It's the Freedom of Information Act.
- She's entitled to that tape as much as you.
- No, no, no. By all means. By all means.
- May I go now?
- Just one more thing.
This old girlfriend of his.
What's her name?
- Excuse me. Is this the Simmons residence?
- I'm Ms Simmons.
I'm sorry. Um, I'm Veronica Donovan.
I'm looking for Crab Simmons.
- Are you related?
- He's my son.
- Is he around?
- No.
- Could you tell me where I could find him?
- Lady, go away. I can't help you.
Look, I'm sorry.
It's just... a man's life is at stake,
and maybe your son could help him.
Crab can't help nobody, lady.
He's dead.
I'm sorry.
Heads up! Seven up, cons.
Stand at your gates.
About to jump off, fish.
Ballard, get back on your number.
- Need backup right away.
- I said get back on your number.
Get back immediately!
Help me.
Inmates, back down!
Scofield!
Inmates, back in your cells!
Get back immediately!
You're a dead man, Scofield.
Do you hear me?
You're a dead man!
I really don't know
what to say to you gentlemen.
I try to give you the benefit of the doubt.
I try to treat you with respect.
You can't even respect yourselves.
So, there's gonna be a 48-hour lockdown.
No mess, no showers, no visitation.
And I strongly suggest
that you all learn to get along,
otherwise the next time it's gonna be a week
and the time after that, a month.
Think about it.
- Got a Leticia Barris on the line.
- I don't know who that is.
She says she used to date Crab Simmons.
- Thank you for calling.
- You wanna hear what I have to say?
- We meet in public where they can't get to us.
- Wait. Where who can't get to us?
You wanna hear what I have to say?
Cos if you don't, I'm gonna hang up now.
No, no, no, no.
You just name the time and the place.
- Over here.
- Hey, Leticia, thanks for coming.
We don't know each other. We'll stay out
here in the open where they can't get to us,
where they can't do what they do.
They gonna kill your boy
like they killed mine.
Coroner said smack killed your boyfriend.
It was an overdose.
- No overdose.
- What do you mean?
Crab didn't use. He had a bad heart.
If he touched the stuff, it'd kill him.
Don't you think it's just a bit of a coincidence
he OD'd a week after your boyfriend's crime?
They killed him cos he knew things,
things they didn't wanna get out.
- Like what?
- Like who was really behind that hit.
It wasn't Crab and it wasn't Lincoln. Neither
of them knew what they were getting into.
They were just pawns in a big game.
They're here.
- Who's here, Leticia?
- Don't try to follow me. I won't testify.
- Just slow down and talk to me.
- I'd get as far away from here as you can, girl,
cos there ain't nobody they can't get to.
Leticia!
- Hello?
- We have a small complication.
There's a lawyer poking around.
Veronica Donovan.
Yes.
You can handle a girl who graduated
in the middle of her Baylor Law School class.
At least, I'd like to think so, given the stakes
of what we're dealing with here.
Anyone that's a threat to what we're doing
is expendable.
- Anyone.
- Understood.
Do what you need to
do to make this go away.
Are you there, pretty?
I know you're there.
Just want you to know I'm coming for you.
You got nowhere to run.
You're trapped in that little hole of yours,
trapped like a pig I'm gonna slaughter.
- Who's my one o'clock?
- Michael Scofield.
- I was wrong about you.
- Here's your PUGNAc.
- A little bit late.
- Better late than never, right?
- Scofield! Infirmary.
- We'll see about that.
Mm-hm.
I'm gonna find out, you know,
what it is you're doing up there.
- How long does this take?
- They've come a long way with glucose kits.
This'll take us about ten seconds.
Slide the strip into the meter
and we're ready to go.
I'm sure you know this, but average glucose
for the non-diabetic is about 100mg/dl,
so we see a number like that here
and we know you've been misdiagnosed.
You seem nervous.
- I do?
- You're sweating.
Must be the needles.
Never really got used to 'em.
Somehow with diabetes and that tattoo
I find that hard to believe.
Ah.
Bad news, I'm afraid.
180mg/dl. You're definitely diabetic.
Do you need anything else from me?
- Arm to stick a needle in.
- OK.
I'll see you Wednesday.
- Cute.
- Prisoner.
- There's something strange about him.
- What do you mean?
I gave him the results of his blood test and
there was this look on his face. It was, um...
relief.
It's all right. I got it.
I'm headed over to A-wing anyhow.
- You're positively beaming, boss.
- Got up on the right side of the bed, I guess.
Hold up. Sugar.
Now, don't you move, fishy.
- What are you doing?
- You're coming with us, fish.
This little polka
you and I have been doing for a while,
as of this moment,
it's over.
Fibonacci.
I wanna know how you got to him
and where he is, right now.
Not gonna happen, John.
Now, I'm gonna count to three.
- One...
- I give you that information, I'm a dead man.
You know it and I know it.
Two...
I'll tell you the moment
we're outside those walls.
You tell me now.
- Not gonna happen, John.
- Hey! I'm gonna give you one last chance.
Three.