Mr. Nygaard?
Oh, you betcha.
Yeah.
She's a beaut.
Got the low-water feature,
but don't skimp on torque.
Am I taking the old one?
Yeah, if that's...
They said on the phone
it'd be no problem.
Oh, sure.
It's no problem.
The T-160? Hmm, yeah.
Geez. I see why
you're trading her in.
She's a real lemon.
Motor mount.
Chinese used plastic screws.
Bet she bucked like a bronco.
You do not know
the half of it.
Stopped making
'em pretty quick.
Recalled, I think.
Surprised to see her,
truth be told.
You'd be better off washing
your clothes
between two rocks.
You know what I mean?
They got Chaz up
at Faribault till
the trial.
Gordo's at Red Wing.
Which is...
Well, you know...
At least they're close.
His lawyer thinks
we can plea it
down to probation.
Time served.
For murder?
No, Gordo...
On the gun charge.
Oh, yeah.
Chaz? Well, good riddance.
Don't care what that man gets.
No, sir,
not after what he did.
Killing my wife,
you mean?
Oh, well, yeah.
Yeah, of course, that.
But also...
Well, I mean,
look at me.
I was Miss Hubbard County,
for Pete's sake.
You don't cheat on
Miss Hubbard County.
I just don't
believe it,
you know.
I mean,
just three weeks ago,
we were sitting
around the table
eating ham.
And now Gordo's having
his night terrors again.
Plus,
we have to sell everything
to pay the legal bills.
Did you know...
Chaz bought
a time share in a boat?
I didn't even know
that was a thing.
Yeah, it's a thing.
So if there's anything
from the house you want...
You know, like
I was thinking maybe
Chaz's hunting gear?
I boxed it up for you.
Not sure
it's anything you want.
Oh, sure.
That'd be fine,
thank you.
Well...
listen, if there's
anything I can do.
Oh, no...
Lester,
you are so sweet.
I am the one who
should be saying that
after what he did
to you, my husband.
Oh, what'd you get?
New washer.
The old one...
Well, I had to get rid of
everything from the basement.
On account of all the...
You deserve it, Lester.
All good things.
You deserve.
Back to it then?
Looks like. Doc
cleared me for duty, so...
More flowers came
for you from Duluth.
A smarter man
would think you
were being wooed.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Put 'em up where we
can see 'em at least.
So, you got a strategy
on this Lester thing?
Well, I'm just gonna walk in
and say, "Bill..."
If you think it's best...
Direct approach.
Your point being?
Got no point.
Okay. Bye, Dad.
Chief, are you busy?
What's that?
Said, "Are you busy?"
Got a request for
your attendance.
Can it wait?
I just ate an omelet...
Waiting for it to digest.
Oh, yeah?
What kind?
It was mushrooms
and cheese.
Sally make it?
Yeah.
She wrapped it
in tin foil to
keep it warm.
Molly needs you
is the thing.
Asked me to see
if you'd come down
to the staff room.
She's back already?
Yeah.
Hmm.
Thought I had another day.
All right.
Let's go see what
we're gonna do today.
There she is,
the gunfighter.
Hey, Chief.
Nice collage, you take up
basket weaving too
in your downtime?
Yeah, it's just
some loose ends
I wanted to...
Molly, before you...
I want you to know...
I'm not too proud
to say I was wrong
on the Lester case.
I had the wrong idea.
I thought it was
a drifter thing.
Which was the wrong
way to go, clearly.
But, you know,
some good police work,
and we caught the guy, so...
That's the problem,
actually, um...
Is that you're still...
Still what?
Wrong.
I mean, no disrespect.
It's just...
It doesn't make any sense.
I mean, the brother?
With all
the things
we know are true.
And I've been lying in bed
just thinking about this.
For example,
okay, if it was
the brother,
then how do we explain
the phone call from
Lester's to the motel...
Molly! Darn it! Now just...
You can't keep going over...
It's time.
You gotta let it go.
We did our job.
The brother Nygaard
killed the wife.
And he cornered
and shot the Chief.
And Lester was
covering for him
on account of
the brother thing.
Which explains...
We had drinks
to celebrate.
I had a greyhound.
And Knutson had...
What was it with the cherry?
Rob Roy.
Rob Roy. Yeah.
You had a few of them
if I'm not... Mistaken.
What about the Hess case?
What about it?
Still open. Yeah?
Yeah. No. See...
We're checking to see
if the hooker had
a boyfriend,
jealous type...
You know, didn't
like her getting tooled
by every Tom, Dick and Jane.
But otherwise...
Who's working that now?
Terry.
Well, that's good.
Yeah.
Except Terry doesn't know
which end of the mop to use
to wash the floor.
He's not the brightest bulb.
I'll give you that.
But he's soldiering through.
Well, good for him.
Except I'm back now.
No.
Chief, please...
Now, Molly...
Deputy, now
I would give it to you.
I would.
Except we both
know in two days,
I'd be back in this room
with you pointing at
names on that whiteboard,
and me chewing my tie.
Chief, for Pete's sake,
I've got evidence
that puts
Lester Nygaard
in a room
with a known killer
on the day of
the Hess murder,
and then the next night,
Lester called the guy.
He called him at the motel...
Look!
You can't...
That's just how
it is sometimes.
Life.
You go to bed
unsatisfied.
They're calling
the lottery numbers
on the TV
and you get
the first few.
And already
in your mind,
you're buying a jet or
a fjord or whatever.
But it's just
not meant to be.
It's just not
meant to be.
Hey. Look, we're all
real glad to have you back.
Okay? You're a heck
of a police officer.
Tell her about the cake.
Yeah.
The guys are gonna have
a cake for you later.
Try to look surprised.
It's really something.
It's got an assault rifle
on top, made of frosting.
Which I don't know
how they do that.
But...
Heya, Lester.
I like your tie.
Thank you.
I got it online.
Oh, yeah?
Uh-huh.
Hmm.
Jacket, too.
I was a bit nervous
about it at first.
Had to send
the jacket back
once actually.
It was...
Too big in the arms.
Well, I think
you look terrific.
Oh.
And...
I was thinking of making
some chili on Saturday night.
If you maybe
wanted to join me?
Where is he?
You son of a bitch.
I'm gonna bust your balls.
You want me to do it, Ma?
Yeah, Ma, want us to?
Shut up!
I am gonna
bust your balls.
Now, Mrs. Hess,
what can I do for...
Don't you
"Mrs. Hess" me.
I was picking your pubes
out of my teeth 12 hours ago.
And then I get this?
That is...
This is highly irregular.
I'll make some calls.
Liar!
Mrs. Hess.
Liar. You knew
the whole time...
No, Mrs...
Gina, this is...
Listen, I'm gonna
make some calls.
Like I said, I was
speaking to the guy
from Mid Claims
just yesterday.
He didn't mention
a single thing.
I let you come
inside of me.
That's really gross.
Yeah, Ma,
don't talk like that.
We don't need to bring
that into the conversation.
You are gonna
get me my money,
you little shit.
$2 million,
you've got until
the end of the day.
Or show him
what we'll do.
Jesus! All right.
All right.
Sorry, loser.
Me, too.
Ow.
Yeah!
So are we calm?
Are we calm?
Now here's
what's gonna happen.
I'm gonna make some calls.
Like I said.
Because this is
the first that I've...
But if it's true,
if Sam did miss
some payments,
then, well, they're
within their rights to...
I think we might
have a problem here.
That was...
I'm sorry you had
to see that, Linda.
No, I'm... That was...
You're amazing.
He'll be right out.
Follow.
Sir? We...
What Agent Pepper
is trying to say,
the Syndicate spree killing,
yes, technically,
we were there outside...
In our car... While it was...
But you have to...
You have to see
it as a positive
because it leaves us,
myself and Agent Budge,
it leaves us...
Poised.
That's the word we like.
Poised to catch this guy.
Because, sir,
first of all,
we got this photo
from an ATM
across the street.
It captures our...
A single individual
who's clearly
armed and about to...
Now, the photo is
not great, but...
I... We were thinking
definitely white male.
Sir?
Listen. Sir...
This is where you work now.
We are highly effective,
highly trained...
I have a commendation.
A commendation?
That's your...
Okay.
Okay. It's...
We're still good.
We're still alive.
He could have...
It could be worse, right?
Much, much worse.
This right here?
Two weeks... Tops.
Just wants to see
us sweat a little...
Feel the...
I mean, it's only fair.
I can see that.
We did...
I mean,
22 people did get killed,
and we're sitting
in the car like a couple of...
Yeah, we're okay.
We're all right.
I've never heard
of a deaf hit man.
Carolina Murphy
had his tongue
cut out by an Indian
back in the '80s.
He worked a little after that,
but never quite the same.
Buzz Mead.
You know Buzz?
He was born
with just a socket.
He used to take
his glass eye out
at parties and
drop it in his drink.
He was a shit shot though.
Now the other fella,
your partner.
He can hear just fine.
We had a kind of chat
before I cut his throat.
You're unemployed now,
by the way
in case you don't
read the papers.
I'll kill you!
I watched a bear once.
Its leg was in a steel trap.
It chewed through
bloody bone to get free.
That was in Alaska.
It died about an hour later,
face down in a stream.
Well, it was on his
own terms, you know?
You got close...
Closer than anybody else.
I don't know if it was you
or your partner, but look...
If you still feel raw about
things when you heal up,
come see me.
Just me and Bill, right?
Slow night...
And the call comes in.
He don't like when
I tell this story.
Heard you
got some flowers.
Yeah, some people do love
to flap their lips.
More than once
is what I heard.
Well, there's a suitor...
Is all I'm prepared to say.
Vern was so bad
at courtship.
One time he gave me
a bouquet of poison ivy.
Picked it himself.
He's up in Duluth...
My gentleman.
Has a daughter.
What's his name?
They call him Sergio.
He's a pirate,
I think.
Very funny, you.
Well.
Yours is the one
with the icing clip.
And, Ida, your frosting
comes from the barrel.
I think.
Good to have everyone
together again,
don't you think?
It's like one big, happy...
Which is good, is all.
I wanted to thank you...
For catching the guy.
Not me.
I was in bed.
Stop. You were
in the hospital
with a bullet.
No.
Bill may have made the arrest,
but we both know
who did the real work.
He's not convicted yet.
I mean,
not all the evidence...
For me,
there are still...
But, yeah, no, I'm...
Glad it's behind us.
Ugh.
Deputy Solverson.
Yeah, hi. It's Gus...
Grimly.
Oh, yeah, hi.
So, what's happening then?
You know, on patrol.
Oh, sure. Yeah.
I helped a fella
who got his privates
stuck to a mailbox.
Oh.
Didn't like his mail?
Something like that.
There's the hearing tomorrow
on the shooting.
Oh, yeah.
That's...
That's tomorrow.
Well, just tell the truth.
Don't you think?
It was a white out,
and you saw a shadow
and you shot at it.
But leave out the part...
Leave out the part where
the person you shot was me.
I am really sorry
about that.
Yeah. I gathered from
the volume of flowers.
Too much?
No.
No, it's nice.
So...
I saw in the paper
this morning,
the logging festival's
coming up
over in your neck of the...
And Greta, she really
likes going to that.
Yeah, me too.
Yeah? Good.
Good. Well, maybe...
I mean,
maybe we'll see you there.
Yeah, a certainty
if we go together.
Yeah. Yeah, that's...
You're right about that.
And when you're right,
you're right.
On Friday,
there's chainsaw carving,
and... All you can eat.
And on Saturday
they roast a
pig underground.
I've never had it,
but it's supposed
to be good.
Oh, I didn't know that
you could do that.
On Sundays,
they do a pie-eating
contest.
Yeah, yeah. No...
I like to just
go for the food.
Greta likes all
the different contests
they have.
Have you ever
seen the guys,
they go all the way up
to the top of the tree...
They've got like bells
and the spikey shoes...
Dad? Come in, Dad.
Over.
Dad here, come back.
What's the deal
with dinner? Over.
Yeah, just finishing up.
Thought we'd do tacos tonight.
Over.
Okay.
Don't forget the red sauce.
Over and out.
I'm home!
You forgot the food,
didn't you?
Mom home?
Yeah.
That your dad?
Did he remember
the red sauce?
Oh, shoot.
I can go back.
No. It's okay.
I think we got some left
from last time.
Go get changed up,
you, and let's eat.
I'm starving.
Yeah.
Just put 'em on the table.
Okay.
Thanks, Greta.
Dad wants to know
about the game Sunday.
Watch at his place or...
I thought we
could watch it here.
I could make that pasta thing.
Um.
The one with the peas?
Capers.
You liked it last time.
Oh, don't forget we got that
thing at Ida's on Saturday...
The anniversary.
No. I remember.
It was a week
before I met you.
Anniversary of what?
It's just your...
Molly had a friend of hers
that got killed last year.
So we'll go over there
and pay our respects.
It was...
Vern, right?
Yeah.
He was the Chief before Bill.
Hired me.
Ida, the lady with the baby...
Yeah?
Is his wife.
Which, speaking of,
she asked if we
could bring drinks.
Yeah, I still got some
of that Halloween beer
I made.
I seem to remember
you spitting
that on the floor.
Yeah, I'll go
to the store.
Mmm-hmm.
You okay?
Oh, sure.
Just hard to sit that long.
Legs go to sleep.
FBI.
Hi.
Deputy Solverson again,
Bemidji police.
Yes?
I called a couple times
now about
the Fargo
Syndicate massacre
how I might know
the fella responsible
meaning he's
a suspect in a case.
Yeah, I see your
name on the computer.
Looks like those
suspicions were
investigated and dismissed.
Yeah. They sent
a fella down, but I'm not
sure he really...
Do you have any
new information?
No. No, I just...
A lot of people are dead.
So...
I'll put a note
on the file that
you called.
Okay, but...
I wouldn't expect
a call back though.
We're pretty busy these days,
with the Patriot Act and all.
File room.
A room with files.
Say you took
one of 'em out.
Took it where?
Doesn't matter.
Say you took one
of the files out...
Is it still the file room?
Pizza today, right?
In the cafeteria.
Or is it meatloaf?
No, I'm saying that
you and I both agree
that the file room
minus one file
is still the file room.
Now, say you took
another one out.
And then another.
If the file
room minus one file
is still the file room,
and you keep
subtracting one
at a time,
you could end up
with zero files.
I'm saying, logically
or even negative files.
And it would still be the...
How do you have
negative files?
No. I'm just...
Logically, I'm saying.
Except no one's taking files.
They just bring more.
What about a cemetery,
I mean,
remove one body
from a cemetery,
it's still a cemetery.
But a cemetery
with no bodies,
what's that?
Condos.
Okay, and this is...
Well, these
are my officers, so...
Where is everybody?
Coffee run.
Who's this then?
This is Tahir. He's...
Hey.
Hello, I am Tahir.
I'm Molly,
Deputy Solverson.
Yeah. So remember I told you
me and Sally were
taking in a foster?
Yeah, from Africa.
Yeah, except...
I am from Sudan.
You know Lost Boy?
I sure do.
Welcome to America.
I thought there
was a problem though.
Oh, I'll say!
The kid disappeared.
Disappeared how?
Oh, tell her the story.
Oh. Ha.
This is the craziest thing.
All right?
Go on. You tell her.
In my village,
I tend goats.
You know goats?
Uh-huh.
One day,
men came
and kill everyone.
Mothers, fathers,
brothers, sisters.
Geez.
I alone am free.
Three days I walk,
then I meet nice people...
Americans.
These nice people put me
airplane to America.
Land of free.
Home of brave.
Yeah, to us.
He's coming
to live with us.
Go on.
At the airport,
man says,
"Take bag?"
He says, "Get in the car,"
but he doesn't come back.
Guy stole his bag.
Can you believe it?
A refugee.
One day and one night,
I wait at the airport,
but this man,
he does not come back.
I had no money
and no paper.
Nice woman says,
"Tell policeman,"
but I am afraid.
I told her I have
a family waiting...
Nice family...
American family.
But the name is in
the bag and the number.
Nice woman give me coat
and money to take the bus.
So not all bad.
I take the bus
to the city.
But I am very hungry,
four days I no eat.
Then I see a store.
You know...
"July in January"?
Phoenix Farms.
Yes, Phoenix Farms.
Should I tell her this?
So... He shoplifts...
Takes some food.
In fact he does
it every day for,
how long?
Three months.
Meanwhile, we're frantic.
You remember?
All those phone calls?
Me raising my voice?
"How could you lose a kid
from Africa in
freaking Minnesota?"
Every day I steal food,
but... I am ashamed.
I don't want to steal.
I want to work,
but what work can I do?
Then a week ago,
Sally and I are
heading into
the city to the ballet.
You went to the ballet?
Sally likes the ballet,
yeah, so...
Go ahead, finish.
I am looking around the store.
Skittles and
peanut butter cups.
Then this man grabs me,
I think I am arrested.
It's me,
is the point
of the story.
All those weeks
looking for the kid...
Writing letters,
making phone calls.
We even put up flyers.
And then,
I stop by a supermarket
in a city I don't live,
all so Sally can have
Chex Mix at the ballet,
and there's the kid.
What are the odds?
I can't even imagine.
I am so worried...
And thinking I am arrested,
but Mr. Bill
is hugging me
and crying.
Well, you know...
And look where I am at.
Who I'm with.
My... American family.
Sally says it's a miracle.
I don't know. It might be.
But don't
question the universe,
that's my motto.
Sometimes
things just work out.
Yeah,
I like to think
that's true.
We found ya, buddy.
We found ya.
- It causes you
to have hallucinations.
- What?
I'll be glad to
explain it to you.
It's a sort of a nightmare
where your
dreams go pell-mell,
helter-skelter and amok.
Oh, shut up!
Pell-mell!
Hello. Inspector Clancy
speaking. What?
You need something?
No, I'm good.
Go back to sleep.
Stand back, everybody.
I've got you covered,
stand back.
What's the meaning of this?
Police parading
all over the hotel.
Who sent for you?
Why are you here?
This is Mr. William's suite.
Mr. Williams
has been murdered.
Quiet, everybody.
You'll be quiet.
And that goes for all of you.
Yeah, the chief
is right. Noise, bed-ly-ham,
who can think?
Well, you can't. So shut up.
Where's the body?
In there.
Now what did
you do that for?
Isn't a girl
supposed to scream
when she knows she's
gonna see a dead body?
Quiet. Now come on
in here, all of you.
We're doing good.
I'm up.
Sorry.
I was just saying
we're doing good.
Mmm-hmm.
We got everything we need.
Well, I'm going
to sleep.
Yeah, me, too.
Oh, it's Jeff,
the night porter.
I left him here
to watch the body.
What happened?
I was standing around,
scared stiff,
and all of a sudden,
the lights went out.
Then something
hit me on the head,
and then the lights
went out again.
That's all I know
and that's all I'm gonna wait
around to find out.
Stun Meadows,
everybody! Give it up.
How does he do it?
Check your wallets,
ladies and gentlemen.
Make sure he didn't
make those vanish, too.
It's been a big
year for insurance...
A banner year.
Reserve trends are up.
And...
Loss ratios are down
a whopping 17%.
Those are just numbers.
We all know that behind
every insurance policy...
And the reinsurance policy
covering that policy,
there's a salesman.
A man or woman knocking
on doors, making calls,
matching people and businesses
with the right
plan for their needs.
And so without further delay,
I give you...
Insurance Salesman
of the Year 2007...
Lester Nygaard!
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Thank you so much. That...
Oh, geez,
that's a real honor.
Um...
Now...
I knew I should
have memorized this.
It suddenly doesn't look...
Speak from the heart.
Speak from the heart. Okay.
Those of you that know me,
know it's been a tough year
for me personally.
And that I wouldn't
have gotten through it
without the love and support
of my beautiful wife, Linda.
Let's give her a hand.
I love you.
You can go through
your whole life...
Without a care.
And one day,
it all changes.
People die.
They lose their homes.
They go to prison.
It's calamity.
I know it,
'cause I lived it.
And if this year has
taught me anything...
Believe me,
I've seen it all.
It's that
the worst does happen...
And you need to be insured.
Thank you so much.
It's a great honor.
So proud of ya, Lester.
Aw, thanks, hon.
You tired?
Oh, aren't you?
Well...
Um...
No. Actually,
I'm feeling
pretty keyed up.
I might grab
a nightcap at the bar.
You want me to go...
No, no, no.
You go up to bed.
I'll be up shortly.
Just... It's my night.
I'm sorry,
I'm such a downer.
You're a sunny day.
Go on.
I'll be up presently.
Hi.
Hey. Big night, huh?
Salesman of the Year.
Oh.
Drugs?
Insurance.
Ah.
They really give an award
to the guy who
sells the most drugs?
Pharmaceuticals.
That makes more sense.
So what are you drinking?
Something dangerous.
Let's have a look.
Ah, oh, a blood and sand,
what's that?
Scotch and blood orange.
That's the one.
All right.
And then I sit down
and every... Oh, Miss?
Can we have some more
sparkling water? Thanks.
Anyways... So, I say,
"Hi, I'm Dr. Michaelson.
Nice to meet you
and everything."
And I get ready to
give him the novocaine shot...
Stick it in my own finger.
And it hurt,
but I don't wanna
look stupid, so I...