Erstwhile on Fargo...
So you think this
is the one who killed
all those people
over in Bemidji?
Could be.
I mean,
you're saying this is all
some... some big coincidence,
that suddenly we got
four victims in 24 hours,
yourself included.
My wife is dead
and you're harassing me.
Just... leave poor
Lester alone, will you?
Found this on my
windshield last week.
You got bronzer on
your blackmail note.
I'm taking over.
I ran his plates
and it turns out
that the car was registered
to one of your victims.
30 milligrams.
Don't take two of these
and think you're gonna nap.
It's basically speed.
It's like
a nightmare.
I told you,
I know a guy.
You know a guy.
A guy.
Better be some
guy, Stavros.
For this...
we gave up everything.
Gave up?
What did we have?
Debts, screaming phone calls,
bill collectors at the door.
At least it was warm.
Shit.
What?
Out of gas.
You bought gas.
Five dollars.
It was all I had.
Idiot, the boy's
gonna freeze.
We can't stay here.
I know.
I'll think of something.
Think of what?
Gasoline?
Yeah, from your
brain into the--
Will you shut up?
I gotta think.
Oh, hey!
Here! Here!
Hey! Here! Here!
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Slow down.
Hey! No, stop.
Stop, wait!
Come on! Come on! Stop!
All right.
Lord, let me
get through this.
Let us find gas and...
a warm bed.
Let us prosper
even in the
smallest of ways...
and I will be
your humble servant
for the rest of my days.
Yeah.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
Oh, God, my God.
Thank you, God.
I can't believe
he wouldn't stop.
A family vehicle.
A baby in a car.
Who doesn't stop
for a baby in a car?
God is real.
We're gonna freeze to death
because a man that hasn't
showered since the '70s
couldn't be bothered
to apply the brakes.
God is real.
God... is real.
You know...
there's nothing here.
No wildlife in your pipes.
Water heater's clean.
Not sure how you got
blood in your shower.
Are you sure it wasn't
rust? 'Cause--
Listen to me.
It's not like
a Band-Aid fell out.
It was buckets...
literally buckets
of blood.
Whoa. Like in
a horror film, huh?
And with the dead dog
you mentioned, too... Uffda.
Sounds like a bad day.
Did you see any
signs of tampering?
Tampering?
Yeah.
Screws loosened recently
or... holes where blood
could've been injected.
Injected?
What the heck
are you thinkin'
happened here?
Nothing.
Thanks for your time.
You know...
You know, I, uh...
I seen your
commercials on TV.
"July in January."
You got any,
like, gift certificates?
The wife, she, uh...
Get the hell
outta here.
Sure. Okay.
Uh, say...
you ever read
the Bible?
What?
The Bible...
you know,
the big book?
All that blood
made me think of it.
You know,
Moses and the like.
"And God sent
a plague of blood
upon the land."
Better get
right with the Lord.
You know what I'm...
What did you say?
Nothing.
Say it again.
No...
What did you say to me?
Say it again!
Boss, let him go.
What did you say?
Boss, he's just
a damn plumber.
Let him go!
He's crazy.
You're crazy!
Car 39, this is dispatch.
Come in.
Yeah. Hold your horses.
Car 39, this is dispatch.
Come in.
Yeah, this
is 3-9, over.
Car 39, you need to
follow up on a report,
murdered canine
at 1301 Bird Lane.
Over.
Is that a...
Can you call it a
murder if it's a...
Anyhoo, that's
animal control's
purview.
Yeah, Joe's sick.
Was supposed to
respond yesterday.
Claimant is super PO'd.
Over.
Jeez. Come on,
that guy is always sick.
What's he got,
the cancer? Over.
Yeah, leukemia. Over.
Jeez. That is...
That's awful. Okay.
Well, uh...
3-9, car 3-9 responding.
Over and out.
One-two-five.
One-two-seven.
Okay.
Oh, jeez.
It's him.
Freeze! Don't...
Put your hands
where I can see...
where I can see 'em.
I'm just on a call.
Drop it.
Yeah, just as
soon as I finish.
This is Duluth.
Package requested,
Frank Peterson.
Okay, all good. See?
Put it down.
It's a new phone.
Now!
Okay.
Okay, um...
turn around and put
your hands on your head.
What's this all
about, Officer?
You know what
this is about.
Okay...
put your left
hand around your, uh...
the back of your...
Yeah.
Okay...
now the other one...
slowly.
Am I under arrest?
You're handcuffed.
Of course
you're under arrest.
On what charge?
It, uh...
We'll figure that
out at the station.
Okay.
All right.
Back...
back to the car.
All right.
Butt first.
Watch your head.
You're making
a mistake.
Be quiet.
You're making
a mistake.
I said quiet.
That's what you're gonna
say a couple hours from now.
"You're making a mistake."
Got one.
What was he,
mean to a cat?
Murder and car
thievery, all right.
This fella's wanted
for the triple
homicide in Bemidji.
Oh, now
hold on a sec.
It's like I told
this young fella,
this is a boondoggle,
plain and simple.
Save it, Cochise.
Now, I'm gonna
ink your right hand.
Press each finger
individually
against the book.
If you try anything...
I can't promise you
fingers won't get broke.
Okay, message
received, young fella.
You won't get no
pushback from me.
What the heck?
Son of a...
Molly, call on two.
Yeah, Solverson.
Yeah, hey, it's Gus.
I got him.
Who's this then?
Yeah, Gus Grimly.
From over Duluth.
You know, we...
we had the milkshakes
the other...
Oh, yeah, hey.
How's it goin'?
Yeah, real good.
Uh...
So, I was on patrol earlier.
Responding to a 613 and--
What's that then?
Dead dog,
foul play suspected.
And I see this fella and
he's standing by a van.
And it was him.
Him who?
The fella from
Mr. Nygaard's car.
The driver?
Yeah, yeah, the, uh...
the one I let go.
But there he was.
I mean, just, you know,
just standin' there,
makin' a call on his...
So what did you--
I stopped and
arrested him,
of course.
Arrested him?
Yeah, for the murders.
I'm looking at
the guy right now.
The Lieutenant's gonna
have a chat with him.
I thought you might wanna...
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, I'm gettin'
in my car.
Great.
I'll be there
just as soon as I--
Okay, then.
Yeah, I'll tell
the Lieutenant
to wait for you.
Thanks.
Yeah.
You're welcome.
Yeah, okay.
So we've been putting in
a lot of hours on the Chief,
but the weather
service is trackin'
a big storm.
They're looking
at Wednesday night,
Thursday, early a.m.
High winds, blizzard,
the whole shebang.
So if you wanna make
extra money plowing,
see Cindy.
Same goes
for traffic duty,
etcetera.
But I don't want this
impacting everyday doings,
so don't sign up unless
your workload is cleared.
Chief, they got him.
Who?
Duluth PD.
No, who'd they get?
Oh. Yeah.
Fella driving
Lester's stolen car.
Deputy pulled
him in an hour ago.
How come
they called you?
Pardon?
You're not even on the case.
How come they called you?
I just...
Well, the other day,
a deputy drove
down from Duluth.
And... you know,
he and I talked is all.
Well, that's irregular.
They should talk to
the officer in charge.
Yeah.
Yeah, so I was thinking
I'd drive up there.
You know, talk to the
suspect. On account of,
you know--
I think he's the fella
who put the naked
guy in the trunk.
No, should be me.
You said he was
driving Lester's car.
That's my case.
Plus, Vern
takes precedence.
Okay, but Chief--
Knutson, you're in
charge till I get back.
Okie-dokie, Chief. 10-4.
Gotta
pick up a few things.
You could've
waited in the car.
No, Kitty said
I should--
I mean, I wanna be
here for you, so--
Oh, jeez.
They just...
they leave it
like that?
All the blood.
Yeah, it's, uh...
You know, they gave me
a number to call, a service.
Lester--
I gotta...
Oh, yeah...
oh, my...
No, no, no. Oh, God.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
What?
God... damn it.
Oh, my God.
Hello?
Was it worth it?
Who is this?
The widow Hess.
Her husband nice and
cozy in the ground.
Insurance money
on the way.
And every night she puts
her kitty in your face.
A guy like you, Lester...
small town, small time...
might think you
won the lottery.
But I think that
you need to ask yourself...
was it worth it?
Worth what?
Your life.
Freshen you up?
No, we're good.
Just the check
please. Thanks.
Everything okay?
He's just not
very hungry. Thanks.
Thanks.
For Christ's
sakes, man!
Seriously?
I'm not looking at you.
You got
two minutes.
Okie-dokie.
Thanks a lot, sir.
Sir...
are you Don Chumph?
Uh...
Yeah.
There's a phone
call for you.
A what now?
Telephone.
You can take it right
here at the counter.
Hello?
Do they have 'em?
Who is this?
Well, let's figure
this out together.
Who knows you're
at the pet store
right now?
My mom?
Do I sound
like your mom?
Uh...
No.
Hold on.
Does your mom know
why you're at the
pet store right now?
She thinks
I'm getting a cat.
Okay,
I don't have
time for this.
Do they have 'em?
Yes or no.
Yeah, but only 100.
Okay.
Well, there are
three other pet stores
in the city, so hit 'em all.
I'm in jail.
I'll be out
in a few hours.
Wait-- What?
Time is up.
In two hours.
Come get me.
And this is the deputy
who effected the arrest.
Yeah, nice
work there.
He give you
much of a fight?
Uh... No, sir.
Bill Oswalt's
the Chief over
at Bemidji.
Oh.
Molly come?
Who?
Deputy over
at my office.
Sounds like your man's
got a thing for her.
Lock that shit down, Grimly.
This is a murder case.
Yes, sir.
So we got a name
on the guy?
Yes, sir.
Driver's license says
Frank Peterson and
an address up in Baudette.
Peterson, eh?
I knew a
Jay Peterson once...
had a dwarf arm.
What about evidence?
Sir?
Proof of his
connection to the crime.
You say you stopped him
driving Lester's car?
Yes, sir, but I didn't
know that it was stolen.
Why I let him go.
Yeah, but you
pulled prints from
the impounded vehicle?
No, sir.
Techs said it
was wiped clean.
Yeah.
Well,
we got a photo
though, right?
I mean, dashboard camera
from the car stop?
You know, proof
he's our guy.
No, sir.
My camera hasn't
worked for weeks.
But Molly's
got a picture.
It's in the file.
She showed me.
Yeah.
She did?
Yeah, this fella.
It's kind of
hard to see though.
It's grainy.
You sure this
is our guy?
Yeah, yeah, no--
That's our guy.
I'm positive.
Yeah, I'm Lieutenant Schmidt.
This is Bill Oswalt,
Chief over at Bemidji.
Yeah, Frank Peterson.
I'm the minister
up in Baudette.
Go Bears.
A minister?
Yeah, Baudette Lutheran.
Six years now.
Frank Peterson.
Before that Aberdeen.
So, you know, I'm not
used to having a firearm
stuck in my face,
which I know
the Lord tests you
in all kinds of ways,
but... ooh, partner,
that's a heart-stopper.
Cut the shit.
You were pulled
over Tuesday night
driving a stolen car.
No, sir. I think
I'd remember that.
Plus, Tuesday is bingo
night at the church.
We had a full house.
Florence Nightgarden
won the entire pot...
if I'm not mistaken.
And we can
check on that?
Oh, sure, yes, sir.
You could call
Florence herself.
Or Jim Avery,
he's our alderman.
Deputy Grimly--
Oh, that's the fella.
Deputy Grimly...
Pulled his pistol,
pointed it right at me.
Thought I was gonna
have a heart attack.
But, you know,
after he told me
about those homicides
over at Bemidji,
I thought, "Frank,
I mean, you can't blame
"the guy for
being a little jumpy.
"A horror show like that."
That son
of a bitch!
So you're saying you weren't
in Bemidji last week?
If I show your picture around,
no one would recognize you?
Me? No, sir.
I have a cousin
who lived in Bemidji
back in the '90s,
out near Leech Lake.
But he moved to
Anchorage in '03.
I said, "What, Minnesota's
not cold enough for you?"
We had a good
laugh about that.
Also, you're saying
you weren't pulled
over for speeding?
No, sir.
I'm a cautious
driver by nature...
on account
of my eyesight.
Glaucoma they say it is,
only in the one eye.
But you can't
be too careful.
That's what I tell
my parishioners.
Deputy Grimly--
Forgiveness,
that's the heart
of the good book.
Turn the other cheek,
second chances. Amen.
So, no, I don't
hold a grudge
against the deputy.
Though I'm lucky
I had my nitroglycerin
pills with me,
I'll tell you. Uffda.
Okay. Well, sit tight.
We're gonna
make some calls,
check your story.
You just...
just pick a name
out of the phone book.
Everybody up there
knows me.
Yeah.
So, uh...
looks like a call
was placed
to your motel from
the victim's house
the night Pearl
Nygaard was killed.
You said that
on the phone.
Right.
So... you remember
any seedy types
checking in last week?
Possible...
with a head injury?
I thought on it
on the way over.
There was a fella
checked in around then,
had a bump on his head.
Gave me guff
when I asked him
if he had any pets.
Oh, yeah?
Is it... this fella maybe?
Yeah.
That's him.
You don't sound
too happy about it.
Well, he just
wasn't very
nice is all.
I brought my book,
like you asked.
Fella paid cash,
I think.
But I make everyone
put their name
in the ledger.
There you go.
Okay, yeah.
Say... you remember
finding anything odd
when you cleaned his room?
What do you
mean "odd"?
Like...
out of the ordinary.
Memorable, I guess.
Well, he had
some tokens from
over the Lucky Penny.
You don't say.
Okay.
All right. Thank you.
All right, then.
Well, it looks like
he's a pretty
well-respected member
of the community up there.
We just had to
call and verify.
Thanks for your time.
Yeah.
Grimly.
Where have
you been? I've been trying
to call you all day.
Thought you were comin'.
Tried.
Are you in the room?
Yeah, they just
talked to him.
Why not you?
Me? No,
I do animal control
mostly.
Listen, I got a name
for the suspect.
Lorne Malvo.
He used it to
check into a motel.
Lorne Malvo, huh?
They're.. they're comin'
out. I'll call you back.
Sorry again for the
confusion, Pastor.
Just glad
nobody got hurt.
You're lettin' him go?
Desk duty, two weeks.
Now, just a--
Three weeks.
For Pete--
You're making a mistake.
Grimly, with me now.
You pointed
your service weapon
at a civilian.
No, a damn minister
on a public street.
No evidence,
no fingerprints, nothin'.
What about
the picture?
What, that Zapruder
film in the file?
Hell, son, that could
be a photo of my
momma for all I know.
No, no, it's him.
I know it's him.
Negatory.
We checked his story.
It tracks.
He's lying!
You have
a blessed day.
How can you do that?
What's that, son?
Just... just lie
like that.
I sure hope you
catch that fella
who killed all
those people.
I'll be praying on it.
Lorne Malvo.
Did you know
the human eye can see
more shades of green
than any other color?
What?
I said did you know
that the human eye can see
more shades of green
than any other color?
My question
for you is why?
Now just hold on.
When you figure out
the answer to my question...
then you'll have
the answer to yours.
Where are they?
In the back.
Can't you hear?
It's driving me crazy.
Yeah?
Yeah, Mr. Nygaard?
This is Dave
from Duluth impound.
Yeah, I'm gonna pick
her up probably Friday.
No, sir, I'm supposed
to tell you your
car's not ready yet.
What do you mean?
It's... Forensic
team's lookin' at it.
Forensic?
Yes, sir. Just routine,
but I can't
release the car to you
till they release it to me.
So, I'll call you
when it's done, okay?
Bye, now.
Hey, Lester.
I'm in a meeting.
Chaz?
I said I'm in a meeting.
Chaz, it's...
it's Lester.
Look, I think I might be
in a bit of trouble here.
When are you not in...
What kind of trouble?
Well, I'm...
I'm in the trunk of a car.
What?
A car. In...
in the trunk.
You're in
the trunk of your car?
No, not my car. It's...
it's these two fellas.
You see, the thing...
I think I may
have been kidnapped
is the thing.
What?
Yeah.
They got me...
in the trunk.
Uh-huh.
I... I don't really
know where we're goin'.
Did you say
you got kidnapped?
Lester, where are you?
I'll call the cops.
No, no, no. Don't...
don't call the...
Yeah, it's just a...
I'm prankin' you.
What?
Yeah.
Remember, how we
used to... You know,
practical jokes and all.
Well... you're it!
You're an asshole.
Come on. Come on.
There you go.
Come on.
Let's go.
You're gonna say it.
"I, Lester Nygaard..."
I, Lester Nygaard...
Louder.
Louder!
I, Lester Nygaard...
"Killed..."
No. No, you see,
I did not kill--
Lester, you're gonna say it.
One way or the other.
Okay, all right?
Mmm-hmm.
"Killed Sam Hess."
That's not true.
I didn't kill him.
Yes, you did.
No, I didn't.
Okay, then who was it?
It was a man.
Who's the man?
The man...
Who? Who's him?
Who... who is him?
It was the guy--
What? Who? What guy?
The guy...
I need... I need...
Is this your car, sir?
What?
Is this your car?
No, no.
I need... a ride back to town.
Not a taxi
service, sir.
What?
I said we're not a taxi...
Please, I just...
I just need...
Just give me a damn ride!
Oh!
Heck, sir.
Now I gotta arrest you.
Good, good. Let's go.
Oh, jeez! Thanks.
Okay.
Jeez.
Yeah, this is car 3108.
Coming in with a 313.
Copy, 3108.
Yeah, guy punched me.
Knock, for Christ's sake.
How many times?
Not now.
Not now!
Look, I wanna
talk about Mom.
I said not now.
You're not
being very nice.
"Nice"?
You think you
go down to the
car dealership
and buy
a car with "nice"?
You think the girls
at the titty bar
care about "nice"?
It's kill or
be killed, son.
Are you crying?
No.
Don't.
Kill or be killed.
Help, get it off!
Get it off of me!
Dad, what's happening?
God!
We demand one million
in unmarked bills.
We'll call
tomorrow at 10:00 a.m.
with the drop instructions.
Do you understand?
Yeah.
Remember,
God is watching.
Was that him?
God is real.
Bartender...
I tend... to have a beer
and then a little tequila guy.
Looks like you
already had a few.
Well, then, they're
working. Right?
What are you lookin' at?
You know,
I'll tell you something.
I will put... your eye out!
What?
I was about to
send a search party.
Yeah, sorry.
Cindy said Bill's
on his way back.
What happened?
Well... they let
him go. Malvo.
Yeah, he had an alibi.
It checked out.
But... it's him.
How do you know?
'Cause I said the name,
Lorne Malvo,
and he stopped
and he looked
at me real funny.
And then he said,
like, a riddle.
What's that
about a riddle?
Like... how come
the human eye can see
more shades of green
than any other color?
'Cause of predators.
Used to be we
were monkeys, right?
And in the woods,
in the jungle,
everything's green.
So, in order to not
get eaten by panthers
and bears and the like,
we had to be able
to see them, you know,
grass and trees and such.
Predators.
So what do we do now?
Lester.
Can I get, like,
a phone call?
And a...
and a chicken pot pie?
Sleep it off,
rummies.