♪ ♪
[Dr. Goodbee] Your son
had a serious electrical event.
He's had some...
neurological complications.
We'd like to keep him here
for a few days, run some tests.
[Dot]
I want a moment alone
with my husband.
Why, so you can get
your stories straight?
Get out.
[Dot]
Listen, bitch.
I've climbed through six kinds
of hell to get where I am,
and no Ivy League royal wannabe
is gonna run me off just because
she doesn't like
the way I smell.
[Danish]
What about Dorothy?
[Lorraine] She's a wolf
in sheep's clothing,
that one.
We keep her close for now.
♪ ♪
[narrator]
The tiger, spelled T-I-G-E-R,
is one of the fiercest hunters
on Earth.
- [Lorraine] I have to run into the city.
- [Danish] Oh.
[Lorraine]
It's in place?
- What we discussed?
- It is.
But I feel I must reiterate...
Yes, yes, you went on
at length last night.
It's funny how
one's tireless moralizing
can become so tiring.
You have power of attorney,
don't you?
In cases where both she and
her husband are incapacitated.
Well, there you go.
[narrator]
Known for its cunning
and strategic mind,
the tiger is most dangerous
when cornered.
Dorothy.
What time is it?
Just past 11:00.
- [Dot] Mm.
- These men
would like to talk to you.
What?
[Early]
Relax, Dorothy.
We just want to talk to you.
[Danish]
It's for your own good, Dorothy.
It's for your protection.
[faintly]
We're very concerned...
[screams] No!
[Danish] The last few days,
with all the upset, and...
[screams]
[Danish]
Mrs. Lyon, Lorraine...
Liars. No.
Hmm. No!
I don't agree to this.
[screams]
[Danish]
...she feels... and I agree...
you've been having some kind
of psychotic...
Oh, okay, well, maybe
that's too strong a word.
You're fired.
We're worried that
you've become a danger
to yourself or others.
You're the danger.
My lawyer?
My A-S-S.
If you take me,
I'm gonna try and blind
you boys, break your fingers,
bite off both your noses.
Dorothy.
Ah-ah. Maybe you heard the story
where I burned a fella alive,
chopped the other one's ear off
when they came for me.
I'm not saying that's true...
...but if you try to force me
against my will...
...you're gonna find out.
[chuckles]
I told you.
[grunts]
[ambulance doors close]
Shoot.
It's done.
[sighs]
Okay.
Well, here we go.
Home away from home.
- I'm feeling much better now.
- Oh, good.
- I mean it.
- Oh, well, uh...
- good.
- [chuckles]
[Dot]
I just think,
to go to all this trouble,
so much fuss,
when all I need is a bath
and, you know,
Calgon, take me away.
Yeah. Okay.
- [elevator bell dings]
- And you're so busy.
- I hate to keep you.
- [Danish] Dorothy.
No.
And I am so sorry
for biting you boys.
[elevator bell dings]
[indistinct chatter]
[narrator] Though it may look like
the tiger has given up,
this is, in fact, a ruse.
Look closer.
Even now, she plans an escape.
[door creaks open]
What a day.
I'm sorry. I mean it.
Geez, I must look a fright.
[chuckles]
Mascara down my face,
my nose running.
I'm so embarrassed.
You wouldn't have a hanky,
would you?
Yeah, I...
[screaming]
[both grunting]
Here we are.
[indistinct chatter]
I'm so glad we could do this.
The numbers look good.
Rupert ran them yesterday.
Yeah, pretty sweet.
Says he's been talking things
through with your Mr. Graves.
Thought he'd be here.
Well, he's not.
You get the headliner.
[Vivian]
Rupert says he likes him.
- Straight shooter.
- Says he trusts him.
I'm so glad.
Thought we'd see him today.
Let me guess,
the last time you negotiated
with a woman
was over the price
of a Tijuana blowjob.
How much to...
stick it in your asshole,
that kind of thing.
I'll have the Cobb salad,
no cheese,
and I'm guessing
burger and fries for these boys.
And bring us
a bottle of the Caymus,
the '92, not the '93.
Goodbye.
Now, Miss...
Mrs. Lorraine Lyon.
CEO of Redemption Services,
a Nasdaq-listed,
multibillion dollar corporation.
Mrs. Lyon has six governors
on speed dial
and her own personal
liaison at
the Federal Trade Commission.
Nice to meet you.
Are we friends yet? Good.
I want to buy your bank,
but, more important,
you need to sell your bank
because I looked
at your numbers,
and you don't have enough
cash on hand to satisfy current
U.S. banking regulations,
which...
...one phone call from me,
and you will have so many
SEC agents up your keister,
you'll be shitting briefcases
for the rest of your life.
Now hold on just a second, lady.
Do you see?
Right there.
I'm going to knock 10 million
off my offer
because you called me "lady."
We just...
Pipe down, pony boy.
I'll tell you
when it's your turn to talk.
I'm willing
to buy your shady
five-gallon bank...
...because I'm
in the debt business,
and I want to get
into the credit business.
Everyone loves a lender,
not so much the repo man,
but I need to test the waters,
make sure the government'll
let me do both,
so I'm starting small,
with you.
And I'm willing to pay a premium
to get this done quickly,
but if you hate women
more than you love money,
I'll just take
my millions elsewhere.
Enjoy the wine.
I expect your answer
by end of business today.
♪ ♪
Hey.
Hear it's supposed
to snow later, hmm?
Here's me putting off
changing out the radials
- till the last second.
- You're not Sarah.
- Oh.
- Where's Sarah?
It's my first day.
Still haven't got all the names
straight. [chuckles]
Sarah's the one with...
- [alarm ringing]
- Oh.
[woman over P.A.]
Code gray on floor two.
Security,
please report to floor two.
Code gray.
[indistinct radio chatter]
There you are. Hi.
Okay. Mm...
What now?
Mrs. Lyon.
Let me guess,
the orphans need a new roof.
Well, probably,
but I'm more of a
"let the orphans fight each
other for sport" kind of guy.
Libertarian, so...
I've got a busy day, Officer.
It's "sheriff," actually.
Roy Tillman,
from over Stark County.
North Dakota.
That's the one.
I was hoping we could, uh, talk.
Uh-huh. And what exactly
are we talking about?
Uh, well, your daughter-in-law.
Well, what's she done now?
She married me.
[stammers]
You better come inside.
[sighs] Okay, sailor.
What are you gonna cost me?
Excuse me?
The "fuck off fee."
Never to be seen again.
[sighs] Oh... Good God,
don't tell me you want her back.
Is it just the money,
or have you always been
this high and mighty?
Like that,
looking down your nose
on a hard-working American.
And me with my hat in hand
just trying to do what's right.
What's right for whom?
Right as in the Bible,
as in a woman swears an oath
to honor and obey her man,
not go out and get a six-pack
and never come home.
May I have the details
of this alleged matrimony,
please?
June 3, 2007.
We got married at the ranch.
My second, her first. Uh...
We were together about
two years, before and during,
and then, all of a sudden,
poof, she disappears. [sighs]
Gone.
Well, I'll tell you,
there were nights
I figured she must've been dead.
Horrible thoughts.
Mountain lions, Mexican rapists.
So you can understand my relief
when the report came in
said she'd been found.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, my first thought hearing
that she'd remarried with a kid,
maybe some sort of amnesia.
Found wandering the highway,
not knowing
when her birthday f...
All right, I-I...
I get the picture.
Listen, slick.
Nothing would make me happier
than to put that girl in a box
marked "return to sender,"
between you and me, but
she's married to my son,
and he loves her,
and she's the mother
to my granddaughter,
whom I'm fond of,
so you need to put
your big boy pants on
and take the hit.
Bible says the wife
is the property of the husband.
Therefore, that makes your son
a thief.
If we're talking about who has
the more legitimate claim.
You know, I've heard of you.
You're one of those
constitutional sheriffs.
Yes, I am.
Defender of freedom
and protector of the common man
against the tyranny of the state
and all its wicked demands.
- Taxes?
- Oh, yeah.
The social safety net?
Well, I'd spit, but, uh...
Respect for the otherly-abled?
The whole
multi-cultural panoply.
Billy has two mothers,
et cetera, et cetera.
So-so,
you-you want freedom
with no responsibility?
Son, there's only
one person on Earth
- who gets that deal.
- Mm.
The president?
A baby.
[laughs]
You're fighting
for your-your right
to be a baby.
Hi, they said...
Oh, I'm sorry.
I just wanted to check, see
how the powwow went with Duggar.
What is that? Uh, Vivian Dugger?
The banker with a woman's name?
He was in my prowler once.
I caught him in flagrante
with a lady of the evening,
but we came to an arrangement.
That's what reasonable men do.
Should I be... Do you want me
to sit in on this?
No. No, the, um,
the sheriff was just leaving.
Oh, was I?
Well, as I said, if you're
willing to sign some papers,
I could see my way clear
to writing a check.
I mean,
between your-your reelection
and my business dealings,
I'm sure neither of us want
any sordid details coming out.
Is that reasonable enough
for you?
So, that's who you are.
That's who I am.
And while we're talking
about property rights,
I'd like to be clear that,
after seven years,
a missing person
is presumed dead.
So, technically,
Dorothy is my son's
property now.
Nadine.
Her name's Nadine.
Not anymore.
[sighs]
Women, am I right?
Here's my card.
I'd be happy
to sit down tomorrow,
discuss the details of a deal.
[sighs] Well, son,
I'm not sure
I can negotiate with a man
named after a breakfast pastry.
- [car approaching]
- Yes, well,
I am Mrs. Lyon's
- chief counsel, so I'm the one you talk to.
- [car door opens, closes]
And who might you be?
Scotty.
He's a muffin, you've got
a boy's name. What's next?
A monkey with a hat? [chuckles]
Nice meeting you there, Scotty.
Tell your mom
Sheriff Roy says hello.
She looks just like her mom.
Yeah. I'll expect your call.
Oh, we'll be seeing
each other again,
just maybe not in the way
you're expecting.
What's that supposed to mean?
You have a nice day.
♪ ♪
Ah...
How many times do I have
to tell you people
- we're not gonna cooperate.
- Mr. Graves,
did you have Dorothy Lyon
committed this morning?
I don't see as that's
any of your business.
Well, it's my business
because she escaped.
Call just went out on the radio.
[chuckles]
That's...
[phone rings]
Talk to me.
[Roy over phone]
Yeah, we're going with plan B.
Take the husband.
Yes.
- Pass me to Bowman.
- [Gator] I don't...[sighs]
Pass me to Bowman.
You didn't have to send him
to babysit me.
Just give him the damn phone.
[distant chatter]
Right.
[phone beeps]
What'd he say?
You stay here.
I'm the law.
You...
I'm coming. I'm...
Fuck.
[narrator]
The female, or lady tiger,
can outsmart even
the most skilled hunters.
She is a literal genius
when it comes
to saving her young
and protecting her mate.
What's with all
the extra security?
[clerk]
Oh, a mental patient escaped.
A female.
Mm.
I'm looking for my cousin,
Wayne Lyon.
Aren't we going?
Oh, yeah. We just got to make
a quick stop first.
Come on.
Oh, uh, third floor.
Oh, and, uh, check in
at the nurse's station.
[grunts]
[elevator bell dings]
Hold it.
[sighs]
You stay in the fucking car.
Okay.
[mutters]
[exhales]
Shit.
Shit. Shit. Geez.
Uh...
[elevator bell dings]
[indistinct chatter]
[indistinct P.A. announcement]
Just forgot some
of your paperwork, hon.
Back in a jiff.
[indistinct chatter]
Well, about fucking time.
I'm supposed to get
Jell-O and broth.
Hey. They said I could get
some Jell-O and broth.
That's...
Sorry, let me see what I...
[Jordan] Two days
I'm sitting in this stupid bed
waiting for you people
to rip out
six feet of my intestines.
Least I can do
is get some Jell-O
and fucking broth.
Of course.
I'll check on that for you.
You stealing my coat?
What the hell
kind of place is this?
No. I'm just...
I'm having it cleaned.
It's part of the service
we provide here.
I am on to you, bitch.
All of you people
sneaking around here
pretending you're so nice,
but I know who you really are.
Ow! Ah!
- Ah! Ah!
- Why are you
- so rude? Hmm?
- Ah! Ah! Oh!
- So angry?
- [grunting]
All of you.
Whatever happened
to grace and dignity?
[muffled shouting]
Everybody here
is just trying to help.
[narrator] The tiger has been
known to set traps
to ensnare her pursuers.
Thus, the popular colloquialism
"Do not hunt the tiger
unless you want the tiger
catching you."
What's money?
Money? That... Oh, hon,
I don't have time to go
into the whole...
Let's get you
to the bathroom, yeah?
Oh, I just went.
Poop came out.
Mm. Oh.
That's good, hon.
- Yeah.
We're gonna go, though, yeah?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
[grunts]
Uh, hold on,
my foot's unconscious.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
- It's okay.
- [grunts]
[grunting]
I love you, too.
Come on.
Mm.
The nurse told me
that we're rich,
and I said I didn't know
what that was.
[Dot chuckles]
What?
Stay here, okay?
Then, you see...
...this lock?
Yeah.
Turn it when I'm gone
and don't come out until I say.
I love you three.
[Dot]
Lock the door, baby.
[lock clicks]
It's this one.
Stay here.
[both gasp]
Oh, Nadine.
- What?
- Dorothy,
he means. Sorry.
I'm... No. I have, I have...
M-Mrs. Lyon, it's okay.
We-We're here to help you, okay?
I don't need help.
- I think you do.
- No.
Let-Let's just...
We'll find a room
and we can talk.
Dorothy?
Mrs. Lyon?
I can't. I, uh,
have to be somewhere.
Do you got a card I could have?
[Joaquin]
Yes, ma'am.
You were supposed to wait
in the truck.
FBI is here.
Look who they're talking to.
Doesn't matter.
We got her husband.
Had to tenderize him.
What an asshole.
Let's go.
I'm Agent Joaquin.
This is my, this is my partner,
- Agent Meyer. Here you go.
- Hey, there.
We've been looking for you.
Can you... We just,
we just want to talk.
- All right? Let's find a room.
- [elevator bell dings]
- Yeah, a quiet room.
- You're okay, you're okay.
- We're here to help you. Okay?
- It's okay.
- I meant to ask, is your,
is your husband okay? - Yeah.
We went by the house.
That must've been some fire.
He's...
[narrator]
Only the tiger shark
is a more dangerous foe.
Though, of course,
the tiger shark,
or any kind of shark, really,
would suffocate
in a hospital setting.
I'll just... I'll be quick.
What do you think?
She looks relieved.
No more running.
Honestly, I don't know how
she made it this far.
Hmm.
Have you seen a woman,
like, light brown hair,
maybe five-two
wearing nurse's scrubs?
She's a biter.
No. I can't help you.
- Okay.
- Wait. What's her name?
Mrs. Lyon?
Dorothy?
No more running?
Well, shit.
[sighs]
[dogs barking outside]
Mrs. Lyon.
If I could just
understand better
why you had her committed.
You're a debtor.
- What?
- I looked it up.
$192,000.
- [scoffs]
- Spread between your mortgage,
car loans, your student loans,
medical bills,
credit cards.
Hell, you've got it all.
Th-That's not...
I don't think...
relevant to this.
Don't feel bad.
You're not alone.
Over 90% of American adults
are debtors.
In the red,
living beyond their means.
Kids waiting in the wings.
I-I'm not...
I'm not that...
what you said.
You see it, right?
The cage you're in.
I see it.
What came first?
Student loan?
Mm. Let me guess.
Your parents sent you
to a private school
they can't afford,
took out a loan, made you sign.
I put myself through school,
working two jobs.
Mm, you got a loan.
Tuition went up sophomore year.
So, nobody tricked you
into debt,
or-or forced you into it.
You went willingly.
At least the animals
in the zoo fight.
I'm not an animal.
But you're in the zoo.
All of you.
And every month,
the interest rate goes up,
the fees and fines.
You tuck your kids in at night,
never telling them
that they're-they're
in the cage, too,
because, when you die,
your debts become theirs.
So,
just know that, when you
talk to me, you're talking
to the zookeeper.
Not some lemming or lemur.
Mrs. Lyon.
Yes, I heard you.
My psychotic...
possibly homicidal
daughter-in-law
escaped a locked
psychiatric ward.
And what I want to know is,
are you gonna look for her,
or are you gonna sit
drinking coffee in the one house
in the state where I know
that girl ain't at?
[man over radio]
Larson, are you there? Copy.
[man 2]
Larson here. Copy.
[whistles]
[whispers] Hi.
Mommy?
[laughs]
[exhales]
I'm so happy to see you.
- They said you were sick.
- Do I look sick?
- You look tired.
- [snorts]
Well, I'm right as rain
where it matters, so...
- Mama?
- Yeah?
Who's Sheriff Roy?
Where did you hear that name?
He was here at Grandma's.
He said to say hi.
He's no one.
Just someone Mommy used to know.
[whispers] Let's go.
Come on, come on.
[operative]
ID, please.
But I'm leaving.
- ID, please.
- Get out of my way.
Sir, I have my orders.
Nobody comes or goes
without showing ID.
I hired you.
I sign your paychecks.
That's who I am.
I appreciate that, sir.
I insist. ID, please.
Uh...
Thank you, Mr. Graves.
Fuck you.
Don't do this to me again.
Do you understand?
- Have you seen Scotty?
- What?
Scotty. She was just here.
- [sighs]
- I can't find her.
Well, I guess you'd better find
Mrs. Lyon's granddaughter.
Toy box. 10-65.
[operative 2] Copy that,
10-65. Moving your direction.
Come on.
Shit.
[sighs]
I made coffee.
You want some?
Why not?
Looks like I'll be up
for a while.
Hey, hon.
We got half the force
looking for you. You okay?
We had breakfast for dinner.
[laughs softly] She loves that.
Who doesn't?
I added cinnamon
and a little honey.
Didn't know you could do that.
Hmm.
You got some cartoons
she could watch?
Uh, they turned off
the cable last week...
...but I think
there's a Little MermaidDVD
- somewhere in the living room.
- Mm.
How about that? Hmm?
How does that sound?
Little Mermaid.
- Princesses are dumb.
- [Dot laughs]
But beggars can't be choosers.
- Remote's on the table.
- Go on.
I'm trying to think of who,
in the history of the world,
has had a week
like the one you just had.
Amelia Earhart, maybe.
It's only been a week?
Give or take.
You got a nice face.
You know that?
Kind, in the eyes.
Oh, I can be scary
when I need to.
- Just ask my husband.
- Hmm.
Is that him in the garage?
What's he doing in there?
It's been hours.
Yeah. The nine iron,
the eight iron, the seven iron.
Don't get me started
on the putter.
Ah. He's a golfer.
You ever have a dream
where you, you wake up one day
and you realize you're just
not tall enough to reach it?
Well, he ain't woke up yet.
Keeps thinking it's the gear.
"Maybe with better gear."
So, every month when I open
the credit card bills,
they just keep getting
bigger and bigger.
Hm.
I need to leave Scotty here
for a few days.
You're not serious.
- Two. Three, maybe, tops?
- [laughs softly]
I got to do something.
I don't...
She's not safe at Lorraine's.
Safe from what?
[movie playing quietly]
Price of admission.
You tell me the truth,
and I'll see if I can
help you out.
[lighter clicks]
Okay.
Some fellas came for me
the other day,
and again on Halloween.
Who?
My husband.
The first one.
Before Wayne.
I was 17.
15 when they took me in.
That's a whole other story.
Keep going.
They never hit you when
it's going their way, you know?
It's when they're weak,
and just pretending
to be strong.
When they need something small
to climb on to feel big.
"They"? You said "they."
- Can I just...
- [golf club thwacks]
[whispers]
Can I leave her here or what?
Dorothy... [sighs]
You're a wanted fugitive.
Your daughter is a missing
person, presumed kidnapped,
and I'm an officer
of the law. I...
- So that's a no?
- [door closes]
[Lars]
Babe, I'm slicing right again.
It's those goddamn clubs
that Walter sold me.
I'm gonna take them back
in the morning,
see if he'll exchange them
for the Epic MAX Star five,
but we need to be prepared
for him to bone me.
Babe, there's a lady
in our kitchen.
There sure is.
This is my friend Alice,
from the potlucks
over at Saint Luke's.
Hi. Forgive the getup.
I just pulled a double
at the hospital.
Hey.
Her daughter Scotty's gonna be
staying with us
for a couple of days.
She's in the living room,
watching The Little Mermaid.
Like, an actual kid?
♪ ♪
[engine starts]
[man]
Now I get it.
[rooster crows]
[roars]