[lively chatter in distance]
[heavy footsteps approaching]
♪ ♪
[leather crunching]
[kids shouting indistinctly]
♪ ♪
[oven buttons beep]
- [doorbell rings]
- [indistinct chatter nearby]
[Tiny Tim] And now, because
you've all been so sweet,
another duet for you.
♪ They say we're young ♪
♪ And we don't know,
won't find out ♪
♪ Until we grow ♪
♪ Well, I don't know,
I guess it's true ♪
♪ 'Cause you got me,
and, baby, I got you ♪
♪ Babe ♪
♪ I've got you, babe ♪
♪ I got you, babe ♪
♪ They say our love
won't pay the rent ♪
♪ Before it's earned,
our money's always spent ♪
♪ Well, I don't know,
we got no plot ♪
♪ Still I'm sure of ♪
♪ All the love we got ♪
♪ Babe ♪
♪ I got you, babe ♪
♪ They say we're young
and we don't know ♪
♪ Won't find out until we grow ♪
[electrical crackling]
♪ Well, I don't know,
I guess it's true ♪
♪ 'Cause you got me
and, baby, I got you ♪
♪ Babe ♪
[in distance]
♪ I got you, babe ♪
♪ They say our love
won't pay the rent ♪
♪ Before it's earned,
our money's always spent ♪
♪ Well, I don't know,
we got no plot ♪
♪ Still I'm sure of
all the love we got ♪
♪ Babe ♪
♪ I got you, babe ♪
♪ I got you,
babe ♪
♪ I got flowers in the spring ♪
♪ I got you to wear my ring ♪
♪ When I'm sad, you're a clown ♪
♪ When I get scared,
you're always around ♪
♪ Some people say
your hair's too long ♪
♪ I don't care ♪
♪ With you I can't go wrong ♪
- ♪ So put your ♪
- ♪ Ah, ah ♪
- ♪ Your little hand ♪
- ♪ In mine ♪
- ♪ Ah, ah ♪
♪ There ain't no hill
or mountain we can't climb ♪
- ♪ Ah, ah ♪
- ♪ Babe ♪
♪ I got you, babe ♪
♪ I got you,
babe ♪
♪ They say our love
won't pay the rent ♪
♪ Before it's earned,
our money's always spent... ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Still I'm sure of
all the love we got ♪
♪ Babe ♪
♪ I got you, babe ♪
[distorted]
♪ I got you, babe. ♪
- [music stops]
- [alarm blaring]
[automated maniacal laughter]
[automated laughter continues]
[yells, groans]
♪ ♪
[alarm continues blaring]
Hey! No, no, no, no, no, no!
[panting]
Go after her!
[grunting]
Jesus, Nadine.
[alarm blaring]
Shame on you, Gator.
- There's a baby in this house.
- I saw her.
She's like nine.
Now get your ass
in that car, let's go.
I'm not going back.
Now, Nadine,
we both know you're going back,
like it or not. [grunts]
[panting]
[automated maniacal laughter]
She's in the basement.
Go get the husband.
[groans] Is-is he...
Focus.
The kid gets you bonus points.
[grunts]
[sizzling]
[smoke detector stops]
[alarm blaring in distance]
[alarm stops]
Where are you, Mama?
It's time to go home.
Your husband...
it's Wayne, right?
He's a nice guy.
A little soft, maybe.
Is that it?
Is he soft?
Well, you don't
come out of there,
we're gonna find out.
[loud banging]
Wipe that stupid grin
off your face.
♪ ♪
[panting]
Nadine.
[whistles]
♪ ♪
Can't find this fucking guy.
[grunts]
Shit.
- [screams]
- [grunting]
- Mommy!
- [Dot] Not now!
[both grunting]
[Brandy]
Gator!
Dot?!
[grunts]
Stay, stay, okay?
Come here! I'll kill you!
- Babe?
- It's okay.
- [Gator] Nadine?
- They're up here!
- [gasps]
- Hon, hold him.
They're up here!
Got 'em up here.
Wait, wait, wait.
What are you gonna do with...
What are you...
- What are you... Wait!
- [grunts]
- Go, Mom!
- [Gator] I'm coming for you, Nadine.
[gasps] Quick.
Down the laundry chute.
Nadine?
Who's Nadine?
- Wayne.
- [Wayne] No. That's...
- You got me in the dark here.
- Get Scotty down the chute.
- [Wayne gasping] No.
- [yells]
- Jesus.
- Uh, down the... the master bedroom,
- the trellis, we'll climb down. Go.
- No. No, no.
- Hon. Oh!
- Come here.
- Nadine!
- [grunts]
- [echoing] No, hon!
[crackling]
- Wha... Oh.
- Daddy?
Check his breathing.
- [door rattling]
- [Gator] Nadine.
Mom!
Oh, my...
Okay. [gasps]
Okay.
Help me get him up.
[banging on door]
Scotty, don't focus on that.
Focus on this, okay?
We got to sit him up.
Okay, baby?
Yeah. [grunts]
Gosh. [grunts]
Okay.
You're gonna climb out.
It's okay.
Yeah.
- [banging]
- Good.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- Okay. [grunts]
- [banging on door]
Okay, mister...
[straining]
Out you go.
[Dot grunts]
[panting]
Okay. [panting]
[Scotty]
Mom?
[echoing]
♪ ♪
Whoa! [exhales sharply]
[breathing heavily]
Trellis. Okay, come on.
You're doing great.
Careful.
Okay.
Wayne, honey?
Wayne?
I need you to wake up now.
[grunts] Nadine?
Nadine?
[grunts] Ooh, sorry, baby.
[grunting]
Ooh! [exhales]
Okay, okay. I'm coming.
[panting]
[sirens approaching]
Grab the stiff.
We're done.
[grunts] Okay.
[panting]
[sirens blaring]
[panicked chatter nearby]
[straining]
♪ ♪
[creaking]
[wind whistles]
[Roy]
Well, old friend.
It's the crossroads,
no question,
and we know who's waiting there.
The midnight man.
With his serpent tongue.
I met him once.
Old Baylor Maze
cut his children to pieces
and hung his wife
with a curtain tie,
and I was first
through the door.
And old Baylor was sitting there
in his easy chair...
- Whoa.
- ...taking it easy.
Behind him, I swear,
and you know this
'cause you were there, too.
Beelzebub himself,
crouched low, whispering
in that poor man's ear.
You protected me then,
old friend.
Be with us again
in our hour of need.
Amen.
♪ ♪
Daddy?
- [Scotty] Mama?
- [Dot] Yeah?
[Scotty]
Were those demons?
[Dot]
No, hon.
There's no such thing
as demons, only men.
[Scotty]
But why were they so mean and nasty?
[Dot]
Listen to me, okay?
We can't talk about those men.
If we talk about them,
they come back, right?
They hear you talking,
and they come back.
You don't want them coming back,
do you?
No.
So we got to...
If people ask,
we got to say it was just wires.
Your dad touched some wires,
and that's how...
And the scratches on his face,
that was...
Him falling in the bushes.
We-we chased him
with the zombie killer,
'cause he was a zombie, right?
And there he goes,
off into the bushes.
That's right.
Good. Yeah.
He fell into some bushes.
He fell into some bushes,
and then when we got home,
he touched a wire
trying to plug in some lights.
An accident.
That's what started the fire.
Because bad things
don't happen to good people.
The wicked stick
to the darkness,
while we get to stay
in the light.
But sometimes accidents happen.
And we all know
your dad is clumsical.
Always tripping
over his own left feet.
And we know that
if you follow the rules
and think of only good thoughts,
that the kingdom of heaven
will be the reward.
I blew up the image.
You'll see that next.
- [Indira] Huh.
- [Witt] See?
[Indira]
Yeah, that's her all right.
[Witt]
And then... here I come.
Ouch.
And then the lights go out.
So, nothing on the perp.
Yeah, that's the shame.
But they say ghosts don't
photograph anyway.
A ghost?
Something else.
[Indira]
I get it even less now.
You get grabbed up, taken,
somehow you manage to get away,
get shot at,
come to the aid of
a sworn officer,
lifesaving actions.
Why the heck would you pretend
none of it happened?
I've seen trained soldiers
couldn't have kept with her.
Get this. Five alarm fire
at the Lyon house.
- What?
- Yeah.
Fire boys are there right now
rooting out the cause.
But Wayne's in the ER,
so you might... yeah.
[Witt]
Wait for me.
♪ ♪
[phone ringing]
- [Indira] Olmstead.
- [Dale] Mrs. Olmstead.
This is Dale Pickney,
debt collection services.
[Indira]
Oh, yeah.
You know, this really isn't
a good time.
[Dale]
It'll just take a minute.
[Lorraine]
It starts as an itch.
[Dale]
You want to make things right here,
don't you, Ms. Olmstead?
[Lorraine]
I want a new pair of shoes
or maybe the minivan
finally gives up the ghost.
[Dale] Well, I see here
an outstanding uncollected debt
from medical services
for $2,671.43.
Yep. That was...
Lars, my husband,
he-he degloved his ring finger
in a...
in a fall last year.
[Lorraine] And just like that
you're in debt.
[Dale]
Well, that debt's just sitting there accruing interest.
[Lorraine]
The stress takes a toll on your body,
like that old joke
about the hangman.
You're at the end
of your old rope.
[Dale]
You want to do what's right...
People in debt feel powerless.
They are powerless.
Here at Redemption Services,
we work to give them
their power back.
Aren't you the one calling them
at breakfast and dinner?
We call, of course,
but not like you say.
These are professional
debt relief specialists.
They're offering solutions...
payment plans, timetables,
debt consolidation...
intended to give people
their dignity back.
Your company earned
record profits last year,
buying consumer debt
the credit card companies
and insurance companies had
written off as uncollectible.
And you're telling me
that you turned those dead ends
into $1.6 billion
with timetables and empathy?
[knocking]
Mrs. Lyon, there's, uh...
I said not to be disturbed.
Yes, ma'am, but, uh...
Your son's house is on fire.
Of course.
Here's what you need
to understand about Americans.
They don't want a handout.
What they're looking for
is an opportunity
to fix it themselves.
We give them that.
Now, why don't we pick this up
again in the morning?
Where is he?
Where's my son?
Lorraine, they're looking at him
right now.
Some kind of shock,
they're saying.
Bad wiring, I guess.
You know, one minute, we...
I want to talk to a doctor.
The head of the department.
Which department?
Call Larry.
He's on the board
of the hospital.
Tell him I expect
the Saudi package...
private suite, experts flown in.
That's not...
I'm just saying,
he's resting now
and then it'll be, you know,
lickety-split, good as new.
You're killing me here.
I'm supposed to be
making up the sit-down
with the Forbes reporter
20 minutes ago.
That got blown yesterday
by the cops showing up
on your last boondoggle,
and here you go
burning down the house.
Not... I didn't burn it.
Like I said, faulty wiring.
We'll just get a hotel
for a few days.
You expect my granddaughter
to live in a hotel?
I'm not...
- This just happened, so...
- Excuse me.
We're waiting on service.
Ma'am, this isn't a hotel.
You got to check in at the desk,
just like everybody else.
She's fired. Get her name.
- Mrs. Lyon.
- Yes.
No. Sorry, we're here
for your daughter-in-law.
I knew it.
You're arresting her.
Well, do-do something.
They're-they're arresting her.
[Indira]
We're not... This is Witt Farr,
state trooper
over in North Dakota.
But we'd like to talk
to Mrs. Lyon in private,
clear some things up.
My husband's unwell.
I can't leave his side.
[Indira]
Well, technically, Mrs. Lyon,
you're not by his side
right now, so...
Hi.
I got my daughter with me.
I'm her grandmother.
I can watch her.
Somebody better.
Her house burned down
last night, under her watch.
Yes, ma'am.
I heard about that.
Fire department's there
right now,
- extinguishing the embers.
- Bad wiring.
[Indira]
I'm sure they'll do a thorough investigation,
ferret out the root cause.
Officers,
my client would be happy
to schedule a sit-down, but
clearly this is not the time,
given the circumstance.
Well, see, I got to push back
on you there, Mr., uh...
Graves. Esquire.
I represent the family.
Well, Mr. Graves.
We've got one state trooper dead
with the suspect on the loose
considered armed and dangerous.
So there's considerable
exigency to the circumstances.
And, Mrs. Lyon...
It's good to see you again,
Mrs. Lyon.
That...
[zips loudly]
That's not accurate.
Ah, well, first of all,
I recognize you.
And second,
we pulled the security tape
from the Gas N Go,
so it's-it's clear
you were there.
And for the record, that's...
that's just reality.
With all due respect,
we've got our own reality.
You can't...
That's not a thing.
[Scotty]
Mommy?
Hi, baby. I'm here.
We're all here.
Grandma, too.
- Hi, Grandma. Our house burned down.
- No.
And whose fault is that?
Jack Skellington.
Who?
[Dot]
It's a character in a movie.
How about you go get
something to eat
from the vending machine?
- Okay?
- [Scotty] Snickers?
For breakfast?
Are we on welfare?
It's fine.
Snickers is fine.
Danish.
Oh. [sighs]
Here you go, kid.
[Dot chuckles forcefully]
[Witt]
Mrs. Lyon.
Dorothy.
You got to tell me,
who were those fellas,
and what did they want with you?
[Dot]
I didn't...
Please.
I need to be with Wayne
right now.
- Can you...
- [Marcy] Mrs. Lyon?
- Yes.
- Oh, I meant...
Your husband's awake.
You'll watch Scotty?
You don't have to tell me
to watch her.
She's my granddaughter.
You're the one
needs watching, I think.
I mean, I've been waiting
for four fucking hours.
Sir.
Look, they're taking six feet
of my intestines tomorrow.
All right? Cancer.
But not if you don't...
I mean,
it's on the goddamn papers.
- Your gal's supposed to do the enema.
- Sir, sir...
[patient]
Well, where is she? I'm fucking waiting there
- with my ass hanging out.
- Just calm down. Yeah.
[patient]
I mean, I've been waiting for four fucking hours.
Hey, baby.
Are you...
How are you?
Hi.
Is everything...
What did the doctor say?
Nadine.
No. That...
I'm Dorothy.
Dot.
Remember?
Your wife.
My wife.
Did they put you on something?
Morphine or something?
[patient]
Bring me the dang thing now.
- I'll do it myself.
- [Marcy] Sir.
[patient]
Or a bottle of freaking Ex-Lax.
I don't care,
I need this cancer out of me.
- [door closes]
- Angry.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Yeah.
Some people don't know
how to wait their turn.
Did you...
I'm wondering...
what you remember about
what happened.
Ladder.
Well, no.
No.
You touched a wire, I guess.
Got some kind of shock.
You know, something like that
can play tricks on your mind,
make you think you did something
that maybe you didn't.
Mm.
Ask Scotty. She'll tell you.
We were out trick-or-treating,
then we came inside
and you went to plug in
some lights, and...
- My wife.
- Yeah.
The one.
I'm so sorry.
I never meant
for any of this to happen.
Our house was on fire.
I'm going to fix it.
I promise.
And the house.
Or we'll build a new house,
and we'll live just
like the fairy tale says.
My wife.
Move over, you.
♪ ♪
[Meyer]
Have you seen his billboards?
"A hard man for hard times."
Meanwhile, he refuses
to enforce the basic law,
which... [scoffs]
can you still call him a lawman
if he skips that part
of his job?
Maybe he loses the election,
and the whole thing goes away.
Arrest him then, you're saying?
As a private citizen?
No, I'm saying wash our hands.
Good riddance.
Oh, so more like
a dysfunctional family
than a federal law
enforcement agency.
Smile and pretend
Daddy didn't touch our pee-pees
- when we were kids?
- [clears throat]
- What?
- Weapons are missing, sir.
Tactical equipment.
We think he bought them
for his department,
and then gave them
to his friends in the militia.
- Odin Little.
- You think.
[Meyer]
We had an informant, but he disappeared.
[Joaquin]
A lot of people disappear around this guy,
including two of his wives.
Just put one of his deputies
in the ground yesterday.
Local coroner said car crash,
but they had him buried
in less than 12 hours,
so... [laughs]
Don't tell me
you want to dig him up.
No. What we want to do
is increase the pressure.
Send a message: respect
the rule of law, or else.
In 1958,
the Chinese went to war
with the sparrow.
- Sir?
- Mao gave the order.
The birds were eating
the people's seeds and grain.
They had to go.
So people all over the country
started beating on pots and pans
to drive the birds mad.
Death by exhaustion.
Two billion sparrows exterminated,
all praised a great leader.
But do you know what happens
when you remove birds
from a food chain?
There's no one left to eat
the bugs and the locust.
So instead of
solving a hunger problem,
they end up creating
an even bigger one.
You ever heard of
the Great Famine?
Possibly 50 million Chinese
starving to death.
- Sir...
- One step ahead.
I'm not asking you
to play four-dimensional chess.
I'm saying think one step ahead.
If we go to war
with the most powerful sheriff
in North Dakota, whose fathers
and grandfathers were sheriffs,
and who's connected
to the most powerful militia
in the upper Midwest,
what do you think happens next?
Until you can answer
that question,
I want you to make Roy Tillman
more like a hobby of yours,
something you do
in your spare time
when you're not punishing
the actual criminals.
[Joaquin]
You're on his side.
[phone chimes]
We're done here.
Thank you for your time, sir.
- [chuckles] A hobby?
- Tony.
- I mean, can you believe this guy?
- They found her.
It's the bulwark.
We're the bulwark.
It's in the Constitution.
I mean, he should...
he should read it maybe,
you know?
Like,
it's-it's the justice system.
It's a system of justice.
You know, not like
just one man on a horse.
- Tony.
- What?
[chuckles] They found her.
Nadine. The second wife.
We just got a hit
on her fingerprints.
Living in Minnesota
under a different name.
Dorothy Lyon.
Feels like fate, right?
- Hobby my ass.
- Ah.
♪ ♪
[Munch]
When Munch was a boy...
...freedom was a potato.
It was you didn't get killed today.
Freedom from hunger,
from the rusty blade.
But to free himself,
the man ate first
so others could not.
He killed before he was killed.
He wanted nothing more,
because only kings...
...had the freedom to want.
But now everywhere you look,
you see kings.
Everything they want,
they call their own,
and if they cannot have it,
they say that they are not free.
They even pretend
their freedom should be free,
that it has no cost,
but the cost is always...
...death.
Life for life.
Me...
...or you.
Please.
I don't understand.
Why are you here?
What do you want?
♪ ♪
Pancakes.
[dog barking in distance]
What happened?
Boogeyman came, left a warning
in the kids' room.
- Who, Munch?
- [Bowman] I don't know his name.
Full-on wild man, though.
Creature from the Black Lagoon.
Where's Roy?
No funny business this time.
Got some groceries, then.
[sighs]
Joshua.
What?
[Roy]
"Now, after the death of Moses
"the servant of the Lord,
it came to pass,
"that the Lord spake
unto Joshua,
"the son of Nun,
Moses' minister,
"saying,
'Moses my servant is dead;
"now therefore arise,
go over this Jordan,
"thou, and all these people,
unto the land
"which I do give to them,
even to the children
of Israel.'"
Joshua.
[sighs]
What the fuck you talking about?
Did you tend to your man
like I said?
Make him feel respected?
Nobody asked you to come here.
See, there were 12 spies
of Israel,
sent to scout
the Land of Canaan.
Joshua was one of the good ones.
Are you one of the good ones,
Joshua?
I tried.
My great grandfather's name
was Roy, Indian killer,
fought in the battle of
Big Mound, Dead Buffalo Lake.
Lost an ear
in the Battle of the Badlands.
He's the only American to ever
earn four Medals of Honor.
Now, he was one of
the good ones.
Me, I try to be.
You... not so much, I think.
You're what we call
a waste of skin.
Defective.
Eating our food,
breathing our air,
wasting precious resources.
Yeah, keep talking,
see what happens.
See, now your beta male thinks
that having a firearm
makes him an alpha,
but it's just lipstick
on a pig, you feel me?
You don't know
when to fucking quit, do you?
Babe, don't.
♪ ♪
A man threatened my children
last night.
Came to my house,
face painted like an Apache.
Maybe it wasn't a man.
Some-some kind of spirit.
My point is, this... you...
Like a paper airplane
in the rain.
♪ ♪
Fuck it.
[gurgling, choking]
[gasping]
Fucking hell.
[gasping, gurgling]
You okay?
Can I get a glass of water?
Lenore?
[water running]
[Gator]
Uh... Dad?
Uh, what are we doing?
Oh, did you get her?
- Um...
- Don't bother, I can see it all over your face.
Worked you over pretty good,
did she?
Uh, Lenore.
Dad, that Nadine, it's...
I don't know.
It's like he said,
some kind of tiger.
The husband got hurt.
House caught on fire.
Not now.
Um, we got Munch.
You did?
Got him right there
on the couch.
The guy
from the filling station.
The cop killer.
Tip came in over the hotline.
Lenore here called it in
herself, didn't you, Lenore?
[shakily] I...
Husband came home bragging
he killed a state trooper,
wounded another one,
I responded.
Shots fired.
You were my backup.
- So...
- Loop's closed, I'm saying.
States can call off their dogs,
and we're free to settle
our differences in private.
Huh.
Now, all I need to know from you
is that you see
how this helps you.
No more black eyes
and broken bones.
Cash in your pocket every month,
'cause Roy Tillman
never forgets a friend.
And we're friends,
aren't we, darling?
Y-Yes, Roy.
Attagirl.
[exhales]
♪ ♪
Think I'll go for a ride,
clear my head.
All right, buddy, let's go.
Come on. [clicks tongue]
Come on, hon, let's go.
♪ ♪
[engine starts, revs]
[man]
Now I get it.
[rooster crows]
[roars]