[wind blowing]
[Gator coughs]
[whimpers]
[grunts]
[groaning]
Uh...
[faint voices in distance]
Oh! [groans]
[moans]
[groans]
[panting]
Oh...
[crying]
[sniffs]
[gasps]
[metallic clanging]
♪ ♪
[Gator sobs]
Uh...
[sobs]
- [guns click]
- [dog barking]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[grunts]
[sniffles]
[spits]
♪ ♪
[horse whinnies]
[panting]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[Docherty over comms]
Alpha team is moving.
[indistinct radio chatter]
[wind whooshing]
[creak]
♪ ♪
[groans, gasps]
[sobs quietly]
♪ ♪
[indistinct voices calling]
[Gator shouts weakly]
[sighs]
I love these moments.
You see a man in a dress
come through here?
Haircut like The Three Stooges?
When the violence comes,
it comes fast, and it's over.
You can never really be sure.
Did I draw first? Or did he?
Shouldn't you be out
on the line, inspiring the men?
It's your goat-fuck.
I saw Karen.
Yeah, well, she should've
pulled the trigger.
What can I say? She's soft.
Maybe that's why
you haven't killed her yet.
Not today, old man.
And then there's why
number two's still breathing.
And how come your son
is such a fuckup?
- Weak.
- All right, go ahead.
Take your dentures out,
so I don't break them.
See, that's your problem.
[sighs]
No respect for your elders.
[chuckles] Well,
you'll be calling me "professor"
by the time I get finished
teaching you a lesson.
[gurgles]
What's that?
- [choking]
- I-I can't quite hear you there,
Professor.
Rot in hell, you piece of shit.
[Karen]
Daddy?
Goddamn it.
I swear to God,
if I got to chase you, woman...
[grunts]
- That's her. Go.
- [Sykes] Weapons free.
[Roy grunts]
[grunts, sputters]
Just give us a minute.
Just give me a minute.
[panting]
[laughs]
Come on.
Give us a kiss.
[FBI agent]
FBI!
Drop your weapon.
Drop your weapon!
What? No! The hostage.
I'm the hostage!
♪ ♪
No!
[Witt shouts indistinctly]
[indistinct shouting]
[gunfire continues]
Oh, he's gone. [pants]
[Witt]
Stay down.
- I got to get him.
- No.
[gunfire continues]
I got him.
♪ ♪
[gunfire continues]
[panicked breathing]
♪ ♪
[gasps]
Whoops.
Drop the knife.
What knife?
Geez. I guess somebody
can't take a joke.
Not a joke.
Next one goes in your mouth.
Now drop it.
Make me.
- This is Witt Farr.
- Belly shot, can you believe it?
- By a female.
- I am underground
- with the suspect.
- Oh, this can't be happening.
- Shut up. There's an entrance...
- I am an emissary of the Lord.
...on the southeast slope,
by a tree... Stop.
Son, my destiny is at
the other end of that tunnel.
I'm not your son.
Now drop the knife.
[sighs]
- [grunts]
- [gun clatters on floor]
[groaning]
There it is.
Don't fight it, son.
It's all over now.
[labored breathing]
[exhales]
♪ ♪
[indistinct radio chatter]
Where is he?
Did he get him? Huh?
♪ ♪
[grunts]
[grunts, exhales]
Come on, kid.
Almost there.
[grunting]
Your son gave you up,
by the way.
[grunting]
[shouts]
I told you, I'm fine.
I just need to call my daughter.
- I need to get home.
- [Gator] Nadine?
Gator.
Nadine.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's over now.
[sniffling]
Did you really see my mom?
No, hon.
I thought I did.
But she was just
a beautiful angel in a dream.
Would you...
...come visit me...
...in jail?
With cookies.
You still like oatmeal raisin?
[Meyer]
Mrs. Lyon?
I spoke to your husband.
He knows you're okay.
Thank you.
He worries so much.
[chuckles]
Could you help me?
I need to find...
I need to find my trooper,
Witt Farr,
just to thank him.
Oh.
♪ ♪
[driver]
Almost home.
♪ ♪
[vehicle approaching]
[laughs]
Come here. My baby.
[squeals] Hi.
[sighs]
Let me look at you.
My beautiful girl.
So, you're okay, then.
Yeah.
I... I just got the download.
Shot him in the stomach,
they said, which...
...that's my girl.
There, there.
Okeydoke.
Good for you.
[pats on arm]
♪ ♪
[sighs]
Something about anniversaries.
You want to do the flowers?
Go on.
I can't believe I never asked.
Was he married?
No. Just a cat named Lucky.
Mine, now.
His mother came to the funeral,
brought his six sisters.
Can you imagine?
No wonder he was so nice.
I want six sisters.
Oh.
How about we start
with one, hmm?
I like the new ads.
You and Wayne together.
Oh, yeah. We're moguls now.
Opening a new location
in Saint Paul.
Wayne's the people person,
so he does sales.
I'm more back-of-the-house, strategy.
- Ah, perfect. [laughs]
- Yeah.
Well, I got to go meet
your mother-in-law.
Some business to take care of.
Sure.
And Wayne's making chili,
so we better...
Hopefully see you soon?
- Oh, yeah. You will.
- Okay.
Shoot.
We got to pick up
sour cream for Dad.
Can I get M&M's?
- Only if you drive.
- [chuckles]
♪ ♪
[Scotty]
I'd actually like to drive.
[Dot] Oh, you would,
would you? Not today.
Not on my watch.
But the M&M's...
I think that we can do.
[conversation continues quietly]
♪ ♪
[indistinct P.A. announcement]
- [buzzer sounds]
- [latch clicks]
[buzzer sounds]
I love that color on you.
You know what I'd love
to see on you?
- A noose.
- [Indira] Hey.
Watch your mouth, convict.
She wouldn't last five minutes
in here, that one.
Too many principles.
But you...
you'd be queen shit.
I saw you filed for an appeal.
That was a mistake.
Please. That whole thing
was rigged.
- Your so-called trial.
- [Lorraine] You should know
I'm the single largest donor
to the Federalist Society.
Oh, yeah? What do they do?
Something with books?
They control the courts,
selecting judges all the way up
to the Supreme Court,
with the president's blessing.
So... [sighs]
...buy a throw pillow
is my advice.
- You're gonna be here a while.
- [Roy] It's funny.
Prison is the way
the world should be.
The natural order.
No apology.
Men separated by race.
Races stacked
with the strong on top.
You fuck the weak,
you kill your rivals,
sleep with one eye open.
Yes. Well, I just came by to say
I hope you've settled in,
because now your real punishment
will begin.
My what?
Wait outside, please.
- Are you sure?
- Oh, we'll be fine, won't we, Roy?
Peachy.
- [buzzer sounds]
- [door opens]
You're right.
She does have principles.
[sighs]
Where was I?
Oh, yes, punishment.
Did you know that 85%
of all prisoners are in debt?
Hundreds, if not thousands
of dollars, interest accruing,
their families put out
on the street.
Well, I've started a fund
to help certain prisoners
free themselves
from this burden.
A private fund.
Plus a little fresh cash
each month
in their commissary accounts.
Vaseline,
Vienna sausages,
that kind of thing.
Which prisoners?
[smacks lips] Oh...
That one, I think.
And him over there
with the scars.
Oh. [claps]
And all of the men
on cell block D
and B and A.
Well, that's mighty Christian
of you.
Oh, no. This has nothing to do
with that book.
It's an older text,
written on stone tablets
in the Age of the Skull Fuckers.
Did Nadine put you up to this?
Please. She's a Girl Scout.
I fight my own battles,
and you need to pay
for what you've taken.
- So you want me dead.
- No.
I want you alive
for a very, very long time.
But while you live,
I want you to feel everything
your wives felt,
every blow,
each humiliation...
Fear.
I'm not afraid of you.
It's not me you need
to be afraid of.
These might come in handy.
- [buzzer sound]
- [latch clicks]
♪ ♪
- Hiya, hon.
- [Wayne] Hey.
[Dot]
Oh, it smells good in here.
- Yeah.
- [Dot] Oh, yeah.
We got the sour cream.
And...
...they had that
sharp cheddar that you like.
[Wayne]
Mm.
[grunts]
Okay.
Hon?
[Wayne]
Hi, hon. Uh...
Yeah, the, uh,
chili's on the stove,
and then this fella
just came to the door,
said he, uh, knows ya.
Sure.
- Ya.
What are you doing here?
A man frees a tiger...
...so the tiger
can finish her fight.
This does not mean the man
is finished with her.
Well, we-we saw a tiger once,
at the Minneapolis Zoo.
D'you know you can,
uh, hear them roar
from, what, two miles away?
And they're good swimmers.
- And they're good swimmers.
- Wayne.
And, you know, they run,
like, 40 miles an hour, so...
Wayne.
So, I don't think
I, uh, got your name.
It's Moonk.
Oola Moonk.
Well, I'm Wayne, so, uh...
And that's Scotty, so, yeah.
You want a pop?
I want a pop.
Would you take these
over to Dad, hon?
Thank you.
We will finish
our engagement now.
I thought we were done.
You said...
The debt must be paid.
A man's flesh was taken.
Now a pound is required
in return.
[Wayne]
There you go.
The man is grateful.
So, are you from, uh,
you from around here?
Across the sea.
But here a long time.
From the age
of the carrier pigeon
and the 600 tribes.
The Arapaho,
the Cree and the Tonkawa.
A man comes,
never having seen a mountain.
He cannot remember
the year of his birth.
He is paid to soldier.
But one night,
he wanders from his post,
drawn by the songs of the river.
Well, Scotty's
grandfather took us
to the Vermillion last year.
My-my dad Wink, well,
he's a big fly fisherman.
- Remember that, hon?
- I caught a cold.
Yeah.
Yeah, she did.
It's-it's kind of funny.
Why?
Why must debt be paid?
I understand keeping a promise.
But people always say
debt must be paid.
Except what if you can't?
If you're too poor
or you lose your job.
Maybe there's a death
in the family.
Isn't the better thing,
the more humane thing,
to say the debt
should be forgiven?
Isn't that who we should be?
Oh, game's on at seven.
Probably time
to make the biscuits.
You know what?
You're right.
- It's not chili without biscuits.
- [Wayne] No.
[Dot chuckles quietly]
How about you two
go set the table, huh?
Oh?
Well, I was thinking chopsticks.
- For chili?
- [laughs]
Come on.
Whatever it is
you think you came here for...
...we're halfway to supper.
And it's a school night.
So either you wash your hands
and you help,
or we do this another time.
[Scotty]
Can I have chocolate milk?
[Dot]
What? You just had M&Ms, so...
[indistinct chatter]
♪ ♪
I wasn't supposed to tell Dad.
Sorry. [laughs]
[indistinct conversation
continuing]
[Dot] You ever made
drop biscuits before?
They're mostly
for when you're in a hurry.
But we maybe like 'em
more than the all-day kind.
- Oh, hon.
- Hmm?
Would you mind helping
Mr. Moonk with his coat?
[Wayne]
Oh, sure.
Yeah, sorry about that.
- [grunts softly]
- All right.
- Mama?
- Ya?
You know what I learned today?
Chimpanzees can learn to drive.
No way.
Did you know that?
Didn't know that.
- Wow.
- A man...
[Wayne]
You know, I was thinking
- has a code.
- I might have a beer. What do you think?
- Let's do it.
- He has a code, and the code...
You're in the way.
[sighs]
The code is ev...
- [Wayne] Here you go.
- [Dot] Thanks, hon.
[Wayne]
Ya.
Okay, so, I'm gonna
tell you a little secret.
It says to use water,
but I use milk.
Even better...
...buttermilk.
So, go ahead
and measure out a cup.
This one's a cup.
Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
Pour it in there.
Okay. Then...
you add just a little honey.
I'm assuming he paid you
to come here...
Roy...
and do what you did.
Maybe you're feeling
sideways about it,
'cause of what it cost you.
A partner.
An ear.
You go ahead, stir.
You took a job
that had a risk to it.
You got hurt.
You can't be mad at the risk.
That'd be like
getting mad at the table
you stubbed your toe on.
I might have gone
over the deep end on the spices.
[Dot]
I know you had a mom back there,
across the sea.
And she loved you.
If someone came for her,
don't you think
she would've done
whatever it took
to get back to you?
You say that as if
life is a circle,
but it's a line.
Mother is the start.
This is the other side.
Well, I don't know
what that means.
What I'm saying
is it's a choice.
You made a choice.
[Scotty]
Bless us, Oh Lord,
and these thy gifts,
which we are about to receive
through Thy bounty,
through Christ our Lord,
we pray.
[Lyons]
Amen.
[Wayne] Hmm. All
right, hon, would you, uh,
pass, uh, Mr. Moonk's bowl?
Honey.
Ah. Thank you.
Well, personally,
I never been across the sea.
[Dot]
Nope.
By long boat we came.
Three dozen men
pulling at the oars.
The rain so heavy,
some drown in their seats.
Geez.
First in forest,
then on grassland.
The man's hair grew long.
He rode the horse
without saddle or reins,
and the people of the plains...
...were his people.
But then came
the cannon and the musket,
and he was alone once more.
For a century
he spoke to no one.
[Wayne]
Hmm.
I don't know if I could
go an hour without talking.
[chuckles softly]
- Daddy does sales.
- [Wayne] Yeah.
- Daddy likes talking.
- [laughter] - A lot.
- [Dot] Yeah.
I, uh...
You ever drive a Kia, Mr. Moonk?
It's like flying a cloud.
I think we should see how
your biscuits turned out, huh?
Before the boat,
the man lived on the moors...
...and ate fleas
from the rats.
He was frightened all the time.
Then one day,
a man comes on a wealthy horse
and offers him
two coins
and a meal.
But the food
was not food.
What was it?
It was sin.
The sins of the rich.
Greed, envy, disgust.
They were bitter...
the sins.
But he ate them all,
for he was starving.
From then on,
the man does not sleep
or grow old.
He cannot die.
He has no dreams.
All that is left...
...is sin.
It feels like that, I know.
What they do to us,
make us swallow.
Like it's our fault.
But you want to know the cure?
You got to eat something
made with love and joy.
♪ ♪
And be forgiven.
[soft chuckle]
♪ ♪
[exhales]
[short sob]
♪ ♪
[man]
Now I get it.
[rooster crows]
[roars]