Previously on Prison Break:
Sona's a one-way street.
What goes in never comes out.
They got me and Sara.
L.J. and Sara will be traded
for Whistler. Are we clear?
I'll tell you the plan
when you tell me who you are.
- I'm a fisherman.
- Really?
My life is in your hands.
How's L.J.? How's Sara?
She's dead, Michael. I lied to you.
You are breaking out of this prison,
Mr. Scofield.
You're taking me with you.
Four more days. If I'm out of here
by then, I can still do it.
There have been two escape
attempts in the past two days.
Say goodbye to Sona, Mr. Scofield.
My predecessor, Colonel Escamilla,
wasn't an effective leader.
He's been replaced.
I am General Zavala. Sit.
A drink of water?
With due respect, general, I had nothing
to do with what happened here today.
I always conduct
a thorough investigation...
...and there are too many
unanswered questions here.
It is my job to find those answers.
If you help me do my job, I'll help you.
The helicopters.
You couldn't be responsible for that. You
weren't flying a helicopter, were you?
- No.
- Who was?
- I don't know. No.
- You know who sent them?
Again, be advised:
Telling the truth is in your best interest.
I am.
Let's go for a walk.
I understand your fears.
But the Republic of Panama
cannot allow this sort of activity.
If you wish to talk, now's the time.
I would,
if there is anything left to say.
Then you give me no choice.
This way.
This isn't good.
They're putting him in the hot box.
Things are gonna get much harder
for you.
There's no way to win.
You must cooperate.
Confess to this escape
and face your punishment by law...
...or face a far greater punishment
in the Panama sun.
It's up to you.
It's done. It's finished.
I hope my brother's all right.
- Does it hurt?
- It's fine.
I need to get to the prison.
I was watching the news
in the waiting room.
They identified a few bodies,
but it wasn't them.
I'll find out when I get there.
You wanna come?
I don't know. After everything that's
happened, I don't know what to think.
What is there to think about?
James has an answer for everything.
Nothing makes sense.
Stop asking questions
and just look at the facts.
I wanted to believe everything
he was saying.
- And I still want him to get out.
- I want him out as well.
Trust me, I've been working on this
every single day.
Lincoln, I really appreciate
everything you have done.
You saved my life.
You didn't have to help me like that.
Yeah, I did.
- Get in the car.
- Come on.
Everywhere I go, there you are.
Go home, Sofia.
Part of me wanted
to drive right past this gate, Alex.
You don't deserve to be here.
Actually, if you take all things
into consideration, I do.
- Thank you.
- Wait.
Don't.
My father worked in the mine
for 30 years.
He took this into work with him
every day.
Kept him safe till the day he retired.
Then he gave it to me.
I can't take this.
Give it back when you get out.
- Take care of yourself, Alex.
- Yeah.
You ain't got the guts
to do it yourself?
Hey, this is for you, so shut up
before I change my mind.
After yesterday,
you may be doubting my ability...
...to make good on our agreement.
I need to keep you motivated.
You have one minute.
L.J., oh, God. Thank God you're alive.
Forget it. There's nothing you can do.
- There's always something.
- Dad.
These guys are thorough.
They follow you everywhere.
Trust me.
That bitch is crazy.
She cut Sara's head off. I was there.
I closed my eyes, but I heard it.
You listen to me. I'm not gonna let
anything happen to you, all right?
The next time you see me,
don't take your eyes off me.
I'll tell you what to do, all right?
Minute's up.
Me and your uncle,
we know what we're doing.
We're gonna get you out of this, okay?
- I love you.
- Yeah, I love you too.
Looks like things didn't go so well.
You should be gone.
So should you.
What happened?
It's still happening.
I feel bad for Michael,
but we have a way without him.
- You should get some rest.
- What's the way?
I'll rest, I'll rest. I'll rest when I'm out.
I won't go without you.
You have my word.
Now get some rest.
You see Scofield
out in that redneck sauna?
Let's see if he has the tattoo
to get out of that.
You were in on it, right?
I see you guys lurking around Lechero's.
Scofield's gotta have a plan to escape.
If so, I know none of it.
Yeah, I bet you don't.
Whoa. Too many cocktails
out on the Lido deck.
Here comes trouble.
Señor Criada.
- Clean it up.
- Yeah, I'll get right on that.
Did you not hear what I said?
I told you to do something, now do it.
Cleaning up chunks
ain't in my job description anymore.
Things change.
You have to answer to us now.
Hey, caveman, you don't scare me.
Go bug someone else.
Oh.
Jorge.
I have a special delivery.
I need it to get in real quick.
- How much?
- I gave you 10 grand.
Ten grand's for the last one.
How much for this one?
- No grand.
- Then, no, thanks.
No, no, no.
- Take this water to the prisoner.
- Why should I? He doesn't deserve it.
I'll do it.
Hi, brother. Remember me?
This isn't gonna work.
Come on, papi, drink this.
You can't let anything
happen to L.J., okay?
It's okay. He's doing much better
than you. Come on.
Drink this. You need it.
I'm sorry about Sara.
I'm gonna try to sneak more
into the prison next time, okay?
- I want you to quit.
- I can't.
- We all have to quit sometime.
- Well, I'm not gonna.
You're in a chicken coop.
You need all the help you can get.
- I don't. Just go, don't come back.
- Not after everything you've done for me.
Go.
I see you tried
to catch a flight out yesterday.
- I did what I had to do.
- But you went back on our deal.
I was saving my ass. I'm sure
you're familiar with the strategy.
Now, you watch it. I'm still boss here.
Who cares about who's boss?
Do you wanna get out of here
or do you wanna keep talking about it?
It's okay. We just need to brace it.
No. We need the engineer.
Move it.
Get out of here
before Sammy gets back.
Ninety-eight degrees in the shade,
125 in the box.
Let's go inside. We'll have a chat
in the air conditioning.
Tomorrow's gonna be hotter,
and the next day even hotter.
The day after that, you'll be dead.
You don't understand.
If I thought you could help me...
I can.
You're unaware of the influence
I have in this province.
You'd rather I be your ally
than your enemy, wouldn't you?
You don't know these people.
We can't stop them.
Not you. Not me.
There was a man.
A drug kingpin.
The most powerful man in Panama.
A ruthless killer with an army of thugs
and thieves behind him.
He killed judges, policemen,
anyone who stood in his way.
They said he couldn't be stopped.
But now, Lechero is in prison
and I'm in power.
I decide whose life is at stake,
and right now, it's yours.
From the moment I got here...
...I've been planning my escape.
He's talking.
How do you know?
You can't get out of the box
any other way.
The people who sent the helicopters...
...they're the same people who
framed my brother back in the U.S.
The same people
who wanted me here in Sona.
In order for you
to break out another inmate?
- Yes.
- Who are these people?
I don't know.
But they have my brother's son.
They like to keep collateral.
I could be putting his life in danger
as we speak.
If what you told me is true...
...you would be saving him.
I would call my troops and order
a search for the boy immediately.
But this story?
- It's fiction.
- It's true.
It's what you wanted.
It's the only thing I have left to give.
Please.
His name is L.J.
He's only 16 years old.
- What's that smell?
- They're Armandos.
- These things cost money.
- Somebody gave them to me.
- I don't smoke.
- Who?
This guy. I ran some stuff
into the prison for him.
- You ran stuff into the prison? Drugs?
- Who cares? He paid me.
- You should've quit that job--
- I know, I know.
I need some cash for my kid.
Maricruz doesn't have insurance.
Listen, I just saw Michael.
- He's in solitary confinement.
- What?
They put him in a box out in the yard
all by himself.
He can't do anything.
It's gonna be okay.
It's not gonna be okay.
I don't know what to do, man.
Everything's just falling apart.
What you looking at?
The view.
I can't help but notice
you and Lechero made friends.
He's been hanging out
with a lot of white boys lately.
- Got a problem with that?
- No, but Sammy does.
See, I've been looking close,
like I always do...
...and I know
you all would be a lot better off...
...if Sammy were no longer around.
Wouldn't have to worry about his snout
poking in your business.
- You're suggesting?
- You and I know it needs to happen.
Aren't many men
that would take on Sammy.
I have one particular man in mind.
A man who owes me.
But if I pull through, I'm in the club,
guaranteed. You're gonna see to it.
Heh-heh. All right.
I assume you have the power
to make this deal?
I do. Agreed.
Right. Well, thank you, sir.
Look, I've been thinking
about what you told me.
- But I can't quit my job.
- Do whatever you wanna do.
I would if you kick me a few bucks.
Again?
I told you, I don't have any cash.
- What do you expect me to do?
- Do what you want.
- You could use my help.
- Charging me for your friendship?
- I got a kid on the way.
- I got a kid I may never see again.
Yeah, get me Gretchen.
Much to my surprise, there seems to
be some degree of truth to your tale.
- Everything I told you is true.
- That's for me to determine.
- What more can I say?
- This inmate...
...the one you've been sent to free...
...he should be able to verify
what you told me.
He should, but I don't know if he will.
Tell me his name.
They won't hesitate to kill my nephew.
I need to know you can find him.
- I will, but I need a name.
- I need your word.
You have it, I'll find the boy.
Now, the name.
Hi.
What's wrong?
Why don't you tell me?
I went to that apartment,
your apartment.
And this woman showed up,
like she knew you.
And then I found a passport.
Who's Gary Miller?
That apartment, that passport...
...it's all for us.
It's how we're gonna get away.
I've been working on a way
for us to be together.
Remember how we always talked
about France?
Oh, James. Yeah. Heh.
Our plan to be together.
James, how can I believe you?
How can I believe anything anymore?
Whistler. Come.
Just know-- Just know that I love you.
You are facing some serious charges.
Michael Scofield told me
there are some people out there...
...who are very determined
to get you out of here.
What's he talking about?
- You know nothing about this?
- No.
Scofield's a smart man, but...
...he's got a rabid imagination.
So you're calling him a liar?
More or less.
I've been able to verify the story.
I already know everything,
Mr. Whistler, in detail.
I just need a name.
Who's in charge on the outside?
We can end this right now
if you can provide it.
What are you talking about?
What's going on here?
Now, start over.
- Hey.
- There you are.
And here I am
without my bag of goodies.
I was afraid you was gone for good.
The party would not be the same
without you.
I'm glad you're back,
because I need a favor.
It involves you, a chicken foot
and a man who's got it coming.
- What man?
- Sammy.
When you get well, you get him out in
that ring and you do that one...
...neck thing.
In exchange, I'm gonna cover
all your medical expenses.
I tell you what, you take your time.
I'm gonna go get my bag right now
and get you out of this misery.
You're the best cock in the fight, Alex.
Please don't let me down.
Maybe now you'll feel more
comfortable telling me the truth.
Are you working with Scofield?
- Are you working with Scofield?
- Yes, yes, I'm working with Scofield.
But there's no one else involved.
As they say in America,
we're gonna get the story straight.
I told them the truth.
I suggest you do the same.
- I have.
- He's confirmed nothing.
Ask him about that woman
he's been meeting with.
Huh?
It's not what you think.
It matters what you know,
and you know her name.
The fact that he won't admit it tells me
that he's no innocent bystander in this.
- You know I am.
- Prove it.
- That's the only way we're getting out.
- Michael, this is suicide.
They'll kill Sofia
and they'll kill your brother's son.
This is the man who can help. He can't
do anything without a name, so tell him!
James, we don't have a choice.
It's over.
Gretchen Morgan.
I don't know where she lives.
I don't know how you find her.
That's all I know, her name.
Gretchen Morgan.
- Two more of those, please.
- Mm-mm. Uh-uh.
- I'm gonna get going.
- No, he'll stay.
Relax. Fernando, is it?
Just wanna talk a minute. Alone.
This right here...
is as alone as we're gonna get.
I heard about your argument
with Lincoln.
You people are everywhere, huh?
Now, you know him better than I do.
But from personal experience,
Burrows can be hard to handle.
That man does not like
to be told what to do.
He sure likes
bossing everyone else around.
You have to start looking out
for yourself, Fernando.
Level the playing field.
All you have to do is go back,
apologize.
Tell him that you'll stay on
a few more days for free.
Tomorrow or the day after,
I'll call, meet me for a drink.
In exchange, I'll pay.
Fifty grand.
I know what you're thinking.
I'm not asking you to do anything
that doesn't help everyone.
I don't see this helping.
Lincoln causes as many problems
as he solves.
He needs to get out of his own way
and I think you can assist him.
I stay one step ahead
and you get 50 grand.
I don't know.
I think you do.
Where do I find this Gretchen Morgan?
She's somewhere in Panama City.
That's not much help
in a city of a million people.
- It would take days, weeks.
- I've told you, I only know her name.
- I have no idea.
- I do.
But I'll need to use a phone.
- Linc?
- Michael.
What phone are you on?
Just listen to me.
I need to know where and when
your next meeting with Susan B. is.
Garfield Price building downtown,
in an hour. Why?
Garfield Price. One hour.
- You can give her a message for me?
- Yeah.
Tell her everything's going as planned.
What's going on?
Why are you in solitary--?
Just give her the message, Linc.
I'll see you soon.
You should've listened.
Are you gonna throw down
a chicken foot over a puddle of puke?
You should've mopped.
Stumpy, wait your turn, man.
Excuse me. I wanted to see
Patron Lechero, por favor.
What you wanna see him about?
I got one of these from him,
and I didn't do nothing.
He don't listen.
The fight goes on as planned
after we eat lunch.
Sammy.
You issue a fight?
Yeah, what about it?
It's not your right. It's not your place.
Well, maybe it should be.
She's arrived. I'm on my way.
You better be right.
What happened?
- It worked.
- It did?
Yeah, she came up to me,
just like you said.
Offered me cash
to talk behind your back.
- So we stick to the plan, right? Cool.
- Yeah.
I'm gonna go and see her right now.
It's okay. I came back for you.
Come on, now.
Everything's gonna be okay.
You can't deprive yourself like this.
Get-- Get out of here.
You don't mean that.
- Yeah, yeah. I do, I do.
- You're not talking straight.
You're not talking straight.
Withdrawals are the worst way to die.
You're gonna shake and sweat
until you evaporate into nothing.
A long road into hell.
Is that what you want, Alex?
Or do you wanna live?
I'll see you on the other side.
When you're up all night...
...and diarrhea is running down both
your legs and vomit is in your hair...
...don't come crawling back.
It's been a long day.
Let's just get this over with.
I got a message from my brother.
Everything's going ahead as planned.
Really? Well, I'd think
he'd be facing a major setback.
You know Michael,
always has things worked out.
I don't. Seems to me
he keeps screwing things up.
He's getting things done
faster than you.
Now, Whistler's out by tomorrow,
right?
- Gretchen Morgan?
- Yes.
General Zavala,
Panamanian National Police.
- Come with us, please.
- Why? What's this all about?
No, I don't understand. Wait.
I had nothing to do with this.
I had nothing to do with this. Nothing.
You're denying that you were involved
in the escape attempts at Sona Prison?
I have never been here before
in my life.
- You've never met any of the men here?
- No.
James Whistler?
- You know what I've been told?
From prisoners? I can only imagine.
I've been told that you're
the mastermind behind a prison escape.
And that you've kidnapped
a boy as collateral.
Really? Am I an alien?
Did I shoot JFK?
Sir, I have no idea
who this James Wilson--
- Whistler.
- ...is.
I am just here to relax...
...before I have to go back
to another year...
...of teaching social studies
to freshman idiots.
You're a tourist here?
No, not a tourist, sir.
I like to think of myself
as a student of life.
A student of life?
What did he say?
"Turn on the hose."
Fight, fight, fight.
I'm gonna give you one chance.
Did you order the escape
from Sona Penitentiary?
Yes or no?
You seem concerned for her.
She holds our entire future
in her hands. Yeah, I'm concerned.
Yes or no?
No.
You proved one thing.
This is not your first time.
Come with me.
Do you know either of these men?
- I've never seen them before.
- That's a lie.
- Never seen them before in my life.
- Where and when have you seen her?
She came to see him in visitation.
Isn't that right?
Is this the woman you work for?
Did she order the prison escape?
Yes or no?
Yes.
All right. All right.
- You're the one in charge?
- No.
I don't know anything
about a prison escape.
I'm just the babysitter.
I watch the kid.
Where is he?
Near Paloma. Highway 2.
I can take you.
Take them back to my office.
Put the girl back in the car.
We're going on a drive.
Was it you?
Did you kill Sara?
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
I'm coming for you.
Yeah!
Congratulations.
You's a regular Buster Douglas,
aren't you?
Hey, what is this?
How'd you get that up there, huh?
Mm-hm.
Right there. The boy's in there.
- In here?
- I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I hope he's all right.
Pick me up. I'm at the shack.
Bring towels.
Hi, Lincoln.
Augusto.
Good to see you.
Yeah, thanks for the cigars.
You didn't open the package?
I'll get around to it today.
You need to make a choice.
Lechero's days are numbered.
You agree?
Then you know what you need to do.
You've done a good job so far.
Now is the time to make a move.
Prove yourself.
Go back in and open the package.
Come on. Let's go.
What happened to the general?
The general was found dead
this morning off Highway 2.
You're going back inside.
I'm sorry to hear that.
He seemed like a nice man.
What are you doing back here?
If you still wanna get out of here,
I need your phone.
Go inside.
- What?
- How's L.J.?
He's fine, but you know what?
Susan's not.
He's fine? You're sure?
Yeah, I just got off the phone
with him.
Why didn't you tell me
what's going on?
He could've died
because of what you did.
We've still got Whistler.
As long as we do, we're good.
I gotta go.
Hey, did you see blanco?
He's walking around like the landlord.
You said Lechero would take care of it.
- He will.
- How long has he been saying that?
If you and Lechero wanna go around like
an old couple fighting this way or that...
- ...maybe you'd like it in the kitchen.
- You be careful--
Then do something.
Or the next thing you know you're
gonna be taking orders from Scofield.
Some people will stop at nothing, huh?
Uh--
Yeah, I know.
At least we're back inside.
Which, of course, is exactly
what you wanted, isn't it?
- What are you talking about?
- You let the fox into the henhouse.
Only reason you gave up
Gretchen's name...
...was so she could pull you out
of the fire.
You wanted me to give up her name.
- You know it doesn't end with her?
- Yeah, I do.
The question is, how do you?
How does a simple fisherman seem
to know so much about the Company?
When she comes back, and she will...
...what am I gonna say?
Are you gonna do this or not?
You can tell her the answer is yes.
But once we're out,
I consider you collateral.
Nothing more.