Previously on Prison Break:
It's known as a one-way
street. What goes in never comes out.
Since the riots,
they left us here to rot.
They figured we would just destroy
ourselves. But instead, we've thrived.
How about we work together?
Help each other out.
You're on your own.
Get me out of this.
You wanna know where she is?
Maricruz. Maricruz.
We can assist you, should you
ever decide to, say, break out of here.
- This conversation's over.
- We're trying to do this the easy way.
Think you can do me a favor?
We have a lot to discuss,
Lincoln. Specifically, your brother.
How are we coming with the transfer?
- You gotta stay.
- What are you talking about?
Dad, I'm so sorry.
They got me and Sara.
You got a week to find this Whistler guy.
Otherwise, they-- They both die.
Bring that up here.
Yeah, get one for me
if you can.
- Where you from up there, bro?
- Chicago.
Michael Jordan.
You meet him?
It's a big city.
Oh, yeah. It's a big city.
- Thanks for saving me a spot.
- Hey.
Forget it.
You ever have sex
with a blond cheerleader?
- Yeah, sure.
- You're the man, bro.
- How long's the water been out?
- Since riots last year.
Government blame us.
They say,
"Screw you. You break it. No water."
Gracias.
Real quick, there's an inmate here
named James Whistler.
- I'm looking for him.
- Welcome to the club.
- Everybody looking for him.
- Why's that?
He killed the mayor of Panama City's son
in a bar fight.
The mayor not happy.
So where is he now?
Disappeared.
Some say he might even escape.
Hey. Hey.
"I don't have no money.
I don't have no money."
That's all I hear from you,
you know that?
But then I see you with this.
Life must be good, eh?
- Man, look, I'm-- I'm hungry, okay?
- You worry about me being hungry.
Hey, hey, hey, come on.
- Come on.
- But you eat all the time.
Okay? I can see you up there.
- Fight, fight, fight.
- Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, get off.
Ah!
- There's gonna be more water.
- When?
I said, there will be more water.
Later, bro.
Go. Go.
Spare a little?
- I need some information.
- Absolutely.
You slipped this note
in my pocket yesterday. Why?
My memory's a little foggy
on account of this thirst.
It's starting to come back to me.
- A little more agua there.
- The note.
Guy gave me rat meat...
...for putting that in your pocket and
the pocket of the guy you were to fight.
- Why?
- He's nuts, that's why.
Anybody who can live down in those
sewers doesn't have all his faculties.
Where in the sewers?
Whistler.
My name is Michael Scofield.
I was sent to get you out of here.
I'm gonna assume
they told you I was coming.
Or that someone was coming.
Whistler?
Last chance.
I'm not coming down here again.
- You're here to get me out of Sona?
- Are you surprised?
It's just that it's gonna be a bit difficult
getting me out of this hole.
Seeing as if I go above ground
and another inmate spots me...
...I'm a dead man.
There's a slight misunderstanding
that I have with the mayor of--
You know what?
It's none of my business.
I'll come back and get you
when the time is right.
- I may not make it that long.
- That's your problem.
I've got problems of my own.
So you work for these people?
The ones that want me out of Sona.
Look, just stay put.
As long as no one knows you're here,
you should be safe. I'll be back.
Why do they want me out of here
so badly? Can you at least tell me that?
Is this where you pretend
you're innocent, just a pawn in all this?
If they told you anything about me
before you came here...
...you'd know that to be true.
I just wanna know
what they want with me.
Stay put.
- Sorry about the wait.
- It's quite all right.
In an effort to save some time,
I gonna have to insist...
...that we skip right past all the threats
I know you're prepared to lay out.
Should anything happen to Sara or L.J.,
you will scour the Earth...
...and hunt me down and rip my heart
from my chest and blah, blah, blah.
I absolutely know how you feel,
as would I.
Okay? So that's done. On to business.
Did your brother get the message?
Good.
You and I will meet here every day.
I'll want a full report
of the prior day's progress.
When I call your cell phone, answer.
Don't ask me stupid questions.
Don't waste my time.
Get a plan together. Execute it.
L.J. and Sara will be traded for Whistler.
Are we clear?
I want a picture of my son and Sara
to prove they're alive.
- Fine, I can do that. Next.
- Why us?
I'll answer that question so we can put it
to bed and you can focus on your work.
There's a political spotlight on Whistler
due to the nature of his crime.
Raids, bribes, what have you
are not an option.
We have to go in through the back door,
so to speak.
This can't be done in a week.
You have a week. That's it.
Are we clear?
What's your name?
Susan B. Anthony.
I'm assuming you weren't born
by immaculate conception.
You're right, Lincoln.
Family trees being what they are,
moms, dads, brothers, sisters...
Anything happens to my son or Sara...
...I'm not coming after you, Susan.
Get to work.
His man knocks over the water...
...and did you see
how Lechero just walked away?
He doesn't care about us.
He doesn't give a damn.
Living like a king up there.
Come out. What, are you afraid?
Come out. Lechero, come out.
In there. Let's go.
Por favor.
Why are you so interested
about that guy down there?
No reason.
Then why are you whispering,
college boy?
- Why don't you lower your voice?
- What's in it for me?
I'm sorry, do you have any other friends
in here besides me? I'm it.
Friends don't let friends go hungry
and thirsty and damn near half-naked.
- I said, all right. I'll take care of it.
- When?
When I can.
What's the big deal? Why is he hiding?
Who's he hiding from?
Mayor get message to Lechero.
He say if Whistler guy gets killed
here in Sona...
...whoever kills him gets to go
to court.
Gets to see a judge.
Judge friendly with the mayor.
Kill him, and...
And you get to get out of here
and be free?
That's what Lechero said.
This will stay between me and you.
If your friend wanted you to know,
why didn't he tell you?
Because--
Because you and I are friends now.
Unless you wanna be enemies.
- Friends.
- Good. Me too.
Sucre.
Sucre, get me out of here, please.
- Where's Maricruz?
- Oh, yeah.
Yeah, Maricruz, she's good, she's okay.
But I'm not telling you anything until--
Tell me where she is right now.
You shoot me,
you'll end up inside this hellhole.
I'm telling you, I don't care anymore.
I can only guess she's dead by now.
So you're dying with her.
I never had her.
At that house in Mexico,
I chased your aunt and Maricruz off.
I told them I'd lock them up
for accessory if they didn't hightail it.
I swear to God.
- And the crucifix?
- I ripped it off Maricruz before she ran.
There was no phone in that dump...
...so I knew you wouldn't be able to call
from the road to...
To make sure I wasn't lying.
- I conned you.
- So...
So Maricruz is...
She's picking grapes. I have no idea.
So just lower the barrel.
Put the gun down.
Now, I came clean with you
and helped you out, right, buddy?
So you gotta return the favor.
Call my mom in Joliet. Edna Bellick.
Think she's listed. Sucre.
I never laid a hand on Maricruz.
I would never do that.
Sucre, help me, please.
Sucre, help me. Help me.
- Hey.
- You find Whistler?
- Yeah.
What's his story?
I don't know.
And maybe it's better that way, huh?
I just gotta get him out of here, right?
Come on, man.
We gotta keep moving.
What's the next play?
Whistler got a note out
on a dead body yesterday.
I don't know what it means
or who it's for.
But we need all the leverage
we can get.
And I need some money.
Step back. Step back.
No one's ever broken out of this place
before, let alone with a week to plan it.
So you tell these people...
...whoever it is that took Sara
and my nephew...
You tell them I get it,
and I'm gonna do everything I can.
I'm gonna break this guy out of here,
or I'm gonna die trying.
And if it's the latter...
...then that should count
for something, right?
That's gotta count for something.
You tell them that.
- I will.
- Tell them.
I'd trade places with you in a second.
I know.
Whistler?
You're not safe here.
I can take you someplace that is.
If you're here to help me,
then just leave me alone.
Please.
Sucre?
Lincoln, man.
What are you doing here?
- What are you doing here?
- Michael's locked up.
- For what?
- I don't know. I'm sorting it through.
I could use your help.
We're in a-- We're in a bad spot.
I feel for you, man,
but I'm done with bad spots, Linc.
I'm gonna go see Maricruz.
I talked to my cousin Petey.
He told me she's back in Chicago.
Hey, you're still wanted in Chicago,
remember?
I'll figure something out.
If you change your mind,
I'm staying at the Plaza del Sol.
I won't. I'm-- I'm out of here, bro.
I'm gonna go see my girl.
The innocent people in your life,
keep them innocent.
If that means walking away from them,
that's what you gotta do.
Good luck, Linc.
Hey, get him.
Have we had our laughs with him yet?
He's useless, man.
You wanna get rid of him?
Then you cut the mango.
You caused me a big,
big problem out there today.
You understand that?
Now there's no more water.
- They'll live.
- Oh, yeah? They'll live?
You go out and tell them that, then.
Theodore.
There's water here.
- Give each man a little, eh?
- At once.
Hey, Lechero.
Don't worry about us. We're fine.
He may have ruled the streets
out there...
...but in here, he's just like us.
Just like us.
Come out. What, are you afraid?
- Come and lean on it.
- Come on, man.
Come on.
The American in his underwear,
you seen him?
T-Bag.
You're gonna be drinking your urine
before you get any of this.
I just need to speak to Señor Lechero.
Please.
- Do yourself a favor. Scamper.
- But I got something.
Oh, yeah.
You got yourself the untouchable status.
Get myself killed
just talking to your mangy ass.
But I got information.
Good information.
- Are you out of your mind?
- He's got info.
- Pick a kneecap, huh?
- I got information.
- I just want food and clothes.
- Patrón, please.
Hold on there.
This better be informative,
or it's your kneecap next.
This morning,
before that whole water thing...
...I heard you and the lads
talking about that Whistler character...
...how no one's found him.
- Well...
- Please, I just want food and clothing.
- Just tell him, idiot.
- A guy is hiding in the sewers.
I figure he's hiding from you
because you run this place.
Figured you'd wanna know
everything that goes on--
Fine, shut up.
It just might be Whistler.
See, patrón, see?
- Is he Australian?
- Yeah, yeah.
Courtesy of the Lechero's munificence.
Go easy, back up. You can't have--
Hey, how long have you been in Sona?
Two years.
- How old are you?
- Seventeen.
As far as you know,
no one's ever broken out of this place...
...except maybe this Whistler guy?
You Americans ask a lot of questions.
- Oh, no.
- What's wrong?
- Come on.
- Please, I have a family.
So do I. Come on.
Just stop. Stop, okay?
Just...
He's coming with me.
Just back up, Michael. Just...
You don't actually think killing somebody
is gonna help you get out of here?
That does seem strange, doesn't it?
But this is a really strange place,
one that I want to get out of.
Then I'll help you.
I'll testify for you, whatever it takes.
Wow, look at that halo.
It just appeared above your head.
That's amazing.
- I don't have a choice, Alex.
- What did you tell me yesterday?
"You're on your own, Alex."
Back up. Back up.
You... You don't want this.
Let me help you, Alex.
Back up.
Hey. Your Majesty.
- Where are you hiding?
- You gotta shut him up.
Where are you hiding?
- I need this bolsón to call me back.
- I need to talk to you.
Don't ever walk in here
without being called.
- Sorry. It's worth a breach in etiquette.
- Is it, now?
I thought you could use my help.
There are ways I can be of assistance.
Just take the bounty off Whistler.
Whistler don't mean
nothing to me, man.
I have five life sentences.
I ain't coming out of Sona no time soon.
And why should I deprive other men
of a chance at freedom?
- I need you to trust me.
- Oh.
Trust you?
I don't know you good enough,
brother.
- Theodore.
- Sí, patrón.
Can I trust this bobo?
He's a snake.
He stabbed me in the back
every chance he got.
A snake who'd stab a man
in the back.
I never hear of such a creature before.
We gotta stop this.
- Just give me two more minutes.
- Leave. Now.
Leave.
Crumbs.
That's what you're giving us,
your crumbs.
Hey, Lechero, how's your television?
How's your whore?
Come out. What are you scared of?
Hey. I'm gonna need some--
Some moonshine.
- Moonshine?
- Some alcohol.
- Booze.
- Booze, yeah.
Well, I need it now.
A liter, a gallon, whatever you can get.
- It's not the time for a party, bro.
- Bring it to me in my cell.
Come on, Whistler.
Whistler, stop, stop. What are you--?
Just come up top with me.
You got a better chance
coming up with me.
At least you can plead your case
to Lechero.
- Just get--
- Go to hell.
Just--
- Go away.
- Not his best batch, he said.
- That's fine.
I'm gonna need some plastic bags.
- You didn't get it for to party, did you?
- Plastic bags. As many as you can get.
I'll make it worth your while,
I promise.
- Gracias.
- Excuse me. You speak English?
- Yeah.
We've met.
I mean, I saw you yesterday at Sona.
Yeah.
You know, you can lose
the whole grieving-widow thing.
You're Whistler's girl, right?
- I'm sorry, I have to be somewhere.
- I gotta do something.
Do what?
Give me that back
or I'll call the police.
You're not gonna call the police.
Why does he want this?
- I don't know. He's just a fisherman.
- Fisherman?
Tell your fisherman friend--
Tell your fisherman friend
Scofield's brother has this.
Why won't you people
just leave him alone?
You think we wanna be forced into this?
You think we wanna be here, lady?
Forced into what?
What are you talking about?
All right, hold this. Hold it.
Watch the hallway for me.
I'm friends with everybody here, bro.
That's how I keep alive.
- You and I are friends, right?
- Yeah, but it looks like you got enemies.
What I did for you,
getting you those things...
No one will ever know.
Lechero! Lechero! Lechero!
Stand up, stand up, stand up.
Come on.
Back up. Back up.
You can have him.
But two of you will die
in the process.
You first? You first.
I'll wrap this right around your head.
Move. Move.
Lechero! Lechero! Lechero!
Enough. Let me go down there.
Let me cut just one throat. Just one.
They'll quiet down, man.
And then regroup later
with a real reason to come after you.
Shut your mouth.
He's right, Sammy.
So, what we gonna do, boss?
Are we just gonna sit up here,
hope they run out of rocks?
- Look, we have a problem.
- What is it?
- Ran out of water.
- So you mean you've got a problem.
Look, there was an accident.
The tank tip over.
My men need water.
I'll see if I can get the water truck
day after tomorrow.
I need water now.
Guess it's too bad there's no guards
in there anymore with you.
You could take hostages,
have a riot, make demands.
Day after tomorrow.
You call me and you raise your voice
at me like that again...
...you're not going to see water
for two weeks.
They got Whistler.
Enough.
- I'll decide this.
- You decide nothing.
You can't deliver, Lechero.
You are done here.
What's that? What's happening?
I don't know.
Now what?
What do we do?
- You've been outbid.
- Wait, what are you talking about?
What are you talking about?
What are you talking...?
Now, that's very useful.
Very useful.
And Whistler's clear?
Yeah. Clear as a blue sky, brother.
- Hello?
- Baby, it's me.
Oh, my God.
Honey, I've been so scared.
I've been praying every day.
I did too, babe.
I just thank God you're okay.
Petey called me after he'd talked to you.
He said you might be coming back here.
- That's what I told him, yeah.
- You have to be so careful.
Baby, I've been thinking...
...and the only thing that I--
That I care about right now
is that you and the baby are okay.
That's all that matters to me.
I'm not coming back.
It's not because I don't love you,
because you know I do.
I love you more--
I love you more than anything.
But all--
All I'd do is bring you down.
I'm no good for you.
- That's not true. That's not true.
- It is, it is, it is.
And sometimes the only way
to protect the people that you love is--
Is by staying away from them.
One day, when I get my life together...
...however long that takes,
I'll find you.
I'll find you, and I'll--
And I'll make you and our baby proud.
I wish we could go back.
I would give anything to go back.
I wish that too. I wish that too, baby.
I love you so much, baby.
I love you too, baby.
Goodbye.
Bye.
You know, they told me
that your brother got all the brains...
...but I didn't realize
you were this stupid.
What do you want, Susan?
No sooner do I tell you
to stick to the plan...
...than you go
and hassle Whistler's girlfriend.
You need to quit playing
Sherlock Holmes and leave her alone.
- Why?
- Because I said so.
- How about that?
- All right.
How about you beat it
so I can get to work?
I will, as soon as you give me
what you took from her.
I took nothing.
I got a gallon of bleach, a tarp
and a hacksaw in my car.
One hour, tops,
you're off the face of the Earth.
- It's just a bird guide.
- I am not gonna ask you again.
Toss it.
Tomorrow, bar, progress report.
I will be waiting.
So it's water you want?
Here's your water.
Thank you.
So how are we getting out of here?
I have no idea.