This is Pam.
Oh, my God, are you sure?
Okay, okay, we'll be right there.
Everybody!
- The balloon is falling!
- What?
There's this balloon
that has been floating
in the rafters of the
warehouse for, like, ever.
And...
Okay, it's not, it doesn't sound
cool, you just have to see it.
Well, I guess it doesn't
look that cool either.
But it's been up there
a long time,
so it's become
a pretty big deal.
Wow. It's the end
of an era.
You did
a good job, buddy.
Now it's time
to come home.
I remember when that balloon
went up there. I was still with Gil.
We were so happy.
When that went up there,
I had hair like Rapunzel.
How long do you think
it's been up there, Kevin?
I just remember pushing aside
my silky bangs to say,
"Look, a balloon."
My Warcraft clan was
still on speaking terms.
My kid didn't
have a face tattoo.
I was still thinking
of going back to school.
And I was still
just a paper salesman.
This has been fun, Pam.
Thanks for calling us all down here.
Kill the balloon!
Hey!
So they accidentally gave us an
extra egg sandwich this morning.
- Who wants it?
- Ooh! Right here.
Right here! Pick me!
Allow me to solve
your problem then.
Nellie.
Mmm.
Ugh! That is disgusting.
Do you call that a King
James breakfast pie?
What brings you to town?
Certainly not the Harry Houdini
museum. What a nobody!
"Oh, look, some Hungarian
just found their way out of a sack,
"let's build a shrine."
No, I've come
to work here.
What?
How could Robert transfer Nellie
here after the Sabre store debacle?
She stinks of failure.
The fact that she could
show her face around here
is an embarrassment.
I should know. I'm in
an identical situation.
Robert did say you'd be
joining us. Welcome, I'm Tony.
What?
I said, "I'm Tony."
Okay, I made a mistake. I
thought it might go unnoticed.
But, I'm Toby.
You messed up
saying your name?
It happens, okay?
So let's just find
an empty desk for you
and I'm sure Robert will be
with you as soon as he gets in.
That one looks empty.
No. It's Andy's office.
Oh, is it?
I have one simple
philosophy in business,
if the seat is open,
the job is open.
It's how I came to briefly
race a Formula One car.
The three slowest laps
ever recorded.
Another beautiful day
in Tallahassee.
Good morning, Alonzo!
Good morning, Erin!
How are you?
How's your family doing?
Bye.
Look at this place. Five rooms
and I get to clean them all.
That's right. I'm a
maid for an old lady.
Her grandson's staying with us,
too, because he ran out of money.
Listen to me,
bragging away.
Nellie.
Robert.
How are you adjusting
to life in Scranton so far?
So far, so good! The water
pressure in the hotel is marvelous.
It is astounding what a
difference that can make, isn't it?
Mmm-hmm.
Now, let's find you something
fun to do here, shall we?
Oh, I've already found it.
I am manager, a natural
next step. It fits like a glove.
We have a manager.
Do you really?
Because it is 10:00,
I've been in this
chair for an hour
and no other manager
has come and sat on my lap.
Excuse me, has anyone
seen Andy this morning?
Yeah, that's weird. He's
usually here by now. Right, guys?
Hello?
Andy, it's Robert.
Why aren't you at work?
Hey, Robert, I really wish I
could come into work today
but I'm super sick.
I don't care.
Please come to
work immediately.
Okay, I'll try to come in,
even though I'm really sick
with the Florida flu!
He just hung up
on me mid-sentence.
I'm in Florida to get Erin.
As soon as I heard she
wasn't coming back to Scranton,
I jumped straight in my car and
drove straight down until I hit the ocean.
My heart is my map.
Turns out Tallahassee is about
two hundred miles inland,
so I overshot a good amount.
But still, not bad
for a heart map, right?
Ew.
Thanks a lot, BP.
Not much we can do about this
until he gets here.
Can't you do
something about this?
Sometimes the flowers
arrange themselves, Jim.
Right.
What is going on,
and where's Andy?
And what is going on?
Erin, you got a package!
I'm in the bathroom!
Where's the postage? I
mean there's no shipping label.
Did you wash your hands?
Yes.
Here I am, signed,
sealed, delivered I'm yours
Andy, what are you
doing here?
It's great to see you.
Ah!
Uh, I am here to take
you back to Scranton
because I love you and
I want to be with you.
Where's the ring?
Hmm?
Where's the ring, Lancelot?
Would you guys mind if we
talked privately for a second?
Sorry, Glenn.
Um.
Andy, I am so happy to see you,
but I'm not
coming back with you.
Why won't
she go with him?
I don't know. Maybe it's
because he's not that handsome.
Hey.
Don't listen.
So what is going on?
That does seem to be
the question, doesn't it?
"Hey, this
is messed up, bro. Who is this weird lady?"
I know. It's a lot.
So, who knows what's
going on? Anyone?
You, yes, wait. I am
very good intuiting names.
Is it Chumbo?
I think it's a cross between
"dumbo” and "jumbo,"
with a hint of "chubby."
It's not a name.
So no one can tell me
what's going on?
Well, let me
illuminate things for you.
We are getting to
know each other.
"But why, my lady?"
Because I am
your new manager.
Robert, is Nellie
our new manager?
This is an odd situation.
But it's very interesting
how it's playing out.
We live in this world
of routines and rhythms.
Kevin ate someone's lunch,
Phyllis has a new necklace.
Who is this woman?
I came in here simply trying to
get to know you, learn your names,
maybe have someone teach me
the company song.
And what I got in return
was nothing but disrespect.
You leave me no choice
but to get to know you
in a more intimate way.
Hot tub party?
Performance reviews.
How can you give us performance
reviews if you don't know us?
On first impressions,
so I recommend smiling.
It goes a long way with me.
Erin, you really
nailed the hot dogs today.
Thanks. I've been reusing the
hot dog water, so it gets more flavor.
It's only going to
keep getting better.
So, Andrew, how does your
skinny brunette girlfriend, Jessica,
feel about you
visiting your ex-girlfriend?
Well, we're not
really dating anymore,
so basically,
I mean I just have to
cross a few t's and
dot a few i's, you know.
So you came to get me,
but you still have a girlfriend.
I think you should leave,
young man.
All right, technically yes. I am
still technically dating Jessica.
But when I realized
that I wanted you back,
I just jumped in a car
and I drove down here
and I didn't want to stop
until I saw you.
You didn't even
stop to pee? Gross!
Any luck?
No, he just keeps letting
all the calls go to voicemail.
Please leave a message
for Andy Bernard
Include your name...
Oh, you're doing so good! Oh, my
God, you're Superman over there.
You should take it.
It's probably your girlfriend
wondering where you are.
Nope. It's just work.
Not important.
You know I can really
feel this in my quads.
I can tell I'm
getting stronger.
You really wouldn't feel those
kinds of results after one session.
I don't know, it's...
Just let it vibrate.
It's fine.
You could put it
on silent.
I don't think
it does that.
Just go to preferences,
then click...
Proctology.
Andy?
Jim?
Andy, where are you?
I'm home in bed.
I've been in bed all day.
I got the serious poops, man.
He's here in Tallahassee,
trying to turn my life upside down.
What? You're in Florida?
Andy, Nellie Bertram's
trying to take your job.
What do you mean,
take my job?
Like, set up camp
in your office
and is calling
herself the manager.
Okay.
Jim, I really appreciate
you looking out for me
but I'm not coming home
without Erin.
So, I'll talk to you later.
Guys!
We cannot do these
performance reviews, okay?
If we go into them,
you're basically
accepting Nellie
as your manager.
And trust me. You do not
want her as your manager.
Trust you?
The way Pam trusted you to provide
for her so she wouldn't have to work?
I like working here.
Dwight,
should she be our manager?
I wouldn't let her
manage a celery farm.
Those who can't farm,
farm celery.
And when was the last time Dwight
and I agreed on anything ever?
All right,
let's get going.
First up, it is the woman with the
beautiful fingernails and the tiny feet.
Phyllis.
Nellie, I'm sorry,
but I don't feel comfortable
being evaluated by
someone I don't know.
Oh.
Okay. I understand. Let me show
you how these are going to go.
Dwight.
I refuse to be judged by
someone that I do not respect.
I lost respect for you
in Florida.
If it was up to me,
you would be in jail forever.
Dwight, I have
completed your evaluation.
You're getting a raise.
What?
Dwight, you carry this company
on your massive shoulders.
You are our Atlas
and for that, do you not
think you deserve a raise?
There's no limit to
what I think I deserve.
Then you accept it?
Five percent, no less!
Absolutely not.
Seven percent.
Six percent!
I know my worth.
Raise isn't real.
Money isn't real, ever since
we got off the gold standard.
So, Phyllis, now you
know the rules of the game,
do you care to have a go? I'm
fairly certain you're going to like it.
Phyllis.
Pam.
So, Phyllis, I have been
very impressed with you.
Really?
Oh, yeah.
The way you conquered
your fear and came in here,
and now the way
you sit there.
All very impressive!
Um...
Are you aware that
Nellie is giving out raises?
I am not. How?
Yeah, she gave one
to Dwight, Phyllis...
Let me guess,
you want one, too.
Take the family
to Disney Town.
Land! World!
It's not that I don't want...
Well, yes, I guess I'd take a raise.
That's not what I'm saying.
That's not... Sorry.
Jim, I told Andy to come in
and yet he is still not in.
By contrast, Nellie Bertram
saw a vacuum and filled it.
I make no mention
of her business experience
or her relationship
with Jo Bennett, my boss.
Jim, would you prefer a nature
metaphor or a sexual metaphor?
Oh, God, nature, please.
When two animals
are having sex,
one of them is communicating
a message to the other.
Nothing is...
This isn't very helpful.
You're going to want
to hear the sexual metaphor.
Was that not the...
All life is sex.
And all sex is competition.
Mmm-hmm.
And there are no
rules to that game.
That wasn't so perverted,
now was it?
Was that it?
No, that wasn't bad.
My point is there is one person in
charge of every office in America.
And that person
is Charles Darwin.
In the end, doesn't he
decide who the manager is?
No. I would have said no.
Hmm. Let's see. Review,
review, review! Yes, good stuff.
Here you go, have a raise.
Oh, great!
I mean if we go in there and take
these raises, what are we saying?
That it's okay for someone to
just take someone else's job?
Shouldn't work like that.
No, you know what?
Nellie's right.
That is exactly
how it should work.
Darryl,
this office is mine now.
Yes!
Yes.
Yes. Sorry, it's too late. I'm
here. This is mine. Back off.
Ow! Ow!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Well fought!
I accept the outcome.
Touch me and I'll sue.
I've heard that's
amazing when it works.
Yeah. If I had my own...
Andy, I care about
you and I think...
Sorry. You go.
No, go ahead.
Well, I was just
going to say that
if I had my own fountain
it would be two frogs
and they're spitting
into each other's mouth.
It's just stupid. What
were you going to say?
Andy, you broke my heart.
Do you know what it feels like
to be constantly rejected by you
and to have to watch
you date someone else?
You broke my heart, too.
You broke my heart more
recently and more often.
And I think at some point in
my head it just sort of clicked
that we're not
meant to be.
I'm so sorry that we have not
loved each other at the same time.
I know.
So, Pamela, I'm
going to start this review
not by telling you
what you lack,
but rather asking you
what it is you want.
Really? Okay, well!
Um...
I like consistency in the manager's
position. No weird silent coups.
Stuff like that,
I'm easy.
That's not
really what you want.
What you want is a good night's
sleep, working mother of two.
Whoa.
That's kind of condescending. Would
you say something like that to Jim?
Does Jim
have to breastfeed?
Did Jim carry around those
babies for, what is it, 12 months?
Be honest. Does Jim
really get up in the night?
Well, I mean, the only reason he
doesn't is because I'm breastfeeding
and Philip
doesn't like a bottle.
You must be exhausted.
Fancy a nap?
No.
Go on. Have a nap.
Lie down right here.
There's a blanket in here.
I used it earlier myself.
Dreamt I could breathe
underwater like Jacques Cousteau.
No one will know.
I'll wake you up.
When you wake up,
you will earn more money.
I think you're a witch.
I think you're amazing.
You know that, right?
Go on. Say it,
“I'm amazing."
I'm amazing.
Erin, I think you're making
a big mistake right now.
Andy is a nice boy.
Really? Because you've been
kind of a "B" to him all afternoon.
I was protecting you because
I thought he was no good.
But I can tell
you really like him.
And he's willing to
lose his job for you.
In this economy,
with Europe on the brink...
Irene, what would
you do without me?
We're not your concern,
sweetheart.
Besides, Glenn's
going to sue Home Depot.
Why?
He got his foreskin caught
in some lawn furniture.
Jim, time for
your review.
No, it's not, because
you don't really work here.
Why are you so
staunchly defending
your friend who
has abandoned you?
Wouldn't you rather come talk with
me, maybe, definitely get a raise?
See, that's the thing.
I don't know if you
can even give raises.
Jim, have you ever heard of a
character named Tinker Bell?
Yes.
I'm Tinker Bell.
No.
I'm a magical fairy
who floated into your office
to bring a little bit of magic into
your lives, to give you all raises.
And we are grateful.
But here's the thing
about Tinker Bell, Jim,
everyone has to believe in her
or she doesn't exist.
And then she dies.
She dies.
Now who here
believes in Tinker Bell?
Let's see it. Show
of hands! I do.
Come on, everyone!
All right, guys, stop!
I already spent the money.
How?
Come on,
Jim, you're killing her!
We believe!
Look at this
wonderful recognition
of Nellie's leadership.
I believe!
That did not go
how I wanted it to.
Ugh!
I have a whole ton of Erin's
favorite food for the drive back.
Eggplant parm!
It's biodegradable.
Animals will eat it.
Andy, wait! Andy!
Andy, wait! Andy, don't go!
Andy, I love you! Stop!
Oh. This is the wrong Prius.
I don't love you.
Erin!
I'm sorry.
Andy.
Let's get out of here.
Okay.
Let's go.
Wait, we have to go back
and get your stuff.
No, I don't have
any stuff.
Like your toothbrush
and stuff. I don't have one.
You don't have a toothbrush? No.
How do you not
have a toothbrush?
I just, there's
always one around.
You just use whichever
one is sitting there?
I always find one.
Have you ever heard
of buying a toothbrush?
Of course,
I own my toothbrush.
I grew up poor. I had
little formal education, no real skills.
I don't work
especially hard
and most of my ideas are
either unoriginal or total crap.
And yet,
I walked right into a job
for which I was
ill-prepared, ill-suited,
and somebody else
already had, and I got it.
If you ask me, that's the
American dream right there.
Anything can happen
to anyone.
It's just random.