Hey, Angela,
you wanna see
a picture of Philip
wearing those little
booties you got us?
So cute.
Hey, you guys wanna see a
picture of Gerald wearing galoshes?
He refused to go out in
the rain until I bought these.
Now, going out in the rain
is all he wants to do.
Oscar thinks having a dog
is just like having a baby.
News flash,
if you didn't carry
it around in your
belly for nine months,
it isn't your kid.
Exactly.
Unless you adopted,
of course.
That is where we disagree.
Hey, are your little
dudes crawling yet?
No. Three-month-old
humans don't do that.
My Philip is crawling.
Angela is such a liar!
It's maddening!
Exactly, that's just
like crate training.
All night long.
Well, count yourself lucky.
Wait until you have two.
That's two sleep schedules,
two naps that don't coincide.
I mean,
you'll never sleep again.
No one said
you must have two.
Like her genes
are so important.
The world just needs more
Pam-Jim DNA. Thank you, no.
No, thank you.
Check this out. My brother
just got a new sailboat.
He has no idea what he
just got himself into.
There's nothing harder
than taking care of a boat.
Am I right?
Unbelievable!
It is the end of the day.
It is the end of the week.
We managed to fill
40 hours, somehow.
That's not bad, is it?
That's great.
Pretty good.
Well, thank you,
this is very helpful feedback.
Dwight, I am still not
ready to name the V.P.
That's not what
I was gonna ask.
Gosh, you jump to conclusions!
Come on, I know. You've
got so much on your plate,
it's right now you're like,
"Oh, what's more important, Dwight's
question, figure out who's the V.P.
"Dwight. V.P. Dwight. V.P."
Dwight. V.P. Dwight. V.P.
I can't be hypnotized, Dwight.
I tried it.
I ended up smoking more.
Can we at least eliminate
those that are not in the running?
Free them up to focus
more completely on the menial.
Like stacking
and sorting, or...
Catching butterflies?
That's a hobby.
Unless it's for food.
Theater.
A waste of time.
Dragging?
That's just a verb.
Dragging sticks.
Yes. Nice. Perfect.
Dragging sticks...
All right, I'm gonna eliminate
three people right now.
Okay? Just. You three. No.
Not good enough.
English people's main use
today is judging American talent.
"You're crap.
You're wonderful."
They're mean,
but they're incisive.
Everyone meet in
the hotel bar at 7-00.
I'm not allowed to
say it's mandatory.
So let's just
call it compulsory.
I'll be there at 6:00.
Ugh. We're gonna have one
of those crazy nights, aren't we?
Maybe we'll see
the real Talla-nasty
we've been
hearing so much about.
Talla-nasty. Very clever.
Thank you.
Wait, wait.
You think she
invented "Talla-nasty"?
No, no, no, no.
Cathy? It's been
great, fun, normal.
I thought I was gonna be
hanging out with Stanley on this trip,
but he's turned out
to be kind of a loose cannon.
My friend and I
are new here in Tallahassee.
Would you like
to get a cocktail?
Maybe go out for a little
dancing? Beautiful day, no?
Okay, everybody.
5.00. Work day's over.
Put your pencils down,
and bring 'em back up!
Because now, the late
night work jam begins!
Yes! The conference
room is set up.
I've got pens, I've got paper,
I've got a whiteboard!
We are good to go.
Say what?
We are good to go!
Good to go!
Stop it!
Andy!
Tonight, we're staying late
to service the accounts
of the people who
went on the Florida trip.
Yes, of course
we could have just
been doing this
the whole time,
but someone dropped the ball.
Ball droppings
can be beautiful.
For example, when it turns an
awkward soprano into a rich, full tenor.
Jason Bourne
would kick Bond's ass.
Jason Bourne has
no support staff,
his own government's
out to get him.
Genghis Khan could
take 'em both down,
'cause he's not
afraid to kill children.
What? It's true.
He would eviscerate
babies and hang them
from poles
outside of the villages.
Okay, drinking game. The
count of three, take three sips.
That's a stupid game. I got
a great drinking game. Okay?
Everyone, empty your pockets.
Whoever has
the most seeds is the king,
whoever has the least buttons
is the hunchback.
What happens if
you're the hunchback?
Oh, you get kicked.
How many buttons do you have?
Forty. Always.
Can I see?
Sure.
So I get to kick you now.
No, they're not transferable
just 'cause I handed them to you.
Well, that's how I
played it in college.
College rules.
And he lost at
his own lame game.
Ooh! Double meaning.
The game was lame, and
now he's lame from the kick.
Quick wit.
Thank you.
I will have a glass of your
oakiest chardonnay, please.
And I will have a waffle.
With your maple-iest syrup.
Sorry, no waffles.
Okay, just forget it then.
Forget it. Forget it?
Waffle?
A hotel waffle.
I know what I wanna eat.
Is that crazy?
No.
I'm moving down here,
you know.
Oh. No, I didn't know.
I'm young and I can.
And if I can't,
I'm still pretty young.
I guess I'll always be young.
You come with me. We're
gonna get you that waffle.
Why would Erin confide in me
that she's staying here in Florida
if she didn't want me to make some
sort of last ditch, nothing-to-lose,
Kelly Ka-who run at her?
Hey.
Watson Carpet ♪ Tile.
One order.
Order reference
number 00983-126.
Eight cases
Bright White Inkjet.
Paid.
I'm dying!
Processed.
And delivered.
Sometimes I get so bored,
I just wanna scream.
And then sometimes,
I actually do scream.
I just sort of feel out
what the situation calls for.
I will be right back.
I will be here.
Hey, I see what you're doing.
It's futile. The V.P. position is mine.
Oh, please, you're through.
She's going to give it to me,
as I'm giving it to her tonight.
The cowgirl has chosen her
saddle.
Well, saddles...
...sometimes fall off.
Especially if you don't
properly cinch the girth.
What? That's a joke, right? You
see the way she's all over me.
If anyone's having sex with
Nellie for personal gain, it's me.
And I'm not joking at all.
If you don't tighten your
saddle, you may fall off.
Who is ready for dinner?
"Oh, I bet it's pizza or tacos
or something stupid." No.
I went south of
the border for this,
and then I went
south of that border,
and we have ourselves
a Jamaican feast, man.
If I wanted Jamaican food,
I'd just hire
a bunch of
bodyguards and go there.
Additional trivia factoid, this
food comes to us through Val,
and our server is none
other than Brandon, her boyf.
Hey.
How you doing, guys?
Jamaican, huh? I just read
about the elections down there.
Crazy stuff.
Oh, no. I'm not
actually Jamaican.
Terrific.
What's up, man? I'm Darryl.
Oh, Darryl.
I heard about you.
You doing good?
Oh, yeah.
You must be doing real good
since you're my girlfriend.
Whoa!
Dude, you didn't tell me you
were Val. High five!
I'm not sleeping
with your girlfriend.
Brandon, what the hell
are you talking about?
Don't play dumb with me.
I know what's up.
Honey, I am not sleeping...
Hey! Hey.
Let's get back to the food.
Brandon, tell us about
these delicious-looking goops.
Hope you all like goat.
Goat.
Blow in my ear.
All right.
Like I'm on the beach.
A seagull.
And a wave crashing.
A wave crashing.
Oh, that is lovely.
All right, that's
gonna do it for me tonight.
Have a lovely evening.
Hey, how's it going?
Good. The heating system,
though, in my room is all messed up.
It's like 90 degrees
in there.
Maintenance is working on it.
Can I hang out in here?
Uh... Yeah, I'm just
watching basketball...
Okay. Yeah.
Okay.
Cool.
Is this March Madness?
I love March Madness.
Oh, no. That's not this.
Because that's in March.
This is just the NBA,
professional.
Miami Heat, actually. So...
LeBron James.
Yes.
Nice, good word association.
Impressive.
Oh, please,
anyone can tie a knot.
The real skill
is in untying it.
Thornwood Wholesalers.
One order.
I read the texts
you sent to Val, man.
That's messed up.
Is this spicy?
No, baby girl.
It would be messed up
if I didn't find anything.
But I did, so...
I'm pretty sure if
Darryl sent Val a text,
it was about some paper
emergency or something.
At midnight?
It happens.
Like, a hospital needs
more napkins for surgery.
You guys, we're not gonna
settle anything this way.
I think we just need to be
grown-ups here. Thank you.
I think we're gonna
need to hear those texts.
Kelly, remember how you wanted
to go home before?
No. There's no way
in hell I'm leaving.
Something interesting
is happening here.
For once in my life.
I am staying here.
Darryl, read the texts!
Yep? Coming!
All right. Hey. My
minibar is oddly out of rum.
We have plenty.
Oh. Hello.
You wanna watch the game
with us? We're watching a game.
The Heat game.
It's just a game.
Got it. Good night.
Careful, Jim,
it gets easier and easier.
No. No, no. Stanley?
Stanley. Stanley?
Stanley. All right. Hey!
You know. Just bring
back those bottles!
Huh. The lights
are still on.
Yeah. They keep
them on, 'cause it's
less expensive than
turning them on and off.
I like how guys just
know stuff all the time.
Girls know a lot
of stuff too, okay?
And nobody
knows more than you.
Especially me.
Hello, waffle iron!
Hello! What do
we have here?
Okay, so the recipe
says we need
a mixing bowl,
a measuring cup...
Get down.
It's the fuzz.
Do you want us
to get scolded?
Shut your beautiful,
beautiful mouth. Please.
"I got too much ice cream,
you want some?"
"Getting my fry on."
Boring.
"The moon is huge tonight."
Gosh, the moon one's damning.
Yeah, sorry.
That's regular text talk.
You forgot one.
"You're such a great friend."
With the dots.
"You're such a great friend,
dot, dot, dot, dot, dot."
Five dots, Darryl?
Are you kidding me?
Okay, 'cause three dots means
to be continued, four dots is a typo.
But five dots means,
"Whoa, do not
make me say what I
want to say, baby,
"but if I did, it would blow your
mind, dot, dot, dot, dot, dot."
See? Yes, thank you, sister.
Brandon, Darryl and me,
that's ridiculous.
Right?
Yeah.
Totally crazy. Puts me in an
insane asylum just thinking about it.
I'm stranded on
Shutter Island over here.
You look like Ed Harris.
If they stretched
him a little bit...
You wanna see a picture of me
trapped under a tree?
Uh...
Excuse me.
What? Not now. I'm busy.
I'm sorry,
I thought you'd want to know
that I saw
a bedbug in my room.
But never mind.
Sorry to interrupt.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Bedbugs?
Oh, no.
Freak, I need a favor.
Well, then you have to call me
by my name. Gabriel Susan Lewis.
I've gotta be gone
for a few minutes.
You make sure that Packer
does not sleep with Nellie.
What's in it for G.S.L.?
You really want
Packer as your boss?
Got it.
If Jim has bedbugs,
that means they're everywhere.
I can't risk them coming
back to Schrute Farms.
Our biggest attraction is our
200-hundred-year-old mattresses.
Where did you see it?
In the bed.
Well, I haven't seen anything.
We gotta find it
before it eggs.
Jeez!
Describe it.
Brown, shiny, painful bite.
Could be a bat weevil.
Describe its mood.
Did it seem sleepy?
Stressed, but to be fair,
it was a tense situation.
Fair enough. But after it bit
you, did it run away fearful?
Or did it walk away smug,
self-assured?
So smug. Like he thought
it was funny. Like this.
That's a bedbug.
Yeah.
Everything's a joke.
I know.
Check your hair!
God! It's so greasy. You
should just shave all this.
Just check it.
You are clean. Okay.
The one thing a bedbug thrives
on is heat and carbon dioxide.
I am gonna generate myself
into a human trap.
When I jump into the bed,
you are gonna
cover me with
the sheet immediately.
And then,
we'll see who's laughing.
All right!
Yeah!
Cover me!
Is this really necessary?
He knows what he's doing.
Let the bedbugs bite!
God! I feel so gross!
I have to go take a shower.
All right,
then I will catch you later.
What do we do now?
We wait.
Come to Papa!
No!
I don't know, Dwight.
I think maybe you should...
No, I wasn't bitten.
Okay, well, maybe it's not
warm enough in here.
It's plenty warm.
And I was farting continuously
under the sheet,
creating a kind of a
greenhouse effect. Come on.
If there were any
in here, they would
have imbedded
themselves in me.
You know what?
Maybe they just ate.
No, you're good.
Clean bill of health.
Besides, I gotta
get back downstairs.
I left Packer alone with
Nellie for way too long.
Okay, well, they're
fine, they're adults.
No. That's the problem.
Packer is trying to bed Nellie
for the V.P. job, unless I do it first.
Is that really how you
want to get this job?
Such a chorus girl.
Okay, Dwight? Dwight?
Dwight, Dwight, Dwight.
Uh...
Is "crazy" gone?
Oh...
They don't make these cords
in boot cut anymore!
Aw...
Pathetic, huh?
A real man swallows his vomit
when a lady is present.
Hey.
Yep, one Death by Chocolate,
one Bananas Foster.
Okay, cool. Thanks.
I know, I'm a pig, right?
Wait, this is why I
exercise like a fiend.
Feel. Seriously.
Okay. All right.
I'm really sorry.
I just have to say it.
I'm married.
I'm very happily married.
Oh, my God,
what are you thinking?
Um...
I mean...
I know that you're married,
I sat at your wife's desk.
How little do you
think of me?
I'm sorry, I feel like
maybe I misread things.
Okay. Let's just
go back to watching.
Can you, without running to the
other side of the room all night?
Yes. I can. Uh...
All right.
I'm really sorry.
I think we'll just...
We'll just watch.
You can watch, not watch,
whatever you wanna do.
Take another shower,
I don't care. Okay.
Whoo...
I am so cold.
Hey, Darryl, you okay?
She's got a boyfriend.
Play it cool, man.
She'll come around.
No, you should go for it. Mmm...
I mean, nothing would've
happened with me and Jim
if he didn't put
himself out there.
Yeah, but my friend Jim
would tell you to play it cool.
My husband would
tell you to go for it.
Hey. Hey.
This is fun.
A lot of fun.
I know. Can I give
you a compliment?
I'm really impressed
by how much you've grown.
Since I met you,
it's like night and day.
You should move down
here with me! Yeah?
We could be roommates.
Really?
We could get a dog,
we could go to R-rated movies!
And who knows, I mean,
you're a guy, I'm a girl.
Yeah.
Maybe in six months,
we'll see. Six months!
Okay. I'm in love
with Kelly.
Put your forehead near mine and
see if you can read my thoughts.
Okay.
Seven, one, one...
Nine... No, no, no,
not numbers. No.
No, okay. Try again.
Okay.
I'm still getting numbers.
Seven, one, one...
Is anyone around here thinking
the numbers seven, one, one?
Please stop. Okay?
Dwight, give me
a key card to your room.
Meet me in seven minutes
for some one-on-one time.
Wait, the numbers.
There you go.
I will see you in seven...
Seven minutes.
Nellie, wait.
Let me write my room
number on the card.
Win at all costs.
Don't respect women.
These are the tenets I was brought
up with, and they have served me well.
But my ancestors never worked
in corporate America.
They were farmers,
and before that, hunters,
and before that, time travelers,
and before that, me again.
At least that's
how the legend goes.
The point is, they never had to
worry about how they got ahead.
They just had to put food on
the table and not alter the past.
1434-967, paid.
It has been processed.
It has been delivered.
That's it, last one.
Andy, this has been
an amazing night. Epic.
Cool down fiesta
begins right now.
I got decaf coffee.
No way.
I've got Romy and Michele's
High School Reunion.
Hey,
I just wanted to apologize.
I mean, that was so weird.
Can we just like
never talk about it again?
Sure.
Okay, thanks.
Hey, just so you know,
me and you,
I don't think that's ridiculous.
Dot, dot, dot, dot, dot.
All right. Now [ think
it's time for you to go.
What? Jim!
I thought we talked about
this. You're cool, right?
Cathy! Go.
Where's the bug?
Awesome!
Stand back!
Stop it! Oh, my gosh!
That burns! What is that?
It's a compound of chemicals
I pulled off of the maid's cart.
Oh, my God!
Dwight, there!
Oh, God! Stop it! Stop it!
Big one! Big one!
I think I saw it!
Stop it!
Nice job, I think
you got him.
You can't
stay here, this place is a biohazard.
If I were you,
I'd just bunk with Cathy.
Second best Bananas
Foster I've ever had.
Yeah, what's the first best?
Dwight?
Hello? Dwight?
- Is that Nellie?
- Don't!
Are you in there?
I can see the light
on under your door.
Hello?
Oh, look at that.
The light went off just
as I said the light went on.
Hello? Dwight?
Dwight?