Val, I need the space.
All right,
guys, clear out.
Everybody out!
Promise me you're
going to clean up.
I can't promise what
I'm going to do or not do.
Promise me...
Obviously,
I'm going to clean up.
Stress is like the uptight
mayor of a town who's saying,
"Hey, we're uptight.
You can't dance."
And then, you have to be like, "Oh,
yeah, Mayor Stress? Well, watch this."
And then, we dance.
Oh, how we dance.
Sex also works.
Hey, Jim's back
from jury duty.
Hey! Tuna!
He's back!
Hey.
Oh, look at this.
Tuna wrap.
Okay.
Hand roll.
How was jury duty?
Pretty uneventful,
actually.
I can't believe they let
someone like you serve on a jury.
Makes me question
the whole judicial system.
What was the case?
A hit and run.
Ooh! The case of the hit
and run. That's exciting.
Did you send him
to the slammer?
No. Not guilty.
Of course you
found him not guilty.
He apologized. And I
just really want him to like me. Mmm!
We're best friends,
actually.
We're going wine tasting next
weekend, if you want to come.
Not coming.
Have plans.
Okay.
I did get called
into jury duty.
And they
released me around noon,
so I didn't
think it was worth it
to come back to work
for a half day.
And then the next morning, Pam
was a little overwhelmed with the kids,
so I took an extra day
to help out.
And then,
three other days happened.
Ah!
Angela had the baby!
Is it black? Because
that would be hilarious.
Why?
You know.
Would it be more hilarious than
Angela having a Chinese baby?
A little bit. Yeah.
Right, guys? Back me up.
Maybe a little bit.
Oh. Did I win the pool?
Uh, no. Right month, wrong year.
No one won the pool. Angela
wasn't due for another month.
We should all go to
the hospital and visit her.
Oh, I'd love to, but...
Oh, man, I would, but I
can't miss any more work.
Well, Kevin and I have to go, because
accounting is its own little family.
Yeah, Oscar's the dad, I'm
Oscar's dad and Angela's my mom.
Everyone,
our very own Angela...
We all got the e-mail. Some
of us are going to go visit.
Oh, I am so in.
I love maternity wards.
It's the perfect blend
of love and horror.
Things can go SO
wrong or so right.
Come on, Judge Judy, tell us
your case. What were the deets?
It was actually
a pretty boring case.
How could it be boring? You
were there for five days. Titillate us.
Yeah, you owe us. I had to stay
until 6:00 twice to cover for you.
My wife got to
the TV first.
I had to sit through damn
Rizzoli & damn Isles.
Yeah. My car got smashed
visiting one of your clients,
and I had to have it detailed
and they took my meter change.
Wow. I'm really sorry.
Yeah.
I never considered
that my week off
would make everyone
else's job harder.
The least I could do
was give them a good story.
So Phyllis,
he was here and then,
the car came and
it was like that.
Yeah, so it had to be a
double backflip, actually.
You know, when I was on
♪-duties, strangler case,
we used to recreate the various
stranglings with empanadas from Ernesto's.
Oh, man, Ernesto's.
That was our
favorite restaurant, too.
You mean food truck.
Ernesto's was a food truck.
Toby, shut your hole
about the empanadas.
Nobody cares
I was in Los Angeles
last year.
Jim tricked me into thinking
I'd won a walk-on part on NCIS,
but that's not important.
While I was being kicked off the
lot, I saw food trucks everywhere.
Everyone in Los Angeles
eats from them
and nobody calls
them restaurants.
Guys, I don't know
how many of you have seen...
Gabe, bring it in.
I don't know how many of you
have seen a premature baby before.
It's going to be really tiny, so
please don't say anything offensive.
Got that, bimbo?
Got it, bimbo.
Yes?
Knock, knock.
- Hi.
- Uh...
I don't want... What are
you guys doing here?
We wanted to say hi to the
newest little Dunder Mifflinite.
Well, meet our not-so-little
bundle of joy, Philip Halsted Lipton.
Philip is so fat.
Kevin.
You warned me not to say
anything if it was tiny, Oscar.
You didn't prepare me
for a big, giant, fat baby.
Yes, he's substantial.
Hey!
He's more than substantial.
He's a monster.
So this whole
hit and run thing,
there's this one part
I can't figure out.
You said it was
at a four-way stop?
Mmm-hmm.
And the victim rode his bicycle
into the left-hand turn lane,
but the perp was already in
the left-hand turn lane?
Mmm-hmm.
See, that's what I'm having
trouble with, because the fact is
you never said he
was on a bicycle.
Busted, Halpert! Yes!
Wait. No.
Andy, get out here!
I never said he
was on a bicycle.
I just said I
wasn't listening to you.
I am making
a citizen's arrest.
You have the right
to remain silent.
to beg for mercy.
You have the right to request
judgment by combat! Dwight's rights!
What's up, gangsters?
Jim was lying
about jury duty.
He was lying the whole time so
he could go do yoga or go canoeing,
I don't know what this
pervert likes. Fire him!
Dwight, not everything
is a conspiracy theory.
I have Jim on the record
saying that the victim...
Dwight,
I have me on the record
saying to you, take
a chill pill, all right?
I don't need to
take a chill pill.
Here, right there.
Down the hatch.
I really don't want
to take a chill pill.
That a boy, good.
Now, chill.
Okay, okay.
But let's just
say that Jim was lying about jury duty,
you would have to
fire him, right?
Yeah, sure. Of course.
I'd fire him to Timbuktu!
Ha-ha!
Good enough for me.
Ah!
And Pam was just going crazy
trying to take care of Philip,
because Cece has been
out of control recently.
Look, Andy, it doesn't matter. The
truth is I just feel terrible lying to you.
I feel terrible
getting lied to.
No one's ever
lied to me before.
Okay.
I think the best
thing to do right now
is just come clean
and tell everybody...
No. Not after what I told
Dwight about firing you. No.
Here's what
we're going to do.
We're going to have ourselves
a good old fashioned cover-up.
You ever heard of a
Connecticut cover up? No.
You know why you
never heard of it?
Covered it up.
Are you sure you can
keep this under wraps?
They used to
call me King Tut,
because I'm so good at
keeping things under wraps.
My nickname was
actually King Butt,
because I had
a king-sized butt.
Where do you
want it parked?
Okay, everybody!
Gather round.
Got a real special
surprise for you.
Ernesto!
Hola, Toby!
Uh, I'm going to say "I"
when I'm talking for Ernesto,
so instead of,
"He says blah, blah, blah,"
I'm going to say, "I say blah,
blah, blah," but that's for him.
Anyway, it was something
like, he remembers Toby.
"I remember Toby."
Oh, Jim. Hey, this
guy look familiar?
It's the empanada guy.
The empanada guy!
Holy . Damn it, Toby.
No, I wasn't asking you.
Ask him if he
remembers Jim.
No.
He says no.
He says no. Boom!
Yeah, but who remembers
all their customers?
I mean, I can name
like three of our clients.
He remembers Toby, the most
forgettable man in the known world.
He doesn't want
any trouble.
He sees lots of people,
they come from all around to
eat his delicious meat pockets.
Uh, you guys are going to love
these, SO empanadas on me.
You guys got to try them.
Usually I'm a burrito guy, but if
you won't tell, I won't. Wink, wink.
Great. And while we're enjoying
these delicious empanadas,
Jim, why don't you
tell us your story again?
Why? Everybody's heard it.
Walk us through it.
What time would you
get there every morning?
Hey, Murder, She Wrote,
how about we drop the whole
Murder, She Wrote thing, okay?
Jim was at the courthouse
for jury duty every morning.
How do I know?
Because I drove him there.
Why?
Because my car broke down.
His car broke down,
so he called me
because I live
near the courthouse.
Wait, wait,
you live by the courthouse.
You drove from near the
courthouse out to Jim's house
and then back to
the courthouse?
Thirty minutes out, 30
minutes back, easy hour.
And I would watch
that cute, little tooshy
scurry up those courthouse
stairs every morning,
and that was that.
I'm sorry, do you have
any American Mexican food?
We're getting
buried out there.
What was that stuff about
the car breaking down?
Well, I think you
handled it pretty well.
I'm not Rumpelstiltskin, Jim, I can't
keep spinning gold out of your.
Okay, listen, all right?
Dwight's onto us. He's going
to figure it out really soon.
So let's just get ahead
of it. Let's tell the truth.
I don't even know what
the truth is anymore.
Wow, it's so
healthy.
I'm going to call
him Little Kevin.
No, you will not.
Is he really five pounds?
Because I squat with five pounds.
This...
Yeah, this
feels like more than that.
No, no, no, he's nine
pounds, seven ounces.
Nine pounds? Really?
I thought you said five. You know
what? I was under so many drugs.
I felt like I was at a James
Taylor concert or something.
So, what did you bring?
Oh, yeah, I don't know
if it's right, but...
Well, if it's anything like that
gorgeous wrapping paper,
you hit it
out of the park.
Oh!
Preemie pajamas.
Again, it may not be
the right size, I can...
No, I think he came early
just so he could wear these.
Thank you.
I got Little Kevin
Call of Duty.
This baby is
clearly not premature.
They're lying about
the date it was conceived.
It's very interesting.
And her husband's gay. I don't
even know which thread to follow.
Uh, excuse me, can I have
everyone's attention for a second?
First off, I just want to
say that I'm really sorry.
I didn't know that
my absence last week
would have been
a burden on any of you.
Because, though I did
have jury duty last week,
they did dismiss me
early on Monday.
And I think you're going
to find this pretty hilarious.
I kind of, well,
maybe took the week off.
What?
Funny? No? Nobody laughed.
You're screwed.
Oh! It's happening.
It's really happening.
What the hell, Jim, I
covered for your bony butt.
Pam really needed some help
with the kids, so...
I promise my
intentions were good.
Your clients,
they're all mine.
Jim, I got my ass chewed out because
one of your orders got messed up.
And Andy, you said you
drove him to the courthouse.
Uh, I did.
Every morning. And if I
didn't, then I hope I die.
All right, well, let's get this
show on the road, shall we?
Allow me to give you
a hand. Here we are.
So long, clump mate.
I'm going to miss you.
Truth be told,
I never thought that this
was how it was going to end.
I always thought I was
going to defeat you somehow,
but you've
defeated yourself.
Dwight, cut it out.
I'm not firing Jim.
No, no, no, no,
you said...
I know what I said.
Jim, you're in deep
doo-doo, you understand?
And I have one
thing to say to you,
and I'm going to say it in
front of this whole office.
Look me in the eye.
That's it?
This is crap!
You've reached
Gabe Lewis. I'm currently indisposed.
Leave me a message. Ciao.
Gabe, it's Dwight again.
Highest priority,
triple urgent.
Call me immediately.
That means ASAP.
I'm going to find Gabe,
tell him what Jim did
and let the little stickler do
what he does best, stickle.
Honestly, I can return
this for a larger size.
It's fine. Pajamas aren't
supposed to be baggy, right?
It's not the barrio.
The only premature baby in this
room is the baby this baby ate.
Little Kevin.
Really?
Angela.
Fine. God.
Philip was conceived
nine months ago.
The Senator and I
wanted to wait,
but we had just seen Thor,
and there was way too much
wine in my chicken piccata.
Chicken marsala.
Right.
And, the point is, Philip was
conceived out of wedlock.
Hmm.
And now you all know,
but you can never tell.
I'm serious.
Dwight.
Hey.
Oh. Hey, have you
seen Gabe?
He went to the car or
something, but he'll be back.
Okay.
Don't you want
to see the baby?
Why? I know what Angela
and the Senator look like.
I can mash that up
in my head right now.
I promised I
wouldn't tell.
So don't.
Angela got pregnant
before the wedding.
What?
She got pregnant
before the wedding.
How long before?
A month.
You didn't hear it
from me.
Yes, I did.
Dwight?
Dwight.
I want to see the baby.
Well, Angela will make you cut
your fingernails. It's not worth it.
Oh!
Yes.
What a beautiful child. Prominent
forehead, short arms, tiny nose.
You will lead millions,
willingly or as slaves.
That baby is a Schrute, and
unless somebody taught Mose sex,
that baby is mine.
He's hungry.
Oh, that's my cue
to leave.
No, you don't have to. I'm
going to wear this cover.
Still.
You won't be seeing...
Do you want the giraffe?
Yes, I am bringing my kids
in to help me get out of this hole.
And you all remember
my beautiful wife, Pam.
Hi.
Wow, I really thought I'd
be more excited to be here.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Game
face, baby. Game face.
Oh, right. Okay.
Hey, Stanley,
it's great to see you!
No, that's overdoing it,
I think.
Hi, Stanley.
Split the difference.
Jim.
Okay. Let's go.
Hi.
Hi, everybody.
What?
Oh, hi.
How about
a little visit?
Wow. What a surprise.
That's crazy.
You guys get to meet
the little heck raisers.
Hey, Angela's back
with her baby.
Yes, well, you guys
all know Cece,
but we wanted to
introduce you to baby Philip.
You guys.
He's licking on my finger
just like my cat does.
Let me have a turn.
No, it's
the pacifier's turn.
All right.
Did you say
something about
this one bringing in
something for these people?
Yes. Cece wanted
to thank everybody
for letting her daddy stay home
with her all last week and play,
so she brought
you a little treat.
Oh, cookies?
No. But that would have
been a really good idea.
That would have
been really good.
No, she
brought you drawings.
Oh, my goodness,
let's take a look at these.
They're usually amazing,
so let's see. Yep, they are.
Uncle Andy.
Oh!
Aunt Phyllis.
Wow. These are incredible.
Cece, did you do these?
No.
She says no to everything. You
know, she thinks my name is "No."
Cece, do you want
some broccoli?
Yes.
No.
It's crazy.
Why am I shorter than the
table that I'm standing next to?
There is
crosshatching in some of these.
That's kind of advanced
for a 2-year-old.
Cece, this is your
big sister, Kelly.
Did you color
this pretty picture?
No.
So then this
means nothing to you?
Hey, Cece,
why don't you draw another
picture for us exactly like this one,
or at least in
the exact same style?
You know what? I don't think
you need to do things on command.
That's very weird. Just
take that. Thank you.
I think we should just wrap
up the show, kiddos, right?
I don't know what
else we can do here.
Okay. All right.
It's okay, sweetie.
All right.
All right. Okay.
It's okay.
I know. I know.
Shh.
Angela, this child is definitely
mine. He looks just like me.
Every baby
looks just like you.
Your face kind of
looks like a baby.
Need I remind you that we were
together a month before the wedding?
That is completely untrue.
Completely true.
Remember?
No.
You said that Robert
was not fulfilling you.
And I said that I
could fulfill you,
and you said,
"I'd like to see you try."
And then I kissed you with the
force of a thousand waterfalls.
That didn't happen.
Then I inserted my
penis into your...
No! Stop it! Dwight.
...vagina and...
And even if it did,
it's just a coincidence.
Admit that there is
a chance. I will not.
Admit it.
I will not.
It's not...
All done?
Yes.
Yes. He's sleeping.
Before I go, may 1?
Sure.
Watch the head.
Nurse! You know that
baby in there? Baby Philip?
Cancel the circumcision.
Who are you?
I just might be his father.
I don't know
what that means.
We're going to
circumcise him.
Cece, want to come?
No!
Want to come play?
Oh, bud, I know.
Do you have a pacifier?
Yeah. I'm looking. I'm
looking for the pacifier.
Cece!
Okay, we're going.
We got to go. All
right, we're going home.
I know. I know, bud. I know.
You gotta grab her.
I'll go grab her. Okay.
Okay. Here we go.
Here we go.
Okay, I'm just going to go down
to the car, and I'm going to put her
in her seat and
I'll be right back up.
We'll see you tomorrow.
No, no, it's okay.
I'll be right back.
No, just go home.
It's all good.
We got this.
I have a kid.
Last week,
Jim at home,
that was no vacation.
Jim, just go.
Hey, we'll be just fine.
Thanks, guys.
All right, here we go.
Let's go.
Oh!
Phew!
Dwight, what the hell?
You can't smoke in here.
Oh, all right.
Ah!
The office looks
different now. Mmm.
Smaller.
Maybe I just feel bigger.
Hello, Gabe.
You had something
important to tell me?
Oh. You know, I did, but now
it seems infinitely insignificant.
Jim? Oh, right.
No, forget it.
He was doing it
for his kids. I get it.
Kids drive us dads crazy.
Sometimes I feel
like they're raising us.
Am I right?