DINESH: So, as you can see,
since I became CEO,
our user growth, undeniable,
our retention, so sticky,
it's pornographic.
We're lean, we're exploding.
And we're more mission-focused than ever
in providing the best video chat
the world has ever seen.
Wow. Well, this seems
really promising, gentlemen.
Promising, indeed.
- I think if We just...
- "Promising"? (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
You're a young associate here,
so, I'm gonna help you out, okay?
We have a lot of these meetings set up.
We will be fine.
What he means by that is...
But you, you don't wanna be known around
here as the guy who fucked this up, okay?
So, when you hip your bosses to our numbers
and they get visible hard-ons,
have them move quickly.
Erlich, you're with me.
- It's "hards-on."
- What?
"Hards-on," not "hard-ons."
It's a syntactical error
that I could have remedied
if you'd just given me the space to speak.
Erlich. I'm seeing you Thursday, right?
You better believe it. I can't wait for it.
- For...
- For Jian-Yang's pitch.
His new idea sounds super exciting.
Yes, well, he is white-hot right now, and
that's why I had him reach out directly,
and we can't wait to pitch you the idea
that is gonna be pitched to you.
Great. I'll see you then.
- You have no idea what it is, do you?
- Not a fucking clue.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
(MUSIC PLAYING ON HEADPHONES)
MEN: (CHANTING)
Always blue! Always blue! Always blue!
- Always blue! Always blue!
- (COMPUTER CHIMING)
Always blue. Always blue. Always blue...
- Hey.
- Always...
Richard? Hey.
What's... There you are. What's going on?
You celebrating something?
We were just chanting.
- Why? What, the pitches go well?
- They went fine, you could say.
You said they went awesome.
All right. Thank you, Big Head.
I mean, I did get us a few offers.
We did receive more than a few offers,
as few often refers to "three".
And today, we're four for four.
(CHUCKLES)
Huh.
- Which... I mean, what does that even mean?
- Nothing. Nothing at all.
(CHUCKLES) Look,
you don't have to do this, really.
It was my choice to leave the company,
and besides, my lnternet thing is going
great. Really, it's going very well.
So, lwant you to succeed,
and I want you guys to be happy.
Sure you do, slugger.
(SIGHS) Stop. Really.
- It's cool. I mean that totally honestly.
- Keep it positive.
Um, I should go skype my dad, I think,
and tell him the good news.
Um, it is good news, though, right?
'Cause we were all sort of,
like, happy and celebrating, but now...
Now, it feels sort of weird...
- Let's go, Big Head.
- Okay.
- It's good?
- Yes.
All right, well, enjoy. Carry on.
Always blue. (CHUCKLES)
- Jared.
- Okay.
- Always blue. Always blue...
- RICHARD: Sorry.
Dinesh, lthink
you accidentally disabled my access keys
for the video chat data repository.
No, actually, I deleted them on purpose.
I've purged all our ex-employees'.
Gleb, Sanjay, Elisabet, you...
Gleb? What, you're comparing me to Gleb?
When we agreed to split the company,
we said that you could take
the algorithm for your video chat,
and I could use
the data flowing through the system
to optimize the algorithm for my thing.
We had a deal.
We had an agreement, not
technically a deal.
What the fuck, Dinesh?
Play, play. Blue, blue.
Always blue, always blue.
Have fun, you're having a party.
You got pizza and everything.
Always blue...
So, what, I should've got it
in writing, Dinesh? ls that it?
You wanna lawyer-up now?
You know, we're just some guys in a house.
But I don't wanna be
just guys in a house, Richard.
That's the whole point.
I want PiperChat to be a real company.
And after all the bullshit we went through,
no offense,
I finally got some real financing
lined up for us.
I cannot have another
lntersite on my hands.
That was fucking Russ
and his shitty tequila.
You know that, man. You were there.
That wasn't me.
Richard, it happened on your watch.
I'm sorry. I really am.
But the answer is no.
Okay. Well, suck a dick.
I'm sorry. What did you say?
- Nice blazer.
- Thank you.
- Where'd you get it?
- DINESH: Does it matter?
Ijust wanna know where I can get one,
so I can look like a
total fucking douchebag.
Wow, right?
Unbelievable.
Gents, why don't we take
this party outside?
Yes. We live in California,
we should take advantage of it.
Gavin, you told me to interrupt
if Jack Barker came to see you. I'm sorry.
Yes. Send him in. I thought Barker
would crack after one day in that basement.
The fact that it's taken him two weeks
to fess up about hijacking my fucking plane
and resign,
will make it all the sweeter.
Hiya, Skipper. Sorry to barge in.
I owe you an apology.
Really? Whatever for?
When you stuck me in that basement,
I was like,
"Jack, what the hell did you do wrong?"
And I'm sorry that it took me so long
to get it through my thick skull.
I finally figured out
what this was all about.
Well, I'm glad to hear it.
You are doing exactly
what Bobby lger does over at Disney.
What?
He makes every manager spend
one day of the year in the Goofy suit.
Because sometimes,
you just gotta be at product level
to be able to see the best path forward.
And once I realized that, it was like,
ka-pow! "lt was so obvious."
It's the algorithm.
Pied Piper put middle-out in their vid
chat, and it's amazing now. I know.
I'm on that all the time with my grandkids.
We could use middle-out
to revamp our entire suite of products.
We can make billions, Chief.
I'm whipping up some proposals right now
that are gonna knock that wig
right off your head.
Yeah.
What the fuck is he up to?
Look like a fucking wig to you?
The point is, Jian-Yang,
you don't set pitches.
I handle the scheduling,
that's the symbiosis of our relationship.
- No.
- What do you mean, "No?"
No.
Jian-Yang, PiperChat has
some real heat, okay?
And we can draft off of that,
but it has to be
a carefully choreographed dance.
You can't just wiggle your little tush
and expect every VC in the Valley
to get hards-on.
I am your lead investor,
you will respect me as such.
I do not respect you.
You're not any kind of investor.
You own nothing.
I own 10%. You live in my incubator.
- No, you evict me, I evict your 10%.
- What are you talking about?
"Santa Clara Sheriff's Department.
Vacate or be forcibly removed."
To be fair, Jian-Yang, I filed this when I had
no expectation that the system would work.
- Okay.
- Jian-Yang, just tell me...
Can you just tell me what the idea is,
so I can gauge
how aggressively I should pursue it?
Hey, Jared, you were there, right?
When we split the company into two,
- Dinesh and I had a very...
- No, no. Stop, stop. Please stop, Richard.
- What?
- What are you doing?
What do you mean?
I'm complaining about Dinesh. He sucks.
- He's my boss now, Richard.
- Well, your boss is being a real prick.
Richard, we have to
bifurcate our relationship.
You and I can no longer discuss business.
All right? We can talk about anything else
two guys might talk about.
We can talk about
sports teams and their scores, or pussy.
But you and I cannot,
and will not discuss business.
(SIGHS)
Hey, man. For what it's worth, lthought
it was super fucked up, what Dinesh did.
I know what it's like to be the one guy
not in the company, you know?
So,
if you want my login, it's all yours.
Really?
- Yeah, man.
- Thanks.
(SIGHS) You know, I shouldn't do this.
Dinesh said no.
- And also, these are Skyrim cheat codes.
- Oh, shit. Yeah.
DINESH: My Bloomberg interview is on!
"How did I come up with PiperChat?"
That's a very good question.
I guess the tech gods
were just speaking through me.
Somehow, Iknew to take
the best parts of the service
as substandard and crappy as HooliChat,
and make it... (INHALES SHARPLY)
How do I put this?
Incredible.
Do you think
I have too much product on my hair?
Nope. I think you should use more.
Wait, are you saying that
because you think I look ridiculous
and you want me to look
more ridiculous next time?
Which answer will get
more of that stuff in your hair?
Wait, wait, wait, watch this.
This is where I make Emily Chang laugh.
Quite a turnaround for a company
that wasn't exactly soaring.
Oh, it was soaring, Emily.
Right into a clogged toilet.
- And not just like a standard clogged toilet.
- (LAUGHS)
Like, I don't need a plunger,
I need a shovel and a bucket.
But enough about the previous leadership,
which was inept, lame, bitter...
Fuck it. We had a deal.
Thanks.
(MOUSE CLICKING)
That's weird.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Hey, Richard. Have you seen the new
Sports Illustrated Swimsuit Edition?
The cover model has the most lovely,
enigmatic facial expression.
Jared, I don't really wanna
talk about guy talk.
I'm here to tell you that I think
Dinesh may be in some serious trouble.
Okay, so, I was analyzing a
bunch of user data, and I...
No, no, no. Richard, Richard.
I told you, I can't talk about this.
You have to bifurcate.
No, Jared, listen,
you're gonna wanna hear this...
Wait. What do you mean
you were looking at user data?
You violated our system?
Richard, you were inside us?
Don't tell Dinesh,
and don't tell any of the other guys, okay?
"Don't tell Dinesh?"
Richard, Dinesh is my CEO.
- Oh, God.
- What are you doing to me?
- Did I make you angry?
- No. (GROANS)
I'm trying to save his ass, okay?
I'm trying to save you.
Just survey the users.
And make sure you ask
how old they are, okay?
And then, that's it. That's it. That's it.
No more.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Stupid fucking Jian-Yang and his shitty
app. I don't even know if it is shitty.
You know, I could probably
find out about Jian-Yang's app.
He asked if he could
practice-pitch it to me.
- Do you have any nines?
- Go fish.
Wait, this could be great.
What time are you guys doing that?
I could listen in.
I don't know. He asked if he could
pitch me, and I said, "Sure,"
and then he just kept talking for a while.
Oh.
You don't think
that could have been the pitch, do you?
- God damn it, what did he say?
- Jeez, I kind of zoned out.
Shit. Fives?
Uh, go fish. Wait.
I don't know if this would be relevant,
but he did say the word "Oculus"
a whole bunch.
- Wait. "Oculus"?
- Mmm-hmm.
Oh, my God. It's a VR play.
That's the frothiest space
in the Valley right now.
Nobody understands it,
but everybody wants in.
Any idiot can walk into a fucking room,
utter the letters "V" and
and VCs will hurl bricks of cash at them.
Then, by the time they find out
that it's vaporware, it's too late.
I have got to get in on this.
Trust me. Just give me five minutes.
There he is.
Wait, is that our lawyer?
Hey!
I thought he was in jail.
Hey. Perfect timing.
Ijust completed the detailing on this Kia.
Come on.
What the fuck is going on?
Wait, I don't understand.
How did Richard have access
to our user data?
Someone must have let him in. lt was you.
You're a fucking rat, Jared.
Richard entered us without consent.
In spite of that,
he has raised a real issue here.
Fuck this. I'm gonna Uber home.
Mr. Monahan, good luck
with this whole work release situation,
but I have more important things to do.
Mr. Chugtai.
It appears that 33% of your users
are under the age of 13.
It's also apparent that you have no
parental permission requirements in place.
You're going to want to sit down for this.
- Are you familiar with COPPA?
- Who?
It's the Children's Online
Privacy and Protection Act.
This act establishes strict guidelines
to protect the privacy
of younger children on the Internet.
You are in gross violation of this act.
You know how kids can't have a YouTube
or Facebook account till they're 13?
It's because of this.
Yes, but our users are chatting
with each other, Jared, not some old creep.
- No offense.
- None taken.
My shame will linger
even after my voting rights are restored.
Now, are there records
of these chats on your sewer?
Yeah, we store everything.
What... Okay, what's going on?
How serious is this?
Each violation of COPPA
carries a penalty of $16,000.
So, we're fined $16,000? Oh, no.
I hope they take cash.
$16,000 per user.
Not only each user, each use.
Fifty-one thousand estimated underage users
times an average 25.6
chat sessions per user
times $16,000..
- $21 billion?
- (COMPUTER CHIMES)
I mean, how is that even fucking possible?
I mean, I knew Dinesh was going
to fuck this all up, but honestly,
this couldn't get any better.
What's with his shirt?
He sort of became ill on himself.
I was wrong. This just got better.
This is all your fault, Richard.
This was your company before it was mine.
What are you talking about?
Dinesh, I specifically reminded you
to port over the terms of service
from the platform.
Right. And I asked if you'd done it,
and you said you had.
Okay.
I checked the TOS box
when we submitted it to the App Store,
but then I didn't end
up doing it, all right?
And then when we caught fire,
the last thing I wanted to do
was to bog our users down
with legal bullshit, you know?
I mean, nobody reads that stuff, anyway.
Well, first of all,
everyone reads the terms of service,
and secondly, they would have given us
legal cover from exactly this.
- (COMPUTER CONTINUES CHIMING)
- Every sound is $16,000.
- Fuck!
- All right, all right. Don't think about that.
Just think about how to solve
this massive, massive problem.
Quickly. Quick as you can.
Jared, just...
- Wait. We could shut down.
- (ERLICH COUGHS)
No, no, no. Not when we're this close
to signing a term sheet.
And in case all of you
gents have forgotten,
I'm on the hook for half a million Clambos
for this thing.
Well, we can't stay online!
We're just racking up more fines!
Well, technically, this is a corporation.
So, whatever they fine you,
they'll really only be able to collect
what the company is worth,
which, at this point,
is, basically, nothing.
That's right. I'm just the CEO.
I'm not personally liable.
Although...
- Although what?
- (COMPUTER CHIMING)
Well, when you lied to me
about adding terms of service,
it could be argued, you violated
your fiduciary duty to the company,
rendering you personally liable.
I mean, if the FTC brought us to trial, I
could be compelled to testify against you.
Jared, I trusted you.
Oh, trust has nothing to do with it,
but thanks for making that official.
So, I could be personally liable
for $21 billion?
Yeah, most likely.
I know in the fable, Pied Piper led
all the children into darkness,
but now, we're doing it.
So, what do you wanna do?
- (COMPUTER commues CHIMING)
{GAGS)
(STRAINING) I'm gonna throw up again.
I'm gonna watch this.
GAVIN: I want full surveillance
on Jack Barker 24/7.
HOOVER: I don't recommend
using conventional listening devices.
He may sweep for those.
I do have a colleague at Facebook
that has a laser microphone,
you can point it at an office window
from a mile away
and read the sound vibrations.
I like it.
Hoover, you're the only person I can trust
at this goddamn company.
- It's good to have a friend.
- I understand that, sir.
Ah, Gavin, there you are.
Well, I don't want to interrupt
your talking with Hoover
and talking and talking about things.
- But I have some concrete news.
Regarding?
Jack Barker.
By foregoing western gadgetry,
simply stationing myself
in the hall outside of his office,
I was able to overhear him
speaking of his plans to move against you.
He even referred to you as "Gavin Smelson."
I knew it.
Good work, Denpok. Good work.
Let's go slice this bastard in half, yeah?
Hold on. We need proof.
Otherwise, he'll just deny it, and it'll
just be a case of "he said, she said."
Good point. Denpok, who was he talking to?
Oh, um...
Alas, I could not see this
from my hidden vantage point.
Hlcheckthelogs
and see who was in his office.
No, because...
No one was there.
I'm confused. Was he on the phone?
Yes. Very perceptive.
- Easy, I'll just pull up his phone records...
- No.
Not the "phone" phone.
So, what was he doing?
Was he video chatting?
That's what it was, chela.
- Even better, I'll pull up the chat data.
- You can do that?
Well, as long as he was on HooliChat.
But the bastard kept grinding in my face
how much he loved PiperChat.
- What if he was using...
- PiperChat!
- Yes.
- Fuck!
He said the resolution was
so vivid and superior to HooliChat.
Ah. Sadly, now,
we'll never know the identity of the person
with whom he was definitely talking.
- Unless...
- Unless what?
RICHARD: Dinesh?
Hey, man. How's it going?
Bad.
Well, look. I've been there, man.
- No, you haven't.
- Lhave.
One time when we were
pitching at Ross Lorna,
I threw up in my pants.
(CHUCKLES)
Don't you mean "on"?
Nope.
No, I mean "in."
We were pitching, and, well,
things weren't really going well.
I was getting nervous,
and, I don't know, lthink
I must've eaten something bad that day.
Anyway, my stomach was upside down,
so I made a beeline to the stall.
But then I pulled down my pants, sat down,
but instead of shit, I
threw up into my pants.
Well, lwas CEO for 11 days.
And in that time, I violated the
rights of 50,000 little girls,
exposed them to sexual predators,
and racked up fines
the size of a small nation's GDP.
Yeah. I threw up in my pants. (CHUCKLES)
Fuck.
What do I do, Richard?
- There are no right answers.
- (SIGHS)
You know, when lwas CEO,
I found that it was more about choosing the
one wrong answer that you can live with.
I really loved that video chat.
(PHONE BUZZING)
Hello?
This is he.
What?
(WHISPERS) It's Gavin Belson.
It's Gavin fucking Belson!
Hey. Gavin Belson. What's up?
Oh, my God, we're crushing it.
All the time.
I'm in a bathtub.
Yeah!
(CHUCKLES) Of course. I'd love to.
Bye.
He wants to meet me at Josephina's tonight.
Did I say yes?
(SCOFFS)
Holy shit.
Gavin Belson wants to acquire PiperChat.
He made the same call to me back when
he wanted to make an offer for Pied Piper.
He could take this entire shit-bomb
off Dinesh's hands?
Where's the fun in that?
More importantly, I could get
all my money back. Maybe even more.
We could 10X this motherfucker, gents.
- Although...
- Although what?
Well, I'm sorry to play the Cassandra again,
but Dinesh can't sell Gavin the company.
- Why not?
- Why the fuck not?
It's due diligence.
Gavin doesn't trust anyone.
When I worked for him,
he tried to microchip me.
Before he finalized any acquisition,
his legal team would uncover
our malfeasance.
They'd sniff out the
user issue immediately.
And they'd probably turn you in.
And you do not want that.
I mean, there's also the moral quandary.
Even if he could get away with it,
could Dinesh really sell the company
knowing it's basically a sizzler buffet
for the sexually deranged?
Of course he could.
Because even if there is
a 1% chance of success
and a 99% chance of failure, and prison,
he will do the right thing
and get me my money back.
I'm sorry, Erlich. I've made my decision.
I'm gonna say no to Gavin Belson,
shut it down, and just see what happens.
(YELLS) What the fuck? Huh?
What the fuck?
Jian-Yang!
Hey, Gavin. Well...
Dinesh. Thanks for coming.
Listen, Gavin. I've thought about it, and
if this is about you buying PiperChat...
I didn't come here today
to buy your company.
You didn't?
No. I came to take it.
I thought I'd have to buy you out,
and lwanted to know
what kind of CEO I'd be dealing with,
so, I had my comms people pull your press.
Like this interview you did with TechCrunch,
where you describe PiperChat as, and I quote,
"Exactly like HooliChat,
but without the suck-ass parts," end quote.
Or the one you did with Emily Chang
where you told her how you took
"the best parts of HooliChat
and made them less crappy."
I was about to throw you
a massive acquisition deal.
And then I realized you'd already
publicly admitted to stealing my IP.
I hope you have a good lawyer.
- He works at the car wash down the street.
- What?
Look, Gavin, you do not wanna do this.
- I can't explain exactly why...
- Shut up.
This is not a negotiation.
If you fight me, lwill win, and lwill
fuck you in the tech business forever.
No one will hire you. I'm taking PiperChat.
By 8:00 a.m. tomorrow,
you will hand over to Hooli
all your data and systems.
All your users
will be converted to HooliChat users.
It will be like PiperChat never existed.
And what you get out of it
is the chance to walk away
and try and get anotherjob in this town.
You have five seconds to decide.
- Five, four...
- Okay.
So, we're in agreement.
For a 10% stake in your current venture,
you will receive full pool privileges,
more room in the crisper,
and you may live in my home for...
- For free.
- For free for six months.
Fuck you. One year.
Fuck! Fine. Fine. It's a deal.
Deal.
Jian, I mean,
your onerous terms notwithstanding,
I'm very excited to be a
part of your VR play.
_IIVRII?
- VR, virtual reality.
- Who's doing VR?
- You are.
That's what Big Head said.
- This play has to do with the Oculus, right?
- No.
But he said that you said "Oculus."
He said you kept saying it,
"Oculus, Oculus, Oculus."
Octopus.
(SOFTLY) No.
No.
Octopus?
- It's a water animal.
- |...
I know what an octopus is. Just...
What does your application
have to do with octopus?
Eight different ways
to make a Chinese recipe octopus.
So, ljust traded one year of free rent,
full pool privileges,
and more room in the crisper
for an application that is just
eight recipes for octopus? Hmm?
Yes.
Hey, guys. They're ready.
- Ooh. Ooh.
- (KIDS LAUGHING)
What the fuck is this?
I went through every chat in his history.
They're all the same.
Perhaps it was another chat format.
Could you acquire Skype or FaceTime
and check them as well?
- What?
- (DOOR OPENS)
Gavin? I'm sorry...
I need to talk to you about
this PiperChat acquisition.
I put together a panel of the most active
users you ported over from PiperChat.
Bear in mind, this group is representative
in terms of gender, race,
and most importantly, age.
Now, who else thinks changing to
a HooliChat login is hella lame?
Madison, Allison, Jennifer, Stephanie,
Quinn, Ingrid,
Kaylie, Ava, Sarah...
Oh, no.
Janelle, Carl.
Now, Carl, you said the new sign-in page
made you nervous.
Did anyone else feel nervous?
- GAVINI (POUNDING AND SHOUTING) Fuck!
- (GIRLS GASP)
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)