RICHARD: Just think about it.
On Saturday, over a quarter-million people
are gonna stream through that building.
A veritable who's who of nobodies.
Richard, we've tried
marketing at trade shows.
We suck at it.
No, I'm not talking about that.
Let me ask you this.
We need 120,000 phones, right?
What is the first thing people do
when they get in there?
Log on to free WiFi.
But Hooli makes you download
the Hoolicon app in order to sign in.
So what if we somehow
hack our code onto the app?
Then we will have our 120,000 phones
all in one day.
I'm sorry, you're...
You're talking about sneaking our code
onto people's phones
without them even knowing about it?
I mean, that's malware, Richard.
No, no, no.
Think of it more as, um, forced adoption
through aggressive guerrilla marketing.
Well, as a product of forced adoption,
I can assure you, there are consequences.
- I like it.
- DINESHI Well, hold On.
Even if we get our code
into that app and onto all those phones,
people are just gonna delete the app
as soon as the conference is over.
People don't delete apps. I'm telling you.
Get your phones out, right now.
(CELL PHONES BEEP)
Uh, Hipstamatic. Vine,
may she rest in peace.
NipAlert?
McCain/Palin?
All right, this works in theory.
But penetrating the Hooli servers
to hack their shitty convention app?
We need a black-hat ninja for this one.
I wonder where we can
find someone like that.
No.
- So great to see you, Mia.
- (CHUCKLES)
- How's Pakistan?
- So great.
I was there for a while,
and as I said before,
I have to go back there right after this
for an extended period of time.
Anyway, how's all this stuff going?
- You must be, like, dying of boredom.
- I am.
And the terms of my plea agreement
forbid me to touch a computer
or go online, so...
Let me run a hypothetical by you,
just to like, exercise your brain.
Like, for instance,
if I had to hack the Hooli app servers,
mess with an app,
and push it out over a venue's free WiFi,
how would I do it?
It's a trick question, right?
'Cause you wouldn't hack the app server.
You'd just launch a man
in the middle attack with pineapples.
Google it.
Speaking of,
if they even catch me talking about this,
they could send me
to maximum security prison,
but I think I found a way to get online.
No!
There's a computer in the library
that's not supervised on Sundays.
I think if I can pull library duty,
I'll be able to sneak on
and track down whoever ratted me out.
I am going to destroy that motherfucker.
Not if I destroy him first.
(WOMAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ON PA)
Excuse me.
What's your policy on anonymous tips?
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
GILFOYLEI Fuck.
WiFi pineapples. It's so obvious.
Not to me.
Look, we set up
a bunch of these at Hoolicon.
We position ourselves between
everyone's devices and the real WiFi.
So they log onto our boxes,
and our boxes log onto the real WiFi?
Exactly.
So we show them a fake landing page
and force everyone to download
a doctored version of the Hoolicon app.
And they'll never know the difference.
No wonder Mia's in prison. She's brilliant.
I think this might actually work.
Wrong. It'll never work.
You don't even know
what we've been talking about.
I don't need to, Richard.
The truth is we've tried and tried.
Every time we've gotten a whiff of success,
a giant pelican by the name of fate
takes a four-and-a-half-pound shit
right on top of us.
There are people
who are destined for greatness,
and people who are not.
Richard, it seems you and I are not.
And so, I've had enough.
I'm ending it all tonight.
Suicide? I have a book for you.
N0, Gilf.
Last night, when I was sitting out there
by the smoldering husk of my palapa,
so cruelly taken away from me...
You burned it down yourself.
Which led me to my epiphany.
This epiphanY-
"Greetings from Tibet.
"If you find yourself in Qamdo Prefecture,
do drop in.
"Gavin Belson."
That was addressed to me.
No, that was addressed
to "Richard Hendricks and Company."
"Company" of which I am a part.
You're not seriously thinking
of going to Tibet?
GILFOYLE: You're broke.
How the fuck are you gonna pay for that?
That's where you come in.
My great friends,
I figured we might pass the hat.
Just give whatever you're
comfortable with...
I'll pay for it. Whatever it costs.
Well, it seems the smallest of us
has the biggest heart.
Thank you, young Jianathan.
- Business class?
- Premium economy. You fly one way.
Don't you need a visa to go to China?
Yes. I can call my uncle in Beijing.
He's very corrupt.
That sounds ominous but, gents,
as I was saying,
where there's a will there's a way.
Just not for you guys.
JARED: N0.
I will not help you on this mission.
IINO"?
Richard, we always said
we didn't want to end up like Hooli.
How are we like Hooli?
We are trying to give free Internet
to the entire world.
If we have to bend a few rules
here and there...
I mean, it's all for the
greater good, is it not?
Gavin Belson started out
with lofty goals, too,
but he just kept excusing immoral behavior,
just like this,
until one day all that was left
was a sad man with funny shoes.
Disgraced, friendless,
and engorged with the blood
of a youthful charlatan.
I am never going to be any of that.
Richard, not that long ago,
you agonized over using a stolen log-in
to get into a bake-off with EndFrame,
a company that stole from us.
But now you're, what,
shrugging off large-scale cybercrimes
against innocent civilians?
It's a means to an end.
It's not who I am.
I mean, (STUTTERS) Lincoln had to suspend
habeas corpus to end the war,
but he restored it after.
Lincoln? Richard, it's not that easy.
There's always a next time,
and a next time, and a next time.
I cannot knowingly contribute
to your moral decay.
Well, what if you didn't do it knowingly?
I mean, you're always telling me
how you spent your entire childhood
pretending that everything
going on around you was okay.
Uncle Jerry's game.
Yeah, that.
Let's play Uncle Jerry's game.
Do you know what you're asking?
Okay, guys. How we looking?
- One second.
- Almost done.
GILFOYLE: All 12 pineapples
tested and packed.
RICHARD: Jared, you can come in now.
All right.
All of our swag is in the car,
and I look forward to a successful promotion
of our legitimate space-saving app.
Yep, that's what this is.
Whatever.
Well, now, gentlemen, this is it. Goodbye.
Obviously, I don't care
to make a big deal out of it.
So I think it's sufficientjust to go around
and each of you say a memory or two
of times where I've
profoundly impacted your life.
Doesn't have to be a profound impact...
We're leaving now.
What?
International flight. Four hours early.
No, international flights
are three hours early.
It's a new rule.
(CHUCKLES)
Gentlemen.
Okay, let's have some fun!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
RICHARD: First hurdle down,
we're past security.
DINESH: Ugh, that made me nervous
sneaking all that shit in.
GILFOYLE: Why? We're bringing tech
to a tech convention.
When did Pied Piper
get added to the vendor list?
JARED: C-42-10.
Oh.
Well, it looks like us.
JARED: Oh, no. That can't be.
No. This is not what I was promised.
What? It's fine.
Well, they told rne that we would have
prominent placement
with proximity to high-traffic corridor.
(LAUGHS)
We're in the middle of the road here.
- So?
- Yeah, who gives a fuck?
Well, Jared does.
And... And we do as well. Uh...
You know, why don't you go check out
what the bathroom situation's like?
Yes.
- Nothing would make me happier.
- Good.
You know, I actually believe him.
(SIGHS) okay-
So gentlemen, okay,
while Jared's gone, let's get our bearings.
All right.
So, uh, we are here.
Now you guys deploy the pineapples.
Start with high-traffic areas,
so that means entrances.
People are setting up equipment everywhere,
so it shouldn't look that unusual.
But be careful, don't get caught,
and remember why we're here.
WINNIE: Richard?
Whoa. Winnie!
- Hey.
- (CLEARS THROAT) Hello. Hi. Yeah.
- Oh.
- (BOTH CHUCKLE)
I haven't seen you since, um...
Since you threw yourself
down a flight of stairs
to prove how smart you were.
That whole spaces-tab thing was...
Kind of petty?
Petty? No, I was gonna say illustrative
of our vast differences, but...
Right. (CHUCKLES)
What are you doing here? (CHUCKLES)
I'm here helping my friend
- launch his new company.
- Oh.
Well, "my friend." He's
actually my boyfriend.
That's his booth right there.
RICHARD: Oh, wow. He's got a big one.
I mean, the booth.
But, um, boyfriend? Uh-oh.
- Awkward. (CHUCKLES)
- VVhy?
Nothing. It's not.
It's actually... Uh, it's cool.
Totally cool. Cool beans.
Beans, beans, magical fruit.
The more you eat, the more you...
- Toot?
- Toot.
Hey, Joel? Come over and meet Richard.
Oh. Not needed.
- Joel, Richard.
- Yeah. Hey.
Oh. Stairs guy.
- Uh, it's quite a booth you got there.
- Oh, yes, thank you.
We really think our company's message
is worth getting out there.
Yeah, us, too. Us, too.
Um, but just, you know,
trying to be a bit responsible
with the spending.
Sure, but when I sold my last company,
I realized I had the luxury
to invest in something I believe in.
- RICHARD: Mmm.
- Helping humanity thrive.
That's why I decided to bring
PeaceFare into the world.
Ah, good for you.
- Okay. It was great to meet you, Richard.
- Yeah. And you, too.
Good seeing you.
Not if I see you first. (CHUCKLES)
Not that you asked,
but you handled that very poorly.
You know, Jian-Yang,
the silence in the car
gave me some time to think about the fact
that our differences...
Jesus!
Sorry.
(TIRES SCREECH)
(ECHOES) Jian-Yang!
- Fuck you, fat fuck.
- Pineapple two is a go.
Fucking look at him.
Pictures everywhere, fucking bearded baby
cost us millions of dollars.
It would make me very happy
to pour boiling metal
down Keenan Feldspar's asshole.
- How would that even work?
- Flip and pour.
He's gonna run,
and then you're slowly chasing him,
trying to not spill your
vat of boiling metal.
You're gonna look like a fucking idiot.
GILFOYLEI Fuck you.
- Anybody looking?
- DINESH: (WHISPERS) No. Just go.
(CLICKING)
What's taking you so long? Hurry up!
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
What are you boys up to?
All right? All right, go through my slides.
Click, click, click. Jamiroquai plays.
Now I would very much
like to welcome my good friend,
Keenan Feldspar!
- Where the fuck is he?
- KEENAN: Yo.
Son, you're supposed to be
coming up from over there.
Totally. I'm just really kind of
digging the vibe over on this side.
- Uh, Terry?
- TERRY: (ON PA) Yeah.
- Kid wants to come from over here.
- TERRY: Okay.
Excuse me, sir. Do you have a moment?
This morning, Pied Piper were
a last-minute add to the vendor list.
So I started watching them
and noticed some suspicious behavior.
I've sent in for a tactical response team,
and with your permission,
I'd like to sweep the convention floor
with Yagi antennas, which are...
- Hoover?
- Yes, sir.
Four days ago, I spent two billion dollars
on a piece-of-shit VR gadget
that's never gonna work.
I had to rebuild the
entire operating system
just to get a 90-second demo
that could play on a phone.
And by the grace of God,
ljust may have pulled it off.
And now you want to talk to me
about Pied fucking Piper?
Sir, I'd like to think that
if Gavin Belson were here,
we'd make sure that...
Gavin fucking Belson is not here
'cause I fired his ass!
Now, look, you go back
to your little security room
and you sit in the corner
with the tinfoil hat on.
And I swear, ifl hear you wander
down the hallway to take a piss,
you are out on your ass.
You got that?
I do, sir.
You know what, this might be a good time
for me to hand out some flyers.
(WHISPERS) Richard,
six pineapples up, six to go.
Good.
GILFOYLE: Something wrong?
Yeah, actually.
(CLEARS THROAT) Very wrong.
- PeaceFare is a game.
- DINESH: What?
Yeah. Look at his website.
Give virtual coins to
virtual homeless people.
Grow virtual corn
to feed virtual starving villages.
What the fuck, right?
I mean, he's over there making all this
noise about turning your mobile device
into an empathy machine,
but it's not doing anything.
Fascinating, Richard.
Have you heard anything
about how Pied fucking Piper is doing?
Yes, our code is in the app.
The pineapples are online.
We're at 3,700 downloads.
We're ahead of schedule.
Shit, this could work.
That's awesome.
Yeah, exactly.
We are doing something real.
He is not.
But, uh, she's with him
and I'm the petty one.
Okay, well, what about the idea
of growing real corn
to feed real starving people?
- No.
- Yeah, his thing seems way easier.
You can do it on your phone
in your underwear.
Just plant the rest of
the pineapples, please.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
Oh! Here he comes, folks.
Richard Hendricks,
the Monet of compressionism.
Jared. (CLEARS THROAT)
Hey, which of the bathrooms is closest?
Um, end of the row, 78 paces to the right.
Great.
You know, this is the actual laptop
I used to code the app.
Hey, let's take some
without my shoes, yeah?
Okay. Okay, come.
Yeah, so please start with my toes.
(CHATTER CONTIN U ES IN DISTINCTLY)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Did you do this?
Did anybody see someone touch this laptop?
- What?
- Oh, God.
This is very disturbing.
Fuck it, I'm just gonna punch him.
Yeah, right. Have fun in jail, you moron.
Holy shit.
Oh, fuck. It's him. What do we do?
Uh, keep moving.
Fuck, do you think he saw us?
- Oh, he saw us.
- Fuck!
- He saw us see him.
- Shit.
Wait.
What if he thinks we did it on purpose?
Like, we snubbed him?
Fuck yeah.
We just snubbed the fuck
out of Keenan Feldspar.
- Hey, Richard.
- Hey.
I'm letting everyone know you might want
to reset your critical passwords
- because we've been hacked.
- Oh.
(STAMMERS) Why would you say that?
Well, someone changed
my PeaceFare screensaver,
and I know it wasn't anyone on my team
because they all respect me too much.
What did they change it to,
if you don't mind me asking?
- Just 'cause...
- No, no. lwon't dignify it by repeating it.
I'm just saying you
should take precautions.
Also, Winnie spoke to security
and they're sending
the tactical response team.
(CLEARS THROAT) The what?
The... Oh. Here they are.
Oh, shit.
Bingo. We've got hostiles.
Red team, Sebastian,
fan out and sweep the entire venue.
(BEEPING)
Hey, Richard.
Guess who has four thumbs
and just snubbed Keenan Feldspar?
Us.
Guys, someone called security.
- Now they're doing a sweep of the area, okay?
- What?
You've gotta go pull up
all the pineapples, okay?
- What the fuck?
- Who ratted us out?
I don't know. Probably we'll never know.
It's impossible to tell.
Just go. Go get them.
Get them now. Go, just go.
Oh.
Bingo.
DINESHI Fuck!
Come on.
(GRUNTS)
Bingo.
DINESH: Oh, crap.
We gotta split up. I'll take the food
court, you take the east concourse.
- I want the food court.
- Just go!
Fuck.
Hey, man.
(HESITATINGLY) Fucking Keenan.
Hey. I have to go.
Totally. Hey, did you snub me earlier?
No.
Yeah, you did.
You know you did.
- It made me feel bad. I like to feel good.
- (SIGHS)
Why would you do that to me?
Seriously?
You fucked us, Keenan.
Richard was gonna take that deal,
and then you pulled it
right out from under us.
You cost me, personally,
a shit ton of money.
Whoa. ls that what Richard told you?
(BEEPING)
- Hey. So?
- They got every single one.
- Every single last one.
- Fuck!
JARED: I don't want to hear this.
RICHARD: But we gotta be close, right?
Like how many more phones do we need?
I don't know. Close isn't good enough.
No, this is binary.
Either we have enough or we don't.
Oh, fuck.
I have an idea.
So I've got one pineapple left.
Now I've rigged some batteries on top of it
because we're gonna have to go mobile.
- Oh.
- We have to try.
Okay, I'm going to put
this in your backpack.
- Oh, no.
- No, it's fine.
I don't want it... I don't want it...
And you, you're gonna
hold this kill switch.
And then you'll walk into the most
densely populated area you can find.
All right? If you see the security coming,
remember, you press that button and poof,
- you're gone. Yeah?
- Okay.
I'll get as many
of those motherfuckers as I can.
We'll be rewarded in the end.
When the fuck were you gonna tell us?
Tell you what?
- You know what, fat sack of shit.
- Richard, do you know what?
N0, I don't. (STUTTERS) I don't know what.
Dinesh, you need to move.
- Well, not until I find out if you know what.
- (SIGHS)
Go on.
Okay, fine. I messed
with Joel's screensaver.
And then he told security,
and now they're the ones
pulling up all the pineapples.
- So...
- What the fuck are you talking about?
What are you talking about?
You acted like you wanted
to take Keenan Feldspar's offer.
Well, ljust ran into him.
He said you turned him down.
(STAMMERS)
Okay, well, (CHUCKLES)
who are you gonna believe, me or him?
Him. He showed me the email you sent him.
Showed you the email.
You fucking snake!
Dinesh, you need to move. Now.
Look, he pulled the deal.
Yeah, but you didn't know that
when you sent him the email, did you?
- Dinesh, you need to move.
- (BEEPING RAPIDLY)
Come on. You need to go.
- Go, go!
- TENLEY: Gentlemen?
(BEEP5)
I'm going to have to see
the contents of that backpack.
- Um...
- (RICHARD STAMMERS)
Bingo.
Huh.
(RICHARD SIGHS)
What did you change it to, Richard?
What?
Joel's screensaver.
- Does it matter now?
- No.
PoopFare. (SIGHS)
I'm sorry.
"PoopFare"?
Yeah. It's like a play on the name.
Is it a play on the name?
PissFare would be way better.
Or PenisFare.
Or PeaceFart. That's just
changing one letter.
Look, he turned around.
I had like a second, okay?
It's the best I could come up with.
PoopFare?
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
You sacrificed everything
that we've worked for
for "PoopFare"?
How was PoopFare for the greater good?
It wasn't.
You compared yourself
to Abraham Lincoln, Richard.
Can you do me a favor?
Can you say it
so I know I'm not hallucinating?
- I just did.
- Just say it.
- Jared...
- Richard! Look me in the eyes!
Look me in the eyes,
and you name our undoing.
Hey, come on. Calm down now.
PoopFare? You reckless child.
Gentlemen. Come with me, please.
Sit down.
Well, well, well. Richard Hendricks.
Sorry, do I know you?
No. But I know all about you.
These WiFi pineapples, are they yours?
Uh-huh.
And this image from the security footage.
GILFOYLE: Smell anything?
These two individuals look familiar to you?
Last question.
Do you recognize this?
It's an interview I just found from
Code/Rag from October of this year,
in which you said
you and Gavin Belson would, quote,
"Put Jack Barker out of a job."
Did you say that, Richard?
You know what? Yes. Yeah.
Yep, this is me.
Because, apparently, everything I
say or type gets me into trouble.
Because I'm an idiot.
HOOVER: Well, now.
- Tenley!
- (DOOR OPENS)
What the hell are these gentlemen
doing in my office?
We caught them with pineapples.
You mean the pineapples that I hired them
to bring to the conference
as part of a covert penetration test
of our WiFi security?
Sorry. Uh, we didn't know.
HOOVER: You weren't supposed to.
Now, give these gentlemen
their passes and equipment back,
and get them back on the floor.
You know, you said some very nice things
about Gavin Belson in that interview.
You could have very easily
kicked a good man when he was down.
Good luck with whatever it is you're doing.
I'd walk you down myself, but for
reasons I really can't get into, uh,
I'm not allowed to leave this room.
Okay.
There you are.
You never came back to the booth. You
didn't want to see how it all turned out?
I wasn't really in the mood.
Are you playing PeaceFare?
Yeah, ljust gave an orphan
her first calculator.
Good. Good.
(CLEARS THROAT)
But I've got something much better.
See that number?
That is the number of installs
that we've got from Hoolicon alone.
We have moved all of Melcher's data
onto a network of mobile devices.
We did it.
Do Dinesh and Gilfoyle know?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, they know.
Now that this worked, they like me again.
They're off getting churros to celebrate.
I told them that we would meet them
at, uh, Barker's keynote.
So, come on.
I mean...
Richard, the fact that you think that
success justifies all your behavior...
We were in crisis mode, okay?
And, yeah, I lost my head,
but crisis averted.
So it's time to reinstate
habeas corpus, huh?
Be Honest Abe again.
What about the next crisis, Richard?
Jared, this won't happen again. I swear.
So let's just enjoy it.
For a minute. Please.
(VIRTUAL INSANITY PLAYS ON SPEAKERS)
JACK: Come on, give it up!
- (AUDIENCE CHEERING)
- I love this company!
And how about you?
And how about Jamiroquai?
Ladies and gentlemen. Oh, let's have it.
But wait a minute,
wait a minute, wait a minute.
Wasn't the original title of their
chart-topping hit Virtual Insanity?
Why is he singing "Virtual reality"?
(SCATTERED LAUGHTER)
You know, I may need a little help
getting to the bottom of this
from my very good friend,
- Keenan Feldspar!
- (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS ON SPEAKERS)
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
JAC KI Oh!
- There he is! Hey!
- (BOTH CHUCKLE)
You guys ready to see the future?
(CHEERING)
You know, at the beginning
of the presentation,
I told all of you
to update your HooliPhone OS.
Right?
Nowl want you to go into settings,
and you're gonna find
a brand-new toggle labeled "Hooli VR. "
- MAN: Whoo!
- You're gonna want to turn that on.
- (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS ON SPEAKERS)
- Novv, look under your seats.
When you power up your Hooli VR goggles, they
will automagically pair with your phone.
Put them on, and prepare to be amazed!
(AUDIENCE EXCLAIMING)
- KEENAN: Say hi to that barmaid for me!
- (LAUGHS)
- Huh. Oh! Ow!
- (CRACKLING)
- (CRACKLING CONTINUES)
- (PEOPLE EXCLAIMING)
(EXCLAIMING)
- (CRACKLING AND POPPING)
- (SHRIEKING)
JACK: What's going on?
Uh, turn up the lights, please.
Something's happening here. Uh...
- (CRACKLING AND POPPING CONTINUE)
- Uh, stay calm.
You don't think this had anything
to do with us, do you?
We appear to have
a bit of a technical problem.
I'm going to get
to the bottom of this right away.
- (POPPING CONTINUES)
- l\/lANI Oh, fuck!
Gelong-la, there is
a loud man here to see you.
He says you sent for him.
Qamdo in the house! Ha-ha!
Whoa!
Haircut!
Are you fucking kidding me?
No.
I'm really here.
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)