Thank you for coming to me.
Ladies, lords. Thank you
for your pledges of support.
Captain Gosset, how goes the count?
Our outposts at Hareburr and Currlye
have pledged 25 soldiers.
Lebnin has pledged an additional 30.
Lebnin considers it an honor,
not just a duty, Your Majesty.
I stand with you,
as my father stood with your father.
When we combine that
with our Pennsan troops...
Nothing from Altoona? Can that be so?
Lord Diego, is it?
Your Majesty, Altoona stands ready
with an additional 20 troops.
Ten less than Lebnin.
Your city is twice as populated.
We are approaching the planting season.
The town council felt that
the farmworkers must continue to plant,
or we will face a shortage.
Lord Diego, are you at all aware
of what transpired at Kanzua?
We all heard tales of your suffering.
Tell me, if I destroyed
your home in front of you,
drowned everyone you knew and loved,
murdered your wife and your children,
would you be worried about crops?
My apologies, Your Highness.
Perhaps we should
go to Altoona and find out.
The Trivantians
made contact. They wish to meet.
Lord Diego, I ask again.
How many troops do you pledge?
Thirty troops, my queen.
Very well.
Captain Gosset?
The count continues
with chambers in Monroe.
Do you ever imagine
the fire is speaking to you?
When I was alone after Father died
and you disappeared,
I swore it told me secrets.
Why didn't you tell me.
Trivantes requested a diplomatic summit?
Because it doesn't matter.
Imagine Father's reaction.
The mighty Triangle frightened of me.
Begging me for peace.
- We have to consider it.
- Why?
We have righteousness on our side.
God leading the charge.
Yeah, well, even so, on the battlefield,
the men must believe.
- In God?
- In you.
They must believe that their queen did
everything in her power to protect them.
My men will do as they're commanded.
Sibeth.
A soldier must believe in his cause,
must believe in his queen,
must love her to the point that
he would be willing to die for her.
Imagine if you could stop Trivantes
from encroaching on our land
without sacrificing a single soldier.
You already have their obedience,
but if you manage this,
you would have their love.
It's never been done.
Well, when was the last time
the Trivantians asked for a parley?
- Never.
- That's right.
Maybe having God on your side means...
you win the war without
having to fight the battle.
The Trivantians have no queen or king.
I cannot negotiate
with common politicians.
Of course not.
But I can go as your emissary.
As the princess and as your sister,
I can speak for you.
Very well.
Thank you, Sibeth.
Of course, any treaty
will require a formal apology
and reparations for
the attack on Kanzua.
What? You know that's not possible.
We're going to win a war without
fighting a battle, are we not?
I would say anything is possible.
So you thought
your wife was dead, but she wasn't,
and now you're about
to be together again.
You must be so excited.
I'm excited, and I've
never even met her.
Of course, it's complicated
now that she's a princess.
Strange, isn't it?
That she never once thought to mention
that she was a princess.
It's hard not to think of an omission
like that as a lie of sorts.
Ooh, if I were you, I'd be thinking
the entire relationship was a lie.
But you did raise two children together.
It would be hard
to lie through all of that.
I imagine if I were you,
I'd be very angry.
Also, confused and nervous.
But also so happy that she's alive.
Oh, I suppose I wouldn't
know how to feel.
What do I know?
I've never even been in love.
Maybe that's 'cause you
talk too much.
I, uh... I think it's dead.
I could, uh... I could
run drills with you.
See how you do with something alive.
I only fight soldiers.
And bales of hay, apparently.
Come on. It'll be fun. We...
You're right.
That was exhilarating. Thank you.
I'm not going to risk the wrath
of the princess
by putting a scratch on her boy.
Now, go away.
Toad!
I couldn't save my sister.
I couldn't help my dad.
I need to be able to defend my family.
I'm too used to having
other people do it for me.
I'm sure the princess can
appoint you a proper trainer.
You're right. I'll ask
her to appoint you.
And why me?
Because we get along so well.
I'm done training for the day.
- General, sir.
- Lieutenant, come.
- It's sharp.
- Yeah.
Virgin steel. Put through
a new forging process.
Wielded properly, it won't be stopped.
I'm rearming the entire battalion.
Here.
This one is yours.
I don't understand.
Didn't the Triangle offer the Payans
an overture for peace?
The queen doesn't
falsely accuse another nation
unless she is looking for a fight.
The peace talks will fail,
and we will make sure they do.
You have been very vocal
with the Triangle.
If something goes wrong,
they will lay the blame at your feet.
Which is why you will go in my place.
If there's a chance for peace with Paya,
shouldn't we try for it?
As it is, we're overcommitted
on the western front
fighting the Ganites.
Wren.
The Payan queen has grown bold.
She's forgotten who we are.
It is in the best interest of the
republic that we remind her.
All right. This way. Stay close.
It's Tamacti Jun.
Wait here.
Go.
I told you to wait
while I gather intelligence.
Is she here or not?
Princess Maghra is here
and safe for now.
You're not telling us something.
She's with the queen.
That's all I know for certain.
And Kofun?
I've heard nothing.
His Witchfinder escort was traveling
without the benefit of compass maps.
Perhaps we arrived first.
Let's go find her.
Seek out the highest house.
The queen will have
fortified herself there.
You're not coming?
The queen thinks I'm dead, which
is how it will have to stay for now.
I need to make contact
with those Witchfinders loyal to me
and be assured of their
continued service.
We'll need their support
if we're gonna confront the queen.
- And how will we find you?
- I'll find you when it's time.
Tread lightly with the queen.
She's unlike anyone you've ever known,
and you're in her realm now.
I can handle myself.
Yes, but less well without your head.
I still don't trust him.
I do not either. But he has
made no false steps yet.
We cannot travel in such a big group.
Paris, you stay here with Charlotte.
We'll send for you once we find her.
I must stay close to keep Haniwa safe.
And who has kept Haniwa safe
for the last 17 years?
Here.
Keep that safe.
Carefully, Baba.
That must be it.
She'll be very happy that we're here.
- She's a princess now.
- She's still Mom.
What if she's not? What if
being here has changed her?
Then we'll rescue her.
Two guards. Six steps.
Guards, six steps.
Identify yourself.
I'm here for Princess Maghra.
The princess does not
receive visitors at the palace.
Move on.
- She'll receive me.
- I said, move on!
Haniwa!
- Maghra!
- Mama!
Stop!
Dad! Dad!
Stand down.
Baba?
No. A bear.
I found you.
I knew you would.
- Mama.
- Haniwa.
Oh, my girl.
- I thought you were dead.
- It's all right.
You're safe now.
I found you. I found you.
Maghra.
You didn't tell me
we were having company.
Baba.
This is Lord Harlan.
- This is his house.
- Honey, please. Our house.
- What?
- Baba. Listen to me.
Baba? This is Baba Voss?
- I am.
- Huh.
I'm Harlan, Lord of Pennsa,
and this is awkward,
but I'm married to your wife.
Baba. Come upstairs.
- What is he talking about?
- Come upstairs, and I'll explain.
Come.
Yeah, let's all go upstairs.
Have a hot tea.
You... You're gonna stop speaking.
- Pretty unlikely.
- Not if I tear your throat out.
And make our wife a widow?
So, this is Baba Voss?
Who is that?
"Who's that?" Only your
queen, that's all.
Welcome, Baba Voss.
And did I hear my sister
call Haniwa's name?
Please.
I'm Haniwa.
My prayers have been answered.
My sister's family
returned to her unharmed.
My babies.
You must all join me for dinner.
We must toast your safe return.
You think she means right now?
The mighty Baba Voss.
Your legend precedes you,
and you did not disappoint.
You walked through my guards
like they were nothing but tall weeds.
They didn't seem very tall.
Some of the world's finest soldiers.
You send them to hunt children.
There's no wonder
they can't fight a man.
Baba.
It's fine, Maghra.
He needn't be polite on my account.
After all, we're all family here,
are we not?
- Hear, hear.
- Mmm.
Besides, as a former
Trivantian soldier and a Slaver,
it's only fair to expect
a certain lack of table manners.
Sibeth, please.
Wait... You're a Slaver?
Seriously? Wow.
I mean, not that I'm judging, but...
- No, I am judging. A lot.
- You be quiet.
Yes, Harlan.
Be very quiet. Like a little mouse.
I just find it so wonderfully ironic
that a Payan princess would marry
a Slaver out of all people.
Though I suppose
Jerlamarel didn't leave you
much of a choice now, did he, Maghra?
Abandoning you like that?
Oh. I apologize,
Lord Harlan...
...for discussing your wife's
ex-lovers in front of you.
No, it's fine. It's fine.
We all have our pasts, don't we?
For instance, this used to be
my house. Now it's yours.
And the great dance continues.
Mmm, you make an interesting point.
Since my birthright determined
my future from a young age,
I have no excitingly
scandalous past to speak of.
I suppose I envied Maghra, in a way.
The freedom,
selfish as it seemed,
to choose her own path
with no regard for others,
no sense of responsibility for anyone...
Respectfully, Your Majesty,
Maghra has devoted her life
to loving her husband,
raising her children,
and serving the Alkenny people.
Respectfully,
mountain woman...
it is because of my sister that
the Alkenny are traitors to the crown.
The Alkenny cannot be
traitors to the crown.
The Alkenny people are no more.
If a hidden tribe
disappears, how are we to even know?
Enough.
Our father
forbade the discussion
of politics at the table
for a very good reason.
Well said, my dear.
- Who'd like more wine?
- Mmm, I would.
It's funny.
When we were children,
I was the romantic.
Maghra always swore she'd never
marry, and yet, here we are.
I'm the spinster, and she has
two husbands at this table alone.
I meant no offense, Baba Voss.
I love my sister dearly,
even though she's lied to me,
betrayed me.
You are my
husband. I love only you.
I would still kill or die for her.
I imagine it's the same with you.
Oh, and you, of course,
Lord Harlan. Mmm.
It's an honor to be in
such fine company.
Do you recognize my voice, soldier?
I couldn't possibly because you're dead.
Only on the inside.
The queen said you took your own life.
The queen has always had
a troubled relationship with the truth,
wouldn't you say?
Not out loud.
So... what happens now?
What indeed?
Kofun, Haniwa,
you must know your mother
never stopped searching for you.
From the moment you were separated,
you were all she thought of.
It's unfortunate she must go
on a journey now just as you've arrived.
- I wish it were different.
- Journey?
What journey?
What is she talking about?
I didn't get a chance to tell you...
It's a mission
of the utmost importance.
Maghra will serve as my emissary
to receive a peace delegation
from Trivantes.
You're leaving now?
It's only for a few days.
I... I have to.
- I'm coming with you.
- Me too.
- No.
You're members of the royal family.
Too valuable a prize
for the Trivantians to pass up.
They wouldn't even know we were there.
You're the future of this kingdom
and quite possibly the world.
We cannot risk any harm coming to you.
My sister is right. You will stay here.
I just got you back.
I will not lose you again.
- Mama.
- Haniwa. Your mother has spoken.
Maghra, the Trivantians will
not send a peace delegation.
They do not negotiate.
I wouldn't call it a negotiation.
They're going to grovel.
The Trivantians have never
groveled, and they never will.
They've never had
a truly worthy adversary.
- You?
- God.
Their soldiers will slit your god's
throat and drink its blood.
Yet it is the Trivantians
who have sued for peace.
It is a trick or a trap.
Baba, we have to try.
If there's even a chance...
There is not.
Then we'll defeat
them on the battlefield.
- There is even less chance of that.
- So what would you have us do?
The Trivantians are consumed with
the war with the Ganites to the west.
Do nothing to draw
their attention to the east.
- What if it's too late for that?
- Then surrender.
Spoken like a true Trivantian.
You must understand.
I needed him to keep us safe.
That little worm down there
doesn't think so.
That's just his manner.
Baba. You've always trusted me.
And you have lied to me
for all that time.
Well, you of all people know the
pain of a past best forgotten.
You were happy to be reminded, Princess.
The princess who ran away from Paya died
the day I pledged myself
to you as your wife.
Then let us leave this place.
Let us take our children
and return to the mountains.
We were happy there. We can be again.
- If only it were that simple.
- It is that simple.
You are my wife, they are our children,
and this is the past you wish to forget.
Well, these are my father's people.
He begged me on his deathbed
to protect them from my sister,
and I failed him.
I abandoned Paya, and so
many died at Sibeth's hands.
I'm the only one who can
truly challenge her for the throne
and save the kingdom.
So princess isn't good enough.
Now you wish to be queen?
Only until I've ensured a lasting peace,
and then I'll hand power over to Harlan.
Maghra, Harlan is making you his tool.
No. I have made him mine.
You are forgetting
what is most important to you.
You, me, Haniwa, Kofun,
we are what matter most.
I would die for my children.
I'm not asking you to die for them.
I'm asking you to live for them.
If I run off...
If I run off, if I turn my
sister against me again,
Haniwa and Kofun won't
be safe anywhere ever.
I have kept us safe for 18 years.
I can protect us out there.
- I cannot do that here.
- I know, but I can.
I can protect them and you.
Oh, good.
Good, you're both here.
Now, let's talk about
sleeping arrangements.
Now, obviously,
in the usual circumstances,
I am open to group activities.
- Harlan.
- Why do you think my bed is so big?
Stop it.
Forgive me.
Just trying to make the best
of a delicate situation.
You even tell him this is my
house? This is my house.
No one cares.
You're drunk.
Yes.
And with good reason, I think.
Look, Baba... Bab... Voss,
I don't care what you do in here
with my wife... Our wife.
Doesn't matter.
But it will be bad for all of us
if people were to find out.
Secret alliances only work
if they stay secret.
If he keeps talking,
- I'm going to feed him his own throat.
- Shh.
Is he like this with everybody?
Leave us, please.
As you wish.
You know, in time, Baba Voss,
you will come to realize
I'm not your enemy,
but that makes me no less dangerous.
I may have lost my house,
but this is still my city.
And you would be well advised
to watch how you speak to me.
I need you. Now more than ever.
Baba?
What did they do to you?
I had to get her back.
I honestly don't know
what the queen's thinking.
Witches in the royal family?
Does she think the people
will stand for it?
There will be rioting at her gates...
Lower your voice,
or the queen will have your tongue.
Presage.
Is that you?
I am called Paris.
Paris.
I have an urgent message
for the princess.
You're the soldier
who brought Kofun to Pennsa.
Yes.
He told me the others
were less inclined.
We had our orders. I followed them.
And now, whose orders do you follow?
For 20 years, I have sworn
my allegiance to the
Witchfinder general.
Not an easy habit to break.
I will make sure Mag...
The princess gets this.
That day, in the woods.
You touched me.
I wonder what it must feel like
to know things that will happen
before they occur.
Mainly it means I'm always concerned.
Never
thought of it like that.
Speaking of those concerns...
You protected Kofun before.
Do the same now.
Stay close to him and keep
him away from trouble.
I pulled him into this world.
He is past listening to me.
I will do as you ask.
Good. Good. Thank you.
But...
only because it is you doing the asking.
You are called Toad?
Yes.
That is a stupid name.
A failure of imagination
on the part of my parents.
Wait here.
Princess Maghra.
I hear a dead man speaking.
Then listen closer.
Is it really you?
Tamacti.
I hear congratulations are in order.
There was a wedding?
Yes. While you were dead,
I've been trying to fix things.
By marrying a lord?
The Pennsan soldiers are loyal
to Harlan first and the queen second.
That's good.
We'll need all the forces we can get
if we're going to overcome your sister.
We're all in agreement.
Harlan is a valuable asset.
- When do we move?
- I'm working as fast as I can.
Explaining why I'm not dead
when I killed myself
in the service of the queen
is proving complicated.
- How much time?
- More than we have.
From what I hear,
your sister is days away
from marching Paya into war.
Perhaps not.
I convinced her to let me arrange
a diplomatic summit with Trivantes.
Why would the Trivantians discuss peace
when they never declared war
in the first place?
It's a delay.
To allow the soldiers to march
from the western front.
You said yourself the Trivantians
are heavily occupied
on the western front.
Well, they can't possibly
want war in the east.
There may very well be
a chance for peace
even if they do have ulterior motives.
As long as your sister is on the throne,
there will be no peace.
However, killing the queen,
or even deposing her,
is no simple matter.
There are many laws in the strands
all designed to protect the monarch.
- And you know all these laws?
- No. Not all.
I do.
So you gather your Witchfinders,
and you let me worry about the laws.
Do you have a plan?
More than one.
So different
from how we grew up.
You should see Trivantes.
It makes Pennsa look tiny.
It's an incredible place.
Except for the slaves and
how they kidnapped you.
- Not all Trivantians are bad.
- Ow.
I met someone there. Someone like us.
- Really?
- Yes.
And no relation to Jerlamarel.
Both of her parents are blind.
So it's not just Jerlamarel's line.
Sight's really coming back.
You don't sound too happy about it.
Look at what it's done to the world.
Look what it's done to us.
It wasn't vision that
destroyed the world.
It was people.
They can do that with or without sight.
Look at the queen waging
war on Trivantes.
She's protecting her people.
Isn't that what queens do?
Why are you defending someone
who hunted us our whole lives?
She didn't know we were family.
If Mom had spoken up, maybe
we wouldn't have had to hide.
Mom was protecting us.
Maybe.
Maybe she was protecting herself.
I would trust our mother
over the queen any day.
What about Jerlamarel?
You trusted him. And Boots,
you vouched for him too.
Do you really want to taunt me
while I have a blade to your scalp?
Sorry.
I am too.
For everything.
All right.
Are you sure about this?
Do it.
- Paris?
- Yeah. Here. Come.
Sit.
Sit with me. Hmm.
So, a shift in the world.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you
about all of this.
About who I really was.
Maghra, I know who you really are.
As for this, I am glad
you did not tell me.
I would not have kept
your secret from Baba.
He's so angry.
And how would you have him be?
Finding his wife married to another?
I've explained that.
Did you explain to him why you concealed
that you were a daughter of Kane?
He doesn't wanna listen to me.
I can't run away from this.
I have to stay.
For Haniwa and Kofun.
You stay for Haniwa and Kofun?
Who else?
The crown is your birthright.
It is no small thing to wear it.
You know...
it was you who started
this whole journey.
You who taught Haniwa and Kofun to read.
Told them the tales
of the great Jerlamarel.
Their father.
I would never have left the mountains.
It was only a matter of time.
The mountains could never contain you.
I've missed you.
Kofun.
What are you doing out here?
Listening to the world.
What do you hear?
Everything. Come.
Close those eyes of yours.
Let the sound fill your mind.
Now, what do you hear?
Nothing really.
Nothing is never nothing.
Even the absence of sound is telling.
Dad.
Shh, I know. I heard him come.
Just relax.
He's breathing slow.
He's not on the hunt.
There. He's gone to rejoin the others.
Are you angry at Mom?
What your mother does, she is
doing for you and your sister.
And what about for you?
I was sure you'd throw Harlan
off the roof when you arrived.
I considered it.
You can't let Harlan win.
Harlan doesn't matter.
This whole place doesn't matter.
We are together again.
I just have to figure out
how to get out of this place.
Back to where we belong.
I can't think of any place
where we all belong anymore.
Wait, I hear it.
Tell me.
Yeah?
Lord Harlan, your brother's horse
was found running in the orchards.
Saddled and riderless.
Well, it wouldn't be the first time.
Kerrigan has a habit of grabbing
the nearest horse when he's in a rush.
Look, um, put her in my stables.
He'll pick her up when he's home.
Sir, this satchel hung on the saddle
with a message for you.
Oh, no.
No.
What happened?
What is it? What happened?
Kerri.
Kerrigan.
I'm so sorry.
Kofun?
Ah. How are you settling in?
Very well, thank you.
Would you like some?
Sure.
Your mother. This house.
It must be a lot to take in.
It is.
Something troubling you?
I forgot for a
moment you were sighted.
I imagine you're able to see my pain?
Yes.
What a gift that must be.
It also means I have no choice
but to trust you.
Because it's a secret.
Kofun.
It must stay between us.
Of course. It will.
I lost the baby.
He was taken from me.
I'm so sorry.
When the people find out...
In our village, it happened all
the time. People will understand.
This is not your village.
And I'm not an Alkenny mother.
I stood before the entire city
and announced my child.
A sighted child who now will not come.
They'll think I'm... I'm
no longer chosen.
That I'm no longer God's queen.
So tell them the truth.
They will understand. They will
feel for you, just like I do.
I... I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Thank you, Kofun.
I'll confess. I came here
because I needed to open
my heart to someone.
I felt strongly that I could trust you.
I felt that from the moment we met.
Do you feel you can trust me?
I don't know.
Because my Witchfinders
killed your people?
Yes.
I hope I can help you understand
that if I'd known it was
Maghra and her children,
I...
- I don't want you to hate me, Kofun.
- I don't know you.
But I want you to!
I want you to know me.
Being queen is very lonely.
I've been alone for so long,
I feared I lost the ability to connect.
But I already feel connected to you.
There's something about you
that soothes me.
That fills me with hope.
Hope for what?
The future of Paya.
I'll not live forever.
This holy kingdom may someday
rest on your shoulders.
It is too much weight for
any mortal woman or man.
I have only borne it because
through all my years on the throne,
there's always been somebody
at my side, inside of me...
guiding my every move.
- Are you talking about God?
- Yes, Kofun.
Without whom, we are dust.
I will show you
- how to seek God's counsel...
- Sibeth.
...so that you will know her voice
when you need it,
and she will know yours.
Listen. To hear her,
you must first feel her.
Let her flame warm you,
as the God Flame warms the earth.
Oh, yes. Feel her.
Ah. Yes.
Feel me, Kofun.
Lose yourself in me,
and you will find God.
Yes. Feel me.
Feel me.