I need what I asked for... today.
Or we'll pop round, pay Jenny a visit.
Whatever he was doing,
he didn't want anyone else to know
he was doing it. Tell me that's not dirty.
He's making a decision on the roll
of a dice. Who to kill, when to kill...
whether or not to kill.
Jenny.
I'm sorry.
I'm really, really sorry.
- Justin, I can't talk tonight.
- We've got another one.
It's started again.
There's two of them.
Somebody stop him!
Somebody stop that man!
♪ Love is like a sin, my love
♪ For the ones that feel it the most
♪ Look at her with her eyes like a flame
♪ She will love you
like a fly will never love you. ♪
I've got to go to work.
- Oh.
- Yes, I have to.
Cos if I don't show up,
they're gonna wonder why.
Can't afford that.
The police are not our biggest worry
right now.
Toby's grandmother is.
We have to move his car.
Hey.
Oi.
I know what you're going through.
I don't think you do.
- I just...
- Only two things matter right now.
And one... is, this was self-defence.
And two...
I'lL never let anyone hurt you.
Ever.
Now, Toby's car is still downstairs.
I don't think I can do that.
Jenny, listen to me. When we're scared,
we don't think straight.
Are you scared?
Yeah.
But if we act like scared people,
we're gonna get caught.
We don't want that, do we?
No.
So I'm gonna need you to help me carve
some time to think this thing through.
Yeah?
What about him?
All right.
Listen to me. Jenny, while I'm gone,
you've got to clean this place.
Use the stuff in this bucket.
OK? Get rid of the bucket.
And I'll be back as soon as I can, OK?
- I know what I saw.
- I'm not saying you don't.
- So what was Luther doing?
- I don't know.
- But you asked him?
- I did, yeah.
Well, what did he say?
"Not to worry, just a misunderstanding"?
At which point, you rolled over
and let him tickle your tummy.
- It wasn't like that.
- Then what was it like?
You've gotta help me, Justin. I'm twisting
in the wind here. I don't know what to do.
I don't know which way to turn. I'm asking
for help and you're giving me nothing.
How bad?
Three dead, four injured.
Stab wounds and chemical burns.
This is the last known victim,
Richard Gardiner.
Younger brother, brother's fiancée
among the injured.
- Killer?
- No sign.
SOCO found this a few hundred yards
down that way.
The killer dropped his wallet
in the chase.
No ID, just cash and a keycard.
Do we know to what hotel?
No. There's a lot of myths
about those things.
All they contain is
a check-in and check-out date.
There's no way to identify
the hotel it came from.
So what do you think's going on?
Do you think we've got a copycat?
No, I think we've got two killers
in competition.
If we can find out the rules
to the competition, then we can stop 'em.
Find out what door that opens.
- Sir, show me the other side, please.
- There's an advert on there.
Got anything I can clean that up with?
I'll see if Benny
can do something with it.
- Brothers?
- No. More than that.
They're twins.
Twins with a shared psychosis.
Turning one will not be easy.
It might not even be possible
without a map into their heads.
We don't even know what their names are.
- I think you're right.
- About what?
It's a scoring system.
You score a certain amount of points
for who you kill,
and then you get bonuses for
where you kill 'em and how you kill ‘em.
So it's a sort of a tally
of experience points.
- Experience points?
- Yeah, a way
to measure your progress
through a game.
So... these men are...
killing with hammers, knives, acid,
because they have yet to score enough
points to graduate to better weapons?
- That's definitely a possibility, yeah.
- And when this man
has bludgeoned and stabbed
enough people to death,
then he qualifies to kill even more people
with, what - guns, bombs?
We'll catch him
before it gets to that point.
- Ideas as to how?
- We've got this.
- We think it's an encrypted password.
- To what?
- If we can decode it, we can tell you.
- What do you need?
Well, it's a non-repeating,
randomised sequence.
- Like a book code?
- Exactly like an old book code.
To break the code...
We need to know the book
he's used to make the encryption.
But not just the right title,
we need the exact edition.
So it's the password,
is the way into this.
- What have you got?
- Er, the advert's
for the Frangipani restaurant.
I'm checking with the owners
to see if they can remember
which hotel advertised them
on their keycards.
Find it, call me and I'll meet you there.
- Will do.
- I won't be long.
Er, Mr Kasemsarn?
This is DS Gray from
the Serious and Serial Crimes Unit.
I'm enquiring about an advert
you put out on a hotel keycard.
You know what you're doing
and where you're going?
I think so.
What if I get stopped?
Does this look like it's my car?
Don't get stopped, all right?
Buy some SIM cards.
Don't use one SIM card more than once.
If you do get stopped,
don't say a word, not even your name.
Tell the duty solicitor to call me
and I'll come get you.
Okey-dokey.
Oi! Don't get stopped.
All right, go on, then.
Easy on the accelerator.
All right, go on. Put your seatbelt on!
Not very good, are you, Frank?
No, but apparently it's what you do
when you get to my age.
So what happened to your pet polecat?
How do you mean?
Where's Toby?
He didn't show?
What can I say?
The kid's an embarrassment.
Do me a favour, Frank.
You tell him
I need more time,
more consultation
and way better manners.
Sir.
Right, good news is, we found this laptop.
Oh, yeah? So what's the bad news?
We need to find a particular book
- to break the password, yeah?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, well, wait till you see this.
It'll take weeks.
But it's not right, though, is it?
Not right, how?
Well, I mean, in order for a book code
to work, you need the exact edition.
That way, if you lose your book...
You can get another copy
of the exact same edition.
Right, but all this, this lot here,
this is all
second-hand junk shop copies, innit?
I mean, how are you gonna get
an exact copy of that?
Eh? Or... or that?
No.
I need to see another room.
Gideon's Bible.
There's one of these in every hotel room
in the country.
The key to breaking that code
is in this book.
Get that and that laptop back to Benny.
Are you...
You know, are things all right?
You solve your problem?
I'm on top of it.
I'll meet you back at the shop.
Toby's missing.
What do you mean, he's missing?
Nobody's seen him since yesterday.
That's not missing. That's... late.
Not for Toby.
He's had an argument with Frank,
so he's probably embarrassed,
had a drink
and decided
to screw himself into a coma.
What kind of argument with Frank?
You can't blame Frank.
I mean, he was doing a decent job.
Toby... Toby is out of control.
Best I can do
is keep my ear to the ground
and if I hear anything,
I'll let you know.
- Yeah, you do that.
- All right.
John?
Listen, I need you
to get out of the flat now.
- But I haven't finished.
- Finish and get out.
- Do they know?
- They know something's not right.
- What if they find him?
- They won't find him.
- But what if they do?
- I need you to get out of the flat,
keep your head down for a while, OK?
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Sorry, Toby.
Wotcha!
Frank, what are you doing here?
Waiting for you.
What are you doing here?
What's in the boot, John?
None of your business
what's in my boot.
Open it.
So what are you saying,
I open the boot or you shoot me?
- Don't make me answer that.
- Frank, you really wanna do this?
All right.
All right. You win.
Step back.
- What's in that bag?
- It's my work gear, all right?!
My stabby, my body armour.
- Zip it open.
- Come on, Frank!
Just do it!
What a performance.
You happy now, Frank?
Listen, I'm gonna go now.
Before you embarrass yourself
with another senior moment,
why don't you do yourself a favour?
Find your boy, slap him,
take him back to his nan.
And while you're at it,
you give him a slap from me.
I'm about done with all this.
Shit!
What do you want?
70 help you out.
I've heard that one before.
I'm still laughing.
Listen, you've got bigger things
to worry about.
What do you mean?
I don't know what you mean.
It means, I want five minutes alone
with Jenny, ask her some questions.
She's not in trouble -
I just need a chat, that's all.
You help me get that and I'm out of
your hair for good. So's John Luther.
Right.
And how do you intend
to make that happen?
- How do you think?
- Oh.
Look...
she's not here.
I don't know where she is.
How did I do?
Did I do OK?
You did great.
Did great.
Well done.
All right?
But this isn't over.
Not yet.
I need you to find a place to hide.
Think you can do that?
Think I might want my mum.
Jenny, I don't think
you should go back there.
But if it makes you feel better...
You're so nice.
Why aren't you married?
You should be, though.
You should be married.
All happy and everything.
No-one'll have me.
Go on.
Let's go.
- When did it happen?
- Six minutes.
- Uniform got there two minutes ago.
- And the killer?
He ran onto Lyntall Street, but he could
be north, south, anywhere, really.
- How we doing with the rest of it?
- Warm off the press.
All right, cool.
Excellent.
- Get that other stuff and get in here.
- OK.
Your password was pretty secure.
Cracked it.
Liverpool Street, this happened.
See, what he's done,
to compensate for a low-scoring weapon,
- he's used a high-scoring strategy.
- Mm.
Then this. People carrier. Broad daylight.
Males, right -
that's good, isn't it, males?
Um... loads of witnesses.
- Again, another high-scoring tactic.
- His name's Nicholas.
Your name's Robert.
The Japanese have got a great word
for it, "hikikomori".
It means people
that withdraw from the world.
That's what you and your brother
have been doing, right?
Now look at you.
Banged up, in here. Game over.
- While Nick...
- Nicholas.
Nicholas...
is out there,
making up for all the times
he was the quiet one.
- He's scoring very high for audacity.
- So?
- So what do you think about that?
- What do you think?
Oh, I'll tell you what I think.
I'm glad you asked that.
I think that you and Nicholas
are very, very close.
Outstandingly so, even for twins.
You want to know what else I think?
I think there's a limit
to that closeness.
A limit.
I mean, after all, you are one of two.
Eh, Robert?
You are a man in your own right.
- Do you know what else you are?
- What else am I?
- You're winning.
- I don't care about winning.
You and your brother
get them strangers all right.
But when it's down
to the last men standing,
it's you against him, isn't it, Robert?
And I think you do actually care who wins,
because you really, really want it
to be you.
What are you asking me?
I'm saying that the way Nicholas
is racking up a great score,
you won't be winning
for much longer, will you?
- So?
- So why don't you help me catch him?
Before he beats you.
I'll play you for it.
I can't do that.
Then it isn't going to happen.
What are the rules of the game?
It's a dilemma throw.
That makes it a straight 50/50,
meaning I roll 1 to 10,
I help you catch my brother.
Iroll 11 to 20, you're on your own.
Go on, then.
- If you do catch him...
- Yeah?
Tell him I love him.
Sorry.
Don't be.
This is your home.
You're welcome here any time.
Do you want to tell me what's wrong?
Are you on drugs?
Is it drugs again?
Did he hurt you?
Did that man hurt you?
No!
Then what is it, love?
I really want to tell you, but I can't.
Why not?
I just can't.
So, if Nicholas Millberry believed
that his brother had escaped...
This is how he would communicate -
via the blog.
Run it past me -
exactly how do they communicate?
Robert and Nicholas
set up an everyday blog -
by design,
the most boring blog in the world.
All but guaranteed to attract no traffic.
But if it does attract a passer-by...
Well, they password-protected it.
- But you cracked it.
- Benny cracked it.
- By breaking the book code?
- Yeah.
Yeah. Once you're in,
the blog just consists of boring posts.
So what, these posts are coded?
Well, no, they speak via the comments.
Nicholas'll have an RSS feed
on his phone.
So as soon as a new comment's
posted, he'll receive an alert.
Which means we can control
and trace the communications.
Have you got any better ideas?
- Who was that?
- God. Sorry, did I wake you?
No.
So who was it?
- Esther.
- Who?
Esther.
Used to live down the road from us,
on Cavalry Close.
The ginge?
No. Esther.
The one with all the boobs?
That's her.
I was supposed to go over and see her.
But I cancelled for my girl.
Thanks, Mum.
John. I think my mum
may have done something stupid.
Give me two minutes and I'll call you
back as soon as I leave this building.
Where's he going?
He's working the case.
Yeah, in mysterious ways,
his wonders to perform.
Why don't you just cut him some slack?
And this feels right to you, does it?
Deliberately feeding lies to the media.
Because, correct me if I'm wrong,
but it looks like that's what he's doing.
The media don't care if it's lies,
as long as there's a good story in it.
Well, that's not the point, is it?
Can you think of a better way
to get Nicholas Millberry off the streets?
Touch a hair on her head
and I'll rip your balls out.
Don't worry -
you're doing the right thing.
Where is she?
Jen?
Jen!
Genevieve...
can you come out a minute, please?
- Jen?
- Where is she?
I don't know...
I don't know.
What is going on here? If there is
some kind of setup going on here,
you are gonna be the first to suffer,
let me tell you now. Get her for me!
- Get her for me! Where is she?
- I don't know!
- Call her!
- I've been trying. I don't where she is!
- Call her again!
- He's in there. Do I do it now?
Yes. Do it now. Call the police.
- Don't worry about your mum.
- Promise?
If you want to help your mum,
you need to keep it together
and do as we agreed.
And don't go back in there,
cos Frank might not hurt your mum,
but he will hurt you.
- All right?
- OK.
I've got to go. Keep it together, do it.
You all right?
It has to come
from an anonymous police source.
Police, please.
I-T just seen a car pull up to this house.
It's a silver... how do you say it?
Hyund...
Hyundai, yeah.
This bloke got out
and he was holding this gun or something.
No, yeah, it was definitely a gun.
Well, there's this other thing.
I know this might sound a bit mental...
Shut up! All right, listen.
Call your daughter.
Tell her to be back here
in ten minutes
or I am gonna go to work on you.
Have you got that?
Who called the police?
Is there another way out?
Yeah. Up... out there. Up...
- Guy, got a body.
- John, you clever bastard.
- Are we prepped?
- Yeah.
OK, so I've prepared some entries, based
on some of Robert's previous postings.
OK. What does that say?
- Um, hello, basically.
- Hello. Nothing wrong with saying hello.
Were you never young?
- DS Gray... if you wouldn't mind?
- Yes, ma'am.
DS Gray, you apprised me that DCI Luther
used the fire alarm the other day
as a pretext to gain access
to Detective Superintendent Schenk's
personal computer.
Yes, ma'am, I did.
I had IT run a report
on Schenk's computer.
It shows no activity
during the fire alarm.
What angle are you trying to work, Erin?
Is there a plan? I hope you've got a plan,
- this isn't just random game playing.
- Ma'am, I'm confused. I don't...
If you're so keen
to smear a superior officer,
you're gonna have to be smarter than that,
a lot smarter.
Now get out of my sight.
Go for a walk.
Do some serious thinking
about your future in this department...
and this service.
Sorry.
Once we've posted a comment,
his alert comes in on an RSS feed
on his laptop or his mobile.
As soon as he responds,
I can trace his connection.
- How did you do it?
- How did I do what?
- Guv, come on.
- No, DS Gray, you come on.
Was it you? Did you do it for him?
Um...
Sorry... what he says, Erin.
You lost me at hello.
Erin, what is going on?
The creatures outside looked
from pig to man, and from man to pig,
and still it was impossible to tell...
which was which.
What was that about?
I'm not sure.
I do know that Carroway had IT
crawling all over Schenk's
computer archives earlier.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
What do you think he's been up to?
I don't know.
I expect we'll find out soon enough.
Right...
let's get started.
Type in "hello".
Robert Millberry was arrested
and taken into custody
in connection with two brutal attacks
in London two days ago.
Police have refused to comment
on reports that Robert Millberry
escaped from custody today
and is currently at large in the capital.
The story has appeared
in several internet news sites
but no official report has yet been
published by the Metropolitan Police.
Millberry allegedly escaped
from a prisoner transfer van
after overpowering a guard.
Fears are growing that
there's a link between Robert Millberry
and the violent massacre that took place
on a London Underground station
the night of his arrest.
I did it.
You did what, Justin?
Hacked into the database, cleared
all the history on Schenk's computer.
So when Carroway went digging,
there was nothing to find.
Oh...
She was only trying
to do the right thing.
She doesn't deserve
to be punished for it - it's wrong.
- Yeah, it is wrong.
- I need to make it right.
Justin, I will.
Not you, me - I did it,
so I need to make it right.
Right, he's answering. He's live.
All right, Benny, what we got?
Just give me a moment. He's connected
to the blog. I'm tracing his ISP.
Got him.
He's at the Enspire Coffee Bar,
Endymion Way.
John, we're closer than you.
I'll see you there.
All right.
Gotcha.
- All right, what's he saying?
- He's joking,
saying Robert should have stuck
to the no-capture zone.
Benny's asking him what his next move is.
He's typed "SEAL".
- Slaying Everyone And Laughing.
- Stay with him, Benny.
What's he saying now?
Benny's asking him
to be more specific.
OK. "Grinding MOBS".
So he's talking about massacre.
Something's wrong.
He's stopped responding.
Benny, we're almost there.
I don't think he's talking
about knives and hammers, guv.
He's talking about carnage.
We've got to stand these men down.
It's too late.
Nicholas Millberry, do not move!
Police marksmen have you in their sights.
Please stand, placing your hands
slowly on your head.
He's got something under his coat.
It's not right, is it?
- All right, stand down, hold your fire.
- Hold fire!
Right, that's a dead man's switch.
We take a shot,
his hand loosens on the trigger.
Vest detonates.
How big of a blast are we looking at?
Given the bulk of that vest, we're
looking at a hundred-foot kill radius.
Boss, setting up.
Assuming he maintains general bearing,
we need roadblocks here, here, here.
We designate this area the hot zone.
Evacuate buildings
outside the hot zone only.
Minimise bodies on the streets,
clear a space, take him out.
- Take him out? What about the bomb?
- We're clearing the streets as best we...
What about the buildings?
Look at all these buildings round here.
Everybody in the shops and offices
inside this hot zone,
they just fend for themselves?
What's the alternative? Cross your fingers
and hope he walks right out of London?
Much more likely he's got
a target in mind. They usually do.
Say he's en route to a hospital
or planning to blow himself up
- in a primary school, what do we do then?
- If you shoot him, people will die.
The question I have to live with is,
how can I keep that number
as small as possible?
Get out of the square now!
- Come on!
- Fast as you can.
Move it! Leave it! Leave it!
John, I can't intervene, it's not my call,
and part of me thanks God that it's not,
because I don't know
what I would do differently.
Look, um, whatever you've got in mind,
we've got to do it quickly.
What's the plan, then?
There is a plan, right?
Wotcha.
I'm John.
- Do you want to play a game?
- I already am.
Oh, I know.
- He's wired.
- See, I've been reading...
Did we know he was wired?
What have you done?
In order to get to the next level,
you need a lot more points.
And correct me if I'm wrong,
but you need a... a boss.
You need to kill a boss.
I am the man at the end of that level,
aren't I?
I'm the man that's chasing you.
I'm that boss.
So if you beat me,
you get to play on.
You're gonna like this.
Check it out.
Now you roll the dice.
I guess the number -
I beat you...
you disarm that switch.
If I lose...
You're not serious.
Look at me.
Do I look like I'm joking?
OK.
Let's play in there.
Joe, those men are gonna
have to come down from that roof
because they have to have
a clear line of fire.
Joe, I need you to issue that order.
Bring five shooters down from the roof.
Make a perimeter round that truck
and wait.
Have I just authorised the death
of a police officer?
You know... I used to do this thing.
Used to... used to play Russian roulette.
And why was that?
Well...
guess because I was scared,
you know.
I could control my actions,
but not the consequences of my actions.
- Does that make any sense to you?
- Yes.
A few weeks ago, I realised that
nobody can... nobody can control that.
An action leads to a reaction
that leads to a reaction
and it all becomes one chaotic system.
That's why I can see how
you and your brother made it simple.
Turned it into a game.
Right?
I can... I can see that, it makes sense
to me. Leave it to fate, to God.
To a roll of the dice.
The rest of that fuel...
0N you.
I mean, it... it's tiny in here.
Just do it.
Yeah.
Roll it.
Well, why don't you
put the detonator down?
Oh, no, I can't do that.
Yes, you can.
Listen to me.
You're at that end, I'm at this end.
I'm covered in fuel
and you have a lighter.
OK.
Close your eyes.
Ready?
Come on!
OK, go.
One guess.
Are you scared?
No, I'm not scared. Are you scared?
No.
So...
what do you say?
What do you say?
All right, here's what I say.
The A between the L and the R.
Aim low.
What?
You heard the man.
He hated the boy,
but he wouldn't kill him.
I want you to find him.
Find Frank and bring him to me.
No.
No, this is done.
We're done.
That's not for you to say.
You see, you made a mistake
coming to me, cos I'm not Frank.
I never was Frank and I'll never be Frank.
What are you, then?
This is what I am.
I spoke to a good friend of mine
last night.
Now, if anything happens to Jenny
or anything happens to me,
she is gonna come for you
with the wrath of God.
She'll take whatever
you've got left to love
and make you regret the day
you ever came across my path.
Are we done?
We're done.
- You didn't really do that, did you?
- Do what?
Like, call up
some totally psycho killer girl.
- Her name's Alice.
- Whatever.
I don't know. What do you think?
Hmm... Dunno.
I do know you were totally epic, though.
Totally.
So, now what?
♪ Come on, baby, let's get out of the cold
♪ And gimme, gimme, gimme
your precious love for me to hold
♪ Come on, baby, come out of the cold
♪ Oh, yeah
♪ And gimme, gimme, gimme
your precious love for me to hold
♪ Yeah, come on
♪ Yeah, come on Yeah, come on
♪ Yeah, come on... ♪
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::