Previously on Dexter...
- What'd you get?
- Two guys in their 30s.
Strong accents, possibly
recent immigrants from Venezuela.
Masuka found a match
on the print we had from the cigar butt -
Carlos Fuentes.
He's got a brother, Marco,
and I got the address.
Cut him, and I'll blow your fucking head off.
Medic! I need a fucking medic!
Don't you dare let him die.
I apologised. He accepted.
It's assault and battery.
Batista could not only lose his job,
he could serve time.
According to
Sergeant Lopez's deposition,
you give the best blowjob in Miami.
Do you recognise this man?
Jonah, is this Kyle Butler?
Back away! Back away!
You're on unpaid suspension
until further notice.
Suspension?
Just tell everyone you're
taking a few vacation days.
I don't want to be alone tonight.
I'm no good for you.
I'm not looking for good right now.
I just want to find out who that girl is
before the M99 wears off.
Lumen Ann Pierce.
- Why didn't you take me to the hospital?
- Because you saw me.
- I didn't see anything.
- We both know that's not true.
Every one of these barrels
has a body in it.
- Look at this.
- No.
This is what happened
to the girls before you.
This is what
was going to happen to you.
I saved your life.
I was locked up.
And I thought it would never stop.
But it has stopped.
He's dead. It's over.
Boyd wasn't the only one
who did this to me.
There were others.
We all have something to hide,
some dark place inside us
we don't want the world to see.
So we pretend everything's OK...
wrapping ourselves in rainbows.
And maybe that's all for the best,
because some of these places
are darker than others.
- Whoo!
- Carefully.
I want to believe that smile.
That watching your mother die
hasn't changed you,
the way watching mine changed me.
Gently falling.
Sweetheart!
Sweetheart, what is it?
Oh! It's OK. It's OK!
He's got a scratch. Looks like someone
was playing a little rough.
That's a little too familiar.
- Let's get a Band-Aid on him.
- OK.
That's it for today!
But I use a scalpel.
All you have are your fingers.
Wiped clean. Not even a year old,
you're already destroying evidence.
And having to flee the scene of the crime.
Oh! It's OK.
Every time you see me,
you look disappointed,
like you were hoping
to find an empty table.
Guilty.
I still think you need
to consider my advice.
Leave town?
Go home to people who care about you.
I told you why I can't do that.
If you stay in Miami,
you'll never get past this.
If you had something
horrible happen to you,
could you just forget about it
and move on?
I would want to.
What if you couldn't?
If you really want to help me get past this,
help me find those guys and kill them.
I saw you kill Boyd.
You knew what you were doing.
Usual?
Thanks.
Going after those men
won't help you get past this.
It'll only make it worse.
How could it get worse?
It'll open up something inside you
you don't want to know is there.
Trust me.
Trust you?
I don't even know your last name.
The less you know about me,
the better.
- Better for who?
- For the both of us.
If you're not gonna help me,
why do you keep coming back here?
I'm trying to help you.
Minneapolis.
Yeah, I used some miles.
Wow.
You really want to get rid of me,
don't you?
I want you to get on with your life.
Lumen...
She took the ticket.
Maybe this is one problem
I can check off the list.
And maybe it'll snow this week.
Where's the fire?
Got to get my ass in gear,
or I'm gonna be late.
I could take that ass back to bed.
What part of "late" don't you understand?
I mean, at least let me
make you breakfast or something.
I have no time.
I've got to meet Batista at the hospital.
We're interviewing that kid
Fuentes sliced open.
Good luck with that.
"Good luck with that"? Fuentes has killed three people. I'm
running down leads,
and you're sitting around in your
boxer shorts watching TV all day.
Is that why you're, like, all,
"Let me get the fuck out of here."
- Cos I'm taking a few days off?
- Just drop it.
This wasn't even my call.
LaGuerta said I had too many days.
I had to use 'em or lose 'em.
- That's bullshit.
- No argument here.
I gotta go.
Quinn's my partner.
He should be here, not you. No offence.
What do you want me to do?
He put in for his time.
No, he told me he was forced
to take his leave.
- That doesn't make any sense.
- Exactly. So will you talk to LaGuerta...
- Shit.
- What?
- It's the mother. What is she doing?
- She's coming this way.
Fuck me so bad.
What am I supposed to say?
"I'm sorry. It's my fault your son
got his throat slit"?
No, let me do the talking.
De nada, de nada.
If it's OK with you, we'd like to ask
your son some questions.
- Sí.
- Yes.
Gracias.
- Jandro, how you feeling?
- ¿Cómo te sientes?
- Poquito mejor.
- A little better.
Bueno. We were wondering
if there's anything you can tell us
about the man who... injured you.
Uh...
He's seen him around,
but he didn't know who he was.
I asked if he had heard anything
about Fuentes around the neighbourhood.
Does he remember anything about that day,
anything Fuentes said or did?
Anything at all?
He doesn't remember anything else.
He was really scared.
Fuentes said he was going to kill him.
OK. Gracias.
Uh...
He had a mark on his hand.
- A small one.
- Like a tattoo?
Sí, como un tatuaje.
Can you draw it for us?
Lumen needs to stay away
from the darkness.
I, on the other hand,
always need names for my table,
and there are few people more deserving
than Boyd Fowler's accomplices.
Nothing in Boyd's arrest record
even hints he had help.
Zero to go on.
I'll have to look elsewhere.
Yours.
Thanks. You didn't have to do that.
No, it really is yours.
You left it on the hood of your car.
Oh.
My head's in 50 places.
Masuka didn't even begin
to keep up the caseload.
Well, good luck getting
the midget porn off your hard drive.
He might have shown it to me.
How was Mommy And Me?
Harrison break any hearts?
No, but he drew his first blood.
I think his little black book
still has a few blank pages.
- Well, not for long.
- He missed you this morning.
He's used to having his Aunt Deb
feed him his mango oatmeal.
Yeah, sorry.
You didn't come home last night.
No, it was late,
and I didn't want to wake you.
- I just crashed at a friend's house.
- Oh. What friend?
What, are you Mom now?
You want to do lunch?
I think I'm gonna be dining on backlog.
And paying a visit to Boyd's house.
Hm. All right, well,
I'll bring you something back. Bye.
Wait a second.
What?
Give me your opinion as a female.
- As a female?
- As a woman, you know?
McCourt.
- What about him?
- Do you find him attractive?
Do you?
I mean, would you ever?
I would rather put a campfire out
with my face.
OK?
I checked in with Cira.
She's gonna stay
on the ATM video surveillance
- while I track down the tattoo.
- Let me see that again.
See, it still looks like a UFO to me.
- Who the fuck knows, right?
- Yeah.
- We need to talk to an expert.
- An expert, huh?
Mm-hm.
The dragon lady represents
the dualities of my inner warrior.
Or your inner idiot.
Hey! If you can't muster up the appropriate respect, I'm
dropping the curtain.
When did you get this?
I've been adding to it over time,
but the main work started
about two years ago.
I was having a bit of a crisis,
and this was my way
of working through it.
- Viagra probably would have been cheaper.
- This was a crisis of the soul, Morgan.
Don't you have to have a soul
before it could be in crisis?
- Point is, you know a little about this world.
- I know a little.
The person you want to talk to
is my body artist, Michael Angelo.
- You're kidding. Michelangelo?
- Two words. Michael Angelo.
And, yes, I'm serious.
If your tattoo were done by anyone local,
Michael Angelo will know.
You can lower the curtain.
From the outside,
a normal home is indistinguishable
from the home of a monster
who puts women in barrels.
But step inside...
There must be something around here
that will point me to Boyd's accomplices.
Somebody's been here.
Oh, great.
Blood.
They were going through Boyd's files.
Whoever Boyd was working with
must have panicked,
tried to cover up any trace
of their existence.
Amateurs.
Here he is, freshly bathed,
clean as a whistle...
and ready for bed.
- Thanks.
- I'm gonna get going.
Cheque's on the counter.
Sonya, can I ask you a question?
Sure.
Have you ever noticed Harrison being... aggressive?
Aggressive?
What do you mean?
Scratching, stuff like that.
No.
He's a very gentle child, really.
Why?
There might have been an incident
at one of the Mommy And Me classes.
Can't be sure it was Harrison or not.
He's a little boy.
My little brother used to bite people.
Bloody little cannibal.
Now he's a vegetarian,
works for Greenpeace.
Well, that's comforting.
Not to worry.
You've got a little angel on your hands.
Nothing can change that.
- See you tomorrow morning.
- Night.
No match for Daddy
in the criminal database.
You're absolutely right. Maybe he drives.
Let's check the DMV.
Minnesota.
Lumen Ann Pierce.
She broke into Boyd's house.
She beat me to it.
Oh, my God.
Dexter, this seem like the product
of a stable mind?
A closet was the only place
she felt safe from them.
She's remade it here.
- Dexter, are you listening to me?
- Yes, I'm listening.
She's not a killer. She's not you.
She's coming undone.
What's that now?
This is the letter she took
from Boyd Fowler's house.
From his ex-cellmate, Robert Brunner.
"I'm getting paroled next week.
Need a place to 'sleap'."
S-L-E-A-P.
She's found a target.
You don't know what she's planning.
I know this isn't gonna end well.
She keeps going this way,
she's gonna get herself killed
or thrown in jail, and you're
gonna be right there with her.
Dex, she's gonna bring you down.
I know what you're doing.
- Having breakfast?
- You're looking for the men who hurt you.
So...
What, you're spying on me now?
What are you gonna do
if you actually find one of these guys?
Maybe...
- what you won't.
- Are you gonna kill them? Is that it?
I'm sorry.
You don't get to tell me what to do.
I asked for your help.
You turned me down.
For your own good.
Look...
You saved my life.
I'm grateful for that.
But what I need from you right now
is to leave me alone.
- Lumen...
- Don't touch me!
These men put five women in barrels.
They're not gonna want to be found.
Please...
stop this before it's too late.
She's not going to stop
until she finds Brunner.
- My favourite colour.
- Help you, Sergeant?
Morgan has been all over me
the last two days about Quinn.
- What about Quinn?
- The vacation he's being forced to take.
She's feeling shorthanded
without her partner.
- To tell you the truth, we need him.
- Well, it's the union.
Not my call.
That all?
Is there anything I need to know
about my case with IA?
Mm-mm.
Is there anything I need to know
about anything else?
I'm sorry, Angel, but I gotta go.
Sure.
I'll see you tonight?
Yeah... Um...
I might be late.
OK, so I'll let you know.
OK?
Hope you didn't have to dig too deep.
Only eight boxes, but I always remember
to lift with my back.
Well, here's the guy you asked for -
Robert Brunner.
- Nuh-uh-uh! Like we agreed.
- Right.
- Hm.
- There you go.
Aw. Oh! That face!
Abduction, torture, rape.
He's so big. Is he a year yet?
- Ten months.
- He's beautiful.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hm.
Seven years for sexual assault.
Out in three for good behaviour.
Mm. Good behaviour.
You ever seen scars like that?
Yes. On Lumen.
And he's out now.
Thank you, State of Florida.
Looks like she stumbled
on to the right guy.
It says he's living under Tuttle Bridge.
Is this current?
Mm-hm.
Sex offenders can't live anywhere near kids.
Tuttle's the only place they can go.
- Can I keep this?
- Well, that depends, now.
You gonna bring this little cutie by
to see me?
- Will do.
- OK.
Tuttle Bridge is the perfect place
for Brunner to hide in the dark,
but not from me.
I've got to get to him before she does.
Yo, what's up?
Tramp stamp.
I think I'm in love.
She's into needles.
Why don't you show her your dick?
That's disgusting.
You are so judgmental, Morgan.
I mean, come on.
We all have our own ways
of expressing ourselves.
I have my ink,
and you have your...
man-boots.
Yeah?
Well, expect my man-boots up your ass
if you're wasting my time, OK?
Vincent?
Now, what can I do you for?
- That's Michael Angelo?
- The one and only.
- M, how are you?
- Come here.
- Good to see you.
- Always good to see you.
M, this is the detective
I was telling you about - Detective Morgan.
- Enchantée.
- Right.
You mind taking a look
at something for us?
Any friend of Sugar's
is a friend of mine.
"Sugar"?
OK.
We interviewed this kid who saw this
on the hand of a suspect we're looking for.
Any idea what it means?
Crude, simplistic, but...
it's definitely an eye.
Look.
The similarity.
- See?
- And that would mean?
Eyes symbolise the third eye in our minds,
like the god Horus
and also...
just like...
the back of a dollar bill.
Hm.
Have you ever done something like this?
Well, if I had,
I would have remembered it.
Anything else you can tell us?
We're kinda desperate here.
Without it in front of me,
that's the best I can do.
- I'm sorry.
- No, it's OK.
M, thank you so much, anyways.
Always for you.
And you...
You come see me anytime, OK?
OK, thank you.
- OK.
- OK, bye.
Bye.
- I'll be in soon.
- Bye.
Hey, I think she likes you.
Don't ever speak about this.
Since we're already here, why don't you
get Quinn's name put on your...
- Hey, I have a gun.
- I'll just wait in the car.
OK.
- Hello?
- Cira, it's me.
- Any luck?
- Just a steaming pile of fuck-all.
Please tell me you have something.
I've gone through most of the bank's
ATM footage. Eight names and counting.
They're all freaking out about something
while they're withdrawing
maximum amounts from their accounts,
just like our first Santa Muerte vics.
I want addresses for all eight names
and any others you can find.
I'll pick you up on my way to work tomorrow,
and we'll check 'em out, OK?
Poor Julia Tuttle.
The Mother of Miami.
They named this bridge after her
in her honour.
Now it's crawling with paedophiles
and sex offenders.
So much for honour.
Japan's total area is slightly smaller than the US
State of Montana...
You mind if I watch?
The kid fuckers stay over by the tracks.
That's not why I'm here.
And why is that?
A stuck-up little co-ed and I
had a legal disagreement
concerning the meaning
of the word "consent".
Take a load off.
Appreciate it, brother.
Where'd you do your time?
Okeechobee.
My last stretch was in that shithole.
Rough place.
Yeah.
Told everyone I was in for armed robbery
to keep a target off my back.
- You from Miami?
- Used to be.
Guy I bunked with
lives down here now.
Thought I'd let him show me the town
and have some fun.
Did that fun include Lumen?
That is until my parole officer,
the cunt, started giving me shit
about staying with someone
from the joint.
- Wound up here.
- Hmm.
- Beats a cell.
- Barely.
Once my parole is done,
fuck Florida.
I'm going north.
Get me some of that farm-fresh pussy.
- You ever tap that?
- Can't say I have.
A couple weeks ago...
I had this hot, little blonde
on all fours.
A few of us did.
Believe me,
that bitch got every fucking inch
- of my motherfucking...
- That's enough.
This room was meant for Boyd,
not his cellmate.
They were co-workers, partners.
- Basically the same.
- You're sure?
I need to kill him...
so Lumen doesn't have to.
I don't want her down that road.
- Think about what you're doing.
- I am.
- He's a sex offender...
- I know.
...on parole.
- What are you saying?
- Think!
Are you listening?
OK.
He's wearing an ankle bracelet.
It couldn't have been him.
She had the wrong guy.
I was ready to kill him.
I was ready to kill him!
Robert Brunner isn't
one of the men who hurt her.
Harry's right.
I have to convince Lumen to do
what I never could -
to move on.
You're home early.
- Where's Sonya?
- I sent her home.
She said you were gonna
be working late.
- Hope you don't mind, I grabbed a beer.
- What's he doing here?
He wanted to...
borrow...
- a book.
- He reads?
- Yeah, he does.
- Here.
Thanks.
Little vacation reading.
Quinn was just leaving.
What she said.
I will call you in the morning, Joseph.
Oh. OK, Debra.
Kinda warm for gloves.
- Good night.
- Thanks for the book.
What was that about?
It's late, so I'll take the couch.
Are you and Quinn?
We're fuck buddies. That's it.
You need Quinn for that?
I know it's insane. I know it's...
wrong for a fuck-ton of reas...
Will you please stop looking
at me like that?
It's your life, Deb.
Just don't bring him around
when Harrison's here.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- He's at an impressionable age.
- We don't know what might rub off on him.
- What will rub off on him?
- Just keep Quinn away from my son.
- Fine.
You know, you're wrong about Quinn.
He's...
not that bad.
Hey.
Sorry. Long day.
Dinner's in the oven.
You mind if I, um, hop in the shower first?
You never called.
Yeah, I know.
I just lost track of time.
Why so late?
Budgets are due
at the end of the month, so...
I'm gonna...
- I'll set the table.
- Thanks.
She's not there.
You just missed her.
- Did my wife say where she was going?
- You two still not seeing eye to eye?
Look, I really need to find her.
It's important.
She was asking about Tuttle Bridge.
I told her that is the last place
she wants to be.
What the fuck, asshole?
Nice. Where you going, baby?
What are you doing?
- I'm taking you out of here.
- Give me the gun.
- No.
- Give it to me!
You have no idea
what those animals did to me.
Passing me around.
I couldn't move.
I couldn't stop them.
- It wasn't Brunner.
- It was.
He was Boyd's cellmate.
He raped three women!
He tortured them, just like he did to me.
- That's impossible.
- You weren't there!
Just listen to me.
He's wearing an ankle bracelet
as part of his parole.
If he leaves this place, it gets reported.
I checked.
He was here the whole time
you were taken.
Robert Brunner's never seen you before.
He's never touched you.
He never hurt you.
You were about to murder the wrong man.
Oh, fuck.
You see?
This is where it leads.
But it's not too late.
There's still no blood on your hands.
I just...
I just want to feel better.
I want all this to go away.
It will.
I don't see how it can.
Go home.
Back to your family.
If you don't put this behind you,
I swear what you're feeling now
will only get worse.
Oh...
OK. OK, OK, I'll go.
OK.
Next one on our ATM list.
0-for-fucking-5,
that's how I like to start my fucking day.
You want to make a bet why this one
was taking a wad of cash out of the ATM?
Gambling, hookers, drugs?
You're very cynical.
It's called being a detective.
And blow me.
You have to put positive energy
out into the universe.
Right. Blow you.
You smell that?
Holy shit.
- Little help here? Anytime you're ready.
- Yeah.
This is Detective Morgan
requesting CSI and body transport
at 2075 Ocean Way
for a possible double homicide.
And you need to tell Masuka and Dexter
that they need to bring a bug kit...
and some fucking crackers.
You good?
You son of a bitch.
- Angel!
- Sergeant, you're making a big mistake!
The only mistake I made was not kicking your ass when you
first laid eyes on my wife.
Angel, let him go! This is a sting!
Let him go!
- You're wearing a wire?
- No shit.
You idiot.
What would have happened
- if he barged in here a half-hour ago?
- I know.
Just give us a minute, Jim.
You just don't learn, do you, Batista?
Have you completely lost your mind?
- I thought...
- What? That I was fucking him?
What am I supposed to think?
You barely talk to me.
The late nights, the sneaking around.
How'd you find us?
Wait. You...
I don't even want to know.
IA needed my help to bust a narcotics cop on the take, and
I
said yes.
Why?
To close the books on your bar fight!
So I don't want to hear about
sneaking around and late nights!
- Why didn't you tell me?
- Why didn't you trust me?
Maria, I...
Morgan needs us on site -
double homicide.
- My car's outside.
- I'll ride with Patrol.
Fuck me.
Come on, Liddy.
Lieutenant, any comment?
- Not now.
- Lieutenant LaGuerta...
It's like the fucking
food chain in action in there.
Flies - the blowflies
are attracted by the smell
and they lay eggs, and the beetles,
they're drawn by the larvae,
- and they burrow into every orifice...
- I get it.
What do we know?
The vics' names
are Daniel and Awilda Ortiz.
ATM footage showed Daniel trying to make a maximum
withdrawal about 4 weeks ago.
Officer Manzon and I show up
to interview him, and we find the bodies.
The remains have already
started to mummify,
but the wounds are consistent
with a machete.
I can make sure
when I get them back to the lab.
- We like the Fuentes brothers for this.
- Only weird thing is,
we can't find any Santa Claus Muerte
mumbo jumbo bullshit.
We might be looking
at the Fuentes brothers' first victims.
The defensive wounds and heavy smearing
suggest our killers were still inexperienced.
Beheading requires skill.
So we got their goddamn
training wheels kill?
Means we're back to fucking square one.
A little downwind, please.
Oh, yeah. That's never coming out.
I liked this shirt, too.
I'll get a jacket out of my car.
All right.
It was never a tattoo.
It was a stamp...
from a nightclub.
It was a fucking nightclub!
It's a nightclub!
- What's gotten into her?
- Find out, Sergeant.
I'm gonna go deal with the press.
Nice to have you back, Dexter.
Good to be back, Lieutenant.
Reports on my desk, first thing.
Ah, all together once again.
One big happy family.
Eh, Dexerino?
Yeah.
- You don't have to wait.
- I don't mind.
I can pay you back for the ticket.
I'll send you some money.
Except...
I still don't know who to send it to.
Dexter Morgan.
And it's not necessary.
The ticket.
I came to Miami for a fresh start.
- Somewhere warm.
- You're doing the right thing.
Your parents will be...
happy to see you.
I tried to call them, but I...
I couldn't.
What would I say?
Just give it some time.
I can't tell them what happened to me.
I can't tell anyone.
You're the only one who knows.
You have my number.
Call me if you need to talk about it.
- I should...
- Oh, yeah.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Go ahead, put it through.
And your bags.
Make sure everything's out of your pockets.
Jewellery, belts.
Step to the mat, ma'am.
- Is there a problem?
- I can't let you through to your gate
unless you consent to a hand search.
Lift your arms.
I need you to stay still.
Spread your legs.
- Are you home?
- Uh...
- Not quite.
- Are you at a bar?
I had to gas up the car.
My fault O'Malley's is on the way?
- So ask me how my day was.
- How was your day?
It was better than yours, slacker,
cos I know where Carlos and his brother
have been hanging out.
- At a local club called the Mayan.
- You got your lead. Congrats.
We stake this place out,
they show up,
then we take these Santa Muerte
no-dicks down for good.
How about I get steaks and beer
and we celebrate?
There's nothing to celebrate just yet,
but I have a good feeling about this one.
- Now get your ass moving, I'm starving.
- On my way.
Thanks for the Cuervo, Stud.
No problem.
I heard what happened.
Fuck those IA rats.
And your boss.
She's the reason I'm here.
Unpaid leave.
Why? For doing my fucking job.
That bitch put handcuffs on me,
then that no-nuts McCourt
parades me around that station
like I'm a goddamn carnival prize.
Well, they can both go fuck the dog.
They think I'm gonna cop a plea,
they're both cracking walnuts up their ass.
I'm gonna fight this thing
to my last damn dime.
You need some extra cash
for those lawyers...
- I might have a job for you.
- Really?
- What would that be?
- Looking into someone.
- Who?
- Guy I work with.
- Interested?
- I don't know if I should be,
considering who's sitting
in front of me making the offer.
What are you talking about?
Have I ever fucked you over?
No, but LaGuerta just taught me
there's always a first time.
Look, Quinn...
you fuck with the bull...
you get the horn.
- You understand?
- Yeah. Do you?
- You got a name?
- Dexter Morgan.
Dexter.
What the fuck kind of name is Dexter?
Rainbows are an illusion -
refracted light to make us think
something's there
when it's really not.
Is there darkness in Harrison?
Or is it just my own fear
being reflected back?
I just know he's the one who scratched Teddy. He was right
next to him.
Did you read about
what happened to his mother?
That boy will never be the same.
There's nothing wrong with my son.
I'm sorry for ever thinking
the worst, Harrison.
You'll always be my son.
Whatever we have to face,
we'll face together, OK?
Ow!
Hello, ma'am. Where you headed
this afternoon? You need a cab?
Welcome to Miami.