Previously on Dexter...
Rita's inside. It was me.
FBI? Fucking Bunch of Idiots.
You want to talk to Dexter,
schedule an appointment.
I'll do that.
If this were anyone but Dexter,
we'd at least be thinking
like detectives.
When the wife is dead,
90% of the time the husband did it.
What are you doing?
You wanna talk about it,
or are you just gonna act weird?
There's nothing to talk about.
All Rita and I ever did was kiss.
Dexter found out
about the indiscretion,
and came over and punched me out.
- Arthur Mitchell.
- Kyle Butler.
And what's his name?
Uh... Kyle Butler.
Something happened to your mom.
She's dead!
And it doesn't even matter to you!
I wish you were dead!
I just got a call from the FBI
about your brother's interview.
- Don't tell me. What'd he say?
- He didn't show.
I don't know where the fuck you are
or why you think you can
fucking run away from the FBI,
but you better get back here...
My wife died, and it was my fault.
Your dead wife can suck my dick.
That's the first human thing
I've seen you do since she died, Dexter.
They're not better off without you.
You're not better off without them.
You need to go back.
It's said there are seven stages of grief.
I suppose killing someone
with my bare hands in a men's room
was my way of working through
the anger stage.
Whatever the other six stages are...
I don't have time for them.
Cos now I'm a full-time dad.
Once the kids and I are back together,
it'll all be fine.
I can't believe we're all gonna
squish in here.
It's just temporary,
till we can get a new place.
Here.
He needs to be hosed off
or something.
Hey.
Welcome home.
This isn't our home.
And why do we need a new place, anyway?
I think starting in a new apartment
will be good for us.
Look, I found a place
practically on the beach.
Or another one right next to a park.
But, until then, Astor,
you get to share the bed with me.
And, Dex, you're on the couch.
Cody, you're on the cot.
Time for you both to get to bed -
school tomorrow.
How can I go to school?
I don't even have any of my things.
Make a list.
I'll go by the house tomorrow.
I want to go with you.
- I don't think that's a good idea.
- Why?
Well... because of what happened
to your mother there.
I know what happened to my mom.
She was murdered.
Don't forget, 9am tomorrow.
FBI interview.
One final loose end to tie up
before putting all this behind me.
At the time of your wife's death,
you were...
I already told you.
I was on my boat.
Right.
Just seemed odd.
You do a lot of night boating, Mr Morgan?
Sometimes. It's more peaceful.
- And you were by yourself?
- Yes, I was alone.
There are security cameras at the marina.
You can see me leaving and returning.
We've seen the footage, Mr Morgan.
The problem is,
according to the coroner's report,
your wife was killed several hours
before you got on the boat.
Is that what this is about?
Are you fucking serious?
Suggesting I have anything to do
with my wife's death...
that I'd slice her artery,
let her bleed out in the bathroom...
Mr Morgan, we know that you
were at Arthur Mitchell's house.
At the time of your wife's death,
you were part of the team
that raided Arthur Mitchell's house.
Right, of course.
We know you didn't kill your wife.
We're just looking for a reason why
Arthur Mitchell might have targeted her.
Because he's a serial killer?
How'd it go?
Fine.
I'm just glad it's over,
and I can move on.
We miss you, brother.
Yeah?
How's handling the department
all by yourself?
Ah, it's a breeze.
- I'll be back in a few days.
- Oh, no, you won't.
You're taking at least another week.
You need to spend time with your family.
Thanks.
Excuse me.
Anything you need, Dexter, just ask.
I will.
See you tonight.
Oh! Grandparents stopping by too.
They're all staying at your place?
Yeah. It's crowded.
But it's temporary.
He just doesn't want the kids
- staying at the house where their mom...
- Right.
So, we all good here?
Yeah, he's airtight.
But otherwise, we got jack shit.
Arthur Mitchell disappeared.
The only lead we have now
is this Kyle Butler.
We had a murder victim by that name
a few weeks back.
Well, our guy's alive,
as far as we know.
Unfortunately,
he's disappeared as well.
We're gonna have a sketch artist meet
with the family, and get a composite of him.
- I'd appreciate it if you'd keep me posted.
- Will do.
Hey...
Maria, your mail.
So, Dexter Morgan,
let's get you a moving van.
Aren't you a cute kid, huh?
- Huh?
- He's not actually talking yet.
Here's your 18-footer.
What's his name?
- Harrison.
- 14-footer.
It's a family name?
Blood.
Er... Sort of.
So, what kind of stuff you moving?
Just, uh, furniture, clothes,
a dresser, maybe.
Plenty of reasons for blood to be there. Someone cut
himself moνing...
If that's all we're talking about, save yourself
some money, go with the 10-footer.
I can't let myself think about this.
I've just got to move the kids.
Actually, I think I'll go with the 14-footer.
OK, let's, uh, write you up.
We're gonna get a much better place.
What do you think,
closer to the park or the beach?
Hello? Dexter?
No annoying neighbours.
- Hey, Dex. Brought your mail.
- Thanks.
Wow. Look at Harrison.
Boy, he's just getting bigger every day.
Hey, look, Dex, you know,
we haven't had a chance to talk,
but I wanted to let you know
how sorry I am about everything.
Thanks.
- Have they caught the Trinity Killer yet or...
- No.
Man, if I could just get my hands on him.
I can only imagine.
Hey, listen,
I know we've had our differences,
but, you know, I'm a single dad.
- I know the ropes, so if you need any help...
- No, I'm good.
Cos you gotta give up a lot.
I mean, I actually had
a pretty decent career going,
but I had to turn down
some major job offers
so I could just work at home
and just be there for those kids.
Good for you.
I mean, forget about any free time.
Or any life of your own, really.
I mean, you just...
you have to be there.
Right? Every morning. Every evening.
Every weekend.
You ready to do that, Dex, for the kids?
Yes, Elliot, I'm ready to do that.
For the kids.
Whoa, whoa!
- Here, let me...
- No. I got it.
But you know what? It works out.
It really does, you know?
I mean, you have to give up your life and all,
but you know what?
You just... You live for those kids,
and it's satisfying.
- Excuse me.
- Yeah.
I'll be a good father.
Everyone makes sacrifices.
I can too.
Focus on the kids.
Wow. I didn't know you were
gonna bring so much.
You can just put that...
- Right there is great.
- I emptied the refrigerator.
Someone left another cake at the door.
I just ate a whole tuna casserole
to make room in the apartment.
Cody, this is a good job for you.
Wanna help me unload the food?
OK.
Wow.
You sure do have a lot of beer, Aunt Deb.
People just keep bringing it.
This is all you brought?
Well, we're a little short on space.
You didn't even bring the right clothes.
This is my reject stuff.
I can't wear any of this to school.
Astor, come on.
No one's gonna notice you.
Honey, would you hold the baby?
- Come here.
- Cody.
Why don't you help us
carry the last load in? Hm?
I like it here. It's like camping.
Exactly.
Boys are easier.
It doesn't matter how much
I loνe my children,
I'm still a creature of the night.
Can't sleep either?
The blood probably means nothing.
Someone cut their finger while moving.
But I won't be able to put it out of my mind
until I know for sure.
Someone did a quick cleanup job
but forgot to wash the door.
Yeah, it's pretty. I know.
But not the story it tells.
Once upon a time, an evil green ogre
left a circular spatter at three feet high,
consistent with blunt-force trauma...
which seems to indicate
the handsome young prince
was hit while on his knees,
at least two or three times.
Or the princess was on her knees.
Small hands.
Female.
I thought the kids were
your number-one responsibility.
- They are.
- But here you are...
in the middle of the night.
It's not that simple.
It never is.
It's like when you get on a plane.
They tell you
if the oxygen masks come down
to put yours on first
before helping the kids.
I have to take care of my own needs too.
Otherwise, I risk spinning out of control.
And that's not good for anyone.
I'm not just saying this for the sake
of the kids, Dex, but for you.
They're not only your responsibility.
They're your salvation.
I have to give him a bottle.
No reason a truck rental agency
would put any serious safeguards
on their records.
The truck was most recently rented
to Boyd Fowler.
Boyd seems to have listed his address
as the Department of Sanitation.
No home address.
Miami-Dade County
Department of Sanitation,
Division of Dead Animal Pickup,
meaning the blood belongs to an animal.
But what about those little handprints?
Two lines.
Human.
Well, well, well.
What do we got here?
Raccoon.
- You call this in?
- Yeah, I did.
I was driving down the road,
and... I saw it.
Kind of creeps me out.
You're probably used to
seeing dead things, though, huh?
Can't say I ever get used to it.
I don't usually come this way, but I'm
in the middle of moving to a new place.
It's a hassle, huh? Moving?
- I wouldn't know.
- No?
Lived in the same house for over 20 years.
So why did you rent a moving van?
Hello there, bandit.
- This don't look right.
- What do you mean?
Usually, you find a dead animal in the road,
it means he was hit by a car.
But there's no tyre marks
or blood on the asphalt.
This raccoon was killed someplace else
and dropped here.
He's CSl-ing me.
He's got defensive wounds on his paws.
Little guy put up quite a struggle.
All righty, then.
He's definitely peculiar.
But I guess the best and brightest
don't typically get into dead animal pickup.
Just so you know, OK?
What do we got?
We got a female victim.
- Part of a female victim.
- Part?
- We got a head.
- Just a head?
Yeah. Decapitation.
Probably some kind of drug killing.
Nice.
Let me ask you a question,
hypothetical.
- Say a newly married person...
- Mm-hm?
...accidentally discovers
that his or her new spouse
has a savings account with a lot of money.
Is that something
that one should expect to share?
Fuck, no. That's your money.
You tell the lieutenant
to keep her fuckin' hands off it.
- Take me to the head.
- All right.
She was still alive
when they cut her head off.
Excision of eyes and tongue
was done postmortem.
That's considerate of them.
You were right. It's just a head.
Unless they buried her standing up.
What are you doing?
Just trying to help.
You're looking a little ragged.
I'm exhausted. There are five people
in my tiny apartment.
I shared a bed with Astor last night,
and she kicked me all night long.
You know, you're welcome
to crash at my place, if you want.
No, thanks, Detective.
OK.
- It looks like Santa Muerte.
- What?
Santa Muerte, the cult.
"Saint Death."
Yeah, I know what it is,
but why do you say that?
Well, the missing eyes and tongue
were meant to send a message.
You didn't see anything,
you're not gonna say anything.
Who are you?
Officer Manzon, Cira.
The golden candles mean money.
The icons, I don't know.
There are so many now,
you might need an expert on it.
- And you know all this because...
- It's my neighbourhood.
And if it is Santa Muerte,
they used a machete on her.
OK, well, we'll keep that in mind.
But this park is a local drug hangout,
and drug cartels like to cut heads off,
- so we might follow that lead.
- Of course.
Hey.
We found the body on the other end
of the park, under some bushes, no ID.
Gotta canvass the neighbourhood,
start asking questions.
No one will talk. They're too afraid.
Well, we still ask, Officer.
"Helping Your Children Cope With Grief."
"Grandpa's Gone To Heaven."
"Saying Goodbye To Fluffy."
But nothing on
"Mommy bled out in a bathtub."
Boyd Fowler, you have a prison record.
Assault with a deadly weapon.
18 months at Okeechobee.
You said you lived in a house,
but there are no mortgage records
in your name.
In the same house for over 20 years.
You inherited it...
from your parents...
Rich and Elsie Fowler in Opa-Locka.
Hey. How was your day?
A whole afternoon getting
doors shut in my face.
Sorry.
You?
OK.
We finished LaGuerta's
cacerola de camarones
and Masuka's chocolate lava cake,
and Astor told me she hated living here.
They're both asleep in the bed.
Looking at apartments.
So it's everything as usual.
They're seeing
their grief counsellor tomorrow.
Maybe that'll help.
- Still, even after...
- What?
You're gonna be a single dad
raising three kids.
Gonna be hard.
Rita was a great mom.
There's nothing I can do
to make up for that.
But I'm gonna have to try.
Well, I'll be here.
You can count on me.
The kids'll be OK.
I know that place.
It's near the station.
They have an open house tomorrow.
Maybe I'll check it out for you.
Great.
You want the couch tonight?
No, you take it.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Glad you called.
- Hey, fuck puddle. What are you doing?
- Just giving you a kiss hello.
I came over here to sleep,
not to have your fat little
sausage fingers all over me.
There's no room for me at my own place.
Unless I want to curl up inside
a fuckin' toaster oven.
I'm trying so hard to be a good sister.
Fuck knows,
Dexter's always been the best brother, but...
it is fucking exhausting.
I'm sure.
Well, look...
you're, uh, welcome to stay here
for as long as you want,
whenever you want.
And I promise to keep my
fat little sausage fingers off you.
You better.
- How's your brother?
- You know.
I heard the FBI interview went well.
That must be a load off.
Why would that be a load off?
Nothing. Never mind.
They're looking for someone
named Kyle Butler
who's a friend of Arthur Mitchell's.
They think if they can find him,
then he can lead them to Mitchell.
- But they can't find him?
- Well, not yet.
They're having sketches done.
They're trying to get a positive ID.
Kyle Butler.
Why does that name sound so familiar?
Well, that's the weird thing.
We worked that case, remember?
A dead Kyle Butler.
Right, he got his head smashed in.
Went unsolved.
- Any connection?
- I don't know.
I'm sure the FBI will
find a way to fuck it up.
Will you get the lights?
Yes, ma'am.
What do you want to do for the next batch?
Mickey Mouse? Silver dollar?
- Great big ones?
- Triangles.
A challenge.
Dexter's making triangle pancakes.
Actually, they're more freeform.
- Wanna set the table for us?
- Sure.
They're just blobs.
How dare you?
Triangles.
I counted too many plates.
Mom's not here.
- That's OK.
- No, it's not.
- She should be here.
- I'm sorry.
- That doesn't make a difference.
- Astor, I'm doing the best I can here.
Let's just sit down
and have some breakfast.
I don't want to!
- I wanna go back home!
- Astor...
- Stop it!
- Yeah, just stop it!
Both of you, just stop fighting all the time!
I hate it!
While they're seeing the grief counsellor,
I'll be getting my own kind of therapy.
So, is this, uh...
something we should talk about?
Whatever's going on between us?
- No.
- We have sex one day, and then...
I'm sorry, I'm not the kind of person
who would ever have sex with you.
- I don't know what we're doing.
- We're not doing anything.
We never did do anything.
We never will do anything.
- So we never had sex?
- Exactly.
That's really weird.
Cos I remember...
I gotta go now. I'm gonna go.
- How's it going?
- I hate this shit.
This is Dexter's job.
Blood. It's gross.
Well, whoever cut the head off
used the same weapon to cut
the eyes and the tongue out.
But I can't find anything that fits.
I've tried two swords, three knives.
Try the machete.
Yeah.
Huh!
I think we have a match.
I'll send somebody over there right away.
OK, yeah.
How's it going in there?
Masuka said he really likes
working with the blood.
He hopes he can get
more assignments like this.
I'll keep that in mind.
Let me ask you a question.
If you were married,
and you found out that the person
you were married to
had a secret bank account
with a lot of money,
do you think that person
should share it?
Jesus, Angel. Just because you married her
doesn't mean you own her.
It's her money. End of story.
Well, you got a dead body waiting for you.
Oh! Fuck me.
Why couldn't he have just hanged himself,
took some pills,
stuck his head in the oven?
People are so rude. Excuse me.
- You again.
- It's my neighbourhood.
You were right about the machete.
Good, I guess.
- So, what do we have here?
- Well, golly gee, Deb,
I think we got a shotgun wound
to the head.
Approximately 24 hours ago.
Make sure you swab the gun.
- And check his hands for GSR.
- I got it, I got it.
I'm just checking.
Dexter usually works cases like this.
Do we have an ID?
According to this, Francisco Alfaro.
Hey, can we roll him over?
Oh! Looks like his face has changed a little
since his driver's license picture was taken.
Looks like him.
- Hey... check out the girl.
- What?
Look at her.
Imagine she has no eyes and no tongue.
- Holy shit.
- It's her, isn't it?
Those are the exact same earrings.
We've got our head.
Bingo.
Looks like we've got a murder-suicide here.
- How you figure?
- Guy gets pissed at his wife,
cuts her head off,
leaves it in the park for everyone to see
and comes home,
blows his head off.
Masuka, we've got some brain goo
on the ceiling you need to photograph.
Fuck me up the goat ass.
What about all that
Santa Muerte stuff, then?
Yeah.
There is no Santa Muerte stuff.
That's what I'm saying.
There was at the park.
There was missing eyes and a tongue
and the gold candles and the icons.
- There's none of that here.
- No.
What do you think?
- I think you're right.
- Who's she?
Hey... when is Dexter coming back?
Boyd Fowler works the seven to four shift,
which gives me time
to check out his house,
see if there's anything
that'll put him on my table.
Let me guess.
This is you putting on
your oxygen mask first.
Being on the hunt keeps me sharp.
Focused.
Thus, the better killer I am,
the better father.
So he takes his work home with him.
No crime in that.
A man of simple taste.
Looks like my grandmother's house.
A loaded handgun.
A no-no for a convicted felon.
But even so, not much to go on.
Boyd, you are very boring.
Shit.
Boyd comes home for lunch.
OK, that's interesting.
Do you want
to have control of your life?
You have that power.
You just have to learn how to use it.
You can make up all the excuses you want.
You're too tired.
Who keeps their attic door locked?
Too old. Too fat.
Too stupid.
You know, I've heard them all.
Chicken noodle, chicken noodle,
chicken noodle. Where's the tomato?
- But if you want something, take it!
- Take it!
You want that job?
- Well, then, take it!
It's entirely up to you.
The world does not...
You want that nice house
on the beach?
- Take it!
The world does not put limitations
on what you can have.
But if you want something...
- Take it!
You have that power.
I can see having
an old girlfriend's lock of hair...
but identified only by a number?
We are our own worst enemy.
Make no mistake about it.
But with a few simple steps,
I can teach you how to take control
of your life.
Take it!
All I'm saying...
if a woman pissed me off enough,
yeah, I'd wanna cut her head off.
Well, that's great to hear.
No, I'm not saying I would do it.
But I understand the impulse.
What are we doing here?
I told Dexter I'd check this place out for him.
Oh! Come in, come in.
- Hey.
- Hi!
We've just painted and installed
new flooring throughout the house.
- Looks great.
- Ooh!
Lots of young couples
in the neighbourhood.
And the elementary school
is about three blocks away.
I'm sure you'd be very happy here.
- Oh, it's not for us, we...
- I think we'd be very happy here too.
Thank you.
Well, I have to get a few things
out of my car.
But if you have any questions,
I'll just be right outside.
Thank you.
- It's a nice kitchen.
- Uh-huh.
- Decent appliances.
- Uh-huh!
Oh, look at this.
Great bedroom. Check it out.
Don't.
Oh! Wow.
Comfy bed.
Feel it.
- Get off the bed.
- What do you say? A little nap time?
- I'm leaving.
- What did I do?
I've got to drop you off at the station,
then pick up my brother's kids.
How desperate am I,
to follow Boyd to the middle of nowhere
when all I've got is a bit of blood
and a lock of hair?
But with nothing else to go on...
It's a rule of nature.
Leave some old bedsprings
out in the middle of nowhere,
and soon it'll be joined by a refrigerator,
couch, car engine.
And now, a barrel,
most likely holding dead animals.
Too lazy to drive it back to the incinerator,
I suppose.
- Hey, Deb.
- Do you have the kids?
Harrison's with Bill and Maura
and Astor and Cody are with you?
- Shit!
- What's going on?
Did you drop them off at school
this morning?
Yeah, they were seeing the counsellor first,
then going to their regular classes.
I just went to pick them up, and the woman
said that they never went to class.
So I called the apartment,
and there's no answer.
Well, where are they?
That's my question, big brother.
Where would they go?
Same place Astor
keeps saying she wants to go.
Astor.
Cody.
Hey.
How'd you guys get here?
We walked.
Don't be mad, Dexter.
They wanted to see where it happened.
Where they lost their mother.
I'm not mad.
Astor, I'm sorry.
I should have listened to you.
I should have brought you back here,
like you asked.
If you want to move back here, we will.
We'll find a way to make it work.
No, we won't.
Astor, I'm sorry.
You keep saying that,
but I don't care.
You ruined everything.
We'd gotten used to it.
It wasn't that bad!
- Used to what?
- To the way things were!
Before you! Without a dad!
Oh.
And then you come along
and become a part of the family,
and we thought that everything
was gonna be good forever.
You made us think that!
And it's not true.
Things got worse.
Now, every time I look at you I get so angry, because it was
all just a lie!
It's not Dexter's fault.
I thought coming here would help.
But that was stupid.
No, I understand.
It looks exactly the same as before.
Yeah, it does.
You can't even tell what happened.
But I know my mom died there.
And things will never be the same.
- I miss her so much.
- I do too.
We all do.
I don't want to live with you.
I want to live with Grandma and Grandpa.
I want to go back with them tonight.
Right now!
Hey. I'm heading out.
You want to grab a bite somewhere?
No. Why would I wanna do that?
All right.
Hey, Lieutenant.
Deb told me about
the Kyle Butler sketches.
Yeah, well, I'm not sure
how useful they'll be.
The mother and two children
all gave very different versions.
It's their biggest lead.
Seems to be going nowhere.
Do you mind if I keep a copy of these?
No, I got plenty.
Angel.
Let me ask you a question.
Can you tell me why you kept
this much money a secret from me?
It was never a secret.
That's my retirement fund.
Now that we're married,
aren't we supposed to share everything?
I don't think we ever discussed that.
Maybe we have different ideas
about what a marriage should be.
Because I always pictured
you and I at 80 years old,
walking down the beach,
hand in hand.
I like to picture that as well, Angel.
I love you.
But I think maybe I have more of a...
- practical side than you do.
- What does that mean?
I mean I've worked my entire career
to save up, to protect myself,
and you live every day like it's a party.
It's one of the things I like about you,
but it also means that you spend money
faster than you even make it.
- OK.
- And it's, I'm...
OK, I get it.
I don't mean to hurt your feelings.
No, I'm fine. I'm irresponsible.
- Oh, Maria.
- Everyone knows that.
Hey, everyone! Drinks on me. Tonight.
Yeah!
Angel.
Hey.
So, everyone's home safe?
Yeah, they're all inside.
You think they're finally settling in?
They're packing.
- What do you mean?
- Astor and Cody are leaving.
Soon as their grandparents get here,
they're going back to Orlando with them.
Dex, I'm so sorry.
For how long?
I don't know.
- Well, maybe if I talk to Astor...
- I already tried.
- And Cody wants to go too?
- No, he wants to stay.
It got very upsetting.
What did you say?
I reminded him that you and I are brother and sister,
just like him and Astor,
and that it's...
important that they never split up.
All the shit we've been through.
I never would have
made it through without you.
That's what I tried to tell him.
Did it help?
Not really.
I really was trying...
to make it work.
- In my own way.
- Yeah, I know you were.
I guess it's time to face reality.
Reality.
- Quinn.
- OK, we had sex.
Was it good sex?
I've said all I'm gonna say.
Are we gonna have more sex?
- Goodbye.
- Come on. Help me out here.
I'm hanging up now.
If she wants to live her life stashing away
all her little pennies, that's her problem.
I can't do anything about that. You know?
- You want another drink?
- You buying, right?
Bartender, a Cuervo silver.
You know how much money she's got?
It's sick.
Did she tell me?
Cheers.
Angel.
It true you married Maria LaGuerta?
I did indeed.
You got yourself a little sugar mama.
- What?
- Oh, yeah.
I remember when she was first starting out.
Such a fine piece of ass.
I think you need to get the hell out of here.
You fuck!
If they need anything,
just let me know. I'll send it.
We will. Thank you.
I lost my innocence at such an early age,
and it left a very damaging mark.
Can't I stay with you, Dexter?
For now, you need to go
with your grandparents.
Don't worry, we'll still see each other
all the time. Orlando's not so far.
Yes, it is.
Any shrink could tell you
that's why I've always liked children.
Because they connect me
to what I can never get back.
I don't want to go, Dexter.
I don't want you to go.
Astor...
What?
Your mother loved you more
than you could ever imagine.
And I...
Me too.
Cody and Astor showed me
that I can still care about something.
That makes letting them go
all that much harder.
And it's losing them
that makes me realise
there must be some small part
of that innocent child still inside me.
Because, just like Astor,
I was foolish enough to think
that things would always be good.
But they're not.
They're worse.
Much worse.
Normally, having a target
would make me feel good,
give me direction, a sense of purpose.
But now...
it means nothing.
And I don't know what's
going to make me feel better.
Should we go home?
Give me a minute.