Oye, mami.
Previously on Dexter...
Ven aquí.
- He's calling me over.
- Officer Manzon, go to him.
Lieutenant, no, this is a problem.
These guys are dangerous.
Stand down, Morgan.
Drop the gun now!
Our informant, Yasmin Aragon,
was shot and killed.
This is a fucking disaster.
If mistakes were made,
they most certainly were not mine.
- I just gave you 500 bucks.
- And I told you about the girl.
But if you want to find out who she is,
where she's from,
and what she's doing in that damn house,
you're gonna have to pay.
Boyd wasn't the only one who did this to me.
There were others.
Besides the ones
that we've already taken care of,
suit and tie.
He'd take off his jacket
and fold it very carefully,
like he didn't want to mess it up.
Someone tried to move
the girls in the barrels.
- Where's the driver?
- He took off.
That means he's still mine to find.
You're never gonna guess
who this truck is registered to.
Jordan Chase.
Nice to meet you.
Do you know this man?
That's the guy who folded his jacket.
His name's Cole Harmon.
He's Jordan Chase's head of security.
- That's Cole.
- And Boyd.
- And Dan the Dentist.
- It's them from, like, 15 years ago.
What does this mean?
We are born primal.
Conceived with the impulse to fight
for what we desire.
It's written in our genes.
It's engraved in our souls.
But we've traded
the wilderness for pavement,
trees for skyscrapers.
We've lost touch with our instincts,
with what we are.
We have fallen from nature's grace.
But we shall be delivered!
It's time to tap into your primal selves
and seize the power of instinct.
We're gonna cast off those shackles
that bind us to jobs we hate,
people we don't love,
lives that aren't worth living.
We are going to...
Take it!
I've never been around so many people
that made me feel normal.
Yeah! Yeah!
Really normal.
- The power of risk!
- Take it!
The power of desire.
Take it!
- The power of instinct.
- Take it!
Instincts are all I've ever had.
Cole Harmon, Chase's chief of security -
torturer, rapist, killer.
It's time to tap into my primal self.
- The power of life!
- Take it!
- We're gonna take it!
- Take it! Take it!
All right.
Lieutenant LaGuerta!
Multiple rounds were fired
at the recent Club Mayan shootout.
Was Miami Metro responsible for the deaths
of innocent bystanders?
I have nothing to say at this time.
Excuse me.
Do you agree with the Mayor? Did this
operation needlessly put people at risk?
Every undercover operation is high-risk.
Is there going to be
an independent investigation?
- No comment.
- Have you personally retained counsel?
Counsel?
Isn't it true the victims' families
have filed a civil lawsuit?
Let me through.
Excuse me, let me through.
Lieutenant LaGuerta, neither confirming
nor denying Miami Metro's culpability
in the recent Club Mayan shootout.
As we know,
two innocent people are dead, six...
Did ballistics come in?
Good news. Bullets from the victims' bodies
belong to the Fuentes brothers, not us.
That is good news.
But this is far from over.
I'm sure you heard the Mayor's statement.
A prime example
of how shit just rolls downhill.
He should have kept his mouth shut
until all the facts came out.
He was right.
This operation was too risky.
And now because of us,
two innocent people are dead.
Not by our bullets.
Shots would have never been fired
if we hadn't been set up in that club.
- Those are the facts.
- On the upside, Carlos Fuentes is dead.
None of us should have any illusions.
There are gonna be consequences.
Yeah, I've seen that look on her face before.
Someone's about to get bent over
and fucked.
It's gonna be me, isn't it? I screwed up.
No, you didn't. You were following orders.
LaGuerta's orders,
just like the rest of us.
That's what you put in your report, right?
You were following her lead?
I haven't written it yet.
I'm still sorting through the events
in my mind.
Sorting through what exactly?
What I'm gonna say about them.
- Here's a crazy idea. How about the truth?
- Deb, I'm on it.
- Who's that?
- It's Yasmin's mother.
You all right?
Three people are dead,
Carlos Fuentes and two girls.
- Nobody's crying about Carlos.
- Fuentes was a scumbag.
Yeah, he's a scumbag
that I shot and killed.
And? What's the problem?
Don't tell me you feel bad
about killing him.
I don't.
That's the problem.
Yasmin didn't feel any pain.
She died instantly.
- I'm ready.
- OK.
I have some bad news for everyone.
You're all going to die.
Some of us sooner than others.
And if you're not in touch with
your primal self, you're already dead.
You may be breathing
and walking around,
but you're an empty shell,
just one of the herd,
completely unaware
of what you truly want.
And when we come back,
we're gonna start using your instincts
to design the life that you deserve,
fuel the passion to make it real,
and find the power...
...to take it.
Jordan Chase's Take It Now
Experience will resume at 2:00pm.
In the meantime,
we invite you to visit our vendors.
Jordan promises change,
but he also accepts credit cards.
- Lumen?
- Can you talk?
Or are you about to have
a major life revelation?
No, that came around 9:00am,
when I realised I really wanted a doughnut.
What'd you find?
I haven't been able to find out
how these guys know each other.
The picture was taken
when they were teenagers, but...
Did you check high schools?
Cole went to Westland Prep in Hialeah,
and Dan the Dentist went to
St Joseph's Academy in Coral Gables.
Boyd... There's nothing on Boyd.
Yeah, he probably never saw
the inside of too many classrooms.
I was able to find out
something else about Cole.
- What?
- He was in the Marines.
He got bounced
on dishonourable discharge.
He beat up a superior officer
and put him in the hospital.
This is a dangerous guy, Dexter.
Do you remember the marks
I had on my back?
That was Cole.
- So be careful.
- Are you getting any rest?
I fall into a deep sleep
from 1:00 to 1: 15 every morning.
When this is over,
I expect to sleep for a year.
I'll talk to you later.
Mr Morgan. Cole Harmon.
I'm sure you remember me
from our visit to the station.
Mr Chase spotted you from the stage.
He's very interested in speaking with you.
He was wondering if you'd join him
in his suite for a few minutes.
Uh...
OK. When?
How about right now?
All the way to the end.
I'm disgusted, to tell you the truth. You
haven't been listening to a word I've said.
Call me back when you stop
being a piece of furniture.
Sorry. New client.
Good to see you again, Mr Morgan,
especially under better circumstances.
- Call me Dexter.
- Jordan.
- Can I offer you a drink?
- Uh...
No, thanks. I'm good.
- Think I know why you're here.
- You do?
You're searching for a way
to cope with your loss.
I know your history, Dexter.
I thought I recognised you
when we met at the station,
but it hit me later on.
Your wife was murdered.
- Yes.
- Are they any closer to catching Trinity?
Not that I'm aware of.
I followed that case very closely.
Trinity, a religious man,
a family, good life.
Yet he was working through such rage,
harbouring so many secrets.
I have to be honest.
He fascinated me on a deep level.
What else do Jordan and I
have in common?
I certainly don't mean to imply
any sympathy for him.
He's a monster, no question.
I can't imagine your frustration,
knowing he's out there, unpunished.
It hasn't been easy.
No doubt.
And now you're a single father,
which has its own set of challenges.
Why did you want to see me?
I've developed a theory
on how the primal self deals with tragedy.
I have to prepare for the next session,
but I am very interested
in what happened to you.
I would like to discuss your situation in
depth at another time if you're open to that.
- OK.
By the way, have you made
any progress on Boyd Fowler?
I'm not really aware of all the details.
You should probably speak
to one of the detectives.
Of course.
I look forward to our next talk.
There's a little something in there
for Harrison.
Thanks.
- You wanted to see me?
- Close the door.
You know there's a lot of heat
coming down on us,
and the public's demanding blood,
our blood.
Matthews wants someone's head.
Sounds like Santa Muerte's catching on.
I'm putting Cira Manzon
on disciplinary leave.
- What?
- I need to put a face on it.
What's wrong with your face?
- Detective...
- You can't pin this on her.
- Her actions precipitated the shooting.
- She wasn't even supposed to be there.
- I tried to take her off, you wouldn't let me.
- That's your impression.
No, that's what happened.
Look, I was the detective in charge,
so if you want to fuck somebody over,
here's your scapegoat.
I know your instinct
is to take the fall for your team.
You were on my team.
In fact, you fuckin' took over my team,
and I had your back, cos your team,
my team, whatever, it's all the fuckin' same.
Cira's just starting out.
Her career will take the smallest hit.
She'll recover quickly.
If something like that
had happened to me back then,
I never would have made detective.
We were all there together.
So why can't we just hold tight
and weather the fuckin' storm together?
Fuckin' think about it.
- Does your printer ever work?
- Lu?
Owen.
- How are you?
- Um...
Um...
I bet you're tan.
The sun feels closer here, even though
I know it actually physically is not,
it feels like it's right there.
You're in Miami?
I got a sunburn just renting the car.
I came to see you.
You did?
Lu, I've respected your wishes.
Since the day of the wedding, I haven't
called, emailed, I haven't even texted.
It's like my life stopped that day
when you left, and I need to get unstuck.
I feel the way to do that
is to see you, face to face,
without 75 of our closest friends and family
staring at us.
Please, will you see me?
I...
- I can't tonight.
- Tomorrow.
Lu?
I'm staying at
the Blue Pelican Motel.
There's a café across the street.
Meet me there tomorrow at noon, OK?
OK, noon.
Hey.
- Hey.
- I got you some supper.
Hot and sour soup,
fried rice with tofu.
- That's what you like, right?
- Yeah, that's fine.
No, I'm not staying.
Oh, right. Harrison.
You're tired.
I spent the entire day
staring at that laptop,
and I got exactly nowhere.
Well, the good news is you won't be
on that computer tomorrow.
- I have something I need you to do.
- What?
- Shopping.
- What kind of shopping?
Supplies. We have to make a room
where Cole will be dispatched.
It has to be covered in plastic.
So does Cole.
To catch the blood.
I made a list.
Duct tape, 30 yards
of clear polyethylene sheeting.
And garbage bags, three mil, black.
- When are you gonna do it?
- Tomorrow.
I booked a room right next to Cole's.
You're gonna do it in the hotel?
No choice.
Jordan's next gig is in Sarasota.
He and Cole will be hitting the road
right after the seminar ends.
So...
...tomorrow night's the night.
There's a parking lot right on the corner
of Fourth and Bay.
Meet me there tomorrow at noon
and I'll pick up the supplies.
One o'clock would be better,
just so I have enough time to shop.
Sure.
What?
A few months ago,
I was shopping for a wedding dress,
and now I'm shopping for...
30 yards of polyethylene sheeting.
It's crazy, isn't it, how... quickly
you can get used to the supremely weird?
Tell me about it.
- Thanks for covering.
- No problem. Sonya just left.
Urgh. Jordan Chase.
I know you're hurting,
so I'll reserve judgment,
but I gotta draw the line somewhere.
It was free.
It can't hurt, can it?
Maybe I'll come away with something.
Yeah, a really ugly onesie.
I don't know. If it's working,
who am I to poop on your parade?
And your day?
I've got six mandatory sessions
with a shrink
coming at me because of Carlos Fuentes.
Feels like a big, fat
fucking waste of time too.
I mean, I'd kill that fucktard all over again.
I'd empty a fucking magazine in him.
OK. Maybe that's something
worth talking about.
I always thought if I landed a bullet
that it would bother me...
that it would...
it would be a burden
to take another life.
They don't issue guns to lab geeks,
so you have no idea what I'm talking about.
I can imagine.
I don't feel bad. Me, of all people.
I don't feel anything.
Maybe I've just run out.
Dad once told me that...
some people deserve to die.
You believe that?
You believe some people
deserve to die?
Some people don't deserve to live.
Trinity should be dead.
Not Rita, not Lundy.
Maybe the world is better off
without Carlos Fuentes.
I'd pretty much given up hope.
I figured I was destined
to go through life alone,
and then I started listening
to one of your CDs.
The Primal Self?
I started listening
in the car on the way to work.
Three weeks later I met my soul mate,
and now we have a baby on the way!
- Come on up here.
- Come on, honey!
Cole will be at his post
for the rest of the session.
That gives me an hour.
I'll have to do this in the dark.
Fourteen steps to the pillow.
Give him the needle,
and drag him to my room.
Sixty seconds tops.
Jordan's about to lose
his number-one fan.
- Sorry.
- Oh. No, no, it's me. Really.
- You look beautiful.
- I don't, really.
You do. You always do.
- Miami suits you.
- Huh.
You must love
all these Art Deco buildings.
Can't get enough of 'em.
Steph had her baby.
Oh, that's right.
She was due last month.
Yes. Meet Mavis.
Look at her.
Mavis?
Mark's grandmother. The name
came down to Mavis or Madison.
Madison? Your niece
could have been named after the city
where you and I did our Sunday beer runs.
Cooler heads prevailed. Mine.
How is Steph doing?
She's tired, glad to not be pregnant
any more, cries at commercials
and is transcendently happy.
Your parents miss you.
They'd like to know that you're safe.
You... can tell them.
Well, I'm thinking of not going back too.
- What?
- You were right.
We were trapped in our jobs,
trapped in that city.
We'd have been trapped in a life
we didn't want. It's time for that to change.
- Owen?
- Lu...
I bought these round-the-world tickets.
Broke the bank.
We can literally hop on
and hop off in any city.
I love you.
No matter what you do,
whoever you are,
I want to take this journey with you.
Have you met someone?
I've met a lot of people here,
but not like you're thinking.
I can't just leave.
Me showing up like this is sudden, I know.
We had five years.
Take a night to think it over.
I'm going either way,
but I'd rather go with you.
Meet me here tomorrow night
and tell me your decision.
God fucking damn it.
- What is it?
- Un-fucking-believable.
Lieutenant, will there be any other...
I don't know who your sources are,
but I can confirm that Detective Morgan
was in charge of the operation.
- Holy shit.
- She's blaming everything on me.
Is it true that Detective Morgan
has been placed on disciplinary leave?
As of today, she's being placed
on immediate suspension with pay,
pending the results of...
Whoa! Not the plasma.
Excuse me.
I thought we were actually friends.
Deb, wait.
I can't do it.
I can't let her throw me under the bus
and drive over me,
then back up a few fuckin' times
and drive off.
Oh.
Fuck! Shit! Fuck!
Didn't you see me driving up?
Didn't you see me backing out?
You know, there's a reason
why cars have rear-view mirrors, lady!
I mean, shit, look at that.
This here's fibreglass. Can't pound that out.
I'm gonna have to pull that whole panel off.
How do I know
it wasn't already there?
You just hit my car.
I was distracted.
Just let me give you some cash.
No cash! I don't want cash!
We'll do this on the up-and-up,
cos that's the kind of guy I am.
We just let the insurance dudes
hash this out.
You do have insurance, don't you?
- Yeah.
- Well, halle-fuckin'-lujah.
Now, let's just trade some info here
and get this sorted out.
Look, now, we can either
do this the right way,
or I can call up the police,
let Miami's finest handle it.
- It's your call.
- No. No, no, no. I...
The Jordan Chase
Experience seminar
will resume tomorrow
at 8:00am sharp.
Vendors are open tonight till 7:00pm.
How was your day?
I guess working for Jordan has its benefits.
- Hello?
- I'm here.
I'm on my way.
No, I mean, I'm here in the lobby.
- What are you doing here?
- I got into a car accident.
- Are you OK?
- Yeah, yeah.
It was my fault.
Actually, no, it was Owen's fault.
Owen who?
My ex-fiancé.
He's in Miami.
Why?
He came to see me.
Don't worry, I didn't tell him
anything about anything.
He asked me to go away with him.
Just up and leave all this behind.
As if I could.
You could, you know.
Do you want me to go?
If you want to, go.
This is the only part of my life
that makes sense any more.
- What about Owen?
- He's leaving.
- When?
- Tomorrow.
Stay the night.
The seminar's out for the day, and Cole
could be anywhere. He could see you.
It's too risky to have you
walk through the lobby again.
If I stay... does that mean
you're not gonna kill Cole tonight?
No, it's still happening.
We're gonna prepare the room together.
This is all much easier with a partner.
But a partner in what?
- Why didn't you tell me?
- I was planning to.
I have no idea
how the press got hold of it.
Maybe it was because
you fucking leaked it.
You'll be a desk jockey for a few weeks,
then your union rep
will have you reinstated.
This time next year,
all will have blown over.
It's just your word against mine
and everybody else that was there.
Some people don't agree with
your version of the events.
Who'd you get to lie for you?
Batista?
Batista's gonna back your fuckin' story?
- Do I have to go to Matthews with this?
- You watch yourself, Detective.
We wouldn't want your
reinstatement to be delayed.
God.
I was fucking happy for you
when you got married.
I thought that you being with Batista
might make you a nicer person.
I never expected you
to fuckin' eat him alive.
Cole's other victims.
Why did you put their pictures up?
Cole needs to see what he's done.
What do you get out of all this?
I like knowing that the men
who did this to you
won't do it to anyone else.
This isn't about me.
- You're standing here.
- Look at all this.
If you didn't know me,
you'd still be in this room.
Boyd wasn't your first.
You've been doing this a long time.
It's Cole.
We'll wait for him to go to sleep,
then you take off and I grab him.
What's that?
M-99. Animal tranquilliser.
Gives me a few hours to wrap his body
in plastic and secure him to this desk.
You're gonna kill him
while he's still out?
No, I'm gonna wake him up,
see if he'll give up the other two names
of the men in the pictures.
My knife can be very persuasive.
Stay here.
Tie my other arm!
Do it now!
Yes!
Oh. Oh.
Oh, God!
No.
No!
No more! Please!
Let me go! Let me out of here!
- What happened?
- You fell asleep.
What about Cole?
He's back at the seminar by now.
- The screamer spent the night.
- So you're not gonna kill him?
No, I am.
I've been thinking about it all night.
Cole makes his security rounds
at every session.
So...
I'll wait for him by the service elevator
and M-99 him there.
I would have rather grabbed him at night,
but I can make this work.
- And what about me?
- You'll wait until the session starts.
Everyone will be in the seminar.
You won't be spotted when you leave.
Just steer clear of the service elevator.
OK.
- I can't believe it.
- What?
I actually slept.
- Hey. Do you want to get up?
- No.
Do you want to go back to sleep?
- Do you want to just...
No, I don't want to do anything.
I just want to lie here.
It's Sunday. I'm allowed.
LaGuerta's an evil bitch.
No, she's not.
Maybe she is.
The best way to get back at her
is to do exactly what she says.
Go on leave, talk to your union rep,
get reinstated,
then come back
and kick as much ass as you possibly can.
No one, not even LaGuerta,
can deny that you're a great detective.
At the end of the day,
you'll be the one left standing.
- At the end of the day?
- Yeah, you know, when all is said and done.
Sounds like one very long day.
Hey.
- I smell coffee.
- Now's not a good time.
Well, it is for me.
- Hey, Debra Morgan.
- Liddy, right?
- Good memory. I like this one.
- This one?
You and I got something in common.
We've both been fucked over by LaGuerta.
Well, maybe we should make
matching T-shirts or something.
OK. Well, this one's going
for a fuckin' breakfast burrito.
I'll see you two later.
Call before you come over.
It's a common courtesy.
Don't you want to know about this girl
shacked up with Dexter Morgan?
I just staged a little meet and greet with her.
Old PI move.
- So you met her.
- Name, Lumen Pierce.
Lumen. Stupid fuckin' name.
From Minneapolis, Minnesota.
Supposed to be married three months ago,
picture in the paper and everything.
Just takes off.
Shows up here in Miami one week before
your boy's wife, Rita Morgan, is murdered.
- Now, what do you think of that?
- I don't know. Is that all you got?
- It's a hell of lot more than I had yesterday.
- Well, stay on it.
- I'd love to, but I am running out of loot.
- I just paid you last week.
And I just fucked up my car
getting this info for you, Quinn.
Now, this boy is dirty.
What you gonna do about it?
I'm not giving you any more.
You know, I thought you and me
had an understanding.
I mean, it'd be a shame if the skirt
you're boning finds out about all this.
- And how would that happen?
- I don't know.
Things go wrong every day.
Fuckin' motherfucker!
You two are starting
to sound more alike every day.
Must be love.
Tragedy.
Many of us here have experienced it
in one form or another.
The kind that leaves you wondering
if there's a reason to go on living.
For two days, you've heard me talking about
getting in touch with your primal self.
But how does the primal self
deal with loss?
Cole's starting his rounds. He'll reach
the service eleνator in five minutes.
In three minutes, so will I.
There's someone in this room
who is dealing with that very question.
Dexter Morgan.
Come and join me onstage, Dexter.
I know you weren't expecting this,
but it's important.
Please.
So much for slipping out quietly.
- Dexter! They want you, Dexter.
- Dexter, Dexter.
Dexter.
Dexter, Dexter.
Dexter works with Miami Metro Homicide.
Recently, he lost his wife.
She was murdered...
...by the Trinity Killer.
The very person
that Dexter's department was hunting.
You were the one to find her,
your wife? Rita?
Yeah.
Yes.
I'm gonna ask you to do something,
and it's gonna be very difficult.
I want you to relive that moment.
According to the newspapers, you were
supposed to be going away on honeymoon?
Dexter.
Y-Yes.
Tell us about it.
Well, we postponed the honeymoon
because we had a new baby, a boy.
Keep going. Tell me how you found her.
Please.
I'd come home after work.
I remember
walking through the house.
I turned the corner and...
...it's like time actually slowed down...
...and then stopped.
It's just a series of pictures.
What'd you see?
I saw my son sitting in blood.
He was crying.
So much blood.
And she was there in the tub.
She'd bled out. Her eyes were still open.
I want you to tell me something, Dexter.
I want you to be very honest.
What did you feel in that moment?
We want to know.
It's difficult to put into words.
Everything...
...fell apart. I felt...
Shattered?
Yes.
When the primal self is shattered,
it reaches out in search of
what will make it whole again.
Do you feel that, Dexter?
That hunger inside you
to be whole again?
- I do.
- That hunger is your primal self.
You must open your heart
and listen to what it's saying.
- Many people after suffering a tragedy...
- Mr Harmon?
...spend the rest of their lives
as broken beings...
- Can you sign this, please?
- ... living in the past.
Your primal self is crying out to be whole.
What is it that will make you whole?
For some, it's a new job.
For others, the love of another person.
Your primal self will tell you,
but you have to be open
to hearing the message. Are you?
Yes.
Then you've just taken your first step
toward happiness.
Dexter.
You fuckin' bitch!
Not this time.
I'm gonna take this gag out of your mouth,
but if you make one sound I don't like,
I'm gonna cut your eyes out.
Blink, so I know you understand.
We know about Boyd
and Dan the Dentist.
And now you.
Who are the others?
The guy who held a watch up to my ear.
"Tick tick tick.
That's the sound of your life running out."
What are their names?
What did he say?
Huey, Dewey, and Louie.
Look at the women
whose lives you destroyed.
Look. Look.
Death was the only kindness
you showed them.
It's a shame you can only die once.
You said I'd done this before. That's true.
This is who I am.
When I was a child, my mother
was murdered in front of me, and it...
...shattered me.
I've done this ever since.
Because for the longest time,
it was the only way I could feel...
...unbroken.
And then Rita was killed
and none of this made sense any more.
Until now.
Miguel couldn't. My father couldn't.
Can anyone live with the truth
of what I am?
Is Lumen what will make me whole?
Moving in?
The Lieutenant said I should bring
some of my stuff into this department.
It was you.
LaGuerta asked you to back her story,
and of course you did.
Deb.
- Deb?
- Detective Morgan...
you're the youngest woman in Miami Metro
to ever make detective,
and I really admire you, like, a lot.
And I came here
hoping to learn from you.
What you did...
you would never learn from me.
Good luck. You're gonna need it.
Deb.
I'm gonna do whatever it takes
to set the record straight.
I thought you were backing LaGuerta's story.
No, I didn't know what I was gonna do.
I was stuck between a rock and my wife,
but I decided I'm backing you.
Might not go over too well at home.
You're flesh and blood to me,
like my kid sister,
but better,
because I actually like you.
Damn.
It's OK.
Yeah.
Most people wait until the seminar is over
before checking out.
Uh... I lose my nanny in an hour.
I gotta get back to my son.
- Is everything OK?
- It's nothing important.
Just a little security glitch.
Like your chief of security's head
is in my luggage?
I want to thank you
for coming onstage.
It didn't seem like I had any choice.
I know it was sudden,
and you probably didn't appreciate it.
But you'll look back on it,
you'll realise it was worth it.
Don't forget what happened
here this weekend, Dexter.
- I won't.
- Act on what you've learned.
Don't let it slip away.
It's what I tell my clients.
Tick tick tick?
That's the sound of your life running out.
My primal instincts were right.
Jordan's one of them.
- Take it, Dexter.
- Oh, I will.
It's a law of physics
that elements want to unify.
Single cells in a Petri dish
thrash around until they coalesce.
And events in the universe
that once seemed random
are eventually revealed to have
an underlying connectedness.
Jordan Chase is one of them.
I'm sure of it.
"Tick tick tick."
But he wasn't in the photo.
Maybe he took the photo, I don't know.
We're gonna take down Jordan Chase?
First things first.
Just... let go?
Just let go.