Previously on Dexter...
Cut him, and I'll blow your fucking head off.
Medic! I need a fucking medic!
We were wondering
if there's anything you can tell us
about the man who injured you.
I know where Carlos and his
brother have been hanging out -
at a local club
called The Mayan.
- You got your lead. Congrats.
- Yeah, we stake this place out,
they show up, and then we take
these Santa Muerta no-dicks down for good.
- Are you and Quinn...
- We're fuck buddies.
Don't bring him around
when Harrison's here.
- Would you like some coffee?
- That would be wonderful.
Son of a bitch.
- Hey, hey, hey! Sergeant!
- Angel, let him go. This is a sting!
IA needed my help
to bust a narcotics cop on the take,
and I said yes,
to close the books on your bar fight!
- Fuck those IA rats.
- And your boss.
That bitch put handcuffs on me.
I might have a job for you.
- You got a name?
- Dexter Morgan.
Boyd wasn't the only one
who did this to me.
There were others.
What are you gonna do if you
actually find one of these guys?
- What you won't.
- You going to kill them?
You don't get to tell me
what to do.
What are you doing?
You were about to murder
the wrong man.
Go home.
OK. OK, OK, I'll go.
You're doing the right thing.
Your parents will be happy to see you.
Thank you.
Maybe this is one problem
I can check off the list.
Welcome to Miami.
I've always tried to keep
the different parts of my life separate.
Becoming a father
made that much more difficult.
And as a husband, I failed.
But I'm a very neat monster...
who won't make
the same mistake again.
I packed up Rita's wedding dress.
I thought Astor might want it someday.
Feels like it took you guys
months to move in...
Only a day to pack up.
The realtor suggested
we paint the walls white.
She wants to stage the house
Miami Chic.
No evidence that a family
ever lived here.
Or died here.
You have to disclose that,
don't you?
The hope is that a ridiculously low
listing price
will help a buyer see past that.
Any idea where you want to live?
I'm sorry. That was a stupid question.
You should take the apartment.
No. No, that's yours.
No, I insist. It's really always been yours.
- I'll move out.
- I thought you already did.
I didn't move in with Quinn.
Well, you're never around.
I'm at Quinn's, but I don't live there.
No clothes in any drawers.
There's no his-and-hers toothbrush action.
Quinn's place is all Quinn.
A vast, empty space?
I don't remember Rita in these.
Because they belong to Lumen.
Me either.
Lumen is home in Minneapolis,
another part of my life
packed away.
Life seems different now.
Manageable.
Everything in its right place.
Soon, Lance Robinson
will be on my table.
Lance trawls the internet,
engaging in casual encounters
with innocent men...
who never suspect those encounters
could turn deadly.
Four times Lance deliberately pushed
someone's fantasies too far.
He will be an easy kill,
just like old times.
Tonight's the night.
OK, people.
Let's go over our positions at Club Mayan.
Everybody be in place by 10.
Batista and I'll be in the van, as usual.
Quinn, you'll watch the door.
Cira...
- Yes, Chief?
- Don't let me stop you.
Officer Manzon, you'll be on the floor
watching foot traffic at the VIP room,
- in case the Fuentes brothers roll through.
- And what if they don't?
Then we'll work
the operation until they do.
You were face to face
with Carlos Fuentes, right?
Yes, sir.
Then that means
he knows that we're onto him.
Tell me why they would ever
return to this club.
The only reason the Fuentes brothers
are forcing people
to withdraw cash from the ATM,
is to pay for table service at this club.
We ran the dates of the ATM hold-ups
past the club managers.
And they confirmed
that on each of those nights,
the Fuentes brothers
showed up at Club Mayan,
and took over the VIP lounge.
So if the Fuentes brothers do show up
at this club, which is highly unlikely,
it means that someone is possibly
lying on the floor of their living room
without their head.
We're working
the only lead we have.
All you're doing is drinking and dancing
on the taxpayer's dime.
I would have expected
more from you, Morgan.
Chief.
We don't have
a lot of options here.
Without this operation, we're effectively stopping work on
this
case,
which we cannot do to this community.
Did you even know
this operation was happening?
Of course I knew. Why wouldn't I?
Well, it seems you've been spending
a lot of time lately with Internal Affairs
bailing your new husband
out of hot water.
Bravo, Mrs Batista.
I'm keeping my name.
And I think working Club Mayan is
a valid allocation of my squad's resources.
It is your squad, Lieutenant.
- How you manage it is up to you.
- Thank you.
But if another murder goes up on the board,
it's your ass on the line, not mine.
You have one more night at Club Mayan.
Make something happen.
Matthews doesn't have
much faith in us, does he?
Well, that fight you had at the bar
didn't help anything.
- He knows about the bar fight?
- Of course he knows.
A narcotics officer got suspended
because of that bar fight.
No. A narcotics officer got suspended
because of you.
- Me?
- You ran to IAD.
You cooked up the sting.
You basically got Stan Liddy fired.
And got all the charges
against you dropped.
I didn't ask for any of that.
I could have handled whatever
IAD had coming my way.
- Oh, so anything that happens is fine?
- When it happens to me, yes.
I can take care of myself.
But now we're married,
whatever happens to me, happens to you.
That's right. That's exactly right.
- We're married.
- Well, here's what's bothering me.
You weren't looking out for me
out of some sense of compassion.
You were taking care of yourself.
God forbid your name
should lose some of its shine.
- Get out of my office.
- Mm-hm.
- Hey.
- I thought you might want a debriefing
before we hit Club Mayan.
Um, sort of... not a good time.
Where's Quinn,
and what have you done with him?
I know, I know. Uh...
Just give me an hour.
- An hour.
- Yeah.
Who's naked
in your apartment?
No one is naked.
Then what?
- I'm such a fucking idiot.
- Debra, wait.
Come here.
Debra, come here.
Debra Morgan,
this is Stan Liddy.
Liddy had a run-in with IAD
and, uh, got suspended.
We're prepping him
for his union-rep meeting tomorrow.
Sorry.
All clothes are staying on.
- I'll just...
- Meet me there?
Yeah, I'll meet you there.
You are boning
our target's sister?
Just tell me what you found out
on Dexter Morgan.
Well...
your boy's squeaky clean on paper.
He's only been out
of the country once, to Paris.
Pays his bills on time,
keeps to himself.
I'll tell you, it's all too neat
and a little too phoney.
You see drug dealers
with the very same profiles all the time.
Ah. That's exactly
what I'm thinking.
I mean, what's he hiding?
Peekaboo.
"Bye-bye, Daddy."
Peekaboo!
Oh, thank you.
You're really very good with him.
I wish I didn't have
to work tonight.
The lab fell so far behind
while I was out.
Night's the only time I can ever
get anything done.
Well, I hope the lieutenant
appreciates your dedication.
I'm pretty sure she does.
Although tonight
will be dedicated to Lance.
So, you think about midnight, then?
I'll try to make it sooner.
Can you say,
"Bye-bye, Daddy"?
Die-die.
Did you hear that?
- He said, "Die-die."
- Don't be silly. He said, "Bye-bye."
Harrison's first word.
There's a good boy.
I hope so.
Die-die.
From the mouth of babes.
I rented an RV, placed an ad online
saying I was cruising down to The Keys,
and just like that...
my victim came to me.
You must be
ten inches of pure steel.
You betcha.
Compartmentalisation began
as an architectural theory -
divide buildings into sections
which can be closed off
to prevent a fire
from spreading.
Life can also be divided
into closed-off sections.
Makes everything much simpler.
Lumen Pierce.
Again?
This is the life
Harry wanted for me...
carefully divided.
Shh!
What the hell?
Dexter!
I...
I shot one of them.
I killed him.
I'm at the marina...
Bayshore, Biscayne or something?
- You're in Miami?
- I never left.
Oh, there's so much blood.
What do I do?
Hello? Hello?
Dexter, don't hang up on me!
Please, help me.
Don't move.
Don't do anything.
The M-99 will wear off in a few short hours.
Not much time to contain the situation...
Not much time...
to protect my simple life.
First, for good luck...
let me see your neck.
I fucking love my job.
Look, I'm gonna go take a lap
through the VIP.
- She's cute.
- Yeah, she's all right.
I could do you both.
That's the sixth girl
that's hit on him.
Let's focus on camera three.
That guy, is he hooked up
with the Fuentes brothers?
Hey, I'm gonna stay on Quinn.
He may need some backup.
He is supposed to be focusing
on the Fuentes brothers.
He's not supposed to be playing
with her fun bags.
Sounds like someone's jealous.
Why on God's green earth
would I be jealous?
Quinn's a good guy.
I'm not interested.
Out there on the dance floor,
shaking his tail feathers.
Really not interested.
Stay single as long as you can.
- Says the newlywed.
- Don't remind me.
You've been married for five minutes.
What happened to the honeymoon phase?
I blinked.
Show me where he is.
There was so much blood,
I had... I had to walk away.
The body's in here.
- Anybody see you?
- I don't think so.
- Oh, God, I hope not.
- You killed somebody.
- Because you wouldn't do it for me!
- But you call me to clean up after you.
- I didn't know what to do with the body!
- I don't believe this.
- Just go if you want to go.
- Go? I'm responsible for you.
Everything you do
leads right back to me.
I didn't think it would be
so hard to kill someone.
- Where is he?
- Here.
Oh, shit!
- He was right here.
- Are you sure?
- He was dead.
- Apparently not.
Don't get mad at me.
This isn't how I was planning
to spend my evening.
- Me neither.
- Would you do me a favour?
- What?
- Stop talking.
He's lost a lot of blood,
at least a pint.
One...
two.
Three...
four.
You're a terrible shot,
but you never shot a gun before.
You didn't anticipate
the kickback...
One of the many things you didn't anticipate.
Give me the gun.
You must have hit him once.
Where was the point of impact?
Where were you standing?
He was standing here.
Bam, bam, bam, bam, bam.
I go down, you run away.
I get back up, and where do I go?
Here.
Come on!
How'd you even find this guy?
You can talk now.
The night that I was taken,
I had gone to a bar.
I thought that
they spotted me there,
so I went back to that same bar
night after night,
hoping that one of them
would walk through the door.
- I wore a disguise.
- Disguise?
A wig, so they wouldn't recognise me.
I know what a disguise is for.
So, you went to the bar,
you waited for one of them to show up.
Where? What bar?
Hurricane 26.
Hurricane 26 is all the way over
on Ocean Avenue.
How'd you get all the way out here?
That's what I've been trying to tell you.
So, go on.
Tonight one of them showed up.
He didn't know it was me,
so I... I flirted with him.
I asked him if he wanted
to go someplace else.
We got in the car, I pulled out my gun,
and I forced him to drive.
This place seemed deserted,
so we stopped,
- and I marched him inside.
- And you shot him.
No. I asked him for the names
of the other men.
He called me a cunt.
Then I shot him.
How'd you know
he was one of them?
I just... I just knew.
You recognise his face?
No. They kept me blindfolded
most of the time.
So how?
I felt it the minute
he walked in the door.
One of the guys
had this smell like...
old sweat or,
I don't know, chlorine.
When I got in the car with this guy,
there it was, the exact same stench.
You shot someone
based on a feeling and an odour.
I shot the right guy.
You were willing to shoot the wrong guy
under Tuttle Bridge.
This guy was one of them.
- What's his name?
- I don't know.
Did you check his wallet?
- No.
- Did you take his cell phone?
He could have already called
the police, you know.
- I'm new to this!
- You don't even know who you shot!
I shot one of the creeps
who raped me.
- You don't have any proof.
- I'm the proof!
My memory! My experience!
- Hardly the most reliable tools.
- Fuck you!
Fuck me?
Wow.
Just go.
I can find him on my own
and kill him.
Like you killed him
the first time?
I have no idea which direction he went,
if he turned right or...
Blood swipe.
He stopped here to catch his breath,
leaned against the post,
put his hand here.
The directionality of the blood
leads which way?
This way.
You sure know a lot about blood.
So, hypothetically,
an office romance is just
the worst idea ever.
Yeah, I would advise against it.
But, hypothetically...
I can see how you and Quinn
make a lot of sense.
So you would advise against it,
but it would make a lot of sense?
What can I say?
I'm a romantic at heart.
Then why don't you patch stuff up
with your wife?
- It's not that simple.
- It is that simple.
Get your head out of your ass,
and do something nice for her.
Buy her a card, some flowers.
- Get her a puppy.
- A puppy?
Batista.
Where?
Baywater Marina,
Warehouse 12.
I'll be right there.
- Possible homicide.
- I'll get it.
No, I'll go.
This is your baby.
We've been on this for weeks,
and had nothing but our asses
handed to us,
and if for some reason
the Fuentes brothers show up tonight,
then they've already seen my face,
so I'm useless.
And you won't have to see
Quinn hitting on other women.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- Yeah. Good luck.
Yeah, you too.
Mmm. Who are you?
No dial tone.
He didn't call anybody.
Who even uses
a pay phone any more?
People who don't have cell phones.
We caught a break.
But he could have gone anywhere.
What are you doing?
- It's luminol.
- Luminol?
No relation.
The hydrogen peroxide
and sodium hydroxide
react with the iron
present in haemoglobin,
and exhibit a...
...blue glow. See?
Why do you have that
in your purse?
It's not a purse.
And I use this almost every day.
- What is it?
- Crime Scene.
"Crime Scene"?
Are you...
a police officer?
"Baywater Marina, Warehouse 12."
Isn't that...
...here?
Shit. Somebody did see you.
- Oh, fuck!
- No, we still have time.
Patrol can't move until Homicide
arrives on the scene.
That's at least 15 minutes from now.
How long have you been a cop?
- I'm not a cop.
- Well, what are you?
Complicated.
This way. Hurry up.
Running pumps the heart faster,
and more blood is spilled.
Look here, how the drops are pooling,
getting closer together.
- He's slowing down?
- Yeah.
This way.
This started out
as an ordinary day.
In one second, everything changed.
Lumen happened.
Why are you here in Miami?
You were getting on a plane to Minneapolis.
I tried to get on that plane.
I couldn't.
I had to stay.
The guy I shot tonight,
he would take these three fingers...
- You don't have to tell...
...and shove them in my mouth!
It tasted like metal.
He would keep them there
so I couldn't scream.
The other guys would just stuff
a dirty rag in my mouth,
but not this guy.
He liked to hold me down himself.
I saw everything.
How? You were blindfolded.
Is this your monster?
Pardon me,
but I couldn't help noticing
that you've been hanging out
with a fool.
Hmm.
- How do you know?
- Cos whoever stood you up... es un idiota.
I'm Angel.
- Yasmin.
- My favourite flower.
Ooh.
- No? OK.
- Mm-mm.
Do you want to get
out of here, Yasminita?
Yeah.
It hurts! Oh, my God!
Calm down.
God... OK.
- What are you doing?
- I'm gonna inspect your wounds.
Yeah, one gunshot wound
penetrated the abdominal cavity.
Oh, God.
- You can't let me die.
- Come over here and hold this.
You're gonna save him?
I don't know who this man is.
My name's Dan. Dan Mendell.
This woman right here, she shot me.
- I have no idea why.
- You know exactly what you did to me!
I've never seen this woman
before in my life.
- You're a fucking liar!
- You're fucking crazy!
Look, you can't let me die.
I got a wife.
I got a daughter.
Please. Just look.
"Dan Mendell, DDS."
Kids' dentist.
- He's a rapist.
- I never did anything to you.
We met in a bar,
but she came on to me.
And then we get in the car,
she pulls a gun on me.
- You panicked.
- Because you were gonna shoot me.
- No, because you recognised me.
- I've never seen you before in my life.
- You know exactly who I am!
- She's crazy.
We got a mental situation
going on here.
- You, in the corner.
- You believe him?
She needs help. This woman needs help.
You're a piece of shit.
Full of shit!
Over there.
I have to take this call.
Stay there till I get back.
Don't leave me alone with her!
Do not move from this spot.
Help!
Everything OK?
Die-die.
Hi-hi, Harrison.
I know you're working, but I thought
you might want to take a break.
- It's wild hearing him talk.
- Isn't it?
I put him down,
and he was up two hours later
talking up a storm, weren't you?
♪ Flies in the buttermilk,
shoo, fly, shoo... ♪
Here, let me get you
on the speaker,
and you can sing to him too.
♪ Lost my partner, what'll I do? ♪
Dexter.
♪ Lost my partner, what'll I do?
♪ Skip to the lou, my darling ♪
Well, I don't want to keep you.
I'm afraid to ask, but...
You want me to stay
a few more hours?
I'll be home as soon as I can.
There's no place I'd rather be right now.
Die-die.
Die-die. I love you.
- Who are they?
- Get off of me!
- What are their names?
- I don't know what you're talking...
Huh?
He's a fucking liar!
He knows who they are!
Who are they?
- What are their names?
- You are ruining my life!
They ruined mine.
If we don't get help,
Dan the Dentist is going to expire.
I don't care.
It's what he deserves.
It's what they all deserve.
They should all get...
He's saying something.
He's talking to someone.
She fucking shot me.
My phone.
Can you hear me?
She shot me.
She's alive. You hear me?
That last fucking bitch is alive.
They're gonna find you...
you...
...cunt.
Die-die.
Lumen didn't witness her mother's murder,
but she was born in blood.
Like me.
Some experiences are so big
they change your DNA.
What now?
We clean up.
Homicide will be on us soon.
Hose this area down. Make sure everything
flows through the grate.
Where are you going?
To get my car.
We have to move this body.
About time.
Come on.
A hooker called in some gunshots,
but didn't actually see the shooter.
- Where's the body?
- Well, haven't found it yet.
Then what are we doing here?
Hey.
Blood.
Bullet holes.
Lots of blood.
A significant amount of blood.
Definitely some sort
of homicidal situation here.
A homicidal situation requires a body.
Why don't we let the EMTs handle it?
Your average person won't survive
this amount of blood loss.
There.
That blood trail there. See it?
Good chance that trail
ends at a dead body.
- Dexter's en route, but...
- I get it. We can't wait.
Will you two guys follow us in,
in case this bleeder's alive?
Whoa.
This dude is a half-litre from dead.
- Yeah?
- Hey, fuckwad, taking the scenic route?
Sorry. I was with Harrison.
He said his first words...
"Bye-bye."
- Yeah? That's sweet.
- Yeah, it was.
I remember your first words...
"Shoes."
You were very girly,
once upon a time.
That's funny, cos I always
remember my first words as being
- "Hurry the fuck up."
- Almost there.
Masuka and I tracked this dude's blood
to a pay phone inside a warehouse.
- You did?
- I think this way.
Yeah. We're gonna keep going.
- So find us.
- Will do.
You changed your clothes.
- Here. This is all I have.
- Thanks.
The police are close.
You have to get out of here.
Go to this address.
3319, Meadow Lane.
It's near Kendall.
Say it back to me.
3319, Meadow Lane,
near Kendall.
This'll get you in the front door.
Run six, seven blocks. Catch a cab.
Get cleaned up and wait for me.
I have it from here.
- You want me to go now?
- Yes.
No, I'm not leaving you.
Yes, you are.
I can help you move the body.
Who the hell is that?
Go, now. Go!
Compartmentalisation is a joke.
Fires rip through buildings
all the time
no matter how closed off
parts of them are.
Life is the same way.
It cannot be contained.
Fuck. Maybe we should
double back the way we came.
Is that?
Dexter's car.
Dexter.
You will not believe what I found.
What in the mother of fuck
went on in here?
I know exactly what happened.
Two words...
autoerotic mummification.
See, Mr Plastic Man...
shot Captain Bloody Underpants,
while Underpants
was in the choke.
Mr Plastic Man has hammocks
between Underpants' man chop...
Thanks to Masuka's keen expertise,
Debra will be able
to close this case.
Evidence will go into
a banker's box and be filed away,
eventually transferred
to a storage facility in Bradenton,
and that is where it will stay,
locked away forever in the dark.
If only everything
were that simple.
Thank you for the visual.
Asphyxiation heightens the high,
but it's not without its risks.
By the way, I wouldn't touch
the nozzle of that hose.
Anything to add?
The blood is consistent
with Masuka's theory.
If there's any follow-up,
I'd be happy to do it.
We're good here?
- You just landed.
- I have to relieve Sonya.
Yeah, we're good. Drive safe.
What a night.
You sure you want to do this?
I'm here, aren't I?
Angel?
This is Yasmin Aragon.
What is she doing on my couch?
Miss Aragon is friends
with Los Hermanos Fuentes.
She also has a boatload
of drug charges against her.
Seems like a trade is in order.
So are we gonna do this or not?
Give us a minute.
Excuse me.
I saw that she was wearing
a Santa Muerte necklace,
so I introduced myself.
If we agree to drop
her drug charges,
she thinks she can get
the Fuentes brothers in the club.
That is...
if you're willing to give us
another chance.
I'm... sorry about everything.
About losing my temper,
about what I said earlier.
You were right.
Say that again?
- You were right.
- I like the sound of that.
I did go to IAD because I didn't want
my husband disciplined.
I really like being married to you, Angel.
And I you.
It's something I never thought
would happen to me
because I've been so busy
making a name for myself,
and now I'm this close
to making captain.
And I would never
do anything to stop you.
Not on purpose, I know.
But get a stink on you...
- and I start to stink too.
- We'll stock up on deodorant.
Nice job bringing in the girl.
Yeah.
Better than a puppy?
I'll see you back at home.
Hello?
- Hey.
Last one.
Sorry.
You got glitter on your face.
Yeah...
hazard of the job.
I'm not sure it's in the job description
that you have to put your face
in Boobie McGee's tits.
Well, you know, the first rule
of working undercover is to blend in.
You disappeared.
- I did, didn't I?
- It's not funny.
Fuck. I...
I have feelings for you.
- You do?
- I tried not to.
I like you too.
Uh...
More than "like".
- You do?
- Yeah.
I mean, you're the one
who keeps putting the brakes on.
Well, what if I don't want
to do that any more?
That'd make me very happy.
If this is gonna end badly...
will you please just tell me now?
Morgan, I just said I want to be with you.
I mean, what more do you want?
Well, I mean,
sometimes you mumble,
and it's kind of hard
to understand you.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
How's this?
I tried to send this woman
1,500 miles away,
and she boomeranged
back into the house I shared with Rita.
Lumen?
So much for keeping
the different parts of my life separate.
Sorry, I'll just be in here.
There are towels...
somewhere.
I found some in a box.
I also found this robe.
Is it OK if I borrow it?
Sure.
The tub's not draining.
Sometimes the thingy gets stuck.
Are you OK?
Do you need to sit down?
Yeah, for a minute.
I know you.
What you are...
deep down.
Aside from your police job,
and your... extracurricular activities.
You're a father.
I saw the pictures out there.
Three children?
The two oldest
are with their grandparents -
their dad's mom and dad.
You have a son?
Harrison.
He just started talking.
Today.
He's tremendous.
It's...
just the two of you?
And an Irish superhero nanny.
Never thought my life
would turn out like this.
I had imagined...
a totally different life
for myself too.
I always did everything
by the book, you know?
Go, go, go.
Never stopped to think.
There was high school,
and college, and graduate school...
Owen.
We were gonna get married at...
the house that I grew up in.
On my wedding day,
I... I tried on the dress,
and I looked out the window
at the backyard where the aisle was, and...
I saw everything
that that aisle was leading to.
Babies and...
matching dinnerware...
Sunday barbecues.
And I couldn't breathe.
I had to get out of there and...
find something...
...more.
Then everything happened, and...
I actually thought,
"This is what I get...
"for trying to...
"live my own life."
Do you have any idea
what I'm talking about?
A little.
But tonight I felt this, like...
this...
peace.
And it's because he's dead.
And I know that it's not gonna last.
And when it wears off,
I'm gonna have to find the rest of them.
Because that's the only way
that I'll find that peace again.
I don't even have a name
for what I'm feeling.
I do.
The Dark Passenger.
I can't get revenge
for Rita's death,
but I can help Lumen
avenge what was done to her.
How many more were there?