So, how the hell was your date
with Rita last night?
Great.
I think I met the right woman for me.
She's perfect, because Rita
is as damaged as me.
I can't believe I found the one good,
truly decent man left on the planet.
- I have a dark side too.
- Somehow I doubt that.
I watched my mother die
when I was three.
She was murdered in front of me.
You have your demons, but I know that
you don't have to be a slave to them.
I wish that were true.
I want to someday be content,
like everyone else.
- I want...
- A normal life.
- I wanna marry you.
- Yes!
You guys are my family.
Now I have a partner for life.
I'm content.
Maybe even happy.
I hope you're not taking
any of this seriously - the wife, the kids.
It's all great camouflage.
It's gotten more
complicated than that.
I'm pregnant.
You want to see him
come into the world.
- Yes. Raise him with Rita.
- I know.
I've never wanted anything
so much in my life.
Wanna know a secret?
Daddy kills people.
There's a monster walking around free.
I call him the Trinity Killer.
Kills in threes.
Trinity's a husband, a father.
He's... like me.
What kind of father
keeps blood slides in his shed?
If I don't figure out how to hide this,
I'm gonna lose my family.
Arthur's kept this up
for, what, 20 years?
My family may not last 20 minutes.
Arthur Mitchell.
Kyle Butler.
Only way it was gonna work
is if I jumped in with both feet.
Jump in with both feet, huh?
This is your new role model, Dex?
Get that axe from him.
Kill him now.
I still have things to learn from him.
You're juggling
too many people, Dexter.
Blood tech, husband, father,
serial killer.
Now Kyle Butler. Which one are you?
All of them.
Hello...
Dexter Morgan.
Hello, Arthur Mitchell.
Hey, sweetie.
The moon tonight is gonna be amazing.
So take a moment.
We love you. Bye.
Rita?
Born in blood. Both of us.
I thought I could change what I am,
keep my family safe.
But it doesn't matter what I do.
This is fate.
Sir, did you call this in?
Sir. What happened here?
I've watched 67 people die,
and at the moment of truth,
I looked into their eyes
and they knew and I knew
they got what they deserved.
But what if that's not
what happens?
If you don't get what you deserve?
If what you deserve
is a white picket fence
and your kids all around
and a husband who loves you?
What if the least you deserve
is a real human being
and what you get instead... is me?
Sir. Sir, we're going to take
the child into safe custody now.
- Sir, hand me the child.
- What are you doing?
- Back off!
- Ma'am!
Miami Homicide. He is too.
I said back the fuck off!
What happened?
Jesus.
Rita's inside.
It was me.
Skin's wrinkled from hours
in the alkaline water.
Rigor mortis full-blown.
Epidermal mottling.
I imagined her naked plenty of times,
but never like this.
Single cut to the femoral artery.
We're looking at Trinity's MO here.
Did he ever kill a married woman
in a bathtub?
First time for everything.
Unfortunately for Dexter.
We're still waiting on the coroner
to move the body.
But overall lividity
puts time of death
somewhere between
eight and twelve hours... ago.
You OK?
Dexter came home to that.
He's gonna need our support here.
Obviously.
What do you want us
to do with him?
The first thing I want you to do
is pack up and get out of there.
- Well...
- What?
The FBI's here. Trinity is their case.
I already ceded jurisdiction.
What are you looking at him for?
It's what I was saying
on the way over.
Rita's one of ours. She's family.
We should be working
on this for Dexter.
Damn it, Angel, it's done!
Just do what I say.
She's stressed. We all are.
My father Harry
taught me a few simple rules.
Neνer hurt an innocent
and never make a scene.
Harry?
Where are you, now,
when I really need you?
When it's my wife in the body bag,
everybody's looking,
and it's the neighbour crying, not me?
Sir?
We're ready for you.
The first responders told me when they
went inside and found your wife
you said, "It was me."
You sure?
That's what was reported to me, yeah.
I don't know what I said. It could have
been anything. I'm very upset.
Of course you are.
Who wouldn't be?
Mr Morgan, before you came home
and found your wife,
where did you say you were again?
Dexter, take off your clothes,
then we're going home.
I was asking him a question.
He already said he came home
and he found her there.
If you wanna help,
why don't you find Trinity?
Or is doing something actually useful
not in your fucking job description?
Detective Morgan.
FBI?
Fucking Bunch of Idiots.
Stop.
Finish up here,
then take your brother home.
You wanna talk to Dexter,
schedule an appointment.
I'll do that.
He can sleep on the floor
until we can bring his crib
over from the house.
- It'll be safest, don't you think?
- Yeah.
I gotta tell you, Dexter,
don't say things like, "It was me."
People will misunderstand.
In fact, I don't understand.
What did you even mean?
Dexter.
This is Dexter Morgan.
3319 Meadow Lane.
What is your emergency?
I just got home and found
my wife dead in the bathtub.
- What is this?
- The 911 call Dexter made.
Listen.
I just got home and found
my wife dead in the bathtub.
- Did you say your wife is dead?
- Yes, I did.
She has an approximately
one-inch incision
midway up her right thigh,
dissecting the femoral artery.
All right. That's enough.
He obviously is in shock.
"Midway up her right thigh"?
"Dissecting her femoral artery"?
- Habit of precision.
- His wife just died.
He's submitting a lab report.
Seriously, the next-door neighbour,
the guy with the, you know, forehead?
He was more broken up about Rita
than Dexter was.
- So?
- So it's weird, that's all.
- What are we working on here?
- Not Rita.
It's Dexter's 911 call.
Did you hear me or not?
I said the case is with the FBI now.
You should have taken her
on a honeymoon.
You were right about one thing -
that neighbour Elliot
being all broken up about Rita.
I'm thinking now there's some things
I shouldn't have told Dexter.
What? What shouldn't you
have told him?
About a significant exchange of saliva
I witnessed at Thanksgiving.
- As in a kiss.
- Elliot and Rita?
Dude was totally
in love with her.
- And Dexter knew?
- Yeah.
If I'd known she was gonna...
I should have kept
my big mouth shut.
Could someone get that? Deb?
Damn it.
Hello.
Dexter, it's Maura.
Hello?
I'm sorry if I woke you,
but I have got two very excited kids here,
and Rita's not answering.
Yeah, there's something
you need to know.
OK. OK, OK.
But first somebody really
wants to talk with you.
Dexter!
Hey, Cody, you OK?
We've been having the best day.
I had cotton candy for breakfast.
That's great.
Here, give me the phone.
Gimme, gimme.
Hi, Dexter. Can I talk to Mom?
- Not now.
- Why not?
She's, uh...
She's in the shower.
Well, can you tell her we miss her?
We miss you too, Dexter,
and Harrison.
Here's my grandmother.
So, there was something
that you needed to tell me?
When you bring them home tonight, uh...
come to Deb's apartment
instead of the house, OK?
What happened,
did you miss your flight?
Something like that.
I'll explain when you get here.
You sure you don't want
to tell them about Rita?
I just want them to have
one more good day.
Look, I know this is really difficult...
but there are a lot of things that need
to happen before Rita can be buried.
I've been on the phone all morning with
a funeral director who does a lot of cops.
And he's willing to see us right away.
You willing to do that?
I'm sorry for your loss.
How does he do that?
My sincere condolences.
He sounds like he actually means it.
Thank you.
Would you like something
to drink? Coffee?
Water?
No. I'm fine.
There are Kleenexes here...
if you need them.
What we need to do now, Dexter...
May I call you that?
What we need to do now, Dexter,
is make some very important decisions
about how your wife Rita
will be remembered.
OK.
We like to start with the obituary.
It's a good way to let people
know about services
and where to send remembrances.
But most importantly,
it's a chance to express
your feelings about Rita
in your own words.
Excuse me.
I'll get you something for the paper.
What else do you need?
So this is how normal people do it.
No hefty bags. No diesel fumes.
This is what she would have wanted -
a grieving spouse...
for once doing what
a person's supposed to do.
- Dexter Morgan?
- Rita?
- Hi.
Sorry I'm late.
- That's no problem.
- There was traffic, of course.
I went to the wrong café.
I went to the one in town.
I didn't know there was
anything even out this far.
How did you find this place?
I, uh... tracked it down.
So, I... Your sister...
Debra's told me so much about you.
- Uh-oh.
- Oh.
Nothing bad, of course.
She omitted the fact
that I'm an axe murderer?
No. She said that you were a...
bloodstain pattern analyst.
Which I have no clue what that is.
Believe me, I barely do either,
and I do it 40 hours a week.
She seems nice, your sister.
You seem nice too.
Thank you.
So, um, what's good here?
There must be something special
to bring you all the way out this far.
I... I usually play it safe
and go with a Caesar salad.
But I don't see one on here.
You know, I think
I'm gonna get the special,
the mushroom ravioli.
Dexter?
- Do you know what you want?
- Yes, I do.
Dex.
What are you doing?
I was just thinking about Rita,
how much...
How much you miss her?
How much I lied to her,
from the very beginning.
Funeral's the day after tomorrow.
I chose an oak casket.
I hope that's all right.
White roses.
I think she'd like those.
They want to know
if there's a particular dress
you'd like her to be buried in.
Not really.
OK.
I'll find something.
Quinn called, and the FBI has released
the crime scene at your house,
so there are some things
I want to do there and...
I'm gonna drop you two off
at the apartment. Is that OK?
Yeah, that's fine.
You're worrying me.
I really didn't expect you to come.
We're partners. I'm here.
What are we looking for?
Nothing.
Trinity wouldn't leave
anything behind.
What are we doing, then?
I wanted to clean the place up.
Make sure Dexter
didn't see it like this.
The FBI left it this way.
They have people who'll do that.
This much blood,
usually you call Dexter.
How you holdin' up?
OK. I guess.
I mean, you know my brother.
It's a little hard to tell.
No, I mean you.
How are you holding up?
Oh.
Fine.
Not used to having to be
the strong one, you know?
It's always been Dexter.
- And now...
- He's the strong one?
To me it's always seemed
the other way around.
Swear to God, I can't even
tell what he's thinking.
Sorry. I didn't mean
to make things worse.
It's OK.
- What are you doing?
- I don't know.
Open the door! Come on!
Hurry, come on, open up! Dexter!
- Are you there?
- Open the door!
Dexter, you came back early!
Hey, guys. Did you have fun?
- It was awesome.
- We got you stuff.
- Perfect.
- There's one for Mom too.
Where is she?
She's not here.
Well, where is she?
Just... sit down.
I need to tell you something.
Dexter?
Is everything OK?
What's going on?
You're... You're freaking me out.
Something happened to your mom.
Something bad?
Yeah. Something bad.
Is she OK?
A man came into our house,
and your mother came home
and he killed her.
- What?
- She got killed?
- Somebody killed her?
- No, she's fine.
Dexter. What...
- You're kidding, right?
- I don't understand.
You said spend the day
at Disney World.
I'm sorry for your loss.
- Astor?
- Go away.
I mean it! Leave me alone!
Just listen to me.
Everything's gonna be OK.
It won't be. She's dead!
I know.
And it doesn't even matter to you.
- How can you say that?
- Cos it doesn't.
I can tell just by looking
you don't even care.
Where were you?
Where were you
when someone was killing her?
You should have been there
to protect her.
You're right.
- That was your job!
- I know.
I should have been there, and I wish
I could take it all back. I wish...
that none of this had ever happened
and your mom was still alive.
Wanna know what I wish?
That it was just my mom
and me and Cody and Harrison.
Cos we all would have been
so much better off if she hadn't met you!
I wish you were dead!
- Do you mind?
- What?
Look somewhere else.
What are you doing?
Jesus, Quinn, you can't
grab a sheet or something?
Sorry.
So, what are you doing?
Trying to find a dress for Rita.
You gonna bury her in one of those?
You got something better?
Great. I gotta go.
I gotta go home now.
You might wanna
put some pants on there.
You wanna talk about it,
or are you just gonna act weird?
- There's nothing to talk about.
- OK.
I mean, you show up here,
which I didn't even ask you to do, so...
Yeah. To help.
Is that what you call it?
Morgan.
Elliot?
- That's your name, right?
- Yeah.
Hi. Quinn. Metro Homicide.
Hey.
You have kids, I take it.
Yeah. They're with their mother.
We're divorced.
Plus, it just seemed better for them
to get away after what happened next door.
Um... you know, I already talked to the FBI.
I told them I didn't see anything.
What did you need?
How well did you know Rita?
I don't know, you know.
We were neighbours.
Yeah. I just couldn't help but notice
how torn up you were
about her the other night.
She was a friend, you know?
It was upsetting.
A friend.
I, uh, was told she might
have been more.
Christ. All right, look,
I don't know what you've heard,
but just so you understand
the actual facts,
all Rita and I ever did
was kiss... once.
That was it. It was nothing.
Her husband was never around.
Anyway, Dexter found out about
the indiscretion and, uh...
came over and punched me out.
Huh.
- Dexter.
- Shhh.
He's sleeping.
Brought some dresses
for you to look at.
Where are Astor and Cody?
At a hotel with their grandparents.
How'd it go talking with them?
Astor's upset.
They got me a hat.
She'll be OK.
I don't see how.
Her mother's dead because of me.
No, she's not.
She's dead because of Trinity.
I know you keep blaming yourself,
but you can't.
There's nothing you could
have done differently.
I could have killed Arthur Mitchell
the first chance I got.
You loved Rita.
You never would have let
anything hurt her.
She was lucky to have you.
She told me that all the time.
How lucky she felt
to have found you.
I was wondering what you were doing,
sitting here by yourself for so long.
Now I see.
I paid her to say that.
You did?
No, I was... just kidding.
Me too.
So what does a blood spatter analyst
do anyway?
Excuse me.
Is this yours?
What's the deal here?
I have to go.
Is everything OK?
It's a stomach bug.
It's going around the station.
I'm really sorry.
It was nice meeting you.
Lucky to have me.
I wouldn't say so.
She trusted me,
and now she's dead.
Like your sister says, I'm toxic.
You'd all be better off without me.
Delete the past. Leave nothing behind.
You're up early.
What are you doing over there
that's so important?
Getting rid of every trace of me.
- Nothing.
- Dexter...
Look, I know this is tough to talk about,
but the funeral's tomorrow,
and there's still a lot of stuff
you have to do.
Like sign the coroner's release.
I need to grab my tools.
And go over the guest list
one more time.
And torch the container.
And the eulogy, Dexter.
I can't do that for you.
That really has to come from you.
I need to top off my boat.
I'm low on fuel.
Yeah.
And the FBI interview,
or the debriefing or whatever they're
calling it - that's really important.
They're total dicks
for wanting to do it today,
but maybe you're better off just
going in there and getting it over with.
You sure you don't want me
to come with you?
No. I'm fine.
All right. I'm off.
I've been thinking about Harrison.
How he needs his mother.
Someone decent in his life.
You've done everything for me.
Not just now. My whole life.
But...
I need to ask you
this one more favour.
That that person be you.
That you...
love him...
as if he were your own.
He is my own.
And he has me in his life.
Of course he does.
But more importantly, he has you.
You're decent and good.
I'm not.
You are.
What's her mood?
How would I know?
I don't know, there's this rumour floating
around the two of you are married.
Look, I just need to talk to her
about something.
I was wondering
if this is a good time.
Just remember...
she's the boss.
All right.
No. No further comment.
"Serial killer murders cop's wife."
The press won't let up.
They want all the gory details.
- So what do you tell them?
- Same thing I told you.
It's not our case.
So, what can I do for you?
There's, uh, something
I think you should know,
having to do with Rita.
OK.
And Elliot,
the next-door neighbour.
I was at the house with Debra...
...Detective Morgan,
cleaning up.
And this Elliot and I
struck up conversation.
Turns out he and Rita had like a...
mini-fling.
What's that mean exactly?
Well, nothing really happened.
But apparently,
Dexter found out about it.
Why are you telling me this?
What are you implying?
I'm not implying anything.
And what are you doing
interviewing witnesses?
I wasn't interviewing. I was there...
What, cleaning? Please.
Look, if this were anyone but Dexter,
we'd at least be thinking
like detectives.
Which means what?
What do you always say?
When the wife is dead,
90% of the time the husband did it.
LaGuerta.
Um... Hang on for a second.
I need to take this.
We'll finish later.
OK. Can you repeat that?
Yeah.
I just got a call from the FBI
about your brother's interview.
Don't tell me. What'd he say?
Nothing. He didn't show.
So now they're asking
for his personnel files.
God damn it.
I knew I should have gone with him.
Morgan?
I so did not fucking need this.
Yeah, you and me both.
I'm headed home now. I'll figure out what
happened, and I'll get him down there.
OK.
Dexter?
Who the fuck are you?
Excuse me?
10-A. Downstairs?
You're the sister, right?
- Yeah, I live here.
- Well, I'll be leaving, then.
He said you would know what to do.
He said what? Don't go.
Wait.
Dexter Morgan.
Please leave a message at the tone.
Guess who I just met.
The fucking cat lady from downstairs.
She was feeding ice cream to your son.
So, I don't know
where the fuck you are
or why you think you can
fucking run away from the FBI,
but you better get back here...
Fuck! Dexter, where are you?
Hope you don't mind
I chose that dress.
You were wearing it when...
we first met.
So I thought since I won't be
at the funeral,
since I don't deserve to be...
Kids'll be fine with Deb.
Way better off without me.
I think we agree about that.
I was never really
honest with you.
I'm a serial killer. That's what I am.
I know I led you to believe
I'm a human being, but I'm not.
That's a lie.
There are only a few things you really need
once you decide to moνe on,
what you'll require
wherever you land.
A fine suit of clothing...
the tools of your trade...
and some token of your past,
a reminder of who you really are.
Everything else...
you just don't need.
So, where are you, Harry?
Speak now,
or forever hold your peace.
I've disappeared so many people.
My turn now...
to disappear myself.
Fucking FBI.
Damn it, Dexter, don't do this.
The sea breeze
has always brought me clarity.
It's hard to get enough oxygen on land.
It's hard to... breathe.
Oh.
Hey, you.
Hey... you.
It's Rita.
Yeah, I know.
I was just checking in.
Wanted to see if you were
feeling better.
Much better.
Glad to hear that.
The way you left
the restaurant so quickly,
I don't know, I felt maybe I...
said something to offend you.
No, you were fine.
Uh, very understanding.
I wasn't completely honest with you.
Um...
You didn't really get stuck in traffic?
I have two kids. Astor and Cody.
They're nine and seven.
I like kids.
You do?
Yeah, they're fun.
Besides, Deb already told me.
And my ex-husband and our... problems?
Did she tell you?
Yeah.
So, you know all about me.
I'd like to know more.
So...
So, maybe we should
get together again sometime.
I would like that. A lot.
A lot.
I know I should hang up right now,
but I just need to say it.
I don't know why exactly, but...
you make me feel good.
Like things could be different.
So do you.
Make me feel that way...
too, I mean.
Glad I called.
I don't know, I felt...
up in the air
the way things ended.
You know, like we never
said a proper goodbye, so...
Goodbye, Rita Bennett.
Goodbye, Dexter Morgan.
Goodbye.
I'm sorry.
Where's the key
to the fucking bathroom?
Or should I just dump out
on the floor?
What's your problem?
Nothing.
Fucking retard.
Get the fuck outta here!
He's right. I should keep moving.
Hey. Hey, hey.
I said...
what the fuck is your problem?
I've had a bad week.
My wife died, and it was my fault.
Well, I'm real sorry
for your fuckin' loss,
but your dead wife
can suck my dick.
I never meant to hurt her.
That's the first human thing
I've seen you do since she died, Dexter.
I thought you'd left me.
I'm here.
It's OK, son...
to show what you're feeling.
They're not better off without you.
You're not better off
without them.
You need to go back.
Deb says
she's sure he'll be here.
Better be. If we don't get going soon,
we'll be burying Rita by candlelight.
So you're not talking to me now?
Is that it?
I have been trying to talk to you.
You're right. You have.
I just need you to understand...
So, tell me.
I could have fought
for this case, but...
part of me didn't want to.
Rita... died.
She died, and it scared me.
We'd been married, what, ten hours?
Dexter was the witness
at our ceremony.
For all I know, he was there
with us while she was...
- being...
- I know.
Well, I didn't want
to be reminded of that.
I didn't want to investigate.
I just wanted...
I just wanted it to be our wedding day.
I don't like it, Angel.
I don't like the way this makes me feel.
I don't know what to do with any of it.
Maria.
What?
No one does.
What's more important
than his own wife's funeral?
People are getting restless.
Thank you for reporting in
with the obvious, Quinn.
Like I'm such a moron
that it's lost on me.
You ever given a eulogy?
No.
Well, I can't do it.
And those agents, those vultures,
are just waiting for him.
Look, there's something
you should probably know.
What?
It's not exactly
an easy thing to say.
The next-door neighbour Elliot,
I spoke to him the other day.
- What the fuck?
- I know I shouldn't have...
She had a big heart.
Big enough for both of us.
Had to be.
I wasn't even human...
when we first met.
I never expected that to change.
She reached out and found something
I didn't even know was there.
She never hurt anybody.
She was innocent.
And she died a brutal death and...
and I can't...
fix it.
But I know I have to try...
here in Miami with the people
who knew her
and who...
who cared about her.
And who loved her.
Like I did.