Previously on Dexter...
Emily Birch?
Is that her? The one whose blood
Jordan wears round his neck?
Yeah.
It was almost 20 years ago.
He was Eugene Greer.
That's Jordan Chase?
No one could ever take your place.
You know that.
You know, I'm glad you didn't touch
any of them.
Really? Why is that?
Because this DNA test will clear you
and leave you all to me and to her.
The men who hurt you,
they made DVDs of everything they did.
Did everyone watch it?
I managed to get it
out of evidence in time.
You think you can just pay me off
like I'm the corner whore?
Stay the fuck away from Deb!
I trusted you.
And while you were fucking me
you were spreading shit about my brother
behind my back.
Fuck you.
- Who'd you say you were?
- A friend of Joey.
I got to pick up a few things
for a stake-out.
It's for Detective Quinn.
You see his name there.
A strange call came into my office
from an Alex Tilden.
Alex Tilden, 3040.
Here it is.
Look at this. Looks like a partial footprint.
What if the vigilante
is one of their victims?
It's all become so... natural.
- You OK?
- Yes.
But with Lumen,
I'm someone different.
In her eyes,
I'm not a monster at all.
- Detectives.
- We appreciate you fitting us in.
We wanted to thank you for your phone call
regarding Alex Tilden.
- It was really helpful.
- That's good to hear.
We followed up immediately.
We went to his house, but...
- it looked like we'd just missed him.
- That's unfortunate.
Yeah, it is, because he seems to have
disappeared off the face of the earth.
- I see.
- Yeah, like Cole Harmon.
- And Boyd Fowler.
- Yeah, him too.
Now, I keep asking myself,
what's the connection?
What do these three people
have in common?
You. You're what they have
in common. You.
Oh, here it comes.
Why don't you just save us a lot of time
and tell us what that connection is?
It's ridiculous that you think
I have anything to do with this.
I gave you my DNA!
What were the results?
Go on, remind me.
Your DNA wasn't found
on any of the barrel girls.
That's correct,
so all this right here
is a colossal waste
of my time and yours.
Well, I've got nothing but time.
So you can keep fooling everybody
in your little seminars, but I'm onto you.
You're obsessed with me.
That's what this is about.
It happens. You achieve a bit of fame
and people latch on to you
in various twisted ways.
I'd be careful, if I were you.
It's typically seen
in someone who's trying to avoid
facing the dismal nature
of her own small life.
- I think you slipped up.
- It's not at all healthy.
- And I think a barrel girl got away.
- It's something I can help you with.
And now she's hunting down
the people that took her.
And people all around you
are dropping like flies.
You could be next.
Seriously, I'll be fine.
It's you I'm concerned about.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Jordan Chase.
We know exactly where he is.
Yeah, but there's no way
to get to him.
The entire top floor is guarded.
Elevators?
Monitored.
Stairs?
- Locked from the inside.
- Yeah.
But you know how to pick locks.
Not without setting off the fire alarm.
OK.
So we have to figure out a way
to get him to come out.
How?
He has everything he needs up there.
Not everything.
Me. He wants me.
No.
There's got to be a way
to use me as bait.
- It worked with Cole.
- I'm not gonna use you as bait.
- It's too dangerous.
- You know I can do this.
Yeah, I do.
I saw you kill Alex Tilden.
But we have to be extra careful.
Jordan has more than
just our eyes on him.
- The police.
- My sister.
I'm so sorry that I put you in this position,
having to lie to her like that.
I don't like it,
but it's not the first time.
She's never suspected anything?
I don't know. Maybe Deb has a blind spot
when it comes to me.
Sometimes I feel like I'm taking advantage
of her, but it's for the best.
She's not like us.
"Us."
Oh.
There's a camera in the room.
The baby monitor
is picking up the signal.
Somebody's watching us.
Jordan has to be behind this...
and close by.
Wireless cameras
have a limited range,
their signal routed
to a recording unit
in a vacant apartment,
a motor home...
a van.
It could be anywhere.
Jordan Chase is up to
his ball sack in this. I fuckin' know it.
Just means we keep digging.
You coming in?
I got to grab something from my car.
I'll be right up.
- Hey.
- What are you doing here?
- My union appeal's been denied.
I am now officially terminated.
So how's your day?
- I'm sorry to hear that.
- I don't want your pity.
Good. Then...
Thirty years of putting bad guys away,
this is what them cocksuckers
upstairs do to me.
Take my pension,
wipe their ass with it
and just flush it right on down the shitter.
Look, I got to get inside.
- I need your help on a bust.
- Bust? What are you talking about?
Something big. Something big enough
to make them stand up and take notice.
Something big enough to make them
give me my job back on the police force.
- Your boy Dexter...
- What the fuck? What are you doing?
Didn't you hear me, Quinn?
I'm not a cop any more.
Now, I need a cop to make this bust.
No. Forget it.
You little fucking wimp.
You're up to your ass in alligators
with this thing, whether you like it or not.
So you're gonna make this bust
and I'm gonna call you,
you'd best come running.
- What are you in the mood for?
- I'm thinking seafood.
It's a perfect night to grill.
I'll go check what's in the fridge.
Harrison's baby monitor made it easy
to pinpoint where this was hidden,
but the bigger problem remains.
What exactly has Jordan heard
and where are those recordings?
On second thought,
let's go out to eat.
It's not Jordan. It's worse.
It's someone from my own station.
What? Why would somebody from the
police department bug your apartment?
I don't know. There's a serial number
on the camera.
I'll go in tomorrow and find out
who checked it out.
I don't understand.
This could have something
to do with my sister's theory.
What are you talking about?
She has this theory about
vigilantes hunting down the rapists.
So you think she planted cameras?
No, it's not her. I'd know.
It could be anyone.
But how could they be onto us?
- We've been so careful.
- I don't know yet.
The one good thing is that no one
has seen those recordings yet.
How do you know?
Because we haven't been arrested.
Jordan is gonna get away with everything
and we're gonna be arrested?
We don't know that.
Look, for now we just pretend
like everything's OK.
If we have something to talk about,
we talk about it out here where it's safe.
But we were so close.
- It can't end this way.
- It's not going to.
I checked with the apartment manager,
then the neighbours.
That motor home is gone.
It's got to be one of these vans.
You said there were four vans last night.
It's down to three now.
I'll keep checking back.
- Sonya, everything all right?
- Everything is great.
Astor and Cody
are spoiling Harrison silly.
Good.
He's taking a little nap now,
so I was just making a list for Sunday,
and I wondered, do you have
any special requests?
- Sunday?
- Harrison's birthday party.
Of course! Right.
Harrison's birthday.
Astor and Cody
can't wait to see you.
I'm looking forward to seeing them too.
But... hold on a second.
It's not safe
to bring everyone here.
- We can go to them.
- You're coming?
I just invited myself.
Sonya, we're gonna have
the party in Orlando.
Oh. OK.
It's just easier than
making everyone drive down here.
Perfect.
Come on, I got to get to work.
Keep an eye on these vans
and call me if you see anything.
No torches, no pitchforks,
no one looking at me
any differently.
Dex, I need you.
In a minute.
I have something I need to do.
Find out who planted
those cameras.
We're all waiting on you.
That doesn't sound good.
So, as I was saying, everything keeps
leading back to Jordan Chase.
Why would he be running
a rape club with these putos?
I don't know.
But I'm pretty fuckin' sure he is.
Where are we on the banker,
Alex Tilden?
- He's gone. He disappeared.
- We got his DNA from a toothbrush.
Ties him to the barrel girls, like the others,
but no connection to Jordan
that we can find.
- Then I suggest you find that connection.
- I'm on it.
- And the dentist, Mendell?
- He's the odd man out.
He doesn't seem to have any connection
to any of the other guys.
Again, let's find that connection.
- Morgan, Quinn.
- We got it.
Phone the neighbours.
Wake the kids. Kick the dog.
Remember that muddy female boot print
outside Tilden's house?
Yeah, we found it.
Well, my brothers in blue, it...
has a twin.
Found it outside
the vacant house next door.
Let me see that.
Naturally, I went inside.
The dining room was spotless, and I mean
recently cleaned kind of spotless,
unlike the rest of the house.
My schnoz also detected
the smell of bleach.
One more day,
and the smell would have dissipated.
My guess, the vigilante brought
your missing banker over
and offed him right there
in the dining room.
Excuse me,
did I hear the word "vigilante"?
It was a theory
I was keeping to myself, but...
It's out there, but we may have
a vigilante on our hands.
I sent Masuka over to Tilden's
to see if he could comb for any evidence
that a homicide had taken place.
Keep going.
Please don't.
There are 13 DVDs
and only 12 victims.
So I'm thinking that
one of the barrel girls escaped
and now she's after the men
that abducted her.
And she is hunting them
and she is killing them.
How is that even possible?
The barrel girls are all slight of build.
- Alex Tilden was, what, 175 pounds?
- Minimum.
Maybe she had help.
- Like who?
- I don't know.
A...
A man. Someone she trusts.
Someone who cares about her.
A father, brother,
husband, boyfriend.
So now it's vigilantes in love.
Yeah, like Romeo and Juliet...
except they didn't kill anyone.
No, more like, uh, Bonnie and... Clyde.
Great.
They ended up dead
in a bullet-riddled car.
We all have our assignments.
Let's go.
Closer to ten minutes.
She likes a cup of coffee
with her smoke.
But that's more than enough time
to see that...
Detective Joseph Quinn
checked out the cameras.
Three cameras, to be exact,
two microphones, a recorder.
Only three days ago.
Maybe no one's seen
the footage yet.
Case number...
It's from 1982, when Quinn was
in grade school eating paste.
It's a fake.
No court orders authorised for my address.
This is off the books.
Quinn's doing this on his own.
Lumen. Plans for lunch?
Start with the hard drive.
Yeah, any storage devices,
video files, flash drives.
Wow, this thing is ancient.
Who is this guy?
Quinn. My sister's partner.
Oh, wow.
Are they... close?
They used to be.
You got anything?
Not much in the way of video files.
Anything of us?
No.
Just a cat that hiccups and farts
at the same time.
Cute.
Check the bedroom.
You take the closet.
I'll check the drawers.
Oh, shit.
What is it?
- Us.
- The marina.
That's the night we dumped Cole.
He's been watching us for weeks.
He knows everything.
Wait. You're not gonna
take them with you?
Tip him off that we found them?
No, he'll just print more.
We have to find the digital source.
Right. Find the recording equipment.
We're not open any more.
- Mrs Mendell? Laura Mendell?
- Yes?
I'm Detective Morgan.
This is Detective Quinn.
We'd like to ask you a couple of questions
about your husband.
Please, OK?
Just no more questions.
We've been through this, OK?
I don't know anything.
- Of course, I should have.
- Why is that?
I was very naive,
but now it all makes sense.
Those week-long fishing trips
he used to take.
- He'd go without you?
- Of course without me.
It was just him and his buddies.
He called it his "man time",
but of course that has
a whole other meaning now.
Did he ever give you names
of the men on those trips?
No. I never met any of them.
He kept me completely in the dark
about his whole closeted gay life.
I mean, why didn't he just tell me?
Actually, Mrs Mendell, we have information
which leads us to believe
your husband wasn't in fact gay.
The crime scene may have been altered
to give that impression.
But he was linked to a series of rapes.
And murders.
My God.
Who is this man I married?
I'm sorry to bring you that news.
But do any of these names
sound familiar?
- Boyd Fowler. Cole Harmon.
- No, I don't know them.
Alex Tilden.
Jordan Chase.
- Jordan Chase?
- Yes.
Well, that's him, right there.
"Best two-man sailing team,
Dan Mendell and Eugene Greer"?
Jordan Chase is Eugene Greer...
or he used to be.
Dan knew him when they were kids.
It was a really big deal to him.
That's our connection.
Why do you think the wife never had a clue
about what was up with her husband?
This barrel girl stuff has gone on
the entire time they were married.
He was probably a really good liar.
Men sometimes have that ability.
It was his fault, not hers.
How do you want
to go at this Eugene Greer thing?
Just pull up everything we can.
School records, juvie records.
I fuckin' knew Chase was full of shit.
Who creates a new identity
for themselves?
A dirt bag who has something to hide.
I've got it.
Jordan Chase lied
about knowing Alex Tilden.
In the past ten years,
Tilden oversaw six properties
purchased by Chase's corporation.
Dan the Dentist also knew him.
And Jordan Chase is an alias.
That whole bullshit persona
that he built for himself is a lie.
His real name's Eugene Greer.
Mendell and Chase were friends as kids.
So, wait. That ties Jordan directly
to each of the barrel girls' rapists.
Yeah, but still all circumstantial.
Not enough to bring him in.
Yeah, but it's enough to bring
his lying ass in for questioning.
We've got to keep pushing at him,
scare him a little bit
till he starts making some mistakes.
Deb's closing in on Chase.
Quinn's closing in on me.
Time's running out for both of us.
Hey, any good news?
Uh, yeah, we've connected Jordan Chase
to all of the rapists,
so I'm about to nail
this fuck to the wall.
Good.
What? What's up? I'm kind of busy.
Just wondering if you want to go with me
to Orlando on Sunday
for Harrison's birthday.
Oh. Wha...
- I do, but...
- You have other plans with Quinn?
What? No, it... It's with work.
It's the case.
Besides, Quinn's the last person
that you'd want to have there.
- Oh?
- Trust me.
- So it's over?
- Yes.
No. Fuck, I don't know.
It's complicated.
You don't have to tell me.
- He lied to me about something.
- Must have been something big.
He lied to me about you.
About me? What do you mean?
Quinn had this...
idiot notion that you were somehow
connected to Rita's death.
- That's...
- It's crazy, I know.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- Because...
Because you've been through enough.
And I just found out.
When he finally told me
I felt so betrayed because...
...as much as I don't want to admit it,
I really care about him.
"Care", present tense?
It's complicated, remember?
I thought I knew him,
and he kept telling me he loved me.
But what he did...
I mean, I can't have somebody like that.
You don't lie to somebody that
you're close to. You have their back.
I need someone I can trust 100 per cent.
Like this.
- A boot print?
- The vigilante.
She has someone in her life,
a guy who's helping her,
someone that would do
anything and everything for her.
How do you know that?
Honestly, I don't know,
but... what they're doing takes devotion.
To kill someone together,
that's some pretty serious shit.
Is that what Lumen and I have,
serious shit?
He's risking his life.
He's putting everything on the line
to make what happened to her right.
As crazy as that sounds, what...
what word would you use
to describe that but "love"?
It's pretty fucked up, isn't it?
Yeah, pretty fucked up.
Kind of beautiful too.
Just got this in.
It's handmade. It's very chic.
Um...
- It's not quite me.
- Perhaps one of the rings.
How about... that?
It's nice.
Small enough to carry,
locking pin, stainless-steel blade.
- How does it feel?
- Good.
We'll take it.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
It's just an hour or so
till Quinn gets off work.
If he decides to check his recording
equipment tonight I should be there.
What is Quinn after?
What does he want with us?
He doesn't want us. He wants me.
He was coming after me
before we even met.
I didn't mean for you
to get caught up in this.
You should leave.
You tried that once before, remember?
You tried to ship me away.
That was different.
I don't want you to leave for good.
Just till I deal with this.
Deal with it how?
I don't know.
Whatever needs to be done.
I appreciate the offer,
but... I'm not going anywhere.
- Lumen, it's getting dangerous.
- Getting dangerous?
I'm not walking away.
We're a team.
We have serious shit.
What does that mean?
It's just something Deb said about us.
You told her about... us?
No, she was talking
about the vigilantes.
She was talking about us without
knowing she was talking about us.
Maybe we should both take off.
Get on a cruise ship.
Hop a freighter.
Steal a tugboat.
You said that you didn't
want me to leave.
Does that mean that you want me to stay?
I do.
We should go.
OK, so Eugene Greer grew up
in some redneck town near Tallahassee.
He had a single mom,
now dead, no siblings,
pretty nondescript childhood.
Moved to Miami when he was 18,
dropped about 100 pounds,
changed his name to Jordan Chase,
pretty much reinvented himself.
Take a look at these
before-and-after photos.
Ooh.
Like a different person.
I think he might have had
some plastic surgery along the way.
Look at this.
When they'd be off at the same time,
each of the barrel girls disappeared.
- Fuck, they did this for years.
- Mm-hm.
I gotta take this.
I'm, uh, having a really tough time here.
Doing what?
This. Being with you.
Yeah, well, you should have
thought of that before.
I'm sorry. I fucked up, I know.
I do dumb things.
I'm a dumb guy.
But the one thing I did right
was to get you to almost like me...
- because I really love you.
- Don't, Quinn.
No, I mean it.
There aren't many women like you.
I know that.
You're more like...
- a guy.
- A guy?
You don't play games
where I have to figure out
what it is you're really thinking.
You just say it,
usually with
a lot of really filthy words
that I've never heard before.
You're the first woman
who's ever called me on my bullshit
and made me take
a hard look at myself.
It's made me a better person, I think.
I just don't want to lose you, that's all.
Bad news.
Not only has Jordan declined our request
for another interview,
but he just booked a multi-city
speaking deal in Europe.
Sounds like he's on the run.
No fucking way.
As of tomorrow he is untouchable,
unless we can find a way
to keep him here.
But, like we keep saying,
we still don't have enough to arrest him.
No, but, uh... we can ground him
as a material witness.
We just have to get a court order.
- Should we go to LaGuerta?
- No.
She shoots me down every time.
She won't help. I can get it myself.
The only van that remains after 24 hours
just happens to be a rental.
Judging by the amount of dust,
it's been sitting there close to a week.
And here comes Quinn, checking in
before he heads to the station.
I never wanted it to come to this.
Agh!
Hello.
- Lumen, it's me, Emily.
- What's wrong?
I got a call from Jordan Chase.
He knows I talked to you.
What? How?
I don't know. You tell me.
- I didn't talk to him.
- What is going on?
I'm scared. He scared me.
Emily, I have no idea what's going on.
I'm going to the police.
- I'll tell them everything.
- No, no, don't do that.
Why? They'll protect me.
Emily, it'll just make things worse.
We'll protect you.
How? Jordan is too powerful.
- He has people.
- Emily...
You know what he did to us.
Just stay in your house. Wait for us.
We'll be there as soon as we can.
Please, just tell me
that you'll wait for us.
OK.
I'll wait, but hurry.
Please hurry.
Very nice.
You're quite the actress.
Dexter Morgan.
Please leave
a message at the tone.
Dexter, where are you? Emily called.
Jordan knows she talked to us.
We have to go see her.
I hope you got voicemail.
- You're Quinn's friend.
- That would be me.
FYI, Stan Liddy is my name.
- What are you doing?
- I just need you to relax.
I'm taking us to a little place to
have a little private chat, that's all.
Why? Why are you doing this?
Because our mutual friend Joey Quinn
hired me to look into you
and I guess you know
I found out some things.
So I just need you
to lie there and relax.
I don't want to zap you again,
but I will if I have to.
- What?
- Come on, now, Joey.
Is that any way to talk
to your new best friend?
- I told you, I don't want...
- Shut up and listen up.
You get your ass in your car
and you drive on down to the fuel docks
at Bayfront Park.
That big bust I want you to make,
I need you to come and make it now.
I don't know what you think you're doing,
but you got to stop it with this shit.
Oh, horseshit. Nobody's stopping nothing.
- You're the one who hired me.
- And then I fired you.
Listen, boy. This is going down
with or without you.
Now, you don't get down here
faster than a fuckin' jack rabbit,
I'm calling in another cop and then there's
no telling how this is gonna spin out.
- Jesus, Liddy...
- Jesus ain't got nothing to do with it.
Old fuel docks, Bayfront Park, now.
Fuck.
Your buddy Quinn is on his way.
Didn't sound like he wants to come.
Well, you're a real popular fella.
Sonya. Who's Sonya?
- My nanny.
- Nanny.
Well, Sonya wants to know
if you want a magician for the party.
Of course you do.
"Yes, do magician."
Well, now,
there's something I want to show you.
Looky here at this.
Ain't that neat?
And that's just a tiny bit
of what I recorded.
But I only got one problem here.
I didn't have no search warrant
and these people are sticklers for rules,
which is why... you're gonna give me
a full confession.
- Where's Dexter?
- He's not here.
No, I need you both.
You said you would protect me.
Emily, it's OK. Calm down.
You have to call him.
Make him come. Now.
OK.
OK, maybe I should just go get him.
Maybe not.
I ain't stupid. You're thinking, "I got
no reason to make a full confession."
So I'm gonna give you a reason.
Lumen walks free.
Why should I trust you?
Cos I don't give a shit about her,
and I don't give a shit about you either.
I just want my goddamn job
on the police force back.
I bring in somebody like you,
I get my picture in the news,
everybody thinks I'm a goddamn hero,
everybody loves me,
and they have to hire me back.
So I don't need your girl.
What do you say?
Shit!
Liddy!
Ah!
Go away, Quinn.
Don't make this any worse.
Liddy, where the fuck are you?
Leave a message.
Liddy, it's Quinn. You're really starting
to fucking piss me off.
Dexter, where are you?
Emily called. Jordan knows
she talked to us. We have to go see her.
I don't have time to deal with you.
- Please leave a message.
- I'm on my way.
Morgan.
My office.
I got a call earlier from the judge
you petitioned for your court order.
- When's it coming?
- It's not.
What?
Your request to detain Jordan Chase
as a material witness was denied.
That fuck is scheduled
to fly out of here one-way today.
- This was our shot.
- I understand why you're upset,
but what I don't understand is
why you didn't come to me.
- You're kidding.
- I'm asking.
You are the last person I think of
when I need support.
Detective, you've been
on the force long enough
to know that situations
are rarely black and white.
Politics come into play.
That doesn't mean
that I signed up to be used.
We all get used, and in this instance
you should have used me.
You made it very clear that you don't
support my vigilante theory.
And I'm still not sure
that there's anything to it,
but I have always trusted
your instincts as a cop.
You know, at one point
I actually thought we were friends.
Well, Detect...
Debra, I'm sorry
if I betrayed that friendship.
OK.
- Wait.
- What? What?
- What is it?
- Here.
- What is this?
- It's your court order.
From a different judge
who owed me a favour.
Fuck me.
Now I'm the asshole, right?
You better get going
if you want to catch Jordan.
Right.
Lumen?
What could he be doing
that is so important
that he would let you
come here by yourself?
- I don't know.
- Yes, you keep saying that.
You're surprisingly short of answers.
Maybe you should let me call him.
Yes, brilliant, because you certainly
wouldn't tip him off in any way.
- I could try calling him.
- Quiet, please.
Are you mad at me?
I did exactly what you told me to do.
Please, shut up.
- I'm just trying...
- Shut up!
- It's not my fault.
- Of course it's your fault!
Aah!
I find this profoundly distasteful.
I've never had to do anything before!
Now I've no choice.
I can't leave any witnesses.
No, you said you wouldn't kill her.
Lumen.
Lumen?
Is this the only kind of love
I'll eνer find?
The kind that ends in blood?
- Can I help you?
- I'm looking for Jordan Chase.
I have a court order that prevents
him from leaving Miami.
Well, I guess I can go home, then.
- Is he on the plane?
- No. I have no idea where he is.
We were scheduled to fly out over
an hour ago and he never showed up.
Emily was killed with two blows.
Lumen was here.
Multiple footprints in the blood,
a scuffle.
More blood, not from Emily,
leading out.
She was running.
She's putting up a fight.
Lumen.