He is not sick.
Dr. Riley is throwing up.
he obviously can't lecture.
You witnessed the spew, or
you just have his word for it?
I think I'm coming down
with a little bit of the clap.
I may have to go home for a few days.
Dr. Riley doesn't have
a history of lying to me.
You said this is the fifth time
he's missed a class this year!
Either he's dying or he's lying.
I'll give you two hours off clinic duty.
Fine, I'll have Cameron do it.
She loves inspiring the inspired.
You'll do it.
Why is it always me?
Because the world hates you.
Or because it's a class on diagnostics.
Pick whatever reason
feeds your narcissism better.
I'm not doing it.
You're supposed to stop me.
Renegotiate.
And you were supposed
to keep on walking.
Sorry, I guess we both screwed up.
Go on, do it again.
I'll do the lecture for
four hours off clinic.
Two.
I know you'd rather
spend a couple of hours
listening to yourself than
listening to patients.
Class starts in twenty minutes.
Dr. House, there's a patient.
I'm outta here,
take it up with Cuddy.
Gregg.
Hi, Stacy.
How're you doing?
How am I doing?
Well, the last five years have been like...
you ever see those
"Girls Gone Wild" videos?
Your life's been like that, or
your life's been spent watching them?
I have missed you.
Is that why you're here?
I need your help.
Who am I looking at?
My husband.
Who is suffering abdominal pain
and fainting spells.
No sign of tumors, no vasculitis.
Could be indigestion,
or maybe a kidney stone.
A little one, can pack a lot of wallop.
Did you think I wasn't
going to get married?
Not to someone so poorly endowed.
This guy's pancreas is pathetic.
There is no kidney stone,
no indigestion.
Three hospitals, five doctors,
not one of them found anything.
Well, maybe there's
nothing to be found.
Right, you suddenly trust doctors,
love puppies and long walks in the rain.
The walks are out.
I was around you long enough to know
when something's not right.
Mark's had personality changes,
he's acting strange, disconnected...
Interesting.
It means there's either a neurological
component or he's having an affair.
No affair, no nothing!
He's sick!
I know you're not too busy.
you avoid work like the plague.
Unless it actually is the plague.
I'm asking you a favor.
I'm not too busy,
but I'm not sure I want him to live.
It's good seeing you again.
Three guys walk into a clinic.
Their legs hurt.
What's wrong with them?
I'm not going to like you, am I?
Most likely cause of leg
pain is muscle strain.
Apply heat and rest affected areas.
Statistically, you're right. Very good.
My experience: Over
half of leg pain is
musculoskeletal, generally
from excessive exercise.
Twelve percent is varicose veins
brought on by pregnancy,
and most of the rest is
the result of vehicular accidents.
I said three people. That's six legs.
So, you've got three hurt jogging,
two in collisions, and one
of the legs is pregnant.
But what were they doing
when pain presented?
I have no idea.
You didn't ask?
You didn't take a history?
Of course, but all that told us was
what they said happened.
Person A, farmer,
says he was fixing a fence.
Tightness of the ankle,
loss of muscle control.
Person B, volleyball practice.
Coach figured it was a pulled muscle.
And C, we've got Carmen Electra. Golfing.
Yes!
Whoa, you treated the Baywatch chick?
The Baywatch thespian.
And no, I've gotta disguise
the identity of each of the patients
and I got tired of using
the middle-aged man.
Carmen seemed like
a pleasant alternative.
Also, she's apparently quite the golfer.
Now, in less than two hours,
one of these three will get
tossed out of the hospital
because they were faking it
to score narcotics,
and one will be very close to death.
Any guesses on which is which?
Okay, I say we start with the farmer.
Did you hike to the fence, and how far?
Yes, it's about half a
mile from my farmhouse.
And where's the pain localized?
It started just above my ankle
and it's radiating up.
So, what should we do first?
Family history?
Indicative of leg pain?
That's a very short list.
Any history of bone cancer, osteogenesis
imperfecta or multiple myeloma?
Could be a blood issue.
We should run a CBC and a D-dimer.
And get an MRI.
MRI or a PET scan?
If the problem's vascular,
he's better off...
Bzzt! Sorry, thanks for playing.
Patient's dead. You killed him.
We had no time to run any tests.
there was nothing we could do!
You had time to look at the leg.
I thought we were starting
with the farmer's case first.
We are.
But if we're going to look at a leg...
I need you to take off your pants.
Puncture.
Snakebite.
That would be my guess.
Farmer didn't know
he had been bit by a snake?
That's what he said.
Sudden shooting pain,
tall grass, never saw a thing.
What kind of snake?
You want me to tell you
what kind of snake it
was from the shape of
the hole in the leg?
How are we supposed to know
what kind of antivenin
to use if we don't know
what kind of snake it is?
Oh, there are people
to find those things out.
Shouldn't we wait for
the Humane Society or something?
The guy might only
have a couple of hours.
And while we wait for
the Humane Society to show up,
what say we check up
on the volleyball player?
You have tendonitis.
How old is this person?
I mean, it's not really a 40-year-old man
on a girls' volleyball team, right?
It's a leg. A leg is a leg is a leg.
Well, I was just worried that...
Would you worry about her more
if she was younger?
Obviously we should care about
our patients no matter what age...
Yeah, right. I saw the way
you were looking at Carmen.
She's mine, stay away.
Would you operate on your mother?
Of course not. I'd be too nervous.
couldn't be objective.
Then why are you so anxious to treat
every patient like they're family?
The actual patient is 16.
Here's what happens
when doctors care to much.
I need to know everything about you.
I went back three generations:
No history of cancer, Parkinson's,
or any other degenerative condition.
But there's this boy at school, and
he's on the boys' volleyball team,
and they made out at a party,
and now he won't call her back,
and this friend of hers at school said
this boy didn't like her and never did.
You got all this from
an examination of the knee?
I think she's depressed.
- She doesn't have tendoni?
- She has tendonitis.
She's depressed about having tendonitis.
She's depressed for
the same reason she has tendonitis.
Not the boy.
No, the boy's a jerk, she knows that,
and yet she's depressed.
I found a nodule.
Ah. Problems with the thyroid
gland causes depressed
mental state, can cause
inflammation of the tendons.
I'll run the tests.
So, because she took
such an extreme interest,
she found out
the person had a thyroid condition.
No, because she took such an interest
she discovered a tiny nodule.
Which, in reality, signified nothing,
but gave us no choice
but to put a person with tendonitis
through an expensive and painful test.
Here's how a well-adjusted
doctor handles a case.
Can I put my pants back on now?
I'd rather you didn't.
Which Carmen Electra is this?
First one. The golfer.
Then why isn't she wearing pants?
You have decreased reflexes
in your patellar tendon. Anyone?
Slipped disc?
Could be. How bad does it hurt?
It hurts really, really bad.
Yeah?
It doesn't seem real.
Is she the one faking?
Oh, for God's sake.
She's here to play out my fantasy,
not because she's Meryl Streep.
Fine.
What the hell is wrong with me?
Do something!
Too much pain
to be a slipped disc.
Could be herniated and
impinging the nerve root.
Or it could be
referred pain from his groin.
Sir, are you getting pain
anywhere else?
He's curling. It's not the back.
- Sir, where are you getting pain?
- Help me!
He's not going to tell us anything
if we don't get him out of pain.
Give him 50mg of Demerol.
We have no history,
he could be allergic.
What do I do?
We can't diagnose him
while he screams.
Better than killing him
with pain killers, then...
Apparently, he's not allergic.
Thank you, I feel a lot better now.
We screwed up.
No, you did exactly
what his attending did.
And that was the proper way
to handle the case?
Yeah.
The guy used him as a dealer!
You're going to see a lot of
drug-seeking behavior in your practice,
and there's a reason: It works.
Meanwhile, back on the farm...
Yeah, timber rattlesnake.
Four vials of the CroFab antivenin.
Hey, how you doing?
All right.
Thank you.
This will start making you
feel better really fast.
He's having an allergic reaction, bag.
Paddles and epi.
- But his heart's fine.
- It's not going to stay that way.
Paddles!
What say we take five?
Get some coffee, go pee.
You didn't think
she was going to get married?
She asked me the same question.
And... what?
You're not gonna treat him?
There's probably nothing wrong with him.
Oh, sure, that makes sense.
She's just using the old
"sick husband" routine
as an excuse to get
back in touch with you.
You think this is easy for her?
The only reason she'd be anywhere near you
was if she was desperate.
So I should help her
because she hates me.
She doesn't hate you.
She loves you, she just...
can't... stand to be around you.
Dr. House?
It's been almost six minutes.
Found him.
The volleyball player
was responding to the anti-inflammatories
as you'd expect in a case of tendonitis.
What about the snakebite guy?
I don't really care
about the volleyball player.
What if I told you the volleyball player
had a sudden massive stroke?
Really?
No. But that would make
you interested, right?
What if her T4 came back low?
It's not quite as interesting,
but it has the benefit of being true.
You said the thyroid biopsy
was a wasted test.
No, I didn't.
I said she put a person with tendonitis
through an expensive and painful test.
Apparently the patient had
tendonitis and a thyroid condition.
We're going to start you on Thyroxin.
It'll make you feel better
and level your moods.
Thank you.
So, that's it?
You were right the first time.
Snakebite guy's way more interesting.
Gross, actually.
The patient responded to epinephrine
and the allergic reaction was arrested.
Unfortunately, the patient
continues to deteriorate.
Maybe the snake wrangler was
wrong about the type he caught.
He faxed us the venom tests
which confirmed it's a timber rattlesnake.
No, it's not. Notice the volume?
I skimmed over that and the
gender and the coloring
and skipped right to
the name of the snake.
200mg.
Our guy got bit less than four hours ago.
There's no way a snake regenerates
that much venom that quickly.
We're supposed to know
how fast snakes make their venom?
Nope.
Unless you've got a patient bit by one.
Then it might be helpful.
So what do we do now?
He must have been bitten
by a different snake.
We go back and find it.
Or you go online and find there's only three
poisonous snakes common in New Jersey:
The copperhead, the timber
rattler, and the coral.
The copperhead and the timber rattler both
respond to the antivenins we gave the guy.
So we give him the antivenin
for the other one.
Is that a question?
Well, we can't just blindly
give him another antivenin.
Especially after the first
one almost killed him.
You said only three types of poisonous
snakes commonly found in New Jersey.
But what if this is an uncommon one?
Pretty good.
We've gotta find the right snake.
No need. Odds are, by the
time you get back the autopsy
results will tell you what
kind of snake it was.
But you said...
So we do give him
the antivenin for the other one.
Again, was that a question?
I asked what you would do.
It seems unfair for you
to ask me what you would do.
Who gives the guy the other antivenin?
And who goes looking for the snake?
I assume that one choice kills him
and one saves him.
That's usually the way it works
at the leg turning black stage.
So half of us killed him
and half of us saved his life.
Yeah.
But we can't be blamed for...
I'm sure this goes against
everything you've been taught,
but right and wrong do exist.
Just because you don't know
what the right answer is...
maybe there's even no way you
could know what the right answer is...
doesn't make your
answer right or even okay.
It's much simpler than that.
It's just plain wrong.
We gave the guy the antivenin.
What if I'm allergic again?
That's why these people are here.
If you have a reaction, we're
ready to do whatever's necessary
to ensure your airway stays open
and your heart keeps beating.
My wife's on her way in,
can't this wait?
I'm sorry, it can't.
It hurts again.
He came back?
On average, drug addicts are stupid.
I'd call the cops.
Good for you.
A lot of doctors wouldn't
risk their careers on a hunch.
It's not a hunch, I mean,
I know he wants drugs.
I believe drug addicts get sick.
Actually, for some reason they tend to get
sick more often than non-drug addicts.
Luckily, you don't have to play your hunch,
there's a faster way.
Actually, there are several.
My preference is urine testing.
But you already know
he has drugs in his system.
That's not what I'm testing for.
We're going to put this hard, rubber tube
up your urethra and into your bladder.
It might be a little uncomfortable.
Shouldn't I be getting
some kind of anesthetic?
We're concerned about
allergic reactions today.
If the guy can handle a rod in his penis
for half an hour, he's really sick.
Or he's really jonesing.
There's easier ways to get a hold of drugs.
Other hospitals, for example.
The volleyball player is not
responding to treatment.
At least we think it's not working
on account of the fact she's getting worse.
Can you still hear me?
No.
A little.
Not really!
Well, if you can't hear me,
how do you know what I asked?
I'm sorry. What did I do?
I don't know. It really hurts!
I promise to be very careful.
Susan!
Not her real name!
Susan, I barely touched you!
- No, it hurts so much!
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
I have to get this blood.
Just hold on.
Hypersensitivity to touch.
- Her calcium up?
- Lab over 16.
The question is why.
Likely suspects?
- Parathyroid adenoma.
- Kidney problems.
- Vit. D intoxification.
- Hyperthyroid.
- Caused by our treatment?
Whoa whoa whoa.
Can you please slow down?
The adenoma
is most likely. Check her PTH...
phosphorus, and ionized calcium,
and do a technetium sestambi.
Okay, that's enough
about the volleyball player.
What's up with the farmer?
What farmer?
Snakebite guy.
Oh, right, you guys don't know about him.
He doesn't get bitten until three months
after we treat the volleyball player.
Luckily, it's been well established
that time is not a fixed construct.
His condition's not improving.
double the dosage.
Already did.
There's another antivenin,
it's not as effective, but...
Already tried it.
The first stuff,
the stuff he was allergic to...
Gave it to him with high-dose steroids.
Nothing's working.
What does it all mean?
Wrong snake?
We tried every other antivenin we had.
We're too late?
Yep. He's dying.
His wife's here,
finally found a babysitter.
Who wants to let him know?
Actually, I'm kidding.
He's not dying?
Oh, yeah, he's dying, but there's
no wife and kid. Which is great.
Makes the "breaking the
news" thing way easier.
Oh, yeah, one more piece of news.
The drug addict is peeing blood.
How do they teach you
how to tell someone that they're dying?
It's not like teaching architects how to
explain why their building fell down.
Do you roleplay and stuff?
Yeah, one of us gives the bad news
and one of us gets the bad news.
And what do you have to do
to get an A in You're Dying 101?
They grade you on gentleness
and supportiveness?
Is there a scale for
measuring compassion?
This buddy of mine, I gotta give him ten
bucks every time somebody says "Thank you."
Imagine that.
This guy's so good, people thank him
for telling them that they're dying.
Eh, needs brown.
I don't get thanked that often.
You're dying.
In a few hours.
There's nothing we can do
except deal with the pain.
Well, I need to go home.
You're not going home.
Well, my dog?
What will happen to my dog?
Her neck looks clean. No adenoma.
Wait, wait, wait. The guy's dying
and all he cares about is his dog?
Any of you guys go the dog route
in your improv sessions?
It's a basic truth of the human condition
that everybody lies.
The only variable is about what.
The weird thing about
telling someone they're dying is it
tends to focus their priorities.
You find out what matters to them.
What they're willing to die for.
What they're willing to lie for.
Well, you must have a neighbor who can...
The neighbors don't like him.
Then the Humane Society
can take him in and...
No, they won't.
Maybe my aunt...
It wasn't a snakebite, was it?
I said I don't remember being bit.
Sure you do. Just not by a snake.
I assume that Cujo bit
one of your neighbors awhile back.
You tell me that he bit you,
and I gotta report it.
Cujo's got a record,
he gets the chair.
The good news is,
you might just live.
The bad news is,
your dog's gonna die.
The guy risked his life to save this thing?
I'll hold him,
you swab the mouth.
I think I've got a better grip here,
you go for the mouth.
- All right, I'm odds.
- What, are you serious?
- Come on.
- One, two, three!
I don't care if he's scratching
your nads off, you don't let go.
Just do it!
I say we let the guy die.
I got his head, just do it!
Got it.
What would you call that?
That's tea-colored, right?
The guy who we thought
was just after the drugs...
what's the differential diagnosis
for urine that's tea-colored?
Kidney stone.
Kidney stones would cause what?
Blood in urine.
- What color is your pee?
- Yellow.
- What color is your blood?
- Red.
What colors did I use?
- Red, yellow and brown.
- And brown.
- What causes brown?
- Wastes.
Which means the kidneys
are shutting down. Why?
- Trauma.
- None that his history would indicate.
Could be damage done by
the self-injection of the Demerol.
- Treatment?
- Heat and rest...
- Other possible causes.
- Infection.
Start him on antibiotics. What else?
Come on, come on!
I... I don't know.
You're useless.
But at least you know it.
Blood tests show elevated creatine kinase,
what does that tell you?
The trauma diagnosis is right.
He takes it easy for a few days,
he'll be fine.
You sure?
The elevated CK rules out infection...
You know what's worse than useless?
Useless and oblivious.
What are they missing?
You know, it's kind of hard to think
when you're in our face like this...
Yeah? You think it's going to be easier
when you've got
a real patient really dying?
What are you missing?
Muscle death.
Not your case.
Nothing wrong with a consult.
Dying muscle leaks myoglobin.
It's toxic to the kidneys.
Brilliant.
MRI his leg, see what's killing it.
Why is the girl getting the MRI?
Because the neck scan
revealed nothing and
her doctor's way more obsessive
than she thinks she is.
But you said the guy needed the MRI.
Because Dr. Cameron back there
said muscle death, not one of your said it!
Not one of this guy's doctors said it.
They gave him bed rest and antibiotics,
just like you guys would have.
Did he get better?
No.
- Well, how long...
- Three days.
It is in the nature of medicine
that you are gonna screw up.
You are gonna kill someone.
If you can't handle that reality,
pick another profession.
Or finish medical school and teach.
Three days before they thought
it might have been muscle death?
No, three days before the patient suggested
it might have been muscle death.
The MRI revealed an osteosarcoma:
A cancerous tumor in your femur.
It needs to be removed surgically.
With chemo, she has
an excellent chance of survival.
But I have to warn you,
depending on how large the tumor
is, and how ingrained it is,
the surgeon may need to amputate your leg.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Well, dogs' mouths are pretty filthy,
but they have natural antibodies
to fight off most of the stuff. We don't.
That's why dog bites can be so nasty.
The lab test of your dog's saliva
revealed a type of strep bacteria.
It's commonly known as
the "flesh eating disease".
We'll need to operate immediately
to remove the damaged tissue.
We may need to remove the leg.
The MRI revealed a problem.
No kidding.
I'm sorry none of your
doctors found it earlier.
I'm personally going to oversee
your treatment from now on.
You're gonna cut me open, aren't ya?
We may need to remove the leg.
His MRI showed that the leg pain
wasn't caused by the self-injection,
wasn't caused by an infection.
It was an aneurysm that clotted,
leading to an infarction.
God, you were right. It's House.
We have to do the surgery.
The necrotic tissue has to be removed.
If there's too much...
I don't care what you find.
It may become necessary
in order to save your life.
I like my leg.
I've had it for
as long as I can remember.
Honey, I love your leg
as much as you do.
They're not cutting it off.
Patient made the right choice.
Tell a surgeon it's okay to cut a leg off
and he's going to spend the night
polishing his good hacksaw.
Right, surgeons could care less
about saving limbs.
Well, of course they care
about their patients.
They just care
about themselves more.
Which is not an unreasonable position.
Trying to maximize the
tissue you save also
maximizes the chances of
something going wrong.
Which means you've gotta
be extra careful.
Which is such a pain in the ass.
Amazing advances have been made.
Kids with prosthetic legs are running
the 100-meter dash in twelve seconds.
Yeah, they're just not as pretty.
Do a bypass, restore the circulation.
Amputation is safer.
For you, or me?
The blockage of blood flow...
Four-day blockage.
Yes. It caused muscle cell death.
When those cells die,
they release cytokines and potassium...
If you restore the blood flow
instead of just lopping it all off,
then all that crap gets
washed back into my system.
The cytokines could cause organ failure,
and the potassium could
cause cardiac arrest.
On the other hand, I may just
get the use of my leg back.
The post-operative pain alone...
I'll get through it. I
understand the risks,
you're in the clear. Go schedule an OR.
God, you're an idiot.
I think I'm more of a jerk.
I'm not being glib.
And I'm not being cute,
I don't want you to kill yourself.
I'm not gonna die.
Oh, I feel completely reassured.
(Not this leg!)
(Not this leg either)
I think they gotta up that morphine.
The doctors say they can't.
The doctors recommended
bed rest and antibiotics.
They screwed up, it doesn't mean
they're wrong this time.
Sure doesn't mean they're right.
- Morphine will kill you.
- I can handle it.
You're in pain,
you're not thinking right.
That's why I need
the damn morphine!
Okay, I'll talk to them.
Oh my God, how much longer
is the pain going to last?
It depends on how much
muscle cell death there was.
He could be right, he could come out of
this with almost full use of his leg.
Or?
He could be in pain
for the rest of his life.
There's a third option, surgically.
A middle ground between
what we did and amputation.
He's not big on middle ground.
Yeah.
Nurse, Nurse?
I need more calcium gluconate.
You just had 5 mLs.
Either your ass is getting whiter
or my potassium is rising.
I'll talk to your doctor.
Well, you better make it fast,
'cause I'm about to go into cardiac arrest.
You give me the dose, or I go
into white count complex tachycardia.
I could get in trouble...
Listen, it's not a narcotic!
I'm not looking for a buzz.
You've got about twenty seconds.
I was wrong.
What have you got?
White complex tachycardia.
- Who diagnosed...
- He did.
Paddles!
- Charge.
- Clear!
The patient was technically
dead for over a minute.
He's back.
Do you think he was dead?
Do you think those experiences were real?
Define real.
They were real experiences.
What they meant...
Personally, I choose to
believe that the white light
people sometimes see
visions, this patient saw.
They're all just chemical reactions that
take place when the brain shuts down.
You choose to believe that?
There's no conclusive science.
My choice has no practical
relevance to my life,
I choose the outcome I
find more comforting.
You find it more comforting
to believe that this is it?
I find it more comforting to believe
that this simply isn't a test.
How bad is the pain right now?
It's bad.
It's not getting any better.
If you were right,
the pain would be subsiding.
You'd be getting better.
- It's just taking longer.
- No, it's not.
We've got to
let him cut the leg off.
It's my leg. It's my life.
Would you give up your leg to save my life?
Of course I would.
Then why do you think
your life is worth less than mine?
If this were any other patient,
what would you tell them to do?
- I would say it's their choice.
- Wha... not a chance!
You'd browbeat them until they made
the choice you knew was right.
You'd shove it in their face
that it's just a damn leg!
You don't think you deserve to live?
You don't think you deserve to be happy?
Now let them cut off your leg.
Sorry. I can't, I can't,
I'm sorry.
The pain alone is going to kill you.
I know, I know.
I need you to talk to the doctor.
He change his mind?
No.
He's asked to be put in a
chemically induced coma
so he can sleep through the
worst part of the pain.
We can do that.
What happens after he's in the coma?
We'll obviously monitor
his condition closely,
and if he can get through
the next forty-eight
hours without another
cardiac incident...
I meant, I'm his health-care proxy,
I get to make medical decisions
for him if he's not able to.
You should talk to him
about what he wants to do.
I know what he wants,
but if he's out it's my call, right?
You'll be out in less than a minute.
Thank you.
Hey.
I'll see you when I wake up.
We'll go golfing.
I love you.
I love you, too. I'm sorry.
You've got nothing to be sorry about.
The middle ground
you were talking about?
We go in, take out the dead muscle.
There's still some risk
of reperfusion injury, but...
Give me the forms you need signed.
You're saving his life.
He won't see it that way.
Because of the extent
of the muscle removed,
utility of the patient's leg
was severely compromised.
Because of the time delay
in making the diagnosis,
patient continues to
experience chronic pain.
She had no right to do that.
She had the proxy.
She knew he didn't want the surgery.
She saved his life!
Well, we don't know that.
Maybe he would have been fine...
It doesn't matter.
It's the patient's call.
The patient's an idiot.
They usually are.
Do you have a buzzer or something.
What time does this class end?
Twenty minutes ago.
I'm not doing this again.
And this guy is not the world's
greatest dad. Not even ranked.
Who the hell lets their kids
play with lead-based paint?
That's why he's always sick.
Find him some plastic cups
and the class is all his again.
Stacy, it's Gregg.
I've got an opening in my calendar
for ten tomorrow morning.
Make sure your husband isn't late.