Hi.
Sounds like a good party.
20 bucks.
Okay. No problem,
I just got it in here somewhere.
Oh god, I'm...
I'm sorry, I guess I must have
forgotten to go to the machine.
Yeah, and, brush your teeth.
Lady, you don't have two cents.
I can... I can get it from...
from my friend who's inside,
he can give it to me and then I can
bring it back out here to you.
You don't know anybody here.
Yes I do!
James, he's blonde and he's really
friendly and he's a big talker.
I need to see him.
Go on in.
James?
Hi.
Do you know where James is?
Oh yeah, he's around here somewhere.
Let's go find him.
James?
Do you know where James is?
Where is he?
I really need to find him.
What are you doing?
Bitch!
No! She's trying
to help me! Get off her!
Get off me!
Settle down!
Move!
Geez, I didn't touch her.
Great. Now we
gotta go to the hospital.
Homeless. Admitted 24 hours ago
with a suspected drug overdose.
Her tox screen's clean,
but she's still delusional.
Homeless, usually
means crazy. No money.
- Cuddy's not going to like this?
- We're a teaching hospital.
No ID.
Doesn't even seem to know her name.
I got called in because of
some lesions on her arm.
Homeless always means no roof,
at least, there's too much sun.
The lesions were non-cancerous,
but I noticed a twitch. Her wrist.
You feel that?
Sure. I'm human.
Make a fist around my fingers,
tight as you can. Squeeze.
I am.
Right.
Raise your arms
above your head for me.
She's seizing.
Get me some Ativan.
She doesn't want to be discharged.
She's manipulating me.
It's real.
Check her finger sticks.
Blood sugar's 38.
I need D15. IV push stat.
Fake low blood sugar.
Now that's acting.
The blood sugar was real.
But she's probably diabetic.
OD'd on her own insulin.
I need 2032.
Do you have her effects out here?
Look, a seizure buys her a
place to sleep while the
nice doctors run their tests,
maybe a few free meals.
$20 says there's insulin in here.
Oh... put this back, please.
What about the twitch?
Her arm moved.
Why fake a twitch?
In case the seizure was too subtle?
A twitch could indicate a
tumor, which could indicate...
A need to see a neurologist,
which is why you called me.
Keep an eye on her until 2:00 PM, watch her
blood sugar, give her a nice hot lunch,
then discharge her.
He's wrong.
Foreman is wrong?
The neurologist is wrong,
about a neurological problem?
He took one look at her
and figured it was a scam.
So, you figure he's not being objective.
House, the woman had a twitch.
She had a seizure.
Both of which Foreman saw?
He just wanted her out the door!
Back up there, big fella.
Foreman's the guy you
want to take a swing at.
I just want her to get
some medical attention.
That's not even close to being true.
Something else. Something personal.
Give me the file.
Looks like this will be fun.
The twitch could be a mini-seizure,
unrelated to the diabetes.
Brain tumor?
Glad you could join us, Eric.
What's the differential
for a twitch in the wrist?
The patient's a thirty-ish Jane Doe.
I just thought I'd discharge her.
Well, she's my patient.
No harm in a second opinion.
A blow to the head?
A subdural hematoma?
Read the file, no evidence
of cranial trauma.
A twitch could indicate a brain tumor.
Or about a dozen other things.
Come on, there's two things
homeless people are good at...
getting sick, and running scams.
If you're so worried about it being
a brain tumor, get her an MRI,
when she's clear on that, then
you can bounce her out of here.
Well, you've got her all figured out.
I've known a lot more homeless
people than you have.
Yes, you've got that going for you.
How could I have doubted
your medical opinion?
The big question,
you're missing it, all of you.
Oh, geez.
Who is she?
Okay. Why are we on this case...
just because Wilson asked?
Do I need a better reason?
Most people wouldn't, you do.
The only thing we know for sure about
Jane Doe is that her name isn't Jane Doe.
Which means no medical history.
Allergies, medication,
previous diagnoses, treatment...
we have no baseline,
no context for medical treatment.
Wow. Looks just like insulin.
Vomit. Still moist.
What do you think...
a couple of days old?
You trying to make me hurl?
Yeah. And here's the big finish...
Salty. Chemical imbalance.
Low magnesium could cause a twitch.
Or high calcium. Or it's a coincidence.
The point is, we don't know anything.
- So do the MRI. Find out...
- The MRI can wait.
Hang a banana bag, give her
24 hours to correct the
electrolyte imbalance,
we'll take it from there.
Great. Thanks.
Okay. Even if she's not faking,
what's so fascinating about this case?
At the moment,
how much you don't want me to take it.
That's pretty fascinating.
Nice likeness of Dr. Foreman.
In fact, he's never looked better.
He doesn't like me. I can tell.
That's okay.
He doesn't like me either.
Who's James?
Pain in your head?
Go! Get away from me.
All right, let's get it out.
One milligram of Ativan, push.
NO! NO! NO!
Hold on.
She bit me!
Good news is, she's
negative for HIV and hep-C.
Yeah?
I'm getting a tetanus shot,
she's getting an MRI.
There's a two day wait
for non-emergency MRls.
She's getting an MRI.
And then she's out of here.
Now Dr. Terharg specifically
said I'd have the MRI at 10:00,
it's almost 11:00, and I haven't
even had the pre-test yet.
Sorry, we're a little backed up.
Excuse me, you're Dr. Terharg's 10:00?
I'm Angela Whitney.
I'm meeting my decorator at 11:30,
she's coming all the way from New York.
Dr. Terharg promised I'd be home in time.
Of course.
She's just about prepped for her MRI?
Mrs. Whitney?
You tried to steal someone else's test?
Dr. Terharg is a plastic surgeon.
The woman was getting a six-month
checkup on a chin implant.
I can't believe you authorized this.
Really? Sounds exactly
like something I'd do.
She can't have an MRI.
The CT scan shows she has a
surgical pin in her arm,
the MRI magnet would have
ripped it out of her body.
You like the Alien movies?
You had no medical history,
what were you thinking?
We'll surgically remove the pin, then
do the MRI, does that sound good?
She has an electrolyte imbalance.
Dr. Foreman, a neurologist, believes
this woman has a brain tumor.
Actually, I...
Hey, don't ever apologize
for a medical opinion.
If he's right, we don't do
this test, the patient dies.
Now I realize that you have
a specialty of your own,
but does yours have anything
to do with the brain?
His does.
Fine. But nothing more
until you find out who she is.
- How are we supposed to...
- Hey!
He knows more homeless
people than any of us.
Go check out the 'hood, dawg.
I don't know.
I've seen a lot of faces around here but...
I don't think I know her.
Great.
Hey, I ah, like that jacket.
Yeah, it's all coming to me now.
I know where she keeps her stuff.
Just bats.
I thought the lining would be thicker.
No tumor, nothing.
Her brain is clear.
Which means, that girl had surgery just
so you wouldn't get reamed out by Cuddy.
Not necessarily, there could still
be something neurological going on.
Sure, she's not conning us, the MRI is.
Not wearing a coat in this weather.
That is so wrong.
She drew these.
They might give us a clue.
She sign them?
Her name would be a start.
All the mythology, the locations,
they're all dependant on life experience.
Philadelphia.
Look at that skyline!
It's very evocative.
The Chrysler Building.
That's a cloud.
And the Chrysler Building's in New York.
Mmm... I'm getting Philly.
And that cactus, well,
that's a smashed car...
car accident.
A cactus in Philadelphia?
Water... well,
water's October, right?
Obviously.
On the page number 22,
so that's October 2nd, 2002.
Ergo, the patient was in a car
accident two years ago last October.
My goodness! Was she okay?
Broke her arm, I think.
They fixed it... with this.
Surgical pin.
Better than a wallet.
Serial numbers in case of recall,
tied to a patient's name.
That's why you insisted on the MRI?
So you could remove the
surgical pin from her arm.
You didn't think I was going to do
it to save your sorry ass, did you?
You might want to take a look at that.
Her name is Victoria Matson,
at least that's the one she used then.
Any hospital with the record of treating
her should be sending that information.
Oh, crap!
Her blood work came back an hour ago,
magnesium was normal.
Did you change her banana bag?
Stopped the magnesium,
started iron dextran for severe anemia.
She's allergic to iron dextran!
Grab some Epi off the code cart.
Respiratory arrest,
call the code!
You have an allergic reaction,
can you speak?
She's not getting any air.
Got the Epi.
Stats down in the 80s and dropping.
We have about another minute.
Well, we got her sedated and stabilized.
And we still think there's
nothing wrong with her?
Well, nothing's changed.
We almost killed her...
that's different.
And we know who she is.
So far we've heard from three hospitals
with records of Victoria Matson.
Seven visits, going back two years.
Any home addresses?
The pin in her arm went
in during an ER visit.
She wasn't conscious,
so they didn't get an address.
The other visits
she gave fake addresses.
Any treatment for neurological problems,
anything that might explain the twitch?
Last winter, Jefferson Hospital in
Philly, got treated for frostbite.
Baby, it's cold outside.
And depression.
They put her on Prozac.
Well, I'd be bummed out too.
Zero degrees, living in a box.
Put her back on it.
She cheers up
She might stop biting people.
There's a billing record from
Hartman Hospital last year.
Two appointments, ultrasounds,
doesn't say what for.
Pregnant?
Only if she was expecting an elephant.
The appointments were ten months apart.
Kept the first,
blew off the second.
Abdominal pain.
- The chart doesn't say...
- Wait a minute.
She goes in the first time,
they look, they can't find anything.
Ten months later, why should she
subject herself to that again?
Why make a second appointment?
She didn't.
The nurse made the appointment.
They were looking...
they were looking for ovarian cancer.
You got all of that from
one cancelled appointment?
With Jerry Lousing, yeah.
He's an oncologist.
Hang on, her current blood work
doesn't show cancer. CA125 is normal.
And the cancer wouldn't account
for the alleged twitch,
or any other of her alleged symptoms.
Actually, it would.
Neoplastic Syndrome associated
with the cancer could
cause her to twitch like
a bunny on crystal meth.
Ultrasound her ovaries.
Did you find a brain tumor on her MRI?
No. Foreman was wrong.
I'm starting to wonder about
that guy's medical chops.
Right.
Shelley Diamond?
Yes?
Dr. House is ready to see you now.
The little ones are
licking each other again,
and Harry's got a seeping
wart on his extra toe.
What room should we go to?
You know, I think I might be
coming down with something.
Hate to give it to you guys. Sorry.
Oh yeah. Just walk out,
like "I'm not going to do anything".
Bye bye.
Working hard?
This stuff's pretty good.
Calendrica, works for the counseled genius.
Bad guy's Mr. Fury, fairly
generic, no special skills,
but apparently very well organized.
Think you work hard,
try ruling the universe.
You trying to
teach me something here?
We've got the flowing dress, the ring.
Think the patient was married?
Maybe it was a bad break up, maybe he
dumped her cause she was on drugs.
You care about her personal history?
Nope. Question is,
why don't you?
I hate to cite a cliche, but...
Dad on the streets?
Dad's with Mom.
They're both living on the streets?
No! On a pension.
So who pissed you off?
Right now, you.
Your turn,
you gonna tell me why this case?
She's my new girlfriend,
I'm having a tattoo designed,
I was hoping you could find out her name.
So she's just another sick
person the kindly Dr. Wilson
has made sure doesn't get
lost in the big ugly system.
Yes, I forgot, I need a
reason to give a crap.
You're giving two craps.
The metric system always confuses me.
Dr. House.
Time for Girl Scout cookies already?
Get me some Thin Mints.
Since you're too sick
to work in the clinic.
Okay.
I thought you...
I thought you could do some teaching.
Patient histories.
My specialty.
When you teach, you learn
so much, don't you think?
It's all about the giving back.
Good old Cuddy. Always thinking.
She assign you a patient to interview?
Then why are you still here?
Why are we on this case?
Because Wilson asked
House to do him a favor.
I think House just wants to prove
she's sick so Foreman will be wrong.
Oh, you boys.
Hey, I'm just doing my job.
Foreman's going to be so embarrassed
when he finds out she's got cancer.
Oh. I thought you were too
sick to be down here.
I had to get away from those
students so I faked a page.
Foreman's parents, happily
married, 40 years.
Mazel Tov.
Keinahora.
So, why does he hate homeless people?
But if it's an uncle
or a grandparent
you'd think he'd use it in
his college application essay.
Family struggles beats a 4.0 GPA any day.
I think he had a 4.0.
Maybe he's just a snob.
You really don't need to know
everything about everybody.
I don't need to watch the OC,
but it makes me happy.
Yeah, delirious.
What's the other file?
Wilson, James. Boy wonder oncologist.
You know him?
You know, in some
cultures, it's considered
almost rude for one
friend to spy on another.
Of course, in Swedish, the word friend can
also be translated as 'limping twerp'.
Did your pager really just go off,
or are you ditching the conversation?
Why can't both be true? Come on.
Solid non-cystic mass on the left ovary.
Five by three centimeters,
central necrosis.
The only question is whether she
dies in two months or three.
Oh, God.
You were right. There's
nothing we can do for her here.
Might as well put
her back on the street.
Unless it's not cancer.
Oh, you're joking.
Well, hard not to...
nothing funnier than cancer.
But what if it's a tuberculoma.
She's living out on the streets,
breathing all kinds of crap 24/7.
The odds are she's got TB, why can't she
have a nice benign growth to go with it?
A solid mass on her ovary.
Ovarian cancer's way more likely.
You're right.
It's not even close.
Start her on INH
Rifampicin and Streptomycin.
But that's the treatment for a tuberculoma.
And what is the treatment for
advanced ovarian cancer?
Pine box.
What are you giving me?
A second dose of some antibiotics.
If you've got a tuberculoma,
it should help.
I don't have a tuberculoma, do I?
Probably not.
Listen...
I'm sorry I didn't believe you.
I'm sorry I lied to you.
I took too much insulin on purpose;
I really wanted a place to sleep.
Were you ever married, Victoria?
But in the comic...
No, it's a comic, comics are just made up.
So who's James?
Is he real, or
did you make him up?
He's real.
Can I help you find him?
The light's bright
it's getting brighter...
Take it easy, everything's fine.
Mr. Fury wants to hurt me.
Please, help me!
Wait, wait, wait, hold on...
Please turn it off...
Please! Oh, god!
All right, hold on Victoria.
Hold on. Take it easy.
Everything's fine.
- Take it easy, - It's burning!
- Everything's fine, Victoria.
- No! It's burning!
Hold on. Take a sip, take a sip.
It's poison, you gave me poison!
Hold on. Take it easy.
Hey, turn off that damn light!
Help me, please!
Take it easy, take it easy.
The bad guys can't get you here,
I've got you covered.
Mr. Fury's not the bad guy,
I'm the bad guy, it's me,
I'm the bad guy...
It's not a tuberculoma. Can't be.
I didn't know the biopsy was back.
Her temperature's 105.
Treatment's not working,
it's cancer. She's dying.
105...
Good news! It's a tuberculoma.
How do you figure that?
Her temp's through the roof.
It's the lab results from the biopsy,
it's definitely a tuberculoma.
So... we're right about the diagnosis,
and the treatment for that
diagnosis is killing her.
Perfect.
The lab checked the biopsy again, twice.
Well, a tuberculoma doesn't
give you a temperature of 105.
Then it's a tuberculoma and something else.
The something else is
gonna to melt her brain.
Poach.
Better metaphor.
A fever that high has to be bacterial.
Maybe the bowel got nicked in the biopsy.
I did the biopsy... no nick!
She could have picked up an
infection on the streets.
Well, she didn't have a fever
when I admitted her!
The Prozac we've given
her could have triggered.
Serotonin Syndrome, which
would explain the fever.
No! Jefferson put her on Prozac,
and it wasn't a problem.
She probably never took it!
Most likely they saw her one time and
dumped her out of the ER with a script.
Oh, just like you were going to do!
Okay you two, grab some scalpels
and settle this like doctors.
Send blood and urine cultures
and get a chest x-ray.
And fine, take her off Prozac
and put her on Bromocryptin
for the Serotonin syndrome.
Might want to get her
in an ice bath as well,
assuming we want her to live long
enough to see those test results.
I said I was sorry.
Your fever's 105.
If we don't bring it down fast...
Foreman,
why are you doing this to me?
We're saving your life.
Hey, come on. You can do this.
Please!
17 year old female presents with abrasions
and apparent trauma injury to her wrist...
Dr. House?
Continue.
You're reading a comic book.
And you're calling attention to your
bosom by wearing a low-cut top.
Oh, I'm sorry, I thought we were
having a state-the-obvious contest.
I'm competitive by nature.
I thought you were supposed to be
listening to our patient histories.
Nope. I'm supposed to be teaching you.
If I can do that without
listening, more power to me.
17 year old female...
This guy's supposed to have universal
power over all of gravity;
How come his hair won't stay down?
That's just stupid.
She fell off her horse while
riding in the county fair.
No, she didn't,
she fell off the steps of her beach house,
you must have gone to the wrong room.
Hard to believe that one
patient could slip past Cuddy
and get herself admitted
with a sprained wrist.
Two seems almost impossible...
what room?
Room 2106.
Patients lie.
But usually only one lie at a time;
How much does she weigh?
It's her wrist not her...
Poundage, ladies, and by the
by, what color is her nose?
- She's thin...
- Flesh toned.
What does this have to do with her wrist?
Almost nothing.
She's either under 90 pounds,
or she has a red nose. I gotta go.
What's wrong with her?
That would be telling.
Oh, I am just too nice.
It starts with 'C'.
Urine cultures are negative.
So's the chest x-ray.
I assume there's a positive coming.
Lumbar punctures revealed elevated
proteins and white counts.
CSF cultures?
Still growing. Nothing on Gram Stain.
It looks like meningitis.
We know it's definitely an infection.
And we know where it is.
Well, meningitis is nice and simple.
Get her in isolation and
start her on Ceftriaxone.
Either she gets better or she dies.
Let me know which one happens!
Oh my God. She was sedated.
It must have worn off.
I did it myself, a half hour ago.
I'll check the nurse's station.
Calendrica.
She's gonna die out there.
You don't walk out of a
room with ten milligrams
of Haldol in your system,
you don't walk at all.
It was ten milligrams,
I gave it to her...
It doesn't matter!
Bacterial meningitis,
highly contagious, if
she is out of the hospital,
we are so liable.
Not to worry. She'll be dead
before she can kill anybody.
Security tape confirms it,
she stole some clothes and she's gone.
Wrong coat.
The cape's in the closet,
I had it cleaned.
Funny.
You gonna save her?
In her comics, Mr. Fury
lives in Sloan Harbor.
The night she came in, she was
at a rave at 1408 Sloan Street.
You've been reading.
My, how you've changed.
You are a doctor;
Do what doctors do.
Pick up the phone, dial 911
and a cop on the other
end does what cops do and
finds the missing person!
I assume the rest of you have doctor
things to do... I know you do.
Cacchi-Ricci disease.
Do you even know what
that is, or are you just
guessing everything
that starts with 'C'?
The kidney problems could
result in weight loss.
Cacchi... C-A-C-
she's going alphabetically.
Doctor, why are you wearing that bird pin?
It sets off my eyes.
Hi, Jodi, I'm Dr. House.
What brings you to the hospital?
My wrist.
How did that happen?
I was riding the Ferris wheel and
this huge seagull flew right at me.
How horrifying.
I swung my arm at the bird,
but I hit the Ferris wheel.
She's making it all up?
No, her wrist really does hurt.
I'm not lying.
Of course you are.
You have no idea what happened.
You have no memory.
Korsakoff's syndrome.
Her brain is damaged by
excessive drinking or
insufficient diet. Pretty
obviously the latter.
She has no new memories,
no new ideas,
can't even process that idea.
So her brain fills the gaps as
best it can using visual clues.
The horse on your shirt led
her to the riding accident
and the surf scene on your
clipboard led her to the beach.
Korsakoff doesn't start with a 'C'.
I didn't say 'C'. Or did I?
Lesson to be learned...
treat everybody as if they have
Korsakoff's, we all lie anyway.
Give her Thiamine right away,
she'll bounce back pretty quickly.
And then get her to eat
some cake and ice cream.
Yes?
Did you need to be so cruel?
I think she's crying.
Hi! Jodi, I'm Dr. House.
What happened to your wrist?
There was this weird old
guy, he had a cane...
See? It's like it never happened.
Perfect forgiveness.
Pulse is rapid.
You got a temp?
Don't know. She's warm, but...
That's something to look into;
She has meningitis.
Sorry, I was more worried
about her heart blowing up.
Pulse is 150.
Rhythm regular?
Yeah.
Ready. One, two, three.
Where'd you find her?
Battlefield State Park.
Narrow Complex?
- She wasn't at Sloan?
- She was just passed out on the grass.
Foreman... I need Foreman.
All right. Super ventricular tachycardias.
Get me Adenosine, one milligram, push.
Thank you.
Hang in there.
Her arrythmia stabilized.
It doesn't make sense.
What would push her heart rate over 150?
Dehydration? Fever?
Unlikely. By themselves,
neither one would do it.
We must be wrong about the meningitis.
Maybe it's structural heart disease.
Her heart rate dropped
when you administered the Adenosine.
Two seconds.
It's still meningitis.
If it is, with the delay in treatment,
she's got almost no chance.
Start the treatment.
Read the report.
I found her lying on the grass.
You should read my reports.
I make up stuff all the time.
What really happened?
Oh, since it's you...
I found her lying on the grass.
Wow. That is a great looking gun.
It's not a gun. It's a taser.
It's so cool looking.
What does it do?
Fire about 60,000 volts?
At least, that's what it would take
to jack someone's heart up to 150s.
Okay. Okay. Let's just say
I tell you what happened.
This stays between you and me, right?
I found her. Lying. On the. Grass.
Fine.
Don't tell me.
Tell my friend, Ben Franklin.
I watch a lot of cop shows.
The good news is, the heart rate thing's
not connected to her condition.
Well then, she's dying.
The meningitis treatment isn't
helping her, she's getting worse.
Well, that brings us to the bad news.
The cop tasered her.
Jerk.
Probably couldn't get to
his real gun fast enough.
The first time he hit her in the thigh,
and she just kept going,
like it was nothing.
Right about here.
She didn't feel the taser.
Localized numbness?
Yeah, in that one spot.
The diabetes?
I don't think so.
No alcohol. Not entrapment syndrome.
Can't be a vitamin deficiency.
We can't chase down every
sensory neuropathy.
Is that where she bit you?
Yeah.
What the hell?
Can't get angry if you don't feel anything.
First there's localized numbness,
then sensitivity to light,
disorientation, paranoia,
ineffectiveness of sedatives,
and then hydrophobia.
Fear of water.
Rabies.
There've only been, what,
20 cases in the last ten years?
Yeah.
That's because non-homeless people,
when they get bitten, they get shots.
There were bats.
She's dying.
There's no treatment.
How much time does she have?
A day, maybe two.
And if you don't get your shot in,
say, the next three hours,
I'm going to have to make another
affirmative action hire.
Come on.
Do it.
You want me to talk to her?
And say what?
There's some experimental treatment,
but it's not gonna work.
Don't worry, we can make you comfortable?
Doesn't matter how.
She's gonna die.
Yeah. That's what you say to her.
Keep that there and rest for a minute.
Tell House I need to go
out for about an hour.
She may not have that long.
I don't want her to die alone.
You're going to find James.
I'm gonna try.
Well, I must say...
he's done a lot with the place.
Hello?
Hey... this is it.
Man, no one's been in here for a long time.
This has got to be James.
Maybe there's another address.
It's not James.
Paul.
Paul Furia.
Mr. Fury.
Her husband.
Then who's James?
Her kid.
Oh, I just want to eat you up.
You're so delicious.
Look at me,
you're just like your papa.
Look at you. Just like your dad.
Foreman.
They're dead.
That car crash two years ago...
she broke her arm...
and they were killed.
She was driving.
James.
No.
It's Paul.
You've come to take me.
No.
I've come to forgive you.
It wasn't your fault.
I'm so sorry...
I know.
It's okay Victoria.
It's okay.
You followed me?
No.
You were wearing rain boots today,
but you were parked in
the underground garage,
so the only reason you'd need boots was
if you were hitting the streets...
I followed you.
Didn't we have a conversation
about friendship?
Yeah. I had some follow up questions.
I've met your parents, and your brother...
I have two brothers.
Why wouldn't you tell me...
It was irrelevant.
Why not?
Because he's not in my life any more.
Well, that's relevant.
This was the last place I saw him,
nine years ago.
I don't even know if he's alive.