Cat got your tongue?
Nah, you killed the cat.
Cut off its head.
Need to take a look at this.
Mom?
Mom. Mom! It's OK.
Just a couple of
questions before I can authorize
extending her disability benefits...
I don't like her. She's fat.
I could lose a little weight.
You all right?
Actually, before she signs...
I killed the cat, lots of blood.
It's OK.
I have a couple of questions
about some of these dates.
The first diagnosis...
Schizophrenia.
Dr. Walters, May 11th, last year.
The letter's in the medical file.
And April 6th?
That was the last day she worked.
But she received unemployment
benefits for that week.
We fixed that, I know we
did, we returned the money.
That's the canceled check.
Not the real one,
you know, it's a copy.
And you're the dependent?
No, that's my little brother.
I'm eighteen. Just helpin' out.
You're all set.
Just need a signature.
Hey! I'm talking to you.
The cat's first.
Now it's your turn, Lucy.
Shhhhh. Shut up,
shut up, shut up!
It's OK, she just, she just
needs a little water, is all...
I'll go get it.
Just hold on, OK, just...
when she comes back, sign
it and we're gonna be done.
We need this, OK? Please?
OK.
The voices...
The voices aren't real.
Mom? Mom!
Dr. Gregory House,
please call Dr. Cuddy at extension 3731.
This is a good hospital?
Depends what you mean by "good."
I like these chairs.
How is she?
Stable. OK. Your mom had a
small pulmonary embolism;
Blood clot that got stuck in
her lungs, blocked the oxygen.
But the pain started in her leg.
Where the clot started. Her calf.
It's called a deep vein thrombosis.
Basically a bigger clot.
It never hurt there before.
I would have noticed.
Piece of that broke off, went
up the vein, through the heart,
blocked the blood flow to her lungs.
No blood flow, no oxygen.
OK...
Is your dad here? I have some
things I need to talk to him about.
Uh, my dad's running a little late.
He's dead. Just talk to me?
I take care of her.
All right. Your mom's blood alcohol
was .12. Ten thirty in the morning.
I gave it to her. Two ounces of vodka.
It cools her out.
But that's the first since Monday.
That was three days ago.
I've been real careful.
She hears voices.
She's schizophrenic?
Explains the DVT.
The alcohol makes her pass out,
she's immobile for long periods of time...
That doesn't happen.
She's not an alcoholic.
She only drinks when you give it to her.
We put her on blood thinners.
You can probably take her home tomorrow.
It's not the alcohol, it's
gotta be something else.
Of course it's the alcohol.
Hello!
This guy's a professional doctor.
Plays golf and everything, I bet.
He's not gonna tell you your mom's
an alcoholic without proof.
I'm sure he scoped for varices, checked her
esophagus, ran all kinds of blood tests.
Doctors like this, they don't make
assumptions, they do the work!
I'd be happy to refer you
the case, Dr. House.
You seem so interested.
What case? It's over.
You're sending her home.
How old is she?
You're a doctor?
Own my own stethoscope.
Did I ask you how
old she was? I forget.
Thirty eight year old woman
with no previous symptoms
or history presents with
deep vein thrombosis.
How did she get it?
Oral contraceptives, smoking, diabetes,
obesity, and what's the point here?
A DVT's a DVT.
Put her on IV heparin to
prevent future clots.
What's the big mystery?
Fine. You're all sleeping.
You need a clue.
She's 38 years old!
She's 20 years too young to
get a deep vein thrombosis!
I treated a 12 year old girl once,
soccer player,
she got kicked in the leg...
There was no trauma,
none of the risk factors.
You took a history?
I... have some notes.
They're not mine, but they're reliable,
I think, for purposes of this discussion.
As for the immobility, well, she's
real active right now, of course.
Paranoia keeps her limber.
Paranoia?
Oh yeah? She's schizophrenic.
And her kid wrote this,
so it might be a little biased.
Having to take care of
his nutso mom and all.
You think there's a connection?
Do we include schizophrenia
in the differential for DVT?
Well...
The answer is no.
Abnormal dopaminergic pathways
in the brain do not cause blood clots.
Schizophrenia is not the cause of DVT.
On the other hand, we don't
really know anything
about schizophrenia, so
maybe it is connected.
Well, the schizophrenia
explains one mystery.
Why you're so fascinated by a
woman with a bump in her leg?
It's like Picasso deciding
to whitewash a fence.
Thanks. I'm more of a Leroy Neiman man.
And it is only about the DVT.
- She's 38 years old, she should be...
- Right. Solve this one
and you're on your way to Stockholm.
We don't even know how to treat it!
Come on! Fumigation of the vagina?
A little louder... I don't
think everyone heard you.
Two thousand years ago, that's how
Galen treated schizophrenics.
The Marcus Welby of ancient Greece.
Clearly you're not interested.
I'm interested.
I'm interested in how voices in the head
could be caused by
malposition of the uterus.
There's a better place for it?
And now what have we got?
We've got lobotomies, rubber rooms,
electric shock - my -
Galen was so primitive.
Where are you going?
Going to see the patient.
That all-important human connection.
Thought I'd give it a whirl.
You won't talk to patients
because they lie, but
give you patient with no
concept of reality...
If it wasn't for Socrates, that
raving untreated schizophrenic,
we wouldn't have the Socratic method
the best way of teaching everything,
apart from juggling chainsaws.
Without Isaac Newton, we'd
be floating on the ceiling.
Dodging chainsaws, no doubt.
And that guitar player in that
English band, he was great.
You think I'm interested
because of the schizophrenia.
Yeah. I'm pretty sure.
Galen was pretty sure about
the fumigation thing.
Pink Floyd.
Mom, this is Dr...
Gregory House, nice to meet you.
Be all right if we spoke alone for awhile?
Well, you're gonna need me to...
Got your case notes... doctor.
There's a cafeteria downstairs.
Get yourself whatever you want
as long as there's enough left
over for a reuben sandwich, dry,
no fries, hold the pickles.
Should run you about $5.80 with tax.
I'll page you when we're done.
No... pickles.
Nice kid.
How much do you really drink?
He's really talking to a patient?
I don't know who I am anymore.
It's a blood clot. What's
so fascinating about that?
He likes crazy people.
Likes the way they think.
They think... badly.
That's the definition of crazy.
Why would he like...
They're not boring. He likes that.
And the meds...
Baseball! I like baseball.
- Very nice.
- Very sad.
My boy and me.
we went to see a game.
Not "Mets"? Meds. Medicine.
You take what he tells you to take.
No one believes me.
I do.
I thought he liked rationality.
He likes puzzles.
Patients are puzzles?
You don't think so?
I think they're people.
Yeah. Well, he hates them,
and he's fascinated by them.
Tell me you can't relate to that symptom.
You told Luke it never hurt before.
Just rough. They didn't hurt.
Didn't?
Don't lie to him, Limpie.
Lively Lucy never lies to Lucas.
Look what I do to him.
Learn anything from the "human connection"?
Yeah. The Mets suck.
Also, for the last two months,
she hasn't shaved her legs.
Because of the tremors.
She cuts herself.
The tremors aren't new
she must always cut herself.
Exactly. Something changed
in the last two months.
I'm thinking the amount of
blood when she cut herself.
So let's start with some bloodwork.
Collect and send for
clotting studies, PT, PTT,
factor 5, protein, CNS,
the whole shebang.
Good luck.
No pickles, and it's cold now.
If it's a reuben, that's
the way he likes it.
Everyone, this is Luke.
Allison Cameron, it's
nice to finally meet...
Yeah, save it, we're busy.
Luke, give us another half hour with
your mom. We need to do some tests.
Nice kid.
Take her off the psych meds,
that way we'll know what's
what on the physical side,
and who knows, we might
get more out of her.
Don't worry? No pickles.
Happy birthday.
OK. Whose?
I was going through your mail,
and it was on a form.
Happy birthday.
Oh.
No, no blood, not mine!
For the test, Dr. House told you...
You're gonna steal it,
sell it, no, no blood,
No, no blood, no, no blood, no!
Haldol, 5 milligrams, stat.
No...
Well, good news, the lab says
it's not strep, so we're done.
Wait a second...
No, really, not strep.
Boys in the lab, sure, they're hard
drinkers, but they're pros, you know.
Plus, your kid actually has
none of the symptoms of strep,
I just figured it was quicker running
the test than arguing with you.
My point is? Go!
I just wanted to ask your opinion, doctor.
She's having a birthday party next week
and she's upset that I'm
getting a sugarless cake.
The other kids hate it!
This is why you're here.
Sugar is the leading cause
of obesity in America.
You want a doctor to scare her
about the dangers of sugar.
She needs to get her weight under control.
Well, you know...
I feel sorry for those other kids,
Wendy, who don't have a mom like yours
a mom who knows that
sugar causes heart disease,
appendicitis, and athlete's foot.
That's not fair.
Oh, yes it is. No, I get it.
You want her to slim down a little, so
she can wear pretty clothes like yours.
Love the bracelets.
Hey! What about matching outfits?
You could be twins!
She can't be your daughter, it's
impossible, you look way too young!
Happy birthday.
Get the kid a damned ice cream cake.
You drugged her.
Actually, I didn't. I've taken
her off all medications.
Your guy, Foreman, gave her Haldol.
We needed blood for some tests.
I assume that was the only way to get it.
He knocked her out.
Look! I have a cane, and
I know how to use it.
I hired you. You work for me.
OK, can I go now?
Boss?
The Haldol changes her.
She says it makes her soul numb.
Don't give it to her.
If there be rags enough,
he will know her name.
And be well pleased remembering it.
You OK?
Old... days...
For in the old days,
Though she had young men's
praise and old men's blame,
Among the poor, both old
and young gave her praise.
Help! Somebody, help!
So, when I said, "no psych meds",
I'm just curious,
which word didn't you understand?
The Haldol had nothing to do
with the bleed. You know that.
I used it purely as a chemical restraint.
Oh, great, well, that's good to hear.
So she won't experience
any of those pesky little
side effects you get when
your motives aren't pure.
Those side effects are so rare!
Passing out, increased confusion,
depression, that's not gonna happen.
That's not gonna screw up our diagnosis,
'cause you just used it to restrain her.
I'm so relieved!
She spit in my face!
It must have been so frightening for you.
What was I supposed to do? Tie her down?
Yeah! Anything but give her drugs.
That's basically my point!
The clotting studies.
Pretty fast, you promise
to date the entire lab?
No. I save that for emergencies.
I told them she bled out two units
and if it happened again, she'd die.
If it'd happened at home,
she would have died.
That ER doc,
he was gonna send her home.
It turns out your best
judgment is not good enough.
Here's an idea.
Next time, use mine.
I think they're choosing a movie.
Why did the patient bleed out?
The clotting studies so far are normal.
Well, cover your ears if you don't
want me to spoil the ending.
Everything was normal,
except for prolonged PT time,
which means what?
Usually it means, whoever drew
the blood didn't do it right.
Oh, that's right. 'Cause...
you drew the blood.
But you were precise, because you knew
the tube was purely for the PT study.
That's right.
And I'm right with you.
I trust this result.
For two reasons. A, because
you are a good doctor,
and b, because five
milligrams of IV Haldol
makes for a spectacularly
cooperative patient.
The prolonged PT time makes me think
she's got a vitamin K deficiency.
Vitamin K would explain the
bleed but not the clot.
Without vitamin K, protein C doesn't work.
Without protein C, she clots.
Clotting and thinning,
all at the same time.
What about another drug
interacting with heparin,
an antibiotic like ampicillin?
That would...
Clever, but she's not on ampicillin.
Two months ago, she complained of a
sore throat. And he got her ampicillin.
Which she refused to take.
He just said she didn't take it.
What is it, everybody lies, except for
schizophrenics and their children?
It's more likely than malnourishment.
Why not scurvy or the plague?
Gee, I wish my idea was as
cool and with it as yours.
What is yours, by the way?
Do you have one?
Alcohol. Simple.
It causes immobility,
which explains the DVT.
It also causes cirrhosis which explains
the bleed and the prolonged PT time.
Let's ultrasound the liver.
Three theories.
Check out her place for ampicillin
and diet, then ultrasound her liver.
Let's find out who's right
before she bleeds to death.
101.
So House says the kid's sensitive.
Thinks he takes good care of her.
If we don't find anything, why let him
know we did it in the first place?
What's the point?
Why not just make old Foreman lift
the key from the kid's backpack?
Looks like Luke sleeps in the living room.
Nothing in there.
He lays out her clothes?
Enough organization, enough lists, you
think you can control the uncontrollable.
Fix her meds, fix her clothes,
maybe you can even fix her.
Pick that up on your psych rotation?
Trifluo perazine, Thorazine,
Foziril. They tried everything.
The ampicillin... never touched it.
There goes Cameron's theory.
Oh, God, I hope it's not
a vitamin K deficiency.
Oh. Damn.
Breakfast, lunch and dinner.
House was right.
That's the only thing she'll eat.
Problem is, you can't
actually live on this stuff.
I checked it out, I looked on the box,
all the nutritional values were solid.
There's plenty of protein, and calories...
Yeah, vitamin A and C, but no K.
That's why your mom got sick.
So, what's the plan?
Load her up with vitamin K.
That's it?
If it all checks out, you can take
her home in a couple of days.
Oh God, you're upset about something.
You're gonna open to me now, aren't you?
It's all my fault.
Here we go...
OK, I'm gonna say this once.
You have done a very good job
taking care of your mother.
If this was all she'd eat,
then what else could you do?
Gosh, just being a kid
is a full-time job...
Shut up! I'm 18, I should be
able to take care of my mom!
I almost killed her.
Good example.
Just the time it takes to express those
ridiculous self-centered teenage ideas...
I don't envy your schedule.
No pickles.
My mom doesn't like them either.
Smart woman.
Before she got sick,
I didn't like how bossy she was,
always telling me what to do,
the right way to do it.
Never thought I'd miss that.
You should get that looked at.
I still don't buy a vitamin K deficiency.
House was right.
That usually makes you happy.
Less work for us.
The kid feeds his mum a steady diet of
booze and the problem is too many burgers?
The kid's in a tough situation.
You do what you've gotta do to survive.
Feeding alcohol to an alcoholic
is not a survival technique.
Where I come from, if it works...
Yeah, right. I'm rich,
I couldn't possibly understand
what this kid is going through.
Just because you're drinking pricier stuff
doesn't mean you don't have a problem.
You've seen someone stagger down that road?
No way vitamin K's the whole story.
It's not broken.
See this right here?
It's the epiphyseal plate,
otherwise known as the growth plate.
What's wrong with it?
Amazing thing, this bone.
If you know how to read it, it can
tell you how old someone really is.
Exactly how old.
Great.
Not even fifteen. Almost, though.
Two weeks away, maybe a month.
Last week.
I was fifteen last week.
Happy birthday to both of us.
If you're gonna lie though, go big, go 21.
That way you won't need your
crazy mom to help you buy vodka.
Great. Thanks for the tip.
Now, when I bring my mom home,
is there anything I need to
know about taking care of her?
I suppose your biggest
worry isn't the booze.
You're 15, basically no mom.
Child Welfare let kids get away with that,
well, they wouldn't need
those nice foster homes,
and that would make them sad.
They'd put her someplace too.
My life is working.
Not the word I'd use.
Most 15 year old kids are doing
what they're supposed to be doing,
you know, they're huffing
glue, catching crabs...
If you turn me in, I'll sue you.
That's privileged information.
Oh, relax. It's not even your x-ray.
She's awfully calm.
House write new orders?
There's a little bit of scarring,
not much, not enough to con...
It's cirrhosis. But she doesn't drink!
Congratulations, you win.
Actually...
no one wins.
A tumor. Cystic?
Solid mass.
Cancer.
The vitamin K caused the DVT,
and aggravated the liver.
But the tumor's the real
reason for the bleed.
The tumor's the problem.
Mrs. Palmeiro, I'm Dr Wilson.
I'm afraid I have some bad
news from your ultrasound.
You have cancer.
It's big. Five point eight centimeters.
We do nothing, she dies from
liver failure within 60 days.
She needs a transplant.
That's gonna happen.
She's a 38 years old, she's a mother...
She's a schizophrenic mother, with
no money, on the public dole,
in fact, who knocks back vodka
every time a breeze blows her way.
Mickey Mantle had a whole
bar named after him.
He got a transplant.
Yeah, well, Lucy can't switch-hit.
Plan B. Surgery to resect the tumor.
Joe Bergen does the knife thing...
laser cauterizes while it
cuts, saves more liver.
The tumor's way too big.
He won't even consider it.
Not a big risk taker, Bergen. He won't
even drink milk on its expiration date.
He has no discretion.
Would he do it at 4.6?
Why don't we just say it's zero,
then we don't need him at all.
Tumors grow, they don't shrink.
This one does.
Ninety five percent ethanol.
The ethanol dehydrates the tumor cells,
literally sucks them dry.
Shrinks the tumor temporarily.
How temporarily?
Well, if we're lucky,
just long enough to fool the surgeon.
Good morning, Dr. House!
Good morning, Dr. Cuddy!
Love that outfit.
Says, I'm professional,
but I'm still a woman.
Actually, it sorta yells the second part.
Yeah, and your big cane is real subtle too.
Gotta go.
Those running noses aren't just
gonna start walking on their own.
The clinic can wait.
How long? Maybe we could catch a movie.
You should know by now my doctors
have no secrets from me.
I don't believe it.
Who came running to Mommy?
It doesn't matter who. The point is,
I know exactly what you did.
You have no idea what I'm talking about.
Somebody knows about a bad thing
you did. That's a big field.
But somebody you think might have told
me, that narrows it down quite a bit.
Someone who views me as a
maternal authority figure.
A young person,
perhaps... How am I doing?
You think I'm gonna get there?
Presumably hospital business.
How many patients...
It's Cameron. She... found
out about my birthday.
I thought she told you, and
I'd have to stand here and
smile while you gave me a
sweatshirt or a fruit basket,
you know, made me feel that
deep sense of belonging.
Actually, I was just gonna remind you,
you owe me six clinic hours this week.
Oops.
Hi, this is Dr. Cuddy.
I need all the charts
on Dr. House's current patients.
I've tried everything.
Pulling the tongue, icepacks
on the throat, hitting yourself...
the groin pinch.
Well, you've certainly covered
all the normal medical bases.
How are you hitting yourself, though?
Is it open hand or fist?
Open hand.
Well, that's how they
teach it at Harvard Med.
How hard though?
I'm sorry, I missed that. Could...
could you do that again?
That's very good. Hiccups.
I need to speak with you. Now.
I need to go peepee.
Just dial it up a notch and repeat.
I'll be back.
Oh, girl in the boys' bathroom.
Very dramatic.
Must be very important what
you have to say to me.
Yesterday your patient's tumor was
5.8 centimeters. Today it's 4.6.
How did that happen?
At a guess, I'd say,
"Dr. House must be really really good.
why am I wasting him on hiccups?"
I wash before and after.
You also requisitioned 20cc of ethanol.
What patient was that for?
Or are you planning a party?
Do me a favor...?
I was gonna say "leave," but that works.
You shrunk the tumor!
Only way to get the
- guy to do the surgery...
- Fraud!
Fraud was the only way.
There is a reason that we
have these guidelines.
I know, to save lives.
Specifically doctors' lives, and not
just their lives but their lifestyles.
Wouldn't wanna operate
on anyone really sick.
They might die and spoil our stats.
Bergen has a right to know
what he is operating on.
True. I got all focused on her
right to live, and forgot.
You do what you think is right.
You really didn't know.
No. I didn't.
And frankly I'm angry.
Which I'm guessing is the correct response.
'Cause I'll know better once you
tell me what you're talking about.
Your birthday.
Oh. Anger was a bad guess.
Well, normally I'd put on a
festive hat and celebrate the
fact that the earth has circled
the sun one more time.
I really didn't think it was gonna
make it this year, but darnit,
if it wasn't the Little Planet
That Could all over again.
It's a birthday.
It's an excuse to be happy.
You think that's lame?
Why are you here?
To buy me a pony?
I'm just waiting for the surgery.
Yeah well, go scrub in.
All right, done. Close her up.
That tumor didn't just
walk itself into a bar
and order up a double shot of ethanol.
Someone shrunk it down.
I'm sorry.
It was very, very wrong.
House is lucky I didn't just close her up.
He tries again, that's what happens.
I'll pass it on.
It looks like the surgeon got it all,
but she's gonna have
to have some chemotherapy.
What kind is it?
Luke, stop writing.
If you stop for a second,
it's not all gonna fall apart.
Give yourself a break once in a while.
The fact is, your mum's gonna have
an extra drink every now and then.
No. No, she won't, she doesn't.
Fine.
There are some things you just
can't fix, that's all I'm saying.
That's how you'd handle
it, something like this?
You'd just give up?
No.
I'd do it just like you.
It's an infusion.
She's gonna have a drain in her abdomen,
you're gonna have to check
for possible infections.
Lucas Palmeiro?
Trina Wyeth,
Child Services, State of New Jersey.
Can I help you?
This is a private room.
He's only 15 years old, a minor,
he's in a tough living situation.
We're just here to help.
I don't need your help.
15?
Lucas, you're gonna have
to come with us. Right Now.
Where are you taking him?
Until the determination had been made
he'll be housed at Children's Services.
I don't wanna be housed,
I live with my mom.
Not for the next few days.
Come on, let's not make
this difficult, huh?
Mom?
I love you.
The Mets lost. You remember?
Yeah. I remember.
I love you.
Cuddy didn't say anything about
pushing Bergen to finish the surgery?
Not a word. Some kind of mind game.
She's waiting for me to crack.
Well, either that, or
she's just being nice.
Yeah, right...
You said you wouldn't call.
You're a real bastard, you know?
Yeah. I get that a lot.
I don't think Mom's crazy.
For in the old days,
Though she had young men's
praise and old men's blame,
Among the poor both old and
young gave her praise.
You called Social Services.
It was you.
No, no. No.
It's OK, it's OK, I get it.
He'll have an easier time
dealing with the system.
Sure, he won't be with his real mother,
but his real mother's sick.
Someone needs to take care of him.
I'm not gonna live here.
What would his future have been?
Taking you to chemo
and back on the bus...
and even if the cancer's
in complete remission,
he'll still have a mother who hears voices.
Talk no more, talk... no more.
"Look what I do to him, limpie."
You said that.
I checked the phone records.
Only one call from this room.
Smart. They charge you two bucks a call.
It was to Social Services
of the State of New Jersey.
You're his mother.
Couldn't do it to him anymore.
Good for you.
Schizophrenics can make rational decisions.
On the small stuff, yeah, when to
sleep, what to drink, you know,
no lemonade but I'll take some
hemlock if you've got it.
Your man Socrates.
But giving up your son,
because it's better for him.
It's so sane, so rational.
Self-sacrifice is not a symptom of
schizophrenia... it excludes the diagnosis.
She's not schizophrenic?
She's 36 years old when
she first presents...
It's a little late, but
within the parameters.
The internist sends her to a shrink,
one shrink sends her to the next,
she tells them all she's
not crazy, the drugs don't
work and why would they
if she's not a head case?
She got clearer when I took
her off the psych meds.
You think I'm crazy.
Well, yeah, but that's not the problem.
Didn't we just leave your office?
I like to walk.
Is that Dr. Jeffrey Walters?
Hi. My name is Greg House, I'm a doctor...
Oh, is that the time? Yeah, I'm sorry,
my watch must have stopped.
Listen, you treated a
patient about eighteen
months ago, a woman
named Lucille Palmeiro,
I wondered if you recalled
running any tests...
at all.
Oh, how terribly foolish of
me, doctor, is it that late?
Yes, I'm calling from London, you see,
must have got my times mixed up so...
I have a headache.
It's my only symptom.
I go to see three doctors.
The neurologist tells me it's an aneurysm,
the immunologist says I got hay fever,
the intensivist... can't be
bothered, sends me to a shrink,
who tells me that I'm punishing myself
'cause I wanna sleep with my mommy.
Maybe you're just not getting enough sleep.
Pick your specialist,
you pick your disease.
If it's not schizophrenia, what
else presents with psych symptoms?
Prophyria.
The madness of King George.
What about that copper thing?
What's it called?
It's genetic... the body
accumulates too much copper.
Oh, uh, Wilson's disease?
Yeah.
Very rare. Nice. I like it.
If any of us did this, you'd fire us.
Well, that's funny, I thought I
encouraged you to question...
You're not questioning, you're hoping,
you want it to be Wilson's, boom!
Give her a couple of drugs, she's OK!
July 17, an appointment with a Dr. Carne.
She didn't keep it. She
never kept another
appointment with a shrink
he made after that.
Carne is not a shrink.
I looked him up, he's an ophthalmologist.
Now why would she want her eyes checked?
Wilson's presents with cataracts, I think.
Yes, it does.
It also causes slight cirrhosis, which Dr.
Chase so eagerly attributed to alcohol.
So what are we still doing here?
Lucy!
I don't think you're crazy.
Neither do I, but I'm crazy...
Come on.
Put your hands on the bar here,
and your chin in here. Thank you.
You're gonna see a bright light, OK?
Your body might be
accumulating too much copper.
If it is, this should help us see
something called Kaiser-Fleischer rings,
copper-colored circles around your corneas.
Well, I guess we should start
treating her for Wilson's.
It's what I'd do.
I will talk no more of
books or the long war.
But walk by the dry thorn until I have found
Some beggar sheltering from the wind,
and there, manage the talk
until her name come round.
If there be rags enough
he will know her name.
And be well pleased remembering it,
For in the old days, though she had
young men's praise and old men's blame,
Among the poor both old and
young gave her praise.
Hi, Mrs. Palmeiro, ready to go home?
Almost.
Mom?
How are you?
I'm good.
Oh, you really need a haircut.
Dr. House!
Luke, you're making Dr. House wait!
That's OK, we're just here for the music.
Luke, come on.
I'm being discharged.
I heard a rumor.
Thank God I had cancer, huh?
It's terrible having everybody
think you're nuts...
Really?
I called to thank you,
did you get my message?
Yes. You're welcome.
I'm never thanking you.
You turned me in.
I told you we were doing OK,
it was none of your business.
Look. I don't care how you were living.
I just wanted you out of my life.
That's why I had Dr. Cuddy
call Social Services.
You OK?
You were right. It wasn't the DVT.
It was the schizophrenia.
I know.
She's not nearly as interesting any more.
Isn't it your birthday around now?