I gotta go.
No, no, he'll be here.
I'm sure he's just running a little late.
He's cancelled two exams,
he's not gonna...
He's scared of you.
Sure. The ex-boy-toy.
Eh, that makes sense.
He wasn't scared before.
Right, you think being afraid of me
is a symptom of a serious ailment.
Sudden mood swings,
infantile regression,
abdominal pain, he's
passed out twice, yeah!
I think it might be a medical problem.
He's twenty minutes late.
I'm outta here.
Please.
He'll be here.
Why? Because he loves you
and does everything he's told?
Because I didn't tell him
you'd be here.
He likes to see.
Yes, he does.
Stace?
What's going on?
Hey...
Hi. I'm Gregg House.
You must be Matt.
Mark.
Mark Warner.
Don't get up.
Sorry, pair of conferences.
- It's okay.
- Hi.
Wow. Gregg House.
Yeah. Wow.
No, I haven't been avoiding you,
I just didn't want to waste your time.
The other doctors checked me out
and they said it was just stress.
College season, kids,
parents, they're all over me.
Makes sense to me.
Gregg...
What do you want me to do?
You said you'd check him out!
He says he's healthy.
What's to check out?
Sorry for the mix-up, but I'm glad
you two got a chance to catch up.
Looks like you're having fun.
Oh, he's good.
If you can fake sincerity,
you can fake pretty much anything.
I can't tell you how
much I like your fella.
Yeah, me too.
You know, I thought you'd be
all sarcastic, bitter, you know,
because Stacy married me.
You know, we should do things together.
Maybe throw a ball around
or something. Guy stuff.
We could go for a run together.
He's Oscar Wilde!
Wow, this pissing contest is
really turning me on.
He needs to go to the hospital.
Here's to women.
You can't live with 'em,
you can't kill 'em
until the neighbors are stripping
in Atlantic City.
Damn straight.
I'm definitely taller.
I have more hair.
And I think that... oh...
Mark?
Someone call 911 for a wagon
to Princeton-Plainsboro?
Garcon!
What happened?
It's okay, ladies and gentlemen,
nothing to worry about.
Unless you had the veal.
You dosed him!
I told you, I'd check him out.
I was a little worried they were gonna
get here before he'd passed out.
Would have been tougher
to get him to drink.
I'll give you a ride.
We can talk.
Tummyache, cranky,
no apparent source.
Any thoughts?
Foreman, you gonna contribute,
or you too tired from stealing cars?
I'm being House. It's funny.
I know. You made milk come out of my nose.
Morning. You guys got the file?
What's wrong?
Previous tests revealed
of nothing that would cause
abdominal pain or the mood swings.
Then we're done!
What do you think,
ball game, zoo?
I don't care, I just want
to hang with you guys.
What about drugs?
His tox screen on admission showed
a massive amount of chlorohydrate.
Yeah, sorry, that was me.
I had to dope him up
to get him in here.
Guy doesn't think he's sick.
Who does?
His wife.
The woman you used to live with.
That's her Indian name.
On her driver's license it's Stacy.
I assume you have a point.
You believe her over the patient himself.
That's why we're taking this case.
The truth, I hear voices.
All the time.
Telling me to do stuff, it's crazy, huh?
What happened to "everybody lies"?
I was lying.
Do the things, the, you
know, blah blah blah
blah blah, all that stuff
the other docs did.
If that's negative, ultrasound his belly.
If that's negative, CT his abdomen and
pelvis, with and without contrast.
Did I miss anything?
Kitchen sink?
Well, we could certainly
give that a... oh, you minx.
What you're thinking is, you're going
to save him, be a hero, and win her back.
It's always impressive,
that level of twisted narcissism.
She's married.
Big clue I lost the game.
You can't be within
fifty feet of Stacy Warner.
I thought she wanted me to treat him.
Treat the husband.
Stay away from the wife.
But what if they get close to each other?
What do I do then?
Hey, you have to treat this
like a regular case.
Be yourself:
Cold, uncaring, distant.
Please, don't put me on a pedestal.
We CTed your abdomen. Nothing that
would explain the stomach pain.
What's the next move?
Leaving.
How many more tests do I need?
How many more doctors need to clear me
before we can get back to our life?
Just one.
House.
It must be awkward being treated by a man
who used to be involved with your wife.
Well, it's awkward being in a hospital
when there's nothing wrong with me.
MRAs were clean,
which means he's probably fine.
He doesn't seem paranoid,
he shows no signs of...
No, it means we have no idea
what's wrong with him.
Ben Goldstein says the schedule's locked.
He can't do it before tomorrow.
No, today. Call him.
Tell him I'll make it work.
You're cutting him open?
Whoa, hold it!
There's no need for exploratory surgery,
Dr. Cameron has a diagnosis.
No, I just think it's premature
and maybe irresponsible to
do exploratory surgery before
we know he's actually sick.
No, it's premature to put him
on a list for hospice care.
And it's maybe irresponsible to imply my
actions are not rationally supported.
All we have is his wife...
Who says that his stomach hurts.
Works for me.
The patient doesn't even think he's sick.
Why would he consent...
His wife's a lawyer.
She's very convincing.
Call Goldstein, surgery's on.
Leslie vs. Leslie seems to be right
in point, but I'm sure they're going
to try to distinguish it by...
Sorry, they'll try to distinguish it
by relying on the minority opinion.
Double milk, no sugar.
I like sugar now.
Some people would be
annoyed by that.
You know why people
sit in waiting rooms?
This is gonna be good.
People think the closer they're sitting to
the operating room, the more they care.
That's why I'm here.
I'm not moving
until everybody sees me.
Are you doing anybody besides Mark?
It's a medical question.
Because if I am his paranoia isn't
paranoia, it's a justified response?
Therefore, not a legitimate symptom?
Knew you'd understand.
On the other hand, if it
was really just a medical
question you would have
sent one of your people.
Why just push my buttons
when you can push theirs, too?
'Hey, Dr. Mandingo, go ask the wife
if she's been messing around.'
You were asking because,
if I am unfaithful, I might sleep with you.
The answer's
'no, I don't sleep around'.
Make sure you note that in his file.
Mrs. Warner. The surgery went well.
he's in recovery, you can see him now.
Goldstein found nothing
but a distended bladder.
Neurogenic bladder
isn't causing the pain.
Also doesn't cause
personality changes.
On the other hand, it would completely
account for Cameron's diagnosis...
the patient's completely healthy.
Give me the video for the surgery.
Dr. Mandingo, you're needed
at the plantation house.
Well, don't everybody talk at once.
There's nothing there.
Stop looking at the suspiciously
empty bottle and look at the screen.
Here's why I get the big bucks.
This is nothing.
An enhanced version of nothing.
This is the problem.
Unbelievable.
Tremors in the muscle fiber.
That's not peristalsis.
That's abdominal epilepsy.
Means there's some sort of
neurological problem.
A time bomb in his brain.
I forget, who said it was nothing?
Saw a very small diffuse abnormality
in the brain waves.
Probably white matter.
Means his axonal nerves are dying.
Explains the neurogenic bladder.
Enough nerves die, he dies.
Global axonal nerve death.
Likely causes are
encephalitis or Alzheimer's.
Early onset Alzheimer's. The worst.
He won't die right away.
He'll just want to.
We'll check his blood
for Alzheimer's protein markers.
Last I heard Alzheimer's
had a genetic component.
Patient have parents?
Parents died in a car crash.
No history of dementia.
Send CSF or CBC and viral serologies
to rule out encephalitis,
and get Tal proteins
to check for Alzheimer's.
And this still feels a little light.
I took a complete medical history.
Check out their house.
Take Sparky with you.
They live in Short Hills,
two hours away.
You can expense the tolls.
You're not interested
in the medical history.
You're a Peeping Tom
trying to spy on your ex.
Her secret diary:
That's the main thing.
But as long as you're there,
take a peek in the medicine cabinet.
Check for toxins, heavy metals...
anything that might
explain this other than
encephalitis or Alzheimer's.
And get receipts for the tolls!
Making lunch?
I assume that's for Mark.
You know about his parents.
What about further back?
Grandparents, uncles, aunts,
how's their health?
Gregg hates fishing.
He's got a theory.
Mostly likely candidate
right now is Alzheimer's.
No. There's been no memory loss.
I mean, he forgets where
he left his keys, but who doesn't?
Any family history?
Of? Whacked-outness?
His sister voted for Nader, twice.
That's about it.
You were with House?
When it happened? To his leg?
You're interested in him.
We went on one date.
It didn't go very well.
Our first date didn't, either.
I was never going to see him again.
Week later I moved in. 5 years.
What would you like to know?
What was he like before his leg?
Pretty much the same.
He's clear. No Alzheimer's.
Yeah, that's what I figured.
Serious mountain bike.
Hasn't been used in a while, though.
He switched to yoga.
Brand new yoga mat and tape.
Man's getting older.
Or it might indicate back pain.
Wife would have mentioned it.
Yoga's good for picking up the ladies, too.
Not when you do it in your own home.
The change could just be a change,
not a symptom.
Chase!
"Dear House boys, a snack
for your highly illegal search.
Hope you like oatmeal raisin. Love, Stacy."
Whoa.
In a desk drawer, hidden in the back
under some papers. Secret stash.
Amphetamines.
Regularly used,
could lead to neurotoxicity.
Explains the axonal nerve damage
and the personality issues.
On the other hand,
prescribed to W. Brown.
Fake name, fake prescription.
Could be, but the prescribing doc,
his name's real. This guy's
just had his license pulled
for writing illegal prescriptions
to high school kids.
Mark's a high school guidance counselor.
And Mr. Brown's birth date
makes him 17-years-old.
You think maybe these were confiscated
by a high school guidance counselor?
Anything else?
Uh, yeah, he switched from mountain biking
to yoga, could have been indication...
He's getting older.
What did the CSF say about encephalitis?
Said no. Champagne tap. No red cells,
no white cells, serology's negative.
Which means we're back to Alzheimer's.
I told her he didn't have it.
The marker tests were negative.
Well, then you should have told her that.
He could still have it.
PET scan will reveal any
change in metabolic
activity in the cerebral
cortex, run him through.
And check his memory.
We're going to inject
a chemical marker called FDDNP.
Then I'm going to ask you
a series of questions.
Test my memory.
Yeah. First we're gonna map out
some specific brain functions,
check out the engine before
we take the car for a drive.
Checking up on me?
I like all the pretty lights.
Yeah.
Okay, here we go. Your full name?
Mark Warner.
Is your mother living?
No.
Limbic system's intact.
Okay, say you find a stamped envelope
on the street. What do you do?
Find a mailbox and mail it.
Jeez, what a guy.
His frontal lobe is working
way better than mine.
You remember when you got married?
Three years ago this July, who is that?
What? There could be a problem
with his long-term memory.
- Big church wedding?
- Is that House?
He remembers voices.
This serves no diagnostic purpose.
I thought you skimped
on the limbic system, there.
Emotional reactions,
I just want to be thorough.
Did the atheistic bride wear
a pretty, white dress?
Was she thinking of you?
Is that what you medically need to know?
What jewelry did your bride wear?
She never wears any jewelry.
Except that cross her mother gave to her.
No underwear, either.
At least, not that day.
I remember because she ripped
her pretty, white dress off in the car.
Is that the sort of answer
you're looking for, Doctor?
I think I upset him.
You gotta to stop this, now.
I remember the honeymoon was in Paris.
I remember because we didn't
leave the room for two weeks.
You want the details on that?
A little defensive.
It's not paranoia
if someone's out to get you.
Here we go.
He's sick, paranoid, and you keep
hammering him about me?
The questions were
designed to define
the operational parameters
of his limbic system...
Elevate the words all
you want, you were just
screwing with him. Low
even by your standards.
Medical screwing.
It's what I do.
And then you run away
like a 12-year-old.
Go hide on the roof
like you always do.
I haven't been up here in five years.
I don't know what's wrong with him.
It's not Alzheimer's,
it's not encephalitis,
it's not environmental,
it's not immunological.
Every test is negative, every time.
He's perfectly healthy,
but his brain is dying.
It never occurred to me that
you couldn't figure out what's wrong.
I haven't given up.
So what do we do?
We wait.
For what?
Something to change.
It's one of the great tragedies of life,
something always...
something always changes.
Nurse! Nurse!
What happened? What's wrong?
My toes. They were numb,
tingling, then nothing.
No pain, nothing.
It's okay.
They're gonna take care of you.
I'm scared, Stacy. Hold my hand.
What?
What's happening?
Time marches on. He's paralyzed.
His symptoms mimic
a peripheral nervous system under attack.
But he's experiencing
significant paresthesias,
and he can't move
his hands or toes.
It's peripheral. Guillain-Barre
syndrome attacks there, not the brain.
No, no. I already did an
indirect Coombs' test.
No glutination, no antibodies!
Initiative! Like that.
Start him on IV immunosuppress?
No antibodies means
he doesn't have Guillain-Barre, period!
Period? More like dot dot dot.
What if he has the virus but
isn't producing those antibodies?
Come on, the chances of that are...
I didn't ask about the Vegas line,
I said "what if?"
It would mean he's sick and
his body's not doing anything about it.
So we either fight it
for him or it's fatal.
Fatal sounds very bad to me.
But without the antibodies
we can't even test for it.
We don't know if we're right.
The treatment isn't all that dangerous,
plasmapheresis and IVIG.
If it works, we're right.
If he dies, it was something else.
So the paralysis
might not be permanent?
That's our hope, but the brain's tricky.
You never know.
What was that?
What?
With the head, the look.
He just wants to talk to me.
Well, if it was medical
he should be talking to me!
I'll be just outside the door.
Leave! Go talk to him!
You're gonna leave me anyway!
No, that's not gonna happen.
You left him, and he had a limp. If I can't
walk, or hold you...
Honey, I'm not going anywhere.
I'm not going to talk to him.
If I can't feed myself?
Mark, what you're feeling,
it's not real. It's the virus.
Mark? His throat's closing up,
he can't breathe. Code blue! Hurry!
He's having a reaction
to the IVIG, I need epi stat!
I can't get the scope in his throat!
Stop that.
He's having an allergic reaction
and he's crashing!
No, he's not. Look at his vitals.
O2 stats are within range.
I'm betting the only abnormal sign
is sweaty palms.
Push two milligrams Ativan.
Not an allergic reaction.
Just a panic attack.
Something obviously freaked him out.
Can we talk now?
You couldn't just come into the room?
He's had five visitors drive down.
I didn't recognize any of them.
Six more have sent him
flowers, candy and a teddy bear,
which I'm sure he
finds very comforting.
But I didn't recognize
any of the names on the cards.
Shockingly, Mark has friends,
and I have some new ones.
No, it's not shocking
that you have new friends.
But it is shocking that
you apparently dumped all your old ones.
I haven't.
No, I didn't think so.
I just think you didn't tell any of them
that you were down here.
Now why would that be?
Why would you not tell your oldest friends
that you were taking Mark
to Princeton-Plainsboro.
Teaching Hospital to
try to save his life?
I've been busy! I haven't kept
track of who knows what.
See, my old friends are
telling me to be careful.
They seem to think...
He. And he sent me the bear.
Figures. He seems to think
that I'm not over you.
And it might be dangerous
for me to spend time with you.
I'm thinking your friends
might have similar concerns.
And so you didn't tell him
you'd be here, with me.
What's your point?
That I'm still in love with you?
I should abandon my dying husband
and we should head for Rio?
No.
Gregg, I appreciate what you're doing
for us, but I think maybe Wilson's right.
Maybe you should just
stay away from me.
What's up?
Love the bear, it was adorable.
My wife's going to kill me.
We're having company, she cooked.
I got Mark's latest blood work,
he's not responding to treatment.
I'm sorry.
I was happy.
He's my patient.
I'm sure he's a good guy,
he's probably a great guy.
Probably a much better guy than I am.
And some part of me wants him to die.
I'm just not sure if it's because...
I want to be with her
or if it's because I want her to suffer.
Hey. Is it okay if I talk
to Stacy for a minute?
I'll be just outside, honey.
You two are good together.
You know nothing about Mark.
He took you to Paris,
that's good enough for me.
We never went to Paris.
Your honeymoon.
It's been your dream
city, you wanted to go
since you were sixteen,
he actually took you.
No, I had to work.
We spent the night in New York,
then went back to Short Hills.
What is it?
When did Mark switch
from mountain biking to yoga?
About a month ago.
The same time he started getting sick,
what is that mean?
We have two more symptoms.
Patient was asked a series of questions to
determine the functionality of his brain.
You grilled him about Stacy.
Whatever.
Yeah, point is he told us everything
we needed to know to diagnose him,
that is if we use your
fancy PET scan as a lie detector.
See, it's a very creative process, lying.
Now, telling the truth is
a much simpler process. See here.
Question nine, this is
where Mark gives a long,
rambling answer about
taking Stacy to Paris.
What does the PET scan say?
Minimal involvement.
Just the frontal and temporal lobes.
He said he went to Paris and
the PET confirms it, so what?
They didn't go.
They didn't go to Paris,
and yet Mark's brain apparently
thinks that he really
did spend 40 francs on a
tour of the Bastille.
So we have an intermittent syndrome
that presents with
abdominal pain, polyneuropathy,
paranoia and delusions.
Now, here's the thing about
Acute Intermittent Porphyria.
It'll jump you in a dark alley, beat the
crap out of you, leave you bleeding.
But it leaves gloves,
so no fingerprints.
Doesn't show up in blood tests,
urine tests, nothing.
Unless you catch it red handed
in the middle of an attack.
But there are other symptoms of AIP.
Such as?
Light sensitivity?
Yeah, well, one of the true tragedies
of this condition is it makes
you want to stick your cool, new
mountain bike in the garage
and take up an indoor
sport like, say, yoga.
Start the treatment:
Hematin and glucose.
If you give him hematin now and
you're wrong, he dies today.
There's only one way to confirm AIP:
Urine sample made during the attack.
And there's no way to predict
when he'll have another attack.
Sure there is.
Acute Intermittent Porphyria
has very specific triggers.
Barbiturates, alcohol,
high levels of protein set off an attack.
Which trigger do you think set off Mark's?
Not the faintest idea, that's why I'm going
to give him the combo plate. All of it.
So if he has this, and you trigger the
attack, the attack makes him worse. Right?
Yeah. But then we'll know
what it is and we can treat it.
What if I don't have this thing
and you give me that shot?
What happens?
No idea. If we don't know what's messing up
your brain we don't know how you'll react.
Okay, I need a minute
with my husband.
He doesn't want the trigger.
He wants to wait, see if we can
come up with another explanation.
If it is the AIP,
how much time does he have?
No idea. Next attack could be fatal.
Could be six months from now,
could be five minutes from now.
I want you to test him.
Fine. I'll send for a HMB
synthetase mutation, genetic test.
Lab will get back to us in a month.
Give him the cocktail,
set off an attack.
No.
Why not?
Because he doesn't want me to.
I'm not going to sue you.
I'm not going to report you.
He might.
He's paralyzed! Either you cure him,
or he won't be writing any letters.
I'm not gonna do it.
Why not?
You keep asking me that question.
my answer doesn't change.
I gave him the parameters,
it's his call.
- You want him to die.
- I diagnosed him, I did my job.
You want somebody to tie him
down and force him into treatment,
well, you're way
better at that than I am.
Is that what this is?
Payback for your leg? How many times have
we been over this. I saved your life.
Yeah, maybe.
You're going to kill my husband
to teach me a lesson?
No, he's going to die because
he's too stubborn to make the right choice.
Now we're in your territory.
I'm respecting your husband's decision, I
don't see why you've got a problem with that.
Because it's crap!
Because you browbeat patients,
intimidate them, lie to them.
If you think you're right
you don't give a damn what they think.
I did what you do all the time,
the only difference is I did it to you.
He'll never forgive you.
Yeah, he will.
Still no change.
He's not getting worse?
No, no change at all.
And that's consistent with AIP, right?
Until he has another attack
his condition's stable?
Yeah.
Mark, you've got to...
I don't want to take that test.
Not until they're sure.
- You don't know Gregg.
- Not like you do.
I only met him
when he drugged me.
Boy, are my ears burning.
What's that?
Cocktail hour.
Just because you can't hoist a few
doesn't mean you should be left out.
Get away from me.
Mark, this is what he thinks
is wrong with you.
You trust his judgment
more than mine?
His medical judgment.
And you'd bet my life on that.
I would.
I don't.
Smart. It's too bad you're paralyzed.
Bing! Paging Dr. Foreman!
Leave the room.
- It's not your problem.
- You need the consent from him.
Doc, he ain't right in the head!
Then you need a court order.
Okay, then get one.
We'll wait here. I won't do nothin'.
Oh, love the Musketeer thing.
I got goosebumps.
Give me the syringe.
Please, if you're right
this may be his only shot.
So what's your plan?
You take the big, dark one,
I've got the little girl
and the Aussie will run like a
scared wombat if things turn rough.
I can't do it.
You son of a bitch!
See what I did there?
When does it happen?
If he had AIP, it should have
already happened.
Everyone's different.
This is not good. He could have
embolism, tachycardia, stroke...
What's happening?
Two milligrams of Ativan!
Is that an attack?
No, you'll pollute the sample!
Chase, get urine
from the catheter.
It's not an attack,
he's stroking!
He needs Ativan!
This is not a stroke! Delta wave
bursts just at the base of the spasm.
Catheter's out, there's no way
to collect the sample.
Heart rate's in the 40s,
bradycardia, we're losing him!
- Hold him down!
- Give him something!
- No pain killers!
- You were wrong!
Straight from the bladder,
that's as fresh as it gets.
Will you give him the Ativan already?
He doesn't need to be awake for this.
It's still yellow.
Move.
What?
You think another light's
gonna make the difference?
Organic chem..
More lights, more oxidation.
Does it ring any bells?
Start the patient on 150 milligrams
glucose, 75 milligrams hematin.
Hey.
You want to thumb wrestle?
Come on.
- He's still a maniac.
- I know.
Dr. House? How's he doing?
Never better.
I thought you were
too screwed up to love anyone.
I was wrong.
You just couldn't love me.
It's good.
I'm happy for you.
You fixed him.
De nada.
Thank you.
You were right.
He's gonna be fine.
No, about me.
I'm not over you.
You were, you were the one,
you always will be.
But I can't be with you.
So I'm the guy,
but you want the other guy,
who by definition can never be the guy.
What's so great about you?
You always think you're right.
What's so frustrating about you is
you are right so much of the time?
You are brilliant,
funny, surprising, sexy...
but with you I was lonely, and
with Mark there's room for me.
Okay.
I want to run something by you.
I will not have sex with you!
Not again! Miserable, that first time.
All that desperate,
administrative need...
Stacy's husband is going to need
close monitoring at the hospital.
And since we can definitely
use her back here,
I've offered her a job.
General Counsel.
Did she say yes?
She said only if it was okay with you.
Yes or no?
Fine. Good.