Did I say anything stupid?
I had two drinks!
Three!
Okay, there was that last one.
That's okay, some day you'll be pregnant
and you can return the favor.
I feel like such an idiot sometimes.
No!
You know, when the baby
comes I am gonna be...
You know what?
You are going to be so great. You are.
Hey!
Oh.
You all right?
Oh, no.
You know why I pulled you over?
I'm so sorry, Officer,
I must have, dozed off.
Have you been drinking?
No.
Of course she hasn't.
- Somebody has.
- I've been drinking.
You all right?
I, I'm not, I, uh...
How far along are you?
Uh, almost...
Ma'am, step out of the vehicle.
Ma'am, walk to the rear of the car.
Naomi, are you... Naomi?
- Naomi...
- Sir, remain in the car!
- Hey, listen, she's not drunk, all right?
- I will arrest you, sir.
- She's sick!
- Badge 302,
- can you roll me another unit?
- Just look it! She's not...
Get back in the car.
Naomi!
Call an ambulance!
Well, the good news is, it doesn't look
like a stroke. No bleeds, no clots.
Thank God.
It sounds like there's bad news.
Why, what would cause that?
It's preeclampsia, isn't it?
I'm gonna miscarry, aren't I?
Preeclampsia is a possibility, but
let's not get ahead of ourselves.
I've miscarried three times,
I'm 39, we had to use in vitro, you've
gotta make sure that the baby's okay...
Let's make sure that you're okay, first.
How about we take care of
both of you at the same time.
The nurse will be in soon to take some
blood. I'd like to run some more tests.
Thank you, Doctor.
Thank you.
Where is everybody?
No one's in the office?
No, haven't heard
from Cameron all day.
You seen House?
Look for a shallow grave
with Vogler standing over it.
You have a Stage 4 cancer.
It's metastasized to your liver.
There's a new drug called 8C 12
that's shown promise in Phase 2 trials.
It's your best shot.
Thank you, Doctor.
You've been so good to me.
Well, I did publicly bash
your company's drug.
When I think about how I treated you...
Oh, hey, come on.
There, there, there.
So, there is some hope?
Always.
But just in case, I special-order
an extra jumbo-size coffin.
Hey!
Don't thank me.
It's just who I am.
Hey!
Up and at 'em, big guy.
Sorry, up late. Internet porn.
How come you're not in your office?
Because there is a computer in my office.
If I log on, romance will ensue.
My wrist might fall off.
Hiding because Vogler's
looking for you.
That's just pathetic.
I don't like loud, angry giants
threatening me with violence.
How is that pathetic?
You think you can avoid firing
one of us by hiding out here?
He'll find you sooner or later.
I'm okay with later.
39-year-old female,
28 weeks pregnant, G 4, P 0.
Three miscarriages?
Gimme.
Altered mental status and
complete loss of coordination.
Tox screen?
Negative for alcohol and drugs.
She was on oxybutynin.
For incontinence.
We took her off, but no change.
BUN, creatinine are up,
LFT slightly elevated.
Preeclampsia.
Call the OB-GYN service
and rub some prayer beads.
BP's normal.
No preeclampsia in other pregnancies.
Because she didn't carry long enough.
The three miscarriages make me think
it's an underlying physiology.
Pregnancy-related autoimmunity.
Too bad that Cameron quit,
I could use an immunologist right now.
We'll see if you're right.
Check the blood.
Cameron quit?
Last night.
And do an MRA for vasculitis, too.
There is no way she quit!
She got fired because
you couldn't swallow your pride!
An ultrasound?
Excellent thought!
And put her on magnesium, too,
in case it is preeclampsia.
Sure.
Here, pussy, pussy, pussy.
I didn't do anything.
Exactly my point.
You wanted me to yell at him?
What the hell would
that have achieved?
What, is he going to jump into
his time machine and fix everything?
When a dog dumps on the floor,
do you pat its head and call it a genius?
No, you smack it
in the nose with a newspaper!
Dogs can learn things, House can't.
Coward.
Child.
Hey, there!
I brought my colleague
along to help out.
Hi, I'm Dr. Chase.
Hi.
Well, ultrasound looks good.
No sign of fetal distress.
So it's not preeclampsia?
Well, it still could be, but
it hasn't progressed, at least.
We're gonna put you on bed rest
and monitor the baby.
Okay.
We'll give you some potassium
and magnesium as well.
So, we should keep the fluids running for now and check her
again in an hour unless there are signs of fetal distress or...
Honey? Wha... uh, she's choking!
Lean forward.
What is, is she all right?
It's probably just some
muscle weakness.
What do you mean, probably?
Naomi, open up.
People choke,
it could be nothing.
You all right?
I can't, I can't, I can't even swallow.
She gets sick a lot but this, this
cold got really bad all of a sudden.
And the fever...
Shhhh, it's okay.
It's not a cold.
It's pneumonia.
Pneumonia?
Relax, pneumonia's her
second-biggest problem.
She has gone from the twenty-fifth weight
percentile to the third in one month.
Now, I'm not a baby expert but I'm pretty
sure they're not supposed to shrink.
Well, there's this diet we put her on
when we stopped breastfeeding...
But it's healthy, raw food. We're vegans.
Almond milk, tofu, vegetables...
Raw food. If only her ancestors
had mastered the secret of fire.
Babies need fat, proteins, calories.
Less important: Sprouts and hemp.
Starving babies is bad,
and illegal in many cultures.
I'm having her admitted.
Is she gonna be all right?
Antibiotics for the pneumonia,
IV feeding to get the weight up.
Don't worry, it's a vegan IV.
Don't see any signs of vasculitis.
Odd, since you're always
right about everything.
Could be a different auto-immunity.
Or you could bite me.
Oh, no.
Naomi, you okay?
I'm getting cramps.
Strong?
Yeah. Feels like my miscarriage.
It's preterm labor.
He's too little, he won't survive!
She's on magnesium already.
Fuse interbutoline, then.
We're going to give you some medicine,
okay? Try to stop your labor.
Okay. Okay.
There you are,
I've been looking everywhere for you.
Listen, you said I had to cut one of my people
if I didn't give that speech about your drug,
and in fairness to your point of view,
my speech really wasn't the one
you had in mind, so I've cut Cameron.
Now we're all squared away, right?
In the morning, I expect you in my
office with your letter of resignation
and plans for a public apology,
otherwise I'll destroy you.
So that's a 'no' on us
being squared away.
She might make it to full term.
Contractions are less frequent
and not well organized.
Great to see you back in the office.
I guess Vogler found you?
Yeah, we had a nice little chat.
I really should have kept Cameron.
She knew where to find the sugar.
It's what I said. Preeclampsia.
A little stress from the MRA,
she pops straight into labor.
What about the myasthenia?
Come on, she didn't seem that weak.
She choked, she couldn't even swallow.
What did she choke on?
Her food. The muscle weakness
isn't a symptom of preeclampsia.
What kind of food?
A little bit of cooked pear,
it doesn't matter! It shows weakness.
She choked on soft, wet pear.
Did she forget to take the bones out?
That's way past muscle weakness.
Did you do an upper endoscopy?
You think there's something
obstructing her esophagus?
We've gotta talk.
Oh. We've gotta talk.
And check her eyelids.
Check her eyelids?
Special board meeting today,
only one item on the agenda: You.
Well, enjoy the bagels. I'm untouchable.
Huh. Right.
Any vote to revoke my tenure has to be
unanimous. I've got you and maybe even Cuddy.
Oh, well that settles it.
Mr. Ruthless Corporate Raider
will be totally stymied, go home,
curl up on the floor of
his shower and weep.
What can he do?
I've got a contract.
Does it say how much
your team gets paid?
Where your parking space is?
If your car should be filled
with horse manure?
Vogler's smart.
He's got some plan to get you.
Does it involve candy?
Because I'm a sucker for chocolates.
She's doing better.
Oh, thank God.
Technically, Alexander Fleming.
He developed antibiotics.
Pneumonia's under control,
and from now on, what say you
go with human food. OK?
Absolutely, swear to God.
This time, that's your guy.
Rachel and Joel Kaplan?
Yes?
You're under arrest.
Give the right to remain silent...
What did we do?
You're being charged
with child endangerment.
What? How? We...
Starving your kid.
I'm from Social Services,
we're taking responsibility for your baby.
This is how Vogler's gonna destroy me?
What did he do, grease your cane?
He had my patients arrested.
No. He didn't, I did.
The nurses were concerned
and they called me.
There was evidence of abuse.
You took a big
legal risk by not calling Social Services.
Those parents were not
abusive, they're idiots.
Oh, well that's certainly a relief.
It was my call.
You made the wrong one.
You know, there's a new biography
of Quisling, I think you might like it.
Sure. No idea who that is.
Norwegian guy,
World War II, traitor.
The fact that I have to explain
this kind of takes the edge off my flow.
I was protecting you.
From what?
Cops aren't gonna bust me.
Disiplinary committee maybe
gives me a slap on the wrist.
And Vogler has an excuse
to get rid of you.
If I don't give him one,
he makes one up.
Vogler's just one vote.
He's gotta convince the other eleven of us.
I'm just trying to stop you from
making that extra easy.
Sean, do your wife's eyelids
look any different than usual?
Maybe one is drooping a little bit,
but you know, she's tired, so...
Naomi, can you open your mouth
for me and tilt your head back?
This is gonna be a little uncomfortable.
Yeah, there's swelling,
indenting the esophagus.
Is that why she choked?
We'll need to do an x-ray.
What? No, the baby...
you said no x-rays.
It's important.
She has a three centimeter mass
in her right upper lobe.
Maybe it's a granuloma.
No. There's no calcification.
It's small-cell lung cancer.
The tumor's starting to press
against your esophagus.
It hasn't metastasized,
but it has spread to other parts
of your lungs so we can't operate.
Wait, that doesn't make sense.
She had kidney failure
and brain problems...
Some cancer patients get what are
called paraneoplastic syndromes.
You were making antibodies
to fight the tumor.
They got sidetracked
and attacked other cells:
Your brain first,
then your liver, kidneys...
even the nerves that
control your eyelids.
That's called Lambert-Eaton syndrome,
it told us the tumor was in the lungs.
How bad is it?
Small-cell is the most
aggressive kind of lung cancer.
The five-year survival rate is
only about ten to fifteen percent,
which is why we need to start you
on chemo and radiation right away.
Not radiation, what about the baby?
You'll need a C-section before
you can start the treatment.
I can get you in first thing
tomorrow morning.
What are the chances my baby will survive?
Pretty good. Twenty-eight weeks,
so about eighty percent.
No, wait, that's one in
five chance he'll die?
I really wouldn't advise waiting.
Naomi, you've got to start
this treatment right away...
What happens if I wait?
Twenty-nine weeks, survival rate
is closer to ninety percent.
I'm not doing the radiation.
You'll die...
Listen, you know the chances, they're nothing,
but a few more weeks will save the baby.
Listen, you're depressed right now,
and you're not thinking right.
Sweetie...
Could you just, tell her, please?
This cancer moves quick.
The median survival's two to four months.
If you postpone, even for a week...
I'm sorry, honey.
As most of you know, Gregory House
recently gave a speech about me.
I'd like to return the favor.
Sorry.
Dr. Wilson.
I was hoping you were
going to miss this one.
A man is the sum of his actions.
Here are a few of Dr. House's.
He violated a DNR and
was charged with assault.
He brought a termite into
the OR and spat on a surgeon.
He accepted a Corvette from a patient who
was a known member of the New Jersey mafia.
Ed, look...
Edward.
You look at anyone's career,
you can find things that are...
These are the last three months.
He's personally had more complaints filed against
him than any department in this hospital.
Okay, he's screwed up.
He's miserable, and he should
probably reread the Ethics Code,
but it works for him.
He's saved hundreds of lives.
He is a drug addict who flaunts his
addiction and refuses to get treatment.
He is a disgrace and
an embarrassment to this hospital.
I'd go on, but it gets kinda mean,
so I'm gonna keep this simple.
House goes, or I go.
You shouldn't personalize this.
And by I, I mean my $100 million.
How's that for personalizing?
You gave us that money for a reason.
Are you really willing to throw it
all away because of one doctor?
Gregory House is a symbol of everything
wrong with the healthcare industry.
Waste, insubordination,
doctors preening like they're kings
and the hospital
their own private fiefdom.
Healthcare is a business,
I'm gonna run it like one.
I hereby move to revoke
the tenure of Dr. Gregory House
and terminate his employment
at this hospital, effective immediately.
Don't you think we should discuss this...
We just did.
We need time.
The vote is on the table. All in favor?
Dr. Wilson?
Opposed?
The motion is defeated.
Dr. Wilson, would you mind
leaving the room, please?
Excuse me?
We're gonna take another vote.
Well, first of all, you can't void my vote
by making me stand in the hallway.
And second, you should check the by-laws.
You need notice and at
least one business day
before you can reconsider any matter.
We're voting on a different
matter which you are...
conflicted out of.
How can I be conflicted?
This vote is whether to
dismiss Dr. James Wilson.
Naomi is refusing to have the C-section.
Her odds aren't good enough.
They do suck. Where's Wilson?
Paged him twice.
She does this,
she knows she's gonna die.
She's saving her child.
Cameron would point out that
people are capable of sacrifice.
Cameron isn't here.
Perhaps proving her point.
You think this woman is
making a rational decision?
I think people can
overcome their baser drives.
Pretty damn rarely. And not this
time, this is purely biological.
In evolutionary terms, the needs of
the next generation are more important.
You're saying she's making the right call?
Darwin is, I'm not.
The next generation is not my patient.
We have to raise the odds for Mommy.
And where the hell is Wilson?
He's the oncologist.
Good plan, cure cancer.
Surprised no one ever
thought of that before.
There he is. Dr. House!
You guys bust out?
We made bail.
They won't let us in our baby's room.
Weird. You'd think they'd
let you take her home
while they figured out if
you tried to kill her.
We're good parents, we fed her
whenever she was hungry.
Big meals. We had no idea
that diet was so bad for her.
The nutritionist said
it had everything she needed!
The kid who stacks the
free-range grapefruit
in your health food
store is not a nutritionist.
But my uncle is.
He went to college and everything.
Foreman, I need a CT scan on...
Olive Kaplan.
Seriously?
Olive Kaplan. Look for
abscesses or occult infections.
Bye.
Listen, Vogler's all about clinical trials
,
the hospital's chock full of them.
There's got to be something
for small-cell lung cancer.
What are you doing?
I got sacked.
Did you make a pass at Cuddy?
Told you, she only has thighs for me.
I voted to keep you.
So he's getting rid of every board member
who votes to keep me around?
Yeah, every one of us.
Just you?
Yeah.
But you're only off the board, right?
They couldn't have got
unanimous approval for you.
Brown from Oncology voted no,
so did Cuddy, Taylor and Peevey.
Eh, so you're off the board, big deal.
Frees up Wednesday nights for bowling.
You're still a doctor...
Yeah, getting dumped looks
great in Who's Who.
Vogler gave me the option of
resigning, and I took it.
Big of him.
I've got no kids,
my marriage sucks.
I've only got two things
that work for me:
This job and this stupid,
screwed-up friendship,
and neither mattered enough
to you to give one lousy speech.
They mattered.
If I could do it all again...
You'd do the same thing.
Well, you'll be gone soon, too.
Those clinical trials?
I'll make some calls.
Thanks.
It's not cancer.
It's not gonna kill me?
It's hemorrhoids.
But all that blood...
that can't be right?
Looks worse than it is.
Nice job of protecting me.
Can this wait?
His ass can wait.
You saved my job by sacking Wilson?
What did you think would happen
when you made that speech?
You think he would just pout for a
little while and we'd all forgive you?
You don't spit on the man
who signs your paycheck.
First Cameron, then Wilson... you're next.
Pull your pants up.
So it's about the money.
Of course it's about the money.
The money Vogler gave,
he could have bought a few jets,
maybe a baseball team, or just stuck it in
Chase Manhattan and collected interested.
But he gave it to us
to buy equipment, to do research!
You are a great doctor, House,
but you are not worth $100 million.
We've sequenced the DNA of the tumor cells.
P53 gene mutation and codon 55.
She's perfect for your trial.
She's pretty far advanced.
Well, you want easy cases,
you picked the wrong speciality.
Otherwise in good health?
Excellent.
When can she start?
Middle of next week.
Cancer's already stage 3,
it'd be a waste of time.
She can start in two days.
She can't start in two days!
She's pregnant!
She won't be in two days.
I've scheduled a C-section.
She'd still have to wait a month.
You can't take part in an trials
until 30 days after major sugery.
Well, it's definitely surgery, but major?
It's not your call.
Again, a question of interpretation.
You're scamming a doctor, now?
Come on, Vogler's looking for
any excuse to can you.
Oh, I think he's got
a big bag of those already.
These regulations aren't
just here to annoy you.
Okay? Doing this is
dangerous to the patient.
Well, I'll be sure to let her know that.
Care to join me?
Angiogenesis inhibitors prevent
the tumors from creating blood vessels.
Without blood, the tumor starves.
- That sounds great...
- What about the baby?
The treatment would be fatal to the baby.
I've scheduled a C-section
for this afternoon.
No.
It's in the trial phase right now,
but so far complete remission
in more than thirty percent of subjects.
I told Dr. Foreman I
didn't want a C-section.
When your chances of living were
less than a third of what they are now.
Well, the baby's premature, that...
Our pediatrics department has the
best neonatal ICU in the state.
No, his lungs, his brain, he's not ready.
And he could be fine!
You don't know what it's
like, raising a sick child!
His odds are much better than yours are.
You have to let them at least try this.
Talk to her.
Okay. Leave the room.
How long have you been
taking oxybutynin?
Since I was about twenty.
Incontinence is pretty uncommon
in a woman of your age.
It's even more bizarre
in a woman in her twenties.
I guess I haven't had the best luck
when it comes to my health.
Seems that way.
You said to your husband,
"You don't know what it's like,
raising a sick child."
You didn't say,
"You don't know what it would be like."
This is not your first child, is it?
And he doesn't know.
I was eighteen.
Got pregnant, got married.
I had the most beautiful
little girl, Grace.
She had infantile Alexander's disease.
I'm sorry.
For two years we watched her die.
My husband was,
my first husband was a, a great guy,
but after that I couldn't even look
at him without thinking of her.
I left him, I left my job,
I left everthing...
Very moving story.
Explains why you're being so selfish.
I'm willing to die
to protect my husband.
Because it's what you want.
Your husband wants you to live.
Well, he doesn't understand...
Oh, who the hell does?
Tragedies happen.
You think that turning
yourself into a disposable incubator
for a few weeks is going to protect
your baby from all the crap in this world
go ahead, die happy.
I got no problems with
people killing themselves,
but don't think it makes you a hero.
Okay.
You're scheduled for 4 P.M.
Yes, this is Dr. Lim.
Count down from ten.
Okay.
Ten...
Nine...
Eight...
That seemed kind of fast, is she all right?
She's fine.
Wake her up.
That was Vogler. Surgery's off.
Hey! You're killing her!
Really? See, I thought you
were the one trying to ram
her into a drug trial five minutes...
She knows the risks,
she was fully informed...
Well, the guy running
the study sure wasn't.
- Not his life, not his call!
- His study, his call!
Right, so she kicks off,
his number look bad.
The numbers look bad,
the study looks bad!
Which would cost you money!
Yeah and keep a life-saving
protocol off the market!
One person, one blip in the data!
You ever heard of the FDA?
They eat blips for breakfast!
One person should never endanger thousands!
Well, thank God you were here
to save all those lives!
The board's meeting again this evening.
Why don't you settle down?
Play some Game Boy.
Why don't you watch your soap?
I hear they're firing the
handsome doctor today,
boy, that should be a good one.
If we had the C-section anyway,
she could
still do the experimental treatment, right?
We'd just have to wait thirty days.
Assuming the doctor running the trial
isn't too pissed off to let her in, yeah.
And assuming I'm even healthy enough to...
Honey? Are you okay?
Stats are dropping. Down to the 80s.
Stay with us, Naomi.
What's going on?
We need you to leave the room.
Respiratory distress.
Could you just tell me what's going on?
We're trying to find out.
- Still kicking.
- Flash pulmonary edema?
Lungs are clear. There it is.
- Pulmonary embolus.
- Gotta get her to an OR.
What happened?
It's an embolism. A blood clot.
It's fairly common with lung cancer.
It's not a full saddle embolism,
so blood's still trickling through.
We've been able to get
Naomi breathing a little, but
we need to remove the clot, and we
need you to approve the treatment.
Yeah, of course
. Whatever you have to do, just do it!
It's not that simple.
Okay. The best course for the baby
would be an immediate C-section.
The longer we postpone,
the greater chance it'll have
brain damage from lack of oxygen.
Fine, whatever, just do it!
Here's the problem.
The C-section would be very,
very dangerous for Naomi.
Dangerous, like...
In her current condition, there's a
real chance she wouldn't survive.
I'm sorry.
Look, your wife's unconscious,
we need you to make a decision.
I just want her to live. No C-section.
Stats are still way down.
We've got to push the streptokinase.
Too risky.
Even if it dissolves the clot, she
could still bleed out anyway.
She's hemodynamically compromised.
It's not good for the baby.
Dad doesn't care.
Embolcine 250,000 units.
BP's dropping. Pressers!
We don't have time.
We've gotta suck it out.
Systolic BP's 80.
BP's stabilizing, O2 stats rising.
Did you get the clot?
I think so. She's stabilized.
How long was her oxygen at that level?
Ten minutes?
Brain function compromised?
Souldn't be but it will...
BP's dropping. Up the dopamine.
She's not responding. How much?
She's up to 30 micrograms!
Is she septic?
She's bleeding into her abdomen.
We won't be able to stop it.
I'll go talk to the husband.
No, you stay here. Keep her as stable
as you can for as long as you can.
She had trauma during the procedure.
She's bleeding into her abdomen.
There's nothing we can do. I'm sorry.
No.
I need you to okay the C-section.
Yeah, that's gonna kill her, right?
It probably will.
I can't do that.
She's dying either way.
I'm sorry, I'm...
Stay with me, Sean.
I need your okay on this.
She makes the decisions, and I'm...
Right, and that's gonna be tough
from now on, but this decision is easy.
You know what she'd want.
I can't do it.
You make this call,
only two things change.
One: Yeah, you feel guilty
for killing your wife.
Two: Your baby lives.
Naomi's baby lives.
Okay, okay.
He's out. Umbilical cord's clamped.
No respiration.
His lungs aren't opening up.
They aren't mature.
Come on, take a breath.
You know you can do it.
What've you got?
Looks like v-fib.
Pulse?
No. Paddles!
Come on, come on.
Clear!
Nothing.
Charging.
Come on, open up.
How's he doing?
He's still not breathing.
We've got to intubate.
Clear!
Thank you.
I'm late for the board meeting.
- We need to talk.
- I don't want to hear it.
It's about a patient.
The pregnant woman?
She wasn't qualified for that trial
and I'm not going to apologize...
I'm not talking about her.
At this point I think it's best that I
concentrate on patients who are still alive.
Pulmonary embolism.
She bled out. Saved her son.
This is Olive Kaplan's CT scan,
the incredible shrinking baby.
Her thymus gland...
DiGeorge Syndrome.
It's genetic, can cause the
gland to wither to nothing.
This is why she couldn't gain weight.
Yeah.
I'll call the police and Social Services
and have all the charges withdrawn.
I've sent a test down to confirm.
When it comes back you should start
Olive on immunoglobulin replacement.
You're not going to do it?
I assume I won't be here.
Your boy's doing good.
It's the same motion as yesterday,
people, same reasons.
All those in favor of dismissing
Gregory House raise a hand.
Dr. Cuddy, you realize
this is going to happen.
I can't do it.
You can't abstain.
I'm not abstaining, I'm voting no.
You've changed your mind since yesterday?
What did he do,
buy you dinner and roses?
Threaten to drown your dog?
He did his job.
Right. He saved another life.
Maybe.
Good for him. It's great.
It's not the point.
It's what we do.
And you could do it a lot better if you
didn't have to worry about some madman
running around the hospital
accountable to no one!
But that's not the choice you're giving us.
House won't listen to anyone...
And you're not accountable
to anybody, either!
Because you think you own us.
I move for the immediate
dismissal of Dr. Lisa Cuddy.
She's upset, we all are. Why would
you risk your career to save him?
If you think House deserves to go,
if you think I deserve to go,
Wilson deserved to go, then vote yes.
But if you're doing this because you are
afraid of losing his money, then he's right!
He does own you.
You have a choice.
Maybe the last real one you'll have here.
Cuddy is a genius,
convincing four people to give up
a fortune to save our sorry asses.
Dr. Cuddy!
The man of the hour.
What are you doing?
We're drinking. I would have thought
that was pretty obvious.
Well, to the great champion.
Saved you, saved Wilson,
saved the whole team.
Of course, none of them
would have needed saving
if you could actually get
along with another human being.
Thank you, Miss Buzzkill.
Well, you only cost us $100 million.
Could have saved some lives,
could have made a few jobs,
helped a few people. Yippee.
You voted to get rid of him.
The lesser of two evils.
You should be mourning.
I know I am.