All right, Jim,
your quarterlies
look very good.
How are things going
at the library?
Oh, I told you.
I couldn't close it, so...
So you've come
to the master for guidance?
(CHINESE ACCENT)
Is this what you're saying,
Grasshopper?
Uh, actually,
you called me in here.
But, yeah.
All right, well, let me
show you how it's done.
Yes, I'd like to speak
to your office manager, please.
Yes, hello.
This is Michael Scott.
I am the Regional Manager
of Dunder Mifflin
paper products.
Just wanted to talk to you
manager a manager.
All right, done deal!
(IRISH ACCENT)
Thank you very much, sir!
You're gentleman
and a scholar.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
My mistake.
(CLEARS THROAT)
That was a woman
I was talking to.
So.
She had a very low voice.
Probably a smoker.
So...
(CLEARS THROAT)
So that's the way it's done.
I've, uh, I've been
at Dunder Mifflin
for 12 years.
The last four
as regional manager.
Uh, if you wanna
come through here.
Ah, see, we have
the entire floor.
So this is my kingdom,
far as the eye can see.
Ah, this
is our receptionist Pam.
(IMITATING BAM-BAM)
Pam! Pam, Pam!
Pam Beasley.
Uh, Pam has been with us,
um...for...forever.
Right, Pam?
Well, I don't know.
If you think
she's cute now,
you should have seen her
a couple of years ago.
Reow, reow.
What?
Uh, any messages?
Um...yeah.
Just a fax.
Oh.
Pam, this is from corporate.
How many times
have I told you
I know...
that there's
a special filing cabinet
for things from corporate?
You haven't told me--
It's called
the wastepaper basket!
(BAWDY LAUGH)
Look at that!
Oh, look at that face.
People say
I am the best boss.
They go,
"God, we've never worked
in a place like this before.
"You're hilarious.
And you get the best
out of us."
Um...
I think that
pretty much sums it up.
I found it at Spencer Gifts.
* Shall I play for you
* Pa rum pa pum pum
(IMITATING DRUMS)
* I have no gifts for you
* Pa rum pa pum pum
(IMITATING DRUMS)
My job is to speak to clients,
um, on the phone,
about...
uh, quantities
and, uh, type of...
copier paper.
You know, whether
we can supply it to them,
whether they can, uh...
pay for it.
And, um...
(CLICKS TONGUE)
I'm--I'm boring myself
just talking about this.
Wassuuuup?
I still love that
after seven years.
Whasuuuup?
Whasuuuuuuuuuup?
Whassup?
Oh, wow.
(GROANS)
What?
Nothin'.
Okay, all right.
See you later.
All right.
Take care.
Back to work!
WOMAN:
Just try to reach him
sometime today.
Um, I don't know,
just before lunch.
That would be great.
MICHAEL:
Corporate really doesn't
interfere with me at all.
Jan Levenson-Gould--
Jan! Hello!
I call her
Hillary Rodham Clinton.
Right?
Not to her face, because, uh--
Well, not because
I'm scared of her.
Because I'm not.
But, um, yeah.
All right, was there anything
you wanted to add to the agenda?
Mmm...me no get
an agenda.
I'm sor--What?
I'm sorry?
I didn't get
any agenda.
Well, I faxed one over
to you this morning.
Really? 'Cause it didn't,
uh, I didn't--
Did we get a fax
this morning?
Uh, yeah, the one--
Then why--why isn't
it in my hand?
Because a company runs
on efficiency of communication.
Right? Just...
(IMITATES GUN FIRING)
Um, so what's the problem,
Pam?
Why didn't, uh,
why didn't I get it?
You put it
in the garbage can
that was a special
filing cabinet.
Yeah!
Uh, that was a joke.
That was a joke
that, uh,
was actually
my brother's.
And it was--
(LAUGHS)
it was supposed
to be with bills,
and it doesn't
work great with faxes.
Do you wanna
look at mine?
Yeah.
Yeah, I would.
Thank you.
Okay, since
the last meeting,
Alan and the board
have decided
that we can't justify
a Scranton branch
and a Stanford branch.
Oh, okay.
Michael, don't panic--
No, no, no, no.
This is good.
This is fine, excellent.
Michael, listen,
okay, don't panic.
Although alarm bells
are kinda going
ringy dingy dingy!
We haven't made
any decisions yet.
I've spoken to Josh
in Stanford.
I've told him
the same as you,
and it's up to either
you or him to convince me
that your branch
can incorporate the other.
Okay, no problem.
This does, however, mean that
there's going to be downsizing.
Me no wanna
hear that, Jan.
Because downsizing
is a bitch.
It is a real bitch.
And I wouldn't wish that
on Josh's men.
I certainly wouldn't
wish it on my men.
Or women,
present company excluded.
Sorry, uh...
Is Josh concerned
about downsizing, himself?
Not downsizing himself,
but is he concerned about
downsizing?
Ha ha ha ha!
QUESTION: How long
do we have to act--
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
Oh, Todd Packer.
Terrific rep.
Do you mind
if I take it?
Go right ahead.
Packman.
TODD:
Hey, you big queen!
Oh, that's not...
appropriate.
Hey, is old Godzillary
coming in today?
Um, I don't know.
I don't know what you mean.
Look, I've been meaning
to ask her one question.
Does the carpet
match the drapes?
Oh, my God.
Ohh!
That's...horrifying.
And horrible.
Horrible person.
So do you think we could
keep a lid on this for now?
I don't wanna worry people
unnecessarily.
No, absolutely.
Under this regime,
it will not
leave this office.
Just...like that.
(WHISPERING)
So what does downsizing
actually mean?
Well...
(WHISPERING)
You guys gotta update
your resumes,
just like I'm doing.
I bet it's gonna be me.
It's probably gonna be me.
Yeah, it'll be you.
I have an important
question for you.
Yes?
(LAUGHING)
Um, are you going to Angela's
cat party on Sunday?
Yeah. Stop.
That is ridiculous.
MICHAEL:
Am I gonna tell them?
No, I'm not going to tell them.
I don't see
the point of that.
As a doctor, you would not
tell a patient
if they had cancer.
Hey!
This is Mr. Scott.
Guilty!
Guilty as charged.
Ryan Howard
from the temp agency.
Uh-huh.
Daniqua sent me down
to start today.
Howard, like Moe Howard,
Three Stooges.
Watch this, this is Moe.
Nyuck! Nyuck! Nyuck!
Nyuck! Nyuck!
Meeeeh!
Ha ha!
Ah, right here.
Three Stooges.
High five!
Oh, Pam.
It's a guy thing, Pam.
PAM:
I don't think it would be
the worst thing
if they let me go.
Because then I might--
I just, I don't think
it's many little girls' dream
to be a receptionist.
Um, I like to do
illustrations.
Um, mostly watercolor.
A few oil pencil.
Um...
Jim thinks
they're good.
Sure. Uh, Mr. Davis,
let me call you right back.
Yeah, something just came up.
Two minutes.
Thank you very much.
Dwight,
what are you doing?
What?
What are you doing?
Just clearing my desk.
I can't concentrate.
It's not on your desk.
It's overlapping.
It's all spilling
over the edge.
ONE WORD, TWO SYLLABLES:
demarcation.
DWIGHT:
Downsizing?
Yeah, I have
no problem with that.
I have been
recommending downsizing
since I first got here.
I even brought it up
in my interview.
I say bring it on.
PAM:
You just still have
these messages from yesterday.
Relax, everything's
under control.
Uh, yeah.
There we go, yeah.
Oh, that's important.
Rrrright.
Oh, this is so important
I should run to answer it.
Sha-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta!
What?
Come on!
Six Million Dollar Man!
Steve Austin!
Actually, that would be
a good salary for me,
don't you think?
$6 million?
MEMO TO JAN:
I deserve a raise.
Don't we all?
I'm sorry?
It's nothing.
If you're unhappy
with your compensation,
maybe you should
take it up with H.R.
Okay?
Not today, okay?
Pam, just...
be professional.
(SIGHS)
MICHAEL:
I think I'm
a role model here.
I think I garner
people's respect.
Attention all Dunder Mifflin
employees, please.
We have a meeting
in the conference room
A.S.A.P.
MICHAEL:
People I respect,
heroes of mine, would be...
Bob Hope.
Um...
Abraham Lincoln.
Definitely.
Bono.
Uh, and probably God...
would be the fourth one.
And I just think
all those people
really helped the world
in so many ways
that it's, um...
it's really beyond words.
(MISPRONOUNCING)
It's really incalcalacable.
Now, I know there are
some rumors out there,
and I just kinda wanna
set the record straight--
I'm Assistant Regional Manger.
I should know first.
Assistant
to the Regional Manager.
Okay, um, can you
just tell me, please?
Just tell me quietly.
Whisper it in my ear.
I'm just about
to tell everyone.
Can't you just
tell us--
Please!
Okay?
Do you want me to tell them?
You don't know
what it is.
(CHUCKLES)
Okay, you tell them.
With my permission.
I don't need--
Permission granted.
Go ahead.
Corporate has
deemed it appropriate
to enforce an ultimatum
upon me.
And, uh, Jan is thinking
about downsizing
either the Stanford branch
or this branch.
Yeah, but, Michael,
what if they downsize here?
Not gonna happen.
It could be
out of your hands, Michael.
It won't be out of my hands,
Stanley, okay?
I promise you that.
Oh, can you promise that?
On his mother's grave.
Well...
No!
Well, yeah,
it is a promise.
And, frankly,
I'm a little bit insulted
that you have to keep
asking about it.
It's just
that we need to know.
I-I know.
Hold on a second.
I think Pam wanted
to say something.
Pam, you, uh...
had a look that you
wanted to ask a question
just now.
I was in the meeting
with Jan,
and she did say
that it could be this branch
that gets the axe.
STANLEY:
Are you sure about that?
Look, Pam...
Uh, maybe
you should stick
to the ongoing confidentiality
agreement of meetings.
Pam, information is power.
So...
STANLEY:
So you can't say for sure
whether it's gonna
be us or them, can you?
No, no, no, no.
Stanley, no.
You did not see me
in there with her.
I said if,
uh, if corporate
wants to come in here
and interfere,
then they're gonna
have to go through me.
Right?
You know, you can go
mess with Josh's people.
But I'm the head
of this family,
and you ain't gonna be
messin' with my chillun'.
If I left,
what would I do with...
all this useless
information in my head?
You know?
Tonnage price of manila folders?
Um, Pam's favorite
flavor of yogurt,
which is mixed berry.
Jim said mixed berries?
Oh, well, yeah,
he's on to me.
Um...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Watch out for this guy.
Dwight Schrute
in the building.
This is Ryan,
the new temp.
What's up?
Nice to meet you.
Introduce yourself.
Be polite.
Uh, Dwight Schrute,
Assistant Regional Manager.
Assistant
to the Regional Manager.
So, uh, Dwight,
tell him about the Kung Fu
and the car and everything.
Uh, yeah, I got a '78 280Z.
I bought it for 1,200,
fixed it up.
It's now worth three grand.
That is his profit.
Yeah, uh, new engine,
suspension.
I got a respray.
I got some photos.
Oh! Damn it!
Damn it! I--
Hold on, hold on.
Judge is in session.
What is the problem here?
He put my stuff
in Jell-O again!
(PAM LAUGHING)
That's real professional.
Thanks.
This is the third time,
and it wasn't funny
the first two times
either, Jim!
It's okay here.
Uh, but people sometimes
take advantage
because it's so relaxed.
I'm a volunteer sheriff's
deputy on the weekends.
And you cannot
screw around there.
It's sort of
one of the rules.
(LAUGHING)
What is that?
That's my stapler.
No, no!
Do not take it out.
You have to eat it
out of there,
because there are
starving people in the world,
and, which I hate,
and it it is a waste
of that kind of food.
You know what?
You can be a witness.
Can you reprimand him, please?
How do you know it was me?
DWIGHT:
It's always you.
Are you gonna
discipline him or not?
Ooh, discipline, kinky!
All right, here's
the deal, you guys.
Thing about a practical joke
is that you have to know
when to start
as well as when to stop.
And, yeah,
Jim, now is the time
to stop putting
Dwight's personal effects
into Jell-O.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Okay.
Dwight, I'm sorry,
because...
I have always been
your biggest flan.
(LAUGHS)
Ho ho ho, nice!
That's the way
it is around here.
It just kind of goes
round and round and round.
You, uh, you should have
put him in "custardy."
Oh, hey!
Yes!
New guy!
And he scores.
Okay, that's great.
I guess what I'm
most concerned with
is damage
to company property.
That's all.
Pudding.
Putting.
I'm trying to think
what other dessert to do.
(LAUGHS)
Do you like going out
at the end of the week
for a drink?
Yeah.
Well, that's why
we're all going out.
So that we can have
an end-of-the-week drink.
So when are we going out?
I don't know.
Tonight, hopefully.
Okay, yeah.
Hey, man.
Hey!
What's going on?
Hi, baby.
Hey.
Uh, Roy is my fiancé.
We've been engaged
about, um...
about three years.
And, uh, we were supposed
to get married in September,
but I think we're gonna
get married in the spring.
Do you mind if I go out
for a drink with these guys?
Uh, no, no,
come on.
Let's get out of here,
go home.
Okay, um, I'm gonna be
a few minutes, though.
It's only 20 past 5:00.
I still have
to do my faxes.
You know what?
You should come with us.
Because, you know,
we're all going out,
and it could be
a good chance for you to...
see what people are like
outside of the office.
You know, I think
it could be fun.
No, it sounds good.
Oh, no.
Seriously,
we gotta get going.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Um...what's in the--
what's in the bag?
Just tell her
I'll talk to her later.
No, definitely.
All right, dude, awesome.
Will do.
JIM:
Do I think
I'll be invited
to the wedding?
So, uh, have you
felt a vibe yet?
We work hard,
we play hard.
Sometimes we play hard
when we should be working hard.
Right?
Um, I guess the atmosphere
that I've created here
is that I'm a friend first
and a boss second.
Probably, uh--
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Entertainer third.
Just a second!
Right?
Oh, hey, do you, uh,
do you like
The Jamie Kennedy Experiment?
Yeah.
Punk'd and all
that kind of stuff?
Okay, um...
you are gonna
be my accomplice.
Just go along
with it, okay?
All right.
Just follow my lead.
Don't pimp me, all right?
Come in!
So, uh, corporate just
said that I don't want to--
You got a fax.
Oh, thank you, Pam.
Pam, can you come in here
for a sec?
Just have a seat.
I was gonna
call you in anyway.
Um, you know Ryan.
Um, as you know,
there's going to be
downsizing.
And you have made
my life so much easier
in that I am going
to have to let you go first.
What? Why?
Why?
Well, theft.
And stealing.
Stealing?
Mm-hmm.
Um, what am I supposed
to have stolen?
Post-it notes.
Post-it notes?
Yeah.
What are those worth,
like, 50 cents?
50 cents, yeah.
You steal 1,000 Post-It notes
at 50 cents apiece,
and, you know, you've
made a profit...margin.
You know, gonna run us
out of business, Pam.
Are you serious?
Yeah, I, um...
Oh, my--
I can't believe this.
I mean, I've never even
stolen as much as a paper clip,
and now you're firing me.
And the best thing about it
is that, uh,
we're not gonna have
to give you any severance pay.
Because that is
gross misconduct, and, uh...
So just clean out your desk.
I'm sorry.
(SNIFFLING)
You've been "Xed," punk!
Surprise!
It's a joke!
We were joking around!
(LAUGHS)
See?
Okay, he was in on it.
He was my accomplice.
And it was just kind of
a morale booster thing.
And we were showing
the new guy around, kind of--
kind of giving him
the feel of the place.
So you sh--
God, you were--
We totally got you--
You're a jerk!
Ah, I don't know
about that.
MICHAEL:
What is the most
important thing
for a company?
Is it the cash flow?
Is it the inventory?
Nuh-uh.
It's the people.
The people.
My proudest moment here
was not when
I increased profits by 17%.
Or when I cut expenses
without losing
a single employee.
No, no, no, no, no.
It was a young
Guatemalan guy.
First job in the country,
barely spoke English.
Came to me and said,
(SPANISH ACCENT)
"Mr. Scott,
would you be the godfather
of my child?"
Wow. Wow.
Wow.
Didn't work out in the end.
We had to let him go.
He sucked.
(SNIFFLES)
Hey.
Hi.
How are you?
Good.
I thought you were
going out for a drink with--
Oh, no, no.
Just going to, uh...
How's your headache?
It's better.
Thanks.
Good.
Good, that's great.
Is, uh--
Yeah?
Um, are you, uh...
Am I walking out?
Yes.
Do you wanna?
Yeah.
Great.
Let me just--
(CAR HORN HONKS)
Oh, Roy.
Yeah.
Listen,
have a nice weekend.
Yeah, definitely.
You too.
Enjoy it.
(DOOR CLOSES)