Possible homicide.
I'll call in forensics.
Previously on Long Bright River...
There might be a bad batch
of something out there.
We've noticed an increase
in ODs all over the city.
How do we know that they were ODs?
There wasn't enough of anything
in her system for it to be an OD.
So what was it?
- Insulin.
You want to know what's weird?
I have no evidence that she was diabetic.
You think somebody killed her?
The receipt that you found on
the girl down the A Street tracks...
...is from a gas station
outside of the airport.
The girl that OD'd this week
had a napkin from 7 Brothers.
Would Elizabeth have any reason
to be down at the airport?
She would have no reason
to be down there.
Help!
You talked to Truman lately?
No. Why?
Some of the guys were talking
about your last partner.
You two still talk?
- No.
How come? -We just don't.
Why are you pressing me on it?
Listen, what happened to these
girls, it's not their fault.
But we can't let all of them go.
She's my sister.
I'm worried about what you're going to find.
So am I.
He asleep?
Get some rest.
We'll talk in the morning. I...
I made up the couch for you.
Thanks.
Truman...
I'm sorry.
I didn't have your back that day.
I think I froze.
And I'm... I'm... I'm really
sorry that you got hurt.
It's the wrong apology, Mick.
Everybody makes mistakes. But
you didn't come around afterward.
You didn't come by the hospital.
Nothing.
It's been months,
and I didn't hear anything
from you until now.
And I thought we were friends.
That's your apology.
Mick, hurry up!
Jesus, were you asleep already?
It's, like, 9:00.
I'm working A-shift tomorrow.
I was gonna go to the gym.
Where's Simon?
He went down to AC.
Chinese food?
What's the occasion?
One year.
Mick, you trying to shake my hand?
I'm so sorry. No.
- You were trying to shake my hand.
Kace...
I told him, when you gotta go,
you gotta go.
He didn't believe that you were gonna do it.
Oh, my God. He was so mad at me.
You gotta tell Gee.
You gotta tell him.
Tell Gee what?
About your token.
It's a big deal, Kace.
- Mm-hmm.
He's not gonna care.
That's not true.
- Yes, it is.
You're the only one left who believes in me.
Is that Mom's?
Yeah.
I don't think I've ever seen it off your neck.
The clasp broke.
Oh.
- Happened once before.
I was four years old.
And I pulled it off her neck accidentally...
...when she picked me up.
She get mad?
No. She never got mad.
You don't remember?
You miss her.
Don't you?
Mm.
I can't remember her, Mick.
Yeah, like, not a single thing.
- What?
Yes, you do. You remember Mom.
You tell stories about her all the time.
Yeah,
but they're all your stories.
They're stories that you told me.
I wanna remember. I just don't.
Can I sleep in your room tonight?
Just tonight,
just while Simon's out.
Please.
Fine.
- Yes!
Thank you.
- Mm.
Mm.
Mickey?
What?
Thank you for letting me back in.
Next time,
don't forget your keys.
That's not what I meant.
Okay, so, remember.
Sugar...
...flour.
What else?
Uh, eggs.
Eggs. How many eggs?
Two. Three.
So...
...baking powder, pinch of salt...
...little bit of milk.
Okay, and you mix it up, and
that's how we get the batter right.
Right. So the key when
you're putting it in the pan,
is not to make 'em too big,
'cause if you do, then the batter
won't cook all the way through.
There you go.
What's this little fella's name?
Oh, that... that's Dun-Dun.
Dun-Dun, huh?
What does Dun-Dun want
for breakfast this morning?
Um...
Chocolate chip, blueberries?
I think Dun-Dun wants plain.
- Plain, all right.
Good morning, Mom.
These are great pancakes,
Thomas. You did such a good job.
Thank you.
Hmm. Mm.
How you likin' your
plain pancakes, Dun-Dun?
Oh, he... He doesn't talk.
What do you mean,
he doesn't talk?
You can't hear him?
Listen.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
I mean, we can agree to disagree...
...but I...
I like the blueberry ones.
He's getting so big.
Hmm. Tell me about it.
I can barely remember the girls at that age.
You know, you blink, and...
Yeah. Do you get to see them
that much these days?
Yeah. When they come home
from school, here and there.
But not...
...not as much as I'd like.
You gonna tell me what's going on?
It's Kacey.
How long's she been gone this time?
Like, six weeks.
Feels like just yesterday,
she was standing...
...in the supper line at St. Francis Inn.
And these victims,
any connection to Kacey?
Other than the fact that
they all worked the Avenue...
So Kacey has been missing six weeks.
And most of these girls' bodies showed
up days after they disappeared, right?
So?
- So maybe it's unrelated.
Kacey's gone missing before.
- I know.
But in Alonzo's video, Kacey was picked
up by a john in a red pickup truck.
I saw a red pickup truck
outside of my house,
and I think I saw a red pickup
truck in Kensington, too.
You think he's been
following you? -I don't know.
My landlord said that a guy
got out of the truck,
was asking about me, and she tried to
describe him. I have no idea who it is.
I thought it might have been Simon,
but he doesn't own a red pickup truck.
Let's assume it was a john that
picked up Kacey in that truck.
What the hell was he doing
outside your house? -I don't know.
I don't like this, Mick.
- Yeah, I don't like it either.
I gotta get going.
I gotta drop Thomas off at
Gee's house before I go to work.
Look, I'll... I'll watch him.
Really?
- Yeah.
He and Dun-Dun can
do my errands with me.
Thank you.
Yeah. Yeah, it's...
It's all right.
I'm gonna go and ask around
near the airport,
and see if anybody recognizes the victims.
Maybe it'll explain why those girls
were down there before they were killed.
I'll make some calls, too.
And see what Ahearn's saying,
behind the scenes.
Ahearn thinks they're all accidental
ODs. It's less work that way.
If it was just fentanyl and tranq...
...in the victims' systems, I'd
agree with him. But insulin?
That's a whole other ball game. Not
even Ahearn can turn a blind eye to that.
I'm going to say goodbye to Thomas.
Mick.
- Yeah.
I don't want you going back
to that house alone.
You need to tell someone at the
station about that red truck.
Ahearn's not gonna listen to me.
Make him.
Okay, folks, this is Detective Davis
Danger-rat of the East Detectives.
He's got a flash for youse.
I'll give him the floor.
Detective.
Danjarat.
Excuse me?
- It's pronounced Danjarat.
Okay.
Over the past several days, three
females in their late teens, early 20s,
have been found dead here, here and here.
Taylor Yoon, Elizabeth O'Connor,
and an un-ID'd third victim.
Time of death, sometime during
Halloween weekend.
All three were likely sex workers,
and all three were, at first, believed
to have died via opioid overdose.
However, all three were determined...
...to have lethal amounts
of insulin in their system.
Were they diabetic?
No. Either someone's putting
insulin in the supply these days,
or there may be a single
perpetrator of multiple homicides...
...at large in your district.
Maybe the killer was diabetic.
Could be. We're looking into anyone
recently arrested for solicitation...
...whose medical records
also indicate diabetes.
I know that's a long shot, but
we don't have much else to go on.
Just be on the lookout going forward.
Any rumors you hear,
anything suspicious you see,
please report it directly
to Sergeant A-hearn or myself.
Ahearn.
But now, more than ever,
all of you on patrol...
...need to keep your eyes open out there.
Ain't easy to tell a dead body from
your everyday nodder on the Ave.
Which is why we need to wake them up.
Make sure they're breathing.
Seems like it should be policy anyway.
Thank you.
All right, that's all.
Hey, hey. Can I talk to you a second?
Right... right now? -Please.
Yeah. I just have a quick question.
Well, I mean, more like an idea.
Yeah, yeah.
Just give me a second.
I'll... I'll...
I'll be right back.
Detective Danjarat, hi.
Sorry. I just... There's
something I have to tell you.
Uh, a couple of the
women from the Avenue...
...have been talking about seeing
this guy in a red pickup truck,
coming around and acting strange.
Have you heard anything about that? -No.
Well, they get a plate?
Make, model, any of that?
No, just a...
It's a red pickup truck.
Okay, well, thank you.
We'll keep an eye out.
You asked if the killer was diabetic.
It was my first thought, too.
We'll keep an eye out for that truck.
Thank you.
Possible domestic assault
in progress.31 G Street.
Come on.
56201 responding.
Hi, ma'am. I received a call
about a possible assault.
Did you make that call?
It wasn't me. I didn't call.
Well, somebody called.
Maybe it's somebody inside
with you. Maybe your kids.
Nope.
Uh, the laceration above
your eye looks pretty bad,
so I think you should get that checked out.
I could come in and take
a closer look if you want.
Laceration?
Who talks like that?
Just say 'cut.'
I'm sorry?
You don't remember me, do you?
I think you're thinking of a different person.
Mickey Fitzpatrick, right?
Kensington High School.
Mrs. Powell's history class?
First row?
Yeah.
- Yeah, well...
Fuck you, Mickey Fitzpatrick.
I don't need none of your help.
You always did think you were
better than everybody else.
Now, in a second,
I'm gonna teach you...
...how to arm and disarm
this thing. All right?
Okay.
- Okay.
Truman, why do we even need an alarm?
I mean, everybody should have one, really.
But it's just something that
will let the right people in.
And keep the wrong people
out, okay? You understand?
Do you have one?
No.
I'll get one, though.
Excuse me.
Hello, ma'am.
May I ask who you are...
...and what exactly you are mounting
to the wall I just had repainted?
He's my mom's friend.
He's installing a security system.
It lets the right people in,
and keeps the wrong people out.
Well,
thank you, Thomas.
And who exactly are the 'wrong people'?
Name's Truman.
Cecilia Mahon.
What a lovely name.
Well, thank you.
I told Michaela I didn't want
any trouble around here.
There's no trouble, ma'am.
Hey, Thomas.
You want to go finish up for me?
Okay?
I installed a camera outside.
It covers the whole property.
Can't be safe enough these days.
I suppose you're right, Truman.
But I'll tell you something.
I'm not convinced that Michaela's
not in some kind of trouble.
And if I'm being honest.
I worry about that little boy.
Is that Mickey?
No, that's not her.
- Fran, is that Mickey?
It don't look like her, Twohey.
She's bigger than that.
Assuming you don't
want anything stronger.
Mm.
Well, she's thirsty,
whoever she is. Mm.
Hello, Mr. McGivney, Mr. Twohey.
How are you doing? -It is Mickey.
I told you that, McGivney.
Mickey, how come you don't
come around here no more?
I do sometimes.
- Oh, hardly.
Mick, are you still playin'
the horn? She was incredible.
When she was a little girl,
no bigger than this bar,
she came in here, gave us a
concert. Wore a ball gown.
Yeah. I was there, McGivney.
It was not a ball gown.
That was a, you know,
a whatchmacallit, a... a jumper.
Idiots.
You need something?
Where's Thomas?
Have you heard from Cousin
Bobby, or Cousin Hailey recently?
No. Why are you asking?
Because Kacey's missing.
And I've texted them,
and I haven't gotten a response. Ah.
Kacey is always missing.
That's what she does.
I'm worried.
Have you heard anything about the girls...
...from the Ave that were killed?
No.
Never mind.
I just think that something might have...
...happened to her this time.
Ain't nothing different about this time,
or the 600 times before this.
I don't know why you keep
letting that girl in.
Yeah, I gotta go.
But thanks for the water.
If you hear from them, can
you just tell them to call me?
And Aunt Lynn, too?
Thank you.
Mick.
Bring the kid by when you can.
Maybe he'd like to see the place.
Or don't.
Oh, Michaela.
Come sit in with us sometime, will you?
Yeah.
- We could use a horn.
Sundays and Wednesday nights, 8:00,
right here in the clubhouse.
She's too good for Golden
Slippers, McGivney. -Oh.
She's classically trained.
Oh. Classically trained!
I would absolutely love to do that,
but I work those times.
But thank you for asking.
You stay safe, Mickey.
Ow.
Whoa!
Jesus. What is this?
Uh, that's our new alarm. Truman put it in.
Do you like it?
Huh.
Hi, Michaela.
We're having a little tea.
I can see that.
Where's Truman?
He's in the restroom.
I hope I'm not intruding.
Thomas was so curious
about my tea service collection.
And then he wanted to show me
this wonderful project...
...that he's working on,
and introduce me to your family.
Mm. Can I see?
It's... It's really coming
together. It's good, bud.
Hi.
- Hi.
Hey.
Well...
I'm going to excuse myself now.
I imagine that it's time for dinner.
But it was so nice to get to know
you a little bit better, Thomas.
And uh...
Nice to see you, Michaela.
Oh, and thank you for the
tea. -Oh. You're so welcome.
Will you go wash up for dinner?
- Yeah.
What?
She's nice.
- She's nosy.
She's...
You shouldn't have invited her up,
she's gonna expect that from now on.
Good fences, right?
Yeah.
- Hey, Mom.
Teacher Dana called.
She said she needed to meet
with you tomorrow before school.
Okay.
Everything okay with that?
Yeah. Why wouldn't it be?
You find out anything about that truck?
Not yet. I told this new detective
they have working the case.
Davis Danjarat. Do you know him?
No.
- He's good.
He seems to care.
He's looking into it.
You make it to the airport
today? -No, I didn't.
A call came in,
so I had to take it.
Of course you did.
- I almost didn't.
Your sister is missing. Kind of
trumps everything else, right?
I better be heading out.
Left instructions for you
on the alarm system.
It has an emergency SOS feature
that will call me if you need help.
Thank you for...
For watching Thomas.
He likes spending time with you.
I like spending time with him.
- Hmm.
And his mom.
I'll let the two of you eat.
Truman.
You were right.
I should've called.
Better late than never.
Night, Mick.
- Night.
Hmm.
Keys? Again?
Sorry.
Kace.
- Yep.
No.
I tried, Mickey.
I really did.
A whole year.
How?
It wasn't my fault,
you know, I tried.
I tried.
Well, you didn't try hard enough.
You know the deal.
I know.
One more night.
Please, Michaela.
I don't have anywhere else to go.
One.
And then you need to leave.
You're gonna end up like her.
Fuck.
I'm going.
I'm really sorry, Mickey.
I know.
But you still have to go.
Miss Fitzpatrick, I just
wanted to check in with you...
...about the emails I've sent about tuition.
Yeah, I um...
I... I... I did receive them,
and I'm... I'm sorry, I...
We've been in the middle of a move,
so I was gonna get back to you.
As you know, we at Valley Green...
...make an effort to be
inclusive of all demographics...
...when making admissions decisions.
I personally believe no child should be
held back in education because of means.
We've done our best to offer Thomas...
...the best package we can produce.
But at this point, your part of
the equation is four months late.
Hey, you were right about that truck.
Sorry?
- The red truck.
Cross-checked it against crimes in the area.
A few weeks back,
Vice busted a trap house nearby.
Said they saw a red truck fleeing the scene.
Now they... they didn't get a
plate. But we're keeping an eye out.
Do you know where the house is?
It's off Opal Street, I think.
Oh, and we also got an eyewitness
account on a possible suspect...
...in the murder of one
of the three girls, Taylor Yoon.
A woman reported seeing a man
leaving the scene...
...wearing a Wildwood sweatshirt.
That mean anything to you?
Just ask around if you can.
Okay. Thanks.
Yeah.
Hey, so I, uh, heard you spent
some time in West Philly?
A couple of the guys
said you went to Penn.
I did undergrad.
Graduated in 2015.
I... I only went for a year.
Still. I knew there was a reason I liked you.
May I help you?
'Kay.
And what the frig kinda instrument is that?
It's an English horn.
It was played by one of the members
of the Philadelphia Orchestra...
...when Eugene Ormandy was conducting.
It's 60 years old.
You got any papers on it?
No, it was a gift.
From Freeman's when they
were in Center City.
I went there.
I tried to sell it through them,
but they, um, they said...
...it would take too long
to investigate the provenance.
And I need the money now.
How much you looking to get for it?
$8,500.
Yeah, okay.
Well, it's worth more than that.
I'm sure. I'll tell you what.
Without any papers, best
I could do is two grand.
This is $2,000.
That's less than a month of our
standard tuition. -No, I know.
I... I'm working on gettin' the rest,
but I'm just gonna need
a little bit more time.
I've tried calling Thomas's
father on numerous occasions,
but he hasn't returned any of my calls.
Perhaps I have
the wrong number in my file...
Oh, no, you don't have the wrong number.
I see.
Mickey, I...
At a certain point,
maybe it's worth considering
whether Valley Green...
...is still the best fit for your situation.
My situation?
I just mean since your
finances seem to have changed.
I'm doing the best I can, okay?
Come on, let's go.
Mom, why were you talking
to Teacher Dana?
Did that have something to do with Dad?
Mickey...
...it's me.
I thought we agreed that it's not a
good idea for Thomas to call right now.
I need this time.
I just have too many responsibilities.
You have to make Thomas understand.
Mom, are you okay?
Did you call your dad?
Thomas. Hey.
I was scared.
Scared of what?
The night we went to Truman's.
You...
- I what?
You looked scared, too.
And Truman was hooking up
those cameras,
and Mrs. Mahon said we were in trouble.
And I thought maybe if I called Dad,
and told him we were in trouble, then...
Are we in trouble?
No, we're not in trouble.
I'm so sorry I scared you.
Those... Those security cameras are
just out of an abundance of caution.
Daddy was mad that I called him.
No, he wasn't mad.
He was just worried.
That's why we can't just call him like that.
He'll... He'll get upset,
and you know, he's just...
Busy.
Do you know how strong you are?
I don't think I get that from him.
Let's get you cozy.
Don't forget about Dun-Dun.
You all right?
Yeah.
Okay, sweet dreams, bub.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Hey, it's Kacey.
Leave a message.
Or don't.
Oh, God. Please don't tell me
you took... Mom's necklace, Kace.
Can you just bring it back?
Can you just bring back the necklace?
I will... I will do anything.
I will give you anything.
I just... I just really... Just
not that. I just need that back.
Okay? Please.
That is all I have left of Mom's, okay?
Excuse me.
Do you work here a lot?
Uh, six days a week.
I do something?
Have you seen either of these girls?
Ah... Can't say that I have.
They missing?
Deceased, unfortunately.
- Shit.
Well, no, I never seen 'em.
Okay. Thank you.
Excuse me. Do you recognize
any of these girls?
Maybe they were customers in here?
Mm. Ask Frank.
He practically lives here.
Hey, Frank. You seen either of these girls?
No.
Yeah, I know that girl. She's
been in here a couple of times.
I'm shit with names,
but I always remember a face.
Do you remember how long ago?
Week, week and a half.
She was in here with this guy,
Jimmy Scanlon.
Comes here all the time.
I remember because
they were fighting really bad.
Do you remember
what they were fighting about?
Home invasion in progress,
36 Ruth Street.
All units respond.
You gotta take that?
- No, it's okay.
I don't remember what she was saying.
I just remember how upset she was.
Upset at him, I mean.
Do you know where I can find this Jimmy...
Scanlon?
- Yeah.
Shop next door.
- All units respond.
26643 en route.
Excuse me.
I need to speak to Jimmy Scanlon.
That makes two of us.
He hasn't been in in days.
Been out since last Thursday.
Wife don't know where he is either.
Do you think something
might've happened to him?
Like what?
Do you recognize either of these girls?
No. Should I?
May I ask what Jimmy does here?
He's a sheet-metal worker,
the same as all of us.
Well, if he comes back...
...would you please have him call me?
Yeah, sure.
Thanks.
- All right.
Backup still requested at 36 Ruth Street.
Please respond.
Hey. What are you doing here?
Probably same as you.
Look, that's what I was trying to
tell you at the station yesterday.
But you ran away.
Ever since we saw that dead girl.
I couldn't get her out of my head.
I thought somebody down here
might know something.
I told Ahearn about the napkin.
And he told me to come check it out.
Backup still requested at 36 Ruth Street.
You find anything?
- No.
Please respond.
Hey, Mickey.
- What?
I know you don't think
I give a shit about these girls,
but I do.
That's why I'm down here after my shift.
I thought a lot about
what you said the other day.
And you're right.
They deserve more.
Backup still requested.
All units respond.
Where the hell were you today?
I mean, what part of 'all units
respond' were you not understanding?
I'm sorry.
I was at lunch,
and I just lost track of time.
Well, far be it for me to get
in the middle of your downtime.
First, you want to ride solo,
then you're just MIA
in the middle of your shift?
What the hell is going on
with you, Fitzpatrick?
You should have told Ahearn, Mick.
Told him what?
About Kacey.
If he doesn't know, he can't put the
weight of the department behind you.
They've never been behind me.
- That's in your head.
Is it?
Listen, you're a good cop.
You care about the neighborhood,
you always follow the rules.
Ahearn knows that.
If he knew about Kacey,
maybe he'd understand
why you're breakin' 'em.
Ahearn's MO in life
is to do the least work possible...
...without getting on
the bad side of the union.
Am I wrong?
I got something else for you.
What?
You heard of a guy named
Dock McLatchie?
No. Why?
Well, he's got a bad reputation.
Rumor is, he's a gunrunner,
and he's tagged in a bunch of
pictures on Kacey's Facebook page.
Kacey doesn't have a Facebook page.
She hasn't had one for years.
Yes, she does.
You didn't know about this?
How do you know about this?
That first time, you told me
she was your sister.
I sent her a friend request.
I wanted to watch out for her.
For you.
Here, take a look.
Listen, I don't want to add to your worry,
but if it's the guy I'm thinking of,
he's not someone I'd want
my sister messing around with.
You recognize him?
I knew she was seeing somebody,
but I didn't know who it was.
What is it?
Come on.
Just live a little, man!
Come on, Mickey.
Nothing.
Can you send me that picture of them?
Yeah, sure.
I had her arrested.
That's why she unfriended me.
When?
Like, ten years ago.
I reported her, and the
cops came in and took her.
What'd she get arrested for?
- Theft.
Wasn't the first time
she'd stolen from me, from Gee.
Cash, jewelry, silverware.
But this time, it was different.
My mom gave me this gold necklace.
It was right before she died.
Hm. -It was a little medal of St. Jude.
And Kacey knew how much it meant to me.
She stole it anyway.
She pawned it for a fix.
And I...
...couldn't forgive her.
Please,
let me in! Please, Mickey!
We're family.
Please let me in, Mickey.
Please let me in.
Please, Mickey!
I shouldn't have called the cops on her.
I shouldn't have taken it
out of the family. But...
I did.
And that was the beginning of the end...
...for us.
It's one thing to be a cop.
It's another thing to use the
police against your sister.
You were upset.
You had every right to be.
There's no way you could've
known this might happen.
It was never the same,
after that.
You haven't talked to her since?
She came to live with me
and Simon a couple times.
She was in and out of rehab.
We fought a lot when she was there.
And the last fight was really bad.
I didn't choose her.
And I should've.
And so when that call
came over the radio today.
I did.
And I want to find her so I can tell her.
Tell her what?
That she meant more than a necklace.
We'll find her.
Come on.
Thomas, are you almost done
with your homework?
I'm just finishing up some math.
You want to do the rest at Gee-Pop's?
Yes.
Hey, the car
hasn't even stopped yet, Thomas.
Sorry, Mom.
Can I go now?
- Yep.
Gee-Pop!
A visit with my great-grandson
on a school night.
You got a hot date or something?
No.
- Probably wouldn't be...
...the worst thing in the world for you.
Gee.
You're gonna go look for her, aren't you?
I haven't heard anything
back from the cousins.
Sounds like a good thing to me.
It feels like they would rather
lose Kacey than help me out.
Forget 'em.
Those two zeros got nothing
to be judgmental about.
Gee-Pop, you coming?
Yeah, yeah.
Hold your horses, kid.
You had every right to do what you did.
Fuck those O'Briens.
Always were the weakest link in this family.
Hello, Mickey.