I ran autopsies,
and all three came back...
...with a lethal amount
of insulin in their system.
Looks like someone's
going after these girls.
Kacey's not missing anymore. Found her.
How'd she look?
- Sober.
And pregnant.
I'm sorry I made you worry.
I just... I was scared.
That I would take this baby, too?
That you'd be right to take her.
I spoke too soon about Dock.
You know his abando
got burned down yesterday.
Word on the street,
it was his old supplier.
Old supplier,
means there's a new one.
Always is.
There's a whole lot of product there.
So we were right about what
Scanlon was doing with his boat.
If Jimmy was bringing it in, maybe the
women were taking it out to the streets.
Do you know any dealers
who would trust someone...
...in active addiction
to run their supply for them?
Paula says that
the guy in the video is a cop,
and then she ends up dead.
We've been cross-referencing Scanlon
with all the women on the Avenue.
But maybe we should've just
been crossing him with cops.
I found her.
I found Melissa.
Did you... What did she say to
you? Did she tell you who shot her?
She said the killer is Truman Dawes.
Listen, what happened to these
girls is not their fault.
But we can't let all of them go.
Mickey. It's still our job to police them.
Mickey, hey.
Maybe they'll be better if they
knew someone was watching them.
No, it's not Truman.
It... it can't be.
Are you sure? Emily Morris
said he was the killer.
Yeah.
What else did she say?
Nothing. That was it.
- What else?
Kacey.
- Nothing. Nothing.
She didn't want to talk to me, Mickey.
She was scared to tell me.
Scared I'd tell you.
Scared that he'll come after her.
That's... that's ridiculous.
Paula said killer was a cop.
Who used his badge to get blowjobs.
Does that sound like Truman?
No, it doesn't. But if you asked the
wives of half the men I've been with,
they'd probably say it didn't
sound like their husbands either.
He didn't do it.
He couldn't have.
You're fucking wrong.
She's fucking wrong.
Shit. Kacey, what's wrong?
What? What is it?
- I'm fine. I'm just fucking...
Kacey.
I left my subs at Dad's.
I don't think I can hold out
till I get back there.
Suboxone?
Yeah. I need it to stay clean.
Stay here.
What up, officer?
- Hey, what's up, Darnell?
You got a second?
- Not for you. Fuck outta here.
I'm not here to bust you.
I just need some help.
Come on. I'm in a uniform,
about to hand
a known drug dealer some cash.
That's not exactly a good look for me.
So please help me.
What you need?
Suboxone. Subs.
We find out popo's a fiend.
It's not for me.
It's for my sister.
Man, whatever.
How much you need?
- Two.
A hundred.
Nice doing business with you.
Darnell, have you heard
of a new product on the street?
Heard Dock's been pushing it.
And some others.
Yeah, it's around. But I ain't
touched that shit, though.
How come?
'Cause cops are behind it?
Is it Truman?
Don't know who's behind it.
I just heard it was blue.
Thank you.
Uh...
I know you want to talk to Truman.
Just drop me off at a park or something.
I'll be fine.
I'm not dropping you off at a park.
Come on, you can rest on the couch.
Where's Thomas?
He's downstairs with the landlord.
Okay.
- Um,
she sometimes watches him.
Can I use your bathroom?
Refresh?
- Yeah.
Hi, Mrs. Mahon. It's Mickey.
I was wondering if Thomas could
stay with you a little bit longer.
I've to run into work.
Uh...
Great. Thank you. Yeah.
Actually, there's one other thing. Um...
My cousin's visiting,
and she's taking a nap.
So if you could make sure that Thomas
doesn't come up here for any reason...
Right. Great. Okay.
Um...
You don't have to worry about that.
Worry about what?
- Thomas.
I would never do that to you.
I just need to...
Oh, I just need to sit down for a bit.
I'm gonna head out.
I need to talk to Truman.
You don't believe me about Truman.
I don't.
Thomas, you all right in there?
- Yup, coming.
You have an hour before bed,
so I thought we could play
another game of Clue, and...
...maybe have some hot chocolate.
Yeah. Be right out.
No. You know what you are?
You're fucking dead weight.
You're the reason
Mickey dropped out of school.
You're like a fucking anvil...
...around your sister's neck,
and you're bringing her down.
Wake up.
Who's the father?
Is it Simon?
Wake up.
Uh...
You were having a bad dream.
Thomas?
You know me?
Yeah.
And I know you.
You do?
You're the girl with the pink hair.
What the hell am I doing here?
This is Ryan, and cousin
Hailey, and Aunt Lynn.
Oh, and Gee-Pop's over here.
And I put you here 'cause I
didn't know where you went.
Um...
Here.
What's your name again?
My name? Um... I'm Kacey.
Ryan told me all about you
on Thanksgiving, and...
Yeah?
I told Mom that I needed
to put you on the family tree.
But when I asked her about it, she
said that she didn't know who you were.
And that Ryan must've been mistaken.
Yeah. I don't know.
Uh... I don't know, Thomas.
Why would she say that?
That she didn't know who you were?
Maybe she didn't know
about your pink hair.
Yeah, I think that must be it. Yeah.
Thomas? Thomas.
Up here.
That's Mrs. Mahon.
She's really nice, and she takes
care of me when Mom's at work.
Thomas, you can't run off
like that. Your mother...
Oh, hello.
- Yeah.
You must be Michaela's cousin.
I'm Cecilia Mahon.
Um, I'm Kacey.
Sorry, Kacey. Michaela said
you weren't to be disturbed.
Thomas, we should be going
and leave your cousin alone.
You grew up with my mom.
What was she like when she was little?
Um...
Thomas, maybe we should leave.
No, it's all right.
It's all right.
Um...
She was...
...really, really smart.
She was so smart.
She uh... I don't think I ever saw
her without a book in her hand.
I mean, I wasn't like that. I
didn't... I couldn't read like she did.
She... she was good.
She always chose the right thing, and...
She loved music.
She loved her horn.
She still does.
She loves playing Tristan and Isolde.
Really? She still got it?
My mom gave me these
from when she was little.
Oh, my God.
She said the killer is Truman Dawes.
You know him, too.
'Cause he's a cop.
Always paid my debts, no matter
how creative I had to get.
I don't get it. It finally
feels like we're getting closer,
and then you want to back off?
You really want what happened to
Paula to happen to you, or Kacey?
Man, Mickey used to play these
all the time after Mom...
...after her mom died.
Even when Gee told her to stop.
Why did he tell her to stop?
Um...
Well, I think,
because Gee was...
...sad, you know, that
Mickey's mom, your grandma...
...was gone.
But Mickey wouldn't listen.
She would... It was funny.
She followed every single
rule he had. But not that one.
Why not?
Probably just... it made her
feel close to her mom.
Gee told her that it made her
weak to keep listening like that.
But I think it made her strong.
I wasn't like that, I, um...
All I could ever do was escape the pain.
But she didn't, she couldn't.
It was like...
...she only ever knew how to face it.
I think I get that from her.
Put your hands where I can see them, now.
Keep those eyes open for me, Kori.
All right. Keep them open.
You hear me?
Wanna tell me what the hell
it is you think you're doing?
Kori, keep those eyes open.
I... I thought...
- You thought what, Mickey?
She OD'd.
And she might need
another shot of Naloxone.
So maybe you want to lower that
Glock you got pointed at me?
Kori. Kori?
Kori.
What... what the fuck?
It's okay, you're gonna be all
right. You're gonna be fine.
But listen to me.
I need you to slow...
...your breathing down for me, all right?
I need you to slow it down.
- Come on. Can you do that for me?
Come on.
Okay. Good.
Good.
Your leg looks pretty bad.
I'm gonna try and clean it out.
But you're headed for sepsis...
...if you don't go and see
a doctor. No hospital.
Kori, you won't survive
the night if you don't go.
Okay? For me, please.
You gotta go.
Truman, how can I help?
You can step the hell out of
my light, so I can clean this.
Okay. Okay.
Hey, is uh...
she gonna be all right?
Good thing you called when you did.
Just let Mr. Winton know I hope
he feels better, all right?
Yeah.
Let's go.
I didn't know about Winton.
Any of it.
Ever since Mr. Winton's sons died,
he spends a lot of nights out here.
When he's not helping folks
out at the shop,
he's helping folks out on the street.
He's not feeling so well these
days. So, I've been stepping in.
I'm so sorry. I...
Please just let me explain it.
Which part, Mick?
Why you followed me,
or why you pulled a gun on me?
Kacey found Emily Morris,
and she told Kacey...
...that you were the one
who was murdering these women.
And so I went to talk to you. And
then I saw you with the duffel bag.
And then the needles. And then
what was I supposed to think?
Not that I was a serial killer.
Or that I was a cop covering up for one.
Why would Emily Morris say that?
Beats me, better question is,
why would you believe her?
Because that's what she told Kacey.
And I've doubted her so many
times, and I just couldn't...
...this time.
So you gained her trust to lose mine.
Truman.
I'm so sorry, okay?
I... I just... I want you
to understand something.
I need you...
- You pulled a gun on me, Mickey.
I know. And if I could take it back, I would.
There's no taking this back.
I was in love with you, Mickey.
I'm in love with you, too.
You got a fucked up way of showing it.
I should probably get going now.
Um...
Are you all right, dear?
Yep.
Just a little light headed.
- Sit back down a bit.
Yeah.
- Thomas,
why don't you go and get Kacey
a glass of water?
Yeah. Yeah.
How far along are you?
I'm... Thank you.
Seven months.
- Oh.
There's a baby in there?
Hello?
Hello in there. It's me, Thomas.
I think she kicked.
- Did she?
She kicked.
- She likes you.
She kicked for me.
Hi. Mom, Mom!
- Thomas.
I felt the baby kick.
That's great.
Thomas wandered up here and
found your cousin, I'm afraid.
Okay.
Well, I guess I should be going.
Thomas, Kacey.
Michaela.
Hey, Thomas,
why don't you get ready for bed?
When will I see you again?
I don't know.
Well, we're family and families
see each other all the time.
So just don't be a stranger, okay?
Mickey, I'm...
Mick, I'm sorry. He just...
he came up here.
I didn't know what to do. I...
Davis.
- Yeah?
You ordered an autopsy on Paula Mulroney.
I need to know why.
Mick... Mick, I'm sorry.
You were right. When he came
up here, I shouldn't have...
Jesus, Mick, I said I was sorry.
Was it really so bad that he met me?
Emily Morris said it was Truman Dawes.
Are you sure that's what she said?
Yeah.
What were her exact words, Kacey?
I told you her...
- Her exact words!
When I found her at that abando.
I told her I needed to talk to her.
But she wouldn't talk to me. She
was high as fuck, but she got up,
she walked away.
She didn't say a thing,
so I begged her to talk to me...
...tell me who shot her, told her he
could try that with somebody else.
But she just laughed at me
and told me to fuck off.
She didn't want to talk to me
because of you,
because you were protecting the killer.
And I was like,
'Wait, I don't understand.
'What does the killer
have to do with my sister?'
And she said...
'Because he's her partner.'
Like, I already knew that or something.
Then she ran away,
and that's it.
Partner?
- Yes.
She said 'partner'?
Yeah. What... what...
what's wrong?
Truman hasn't been my partner in months.
Oh, fuck.
Then who has?
His name is Eddie Lafferty,
and he was assigned to me when
Truman went on medical leave.
There. You know him?
He's Dock's supplier.
He's a cop, huh?
- You didn't know?
I mean, I guess I'm not surprised. He's...
...also been with a...
lot of the girls on the Ave.
No, not with me, but...
...a lot of them.
So what made him
graduate to killing them?
Mick, I'm so sorry about Truman. I mean...
I really... I...
I didn't know he was on leave.
And maybe if you just explain
that to him, he'll understand.
No, he won't.
He won't understand.
Oh, my God. Wait.
What is it, Mick?
Oh, my God.
- What?
That's Lafferty with my boss, Ahearn.
And that's Scanlon, the guy
who got shot with Emily Morris.
They all went to high school together.
Ahearn, Lafferty and Scanlon.
So Jimmy was bringing it in
off those boats,
and Lafferty was bringing it to the street.
I mean, it still doesn't explain
why those girls were killed.
I need to find Lafferty.
I need to bring him in.
There's a detective in my
department who I think I can trust.
A cop?
- Yeah.
Are you kidding? No fucking way.
We don't know how high up this goes.
We're better off going to Dock.
You're not better off going to Dock.
I met him. He's not a good guy, Kace.
Yeah, he is.
He's just not clean.
Thomas, I love you
more than anything else.
I know.
Hello?
- Detective Danjarat.
It's Mickey Fitzpatrick.
I know who the killer is.
We've got the wrong guy in custody.
Hey, Lafferty,
it's Davis Danjarat.
Whoops.
It's all clear.
Holy shit!
What is it?
Prescription... for insulin.
A fuck ton of it.
Mickey!
Mickey! It's me. Danjarat.
Hey, you were right about Lafferty.
And you were right about everything.
Hi. Did you find him?
No, he wasn't home.
We don't know where he is.
What is it?
My sister's gone, too.
Kacey Theresa Fitzpatrick, 5'5'.
Approximately 115 pounds,
pink hair and pregnant.
And Mike, keep this quiet,
okay? Only cops you trust.
Hey. Don't worry.
Okay? We'll find Kacey.
I also have DiPaolo
on the lookout for Emily Morris.
I'm coming with you.
Don't worry, dear.
I'll stay with Thomas.
His Gee-Pop is coming pretty early to
pick him up for the New Year's parade.
Mickey, it's better if you stay here.
Kacey might come back,
all right?
Okay? I'll call you
as soon as I find anything.
You're not gonna listen to him, are you?
Mr. Winton. Hi, it's Mickey
Fitzpatrick, Truman's um... friend.
I'm looking for Dock McClatchie.
Hey, Dock.
- Got something for me?
Yeah.
- I got something for you, too.
Are you sure I can't be a devil?
They're all taken, kid.
You're either an angel or you're nothing.
Look at me and McGivney.
Look at how sharp we are.
What's the matter?
You don't like it?
I know, you're shy.
You don't like people looking at you.
Twohey don't either.
That is true. I don't.
Listen to me.
You belong here.
This is your birthright.
Come here.
Read me these names.
You can read right?
Gerald Francis O'Brien.
Francis Patrick O'Brien.
Robert Paul O'Brien.
This is your great-great-great grandfather.
This is your great-great uncle.
And this is your other great uncle.
You may be a Fitzpatrick by name,
but you've got O'Brien blood in your veins.
Oh, that's godawful.
That'll be O'Connor,
out of tune again.
Hey, McGivney,
what's worse than a banjo?
What?
- Two banjos?
You know why I like New Year's, Thomas?
It's a fresh start.
You couldn't stay away,
could you?
I need your help.
Have you seen Dock McClatchie?
You've been asking for a lot lately.
You want to find Dock,
you gotta talk to God.
Immaculate Heart.
...too much heat.
Yeah, you and me both.
Had so much heat,
my house got burned down.
I heard about that.
But I'm here now, aren't I?
That's everything?
That's all I have left.
Damn shame about that bust.
You're telling me.
You got kids?
Fucking alimony is no joke.
I like these new digs.
A real fairy tale come true.
No, I'm serious.
Something romantic about it.
My mother used to make me
take her to mass on Sundays.
Other kids hated it,
but I... no, I loved it.
The altar, the smell...
...the way the light came through
the stained glass, you know.
Don't move. Hands up.
Mickey!
- Shut up! Hands up!
Where is she?
Where's Kacey?
What are you doing here?
Where the fuck is Kacey?
Huh? Where is she?
You, get down! Get down!
Hands behind your head.
You, too, Eddie.
What are you doing here?
Where the fuck is Kacey, huh?
Where is she?
Who's Kacey?
- Shut up! I said, get down!
Mickey.
- Get down.
Kacey? Kacey, you here?
I know she's here.
I saw her purse.
Where is she?
Mick. Mick, I'm here.
I'm working.
I'm undercover, working. Fuckin'
talk to Ahearn, all right?
He'll tell you everything.
You're a liar.
You've been lying to me.
Since the day I met you.
You lied to me
when I came to your apartment,
and you were telling me
about how Ahearn and his buddies...
...are the ones who
toe the line, when it's you.
It's you. Yeah,
maybe they do, too.
But they're not the ones who
killed those women. You are.
You really think that I could
do something like that?
I do. Yes, I do.
And there's a living witness who knows
that you can do something like that, too.
Now tell me where the fuck my sister is.
She ain't here, Mick.
- Shut up!
Kacey trusts you.
She said you were a good guy.
I am a good guy.
Who the fuck do you think brought
you to the fucking hospital?
Jeannie, Nicole beat the piss out of you.
Then where is she?
I don't know.
You're lying. You're both lying.
Tell me the truth, or I swear
to God I will pull the trigger.
I know you killed those women.
And I know you killed Paula, too.
And for your sake,
Kacey better still be alive.
Tell me what you did.
Okay. All right.
I'll tell you what happened.
But you gotta let me explain.
I didn't mean for any of this
to happen, okay?
It just...
...it got out of hand.
I didn't mean to.
I just... I was lonely.
So I was with some of the girls,
and then I don't know,
they turned on me.
Maybe it was because you used your badge
to force them to have sex with you.
Step back, Mickey.
Mickey. Listen...
I didn't mean to hurt nobody, Mick.
I swear. You gotta understand.
They were threatening me, saying
they were gonna go to my bosses.
Mickey.
- I couldn't let anybody find out.
I lose everything.
- Mickey.
I've got kids.
Do you know what it would do to them?
What it would do to them?
What about what it did to those women?
What did it...
what did it do, hm?
What did it really do?
'Cause when we discovered
that first body on the tracks,
nobody did nothing about it.
They barely mentioned it at roll call.
You think I didn't care?
Well, nobody else did neither.
Mickey, step back.
What kind of life, right?
That's for Taylor.
That's for Elizabeth.
That's for Amelia.
Go ahead.
I spent a lot of my life locked up.
At least this time,
it was worth it.
For Paula.
Everybody needs to go.
Well, I'm gonna stay.
Hey, go, keep walking until you
can't see the cathedral anymore. Go.
I was trying to warn you.
- I know.
Go.
Kace...
She said, 'That's for Amelia.'
Who's Amelia?
Emily's friend.
She have pink hair?
Are you in trouble?
I don't know.
Do you want to go home?
Can we go somewhere else for a minute?
Yeah.
I'm so sorry for all of this.
You weren't supposed to be there, Mickey.
I was trying to help.
Yeah, it wasn't your
place. It wasn't about you.
It was about of our existence,
you know. About...
It's about taking care
of ourselves and each other.
I was...
I was trying to take care of you.
Yeah, well, that's, like, my
whole point, Mick. You can't.
We needed to do it on our own.
If only to...
...prove to ourselves that we could.
So many people write us off for...
...this choice that we made. But it
wasn't a choice, not for all of us.
I know.
Gee told me...
...that Mom was using
when she was pregnant with you.
You didn't have the same start as me.
I... I didn't know that.
Now that explains a lot.
Yeah.
'Cause, like,
for the longest time.
I tried to think back to the time...
...the moment when it all went bad.
I know when that was.
When I let Simon come between us.
You know, he took me here when
I was 18 years old to this pier,
and he kissed me for the first time.
I never told you that.
Maybe it was
because I knew deep down that
I was letting you down.
You were a kid, Mick.
You were a kid just like me. You
were supposed to be able to fuck up,
and make mistakes,
and have that be okay. But...
I don't know. I guess you thought
you couldn't or something.
You were never supposed
to take care of me.
I felt guilty.
I just felt guilty.
About what?
About the fact that I...
...had something that you didn't.
I got something that you never got.
I got Mom's love.
Or, I don't know,
the memory of it.
I have these memories of her.
And, like, I just...
I could just feel her love in them.
And some days, it's...
...that feeling is all that keeps me going.
Sometimes I...
I feel like that's the thing that separates us,
you know, more than anything.
I do have that Mickey,
the memory of love.
I just got it from you.
Lafferty was wrong, you know...
...when he said that nobody cared.
You cared.
You wouldn't let this place ignore us.
You said their names when no one else did.
Taylor Yoon.
Elizabeth O'Connor.
Amelia DelVecchio.
Paula Mulroney.
We gather today, to mourn
the loss of these friends.
Each of them was a member
of our community.
Each of them
was one of God's own children.
People with promise,
people loving and beloved...
...and one after another in a line, in a river...
...no font and no outlet.
A long, bright river...
...of departed souls.
May you all rest in peace,
and find comfort in the kingdom of heaven.
Amen.
- Amen.
You know,
it took us a while...
...to figure out what the women
had to do with it all.
It's a lot, as it turns out.
Amelia DelVecchio.
- Yeah.
She was the woman I found on the tracks.
According to her parents, she'd
been on and off the street for years.
Most of the time, she couldn't
keep a cell phone, but...
...you know, there was
a month long stretch last fall...
...where she had the one
her mother gave her.
And once we had her name,
we were able to look into the records.
Some pretty damning evidence
against Lafferty in there.
Apparently, a few of the women
started threatening...
...to expose him for the drugs if he...
...you know, didn't stop demanding favors.
That's when he freaked,
began going after them.
I think Lafferty is the one who killed them.
But I do think Ahearn
was involved somehow.
My guess is he benched Lafferty to try
to distance himself from the whole thing.
But Ahearn denies it all.
Fucker won't talk.
God. Maybe he'll talk when they
throw a plea deal his way.
Maybe, or maybe Ahearn
will just keep on doing...
...exactly what he's been doing...
...all his career...
- Mm.
...all his life.
Maybe he'll never get caught.
So, am I hearing right?
You're gonna quit the force?
Well, IA's investigating.
They're probably gonna fire me anyway.
So I figured I'd beat 'em to the punch.
Well, you know, IA cleared you.
When?
After I told them you were telling the truth,
that I heard it all...
...on your cell phone.
I thought my cell phone died.
Yeah.
So how much did you really hear?
Enough to know that you shouldn't quit.
The force needs cops like you.
Cops who are inept?
Cops who care.
Imagine what this place would
be like if we had more of them.
Hey.
You got a second to talk?
I don't think...
- Just hear me out.
Just let me apologize.
And then I'll go, I promise.
Okay.
I'm sorry, Truman...
...for ever believing that you could
be anything but what you are.
You're the best person I've ever met.
And the sad part is.
I didn't believe it,
that you were the killer.
But I wanted to show Kacey
that I believed her for once.
Does that make sense?
Wrong apology?
Yeah.
You pulled a gun on me, Mickey.
We can't come back from that.
Even if I wanted to.
I understand.
So, anyway, I quit the force.
I guess we both knew that I
shouldn't have become a cop.
I don't know what I'm gonna do now.
It's a little late in life...
...to figure out who I want to be
when I grow up.
All right, um...
I'm gonna go.
You'll never truly understand...
...the amount of regret
that I'll carry with me...
...for the rest of my life.
You're right, you know.
You were never meant to be a cop.
You should've been a music teacher.
I told you the first time I met you.
You got that...
...vibe.
Thomas.
Bye.
How was school today?
Great.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
- How was music class?
You still liking it?
- Yeah. I'm loving it.
Give me that. Good.
So what are your three things?
How is she doing?
- Which she?
Both of them.
- They're both great.
She wanted a minute alone
before she lets the cavalry in.
Have you decided yet? On a name?
No.
Mm-mm. Every time I think
I have one, I get scared.
And I just think...
...that's what she's gonna be
called for the rest of her life.
And it stops me.
Is that what Thomas sounded like
when he was born?
But it's not what she sounds like.
I know, sweetheart.
They say that um...
...that she doesn't need that,
the medicine.
They say that she's doing good without it.
Do you think they'll be okay?
Who?
The baby.
All the babies in here.
Do you think they'll be okay?