- [phone beeps]
- [Parker] Previously on Ballard...
Cops can be assholes.
Doesn't make it personal.
You were my partner,
and I should've had your back.
I wasn't just your partner.
I was your friend.
- I just--
- No, get off me!
[Tutu] You keep putting these walls
up around yourself.
You're the one missing the view.
[Bosch] Harmon Harris.
He and this other guy, Adam Lennox,
they said that they'd
been out together that night.
Ironically, this guy Lennox was
a student in Harris's acting class.
[Ballard] Sarah Pearlman
was interested in acting.
Maybe Harmon Harris coached her too.
Good a lead as any.
Dispo order? Who signed for it?
[Ballard] Guy named Charlie Grant.
He worked Gangs with Laffont
back in the day. [sighs]
So I'm gonna be roping him in.
Is that a good idea?
What am I supposed to know
about some illegal getting whacked?
The bullet that killed him
is missing from Property,
and you signed the dispo order.
You know she has a habit
of making false accusations,
and almost ruined a good man's career.
[Colleen] Who would order a bullet
to be destroyed in an unsolved murder?
[Parker] Look, it's one thing
to let a John Doe go unsolved.
But they destroyed the damn evidence?
This is a cover-up.
Why can't you see
what's right in front of you?
You wanna help me?
Get your goddamn badge.
[Parker] Paw Paw, I wanna go back.
It's rotten.
I struggled to find a reason to stay.
[Parker] Then why did you?
When you knew what your so-called brothers
were capable of?
[Grandaddy Parker]
Because once you know that,
someone has to watch the watchmen.
Gonna be near impossible
investigating potential corruption
without stepping on a land mine.
- So, we should just ignore it?
- That's not what he's saying.
I'm just saying, given the circumstances,
we might need more firepower.
[Parker] What we need
- is some physical evidence.
- [Laffont] If we loop in Berchem--
[Ballard] No Berchem.
And definitely no IA.
Look, this doesn't work
unless we're all on the same page.
You need to start trusting me.
[sighs] No one knows about this
until we figure out what's going on.
And that includes the squad.
As far as they're concerned,
this is a John Doe murder
until we can prove corruption.
[Parker] Gonna be hard to do.
We don't have a bullet to work off of.
[phone beeps]
That may not be the case.
What do you mean?
Head back to the Ahmanson.
Martina can fill you in.
Fill me in on what?
We may get that bullet after all.
I told Hastings
we were re-interviewing this witness
in Laura Wilson's case.
I just hope we don't stall out here.
So, Adam Lennox.
What was Bosch's take on him
during the initial investigation?
He thought he was covering for
Harmon Harris. Just couldn't figure why.
- [bell rings]
- [director] Quiet on set.
Maybe now that he's dead,
he'll give it up.
Gotta love LA.
[scoffs]
So, how do we find Adam?
You said he works in craft service.
Just find the doughnuts.
[chattering on TV]
Can I help you?
- You're Dolores, right?
- Yes.
I understand that you knew Yulia Kravetz.
I wanted to ask you
a couple of questions about--
You police?
I thought you got the guy who did it.
Oh. [stutters] I'm just a volunteer.
Uh... And I'm not here
about the investigation.
I know Yulia came from Ukraine,
and I wanna find her family,
let them know what happened.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know much about her family.
Hmm.
Did she ever say their names maybe,
or what town she was from?
She didn't talk about home.
It made her sad.
She missed the coffee though.
Wherever she was from,
they were famous for it.
Adam Lennox?
I'm Detective Ballard, LAPD.
I have some questions for you about
an old friend of yours, Harmon Harris.
Harmon?
He died two years ago.
You alibied for him back in '08
in the Laura Wilson murder, that right?
Yeah. I told the detective back then
that he'd be crazy to think
Harmon could do something like that.
That would be Detective Bosch?
Uh, forget his name.
Super intense guy though.
Yeah. That would be Detective Bosch.
So, you were with Harmon all night?
I thought we settled all this.
It's not settled
until Laura's killer is found.
Look, I know it wasn't Harmon, okay?
He was a decent guy.
He took care of a lot of people back then.
Must've been hard to lose him then.
And Laura too. She was so young.
Whole thing was a nightmare.
But it wasn't Harmon.
Tell us how you know.
Okay, look, I was covering for him.
But not because he killed Laura.
He was with another guy.
Intimately.
And Harmon wasn't out?
Harmon didn't care who knew about him
or what people thought. [chuckles]
He was covering for the other guy?
We both were.
This guy's career just started
to really take off.
Outing him would've ended all that.
So I said it was me.
We're going to need the name
of Harmon's actual alibi.
I can't do that.
Mr. Lennox,
we're talking about murder here.
[glass shatters]
Phil? [stammers] One second.
We need that name.
Do we? Right now?
And add this actor
to the list of casualties?
If Harmon is our killer, then he's dead.
Why not try to prove it some other way,
see if we can avoid
any other collateral damage?
We can always come back to him
if we have to.
- All right.
- [Adam] Look, guys,
- I should really be getting back to--
- Wait. One more question.
About the van you saw outside of Laura's,
a few nights before the murder?
Yeah, um, license plate started with a 4.
It was a blue Ford. It was a beater.
Wait. It was a Ford?
- [Adam] Mm-hmm.
- It didn't say that in the report.
Funny.
I wouldn't have known that back then.
[stammers] My brother-in-law bought one
just like it a couple years ago.
Definitely a Ford.
Yesterday on the Pearlman case,
this was our list.
Over 3,000 blue vans that matched
the description in Bosch's murder book.
Today, we have narrowed it down
to 378 blue Ford vans.
Ooh, a smaller haystack!
[Ballard] Split up these VIN numbers.
Look for criminal records
or anything else that may be a flag.
- On our John Doe case, we--
- I have a lead.
All right, show 'em.
Mmm. I, um, hate to be that guy,
but what are we looking at?
Well, thanks to Martina
and one of her classmates,
that is the John Doe bullet
that was destroyed.
How did you get this?
I promised him I'd go to
a Lord of the Rings marathon.
I don't think he meant--
Yeah. They used photos of the bullet
from the John Doe autopsy.
Right. My friend, he interns at a place
that builds renderings
of crime scene evidence for lawyers.
[Ted] Oh, that's cool.
It won't hold up in court.
It doesn't have to. Just need a lead.
Now I can take this to Firearms Freddie
and see if he can connect it
to any other crimes.
- [music playing on radio]
- You mind the radio?
As you can see,
I'm not exactly Bluetooth-capable in here.
My mom says the day
they started putting computers in cars
is the day it all went to hell.
You tell her yet,
that you joined the reserves?
Yeah, that's a problem for future me.
- Look, about this morning, I...
- I know I got a little hot.
You're just making some moves
I didn't expect.
Like Laffont?
I know you trust him, but...
Look, he's like this car.
He's more reliable than he looks.
I'll try.
[Ted] Last five of the VIN are 11298.
I'd rather not hold.
[stammers, sighs]
[music playing on headphones]
[Colleen] Martina?
Martina?
[music continues]
[gasps, in Spanish] Ay, dios.
[sighs]
Sorry. These are my heavy-duty ones.
The brain's not braining very well today.
What's up?
I think I have something.
Slogging through these VIN numbers
didn't seem particularly efficient,
so I lobbed some details
about the Laura Wilson killing
- over to some murder buddies on Reddit.
- Naturally.
And this user named
HootDunIt reached out--
Did you say "HootDunIt"?
Yeah. HootDunIt. You know, the owl theory?
The Staircase?
[stammers] Anyway, uh, Hoot messaged me
about a homicide in Vegas in '98.
Had some of the same deets,
including a blue Ford van.
Astonishingly accurate.
You know AI is gonna take our jobs, right?
And then it's gonna kill us in our beds.
Can you run it through NIBIN
without destroying the world?
For a Florida Ghost Philodendron.
Just a cutting.
Done.
Long as you can do it right now.
"Kathy Goodman, 27,
was on vacation in Vegas.
Seen at the Tropicana"--
[Ted] Oh, Tropicana.
The first swim-up blackjack table
in Nevada.
How's your VIN list coming?
Ugh.
Single woman, traveling alone.
Strangled to death in her motel.
Blue Ford van spotted outside
the night she died.
This could be our guy.
I should call Vegas PD, right?
See if they'll send the murder book?
You can't actually.
It needs to be someone with a badge.
What?
- You can bribe him.
- Ding, ding, ding. We got one.
Incident within the last five years?
Southeast Division case
from November 2023.
A suspect named... [sighs] ...Javier Fuentes.
Charges?
Uh, "Gang member in possession of
a loaded firearm, discharging a firearm."
Could be he's still in custody.
Maybe we can keep him there for murder.
You're right. Strangled in her bed
just like Laura and Sarah.
Could be a third victim.
Gotta get into the murder book
to be certain.
[stutters] I reached out to the captain
in Vegas. He's sending it over.
And, um... [stammers]
Colleen's the one who figured it out.
Colleen, go ahead.
[stammers] Rawls is right.
Uh, we need confirmation.
But if we work under the assumption
that it is the same killer,
we can assume that the van
was manufactured before 1998,
which narrows the amount of vans
that we have to track from 378 to, uh, 54.
Let's bump up the 54. And show me
the Vegas book when it gets here.
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
[Ballard] Great job.
Hey. Did Parker tell you we got a hit
on that John Doe dummy bullet?
Guy's name is Javier Fuentes.
He's actually still in county.
- That's great.
- Yeah.
[clears throat] Um...
Listen.
- Uh...
- What's up?
It's about Chastain.
Is he calling you now?
Because he approached me outside
of Patrick's Roadhouse the other--
No, no. Renée...
there was a car accident.
Chastain is dead.
No one else was injured.
He just hit a telephone pole.
Let's get back to work.
["Speak Your Mind" playing on radio]
[Aaron] Starting to take shape.
Hey.
Uh, you're early.
Oh, am I? It's nine o'clock.
It is. I lost track of time.
- I'll take one of those.
- Oh.
Aw, look at you. Same goofy smile.
Is that your dad?
Yeah.
Is he still around?
No, he died when I was 14.
Surfing accident.
And Dr. Tutu in there thought it would be
cathartic for me to build his board, so...
Ah, 14. That's young.
Yeah.
Just one of those things, you know?
It's always there.
[song continues]
[Ballard] You picked up your badge.
Yeah, I'm official now.
Hey. I heard about your old partner.
That's rough.
How long were you guys working together?
Four years.
Put me this close to chocha,
you expect me to think straight?
Mr. Fuentes, you were arrested in--
Call me Little Javi.
I wanna hear it come outta your mouth.
You were arrested for possession and
discharge of a firearm, November, 2023.
Parole violation and time served
if I ever get in front of a judge.
Maybe. Except we've just
connected that gun to a murder.
[smacks lips]
No comeback for that?
Hold up.
Him?
- You know him?
- [stammers] No, no, no, no.
There's no way I'm doing time
for someone else's shit.
I walked in here on two legs, and I got
jumped over a plate of mashed potatoes!
If you didn't do it,
where'd you get the gun?
I don't remember. [stammers] I found it.
All I know is I didn't kill that dude.
[stammers] I wouldn't go near him.
Why? Who is he?
He's a coyote for the cartel.
[Ballard] Which one?
Tell us, or your name starts coming out
of our mouths on the streets...
Little Javi.
Zacatecas Nuevas.
Okay. Now tell me who that is.
Pending confirmation,
we no longer have a John Doe.
So our undocumented father on the run
was a coyote? I'm stunned.
Doesn't change the job. Solve the murder.
What about that guy in jail
who got caught with the gun?
Oh, he didn't do it.
- That your woo-woo talking?
- [chuckles] No.
He had an alibi.
Javier was on a job in Fresno
at the time Ibarra was killed.
Got the gun afterward.
- So he's off the board.
- Great.
It's still progress, guys,
because of Martina's bullet.
If I were giving out stickers,
she'd get two.
Hey. Do we have the murder book
on the Tropicana victim?
Yeah, but it's pretty thin.
Nothing concrete linking her
to our killer.
Let me have a look.
And, guys, let's keep
moving on those vans.
Hey, Ballard,
I heard the funeral is tomorrow.
I guess his wife wanted
to get it over with.
You going?
You know, we got a lot going on. I'll see.
[sighs]
You bring that in?
Yep. Trying to warm this place up a bit.
My next project is the conference room.
Uh, hey. Are you, uh, still looking
for that Ukrainian girl's parents?
Yes, but I'm striking out.
I actually think I've reached
the end of the Internet. [chuckles]
[chuckles] That's saying a lot
coming from you.
Yeah. I think I found the town
that she's from.
They have a coffee company
that won an award.
- They grow coffee in Ukraine?
- Yeah. They roast coffee in Ukraine.
Anyway, I can't reach anybody over there.
It's like... [smacks lips]
Uh, it's like a black hole.
Yeah.
[stammers] You know,
one of my security guys, Andrei.
He's from Kyiv. Ex-military.
He might be able to help.
Um. Wow. Yeah.
You'd do that?
I'm happy to.
[stammers] I'll get his number.
[Chastain family, through phone]
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
- ♪ Happy birthday, dear Ballard ♪
- [chuckling through phone]
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
- You're gonna help me blow it out?
- Yeah.
Ready? One, two, three.
- Yay!
- [applauding through phone]
[Ballard]
Did you guys make these yourself? Boys?
- Daddy made the ugly ones.
- Of course he did.
- That is true. Yeah.
- [chuckles]
[knocks on door]
[sighs]
We found a '95 blue Ford registered
to a dude named Coleman up in Topanga.
And he's got a record for stalking.
- Well, that fits our guy's MO.
- That's what I thought.
But the court documents
are sealed for privacy
so we don't know much more than that.
[stammers] I can check it out.
Our firm deals with
these kind of creeps all the time.
Yeah, I'll swing by, see if there's
anything suspicious enough for a warrant.
You going alone? No backup?
You volunteering?
Great. The city ride won't start,
and I'm not waiting for a jump.
So, hope you like it bumpy.
[chuckles]
Martina said Topanga,
I didn't know she meant this far out.
You know, we should've taken my Bimmer.
Bulletproof windows.
Perks of owning my own security company.
It's a door knock, Rawls. Calm down.
- You nervous?
- Oh. [blows raspberry]
We don't know anything about this guy.
What's the harm in calling
for a little bit of backup?
I call out the whole dog-and-pony show,
and he's not our killer--
- You got a little bit of egg on your face?
- [chuckles] Oh, man.
Big deal.
[sighs] Easy for you to say.
["Me Estas Olvidando" playing]
Are you Andrei?
I am.
- And you are Colleen.
- Yeah.
[grunts]
I hear Ukrainians are coffee connoisseurs.
Is it good?
No. But I will have another.
Oh, okay.
I appreciate you helping me.
[stammers] Can I pay you for your time?
I am paid well by Mr. Rawls.
Is he a good boss?
A loyal employee
would never answer this question.
Well, then you passed the test. [chuckles]
Oh... [gasps, whispers] ...my God.
I'm so sorry.
You are a policeman?
Um, undercover.
Very deep.
Long drive for a whole lot of nothing.
[sighs] You know, a little positivity
goes a long way in this job.
You should get some.
Rawls.
- I told you this was just a door-knock.
- I'm just taking a look.
[Ballard]
You know what's so frustrating about you?
You could actually be good at this
if you quit acting like a boot.
Look, I know you're going through it
right now with your old partner and all.
But I'm not your enemy.
[car engine revs]
Son of a bitch.
[Ted] Now what do we do?
Now we call for backup.
Right. [sighs]
4 King 80 requesting backup, airship,
Topanga Canyon.
[static on radio]
That's not good.
[Ballard] Where the hell
is this guy going?
4 King 80 requesting backup,
airship in Topanga Canyon.
Looks like we're on our own.
Great.
Look at that dust.
[Ted] Whoa.
Great. [sighs]
All right. Keep your eyes
on the back doors as we approach.
I'm gonna cover you
while you clear the passenger side.
But slow and easy.
Shots fired ends badly for everyone.
Exit the vehicle! Put your hands up!
Police! Exit the vehicle!
[engine rumbling]
[Ted] Passenger side clear.
[magazine loading]
- LAPD! Drop down your weapon now!
- Get off my goddamn land!
- I don't care what kind of PI you are.
- Mr. Coleman, we are LAPD!
- Drop your weapon!
- I didn't break any
of her bullshit restraining orders.
- We're investigating a murder.
- A murder?
- Put the gun down.
- The hell is she saying now?
[Ballard] Drop your weapon now!
- It's just not fair.
- Backup's on the way, sir.
She has everything!
Drop it.
[Ted] Come on, buddy.
Put your hands behind your head.
Get on your knees.
- [breathes shakily]
- [Ballard] On your knees.
I just wanna see my kids.
[breathes shakily] All right?
[stammers] I'm not a stalker, I swear.
I didn't kill anybody.
She won't... She won't let me see 'em.
Okay, buddy. Come on. Easy does it.
Come on. [chuckles] Think about it.
Two basic rules. All you need is a ball.
It's the most accessible sport
in the world.
And the most popular.
Okay, okay. I see you.
But if you're gonna get me into soccer,
I'm gonna get you into football.
The steroid-fueled concussion factory?
I don't think so.
[stammers] What? Come on.
Rams play, like, two miles away
from your office.
Would make a pretty great second date.
You're very confident.
It's one of my flaws.
Seriously though,
I would kill for the experience
you're getting in Cold Cases.
I'm shooting for detective
in a couple years.
Mmm.
What?
Just picturing you in a suit.
And how do I look?
[sports hosts on TV chattering]
They're paying this guy 50 million a year,
and it's a total waste
with this offensive line.
- [Gary] Hey, Teddy.
- Hey.
- Hey, buddy. You missed kickoff.
- Yeah, sorry.
I was stuck in the woods for an hour
waiting for the blue suits
to impound that--
Hey. Let's get you a drink, huh?
Yeah, yeah.
No case talk in front of Dad, okay?
I don't want him to get his hopes up
about Sarah until we got a solid lead.
Oh.
Right. Um, it's probably gonna be a while.
Ballard's got us chasing down
every van this side of Vegas.
Hey, look, she might be a pain,
but she's right for the job. Hmm?
You gotta be kidding me. Hey, Jakey
They're going for it on 4th and 1.
Okay. Yeah.
Jake can feel what he wants about Ballard,
but he pays me to think for him.
If she's bungling the investigation,
I need to know.
Oh, no, I wouldn't go that far.
Hmm.
[Gary, Pearlman] Oh!
Sounds like you and Rawls had a real Butch
and Sundance moment out there in Topanga.
I mean, it got a little intense,
but then the guy settled down.
I wasn't worried about the suspect.
I was worried about Rawls.
Four hours together? [laughs]
I thought you'd be
the only one driving back from Topanga.
[smacks lips] He is a police boy for sure,
but he didn't do too badly out there.
Mmm. And what about the suspect, Coleman?
Well, Darcy's rushing his DNA,
but he's not our guy.
I'm sure of it.
Between him and Javier, we're 0 for 2.
- [sighs]
- Yeah.
Just got confirmation
from the authorities in Mexico.
Luis Ibarra is definitely our John Doe.
And... [sighs] ...he had a baby
a year before he went missing.
So the kid in the video's probably his.
[sighs]
Do they know where the kid is now?
Federales are tracking down
next of kin to notify them.
Maybe with them?
- Let's hope.
- Mmm.
Interesting choice of venue.
Yeah, no cops.
And they make a killer Singapore sling.
Okay. Guys, where do we go from here?
Javi's intel is holding up,
but it's not getting us any closer
to who killed our John Doe.
I think we should track down
Ibarra's family ourselves.
They may know something.
We can't count on the Federales.
- So tomorrow, why don't we do first--
- Tomorrow?
Tomorrow, you're out, right?
Why?
The funeral.
I don't know if I'm going to that.
He was your partner.
You shouldn't let those RHD assholes
keep you away.
She's right.
Whatever the baggage,
you'll regret it if you don't go.
All right. [sighs]
- [Laffont] Ballard.
- [sighs] Sorry. I didn't mean to pry.
I just was...
It's all good. Fine.
[sighs, smacks lips]
[mournful music plays]
[Olivas] You two made a great team.
Just came by to offer my condolences.
Never lost a partner. I can't imagine.
[Laffont] Saved us some seats over here.
Robert.
Hey, Tom.
Renée.
I didn't know you were coming.
Blame her.
She thought you could use
some solidarity today.
[Barrel] As most of you know,
Ken Chastain was my boot detective
just a thousand years ago.
First day I met him, Captain called me in.
I'm expecting to meet my new partner.
And there was this kid.
Baby face, wide eyes,
ready to fight for the good in the world.
I thought to myself, "How in the hell
did this mook make detective?"
[mourners laugh]
[Barrel] Well, pretty quickly
I found out that he had the stuff.
No doubt, the guy was a goofball.
But we all know that
that goofball act is vital
to how we survive doing this job.
It's how we look past that line
of life and death
that we all walk every day.
Ken Chastain could always be depended on.
When things got bad,
he was the guy you wanted in your corner.
He was the one who would give you
the shirt off his back...
and then he would tell you
that it made you look fat.
[mourners chuckle]
To my friend. Ken!
[all] Ken!
Did I muck it up?
No, no. It was great. Great.
[Laffont] I know he let you down, Renée.
I'd like to think I wouldn't have.
But honestly, I know what it's like...
to need to keep your head down.
Widow on your 6:00.
Glad we came.
I'm glad she came.
I can see why she read you in.
[chuckles]
It would've meant a lot to him
that you're here.
I know things didn't... [sighs]
...end well between you.
We had a lot of good times too.
He told me about your argument
the other night.
[inhales sharply]
He's been messed up for a while.
I tried so hard to get him to rehab.
He was scared it would ruin his career.
I had no idea it was that bad.
[sighs]
And he knew he got it wrong, Renée.
About Olivas.
He overheard something at work recently.
Olivas joking about sleeping
with an ex-partner,
saying that she was back for more.
But it was the way that Olivas said it.
It was like he had crossed a line
with this woman.
And Ken realized...
you were telling the truth.
It hit him hard, Renée.
[sighs] Goodbye. Take care of yourself.
[sighs] Oh.
- Hey.
- Morning.
Did you ever hear back from Andrei?
[stutters] I did. That's why I wanted
to catch you before you went inside.
Tell me.
Um...
Yulia's parents were killed
in the conflict.
The whole town was pretty much leveled.
Um...
Which is why you haven't been able
to do your magic...
[stutters] Your Internet magic,
not your other magic.
- Oh, okay.
- I'm sorry, Colleen.
That's...
Wow.
[smacks lips, stammers]
You can go back inside. I just...
I need a minute. I'll be okay.
[sniffles]
[sniffles, sighs]
[Colleen sighs]
Thanks for coming yesterday. Meant a lot.
It was no trouble.
[Ballard] So, why are we here?
Mr. Fuentes is very eager
to help the LAPD out in any way he can.
Oh. He was very eager to do
a lot of things last time we saw him.
But his cooperation
is predicated on a deal.
What kind of deal?
Time served and protection.
Why should we trust an ex-con
with known ties to the cartel?
That's exactly why.
[sighs] If he's talking,
he needs assurances.
Look, due to backlogs,
my client has been denied trial
for longer than the sentence
he would've received.
And he's endured life-changing injuries
as a result.
We'd like time served
and witness protection.
Not if he's involved.
I promise you that's not the case.
Well, I'll take it to the DA,
but she'll only deal if the intel's good.
The gun that killed Ibarra was, like...
recycled.
We know the cartel runs guns
through Mexico and back.
It's not our jurisdiction.
It's not the cartel.
It's the cops.
Go on.
A ring of cops is running hot guns.
They take 'em straight off the streets
and sell them to the cartel for big bank.
It's not just guns.
They got their hands in all
the cartel shit. Drugs, trafficking...
Is this why Ibarra was killed?
You're not listening.
This is way bigger than a coyote, or some
fool like me frontin' big on the block.
Then what's a fool like you know about it?
I needed a piece.
You ask, you get.
Who gave it to you?
It was definitely a cop.
LAPD. White dude, 40s.
Street guys call him Montana.
He lives for this gang shit, but
he doesn't mind playing sheriff either.
He's playing both sides.
Uses his badge for fun.
A few years back,
a huge raid locked up five homeboys.
Two got sent to intensive care,
compliments of this dude.
That's all I know.
But if you find him,
I bet you find the others.
[Parker] And there's no chance Javi
was talking about a different raid?
[Laffont] No. This has to be the one.
It's the right time frame.
Uh, five lockups, two ICUs.
Although, it is unclear
who put those two in the hospital.
Of course it is.
FID'd wanna keep that quiet.
I could pull personnel files
for everyone on the raid.
Try to narrow it down
based on Javi's description.
But that would leave a paper trail.
Lucky for you I got them already.
And with no digital footprint.
Look at you burying our lede.
You know I have a flair for the dramatic.
What did Javi say, uh... Mid-40s, white...
Here are six candidates.
How did you get these?
Apparently there are still some women
who are not immune to my roguish charms.
Oh, Linda from personnel? Still?
Why the tone of surprise?
This guy, Anthony Driscoll.
He's got more than a few complaints
against him for excessive force.
Javi said Montana was violent.
In lieu of termination, resigned 2022.
Under the influence of illegal narcotics.
- Wait, what did you say his name was?
- Anthony Driscoll.
Anthony AKA Tony.
Who's another Tony with a violent streak
and a drug problem?
Tony Montana.
Y'all, Scarface is like
a patron saint to gangbangers.
All right.
Let's get a six-pack in front of Javi.
[Javi] That's him right there.
That's the cabrón they call Montana.
No doubt in my mind.
[Ballard] Let's start a workup
on Driscoll.
Everything that he did in the department
and everything he's done since.
Oh, uh, first thing tomorrow?
I gotta pick up Ralph
from doggy day care, okay?
- Well, obviously. First thing tomorrow.
- Bye.
You good?
[scoffs] Moratorium on anyone asking
me that for the next couple of months.
Okay.
- You good?
- You kidding?
Finally got confirmation on what
I suspected after all these years?
I am ready to get those fuckers.
Aren't you?
I'm just preparing myself.
Last time I came for one
of the Brotherhood it didn't go so well.
[inhales deeply] The complaint you filed?
[sighs] Against Olivas, right?
- Yeah.
- Hmm.
You know what that was about?
Figured if you wanted me to know.
I want you to know.
He tried to assault me at a party.
Chastain saw me afterwards, and I thought
he would back me up but he didn't.
So, Olivas got away with it.
I'm sorry that happened to you.
Me too.
Thanks.
Have a good night, Ballard.
So...
[sighs]
...tell me about your new girlfriend.
[chuckles]
[inaudible chatter]