[keys clacking]
[Modest Mouse's
"The World at Large"]
♪ ♪
BROCK:
♪ Ice age heat wave ♪
‐ "Verbally threatening
suicide,
"recent loss of a loved one
to death,
expressions of hopelessness
and anger..."
‐ "Sudden decline
in academic performance,
"increased used
of mind‐altering substances,
loss of interest in sex."
Alaska displayed
two of those warning signs.
She had lost,
though not recently, her mom.
She was definitely drinking
a lot more at the end.
‐ She did talk about dying.
‐ Yeah, to be pretentious,
not because she meant it.
‐ Her grades didn't drop,
and she sure as hell
didn't lose interest in sex.
I mean, you had to like sex
an awful lot
to make out
with your scrawny ass.
‐ Funny.
BROCK:
♪ And the nights get cold ♪
♪ I like the autumn,
but this place is getting old ♪
♪ I pack up my belongings,
and I head for the coast ♪
♪ It might not be a lot,
but I feel like ♪
‐ Her mood could be
so unpredictable.
Whenever she didn't feel
like answering
"how," "when," "why,"
or "what" questions,
she could get so dark.
COLONEL: What?
And I can't get dark?
By the way, you haven't been
all sunshine and rainbows
lately,
and you not gonna off yourself.
Wait, are you?
‐ Funny.
BROCK:
♪ I couldn't hear my mouth ♪
♪ My thoughts were so loud ♪
♪ ♪
‐ Okay, I have a theory.
It's not terribly likely,
but it is plausible.
So that night, the phone rings.
It's Jake, calling to wish her
a happy anniversary.
What a nice guy.
So she feels awful
for hooking up with Pudge
and wants to go see him.
So now she's furious and drunk
and just mad at herself.
She's driving along,
and she sees the cop car.
And in a flash,
everything comes together
and she does it.
Not because she was drunk,
but because she killed herself.
[solemn music]
‐ That's ridiculous.
We've already been over this.
She wasn't thinking
about Jake‐‐
‐ Do you even care about her
or give a fuck about the truth?
‐ What are you
even talking about?
‐ Easy, Colonel.
‐ If she loved you so much,
why'd she leave that night?
And if you loved her so much,
why'd you help her go?
I was drunk.
What's your excuse?
‐ Shut up.
‐ [huffs]
‐ Fuck you.
♪ ♪
‐ What the fuck
is y'all looking at?
♪ ♪
HYDE: "How will we ever
get out of this labyrinth
of suffering"?
And lately, we have all been
given more than enough reason
to despair,
but here you all are
in my class.
In the face of great sadness,
you are all getting through.
You are, as they say,
surviving.
So as you work on your paper,
as you try to answer
the question
of the late Alaska Young,
ask yourself...
"What is my cause for hope"?
COLONEL:
Hey, Pudge.
Pudge, slow those
scrawny legs down, man.
I, uh...
I know I said
some pretty hurtful shit,
and I was wrong.
I just want things
to be normal again.
Just me and you, normal.
‐ That's all I want.
‐ I feel like
if we just knew...
‐ You're right.
We have to keep on looking.
‐ What if we don't figure
anything out?
‐ There are answers
to every mystery,
just gotta know where to look.
Good thing I got a plan.
[door bangs open]
Excuse me.
I'm Alaska Young's brother,
and I need to speak
to the cop who saw her die.
[phone ringing]
Extracted from MKV & Synchronized By X Person
[over radio]
OFFICER: 26‐8‐7, repeat.
Extracted from MKV & Synchronized By X Person
OFFICER CONWAY:
You sure you're 19?
COLONEL:
Excuse my French, officer,
but that's bullshit.
You can get married
at 18‐‐hell, 14
with your parents' permission,
but I have to wait till I'm 19
to smoke?
So you're 18.
‐ Man, write me a ticket.
We just need to know
what you saw.
[birds chirping]
[glass shatters]
I've seen plenty,
but I ain't never seen that.
She didn't brake.
She just hit it.
Thought I was gonna die.
But here I am.
‐ Did she say anything?
Like, did she have
any last words?
‐ Sorry, it's kind of a thing
he's into.
‐ She was, uh...
She was passed on, son.
‐ Do you think it was
an accident?
[somber music]
♪ ♪
‐ Well, I...I been
a state trooper for 26 years.
I seen more drunks
than you can count.
Never seen anybody so drunk
they can't swerve.
‐ How drunk was she?
‐ [clears throat]
Her, uh, blood alcohol was .21.
That's drunk, certainly.
It's powerful drunk.
♪ ♪
‐ Is there any chance
we can get a copy
of the police report?
[door clicks open]
‐ Um, I'm not supposed
to do that
and certainly not to hand over
to some kids.
‐ I understand, officer.
I really do.
But we're desperate
and just searching
for any sort of clues
as to what happened
and maybe, just maybe,
there's something
in that police report
that can help us out.
‐ All right,
but only because you're family.
I'll go copy what I can
for you boys.
I hope you find
what you're looking for.
COLONEL:
Well, that cop
just convinced me
it might have been a suicide.
And if she knew
what she was doing,
she made us accomplices, Pudge,
and I hate her for that.
‐ Maybe we should
just let her be dead.
[solemn country music]
SINGER:
♪ So I looked her in the eyes ♪
‐ You kids go to Culver Creek?
[clears throat]
Y'all had a death up there.
Uh, awful sorry to hear that.
It's on the house.
♪ ♪
COLONEL:
I always knew Alaska was good
for something.
It turns out she was.
TAKUMI:
Free Ding Dong.
‐ The web says that suicides
usually involve
carefully thought out plans,
but nothing in that report
makes it seem like
she thought this out.
Her car had college brochures,
and she was clearly planning
for the future.
‐ Okay, fine.
It wasn't suicide.
‐ But it doesn't make sense
as an accident either.
‐ [sighs]
We're really making progress.
‐ We have one move left.
The only way to get
into Alaska's head that night
is to get as drunk as she was.
The Eagle keeps a breathalyzer
in his house, and we need it.
[doorbell rings]
‐ Gentlemen,
this is a pleasant surprise.
‐ So is the sight
of your upper lip.
‐ Can I get you boys
a couple of croque monsieurs?
I just happened to be
cooking up a petit déjeuner,
if you are interested.
‐ Uh, no thank you, sir.
‐ Uh, we‐‐we just ate.
[chuckles]
‐ So, what brings you
to the Eagle's Nest?
Yes, I know what you call me.
It's charming.
MILES:
They are a majestic bird, sir.
COLONEL:
And patriotic.
‐ Um, but anyway,
we've been talking,
and we think it would be nice
to do something official
to memorialize Alaska.
COLONEL:
Uh, perhaps you didn't hear us.
We already ate.
‐ Yes, I have company.
[toilet flushes]
MILES:
Uh, those look fantastic.
COLONEL: Madame O'Malley!
EAGLE: Thank you.
Oh, mon Dieu!
I had no idea you and the Eag‐‐
Mr. Starnes‐‐
were spending time together.
You know, the French are known
for their sophistication.
MILES:
Yep, they are
very sophisticated
with their taste, I've heard.
‐ Well, I'm from Albuquerque,
originally, but‐‐
COLONEL: Oh, great place.
O'MALLEY: Merci, Chip.
Gonna go grade some papers.
COLONEL: Oh, come on!
Grading papers can wait.
Plus, you have a delicious
egg sando coming fresh
off the stove.
[Miles chuckles nervously]
And I need to know
all the deets about you two.
Mr. Starnes, you sly devil...
‐ Watch your step, Chip.
‐ Wow, that is some
high‐end fromage.
COLONEL:
Oh, wow.
MILES: Really should not
be interrupting
this, uh, petit déjeuner.
O'MALLEY: Hang out, Miles.
‐ I can't take credit.
Um... but anyway,
we should get going.
[door clicks shut]
COLONEL: Yeah, we should go.
MILES: 'Cause we got
so many things‐‐
‐ Was that the front door?
‐ I did not hear anything.
‐ Neither did I.
‐ Merde, are you two
up to something?
MILES:
Ah, merde.
[music playing over speakers]
‐ Sorry, I... think
I might still just be
a little on edge,
and you two don't exactly have
the best reputation.
‐ It's totally understandable.
COLONEL:
We have been known to cause
a little trouble
in the past.
‐ There's no comfort
from this grief, is there?
It's just been awful.
But some kind of memorial
would be lovely.
I'll think about it
over Christmas break.
‐ Thank you
for your kind consideration.
‐ And I am gonna be sending
you two a mistletoe.
Y'all are crazy cute,
and I'm rooting for you.
Don't have too much fun.
‐ Thank you, Mr. Martin.
‐ A bientôt.
[J‐Kwon's "Tipsy"]
J‐KWON: ♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ ♪
‐ Ah, help me, Pudge!
MILES: All right.
‐ Help!
‐ That's shot number six.
We gotta go again.
Drinking this much vodka
is bad enough,
but it's the milk
that may actually kill me.
‐ It says there are
no tire marks.
That means she didn't brake.
That's suicide.
‐ Unless she fell asleep.
I don't know if you can
drive straight
while y‐you're asleep,
but if anyone could‐‐
‐ One of y'all can be
a guinea pig
for that little experiment.
[exhales]
J‐KWON:
♪ Homeboy tripping,
he don't know ♪
‐ Oh, it burns!
It burns.
‐ Okay, blow hard into this
for at least two seconds.
‐ Is that what you told Lara?
MILES: Shut up.
‐ [blowing]
[device beeps]
MILES: .14.
‐ Oh, come on, man!
‐ You're almost 2/3
of the way there.
‐ Well, I'm 3/4 of the way
to puking.
J‐KWON:
♪ Everybody in the club
getting tipsy ♪
‐ Ooh.
J‐KWON: ♪ Everybody
in the club getting tipsy ♪
♪ Two, here comes the three
to the four to the five ♪
♪ Now I'm looking at shorty
right in her eyes ♪
‐ I did it!
MILES: .21!
Way to go, Colonel.
J‐KWON:
♪ In the club getting tipsy ♪
MILES: Sit back down.
TAKUMI: Whoa, take it easy.
‐ I'm gonna puke.
‐ No, no, no, no, no, no.
You can't‐‐you can't do that.
If you do that,
you're gonna ruin
the whole experiment,
and we need more information.
We need you to pass
the field sobriety test.
MILES:
Just walk a straight line.
‐ Oh, that's it?
BOTH: Yeah.
‐ I can do that for sure.
Was she really this drunk?
TAKUMI:
Apparently.
Hey, could you drive right now?
‐ No, no, no, no, no.
Pudge, we're really stupid.
‐ We were worse than stupid.
[melancholy music]
She must have been wasted.
Why did we believe her
when she said she wasn't?
♪ ♪
‐ Because we never knew
if she was drunk or not...
if she was happy or not.
And we always did
what she wanted.
[banging on door]
[clattering]
MILES: Cry.
‐ What?
‐ Cry.
EAGLE: I'm coming in.
[lock snapping]
‐ [whimpering]
EAGLE:
Do you have any idea
what time it is?
What is going on in here?
[Colonel sobbing]
MILES: Uh‐‐uh, we do,
and‐‐and I'm really,
really sorry.
The Colonel's just having
a really tough time right now.
It's the Alaska thing.
It's just really hitting him.
I didn't know what to do,
so I got Takumi.
‐ My‐‐my, uh, shoulder's known
as Culver Creek's best
for crying on.
‐ Mr. Martin, is there anything
that I can do?
‐ [breathes deeply]
No, sir.
I'm just really grateful
I have such good friends.
‐ I am too.
Mr. Hikohito, why don't you
get back to your room?
It's well past your bedtime.
And Miles...
Just keep an eye on him, okay?
If he needs a grief counselor,
the school can provide one.
MILES: Will do.
EAGLE: Thank you, Miles.
Now, lights out.
[ambient music]
♪ ♪
[Colonel snoring]
JUDY:
How are you, Miles?
WALT:
You hanging in there, pal?
‐ I'm, uh... you know.
JUDY:
Well, we are so excited
that you're coming home.
WALT:
Yeah,
your mom's almost forgiven you
for bailing on Thanksgiving.
She didn't stop talking
about all the leftover
cranberry sauce.
JUDY:
That is untrue,
because there are
never leftovers
when your Uncle Melvin
joins us.
WALT:
Don't shame Uncle Mel.
He got the lap band surgery,
and he's doing great now.
[voices fading]
♪ ♪
JUDY: ...talk about
the surgery, Miles?
Miles, are you there?
‐ Uh, I love you guys.
I'll see you soon.
[phone clatters]
♪ ♪
Hey.
Her plastic daisies.
When we were packing up
her room,
do you remember,
were her plastic daisies
in there?
‐ I don't know.
What?
Why?
‐ Where's the police report?
COLONEL:
What's going on, Pudge?
MILES:
Holy shit.
Here it is.
Found in her car:
her plastic daisies.
The daisies mean something.
Why would she leave here with
plastic daisies in her car?
‐ She was on the phone
with Jake,
and she got upset
when he brought up
their anniversary,
so maybe in her
feminist fashion,
she was bringing him flowers
to apologize?
‐ Yeah, maybe.
‐ We need to talk to Jake.
Maybe he can explain it.
‐ I don't know.
‐ We have to go where
the investigation takes us,
even if we don't like
what we find.
Oh.
I still feel like death
warmed over.
So I'm gonna need you
to do all the talking.
Can you turn off the sun?
[guitar strumming softly]
♪ ♪
[phone ringing]
[phone beeps]
‐ Yo.
MILES: Hey, Jake.
It's Miles.
‐ Oh, hey, Miles.
Good to hear from you, man.
Actually been thinking
of calling you.
‐ Is that right?
JAKE: Yeah.
You and I are kind of in
the same boat, you know?
How we felt about her,
how we feel now,
like an Alaska support group.
‐ That sounds nice.
Actually, Alaska is
the reason I'm calling you.
JAKE:
Yeah, she's all
I think about too.
See, man, we're the same.
‐ Um, is there any chance
that she was driving
to bring you plastic daisies?
JAKE:
Sorry, what does that
have to do with anything?
‐ Um... I‐I don't know.
I, uh‐‐it sounds weird
saying it out loud.
Maybe it wasn't a clue
after all.
‐ It's funny.
I remember the day I met her.
[dramatic music]
She had a daisy in her hair,
sitting on that bridge,
just so freaking sad.
So freaking beautiful,
just drinking all alone.
I'm so confused, man.
‐ Hang up.
‐ Shh.
JAKE: She broke up with me
and I still love her.
‐ I'm really sorry, Jake,
I‐I didn't mean to upset you.
I‐I'll call you again, okay?
That was really rude.
‐ We got as much
as we gonna get
out of that beautiful, sad man.
So the daisies
weren't for Jake.
‐ Yeah, as I've been saying.
‐ And they had nothing to do
with the anniversary,
but where else
do you take flowers?
‐ Uh, a wedding.
‐ Why would you drive off
crying and hysterical
if you're going to a wedding?
‐ A funeral.
‐ No, Alaska don't know
nobody who died.
‐ Not recently.
Come on.
[keys clacking]
"Mary Ellen Young leaves behind
a daughter, Alaska."
This is it.
This is her.
‐ Look at the date.
December 12th, 1997.
‐ Which is the same date
that Alaska died.
‐ And the anniversary
of the day she met Jake.
‐ Which is also the anniversary
of her mom's death.
‐ I forgot.
BOTH: That's where
she was going!
‐ Holy shit.
[exhales deeply]
‐ Takumi, my man.
We was looking for you.
‐ You missed class.
MILES: We solved it.
I saw a daisy on the wall
by the payphone
and remembered
her plastic daisies,
and they were in the car
with her,
because she was driving
to her mother's grave.
COLONEL:
It was the anniversary
of her mom's death,
which she forgot‐‐well, almost.
That's why she was upset.
‐ I can't believe
we didn't think of it earlier.
‐ I mean, don't sell
yourself short, Pudge.
We thought of it eventually.
‐ Yeah.
‐ And what did I tell you?
There are always answers.
‐ Yeah, you did say that.
COLONEL: I always say that.
‐ What answers?
‐ Well,
the part about the daisy.
‐ The flowers.
TAKUMI:
Yeah, what does that prove?
We still don't know
if it was an accident
or if she did it on purpose.
What exactly have you
figured out?
Only Alaska knows
if she fell asleep
or was fumbling for a cigarette
and didn't see a cop car,
or did see it and hit the gas.
And those secrets
died with her.
Even if you did
figure it all out,
what would it change?
‐ It won't make her less dead.
‐ Listen, man,
if you don't wanna know‐‐
‐ We will never know.
This mystery can't be solved.
We have to live with that
for the rest of our lives.
[solemn music]
♪ ♪
[The Wailers'
"She's Comin' Home"]
♪ ♪
SINGER:
♪ There's a feelin'
in the air ♪
♪ Happy people everywhere ♪
JUDY: [muffled]
Miles.
WALT:
JUDY:
Miles!
SINGER:
♪ Oh, can you see ♪
JUDY: Are you gonna spend
your whole vacation
in the pool?
‐ We wanna spend some time
with you too, pal.
It's almost Christmas Eve.
‐ Okay.
I‐I'll be out in a few.
And could you get rid
of that for me?
Please.
SINGER:
♪ Christmas carols, everyone ♪
♪ My love for her I'll show ♪
♪ When I catch her
under the mistletoe ♪
♪ Oh, can you see ♪
MRS. WIGFIELD:
Any big plans
for Christmas, Chip?
‐ You're looking at it.
I'll just be here,
peddling lawn ornament reindeer
as one small cog
in the big Christmas
industrial complex.
‐ I hope you have
a happy holiday.
‐ Probably won't.
MRS. WIGFIELD: What's that now?
‐ [clears throat]
‐ I said, you too,
Ms. Wigfield.
SINGER:
♪ Now I'm so glad ♪
‐ [sighs]
‐ All right, Chip,
it's one thing to be sad,
but it's another to be rude
to my customers,
who are also our neighbors.
So leave the attitude behind
when we get to church tonight.
‐ I'm not going to church.
SINGER:
♪ Till she has to go away ♪
DOLORES:
Excuse me?
Oh, you're gonna turn
your back on Jesus?
‐ I'm pretty sure
he turned his back on me.
DOLORES:
I know you're upset, son,
but now, more than ever,
you need prayer
and community, and God.
‐ God?
What kind of God would let
a teenage girl die
in a car accident?
Not one that I need.
I'm done.
[TV narrator
speaking indistinctly]
[meerkats on TV chirping]
WALT: Hey, Miles?
Want to watch a little
Meerkat Manor with us?
‐ It's gotten really good.
Flower just evicted
Kinkaju and Mozart.
WALT: Spoiler alert.
‐ Uh, I‐I'm working.
Trying to finish this essay
for my World Religions class.
Or start it, actually.
It's important.
I'm not really interested
in the domestic issues
of meerkats.
TV narrator:
While the rest
of the Whiskers family
hang out together
in the stolen burrow,
grooming and enjoying
each other's company,
it's a very different story...
‐ I can't write
with you staring at me.
[knock at door]
I'm good.
I‐I'm sorry, I just, uh...
this‐‐this essay
is a big part of my grade,
and I don't even know
what I'm gonna write.
And so... I'm just‐‐I'm just
under a lot of pressure.
‐ Your father and I
want you to know,
you don't have to go back
to Culver Creek.
You can return
to your high school here.
You can come home, Miles.
We'll help you get over it.
‐ I'm not gonna get over it.
JUDY: I didn't mean
right away, of course.
But in time,
you will weather this storm.
‐ Not this one.
If people were rain...
I was drizzle.
And... she...
She was a hurricane, okay?
There's not gonna be
a day in my life
where I don't think about her.
‐ It feels like that now,
but it will get easier.
‐ I don't want it
to get easier!
Because then that means
that I've stopped
remembering her.
And is that what
we're rooting for here?
That‐‐that I forget her?
That she just becomes
some distant memory?
Is that you want me to do
when you die,
for me to forget you?
Because the bodies
are gonna keep on piling up,
and the longer that I live,
the more people that I know
will die.
And do I even have enough space
in my memory for all of them?
And what does it
even matter anyway?
Someday, no one will remember
that she even existed,
or that I did.
Everything falls apart...
memories too.
And then you're left
with nothing,
not even a fucking ghost.
‐ Just think about it.
[phone ringing]
‐ Hello.
MILES: Hey, Colonel.
‐ Merry Christmas Eve, Pudge.
I hope you note
that that was dripping
in irony.
MILES:
Noted.
My ability to understand
sarcasm is still intact.
‐ Good, otherwise,
this friendship is over.
And seeing as though
you are my last
remaining friend,
I can't afford to lose you.
‐ Listen, Colonel, um,
I was talking with my parents.
‐ Walter Halter and Judy.
Send them my best.
‐ Sure, I will.
But, uh, we were
discussing everything,
and...
I'm not going back
to Culver Creek.
I can't.
It's‐‐it's gonna be
spring soon,
and she's not gonna be there
to see it.
And I just...
I‐I don't wanna see a world
she will never get to see.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
‐ Okay, seasons are a thing.
There's no avoiding that.
So, uh, what you gonna do?
‐ Well, my grades were good,
and my teachers
at my old school loved me.
‐ How could they not?
‐ So my parents say
they'll be happy
to have me back.
‐ Well, good.
That's great.
Must be so nice to be able
to run away from your problems
and know everything's
gonna be all right.
I wish you a soft landing,
and good luck.
♪ ♪
[soft folk music]
SINGER:
♪ Think of you quite often ♪
♪ Wondering how you've been ♪
♪ ♪
[gravel crunching]
♪ Memories are not so bad ♪
♪ They crawl under my skin ♪
♪ ♪
‐ Sorry,
we're closed for tonight.
SINGER:
♪ The last thing
we could picture ♪
♪ You waved to me good‐bye ♪
♪ ♪
‐ What are you doing here?
‐ Dr. Hyde!
SINGER:
♪ I think it's worth a try ♪
‐ You didn't want
to go to church.
Looks like church
did come to you.
SINGER:
♪ 'Cause oh ♪
♪ You are ♪
♪ Such beautiful friends ♪
♪ The beautiful prize ♪
♪ And ♪
♪ All we know ♪
‐ Here we go.
COLONEL:
No, Mom.
I don't want a cookie.
I can't believe you called him.
‐ I can't believe he came.
We're honored
to have you here, Dr. Hyde.
I'ma leave you all alone,
but if you need anything,
you just holler.
‐ Thank you, Dolores.
‐ Thank you.
[door clicks shut]
‐ So...
I understand you're having
a crisis of faith.
‐ No crisis, no faith.
‐ People need to believe
in something, Mr. Martin.
‐ Yeah, well, people are fools.
HYDE:
So you're prepared
to render judgment
on all of humanity?
‐ Just fools.
Look, I appreciate
you coming out here,
but it's not necessary.
I really don't need to hear
no inspirational
"it's all God's plan,"
circle of life bullshit.
‐ That's not why I'm here.
‐ So you're not here
to cheer me up?
‐ I am not.
I'm here to be with you.
You're grieving,
so let yourself grieve.
You don't have to fight it.
‐ Well,
maybe I feel like fighting.
Alaska's dead,
Miles isn't coming back,
and I'm spending Christmas Eve
with my teacher.
HYDE:
So be with your anger.
Allow yourself to feel
what you're feeling.
The only hope of getting
to the other side of this
is to go through it,
and I'm here
to go through it with you.
‐ Yeah, well, you're gonna be
sitting here for a long time.
‐ Well, that's all right.
I got no place to be.
It's all right.
It's okay.
‐ [gently sobbing]
HYDE:
It's okay.
‐ [sobbing]
[yells]
HYDE:
It's okay, son.
It's okay.
COLONEL:
[sobbing]
I don't understand
why He has to take my friend.
I just miss my friend.
HYDE:
I know, son.
I know.
Just let it out.
That's good.
I miss her too.
‐ [sobbing]
[Hyde gently shushes]
[solemn music]
♪ ♪
ALASKA:
"Great Perhaps."
I like it.
It's just ambiguous enough.
Unquantifiable,
kind of magical.
Hell of a metaphor.
♪ ♪
[low chatter]
‐ So.
Looks like I'm not getting
a single after all.
‐ Sorry to let you down.
‐ You can never let me down,
you skinny bastard.
[uplifting music]
♪ ♪
[bell tolling]
[birds chirping]
EAGLE:
We put a lot of thought
into how best to remember her,
and so I am proud to present
the Alaska Young
memorial bench.
Alaska loved to read,
and so maybe,
with spring upon us,
other students will sit
on her bench,
reading and daring to dream.
[applause]
COLONEL:
A bench.
They gave her a fucking bench?
She would have hated that shit.
LARA:
Well, then get her something
she would have loved.
‐ What, like shitty wine
and pretentious metaphors?
‐ I don't know.
How 'bout a prank?
‐ Yes.
That's great.
A memorial prank.
‐ Alaska Young Memorial Prank.
TAKUMI:
She did have that one idea
she was working on.
She was saving it
for our senior prank.
Never made it out
of the planning phases,
but it's really good.
‐ Executed as designed,
it's more than just good.
It's epic.
But to pull it off,
we gonna need more
than just us.
‐ True, we're gonna need
the whole school,
and we could get in
so much trouble.
‐ I'm in.
LARA: Me too.
‐ Down.
‐ Let's make history.
[Goldfrapp's "Ooh La La"]
♪ ♪
GOLDFRAPP:
♪ Dial up ♪
‐ Hey, man, I can't
give you any more free stuff.
Management was not pleased.
‐ I don't want
a free Ding Dong, Gus.
‐ What you want?
‐ I want you.
‐ Oh, hey.
‐ Sara, I need you.
‐ Please don't do this.
‐ What?
No, not like that.
LONGWELL: What's going on?
‐ Jesus, Longwell,
put a damn shirt on.
Your alabaster skin
is blinding me.
‐ What's this about, Chip?
GOLDFRAPP:
♪ Switch me on ♪
‐ Something bigger
than all of us.
‐ Okay.
‐ Miles, what's wrong?
MILES: Hey, uh...
remember when you stole
the school bell
and buried it in the cemetery?
‐ Greatest prank
in Culver Creek history, yeah.
‐ Well, how would you like
to be a part
of the new greatest prank ever?
‐ Go on.
‐ Mr. Starnes,
Miles and I are here
as representatives
of the junior class
to let you know that
we've selected our speaker
for Speaker Day.
‐ Well, wonderful.
It's always
such an enriching day.
Please, who is it?
‐ It's a close friend
of Miles' dad.
‐ Dr. William Morse.
He's a professor
at a university in Florida.
He studies
adolescent sexuality.
‐ Mm.
Aiming for controversy, are we?
‐ Oh, no.
I‐I mean, I've met Dr. Morse.
He's interesting,
but not controversial.
He just, uh, studies
the adolescents' understanding
of sex and how it's constantly
changing and growing.
‐ He's opposed
to premarital sex.
EAGLE: Ah.
‐ Oh.
Well, Lee, this sounds
très intéressant.
When it comes
to teenage sexuality,
the most important organ
is their mind.
GOLDFRAPP:
♪ Ooh, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ I need la, la,
la, la, la, la ♪
‐ Let me give him a call.
[phone buttons beeping]
[line trilling]
‐ [in sophisticated voice]
Dr. Morse speaking.
EAGLE:
Welcome, everyone.
This is a day of historic
significance at Culver Creek.
It was the vision
of our founder, Phillip Garden,
who thought that you,
as students,
and we, as faculty,
should take one afternoon
a year
to benefit
from the wisdom of voices
outside of the school.
Now, this year, we have two
distinguished guests.
The senior class has chosen
Alabama Assistant
Attorney General Tim Harris.
Welcome, Tim.
And the junior class
has selected a speaker
equally as compelling,
just not quite as punctual,
it would appear.
[door thuds open]
EAGLE:
Ah, there he is.
The junior class speaker.
Dr. William Morse
is a professor of psychology
at the University
of Central Florida
and a widely respected scholar.
‐ They talking about you.
‐ Okay, smile.
‐ This‐‐this itches, this...
EAGLE: ...very interesting.
So please help me welcome
Dr. William Morse.
Doctor.
[applause]
Welcome.
Thank you for being here.
Thank you.
‐ [clears throat]
[microphone feedback screeches]
‐ Did we confirm he can read?
‐ Good afternoon.
I'm here today to talk with you
about the fascinating subject
of teenage sexuality.
Uh, my research
was in the field
of sexual linguistics,
specifically the way
that young people discuss sex
and its related questions.
In today's world,
boys are much more likely
to objectify girls' bodies
than the other way around.
Boys will say
amongst themselves
that so‐and‐so
has "perky breasts,"
while girls
will more likely say
that a boy is cute,
a term that describes
both emotional
and physical characteristics.
See, this has an effect
of turning girls
into mere objects,
while boys are seen by girls
as whole people‐‐
LARA:
Hey, Doc!
You're so hot,
I wish you would just shut up
and take off all your clothes.
[laughter]
‐ Why, thank you.
See, what just happened
is a very interesting
case study,
a female objectifying me,
a male.
It's so unusual,
I can only assume
you were kidding.
‐ She's not kidding!
Take off all your clothes!
‐ Do it, hot stuff!
‐ Yeah, baby!
[laughter]
‐ Well, it certainly
is important to subvert
the patriarchal paradigm,
and I suppose
this is one way to do so.
All right, then.
[audience murmuring]
This is for Alaska Young!
[grunts]
[Kelis' "Milkshake" playing]
KELIS:
♪ My milkshake brings ♪
♪ All the boys to the yard ♪
♪ And they're like,
"It's better than yours" ♪
♪ Damn right,
it's better than yours ♪
♪ I can teach you,
but I have to charge ♪
♪ My milkshake brings
all the boys to the yard ♪
♪ And they're like,
"It's better than yours" ♪
♪ Damn right,
it's better than yours ♪
♪ I can teach you,
but I have to charge ♪
♪ I know you want it ♪
♪ The thing that makes me ♪
♪ ♪
♪ What the guys go crazy for ♪
♪ They lose their minds ♪
♪ The way I wind ♪
♪ I think it's time ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ Warm it up ♪
‐ This is for Alaska Young!
[cheering]
‐ Yeah, Pudge!
‐ This is for Alaska Young!
[cheering]
KEVIN:
This is for Alaska Young!
HANK:
This is for Alaska!
[cheers and applause]
STUDENT:
This is for Alaska!
[cheering]
STUDENT:
This is for Alaska!
‐ Oh, my God.
KELIS:
♪ I can see you're on it ♪
♪ You want me to teach thee ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Techniques that freaks
these boys ♪
♪ ♪
♪ It can't be bought ♪
♪ Just know
thieves get caught ♪
♪ Watch if you're smart ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la ♪
EAGLE: Okay.
KELIS:
♪ Warm it up ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ The boys are waiting ♪
EAGLE:
All right, all right.
That's enough.
That's enough, Dr. Morse.
Wrap it up.
You need to leave
this campus immediately.
Please stop.
I did not approve
of anything of this nature.
GUS: Yeah!
‐ Okay.
That's enough.
Okay.
That was‐‐
well, that was unexpected.
Uh, okay.
All right.
So it's not‐‐it's not funny.
So, up next, we have,
uh, the seniors' speaker,
uh, Alabama Assistant
Attorney General Tim Harris.
Please.
[cheers and applause]
[doors click open]
Mr. Martin, Mr. Halter.
You boys have some nerve.
‐ Before you get too mad,
it can only be proven
that we brought a person
onto the campus
that we presumed to be
an expert on sexual expression,
but turned out to be someone
that expresses sexuality
expertly.
‐ What he said.
‐ I'm not mad.
‐ You're not?
‐ No, I mean, don't ever
do anything like that again.
But my goodness,
"subverting
the patriarchal paradigm"?
It's like she wrote
that speech herself.
[laughs]
[tender music]
‐ Though I am unfamiliar
with the sound,
I do believe we just heard
the Eagle laugh.
‐ Miracles do happen.
‐ Greatest prank ever.
[laughter]
Oh.
COLONEL:
I gotta hand it to him.
Gus has some moves.
MILES:
I came here looking
for a Great Perhaps,
for real friends,
and a more than minor life.
‐ What you up to?
‐ Um, finally writing
the essay for Hyde.
She said I might be a writer,
so...
I want the first thing
I write to be about her.
♪ ♪
‐ Sorry to interrupt,
but there's still one
last thing we need to do.
♪ ♪
MILES:
Until I got here,
my only friends
were the last words
of the already dead.
♪ ♪
Like William McKinley,
the third American president
to be assassinated.
He lived for several days
after he was shot.
But towards the end,
his wife started crying
and screaming,
"I want to go too."
With his last measure
of strength,
McKinley turned to his wife
and spoke his last words,
"We are all going."
And then Alaska had to go,
because I screwed up
and the Colonel screwed up
and we let her go
and she slipped
through our fingers.
♪ ♪
We will always live
with things done
and things left undone
that day.
If only we could see
the endless string
of consequences
that result
from our smallest actions.
♪ ♪
But we can't know better
until knowing better
is useless.
♪ ♪
I thought at first
that she was just dead,
just darkness.
Just a body
being eaten by bugs.
I still sometimes think
that the afterlife
is just something we made up
to ease the pain of loss,
to make our time
in the labyrinth bearable.
But here's what gives me hope.
If you take Alaska's
genetic code
and you add
her life experiences
and the relationships
she had with people,
and then you take the size
and shape of her body,
you do not get her.
There is something else
entirely.
There's a part of her
greater than the sum
of her knowable parts.
♪ ♪
And that part
has to go somewhere,
because energy once created
is never destroyed.
♪ ♪
And if Alaska took
her own life,
that is the hope I wish
I could have given her,
to understand that anything
in life is survivable,
because we
are as indestructible
as we believe ourselves to be.
♪ ♪
[engine revving]
[tires screech]
So I know she forgives me
just as I forgive her.
We cannot be born,
and we cannot die.
We can only change
shapes and sizes
and manifestations.
♪ ♪
I know so many last words,
but I'll never know hers.
I'll never know her thoughts
in those last minutes.
We'll never know
if she left us on purpose.
But the not knowing
will not keep me from caring.
♪ ♪
[sniffling]
[both sobbing]
[Colonel breathing heavy]
We must look so fucking lame.
[both sobbing]
MILES:
Alaska's last words
to me were: "To be continued."
And she was right.
I must continue
I choose the labyrinth,
even if there is no way out,
even if we're all going,
even if everything
falls apart.
♪ ♪
‐ Hi.
EAGLE: Morning.
♪ ♪
[lively chatter]
[laughter]
COLONEL: Okay.
[chatter continuing]
♪ ♪
All right.
Good.
♪ ♪
[Lara laughing]
[singer vocalizing]
[stirring music]
♪ ♪
MILES:
I will always love
Alaska Young,
my crooked neighbor,
with all my crooked heart.
♪ ♪
Thomas Edison's
last words were,
"It's very beautiful
over there."
I don't know
where "there" is...
But I believe it's somewhere.
And I hope it's beautiful.
♪ ♪
Extracted from MKV & Synchronized By X Person
[Mondo Cozmo's "Shine"]
♪ ♪
COZMO:
♪ Stick with me, Jesus ♪
♪ Through the coming storm ♪
♪ I've come to you
in search of something ♪
♪ I've lost ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Shine down a light on me ♪
♪ Show a path ♪
♪ I promise you I will return ♪
♪ If you take me back ♪
♪ Let 'em get high ♪
♪ Let 'em get stoned ♪
♪ Everything
will be all right ♪
♪ If you let it go ♪
♪ Let 'em get high ♪
♪ Let 'em get stoned ♪
♪ Everything
will be all right ♪
♪ If you let it go ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Let 'em get high ♪
♪ Let 'em get stoned ♪
♪ Everything
will be all right ♪
♪ If you let it go ♪