"And then Lord Vanon said,
'Candita, I will love you
until my dying day. Marry me!'"
"But Candita didn't wanna be owned
by some rich, alien dude."
"So she said,
'I don't love you, Lord Vanon,
but I do want to have sex with you.'"
"Lord Vanon agreed
to have sex with Candita
and showed her
his penis hands for the first time."
"She was repulsed, but she liked it."
What's with the cape, Lily?
It's my nebula protector, obviously.
Lily wrote another story.
Sarah, why don't you go
and chat with the other girls?
I'm going to have to confiscate this.
And I need to speak to your parents.
Lily Pad,
Miss Talbot called. She was really upset.
She said you'd written a story.
Something about
hands looking like...
Penises?
She asked if everything was all right
at home. It was embarrassing.
The thing is,
nice girls
don't really talk about all that
S-E-X stuff.
You know,
it's... it's just not really appropriate.
I like writing stories.
Well, maybe keep 'em to yourself.
♪ Pressure on people, people on streets... ♪
♪ Pressure ♪
♪ Pushing down on me ♪
♪ Pressing down on you, no man ask for ♪
♪ Under pressure
That burns a building down ♪
♪ Splits a family in two
Puts people on streets ♪
Are you fucking kidding me?
Fuck!
Mum?
Yeah?
Aimee's here for her appointment.
Oh shit. I completely forgot.
- All right, I'll be right down.
- Okay.
So this one has a longer labia,
which is really common.
This one's all tucked in.
With pubes, without pubes.
This one's more frilly.
This one's crooked, like mine,
and this one,
as you can see, is on its period.
- I'll go for the one with pubes.
- Great choice!
- Thank you.
- Sorry, Aimee.
I'm a bit disorganized this morning.
- Morning!
- Morning.
- Vulva cupcake?
- Ah.
Yeah.
Thanks.
They must have had a fight.
Wow.
Look at all those tits.
Yeah, I'm reorganizing
my vintage men's magazine collection.
Those are my favorites.
Oh, they're lovely.
Anyway, how you doing today, Aimee?
Well,
I had a big fight
with my best friend, Maeve,
and I'm feeling really sad about it.
But also like I wanna
punch her in the face.
Why don't we talk about it?
You seem quiet.
I'm just a bit tired.
What is it?
I just got into
the Gifted & Talented program.
I can't believe it!
I can.
I knew you'd get it.
- Hey, that's amazing!
- Thank you.
Try to enjoy it.
Otherwise, I will have to tell a joke.
Please don't.
- Knock, knock...
- No. Okay, I'm going to school.
I'll see you later.
Ay, ay, ay, ay, Mummy,
this is for you.
My friends will be jealous of these gifts.
Abeo is so generous.
Me, I'm always boasting
about my son-in-law.
The successful accountant in England.
What is she on about?
Dad's not an accountant.
I don't know.
I'll get you some more.
Ah-ah. Don't worry, Mummy. I will get it.
No, now it's not often
I get to wait on my grandson.
Oh!
- Hey!
- Hey, my sister!
Bebe. Emeka.
Hm.
- He's going to be at the wedding.
- I haven't seen him for years.
- His business is doing so well!
- Who's Emeka?
- I don't know who he is.
- And he's still single, you know.
Stop gossiping, Beryl!
- Who's Emeka?
- No one!
Eh? You were engaged!
- Engaged?
- Okay, girls.
Time to start getting ready
for the wedding!
- Mm-hmm.
- Hey! Go!
- Grandma!
- Yes.
She said
I was being unfair to Steve
because I'm too much
of a people pleaser to break up with him.
And how did that make you feel?
Like an idiot.
Because she's probably right.
She didn't have to say it
in such a mean way.
Why do you think she's right?
'Cause it's true.
I hate fights.
I hate making people feel bad.
So I just lie and tell them
what they wanna hear,
which is why
I probably won't break up with Steve,
and why I had such awful friends
for so many years.
And why I smiled at that gross,
stupid man on the bus
and made him think
he could rub his stupid dick on me.
Do you feel
that if you hadn't smiled at him,
he wouldn't have assaulted you?
I don't know.
Had you smiled at strangers before?
Had that led to them assaulting you?
Listen to me, Aimee.
What that man did to you on the bus
has nothing to do with your smile
or your personality
and is only about him.
And it is absolutely not your fault.
Do you understand?
Okay.
How do I get stronger?
Like you.
Like Maeve.
Oh, I bet you're stronger
than you think you are.
The fact that you can say you feel angry
because of the fight with Maeve,
that's a positive step towards
feeling your full spectrum of emotions.
But also,
it's not anybody's place
to tell you that you should or shouldn't
break up with your boyfriend.
Yeah, I guess so.
I mean, I did tell her to get over herself
and be with Otis,
but I think I have a point.
They're clearly in love.
Yes, he's been a bit of an arsehole,
but he's apologized a lot.
And she isn't the easiest person
to get to know, so it's kinda like...
I probably shouldn't have talked
about Otis, should I?
How was he an arsehole?
Oh.
Well, see you next time, Aimee.
Thank you.
- Oh, Aimee, can I grab a lift?
- Yeah!
- Who's that from?
- Just Eric.
♪ Sweet mother ♪
♪ Sweet mother, I no go forget you ♪
♪ For this suffer way you suffer for me... ♪
Aw!
- I like your moves.
- Thank you.
Here.
Let me fix your Aso-Oke.
Okay.
Wow! What is this called, Mum?
- "The Senator."
- Uh-huh!
- Do you like it?
- Yes! It is camp as hell!
Your grandma might hear.
Um,
who's this Emeka guy?
It was a long time ago.
We were silly teenagers.
Mmm!
Okay. And why did you not get married?
I met your father.
- Okay, you met my father in the war...
- You look lovely.
Thanks!
Thanks, Mummy!
If I could add some gold eye shadow,
I'd look even better.
I'm serious, Eric. Not here.
I'll see you outside.
Rubbish.
"Lord Vanon unsheathed
his throbbing cock-rod,
plowing Princess Zandora all night long."
The musical was weird,
but she's actually into banging aliens!
Hey, Lil, can we please talk?
What's going on?
They published my story.
Oh my God.
Hope, um,
I was wondering if I could talk to you
about getting
a gender-neutral changing room on campus?
I think it would really help
the trans and queer students here.
Cal, we can talk about whatever you like
once you come to school
wearing the correct uniform.
How exactly would you define "correct"?
Layla, could you come here, please?
Layla is a perfect example
of how you can express your identity
and still abide by school rules.
So Layla's a good NB,
and I'm a bad one. Is that right?
I don't understand your slang.
N-B.
Like, nonbinary person.
Layla, you can step back. Thank you.
I think it's interesting
how you like to split us up.
Layla and me, Jackson and Viv.
Is there too much power
in multiple otherness for you?
Like I said, come to me
when you're sticking to protocol.
Can you believe Adam Groff threw poo
out of the coach window?
I always knew he was deranged.
Oh my God, Mark!
You scared me.
Why are we in the paper again?
And why have I been
fielding complaints from parents
telling me their children
went on a school trip
which involved missing students
and human feces?
- I'll look into it.
- Hm.
I told our investors
and the rest of the school board
that you were going to turn
the narrative around.
Yes.
And our upcoming open day
will nip this in the bud.
We'll be announcing
the rebrand to the press...
A rebrand isn't enough.
You need to show them
that this place has changed.
If we don't get the next round of money,
we are screwed. Do you understand?
Yes. I will not let you down.
Good. I've got a meeting to get to.
Of course.
Of course you do.
Thank you.
Thank you so much
for that encouraging pep talk.
So supportive.
- Gentle. Fucking fucklord...
- Hi, Hope.
- Hi.
- Sorry, I can come back...
No, absolutely not.
Um, how can I help you?
Um, okay, so I got onto the GTIP.
- Oh. Well done.
- Um...
So I was wondering if you'd managed
to get that funding we talked about.
- I spoke to the school board.
- Mm-hmm.
And unfortunately,
things are a bit tight at the moment.
And so, they said no.
Yeah.
I'm so sorry, Maeve.
No, it's fine.
Hopefully, your family can find the money.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
- Enjoy!
- Thank you.
Free vulva cupcake?
Ew, they're so ugly.
I thought so, too, at first,
but every vulva is unique and beautiful
and deserves to be cherished.
Cherish it.
Mm, this is so good.
Why don't you just speak to her?
'Cause I'm still pissed off.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- How are you?
- Good.
I just got into
the Gifted & Talented Program.
That's amazing! Oh, congrats, Maeve.
Thanks. Don't think I have
the money to go, but, you know...
So,
I can tell you are ignoring my texts,
which, under the circumstances,
is quite a point of vulnerability.
Yeah. I'm sorry.
Mm...
It's just... I just wasn't expecting
what happened between us to happen.
- Yeah.
- And, um...
I like Isaac.
You know, I think we have something good.
So, uh...
What, we should just forget about it?
I think so.
All students
to the assembly hall, please.
I've asked you all here
to announce
a new direction for your school.
A fresh start.
Moordale Secondary
will soon be known as Sparkside Academy.
I'm sure
you will have many questions,
but our goals for Sparkside
will be made clear
at our upcoming open day.
We will also be inviting the press
to show them
that "Sex School" is a thing of the past.
And speaking of press,
I'm sure you're all aware
that our school
once again made the news today.
Take me now, Lord Vanon!
Yes, it was very funny, wasn't it?
However, the part where they called us
an "institution full of sexual deviants"
was not very funny at all.
It seems that there are some students here
who get a kick
out of giving us a bad name.
And it has to stop.
So, Lily Iglehart, Cal Bowman,
and Adam Groff, come to the stage, please.
Take a seat, please.
From now on, punishment will be
dealt with differently on this campus.
Will you read that out, please, Cal?
"I am a slovenly troublemaker..."
A little louder, please.
"I am a slovenly troublemaker
who doesn't care about my peers!"
- This is fucked up!
- Sit down, Jackson.
Put the sign on, Cal.
I don't think my story was dirty.
Then why is everyone laughing at you?
Read it.
"I wrote
dirty and disgusting words
which have brought shame on my peers."
Um, I can't read that word.
It says that you are unhygienic.
Because what you did in France
was filthy and put your peers at risk...
Enough!
Sit down.
It's supposed to be school,
not somewhere we should be afraid.
Okay, you're suspended.
- What?
- Leave.
What?
I said, leave!
"I am unhygienic
and put my peers at risk."
You will not be allowed your phones
for the remainder of the week.
No one is to speak to these students.
And you will not be allowed
to remove your sign until I say so.
You better shut your cake stall down.
Okay. Back to class.
Hey.
- Hello, what's going on?
- The police are here.
- They're looking for Elsie...
- Slow down, Isaac. What?
Your mum took Elsie for a walk
at her visitation. She didn't come back.
- They think she's kidnapped her.
- What?
They're heading to Anna's now.
They wanna talk to you.
Um, okay, I'll meet them there.
You okay?
No.
Um, I need to go to Anna's.
There's an emergency.
- Do you wanna borrow my bike?
- No.
- It's quicker!
- I can't ride a bike, Otis.
- What do you mean you can't...
- No one ever fucking taught me! Okay?
Fuck!
When will you get married, Eric?
He's 17, Mummy!
I got married at 18. Young people
are getting married very old now.
It's foolish! Why wait?
Listen, Eric,
don't get married until you have to.
Have fun while you can.
Ow! Hey!
Atinuke, I told you
you are not in this photo.
- Uh-uh.
- What if you and Jimoh break up?
Out!
- Have you got a girlfriend, Eric?
- He hasn't...
Eric doesn't have time for girlfriends.
He's too busy focusing on his school work.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah.
Don't wait too long.
I'll pray every day
that you meet a good Christian woman
and have a big wedding in Nigeria...
Yes!
...before I die.
Okay.
Everybody, bunch together!
Okay, on three, and then smile.
One, two, three, smile!
Hey, you.
You. Why are you not smiling?
You're ruining my picture.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry!
- Sorry!
- Okay. One, two, three, smile.
Just here.
- Hi.
- I wanted to make sure you're okay.
- Thank you.
You all right, Maeve?
- What's he doing here?
- She needed a lift.
That's convenient.
Well, I'd better go inside and help,
but thank you for dropping Maeve off.
You know, I'm gonna come help too.
Can you
tell me about this morning?
She seemed okay.
- Her appeal for custody failed last month.
- There you go.
She'd never been happy
about the supervised visits. Thank you.
She didn't seem distracted?
Yes, did she seem on edge at all?
How about I ask the questions, boys? Hm?
So, how did Erin seem this morning?
She wanted to take Elsie
to the playground.
I had never imagined...
Will my mum be in any trouble?
This is serious. She could face
prison time when we find her.
It's gonna be all right.
She used a cashpoint
on Barrow Street at 10:17 a.m.,
but that doesn't give us any indication
as to her whereabouts now.
She's probably left Moordale.
Have you checked CCTV at the station?
Yeah, we have.
- And what about buses?
- We thought about buses too.
And you can tap her phone.
Sorry, how are you both connected
to the case again?
I'm Maeve's friend.
He is her complicated love interest.
You used to be her friend
until you were an arsehole at that party.
The only arsehole is the man who deleted
my voice mail without telling her!
Outside, both of you.
- Outside. Yep.
- Okay.
Always popping up
where people don't want you.
- Just go home, man!
- You... you don't know me.
- Always making things worse.
- What are you even doing...
Shut up! The pair of you!
My sister is missing.
This is not an opportunity for you
to swing your dicks around!
Dunno how you can even think
of choosing this guy over me.
Choosing? What are you talking about?
You're so deluded!
Oh right.
Did something happen
between you guys on the trip, then?
Yeah, yeah.
But it doesn't mean anything.
I mean... I do... I don't know what it means.
Elsie's missing.
That's all I care about right now.
Well, good luck finding her, Maeve. Um...
Isaac, don't go.
Oh fuck.
- Thanks, Otis.
- I think I should stay and help.
No, I don't think you should.
- You'd make things worse!
- What do you mean?
Since you stopped the clinic, you stopped
caring about anyone but yourself.
No, that's not true.
It... it's just not my responsibility.
I think you should go.
I don't wanna see you anymore.
Maeve.
Jakob!
I think we need to work out
what we're going to tell the kids
about why we're sleeping in separate beds.
I don't think they need to know.
It's private between you and me.
Well, I disagree.
Open dialogue is important with teenagers.
Okay, you go ahead and tell them.
I was just dropping off your book.
Would you like to come in for a chat?
Have a seat.
So,
why did you decide to return my notebook?
I thought you should have it.
So I assume it was also you
who made the photocopies last term.
Yes, it was.
And I'm ashamed of my behavior.
Um...
I keep reading the things
Maureen said about me to you.
And I think they're all true.
But I don't know how to change.
Come and voice your opinion
at the Student Forum tonight. Thank you.
Viv, listen, I've had an idea.
Let's use the forum to ask people
how they feel about Hope's new values.
If enough people don't like
what she's doing, we can change things.
- I can't do that.
- I don't get it.
Why are you trying to help her?
She's bad news, Viv!
Jackson, I'm not an idiot, okay?
I need to get into a good university.
It's not just my dream.
It's important to my whole family.
And I do not have the privilege
to fuck up school.
Viv, I know you're not an idiot.
You're the smartest person I know.
You're kidding yourself
if you think she cares about your dreams.
Vivienne Odusanya
to Hope's office, please.
Think about it.
I asked you to keep an eye on your peers
during this trip.
And then I hear rumors,
and I'm left feeling confused
because when I asked you
how the trip was going, you said,
"Great!"
So help me out here, Viv.
I didn't wanna get anyone into trouble. I...
- I felt in the middle.
- Right.
When I first met you,
I thought,
"This girl's going somewhere."
You know, "She's driven. She's focused."
But I don't know
how far you're going to go
if you can't
keep your head above the parapet.
I'm sorry. I... I should have been honest.
Don't apologize to me.
Apologize to yourself.
I would hate
to see you lose out on opportunities
because of a need to play nice.
It's a very female trait,
and it holds us back.
It will not happen again.
It better not.
Oh, one more thing, Vivienne.
I want you to make
a presentation to the press
and prospective students
on our upcoming open day.
Even after this?
Yes. You're our head girl.
And having a strong, smart,
young woman of color leading the way
shows how progressive we are as a school.
So it's about how it looks.
Of course it is.
Here's the video
and the slides for you to prepare with.
Uh, will you be
coming to the Student Forum?
Perhaps there'll be some interesting ideas
I can add to the presentation?
Why would I want to come and listen
to a bunch of teenagers whinging on
about their insignificant problems
for an hour? No, thank you.
I've had quite enough
of this navel-gazing,
identity-obsessed hysteria for one day.
The quicker you and your fragile,
petty little peers realize
that you're not that special
and that the real world doesn't care
about your supposed issues, the better.
I'd like to ask you
about your childhood, Michael.
Can you tell me about your mother?
She was quiet.
And gentle.
And she loved to cook.
And she always smelled rather lovely...
of shampoo.
And your father?
Dad. Well, he...
he was just different from my mum.
- Terrible, Dad, terrible.
- You're supposed to stop it.
I think Michaela's crying, Dad!
What?
Why are you crying?
Stop it! You're a boy!
Boys don't cry.
Hm.
When was the last time you cried?
Can't remember.
Not even after your separation?
And what do you do
that brings you pleasure?
Are you suggesting I...
masturbate?
No.
Believe it or not, Michael, I don't think
everything comes back to sex.
What I'm asking is,
what do you do that makes you feel joy?
I don't think I feel that emotion.
Very often, Michael,
when children are bullied by a parent,
they falsely learn
that emotions are a sign of vulnerability,
and so they shut them off.
What I'd like you to do
is to find something
that makes you happy.
Um, thank you.
And I'm sorry I said that thing about...
masturbation.
That's really okay.
However, in your case, Michael,
masturbation might not be such a bad idea.
You okay?
What happened?
Oh, well,
I just messed everything up. Again.
'Cause I am clearly incapable
of forming healthy relationships
with anyone.
Is this about Maeve?
I've never told you about Maeve.
Aimee mentioned,
just briefly, in her session with me
that you'd had a romantic tension
with someone called Maeve,
and something happened
at the party that you had here,
and you fell out over something you said.
Do you want to talk about it?
No, I don't want to talk about it.
Jealousy can make us act out of character
and say things we don't mean.
- Was there another boy on the scene?
- You're doing it!
Again!
I can't believe you had the audacity
to tell me to stop giving out advice
because I was being unethical.
You are the most unethical woman
in the world!
- Why won't you let me help you, Otis?
- Help me?
How could you possibly help me?
You push every man
you come into contact with away.
- You literally suck at relationships.
- Where is this coming from, Otis?
You brought Jakob into my life.
You make me live with Ola like a sister.
And I like having them around.
It feels normal, for once.
But that's over,
isn't it?
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Shit.
- Thank you.
- My pleasure.
This is my fault.
I should've told you what my mum is like.
Maeve, this is not your fault.
You're 17. You shouldn't have
to deal with stuff like this anyway.
It's too much.
Will you stay tonight?
- Eric, what do you think of the wedding?
- Auntie Beryl!
It's good!
It's good, you know. I think?
- I don't know. I've not been to many.
- Ah. You will go to more.
Hmm. Ah!
See Emeka?
Mummy was heartbroken
when Beatrice didn't marry him.
- Why?
- Hm.
His family is good.
Very wealthy!
Ah! He would have
given your mother the world.
Uh, and what about my dad?
- Your father?
- Uh-huh.
He was a very local guy! So bush!
Hm. You see?
Mummy didn't even think
he had any prospects.
Wow, wow.
But he's proven us all wrong.
And he has made a name
for himself in England.
Mm.
Ah!
They barely gave me any stew!
Auntie.
Auntie!
Hey.
I'm so sorry she did this to you.
I was happy not having any friends.
And then you came along and made me feel
like I wasn't so strange after all,
but it was just a lie.
You told me not to submit my story
because you said it was weird,
and then you judged me.
I was only trying to protect you.
You shouldn't be speaking to me.
Jackson?
- Hey. Um...
- Hey.
Thanks for sticking up for me.
What Hope did was complete bullshit.
- I know.
- And I think we should fight this.
All right. Let's do it.
I've had quite enough
of this navel-gazing,
identity-obsessed hysteria for one day.
The quicker you and your fragile,
petty little peers realize
that you're not that special...
- ...navel-gazing...
- ...doesn't care about your supposed issues...
I've had quite enough
of this navel-gazing,
identity-obsessed hysteria for one day.
...hysteria for one day.
The quicker you and your fragile,
petty little peers realize...
Weddings are weird, right?
Can you imagine dancing
to a whole room of people looking at you?
I think I'd like it.
My name's Oba.
Uh, I'm Eric.
You must go to a lot of these, then?
Oh. No, not really.
The groom is my close friend.
Ah.
I've always taken photographs as a hobby,
and he's a bit cheap.
It's funny.
I feel happy for them, but also a bit sad.
Because I know
I'll never have this for myself.
Do you know what I mean?
Ah...
I thought
we weren't supposed
to talk about that here.
There are lots of people like us here.
We just have to speak quietly.
I'm going out after this
if you want to meet them.
Uh, no, no. I, uh,
I don't think I can.
Okay.
Hm.
What are you doing here?
I feel bad
that you got suspended for me.
I got suspended for my beliefs.
I, uh...
I'm trying to write a poem for Eric,
and I thought you could help me.
You want me to help you write
a poem for my ex-boyfriend?
Forget it.
Let me see the poem.
- "Eric, you make me smile..."
- Do you have to read it out loud?
This is a bad poem.
You need to write from your heart.
Not overthink.
You shouldn't try
to write poetry because I write it.
I'm not. I'm... I'm...
I'm writing it because Eric likes it.
What about you? What do you like?
I... I, um, I like...
dogs.
I'm a cat person.
Of course you are.
♪ There are miles between us ♪
♪ Time between us ♪
♪ There is something between us ♪
♪ I may be a fool ♪
♪ To dream of you ♪
♪ But, God
It feels so good to dream at all ♪
♪ Something short and sweet ♪
♪ There's always a light
Over my head for you ♪
♪ I am waiting, I am waiting... ♪
Oh yes!
♪ Time will always try to kill me ♪
♪ There are mountains between us ♪
♪ There is time between us ♪
♪ Oh, ain't there something between us? ♪
- Your drink, sir.
- Thank you.
Unbelievable, man.
Are you sure
you don't want to see the rest of Lagos?
I'm sure, Oba.
Oya!
Take me to my people, then.
♪ Money fall on you, banana fall on you ♪
♪ Prada fall on you ♪
Oh! Well, we're out in Lagos, baby!
Mm-mm-mm-mm!
- Where are you taking me, then?
- You'll see.
Somewhere sexy? Somewhere fun?
Somewhere a little bit sweat?
Yeah, man. Here now.
Yeah, okay. Thank you. I'll be right back.
You... What?
Where are you running off to?
So I... I just don't know you that well,
and I think I should probably go.
What? We just got here.
- Where are you taking me?
- You'll see.
No, sorry, where did you go before?
I was checking escape routes.
- Escape...
- I've got you.
It's okay.
You're going to love it. I promise.
All right, love.
What's all of this rubbish
with this small club boys, eh?
- Omo England! Welcome!
- Oh.
Hi!
- Oh my gosh! You look incredible!
- Mm, mm, mm.
Bow bow! Ah!
Hey!
- Hey, sister. How are you?
- Hey, how you doing?
Hi! How are you guys?
Okay.
Thank you!
Don't worry. You are getting there.
- You're not ready. You're not ready!
- I don't actually even know.
- You're gonna dance up in here!
- Ooh la la.
Oh my gosh.
How do you feel?
Like I've come home.
Oba?
Hm?
Oba, wake up.
Oba, wake up. I... I need to go home.
My family will be worried.
Okay.
It was nice to meet you.
What do you mean, nice to meet me?
How am I supposed to get home?
We're in Lagos!
I'm kidding.
I'll make sure you get home okay.
Fine.
Um...
Did we...
No.
Cool.
Where were you? I was worried!
I was out with Oba.
- He showed me some of Lagos.
- Why didn't you tell me?
Well, you were too busy flirting
with your ex-fiancé.
- Eric, that's...
- No, Mum.
I was so excited
to come back here, you know?
And all we've done since arriving is lie.
Why'd you tell everyone
Dad is a successful accountant?
Your dad is an accountant.
At least, he was when he lived here.
No... no, but he's not back home.
So...
...why don't you tell the truth?
- Are you ashamed of him?
- Not at all!
But my mother didn't always approve
of your father. It's been easier to lie!
Do you wish you married
that Emeka guy instead of Dad?
No! That man is so vain!
We were never the right fit.
Not like your father.
What do you mean?
Being with your dad,
I always felt at peace.
I don't want to pretend, Mum.
Not here or anywhere.
I love that you're not afraid
to be yourself, Eric.
Maybe one day I'll get there too, hm?
But it takes time.
I'm sorry for scaring you, Mum.
I'll make you something to eat, hm?
Thank Abeo for my beautiful presents.
- Tell him he must visit next time!
- I will tell him.
- Oh, Eric!
- Mm.
You let me know
when you get yourself a girlfriend.
- Actually, Mummy, Eric is dating someone.
- Mm-hmm.
I told him not to tell you
until he knew it was serious.
Huh. Ah!
What is she like?
- Uh...
- Mm-hmm.
They don't talk much,
but they really love dogs.
- Mm-hmm.
- And, uh, they can be very kind.
Mm-hmm.
And they make me laugh.
A lot.
And I think you'd really like them.
Laughter does wonders for the heart.
They sound like a good choice.
Come on.
♪ Break, oh ♪
♪ Enough of your promises ♪
♪ You say you gon' make it up to me ♪
♪ But you keep getting worse o, worse o ♪
♪ When was the last time you carry me go ♪
♪ Cinema to see a movie ♪
♪ You don't take this thing
Like play o, play o ♪
♪ And when last you tell me to bend over ♪
♪ Make you jam the ting enter ♪
♪ I guess you're giving it
To someone else ♪
♪ If you no give me quality attention ♪
♪ Attention ♪
♪ I might get it from somebody else ♪
♪ Body else ♪
♪ If you no give me quality attention ♪
♪ Attention ♪
♪ I might get it from somebody else ♪
♪ Body else ♪
♪ O sun mi o, oro re tin sun mi o ♪
♪ Before na you dey do the caring
Calling, texting, chatting ♪
♪ Now na me dey do the things
That you used to do ♪