After eating her mother,
Glenoxi found herself
exiled from Oblivion 6
and left to wander the desolate crevices
of the planet Zorg on her own.
With no food and no water...
...Glenoxi was feeling
her lifeblood drain away.
She made her peace with dying like this.
As a creature
that never felt she belonged,
facing the end on her own
seemed only fitting.
But then Glenoxi saw Starlanza
for the first time.
As the water hit her lips,
Glenoxi knew that this was her soulmate.
The only creature in the whole universe
who would understand
and accept her completely.
And she was overwhelmed
that Starlanza felt the same.
Lily Pad,
you should get ready for school.
I'm not going.
Still feel sick.
Well, it's been three days.
Ola's called on the house phone again.
Have you two had a fight?
No, we're fine.
Well,
I've got to go to work now.
Hopefully, you'll feel better tomorrow.
193.
194, 195,
196,
197, 198,
199, 200.
Yeah!
Can you change this bulb for me?
Sure.
Thank you.
Ah.
There you go.
Bit sweaty.
Sorry.
I'll jump in the shower.
Thanks for that report
from our traffic correspondent.
And all eyes
are on Moordale Secondary today
as they hold their first open day
since the "Sex School" controversy
of last term.
Hope Haddon has said she aims
to clean up Moordale's dirty name...
Yeah?
Gotta get my jacket.
We have our session
with Dr. Cutton later today.
I'll think about it.
Good luck with your TV interview.
Oh f...
Hey.
I'm worried about Lily.
She hasn't spoken to me
since everything that happened with Hope.
- Could you go talk to her, please?
- I'm not a therapist, Ola.
I know, but she told me about how much
you helped her with the vaginismus stuff.
I think she really trusts you.
I'm not the right person to ask. Sorry.
Could you please do up my buckle, Otis?
Really?
I thought we'd grown out
of the silent treatment phase.
Look,
I know that you're both aware
that Jakob and I are having some issues,
but I want you to still feel
that this is your family home
and a safe space
for you to talk about your feelings.
Why is my dad
not part of this conversation?
Your dad feels it's better not to talk
about these things with you guys.
So you can't even agree on
how to tell us you might be splitting up?
Lots of couples have differing opinions
on how to parent children.
Maybe you should have thought about that
before you decided to have a baby
and make us
all pretend to be a bizarre family!
I'm going to school!
I'm sorry.
It's all a bit of a mess.
Everything you do
seems to turn into a mess, Mum.
Through! And over! Over!
Up! Yes! Well done! Yes!
Yeah! Good girl. Oh!
Didn't know she could do that.
Don't forget, it's your uncle Peter's
dinner party this evening.
Oh, no. I'm not going.
Uncle Peter's a dick.
- Adam!
- I'm just saying.
You're not with Dad anymore.
I don't know why you're going.
Okay. Yeah, you're right.
Peter is a bit of a dick.
But I'm just trying
to ease the adjustment process.
- Is your friend Eric back?
- Yep. Okay.
- Bye.
Hey.
Hey!
- How are you?
- Yeah, good.
Yeah?
Ooh! My mum.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, let's go.
Hello, Maureen.
Okay.
I missed you.
- I missed you too.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
Come.
Let's go.
Hello?
Yeah. Hey.
- Mum?
- Um...
Where are you?
Mum, you need to bring Elsie ba...
Have they found Elsie yet?
No.
I think I know where my mum is though.
So you haven't been replying to my texts.
Yeah, well,
I am quite annoyed at you right now.
Fair enough. I would be too.
Listen, we don't have to talk about this
when you've got stuff to worry about.
Okay, fine.
But I just want you to know
that I'm confused about all of this.
What am I supposed to say to that, Maeve?
If you're not sure you wanna be with me,
then it's probably not right.
- Isaac.
- Look.
I need to be with someone
who's sure about me
because I think I deserve that.
And even if you and I
were able to work this out,
I would still be worried
that you'd regret not trying with Otis,
and I can't do that.
So with respect,
I'm taking my heart off the table.
Good luck finding your mum.
- You both still wanna do this?
- Absolutely.
- Yep.
- Yes!
Incoming.
Happy Open Day!
Are you prepped?
I'm really looking forward to it.
That's good.
- Eric! You're back! Yes!
- Hey!
I missed you!
How was Nigeria? Tell me everything!
Oh, it was good. The wedding was great,
and my family was the best!
What are you doing?
I've run out of clean pants,
and I'm chafing real bad.
- What is that?
- It's my shame sign.
I threw a poo
out the coach window in France.
Except it wasn't me. It was Rahim.
We're kinda friends now.
- You're friends with Rahim?
- Kind of.
Whoa, whoa, wow. Wow! Wow!
What? It's itchy.
You know how big my balls are.
Okay, fine. But we are in public.
Go to the bathroom and sort yourself out.
- Fine.
You need to tell him about the thing.
What thing?
- Hey! Sorry. Hi. Have you seen Aimee?
- Oh!
- Hi. No. Maeve?
- Okay. Yeah?
I was gonna text you to apologize,
but that felt pathetic. Can we maybe talk?
I don't really have time right now.
I think I found my mum, so...
- Do you need any help?
- It's okay. I'll let you know how it goes.
What are we apologizing for?
Okay, okay.
So, in France,
and please don't freak out, but...
Maeve and I kissed.
You okay?
I'm actually speechless.
What kind of kiss?
A peck-on-the-cheek kiss or a kiss-kiss?
Um, it was a kiss-kiss.
What happened after this kiss-kiss?
Are you guys a couple now?
No. I messed it all up again.
She thinks I don't care about anything
now I don't do the clinic.
You think that's true?
You don't do the clinic anymore
because you had your heart broken,
and you couldn't be around Maeve.
I don't think you stopped caring.
I think you had to protect yourself.
Please, tell me this was at least
the best kiss of your entire life!
- It was pretty amazing.
- Aha! I'm so proud of you!
Otis! Can you help me out
with something for the thing?
Our computer guy has dropped out,
so we need a replacement.
I thought of you 'cause you seem nerdy.
- Yes.
- Mm-hmm.
- So, yeah.
- Okay.
Well, I was kinda hoping
to stay out of this one.
Um, what?
Of course you'll help. I'll help too.
Thank you.
Hey, be more Eric, okay? Thank you.
I agree with that, actually.
What's the thing?
- Thought you were shutting down the stall.
- It's for the thing!
They look great.
- Aimee, have you got a sec?
- Thought we weren't talking.
I've been an absolute arse.
Me too. Steve, hold the cakes.
I'm so sorry. You're right.
I'm shit at asking for help,
and I push people away.
No. I should never have done
what I did without asking first.
I didn't realize how hurtful it would be.
Thing is, I need help now,
and you're the only person I can trust.
Okay. What we doing?
Can you drive me to Lockwood-on-Sea?
Right. Steve, you're in charge
of vulvas from now on.
If anyone asks, the wobbly bits
aren't mistakes because...
All vulvas are unique.
Good lad.
They better not be squished.
He does these silly air punches
like he's Bruce Lee or something.
He bites his fork when he eats.
It's only been a few months.
I shouldn't be
so irritated by him, should I?
Are there any positives?
We have lots of sex.
Ooh.
Well, a healthy sex life is important
for many people.
I know it won't last though.
There was a time that Michael and I
couldn't keep our hands off each other.
And then
it just stopped.
Well, that doesn't have to be inevitable.
Oh, I've been meaning to tell you
that Michael stopped by the other day.
He was returning something that
belonged to me. We ended up having a chat.
About what?
I think he's struggling a bit
and just needed someone to talk to.
That's a bit rich.
Sorry.
It's just... Why wouldn't he talk
to me all those years?
And Adam's exactly the same.
It's just so lonely sometimes
with all these men.
Well, Adam will talk to you
when he's ready.
You know, I'm not very good
at letting Otis come to me.
I admire your restraint.
- Twenty minutes.
- Thank you.
Oh, that looks nice.
We are making way for a brighter,
cleaner future
here at Sparkside Academy.
You can fucking do this.
The press are arriving.
It's Superman pose.
It helps with nerves.
There's a TED Talk on it.
Right.
Making way for a brighter,
cleaner future
at Sparkside fucking Academy.
Fuck.
Yes.
- Why are you wearing that?
- You told me to.
Okay, take it off now.
Yeah.
- Hope! It's a good turnout.
- Yes!
Lots of prospective students,
the press, and all our private investors,
so, uh, no pressure at all.
Right. Well, I'll be interested
to hear your feedback.
Would you, um, just excuse me a second?
Mm. Yeah.
Cal?
Come with me.
Get your hands off me!
You have been told repeatedly
to change your behavior,
but you are clearly innately disobedient.
The press would be interested
to hear about
the way I've been discriminated against
due to how I present.
I'm left with no choice but to keep you
in here for the remainder of Open Day.
You're in violation of my rights.
Let me go!
Well, this... this is different.
Oh.
So, yeah,
all pretty self-explanatory.
- Mm-hmm.
- Um...
- Stop.
- Okay.
- Start.
- Dimmer.
- Mm-hmm.
- And do not press these red...
- This one?
- Yeah. Don't press that.
- Okay.
- I'll keep him...
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I mean, I was imagining something
more center stage, but this is cool.
It's likewe're in Ocean's Eleven, innit?
Maybe I'm George Clooney,
and you're Brad Pitt?
- No.
- I'm Brad Pitt. You're George Clooney.
- I'm Andy García. If I'm anyone.
- Who's Andy García?
Okay, well, I'm gonna go
while you boys hash that out.
- Yeah.
- I'll see you both on the other side.
- Thank you! Don't do that.
- Yeah! Yeah.
I think that
Jackson is Rihanna in Ocean's Eight
- Because of the bone structure and eyes.
- I've not seen it.
- No?
- No.
- Okay.
- But fine.
It was very good.
- Ugh, this fucking fringe.
- Aimee, can you please look at the road?
- Sorry.
Right, come on. You and Otis kissed
in France. What happened?
I don't know.
My head's all over the place
at the moment.
- Things are over with Isaac as well.
- Hmm.
I feel bad about hurting his feelings.
I'm sorry, babes.
Does this mean you and Otis
might actually finally get together?
I don't know.
We've changed a lot,
so I don't know if it would work out.
I think you should just
bloody go for it, love.
It's like Simone de Beauvoir says,
"From the hour you're born,
you begin to die."
I think it means "live for the day."
Yeah. Once I realized
she wasn't a lad called Simon,
her writing started
to make a lot more sense.
I shouldn't have said
that stuff about you and Steve.
I didn't mean it.
I think you're great together.
No, you were right. It's not working out.
I'm sorry.
- Can you please look at the road?
- Sorry.
- I love you, love.
- My concentration's not great.
- It's all right.
I'm sure some of you probably had
your reservations about coming here today.
I don't think anybody wants
to send their child to a school
that's famous for STIs and sex musicals.
But I'm here to assure prospective parents
that these scandals are
a thing of the past.
And so it is my promise to you
that if you should choose
Sparkside Academy for your child,
that they will receive their education
on a safe
and sex-free campus...
Sex-free camp... People fuck in the bushes!
We will protect our youth at all costs.
Now, let's hear it from a shining example
of Sparkside's new ethos,
Vivienne Odusanya.
- Here we go.
- Whoo!
Come on, Viv!
Thank you, Hope, for giving me
the opportunity to speak today.
Firstly, I'd like to invite
Jackson Marchetti onstage
to reclaim his position as head boy.
Whoo!
Thank you, Viv.
Ah.
It's good to be back.
We agree with Hope
that students should feel protected
whilst on campus.
The students of Moordale Secondary
would like to share some ideas
on how we think
listening to young people
could make our new campus
the safest place to study in the UK.
We hope you enjoy.
What the hell is going on?
- It's a very slow screen.
- It is a slow screen.
And here we go.
Hi! We're the students of Sex School.
You might recognize us from the press.
We're the deviant youths
having loads of S-E-X.
And catching chlamydia.
And writing musicals about dicks!
But I'm not embarrassed
to be a student of Sex School.
Sex, well, it's part of being human.
Whoa!
How did you let this happen?
- I'm going to stop the video.
- Do it quickly. Don't make a scene.
...bodies and identities.
Which is why
schools need safe spaces
for people to ask those things
that some might find a little awkward,
where there's no shame, stigma, or fear.
Because when shame
is used as a weapon,
it doesn't just hurt people.
It can damage them forever.
But the opposite of shame is pride.
And the students of Sex School are proud
of the things people like to shame us for.
Because if Lily Iglehart
is a weirdo
for writing short stories
about aliens with penis hands,
we're definitely weirdos too.
I love my clitoris,
and I feel no shame.
Ladies, get your wank on!
I bind my chest, and I feel no shame!
I have a hairy bum, and I feel no shame.
I am literally perfect...
Stop the video now!
I'm great at anal douching,
and I feel no shame.
- I'm great...
- That's not gonna do anything.
There's nothing to see here.
- Get out of my way!
- Eric!
I'm great at anal douching.
Drop the plug.
- What?
- Ruby?
I said, drop it! Ah!
- Ruby. Miss!
- Miss!
- Oh my... Is that?
- That's a burn.
Ow! What are you doing?
Yes, yes.
Oh my God! Wow!
Ruby!
I'm great at anal douching,
and I feel no shame.
Right.
Ru... Ruby!
You cannot do that!
You mustn't do that!
- Ow!
- Oh God! Jeez!
I'm great at anal douching...
That is very expensive perfume.
- You're incredible!
- I know.
I'm attracted to boys and girls,
and I'm trying not to feel shame.
What have you done?
I have a third nipple,
and I have no shame.
Now, was that Fleurs du Mal?
- Come on! Come on!
- What the fuck?
Oh, this school...
A lot of shame comes from
old-fashioned views on sex.
Sadly, schools have taught a lot of people
to feel ashamed
of their identities and bodies.
The cycle continues today.
But the world is changing,
and young people have had enough.
So if you agree that communication
and empathy are better tools
than silence and shame,
then join us
by asking your school for better.
We are Sex School!
We are Sex School! We are Sex School!
- We are Sex School!
- What?
We are Sex School! We are Sex School!
We are Sex School!
We are Sex School! We are Sex School!
We are Sex School! We are Sex School!
Thank you! Thank you all for listening.
And now the choir will sing us out
with our beautiful new school anthem.
♪ Bom-bom, bom-bom ♪
♪ Suck-a, suck-a, suck-a, suck-a
Suck-a, suck-a, suck-a, suck-a ♪
♪ Suckin' on my titties
Like you wanted me ♪
♪ Callin' me all the time like Blondie ♪
♪ Check out my Chrissy behind
It's fine all of the time ♪
♪ Like sex on the beaches ♪
♪ What else
Is in the teaches of Peaches? ♪
♪ Huh? What? ♪
- ♪ Fuck the pain away ♪
- ♪ Fuck ♪
- ♪ The pain... ♪
- ♪ Fuck the pain away ♪
- ♪ Fuck ♪
- ♪ Away ♪
- ♪ Fuck the pain away ♪
- ♪ Wow ♪
- ♪ Away ♪
- ♪ Fuck the pain away ♪
♪ Fuck the pain away, fuck the pain away ♪
♪ Fuck the pain away
Fuck the pain away... ♪
Yeah! Vulva cupcakes!
♪ Suck, suck, suck ♪
- Fuck yeah!
- ♪ Sucking on my titties ♪
- I wanna hear ya!
- ♪ Suck, suck, suck ♪
- What are we gonna do?
- ♪ Sucking on my titties ♪
- That's right.
- Whoo!
♪ Fuck the pain away ♪
♪ Suck, suck, suck
Sucking on my titties ♪
Fuck!
What?
Hey, Hope.
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Fuck the pain away ♪
♪ Suck, suck, suck
Sucking on my titties ♪
♪ Fuck the pain away ♪
♪ Suck, suck, suck
Sucking on my titties ♪
♪ Fuck the pain away ♪
♪ Sucking on my titties ♪
Yeah! You know it!
Those are my kids!
You're my kids!
Come on, Moordale!
What's wrong
with schools teaching abstinence?
Well, schools that teach abstinence
actually have a higher rate
of teen pregnancies and STIs
than schools
with comprehensive SRE programs.
And when we give teens
agency, information, and trust,
there's a much higher success rate...
Sorry, Dr. Milburn, apologies.
It appears there's a situation developing
as we speak at Moordale Secondary.
Let's go live there now
to our reporter on the ground.
What was meant to be the day
that Moordale Secondary squashed
the title of "Sex School"
has evolved
into something quite the opposite.
Students have taken to protest,
doubling down
on their belief in sex positivity,
and saying that
new head teacher Hope Haddon
is quite simply behind the times.
But as you can see...
Otis?
- ...from the "Wall of Vulva" behind me...
- Oh.
- ...the question remains...
- Ooh.Ow.
...how progressive is too progressive?
These people will know. I can sense it.
Okay.
Hi! Have you seen a woman
with blonde hair and green eyes?
Kinda looks like her, only older.
- Oh. Thank you.
- Okay. Thank you.
Maybe this was a stupid idea.
She used to bring us here
as kids all the time,
usually when she was feeling guilty
about something.
At least you've tried.
Hi, Mum. Hi, Elsie!
- What you doing here?
- Should ask you the same.
- Mummy's taking me on a boat.
- Fuck!
Come on!
- This is amazing.
- Mm.
You know this started with you, right?
- What do you mean?
- You and Maeve.
The clinic thing. Getting everyone
to talk about their problems.
If it wasn't for that, I don't think
vaginas would be getting drawn on a wall.
Vulvas.
You like helping people.
It's one of the reasons
I love you so much.
I know you've been hurt, but I don't think
you should lose this part of yourself.
It's a very good part.
- Thanks, man.
- Mm-hmm.
- I've gotta go, actually.
- Where?
Oh my God! That clitoris is gorgeous!
- Shall we get out of here?
- Yeah.
- Mm-mm-mm.
- There he is.
♪ Clap your hands now, people, clap now ♪
♪ Clap your hands now
People, clap your hands ♪
♪ Clap your hands now, people, clap now ♪
♪ Clap your hands now
People, clap your hands ♪
♪ A little softer, people, get softer ♪
♪ A little softer
People, get down and low ♪
♪ A little softer, people, get softer ♪
♪ A little softer
People, get down and low ♪
♪ A little louder, people, get louder... ♪
Uh... Hello?
Michaela!
I've invited Maureen for tonight.
Hope that's all right.
You're not technically divorced, right?
No. No, that's fine.
Is the new boyfriend coming?
Ha! Hope not.
That would be really awkward for you. Ha!
- Anyway, gotta go. See you later, bye!
- Bye.
♪ Clap your hands now
People, clap your hands ♪
- I can't believe we did that!
- Yeah.
- I am so proud of you.
- Oh, I'm proud of you too.
- Come on. I'm feeling a bit left out here.
- What?
Oh, I'll see you guys tomorrow.
- Yeah, see you later.
- See you, Viv.
Hey.
So, you wanna hang out?
Yeah.
Okey dokey, let's be having you.
All aboard the Skylark!
I'm not due for eight weeks.
That's it, darling.
You're the lady
who used to do therapy at the school?
Yeah, that's me.
My daughter's at Moordale.
She's going through a bit of a tough time.
Quite worried about her, to be honest.
I wish she had someone professional,
like you, she could talk to on campus.
Sorry. That's the last thing
you want to be thinking about.
Oh, no, it's good to be thinking
about something else.
Why's she having a tough time?
Keep breathing.
Um, well, she's refusing to go to school.
She's always been a bit of an outsider.
She's obsessed with aliens
and things like that.
I don't think people really get her.
I don't think I understand her sometimes.
Well, I'm sure
you're more alike than you think.
Maybe try and find some common ground,
something you can relate to in her world,
and see if the conversation starts there.
Ooh, oh shit!
Okay, blow out the candles
with me, darling.
I'll try Jakob again.
It's funny.
She's the one that wanted this meeting,
but she's the one that's late.
You mean, you wouldn't choose
to be here if it weren't for Jean?
No.
Well,
perhaps we can use this time to talk
specifically about your feelings, Jakob.
I feel fine.
You don't seem fine. You seem angry.
Well, she's late.
Can I ask you
about your previous marriage?
She... she passed away.
Yes, but I wonder,
can you tell me a little bit
about the relationship before she died?
We met young.
I loved her very much.
And I think she loved me.
But it was young love.
Um, we were both very naive. And...
then things changed
once we had our children.
How did it change?
She met someone else.
I think she...
she wanted to leave me.
Then she got sick.
It was all very confusing.
Yes, I can imagine it must have been.
But you stayed with her.
Yeah. You don't leave
when someone is sick.
And we made it work...
...until the end.
When did you grieve?
When she died,
I...
broke down into pieces.
Yes, but when did you grieve
for what you lost
when your wife had the affair?
It must be very hard
to trust anyone properly again.
Especially when you weren't able
to fully process the feelings that you had
about your wife's betrayal.
Yeah, I have a problem with trust.
But I want to try.
Mm-mm.
Too fast?
- Yeah, I'd rather keep it off.
- That's cool.
I mean on.
- Sorry.
- It's fine.
You really are so beautiful.
Oh shit, that's a gendered word.
Pretend I didn't say that.
I'd also still be into you
if you weren't beautiful...
Not that I don't find you beautiful.
I do think men can be beautiful.
- Like a beautiful soul. Know what I mean?
- Jackson.
Don't worry about it.
- Okay.
- Mm.
I really didn't mean what I said.
I'm sorry.
No, it's... it's fine. It's okay.
Okay.
I just feel like I fucked up.
Should we just stop?
Um, yeah. I mean, you seem tense,
and now I'm tense too.
Yeah.
- We can try again another time.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
If this was going to become more serious,
then you would be in a queer relationship.
Is that okay with you?
Yeah.
Yeah, I haven't, like,
got a problem with that...
Hm.
...at all.
Um...
- I have to go.
- What?
Just... I just gotta help my mum out
with some stuff.
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay.
But I'm... Yeah, okay.
- Bye.
What the fuck?
Ugh!
You don't wanna do this, Mum.
That's why you called me.
Don't tell me what I wanna do.
Who is that girl who keeps staring at us?
She's freaking me out.
It's my best friend, Aimee.
She gave me a ride here.
- And what? Is she undercover, is she?
- No.
Thanks very much.
How am I supposed to know?
You're good at calling the police on me.
- You have any idea how that fucked me up?
- You've been fucked up about it?
- Try having your kid taken off you!
- Mum, I'm 17!
- I should never have had to report you!
- I know I wasn't there for you, okay?
But it's different with Elsie.
I'm gonna give her a better life.
Mum, you can't stay clean.
It doesn't make you a bad person.
It's just Elsie needs someone
in her life who isn't using.
What, like Anna?
Can we go and see Anna?
Come on, Els, let's go.
Did you get onto that thing
for smart kids in America?
- How'd you know about that?
- That boy Isaac told me about it.
Yeah, I did, but I can't afford it.
Mummy, I want to see Anna.
Do you think Anna loves her?
Yeah, I do.
Hey. You're gonna stay with Maeve.
- I wanna stay with you, Mummy.
- It's not very nice where I'm going.
It rains all the time,
and there's no chips!
I love you.
Oh, I love you too, darling.
You go back to Anna's
with Maeve, and I'll visit.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Oh, I'm a lucky mummy.
Bye-bye, darling. Bye-bye.
Please just take her
before I change my mind.
Elsie, come here. Come give me a hug.
Bye, Mummy.
Hey, Lily. It's Otis.
Can I come in?
We missed you today.
And the school realized
what Hope did to you guys was wrong.
We all got together to fight
for what we wanted Moordale to be like.
It was kind of amazing.
It also made me kind of sad
'cause, uh...
I've realized
I've shut myself off recently.
I stopped believing
it was my place to try and help anyone.
I got hurt last term.
Badly.
And I didn't wanna do the clinic anymore.
But that doesn't mean
I shouldn't try and be a good friend.
I saw you
after Hope humiliated you.
I didn't even ask if you were all right.
I should've checked in.
I'm...
I'm really sorry I didn't.
Ooh!
Why are you on the floor?
Do you want some alien stuff?
I'm throwing it away.
I'm okay.
Thanks.
Ola said you guys aren't speaking.
We're kind of fighting.
I think she's going through
a tough time too.
She's really missing her mum.
Maybe I've been a bit distracted,
but I'm not ready to talk to her yet.
I didn't think we were friends.
Well, I... I know we don't hang out much,
but I think we like each other.
Meh, you're all right.
I know what you mean about shutting off.
I do that, too,
when I'm hurt
or I feel like I don't fit in.
What do you do when you shut off?
Hm.
Think about my stories.
About alien planets and galaxies.
I used to do it all the time
when I was a kid, but...
I guess it's just weird
now that I'm getting older.
It's really common
for people to create
rich fantasy worlds to escape into.
It's what most artists do.
They are brave enough
to show the weirdest,
most vulnerable sides
of themselves in their work.
Which helps a lot of people
not feel as alone.
Thanks, Otis.
But I don't think I'm an artist.
I wouldn't be so sure.
And even if you do decide
to not write about aliens anymore,
you shouldn't ever give someone
the power to humiliate you.
You're great.
Just the way you are.
♪ Oogum, oogum, boogum, boogum ♪
♪ Boogum now, baby
You're castin' your spell on me ♪
♪ You got me doin' funny things
Like a clown ♪
♪ Just look at me... ♪
♪ When you wear your high-heeled boots
With your hip-hugger suit ♪
♪ It's all right, you're outta sight ♪
♪ And you wear that cute miniskirt
With your brother's sloppy shirt... ♪
♪ I admit it, girl, that I can dig it... ♪
I don't know if she's gonna be ready
for the competition.
- It's probably dumb.
- Adam!
It's so great you've entered at all.
Your mum will be so proud.
Hm. Well, I've not invited my mum.
So you only invited me?
Yeah. You're the only one I want there.
I've been thinking
that maybe we could try
going out together.
Maybe somewhere a bit more gay?
Like a... like a gay bar?
Yeah.
Or like, um, a club or something.
Mm.
We could get dressed up. Could be fun.
Mm. Uh...
I don't think that would be my thing.
- You like it when I put makeup on you.
- Yeah, when we're in my room.
I don't know if I'm ready to do that with...
in front of people.
I like it when it's just you and me.
I have to tell you something.
I kissed someone else.
In Nigeria.
You what?
It just happened. I'm so sorry, Adam.
I need to go and feed Madam, so...
Madam?
Amazing!
You're nearly there, Jean.
Where the fuck is Jakob?
Keep breathing, Jean.
You're doing amazingly.
Amazing!
That's it. That's it.
Brilliant.
Why are there so many people?
When babies are a little early,
they always like to have us all here.
I said,
"I'm injured in three places,"
and the doctor says,
"Well, don't go there."
Ah, bummer!
- Maureen says she can't make it.
- Aw.
This salad's delicious.
Did you make it, Peter?
No, I don't have the time,
unfortunately, to cook.
That's why God gave us caterers!
Very good.
I made that one, actually.
Oh. Where'd you get the recipe?
- I saw it on a television program.
- Mm.
But I added the feta and the parsley.
I love a man who can cook.
I don't think making a salad
is exactly cooking, is it?
Putting a lot of leaves in a bowl.
But wait till you taste the chocolate
and beetroot cake for dessert.
It's to fucking die for and gluten-free.
- Guilt-free. Huh?
- Mm. There is something sweet in there.
I put honey in the dressing,
and there's also pomegranate seeds and...
Pomegran...
Could somebody here give
my little brother a job?
He's got too much time on his hands.
What you doing?
I'm leaving.
Why? The grown-ups
are in the middle of dinner.
Because I can't bear to waste
another precious second of my life
pretending to like you.
You're awful.
Oh, that's a wee bit dramatic,
don't you think, Michaela?
My name is Michael!
And my life is a failure.
My wife's left, I'm quite sure
my son hates me, and I'm unemployed.
But I'd rather all those things than be
a pumped-up shit of a man like you.
You've been a shit since you were a child.
I think you'll be a shit until you die.
Probably because our dad
was the biggest shit of all.
And you learned to bully me
so he wouldn't bully you.
And that is such a great shame.
But I am too old
for it to be my problem anymore.
Goodbye, Peter.
He, uh... He's...
I like this bowl.
Hi. I got your messages. Where is she?
She's in there.
That's it, darling.
I need you to give me
one last big push, Jean.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
That's it. You've done it!
It's a little girl!
I'm so sorry I was late.
It's a girl.
You did it! You did it!
She's so tiny.
So tiny.
You did so good.
- I feel strange.
- What?
Something's wrong.
What? Something's wrong.
What's happening here? What's happening?
Can you please step outside?
Thank you so much, Maeve.
Come here.
Will you stay again tonight?
You've had a really shitty day.
Yeah, that would be nice.
I'm just gonna say goodbye to my friend.
Okay.
Maeve, I know
you don't like emotional shit,
but I've been thinking about
how you don't really have a proper mum,
and I wanted you to know
that even though my mum has money,
she's also crap sometimes too.
So I was thinking
that maybe we could be each other's mums.
Thanks, Mum.
You're welcome, Mum.
- Hi, Maureen.
- Hi.
I made a salad.
I thought you and Adam might like it.
Actually, that's not true.
I just wanted to see you.
And I just wanted to say
that I know I was hard to live with,
that I'm rigid, and I'm uptight.
I don't know how to be spontaneous
or anything close to happy.
But I do want to change.
I want to try to be the man that you want.
Do you think we could talk?
I don't want to talk.
♪ She was an ex-marine
She had her own machine ♪
♪ She put my soul in dirty... ♪
♪...And it came out clean ♪
♪ I was in toxic awe ♪
♪ I had my locked-up jaw ♪
♪ I didn't talk much, I listened
And I looked and saw ♪
♪ And I was just 19
I must have seemed quite keen ♪
♪ She broke me open
I was no longer on either team ♪
♪ Jumped on the right time ♪
♪ I'm gonna buy time ♪
Hi. Oh, it's me again.
Is Maeve here?
Yeah. Yeah, she's in the back garden.
Hey.
Hi! What are you doing here?
I, uh, I needed to talk to you.
What's... what's going on?
It was never about the clinic.
I did the clinic to be close to you.
And then you made me realize
I'm good at something,
and I like helping people.
And I thought you ignored my message,
and it crushed my heart.
I stopped doing the clinic
because it reminded me of you. It sucked.
'Cause I wanna help people.
I know this is only about money for you,
but let's just be a team again, please?
If I can't be with you romantically,
I still wanna see you every day.
Nothing feels right
when you're not around.
It wasn't just about the money for me.
I wanted to be close to you too.
♪ It's every day ♪
♪ I'm in this place ♪
♪ I feel this way ♪
♪ I feel the same ♪
♪ It's every day... ♪
♪ I feel this way ♪
♪ I feel the same ♪
♪ Is it all inside my head... ♪
♪ Is it all inside my head ♪
♪ I view the list ♪
♪ And take my pick ♪
♪ I view my fate ♪
♪ And make the choice ♪
♪ 'Cause it's nobody else's but mine ♪
♪ But you're in my heart ♪
♪ I can feel your beat ♪
♪ And you move my mind ♪
♪ From behind the wheel ♪
♪ When I lose control ♪
♪ I can only breathe your name ♪
♪ 'Cause you're in my heart ♪
♪ I can feel your beat ♪
♪ And you move my mind ♪
♪ From behind the wheel ♪
♪ When I lose control ♪
♪ I can only breathe your name ♪