Antecedently on Fargo...
[Roy] What happened?
[Munch] You send a man to do a job
without all the information...
...how can the job be done?
You say how woman is
a woman, a...
housewife.
Never do you mention
she is, for real...
a tiger.
[screaming]
[grunts]
[Gator] You're saying
you couldn't handle some girl?
Hundred pounds soaking wet? Huh?
This half-wit shot up a filling
station outside Beulah.
Murdered the clerk.
- [horn sounds]
- [clerk screams]
Killed a state trooper.
[grunts]
Put a hole in the leg of another.
And this retard's partner
with a cracked skull
and his face half burned off
in the morgue.
[whimpering]
[grunts]
You say housewife,
so I bring one guy.
You say tiger...
that's a different guy.
It cost you three times.
Did they take her? The police?
[Munch] Fled on foot.
Possibly home.
Possibly to the wind.
- Will you find her?
- It's a question
of price.
And the job, it was not the job
you said.
- Pain... and suffering.
- [grunting]
And it forces a man to ask...
why you want the tiger.
She's my wife.
She made vows to me.
Consider it a debt unpaid,
leaving me in limbo.
See, she hid from me
nine, ten years.
Interest accrued
until the debt could
no longer be paid with money.
Then, one day, there she is.
Fingerprints in the system.
Now the limbo can end
and debt can be collected.
Well, thanks for your help.
Go on with Gator,
he'll get you paid.
Original,
plus pain and suffering.
[Roy]
Yeah, of course.
Take it out
of the rainy day fund.
- Fixing place.
[Gator]
Hundreds okay?
Surprise, shitbird.
- [shouts]
- [grunts]
[screaming]
[shouting]
["All Shook Up"
by Tennessee Ernie Ford playing]
♪ Some ♪
♪ People say a man
is made out of mud ♪
♪ A poor man's made
out of muscle and blood ♪
♪ Muscle and blood
and skin and bones ♪
♪ A mind that's a weak
and a back that's strong ♪
♪ You load 16 tons,
what do you get? ♪
♪ Another day older
and deeper in debt ♪
♪ St. Peter, don't you call me
'cause I can't go ♪
♪ I owe my soul
to the company store. ♪
[Gator] Called you directly.
I didn't want this
going out on the wire.
Didn't know what to do with him
so I just put him in the back.
[exhales]
Then where were you?
I was draining the snake.
Two minutes in and out.
Did you get a look at the tape?
[sighs]
State cops took the whole system
last night on account
of the other thing.
[scoffs]
Can you believe this guy?
Coming back
to the scene of the crime?
Like that?
Talk about big balls.
Yeah, well, I bet yours
shriveled up a little bit
on account of him getting
the jump on you. Again.
Son of a bitch!
[yells]
All right, are you done?
[sighs]
Tell me again where you found
this Munch guy.
Is that really his name, Ole Munch?
He says it,
"Ooh-lah," and I-I, I didn't
find him, I found his partner.
What, the guy
with his head in the toilet?
Yeah.
All right, well, first order of
business, we need information.
Find out who this guy is.
Priors, known accomplices,
known hangouts.
Then we smoke him loose.
If he comes for us again?
Oh, believe me, he's coming.
Sleep with your hammer cocked
is my opinion,
if you sleep at all.
Jesus.
All right, the truck goes in a ditch.
Alvie behind the wheel.
Tell Bruno to report the cause
of death as accidental.
Then you
go to his fiancee's
and break the news.
- What are you gonna do?
- Don't worry about what I'm gonna do, all right?
- Okay.
- Now you're oh for two here, kid.
How do I teach you
how to be a winner,
you keep losing all the time?
I swear to God,
him versus me, man-to-man,
I'd wipe the floor with him.
Yeah. Right. Like High Noon?
Hmm?
That only happens in the movies, son.
Real life, they'll slit your throat
while you're waiting
for the light to change.
[car door opens]
- [car door closes]
- [engine starts]
- [indistinct chatter]
- ♪ 'Tis the gift to be simple ♪
♪ 'Tis the gift to be free ♪
♪ 'Tis the gift to come down
where we ought to be ♪
♪ And when we find ourselves
in the place just right ♪
♪ 'Twill be in the valley ♪
♪ Of love and delight ♪
♪ When true simplicity
is gained ♪
♪ To bow and to bend ♪
♪ We shan't be ashamed ♪
♪ To turn, turn ♪
♪ Will be our delight ♪
♪ Till by turning ♪
♪ Turning we come
round right... ♪
[Karen] Hey, babe.
Daddy's here.
[Roy groans]
Odin.
[Odin] Sheriff.
I saw your boys outside.
You know, we could, uh...
we could have them in.
Fix them a plate.
[Odin] Nah, they're outdoor animals.
Mountain lions in training.
Don't want them getting soft.
Well, I'm gonna have a drink.
You want one?
Got my special sipping whiskey.
Can't be too careful.
[Roy] Twins still up?
They're in the bath.
Sit down.
I want to see my man.
Ah, I just want to say good night first.
I'll be right back.
Need to talk about munitions, boy.
Gonna need another delivery soon.
Yeah, I'm wrangling things.
Uh, got to space it out, though, yeah?
Requisitioned weapons going missing.
Feds are already on my ass.
Things are in the works, kid.
1776.
And we're not gonna
take this country back
with harsh language, feel me?
Uh-huh.
♪ 'Tis a gift to be joyful ♪
♪ 'Tis a gift to be free ♪
♪ 'Tis a gift, 'tis a gift ♪
♪ 'Tis a joyous gift to be ♪
♪ And when you find yourself
in the pure delight ♪
♪ The gift to be simple
has led you aright ♪
♪ When true simplicity is gained ♪
♪ To bow and to bend,
we shan't be ashamed ♪
♪ To turn, turn will be our delight ♪
♪ Till by turning, turning,
we come round right... ♪
[song fades]
[children chattering indistinctly]
♪ ♪
[faint playful chatter]
Alone at last.
What do you want tonight, Daddy?
You want helpless hitchhiker?
[faint playful chatter]
How about angry feminist?
Okay.
How about...
[faint playful chatter]
How about that mean ole governor?
Hmm?
Oh, sorry.
♪ ♪
[playful chatter]
[dog barking in distance]
I see you.
♪ ♪
["Bogey Wail" by Jack Hylton playing]
[Wayne] I called the alarm guy.
Got an appointment for Monday.
Hon?
Oh. I told Cheryl to mark me
incommunicado for this afternoon,
so we can go to the, uh, Gun World.
I changed my mind.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
You're gonna be
a zombie for Halloween,
and Scotty and I are gonna be
zombie hunters now.
Hmm.
But I...
I thought she said, uh, witch bears.
Which whether that is, uh, bears
that practice witchcraft or witches
that become bears,
I don't know, but... [laughs]
No. Zombie hunters.
Scotty signed off on it.
Hmm.
Ooh, maybe we can find something
for the costumes at Gun World.
Bulletproof vests and the like.
I'm gonna write that down.
["He'll Have to Go" by Jim Reeves playing]
[child] I got so much candy.
♪ Put your sweet lips
a little closer to the phone ♪
- [child 2] Trick or treat.
- [child 3] Trick or treat.
- [child 2] Mmm, thank you.
- [child 3] Thank you.
♪ Let's pretend
that we're together ♪
♪ All alone ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ I'll tell the man
to turn the jukebox ♪
- ♪ Way down low ♪
- [child screams]
♪ And you can tell ♪
♪ Your friend there with you ♪
♪ He'll have to go ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Whisper to me ♪
♪ Tell me do you love me true? ♪
♪ Or is he holding you ♪
♪ The way I do? ♪
♪ Do-do-do ♪
- ♪ Though love is blind ♪
- [clattering]
- ♪ Make up your mind ♪
- [footfalls pass overhead]
[distorted]
♪ I've got to know. ♪
[floorboards creaking]
[creaking rhythmically]
[door creaking open]
[creaking stops]
I live here... now.
♪ ♪
[priest] Woe unto man,
for he has sinned
in the eyes of the Lord.
And for this wickedness,
he must pay.
[crowd gasping, murmuring]
In forgiveness of your debts to man,
will you consume
his Lordship's sins to God?
I will.
You may begin.
[exhales]
[gasping, clamoring]
[Bryn grunts]
[Uncle] More.
Say it.
[Bryn moaning]
[Uncle] Say it.
I give easement and rest
now to thee, dear man.
And for?
For thy peace...
...I pawn my own soul.
[speaking Latin]
[gurgling]
[moaning]
It is done and cannot be undone.
[tennis ball bouncing]
I live here now.
[opens can]
♪ ♪
Arr! Welcome to Gun World.
How can I help ye?
I like your eye patch.
[stammers]
Actually, that's a,
that's a hunting accident.
Oh, geez. Oh, I stepped
right into that one.
Oh, no, no. I-I-I can see
where the confusion would...
We're looking
for a home defense solution.
Arr, then you came to the right place.
- Hmm.
- Tell me,
what would you say
is the most critical
in the family conversation,
ease of use or stopping power?
- Stopping power. Definitely.
- Uh, ease of u... Oh.
Yeah.
Can I see the Benelli M4 Tactical?
Benelli, yeah.
Your missus knows her stuff.
- Ah.
- Oh.
That's a...
How-how much is, uh...?
Oh, $1,300?
[pirate] It's hard to put a price on life.
Not-not for you, apparently, so...
Oh.
Is it 12-gauge? Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, you could go 12 or 20.
- Uh-huh.
- How about the Heckler 416?
Gas-operated, short-stroke piston.
Shoots 850 rounds per minute.
Well, 800 rounds per...
- And a handgun.
- And? You want to get both these?
Maybe the Desert Eagle.
Oh.
[woman] [over P.A.]
Trick or treat, Gun World families.
It's the best holiday of the year.
Uh...
Get 25% off all gunstocks.
No gun is off the market.
[Dot] Plus ammunition.
Yeah, sure.
This is $5,000 worth of...
Well, like I said, yeah,
peace of mind is priceless.
Yeah, hon.
- Yeah.
- Is that gonna be cash or credit?
[Wayne]
Uh...
No credit. I'll write you a check.
[pirate] That's music to me ears.
- Yeah. - [Dot] So, you got
cases for these or...
[pirate] Yeah, I'll have
them all boxed up for you
and ready to go next week
when you pick up the armaments.
- What do you mean?
- [pirate] Well, of course,
there's the mandatory
waiting period
while we run the check.
Make sure you're not psychopaths
or, you know, socialists.
That last one's a joke.
- No.
- Oh. Yeah.
We need...
Our home is not safe right now.
Yeah, listen, I hear you.
It's this darn federal mandate.
They're taking aim at it
at the state house,
but until they can shoot it dead, well...
It's only one week.
Yeah.
Let's take a look
at that pepper spray, then.
The what, now?
[wind whistling]
[heavy metal playing in distance]
[heavy metal playing]
Asshole.
I'm a winner.
I am a winner.
I'm a fucking winner.
[exhales]
I'm a winner. I'm a winner!
Hey, Pete.
[Pete] What part of bed
rest don't you understand?
- [both chuckle]
- All of it, apparently.
I feel just sick about Iron Mike.
Yeah, he was a fine man,
is what he was.
Say, uh, I'm looking for
anything you took off the D.O.A.
- Donny Ireland.
- Yeah, it's, uh...
You're just in time.
Uh, that other fella's
taking stock right now.
Who, now?
[sighs]
Well, look who it is.
[Witt sighs]
Did you just take something?
You know, I was on crutches once.
Cornerback tackled me funny
senior year.
It's the armpits, right?
Super painful.
Just now, I, uh...
I saw you put something
in your pocket.
Uh, looked a bit like you, actually.
Fella who blindsided me.
Black boy, fat through the middle.
What'd you take?
[clicks tongue] Now...
son, I've been humoring you
on account of they gave you
the general anesthesia
not too long ago,
and that shit will make the Pope
see spaceships, but...
you accuse me of stealing
one more time,
and I'm gonna do to you what I
did to that boy in high school.
And believe me,
you never want to see a tire iron
moving that fast in your direction.
Last chance.
Tell me what you took.
You don't know?
I took your mama out for dinner.
She gave out that ass
like a coupon on coupon day.
[grunts]
♪ ♪
[box thuds softly]
- [Pete] You okay, Witt?
- Yeah, yeah. I, um...
Say, did that fella leave his card?
Yeah.
[grunts]
[laptop chimes]
[Witt] There you are.
[dialing]
- [line ringing]
- [Danish] Before we dig in,
I want to make clear
this is an informal gathering
with information traveling
uphill from you to us,
not an interview-type situation
where we feel interrogated.
- Well, I do have...
- That's fine.
Deputy.
[sighs] Well, as you know,
we have evidence
of a break-in at your son's
house in Scandia.
To wit, blood residue and DNA traces
from hair samples
found in the master.
Yeah, my daughter-in-law says
that never happened.
Plus there is a state trooper
in North Dakota
who looks like is going to ID
Mrs. Lyon as present in the car
of two men who opened fire
on his prowler the same night,
with whom he then retreated
to a nearby filling station,
where they were held under siege
until reinforcements could arrive.
Can't we just make
this whole thing go away?
I mean, really.
Whatever did or didn't happen,
I-I'm sure we can
handle this internally.
[laughs softly]
Mrs. Lyon, a state trooper is dead.
In North Dakota.
Remind me which state
we're in again.
That's, uh...
We have real evidence
that two extremely violent men
kidnapped your daughter-in-law
for reasons unknown.
- You're not worried they might
come back? - Which?
The dead one
or the one whose blood
is all over my son's floor?
Seriously, I can protect my family,
whatever mischief
they may or may not get into.
And if the state trooper IDs
your daughter-in-law
as present for the melee after?
If North Dakota wants
to question either Mrs. Lyon,
Wayne or Dot,
they'll need to go through me.
So we're through.
Yeah. Yep.
What is your function?
Excuse me?
The police.
I mean, why do we need you?
Except as a tool to keep
a certain element in line.
To separate those who have
money, class, intellect
from those who don't.
You're gatekeepers,
standing outside the walls,
keeping the rabble from getting in.
But in here, inside these walls,
you have no function.
You should remember that.
[Indira clears throat]
So, what do you want to do?
Bring in the security detail
we used last year.
Burl Huffmen's unit
from out in Las Vegas?
Put a team at Wayne's,
and up the security here
- and at my house.
- And what about Dorothy?
You said she showed you
the other side of the coin yesterday.
She's a wolf in sheep's
clothing, that one.
We keep her close for now.
You said your man
is looking for dirt?
Yeah, former CIA.
Whatever she's hiding, he'll find it.
[indistinct radio transmission]
[dispatcher] Car ten,
car ten, what's your 20?
[officer responds indistinctly]
[dispatcher] Copy that.
We got a 1015 on Elk Street
near Main.
Whenever you're done, if you
could head over and take a look.
[officer]
Uh, roger that. ETA 20 minutes.
[dispatcher]
All Stark County deputies,
we're hearing there's chickens
on the road out on 290
and a truck in a ditch.
[Clem] This is Clem,
car six. On my way.
[Roy] Sheriff to deputy.
[Gator] Yeah, shoot.
[Roy] Got to talk to you.
Meet me at Hammurabi Pawnshop.
[Gator] Roger, Wilco.
[indistinct radio transmission]
[Roy]
What are we doing about Nadine?
[Gator] I told you
she goes by, uh, Dorothy now.
[Roy] Yeah. We'll leave her
alone until after the election.
- But...
- Is what I was thinking.
And with the feds sniffing around.
But then last night I had a dream.
What's today?
Uh, I don't know.
- The 31st?
- Halloween.
All Hallows' Eve,
in which the world of the gods
is made visible to humanity
and the dead come back to life.
That's what Nadine is,
can't you see?
She was dead, now she's back.
- So...
- So we get her tonight.
Everyone's in costume,
the streets are busy.
It's 2:00 already.
- Do you want me to...
- Only guys we can trust.
Ding-dong, trick-or-treat,
we send two around the back,
breach from both sides,
tie 'em up, put their masks on.
Their, uh...
- Their Halloween masks.
- Yeah.
Victor and villain, incognito,
then boom.
You're out the door,
you're in the van.
No one's the wiser.
Only guys we can trust. Say it.
Only guys we can trust.
You got this.
I believe in you.
["Smack My Bitch Up"
by The Prodigy playing]
♪ ♪
[clicking]
Husband and the kid
won't be a problem.
It's the missus
you got to watch out for.
♪ ♪
[groans]
♪ Change my pitch up,
smack my bitch up ♪
[exhales]
♪ Change my pitch up,
smack my bitch up ♪
[Bryn] For thy peace,
I pawn my own soul.
[groans]
[gasps]
Ah.
♪ ♪
[woman vocalizing]
Going out, Mama.
♪ ♪
- ♪ Smack my bitch up. ♪
- [phone ringing]
[Roy sighs deeply over phone]
[Roy] ♪ Nadine ♪
♪ Honey, is that you? ♪
♪ Oh, Nadine ♪
♪ Seems like every time
I see you, darling ♪
♪ You got something else to do. ♪
[Munch breathing sharply]
[Munch speaking Latin]
[bells clanking]
- [goats bleating]
- [Munch continues in Latin]
[group singing in foreign language]
[exhales]
[speaking Latin]
Left or right?
[Gator] Not sure.
The phone's saying one thing,
sign's saying something else.
Turn right, circle back.
We'll find 'em.
Fuck.
♪ ♪
[speaks indistinctly]
[Munch speaking Latin]
[grunts]
[panting]
[Munch speaking Latin]
[grunts]
[sharp breaths]
[speaking Latin]
[growling]
[shouting]
[exhales sharply]
♪ ♪
- [child] Trick or treat.
- [child 2] Trick or treat.
Mom? You coming?
[Dot] Yeah, right behind you, squirt.
[engine approaching]
[Scotty] Mom?
I'm coming.
[footfalls crunching]
[door opens]
[door creaks]
[knife sharpening]
♪ ♪
[man] Now I get it.
[rooster crows]
[roars]