BETH: Previously on Good Girls...
Who the hell are you?
I'm a friend of your friend's.
Give me your car keys.
Downstairs, on the counter.
RUBY: I've never worked
so hard for so little.
I say we get out.
We just need some extra hands.
You wanna bring
other people into this now?
So, what's a secret shopper?
Nancy and I are suing you for custody.
I got cola, Tina, Molly, Oxy,
K, Addys, and fat bags of herb.
I started a business.
Okay.
I didn't wanna tell you
because I was afraid I'd fail.
I didn't fail.
I'm crushing it.
Dangerous people took advantage of you.
They didn't take advantage of me.
It was a choice.
I wanted to.
An!
Where did this come from?
(HOUSE SONG PLAYING)
Okay.
Are you a drug lord?
Are you running a prostitution ring?
(CHUCKLES)
Don't you wish?
What is going on?
I mean, 'cause I have a right to know.
Remember when you were
screwing your secretary
and lost everything that we had,
and I was completely in the dark?
Yes.
So, this is kind of like that.
Oh, don't forget that I need you out
of the house tonight.
Book club?
Book club.
What am I supposed to do with the kids?
I don't know.
Take them to the movies.
What the hell...
Take them to Disneyland.
(SONG CONTINUES PLAYING)
Who are these people, Daddy?
Uh, Mommy's friends.
EMMA: What are they doing here?
Book club.
Come on.
Let's go.
Go, go, go.
Come on. Hi.
WOMAN 1: Hi.
Hi.
WOMAN 2: Hi.
Heaven, you're on five, till close.
Copy that.
BOOMER: Hey, have you seen Annie?
Uh, no, she called in sick again.
She hasn't been in in two weeks.
Hey.
Is she gonna quit?
I don't know.
Well, what did she say?
That she was sick.
What kind of sick, Heaven?
There's cold.
There's flu.
There's diarrheal.
Ew, I don't know.
All extremely different
virus pathologies.
What did she tell you?
Just that she was Sick.
You know what, you tell me when
you hear from her.
I wanna know when she's coming in.
Okay. Great.
Smile.
Okay.
ANNIE: Okay, people, so listen up.
R.
What does it mean?
Okay. (CHUCKLES)
I can see we're all taking
a little evening nap here.
Hey, Beth, let's get
some more coffee in here,
and you know what,
throw in some espresso shots
for the bitches in the front row.
R.
What is it?
(COFFEE POURING)
Do Not Resuscitate?
Yes, but the thing is, Tyler,
that's for when you're dead.
That's for when you've given up.
Are you giving up, Tyler?
No.
Is anyone else here giving up?
ALL: (MURMURING) No.
ANNIE: No? Excellent.
(PHONE CHIMES)
Then let's go ahead
and pull our heads out of our asses...
And, oh, my God, Heather,
I'm not gonna say it again.
Get the hell off your phone.
(CELL PHONE LOCKS)
"ZR
"Do your surveys."
The more you buy and return,
the more money you're gonna make.
"N..." "Never buy
and return from the same store."
That one should pretty much be a duh
at this point.
Which leaves us with "R."
Any guesses?
Um, recycle your shopping bags?
(ALL MURMURING IN AGREEMENT)
(CLEARS THROAT)
Are we trying to save the planet?
Um, no.
Are we at a Greenpeace meeting?
No.
What are we here for, Mary Pat?
To make money.
(SHOUTS) And what
is an essential component
of making money,
when you're a secret shopper?
Re...
ANNIE: Re...
ALL: Re...
Really do your surveys?
(SHOUTS) Receipts!
(PEOPLE GASP)
ANNIE: (SHOUTING)
Save your receipts!
Come on! Say it with me people!
Receipts, receipts!
ALL: Receipts, receipts!
ALL: Receipts!
Receipts! Receipts!
Receipts, receipts!
Man, they trashed my house.
Mmm. It was that bloody Ruth woman.
She sucked down, like, 17 eggrolls.
I saw her do it.
Maybe I should stop serving food.
No, it's good.
It keeps them hyped up.
Hey, speaking of which...
Here we go.
I think we should up the ante, you know?
Maybe offer a little
sales incentive next month.
What? Like a flatware set?
Actually, I was thinking
more like a trip to Cancun.
What?
I mean, why not?
Because we don't have money to burn,
and we have to be smart about this.
(ANNIE SCOFFS)
We have a six-month plan.
Dawg, the way this operation
is blowing up,
we're gonna be in the black
a lot sooner than that.
She is not wrong.
(GASPS) I'm sorry, could you...
Could you say that one more time,
but slowly, with feeling?
We got a lot of shoppers.
We are rolling deep now.
How much did we clear this week?
(SIGHS)
(CALCULATOR CLACKING)
You guys...
Shoppers be shoppin'.
Yo, make with the info already.
How much?
Come on!
(POP SONG PLAYING)
SALESWOMAN:
We just got it in.
Fourteen-karat, emerald cut, white gold.
It's so beautiful.
It would look stunning on you.
With that skin...
How much?
$1,100.
ANNIE: Come on.
Just try it on.
I'm 11.
They're gonna laugh.
No, no.
Excuse me, sir.
Hi. What can you tell us about this
incredible suit here?
Are we looking
to buy a gift for Daddy or...
Actually, Daddy couldn't pull this off.
We're looking for my daughter.
(SCOFFS) I'm not sure something like this
would really work on her.
We do have a kids' department.
Mmm. Honey, I'm sorry.
Could you just...
Could you hang on to these for me?
My purse just won't close.
SALESWOMAN:
It's just stunning.
Thank you.
If you want to give your husband my card,
I'm happy to set it aside.
My husband can't afford this.
Well...
Thirty-six short?
Let's start with 34.
Something with no break
and a tight inseam.
GQ says the clean look's still in.
(SONG CONTINUES PLAYING)
(WHISPERS) Hey.
(CHUCKLES)
And we finish it with our pistachio foam,
which Chef has infused with local flavors
from his favorite
Peruvian coastal village.
We then flash-caramelize it
using a refracted laser.
(SONG CONTINUES PLAYING)
What?
That looks...
Oh, okay.
WAITER: Enjoy.
Is that a...
Uh-huh.
It's a grape.
STAN: Mmm, it Sure is.
I mean, that grape has been places.
It's better-traveled than me.
That grape has seen things.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
But, and this is the true test...
Mmm.
Has this grape
ever arrested anybody?
(SCOFFS)
Come on, now.
It was just an assist. Okay?
Small-time drug bust.
Did you get to put on the cuffs?
(SIPS, SMACKS LIPS)
Uh, maybe.
(BOTH LAUGH)
Well, in that case,
you get the bigger half, Mr. Officer.
Oh, no, no, no, no, Please. Please.
I'm still full from the heirloom carrot
on a bed of micro greens
foraged by gnomes.
(CHUCKLES)
We're gonna need to get
some pizza after this.
Please.
You Know what, though?
It feels good to treat ourselves
for once.
Right?
Yeah.
Hey, are we good to spend like this?
I mean, I know you got the new gig...
You know what else I got?
Mmm?
I have a new theory on money.
Tell me.
It's like a boomerang.
If you throw it out there,
it's gonna come back.
That's gangster.
To your first arrest.
(CLINKING)
(DOOR OPENS)
Well, it's about time.
Eddy, right?
Jim Turner.
People call me Jimmy.
It's nice to meet you.
Let's see what's going on here.
Oof!
Third strike, huh?
Well, that blows.
Whatever.
Possession, armed robbery.
Damn, son, you fell in
with a rough crowd, as my mama would Say.
You think I'm gonna snitch?
Or tell you anything about anybody?
It's okay. Let's go.
Where?
Home.
You're on my way.
I'll drop you off.
You ain't gonna charge me with anything?
No offense, but no one really
cares about you,
so if you're not talking,
might as well free up the room.
You mind if we grab a bite on the way?
I haven't eaten.
What's that shawarma place
your boys all hang out at?
Aman's?
Amir's.
Yeah, I can eat that
fried eggplant all day.
We'll grab a booth
by the window, do some people-watching.
We watch them, they watch us.
You, uh...
You on Instagram?
Nah.
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS)
Now you are.
What's your problem, man?
Oh, me? No problem,
but you might have one
coming home smelling like cop coffee.
Do you wanna get me killed or something?
See, now, that's up to you, son.
Should we go?
(SIGHS)
WOMAN ON TV:
And something was dumped on my lap,
and I don't want this
to be happening right now.
Oh, she's gonna do it.
No. No!
She's doing it.
No!
I can't.
(BOTH GASP)
I cannot!
I don't wanna be the one
to have fo tell you this
because it's not like...
Please don't let it be about Tom.
It's about Tom.
(BOTH SCREAM)
No!
Just don't...
Get away from me right now.
Oh, Countess, you knew he was a playa.
Dude, you are on a reality show!
Oh, you can't turn those cameras off.
(BETH AND ANNIE GROAN)
WOMAN ON TV:
Coming up...
I'm mortified for her.
(SIGHS)
Okay, you guys...
I did something.
What?
What does that mean?
What did you do?
Tell me there is not
another man up in that treehouse.
Wait here.
I don't like that look in her eye.
Mmm.
Tension's killing me.
I'm getting more Bugles.
Ooh, wine me, please.
Yeah.
(SLOW POP SONG PLAYING)
I want you guys to be honest.
I kind of love it, but...
Maybe it's over the top.
(SONG CONTINUES)
Not over the top at all.
(SCOFFS)
What is that?
Is that...
Is that emerald cut?
Please put down the gun.
How much of my money
did that set you back?
This isn't your money.
Oh, see, but it is.
What are you doing?
I thought we were past this.
Me, too.
But you bitches just keep stealing
from me.
You think you could slip in
fake cash with the real
and I ain't gonna notice?
No, it's not possible, we have a system.
Ah, me too.
No, we know what is real and
we know what is fake.
Oh, me too.
And you tried to rip me off 100Gs?
What?
What? No!
I swear to God we would never do that.
Maybe it was one of the women.
Maybe one of them didn't wash the money
and just turned in
her surveys and didn't go shopping.
What women?
We couldn't wash the cash fast enough,
so we had to outsource.
You shared my business with other people?
RUBY: None of them
actually knows anything.
(STUTTERS) They're just women who think
they're literally shopping.
Which one of your lady friends
screwed me?
How could we know?
I'm gonna need a name.
Why?
To handle it.
Listen, there could be
any one of 30 people who...
And you're gonna give me a name.
Or I'm just gonna pick one.
At the next PTA mixer.
(SIGHS)
You can't tell from these surveys.
These all look totally legit.
I mean, it could be any of them.
It's not like it would take
a criminal mastermind,
just somebody smart but, like, lazy.
It wasn't me.
Well, we gotta figure it out before
he "handles it."
What's with the air quotes?
I think it's pretty clear
what he meant by "handle it."
Again, with the air quotes.
He's not gonna take it up with HR.
He's gonna cap a bitch!
BETH: That's not gonna happen. Okay?
Not if we handle it ourselves.
(GASPS)
That is not with air quotes.
(SIGHS)
What if we send everyone
to the same store, just in one day?
We give them a small drop to spend
so we don't raise flags.
What does that do?
Well, then we can sit and watch and see
who doesn't show up to shop.
Like a stakeout.
Well, that's kind of more for cops.
Yeah, we're watching to see
who doesn't show, So...
Oh, sorry. So, like,
the very definition of a stakeout.
Do you always have to label it?
Or be down with the lingo?
It gets to be a bit much.
Wow. You guys just cannot
give it to me, can ya?
(PATS TABLE)
That's sad.
Unbelievable.
RUBY: Hey, babe?
STAN: Yeah?
Can you make sure Harry
brushes his teeth, please?
Oh, he's good.
He's not good.
He's Six.
And he has dog breath.
What's all this sunshine?
What you got back there?
I don't know.
Why don't you pick a hand and find out?
Stan, I have to
get these kids ready for bed.
I have to prep for a crazy day tomorrow.
Well, then you need to come on.
Oh, my God, really?
(LAUGHING)
What!
Glass seats behind the net, baby.
(CLICKING TONGUE)
What'd they cost?
Who cares what they cost?
You always wanted seats
behind the glass, right?
Glass seats.
What I want and what we can afford
are very different.
(SIGHS) Now wait a minute.
I thought we were
living a little bit here.
Yeah, a little, not like Jay and Bey.
What? No, I'm...
I'm sending the boomerang out, remember?
Yeah, and I'm trying
to keep it from taking our heads off.
Look, I may have gotten
a little ahead of myself.
This business, it's just...
We're gonna need to pump the brakes
a little bit.
Just one hockey game.
How much were they?
Stan?
Huh?
Stanley Lamont Hill!
(PEOPLE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Annie Bananie!
Welcome back.
How you feeling?
Better.
OFFICER: Are these gonna be necessary?
You look like you know the drill.
I'm sorry, Officer.
What am I being arrested for?
Trafficking a class-one
controlled substance.
Wait, what?
Well, they'll explain
everything to you down
at the station, okay?
Wow.
You vile little weasel.
You planted something on me?
Okay, that's it.
Unbelievable.
Even for you, that's low.
I didn't think you had it in you.
Wow. That's cool, you little dick.
'Cause you know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna rip that wormy little mustache
right off your face,
and that ugly-ass nut duster, too.
And I'm gonna cram them
where the sun don't shine, buddy.
That's right.
It's on now!
You have no idea the pain that I'm gonna
bring upon your house!
You are over, you little punk-ass bitch!
(SCOFFS)
Guys, that's not
Fine & Frugal behavior, okay?
Back to work.
Clean up aisle 10.
Seriously?
I'm sorry I didn't get
your message until this morning.
I had to sleep on the floor.
It was like frigging Oz in there.
Who's with Sadie?
She's at a sleepover, thank God.
Hey, Beth!
Seriously?
I couldn't get a babysitter.
Dean's at the oncologist.
What did you want me to do?
I don't Know. Maybe not
make them watch Auntie do a perp walk.
Oh, don't get mad at me.
I'm not the one who got arrested.
Yes, thank you.
I'm aware...
For drugs, no less.
They weren't mine.
Said everyone ever busted for drugs.
I'm telling you I was set up, okay?
Like the cinnamon schnapps at prom?
Why would you even throw that in my face?
That's not relevant.
Because I'm still bailing you out.
I'm telling you, they were not mine.
Boomer set me up.
What?
(SIGHS)
(SNIFFLES)
I'm gonna lose Sadie.
You Know it's true.
There's no judge in the world
that would let me keep her
after a felony drug charge.
(SOBBING)
I'm gonna help you with this.
We are gonna figure this out
together, okay?
This is really bad.
Together, okay?
(SIGHS) Okay.
Okay.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Hey, guys!
Auntie has a funny story.
ANNIE: The lawyer thinks
that it would make me look
more responsible
if you stayed with
Dad and Nancy for a little while.
Baby, please don't be sad.
Please.
I promise, I'm gonna fix this.
Can we just
sit here a little?
Of course, baby.
(SIGHS)
RUBY: Honey, you gotta get a lawyer.
I have a custody one.
You need a criminal one.
Yeah.
Ugh! I'm gonna have a whole legal team,
O.J. style.
Yeah, and fight it.
That little grocery-store turd
is going down.
I just want my kid back, you know?
(WOMEN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(SHOPPING CARTS RATTLING)
Yo, bogie, 11 o'clock.
BETH: That's...
RUBY: Brooke.
Red glasses.
Okay, how many more?
Twenty-eight.
Settle in.
ANNIE: (IRRITABLY)
How many more now?
RUBY: I'm not telling you.
Why not?
'Cause it's the same
answer as it was five minutes ago.
(SIGHS)
This is the worst stakeout ever.
At least you don't have
somebody's nasty-ass feet in your face.
Ow.
I'm gonna die of natural causes
in this minivan.
You might just go quicker.
Just find out who it is, okay?
Okay.
If we had to sacrifice someone
to the gang...
I nominate that lady Heather.
Are you for real right now?
I'm talking, like, gun-to-the-head had to.
Annie.
She is always on her phone.
And that's a reason to kill her?
It's like,
"Chill, bitch.
"Nobody's posted on Instagram
in the last three seconds, 'Kay?"
Oh, my God.
I'm just saying, back pocket.
Should we wake her up?
No.
I'm enjoying the quiet.
(SIGHS)
Check it.
Closing time, and one name left.
So what now?
We handle it.
(ENGINE STARTS)
MARY PAT:
I'm so sorry about the mess.
If I'd Known my bosses were coming,
I would've...
(CHUCKLES) You know?
Hey, boys, can you keep it down, okay?
I can't even hear myself think.
BOY: Okay, Mom.
Uh, what can I get you guys to drink?
We're fine.
Do you have any lemonade?
Uh...
I have...
I have water.
That's perfect.
That's great.
I love water.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(REFRIGERATOR CLOSES)
(CHUCKLES)
Okay, um...
Can you just...
Can you...
Oh, okay.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I just haven't, um,
really gotten used
to doing, like, everything
all by myself, you know,
since Jeff passed.
Oh. We didn't Know.
Yeah, he had a heart attack,
um, six months ago.
Oh, God, that's...
That's terrible.
We're so sorry.
And I'm so thankful
for your shopping club.
You know, I feel like
I finally have a shot
at getting my head above water. You know?
(SIGHS)
I'm just gonna rip off
the Band-Aid here, uh...
We know what you've been doing.
I don't understand.
(SIGHS) You've been
turning in the same cash, and it's okay.
You know, you obviously
have a lot on your plate,
and you're not in trouble.
But unfortunately,
we do have to let you go.
He's very cute.
(BABY FUSSING)
I'm so embarrassed.
Oh, please don't be.
You know, I ran out of time,
and I really needed the money.
(BABY CRYING)
No judgment here.
Uh-uh.
Oh, my God.
We'll just, uh, let ourselves out.
ANNIE: You take care, okay?
Good night.
(DOOR OPENS)
Wait, what...
What did you...
What did you mean when you said that
I turned in the same cash?
What?
I mean, how would
you know that I turned in
the exact same cash?
Obviously, we don't know that.
But we know from your survey
that you weren't
actually doing the shopping.
But that's not what she said, though.
Well, that's what I meant.
But it's not what you said.
I mean...
Do you guys check
serial numbers or something?
No.
Now, that...
That'd be crazy.
Girl, it is never easy to be let go.
Mmm.
Trust me, I know.
I've been there.
And we would've kept you on, but
it was corporate's call.
Right.
You know, um,
come to think of It, if I am being fired,
it seems like I should
probably hear that from corporate.
Right?
Not you guys.
So what, um...
What's their number?
ANNIE: They're closed.
Yeah.
I mean, it's what time?
Come to think of it, what's their name?
I...
I know... I Know you're upset.
No, I'm not upset.
But, you know, who I think might be
is the Better Business Bureau.
Just hold on a minute.
BETH: No, no, no.
Let her do it.
We don't have anything to hide.
Go ahead.
I don't Know what you've
gotten me involved in,
but it's something super-shady.
I'm calling the police.
(LINE RINGING)
WOMAN: (ON PHONE)
Ashfield Police.
Put down the phone.
Hello. Hello, this is
the Ashfield Police,
do you have an emergency?
What do you want?
Who even let this bitch in?
Is she Tracy's friend?
Elena. Carpool or something.
(GROANS) Wow.
Yeah.
I mean,
we could let Rio
"handle it."
I'm just saying.
I don't want to, but,
you know, it would solve
the problem cleanly.
She's a single mother.
With a dead husband.
She's probably drowning in debt.
Oh, my God, you guys, it's not like
she's this great person.
She's blackmailing us.
I mean, that's illegal.
So is washing counterfeit money.
And robbing a grocery store.
And crossing the border
with counterfeit money.
(SIGHS) Okay! Okay.
(SIGHS) I mean, I hate to be the one
to say I told you so...
Then how about you don't.
But did I not tell you
this was a bad idea?
We never, ever should have brought
other people into this.
The system works.
Uh, clearly it doesn't.
Someone found the one flaw.
And is extorting us
to the tune of $10,000.
Okay, I know it would be
really nice and neat
to just make it my fault...
We were out.
We were done with the gang.
We were done with all of it.
Are you serious?
And then we went back and asked for more.
Because we needed the money
and you got on board real quick.
And now you're rolling
like some evil mastermind.
Don't you call her evil!
RUBY: With your six-month plan and
your secret shoppers,
luring them in like some crazy Pied Piper.
Don't you call her crazy!
Okay, pause.
You call her out all the time.
We are blood.
Okay. Thank you.
But...
Okay.
I see.
Okay,
I mean, I'm just the one
that held your hand
when you went through
the hell of signing your divorce papers,
but whatever.
'Cause I'm not blood.
You know what?
Do what you want.
Pay her, don't pay her.
Just leave me the hell out of it.
Wait. Where are you going?
Home. To my family.
My blood.
You can't just bail when things get bad.
Things got bad the second we took down
that grocery store.
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
(KNOCKING CONTINUES)
DEAN: Beth, are you decent?
Yeah.
Are you okay?
I...
I heard the water running
for like the last hour,
and I... I got worried.
Yeah, I couldn't sleep, and then I...
couldn't shower, So...
Do you mind if I turn off
the shower? Just...
Our water... water bill's
gonna be insane.
God, no, of course.
I'm sorry.
(SHOWER TURNS OFF)
(SIGHS)
Can I ask you one thing?
Okay.
Are you doing it for us?
I mean, the kids.
I mean, are you doing this for the kids?
Yes.
That's all I need to know.
(SCOFFS) Nice.
I'm having a "me" night.
Mmm.
What is it?
Uh, Sadie forgot some jeans.
Mmm, with the patches?
Yeah.
What's with all the Post-its?
ANNIE: Oh, uh, Sadie gets scared
that I'll forget stuff,
so she writes them down on Post-its.
Like the rent?
(SCOFFS) Please.
I would never forget that.
Because I have the Post-it.
She worries about you too much.
It's just, like, our shtick, okay?
Yeah, but she doesn't know that
because she's only 11.
You know what, Gregg?
I have had a really tough week,
so if there's any way
you could spare me the judgement...
How did you get picked up for pills?
(SCOFFS) Here we go.
They weren't yours, right?
I mean, if it had been
peppermint schnapps,
then you wouldn't
really have a defense, but...
Actually, I'm partial to cinnamon.
Ah, right, yes.
It's all coming back to me now.
So, do you want something to eat or...
Uh, what do you got?
Cheese and crackers.
Oh.
Mmm-hmm Okay.
Okay.
Ooh, what if...
they were combined, hmm?
Is this your dinner?
Hey, they're not just
for breakfast anymore.
Hmm?
You want, like, a glass of wine
or something with that?
It's SO grown-up.
You have wine?
Mmm.
Nah, just playing.
Only vodka.
Room temp?
Hey, you know me SO well.
(CHUCKLES)
This is clean-ish.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Classy.
You can be a real dick, you know that?
SO can you.
Oh, my God.
What did you buy this time?
Pick a hand and find out.
Seriously?
We're doing this again?
Not if you don't pick a hand.
Pick another one.
Stan.
All right.
Where'd you get that?
I put our tickets up for sale on StubHub,
and your man here made a tiny profit.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You were starting to get a little crazy.
I'm not crazy.
(IMITATING RUBY)
"Gonna spend money now.
Don't spend money."
I just worry.
Well, I worry too.
But we don't have to live
like the sky's always falling.
The sky is always falling.
Look at Sara.
She's healthy now, isn't she?
Yeah, but what about
in two weeks when she
stops taking her meds again?
(SIGHS)
It's like every time
I look down, it's pieces of sky.
Let's just take it as it comes.
I feel like the damn sky's out to get us.
Baby.
Yeah?
I got you.
Oh, my God!
Right?
No, stop!
I Know!
(LAUGHING) Oh, no.
Oh!
He remembers his little friend.
Wait, wait, wait.
Are you laughing or are you crying?
I can't tell.
I actually can't.
I have tears in my eyes.
No, it's over?
Yeah.
How am I gonna know what happens?
Oh, wait. Um...
He tears his throat out.
(LAUGHS) Shut up.
(GROANS)
Oh, no.
Aw, man.
Party's over.
What?
Wait, I have Fruit Roll-Ups
or some old raisins in there, I think.
Mmm, no. I should probably go home.
(SIGHS) Hmm.
Yeah, I mean, who's watching
Sadie right now?
Oh, Sadie's in bed.
(DRINK POURING)
Nancy's in bed.
Everybody's accounted for.
I'm, like, supes responsible.
You look so sleepy.
Are you sleeping any better these days?
Nah.
Mmm, Greggles.
(CHUCKLES)
Some things never change, huh?
Mmm-hmm.
(GASPS)
Have you seen the one
with the chimp and the frog?
No.
It's gonna blow your mind.
(ALTERNATIVE SONG PLAYING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
I know, I know.
Oh!
Oh.
Oh, no.
Huh?
Okay, I Know.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I know, I know.
(BOTH MUMBLING)
GREGG: Okay.
Oh, jeans, jeans.
What?
Sadie's jeans.
The jeans, the jeans...
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
I Know.
I know, I know.
(SIGHS)
Oh, no.
It's all there, and it's all real.
And it won't happen again.
So, who was it?
You got your money.
Yeah, I'm also gonna need a name.
I took care of it.
Come on.
Just give me a name.
Beth Boland.
(SCOFFS)
Now let me give you some advice, yeah?
When you got a rotten egg in the bunch,
it stinks up the whole lot
till you get rid of it.
Like I said, I'm handling it.
And don't ever point a gun at me again.
(HIP-HOP SONG PLAYING)
(SONG CONTINUES)
F.B.I. appreciates the D.P.D. tagging in
on this.
These guys are organized,
but an arrest you made
this week, gave us a man on the inside.
I Know a task force means
a little longer hours,
but Detroit's gonna appreciate it big-time
when we put these guys away,
so let's get started.
If you all would turn
to page four of your hymnals.
(SONG ENDS)
Open up.
(DOOR UNLOCKS)
(SHIVERS)
What?
We just didn't think you'd show.
Please. I'm stuck with you guys.
Good. 'Cause we need you.
Where the hell would I go, anyway?
I don't know, the diner would
probably take you back.
There's no going back.
Ever tell you guys about the sauce?
I don't think I've even told Stan.
You gotta swear.
Promise.
Ride or die.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
So, for a while, the diner was running
this Italian sub deal.
Salami with peppers and onions
and special sauce.
To save money,
Tony orders a 55-gallon barrel.
We kept it in the basement.
It was so damn hot down there,
the heat would cause the oils
to separate.
We'd use this wood canoe paddle
to stir it back together.
Eventually, the paddle breaks.
And you know cheap-ass Tony,
he's not gonna buy a new paddle.
You tell yourself
you'd never do something...
Wasn't there a ladle you could use
or something?
A broom, even?
Just my arm.
I had the longest.
So, every day,
twirling in these sauce oils
like a conductor for the New York Phil.
Then one morning,
I get a paper cut opening the mail.
Whatever.
I go about my day.
I'm elbow-deep in sauce,
and when I pull out my arm,
my Band-Aid's gone.
(SHUDDERS) No.
Yeah.
I can't tell Tony.
His cheap-ass isn't gonna
buy another barrel.
Oh, my God.
Six months go by.
This sub deal is still a hit.
One day, a customer comes up to Tony,
opens up his sub,
and in the middle
of those peppers and onions
is my Band-Aid.
Are you crying?
It's just So gross, I...
(WHISPERS) I can't.
You never have to go back there, okay?
(GROANS)
We got you.
And, hey...
You know you're our blood.
You know that, right?
I love you guys.
(CHILDREN YELLING)
(CARTS RATTLING)
Mary Pat on your two.
(R&B SONG PLAYING)
BOY: Hey!
MARY PAT:
Get in the car.
(CHILDREN CHATTERING)
MARY PAT: That's good.
Thank you.
Thank you, guys.
MARY PAT: Okay.
Everyone's all buckled in.
Thank you.
So much.
Wow. Thank you so much for the help.
I really appreciate it.
$10,000.
Yeah, that too.
It's all there.
(CHUCKLES)
So, we're good now, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, we're good.
Till next month.
Excuse me?
Whoa.
I thought this was a one-time deal.
Yeah. I mean, I thought I was
a secret shopper.
Bye.
(ENGINE STARTS)
(R&B SONG CONTINUES)