BETH: Previously on Good Girls...
I don't know what
you've got me involved in.
But it's something super shady.
What do you want?
She's blackmailing us.
To the tune of $10,000.
We're gonna be shutting things
down for a while.
RUBY: How long?
I don't know.
What about us?
I guess we go legit for a while.
Welcome to Dandy Donuts.
What can I get for you?
I would suggest that we put Sara
on our list for a transplant.
EDDY: Who the hell are you?
BETH: I'm a friend of your friends.
RUBY: Who's that?
STAN: It's that fool we arrested.
He's ours now.
They have him!
The FBI! And he's talking!
He is talking to them!
We have to tell Rio.
If we tell him, he'll kill him.
It's that kid or us.
GIRL: Tag! You're it!
BOY: Tag!
(CHILDREN CLAMORING)
So, we're murderers now.
Yeah. Straight-up execution is what it is.
Cold-blooded killing of a man.
ANNIE: His name is Eddy.
He likes his mom,
vintage watches, and Mexican food.
What? I'm just trying
to, like, humanize him before we...
We're not killing anyone.
What do you call it, then?
We're just telling
a gangbanger that his boy's been flipped
by the cops.
Yeah. And you know they're not going
to couples therapy to work it out.
RUBY: The second we open our mouths...
You just wanna sit here
and let him tell the FBI all about us?
We're looking at 20 or more,
and I'm not doing that.
BOY: Tag!
GIRL: Hey!
Tag!
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
Watch out! You're it.
(CHILDREN CLAMORING)
Let me just say,
it's one thing to wash fake cash
or rob a grocery store.
But there is a line here.
And if you cross it, you can't come back.
Then we don't come back.
Have yourself a dandy day.
MAN: Thanks. You, too.
Welcome to Dandy Donuts.
What can I do for you on this dandy day?
(MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY OVER HEADSET)
Two decafs and a glazed, please!
Stepping it up.
Yeah, thanks.
You know, I think you're ready
for the night shift.
It pays an extra 75 cents an hour.
I have two kids, So...
Can I please
get a large coffee
and a glazed?
Come on.
Pep in your step, folks!
Okay, here you go.
Dude, this is a promotion.
(SIGHS)
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
(SCREAMS) What?
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
So I take that as a "yes"?
(SCREAMS)
STAN: Ring, ring.
(SARA GASPS)
(LAUGHS)
Bing! I upgraded, okay?
It's got the three-day battery,
so it's not gonna short out on you.
You're not gonna drop any phone calls
unless you put that thing
in the toilet bowl
or something.
Do not do that.
STAN: Please don't do that.
What do I get?
A hug.
And you get a very important job,
Little Money.
Because you need to make sure
that your sister has got this phone, okay?
Because we have to be
able to be reached by
the hospital, day or night.
Can I get Instagram on this?
RUBY: Forget Instagram, baby doll.
You got a big-ass healthy kidney coming!
Top of the list!
New kidney!
Top of the list.
New kidney. Top of the list.
(RUBY SCATTING)
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Can!godo my homework?
God. I love you.
You're such a nerd.
Yes. Go ahead.
Go ahead, babe.
Yeah. What's going on here?
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Okay. Okay.
(SIGHS)
I mean...
I Know.
It's happening.
It's all happenin', babe.
So, if this call comes...
When the call comes, baby. When.
How are we gonna pay for it?
Insurance is gonna cover some.
It's gonna be
almost 100 G's out of pocket.
Hmm.
(CLICKS TONGUE, SIGHS) I know.
(GROANS)
Have you heard from corporate yet?
What?
No, I'm just saying it'd be real good
if, you know, you got your business
started back up.
Yeah, it would.
(SIGHS)
Oh!
Oh, God. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Sorry.
(DOOR SHUTS)
DEAN: What are you even doing here?
What are you even doing here?
I live here.
I mean, kinda.
It's... It's my house.
How long are you gonna stay?
Oh, just stop! Please?
Sadie is with Gregg.
Oh.
Well, sorry. (STAMMERS)
That sucks. I didn't know.
Yeah.
And Bethie said I could stay here
until I feel better.
That's great.
Mi casa, Su casa.
Mm-hmm.
Gracias, hermano.
So, how you feelin' right now?
(INHALES SHARPLY)
Not so good, Deansie.
(SOFTLY) Settle in.
Hmm.
Uh-oh.
What happened?
Oh, nothing.
Some quality time together.
We were just having a chat...
(ALL CHATTERING)
We gotta go.
We've got that thing.
Bye.
RIO: Y'all ready to be
back in business or what?
RUBY: What'd you have in mind?
Just need you to go
pick up a truck for me.
In Canada?
No, right here.
Parked in a garage off I-75.
What's in it?
You ain't gotta worry about that.
Just go get it, and we're good to go.
I thought y'all would be
more excited than this.
But, hey, if you don't need
to get back to work...
Oh, we do. We do.
There's something we
need to talk about, though.
Yeah, uh, none of us drive stick.
I mean, everything's automatic.
So, I just never learned.
I don't know about you guys, but...
You know what?
It'll be fine.
It's not an 18-wheeler,
so problem raised, problem solved.
Problem not solved,
though, because there's the other problem.
Which is a much bigger problem.
Are you bitches tryin' to do this or not?
Hey! We got 99 problems, but
this bitch ain't one, okay?
So, we're in like Flynn.
Where the keys at?
We're gonna get pinched
the second we pull
that thing out of that garage.
Now look who's down with the lingo.
There's no way
that kid didn't tell the FBI
about a truckload full of God knows what.
And Sara will literally
be bumped off the list
if we don't get the money.
Wait, seriously?
You have to pay upfront
before the surgery.
What? You can't, like,
finance it or something?
It's a kidney, not a refrigerator.
All right, this is it.
Up here, on the left.
There it is.
I don't see any cops.
Yeah, that doesn't mean
they're not around.
(INHALES) What do you think"s in it?
The next shipment of fake cash?
Bodies. Dozens, maybe.
(SCOFFS) Could be hundreds
if they're chopped up.
Just give me the keys.
Now?
We gotta get back in business.
Oh, dude, don't do it. Seriously.
It's my family.
(SIGHS)
(KEYS JANGLING)
(STAMMERS) Wait.
Maybe we should ask Stan first.
We?
Well, you.
You want me to ask my cop husband
if his cop friends
have their eye on a truck
that's potentially filled
with dead bodies?
Well, I would be a little bit more subtle,
but that's your call.
(SIGHS)
You okay?
I mean, just add it to the list of things
I'm not okay with.
Like taking orders from grown men
who go by the names
of Bullet, Demon and Mr. Cisco.
(GASPS) Which one is Mr. Cisco?
(SIGHS)
Ew!
(LAUGHING) You are making those names up!
I am not!
I saw the one with the skull tattoo
call the one with the grill "Mr. Cisco."
Now, whether that's a God-given name
or a nickname, I don't Know,
but he answers to it.
I am truly disturbed.
Yeah, well, get in line.
Mr. Cisco is the one to watch.
Mark my words.
Nothing but trouble.
BETH: Let's go.
ANNIE: Please.
Ma'am, did you find everything okay today?
Um, yeah, where do you guys
hide the baby formula?
Hi, by the way. (CHUCKLES)
Uh, it's in aisle six with the diapers.
Duh, obvs.
Hey, honey. Aisle six.
Will you go get some baby formula?
Okay, but nothing organic or expensive.
Yeah.
A few pesticides never hurt anybody,
did they? No, they didn't.
(BABY COOING)
Oh, my God.
This is so random, but...
BOY: Can I have this?
No, no candy.
Um, do you know anything
about hot water heaters?
They keep your water hot.
Right. Until they get old and rusty,
right? (CHUCKLES)
Call the plumber.
I did, believe me.
The whole thing cost me
8,000 bucks, plus another
$1,500 to dry the carpets.
We just gave you $10,000.
BOY: What about this?
One, okay?
I Know. I feel so sick about this.
What am I gonna do?
You know I gotta feed my kids, right?
Oh, hell no.
Come on. I just need
to get through to next month.
I need a restock at register three.
Restock at register three.
So, you don't have,
like, a house account, or...
No.
Um, how about a "you gave me
"counterfeit money to spend" account?
Do you have one of those? Ora, um...
What are those things called?
Um, an "I could still
call the cops on you"
account, maybe?
No? All right.
We'll just put the whole thing
on the "I'm what's
keeping you out of jail" account,
and we'll just...
We'll just call it a day.
Sound good?
(HUFFS)
(REGISTER BEEPS)
You're the best.
Thank you so much.
Don't forget the candy bar.
BOY: I got it. I found it!
Thanks, honey.
Okay. I said
"not organic," though.
Ah, it's fine.
It's on sale. (CHUCKLES)
Uh, oh, and I brought my own bags.
So, that's good for the environment.
Hey, you!
TYLER: Hey!
How are you?
Good, how are you?
MARY PAT: Can I hug you
at work? Is that allowed?
TYLER: Yeah, that's fine.
MARY PAT: This is my brood.
Guys, please stay in the store, at least.
(STAN SIGHS)
Kids are down.
Good. (EXHALES)
What you got there?
Uh... What is that?
Leftovers.
From when?
Nelly concert, 2003.
Babe...
I am an officer of the law.
Off duty.
I shouldn't even be seeing that.
(SINGING)
It's gettin' hot in here So hot
Oh, my God.
So take off all your clothes
Put that away.
I am getting so hot
No. See...
I wanna take my clothes off
You need to stop playing.
You remember that show?
(SINGING)
I was like, good gracious
Ass Is bodacious
Ooh.
Flirtatious, trying to make faces
Ooh!
(LAUGHS)
What's going on with you?
I don't know.
I'm just, you know,
finally seeing some light
in this damn tunnel.
(SIGHS) Yeah.
Haven't we earned at least one night off?
(SNIFFS)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
Kids are down?
For the count.
You're with a winner, baby
So you can't lose
I can't.
I got a secret Can't leave Cancun
Shh.
DEAN: It's solid...
I mean, it's solid pine,
and I countersunk the screws.
And these...
These are for paint,
or Modge Podge, or whatever.
What do you think?
It's really, really nice.
DEAN: I mean, it...
It's rustic on purpose.
I left it unvarnished in case you wanna,
you know, decoupage or whatever.
If a bug has six legs, it's...
Disgusting.
You hate it.
No, I don't. I don't.
The woodworking is top-notch.
I just think maybe
I'm not as into crafting as I used to be.
Oh.
Well, it's not only for that.
It's for your stash. You can
put, like, half a million
bucks in there, easy.
That way, you don't have to hide it
in the dog food container.
I don't have a stash anymore.
Yeah, but you're going to, right? Soon.
I love it.
DEAN: You do? Yes!
Hey, Kenny! You wanna
know a fun bug fact?
Mm-hmm.
The girl praying mantis
eats the boy after they have sex.
What?
Oh, yeah.
She just bites his
weeny little head right off.
He's so obviously trying
to get back in your pants.
Please.
He's using your bathroom!
He lives here.
Ugh. Since when?
Since he got cancer.
(CLICKS TONGUE) Well,
he lucked out on that one.
Yeah, that's what they call
cancer patients.
"The lucky ones."
You are making a giant mistake.
You just slept with your ex.
Dude, he cheated on you
and almost left you
and your family homeless.
In the middle of a custody battle,
no less.
I'm sorry. But do you
remember what he bought that little skank?
Of course I do.
I'm gonna need you to Say it.
Underwear.
No. That was not underwear, baby girl,
that was bedazzled vagina floss, okay?
And it was horrible and humiliating.
And you're starting to forget.
No, I'm not.
Then you're starting to forgive him,
which is way worse.
Let me worry about it.
It's my marriage.
You can't do both.
Both what?
You can't be this sweet little wifey
and then also this, like,
badass criminal boss lady.
I sound like Carmen Sandiego.
You should be so cool.
Can we just go to bed?
Oh, man. All your drama
made me have to poop.
Oh, my God.
You have got to go home.
(HOT IN HERRE BY NELLY PLAYING)
(BOTH MOUTHING SONG LYRICS)
Babe.
Yeah?
Can you turn it off now?
Why? I thought you loved it.
Because, if I listen to it one more time,
I'm gonna need to dance.
Yeah?
I am no condition
to get my groove on right now.
(LAUGHING) No?
No.
But it's hot in here.
Oh, my God!
(LAUGHS)
(TURNS OFF MUSIC)
(CLEARS THROAT)
(SIGHS)
Hey, you still pack Little Money's lunches
with those cheese puffs in there?
I like where your head's at.
He gonna be mad, though.
You could take him.
He's tiny. (CHUCKLES)
He is.
He's so small.
Why's he so small?
Oh, oh, oh...
But I could also get the cookie dough
out the fridge, too, though.
Do it. Do it. Do it...
What? Yes. I'm a genius.
Okay.
(CHUCKLES)
(SOFTLY) Okay.
(LINE RINGING)
What's up?
I forgot.
You called me.
I forgot what I was supposed to ask Stan.
Huh?
RUBY: Literally.
What am I supposed to be asking?
Dude, are you faded?
I mean, yeah.
He gets chatty when he smokes, So...
(LAUGHS)
Well played.
So, what am I supposed to be asking?
If the kid told the cops about a truck.
Right.
ANNIE: Okay.
I mean, can you just do it?
What? No.
I can put you on speaker.
Trust me, that would be super weird.
It doesn't seem that weird.
Just slip it in there.
You know, real caj.
No big deal.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
(LAUGHS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Hey, babe.
So, that gangster kid
that you all flipped?
Did he say something
about a truck or something?
All right, so...
We sit this kid down, right?
And before we can even start,
my man is acting like
he's about to get
waterboarded or something like that,
starts singing like a bird.
For real?
Yes.
Talking about places, times, faces...
Stop.
...Names.
Trucks?
What?
All kinds of stuff.
Tyler! Got a sec?
Oh, I'm technically on break
for three more minutes.
Well, uh, I don't think
you're gonna wanna wait to hear this.
Am I getting a Segway?
No. No, this is not
about a pursuit vehicle.
Um...
Is it about the hamburger meat?
I'm making you employee of the month.
Seriously?
Yeah.
Well, not this month,
but I'm putting you on the fast track.
Thank you, Mr. Petersen.
No, come on.
Call me Leslie.
Yes, sir... Leslie.
Rolls right off the tongue.
Uh-huh.
An.
Hey, you know, um...
I saw you were, uh, helping a lady out
at Annie's register the other day.
You know, you gave her a hug.
Oh, no, she initiated contact.
Plus, I know her.
Oh, it's okay. Mm.
Oh.
I was just, uh... I was
just wondering, did you,
um, meet her on the job?
No, not this job.
Mary Pat's from my side job.
Mm.
Yeah.
Oh, what's the side job?
You know, it doesn't matter.
(CLEARS THROAT)
I mean, the only reason I was asking
was because Ms. Mary Pat left her,
uh, club card behind.
So I just didn't want her
to miss out on any Two-for-Tuesday deals.
That's really nice of you.
Hey, um...
You wouldn't have her number, would you?
Uh-uh. But I do follow her on Instagram.
She mainly posts
about church and her kids.
It's pretty boring.
Hey, so, for employee of the month,
is there gonna be a ceremony?
See you, Leslie! (CHUCKLES)
How sure are you?
Pretty sure.
No, that's not enough.
I need, like, a percentage.
Ninety-seven percent.
Hmm. Almost as accurate as the pill.
More.
No, the pill is 99.9.
You can't be 0.1% knocked up.
Uh-uh. That's if you take it perfect.
For most people, it's like 91%.
For you, it was zero.
Okay.
Look, I'm never gonna remember every
single thing that Stan said,
but I think we should just go for it.
All right, here's the test.
Do you remember that you called me?
Yes.
Do you remember that you were so high
you forgot why you got high?
Mm-hmm.
Look, I'm pretty sure the cops don't know
anything about a truck.
(SIGHS) All right, who's gonna drive?
Let's draw straws?
ANNIE: / always lose at that.
RUBY: So, the straws?
What about rock, paper, scissors?
BETH: We can't do that with three people.
ANNIE: Why not?
Basic math.
Everybody okay?
No smokies on my tail.
Yeah. I'm good.
ANNIE: (OVER RADIO) You guys,
that was So Sick.
They should totally make a movie about us.
RUBY: Uh, no thanks.
ANNIE: Wait, why not?
RUBY: Because I'd have to be
the wisecracking Black getaway driver
with one line who dies five minutes in.
ANNIE: Mm. True, true.
I'd be the Pacino.
Oh, you'd so be the Joe Pesci.
What?
Total Pesci.
Because I'm short?
RUBY: It's just, like,
a whole Pesci vibe with you.
ANNIE: (SCOFFS) All right.
You know what? Forget it.
The movie's off.
Guys...
ANNIE: "Pesci vibe."
ANNIE: What?
There's a cop behind me.
Okay. Okay. Just relax.
Yeah. That's easy for you to say.
You're not the one hauling a truckload
of life sentences here.
RUBY: Make a turn.
ANNIE: Yeah, lose that sucker.
RUBY: Don't lose him.
Just go slow and chill.
See if he follows.
Okay.
(BRAKES SCREECH)
RUBY: What's up?
He's still there.
RUBY: Just keep it together.
We got you. We're here.
You guys have to help Dean with the kids.
He can't do it alone.
Will you stop?
BETH: / don't want him marrying a bimbo.
He's 100% gonna marry...
No bimbos around my kids.
ANNIE: All right. No bimbos.
Monday's pizza day.
The kids don't need lunch.
Dance Tuesday.
Same as the math tutor.
Dentist appointments
are on the refrigerator.
Trash and recycling goes out Wednesdays...
(POLICE SIRENS CHIRPING)
RUBY: What's that?
What's happening?
(SIRENS CONTINUE BLARING)
ANNIE: Beth? Beth!
Say something!
RUBY: What's going on?
I'll write it all down,
but he'll need a village.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER OVER POLICE RADIO)
I gotta go.
(RADIO BEEPS)
Is there a problem, Officer?
Driver's license and registration.
Just give me a minute.
I hope I wasn't speeding,
I've been rushing around
like crazy all day.
Why's that?
Um...
Little bit of a domestic situation.
Not a good guy, you know?
Had to get out of there
as quickly as possible.
Hashtag, time is up, am I right?
It's one of those.
This your truck?
I borrowed it. From
a friend who's helping me
with the domestic thing.
Am I in trouble here?
First off, you're driving
without a license plate.
My friend's a little bit
of a mess, too. (CHUCKLES)
What's her name again?
Sorry?
The friend who loaned you the truck.
Oh, it's more of a friend of a friend.
I need you to get out of the car.
You got a key to this lock?
Must be one of these.
(KEYS JANGLING)
That's weird.
Hashtag, time's up.
(LOCK CLANKS)
(SINGING)
Praise Him, praise Him
Ever in joyful song
CHOIR LEADER: Praise Him, indeed. Amen.
CHOIR MEMBERS: Amen.
CHOIR LEADER: Okay!
Fellowship with your neighbors.
See you all next time.
Hey, give me five!
He's alive!
Give me ten!
He rose again!
(CHUCKLES)
You'll like it here.
The people are cool, the choir's strong.
But most importantly, how are the donuts?
Oh. (CHUCKLES)
Always fresh, always sprinkled.
Oh. Sold.
Well, it was really nice
to meet you, Leslie. And...
You know, you have a really good voice.
Oh...
(LAUGHS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
Uh, would you ever wanna
grab a coffee or something, ever?
I can't.
Oh, yeah. No, totally, I get it.
It's not you...
No, no, no, that's fine.
You don't have to...
I get it. Totally.
No, I... It's not...
Sorry for bothering you.
Have a great night.
My husband's dead.
He passed away six months ago.
Do you think you could come back closer,
so I don't have to shout about it?
Oh. Yeah, sorry. Uh...
Um...
(STAMMERS) So it's not that
I don't wanna go. I do.
I Know I should get
back out there, but I'm...
You know, it'd just be downhill
from here, so... (CHUCKLES)
How did he pass?
Heart attack.
He was, um, playing water guns
with the kids.
My son thinks that he killed him
because he shot him in the chest
with a Super Soaker
right before he actually died.
Oh.
Told you it was downhill from here.
(CHUCKLES)
No, no, that...
That was a good story.
(LAUGHS)
Well, if that's what you're into, there's
more where that came from.
Hey, takes a lot to scare me off, okay?
Okay, 2001.
Summer of the Shark.
And guess who gets her period.
Ew.
No, that's not...
That's not a true...
That was a joke.
That was a bad joke. Sorry.
Oh. No, that was funny.
No, you...
You're funny. (CHUCKLES)
Well, if that's what you're into,
there's more where that came from.
(LAUGHS)
I just got pulled over!
RIO: So?
So I barely talked myself
out of being arrested.
For driving an empty truck?
Why didn't you do it yourself?
Why did you need us
to bring you an empty truck?
I had a kid.
The Feds turned him.
So, this is a test?
I needed to know if he talked.
I guess he didn't.
And now we're back in business.
You're catching on.
Give me the keys.
I have a family.
I have children.
Yeah, you love telling me that, huh?
If you think you can use me
like a worm on a hook
so that you don't get caught...
I don't got time to hold your hand through
this. Give me the keys.
That family you're always talking about?
Go home to 'em.
What me and you had is done. Over.
You can't just fire us.
You think I need you?
Ain't nothing but
a damn charity case to me.
We need the money.
I need more of your bitch-ass drama
like I need a hole in my head.
Go home.
What do you mean, you had a kid?
What happened to him?
What's that you're always saying
about your rotten eggs
and how you have to handle 'em?
Go home.
I don't see how you're
gonna let me do that.
Is it gonna be you?
Or do I come home one day and your boys
are in my kitchen?
Elizabeth...
Go home.
ANNIE: Chimney fell on
an old lady in Wixom.
Fatal accident on Southfield Freeway. Hmm.
Drowning. What kind
of nutjob goes swimming
this time of year?
RUBY: You're kind of asking for it.
ANNIE: Ugh.
I don't see anything
about a dead gang kid.
You're sure he's coming for us?
We know too much now.
He'd be an idiot not to.
I mean, homie has made this
threat before.
I'm telling you, it's different.
We're no good to him now.
He said the actual words?
He just looked at me funny.
Sadie just did a project on great whites.
They have these inky black eyes
that turn white
right before they kill you.
Was it funny like that, or...
RUBY: Okay, glass half full.
He's just upset, and when he calms down,
he realizes we're good earners.
What's half empty?
Getting put in a woodchipper.
I feel like he's more creative than that.
He'll probably drop us
into molten steel or feed us to pigs.
Everything's a joke to you?
I just deal with it in my own way, okay?
What do we do?
Why are you looking at me?
Because, you know,
last time this happened,
you were all like,
"Yeah, just try to hurt us. We eat
at P.F. Chang's, bitch."
Can't you...
You feel really strongly about this.
(LAUGHING)
I've Got the Joy just...
It just sounds better
on an electric guitar.
No offense to Leonore's organ playing.
(CHUCKLES)
Jeff used to play it on guitar.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
He was also really into hard rock.
Like, he knew every Creed song
by heart, you know?
I was doing so good.
You made it the whole night.
Yeah, till now.
Well, you're home, so it doesn't count.
(CHUCKLES)
I had fun tonight.
You're... You're easy to have fun with.
(CHUCKLES)
Do you know why that is, I think?
(SINGING)
I've got the joy, joy, joy, joy
Down in my heart
Where?
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
With a little electric riff,
that would sound so good.
It would be so good.
(CHUCKLES)
Uh...
Should I put on some tea?
I, um...
Oh, I don't mean to...
I mean, if you have an early morning or...
Like, no pressure if you...
I guess I could.
Okay.
I can... If you're...
Oh, yeah.
Thanks. (CHUCKLES)
(WATER RUNNING)
(BEEPS)
Honey?
Yes, dear.
(BOTH LAUGH)
Hey, it's Mom. Um...
Your window's dark,
so I figure you're asleep. Um...
I just wanted to tell you
that I love you so much.
You are so awesome.
And you're really funny, uh,
and you're really kind.
And you're also really cool,
which is rare for a kid.
And it's great for me,
'cause it really ups my cool factor...
(VOICE MAIL BEEPS)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
If you are satisfied
with your message, press one.
If you would like to rerecord...
(VOICE MAIL BEEPS)
Hey, it's me. Um...
It's late, So you're...
You're probably sleeping, but, um...
I just wanted you to know
that I think you are the best.
You are so smart,
and you're really funny,
and you're really...
Polite, oddly,
which I don't know
where you get that from,
because neither me or your dad is...
(VOICE MAIL BEEPS)
AUTOMATED VOICE:
If you are satisfied
with your message, press one.
If you would like...
(VOICE MAIL BEEPS)
Hey, baby, it's Mom. Um...
I think you're asleep, but I just...
In case I get cut off,
I wanted to say that...
AUTOMATED VOICE:
If you are satisfied...
Ugh. Dude, come on!
...Press one.
(VOICE MAIL BEEPS)
Uh...
AUTOMATED VOICE:
If you are satisfied
with your message, press...
(VOICE MAIL BEEPS)
Hey, um, it's me.
Uh, I love you. Okay, bye.
What are you doing?
What? I just miss my kid.
You just called her 11 times.
Well, I miss her a lot, so sue me.
(SIGHS)
What is going on with you?
If you'll just tell me...
Yeah. Don't you think
you have your hands full?
What with the IVF and everything else...
To help you...
Would you stop talking?
What is up?
All right. You wanna know what's up?
Yeah, I do.
(SIGHS)
Well, I wanna know
what's up with those PJs.
I mean, really, you look like you're in
a Dickens novel.
Who's coming for you tonight?
Is it the Ghost of Christmas Present or
the Ghost of Christmas Past?
Actually, I wanna know
what's up with this car.
Mm.
'Cause I don't think a homeless person
would even sleep in here.
Hmm. Well, joke's on you.
'Cause a lot of homeless
people have slept in here.
Oh, is that right?
I mean, maybe not a lot,
but, you know, a fair amount.
Sort of like a selective
few homeless people?
Yeah, I kind of have,
like, a lottery system going.
Oh.
Mm-hmm.
(BOTH LAUGH)
Why are you trying to help me?
You're the mother of my child.
Is that all I am to you?
Come on.
You're not really gonna
make me Say it, are you?
Do you and Nance have matching sets?
Or is this a bespoke number?
Take care of yourself, Annie.
(SNIFFLES, SIGHS)
What would it take
for you to walk out on me?
Hmm...
Become a Packer fan.
I'm serious.
Soam Il.
You become a cheesehead,
you'll have to find yourself a new man.
Stan.
Hmm?
Put down the book.
(STAN CLEARS THROAT)
I don't always do the right thing.
So what? I mean, who does?
And, uh... I think I Know you pretty well.
But what if you didn't?
You wanna tell me
what we're talking about here?
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(SNIFFLES)
Hello?
(INHALES)
Yeah, this is... Okay.
Okay.
Um...
What?
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
So, um, a girl just...
A girl in Madison
just got hit by a drunk driver,
and her family
is getting ready to
take her off life support.
(SOFTLY) Is she...
She's a perfect match.
(SIGHS)
(CHILDREN CLAMORING)
RUBY: How'd you sleep?
BETH: I didn't.
You guys...
Maybe we should turn ourselves in.
You wanna go to the cops?
I Know. I Know.
Now you wanna go to the cops?
We'll go to jail, Annie.
Well, it's better
than waiting to be murdered
in some gnarly way that I haven't even
thought of yet.
We got the call.
What if it goes to someone else?
I'm a princess...
All those fairy tales
they told us when we were little girls?
The morals were always,
"If you're good,
and if you follow the rules,
"if you don't lie and you don't cheat,
"if you're good, you'll get good things.
"And if you're a dick, you get punished."
Well, what if the people
who made up those stories are the dicks?
Are you following her?
Mm... Mas o menos.
What if the bad people made all that up
so the good people
never get anything good?
And now I'm lost.
What's the takeaway?
It doesn't matter
what we've done, we're the good guys.
He's the criminal here.
He's the one who
should be in jail, not us.
That's what I'm talking about.
Right?
Hell to the yeah. Right.
Then let's put him there.