RUBY: Previously on Good Girls...
Why does a grocery store
even have this kind of money?
Because it's hella shady.
Call your friends over
SO we can have a little talk.
He wants us to pick something up
for him in Canada.
It's just wrapping paper.
We have a business proposition
to clean your fake money.
What are you proposing?
Let us do it.
Right here.
Fake money in, real money out.
(WHISPERS)
What do you want?
You can't just walk in here.
Your door was open.
DEAN: Beth, who's your new friend?
Is he the reason you're
not wearing your ring?
Oh, my God.
I want you out.
What?
Yeah, I want you gone now.
I have cancer.
Agent Turner.
I saw this guy.
Okay? He was with
the three of them before,
and I saw him again yesterday.
I'm sorry.
Whatever they're into, he's involved.
TURNER: Hi. I'm looking for Mrs. Boland.
Can I help you?
I'm hoping you can.
Cute kids.
Oh, thanks.
We like them.
Yeah, most of the time.
How's the neighborhood treating you?
Pretty quiet mostly, or...
Is something going on?
Just some ugliness
bleeding in from the city.
We try to stay on top of it.
Well, that sounds scary.
Yeah. Have you guys seen anything weird?
Like what?
You know, people that don't
quite go with the vibe here.
Actually, I have.
That guy.
(STUTTERS) The guy...
Question. Is it illegal
to throw dog poop into
other people's trash bins?
Because we have this guy
in the neighborhood who...
(CHUCKLES) It's probably
not FBI jurisdiction.
I'm guessing not.
Those are government bins, right? So...
(CHUCKLES)
Let me know if you see anything
out of the ordinary.
Copy that. We will be your eyes and ears.
Yes. And thank you, Agent Turner.
Jimmy.
DEAN: Here, I'll show you out.
So, yeah, this guy,
he walks his dog, and...
(CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
BETH: We shouldn't do it.
What do you mean we shouldn't do it?
I mean, we shouldn't clean
a bunch of counterfeit money
when the FBI is on our trail.
It was your idea.
Will you all keep it down, please?
Look, they're not on our trail.
He was in my kitchen.
Stan is in my bedroom.
If the guy knew anything,
he would have just said it.
He gave his card to me, and not to Dean.
Well, maybe he didn't know
if Dean could read.
Look, I got fancy lawyer bills
coming out the wazoo, dawg.
I talked to her for 15 minutes,
it cost me $800.
You know how much a criminal lawyer costs?
I need this payday.
We didn't get the last one.
We all need it. But let's
not be stupid about it.
What's stupid is if we screw this up
because gang friend
is not gonna give us another shot.
Gang friend?
Probably some teenagers,
like, stolen Xbox or something.
I promise you it was nothing.
It wasn't nothing.
It was the FBI.
Okay. So, it was two Xboxes.
STAN: Freeze, ladies.
(ALL GASP)
(EXCLAIMS)
Whoa.
Hey, look at you.
Uh-huh.
What's up, y'all?
ANNIE: Hey. (LAUGHS)
First day as an Officer in training.
Mm-hmm. Now, tell me, would you pull over
if you saw this coming at you
in the rear-view?
Oh, I'd pay the ticket on the spot.
I! mean, I'd run, but you'd catch me
in five seconds.
Hear that?
Getting real now, huh?
Oh, yeah.
Realer by the minute.
What about sunblock?
Nancy has the spray kind.
I guess if you can afford to go to Hawaii,
you can afford the spray kind.
Don't eat just mac and cheese, okay?
I Know how to make at least two to five
other dishes.
And set your alarm for work.
I am a fully functioning adult human.
You're not good alone.
(CHUCKLES) I can take care of myself.
I mean, sometimes.
Okay. I love you.
I'm going to miss you.
Have the best time.
I promise I will not call
unless it's an emergency.
Okay.
Okay?
Okay. Hey.
Love you.
BOTH: Never put no one above you.
Miss you. Miss you. Bye.
Miss you. Okay.
Well? Amscray.
I'm, like, dying for some alone time.
I love you so much, Mom.
I love you, baby.
(SMOOCHES)
Bye.
(IN CUTESY VOICE)
Bye. Bye.
(SIGHS)
(EXHALES)
Okay. What if I just
mark you down for, like,
clean up or something?
I'd really love to.
I just don't have any time right now.
Oh, my God, what happened to your car?
Oh. Got Kenny a BB gun.
When did we start this service?
Anyway. Think about it, B.
I'll call you.
Okay.
What do you want?
Careful with those snacks.
I don't wanna spend my weekend
cleaning up this car.
Yeah. I'm not sure I see the problem.
ANNIE: You and me both, brother.
Annie.
(SIGHS) I just would
like to take this moment
to personally thank you
for this opportunity.
I promise you, we're going iron this out.
We're going to make you proud.
Okay. Hold on, Annie.
Y'all asked for a piece of this.
Yes, we did, sir.
That's true.
That was before the FBI dropped by.
Okay, let's just calm down.
Sorry. She just kind of does this.
It's all part of the process.
What is that supposed to mean?
Hmm. I don't know.
You begged our parents for a piano,
and they dropped three grand
on a baby upright.
And guess who decided
she'd rather play violin.
I'm staying out of it.
It sounds like y'all
got a lot to work out. So...
(STAMMERS)
Wait a second.
Don't you want to take your product?
This ain't the Girl Scouts.
You can't give the cookies back.
Aren't you worried about the FBI?
Nah.
See?
There's a distribution system.
You've been distributed to.
What does that mean?
It means you're on the hook now.
It's, like, 100 grand.
Oh, you don't got to wash it.
Then, what do we do with it?
Burn it. Eat it.
Wipe your ass with it.
And then, write me a check.
Because, either way,
I'm coming to collect.
ANNIE: Hey.
Guess who ended up
taking the piano lessons.
Six years.
It's gonna be fine.
(CLEARS THROAT)
What?
Okay, the pins represent the stores
with the biggest ticket items.
We've got blue for electronics,
yellow for appliances.
Is this the same map
you used for Black Friday?
Yes. But I expanded it.
Because it is way too risky
to shop locally right now.
Damn. Really upped
your crafting game, Martha.
Hey! Hey!
There is a system.
I am trying to keep us organized
so that we don't get caught.
Okay.
What if they test the bills?
I once saw a guy at 7-Eleven
get straight-up tased.
Well, at least, he wasn't arrested.
And then, he got arrested.
ANNIE: I used the security pen
from work on one of the 20s.
We're not getting tazed or arrested.
This cash is
(SMOOCHES) primo.
The red bands are the fake money.
So, when you make a return,
you put on a green band
and you keep it separate.
Red goes out, green comes in.
Just like Christmas.
This is who we are now, huh?
I mean, desperate times.
We can do this.
We're just normal women, shopping.
With money to burn, baby.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
CASHIER: Next.
Find everything okay?
Yeah.
(BARCODE READER BEEPING)
Couldn't decide.
I see that.
$4,822.38.
(DEVICE WHIRS)
What's that?
We have to check our large bills.
You guys don't use the pen thingy?
No, not anymore.
Those never really worked.
You know what?
I'm actually in a hurry.
I'm just gonna come back.
This will just take a second.
(DEVICE WHIRS)
So, we just finished
this major remodel, right?
Tear the kitchen right down to the studs.
So, I can buy all-new appliances.
Fun, right?
Only not fun, because the appliances
don't match the counters.
And now, I've got to buy
all-new colors to try out.
First up was eggshell.
What kind of color is eggshell?
I'll tell you what kind.
It's white, just plain white.
(CLEARS THROAT)
And then, I tried seashell,
and I don't know if y'all
ever been to the sea and seen a shell.
You might need a vacation.
But I assure you, that ain't it.
(SIGHS) And don't even
get me started on cornsilk.
That is nonsense.
I need a manager to the front, please.
Manager to the front.
Is there a problem?
(DEVICE WHIRS)
(BEEPS)
CASHIER: Great.
Everything looks good.
You want your receipt in the bag?
Uh, no.
I'll hold on to it.
There you go.
You want all this back on a card?
Cash is fine.
Did you get the verifier?
This shizz is good.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Do you play games?
Uh, you know, I'm actually in the market
for something more like
a flatscreen-type deal.
Something kind of stupidly pricy.
Price doesn't always equal quality.
You're talking to
an irresponsible millennial here.
Uh, well, in that case,
our, uh, 4K ultra high-defs
are rated the best.
But they run upwards of four grand. So...
(WHISTLES)
Yeah.
Steep.
Ouch.
Well, I guess I should only get four then.
Four?
TVs?
What do you think, five?
Uh, I don't know.
I mean, are you messing with me?
(LAUGHS) No.
Why would I be messing with you?
Nobody who looks like you would ever be
that good for my commission.
What do I look like?
Uh, you know, hot.
Okay, man.
You know, you got
this whole thing all wrong.
Okay. You're not hot?
No, no, I'm hot. Obviously.
I'm just serious about the TVs.
I'm not messing with you.
Ringing up the hottie.
(LAUGHS)
(GASPS) Okay, creeper.
You just getting home now?
You didn't have to wait up for me.
I'm surprised you could
see Straight with all these
doubles you've been pulling.
I mean, it's hard to say no
to the extra shifts.
Yeah.
How was rehearsal?
Ah. Sara seemed a little tired.
She okay?
She said she was.
Oh. (CHUCKLES)
By the way,
our little girl, she's got my moves.
No, dude, she was like...
Hey, hey, hey.
Okay. If those are her moves,
we need to take her off that dance team.
Oh. What?
Come on, now.
You remember.
What it was...
(SIGHS)
I need to get off my feet.
Oh, we could do that, too.
(SIGHS)
Hey. Hey...
Where's your uniform?
Oh. Um...
I left it at work.
It's covered in ketchup and frustration.
That's nasty.
(LAUGHS)
You don't even know.
I don't even care.
Hey, what...
(LAUGHS)
Oh. You wanna...
Come on. All right.
Hey. Hey.
Oh, we're doing... Oh.
Oh...
Oh, yes.
19,685 bucks.
(HUMMING)
I'mma need a receipt.
Okay. Um...
I forgot to mention
we offer in-home installation.
Oh. That's okay.
I'm all set.
Are you sure?
It's free.
Yeah, no. Uh, they're gifts.
So, I'm all set.
If you change your mind...
Mm-hmm.
"In-home hookup"?
I've been waiting
to use that line for years.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, I'm honored to be the chosen one.
Seriously. It's the only reason
I took the job.
They don't give us overtime here.
Well, I guess now you can quit.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(KEYS CLATTER)
Hey, what are you doing?
Just some reorganizing.
Here, let me help.
It's okay. I have a system.
Okay.
I... I already fed the dog.
Okay. Well, what can I do to help?
What do you mean?
Well, I'm back home.
So, you know, I want to be useful.
You should be resting.
I'm okay.
Well, what did the doctor say?
We'll know more after the appointment.
There's gonna be chemotherapy
or radiation or whatever.
Um...
You know, you could
fill my car up with gas.
Yeah? Yay!
It would be nice.
Sorry, that was...
Uh, that was...
It's okay.
Just sort of forgot.
My keys are right by the door.
Thanks.
(SIGHS)
Ugh.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
Don't judge me, Rex.
(BED CREAKS)
Hey.
What are you doing?
I'm just gonna get a glass of water.
Here, I'll get it for you.
No. Stay here. Stay.
Be right back.
Okay. Never mind.
(DOOR OPENS, CREAKS)
Hello?
Hey!
What a a-hole.
Wow, real classy move, jackass!
God!
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. No. No. No.
Oh, God.
(GASPS)
BETH: He stole your receipt?
I mean, he must have.
Because I've looked
everywhere, and it's gone.
Everywhere? Have you checked your pocket?
What do you think I am, an idiot?
Don't answer that.
Okay. Well, how much was it for?
$20,000
worth of flatscreens.
Oh, my God.
Who steals a receipt anyway?
He wrote his number on it.
So, I guess he just didn't
want me to call him again.
Isn't it in your phone?
Well, yeah.
Who is this guy?
(SIGHS)
It's a Brad or a Brian.
I'm picturing the name tag,
and I feel like there was a B in there.
Look, Sadie is gone, okay?
I was in a dark place.
Well, call his shady ass and get it back.
I'm trying, homie.
He is ghosting me hard.
Wow. He sounds like a winner.
Yeah, I know, Beth.
I guess he got what he came for.
Okay.
We will fix this.
How? You can't do returns
for cash without a receipt.
Okay. Well, I personally
would love a solution
that doesn't involve
crawling back to Brad-Brian.
Like?
Well, like, we could give gang friend
the cash that we do have
and the flatscreens.
Yeah, because that went so well
with the Hummels.
Nope. I value my life.
I am not going back
to those lunatics short again.
I very much agree.
And can we please
stop calling him gang friend?
Okay. What's his name, then?
Ron.
Yo, you see Ron cap that B?
Okay. It's not Ron.
(CHUCKLES) Rio.
Okay.
His name is Rio.
Oh, is his name Rio?
(STAMMERS) I'm sorry, but...
It looks like we're gonna
have to go find your...
The guy.
(GROANS)
Could you be worse with names?
All right.
(STAMMERS) Hi.
Um, I am looking for a Brian,
or a Brad or a Brendan in electronics.
Brian. He's not here today.
Okay. Um, I need you
to give me his address.
I'm sorry.
We can't give that out.
I just really need it.
Like it's extremely important to me.
Uh, you could leave him a note.
I think he works again next week.
Okay. Well, by next week,
our headless bodies will be
badly decomposed.
But thanks anyway.
Now what?
Hold this.
I'm going to take you
off the floor to inventory.
Corporate wants it today.
I was right in the middle...
I don't have the time, Rita.
And I'm going to need
a current employee list.
Names, numbers, and addresses.
Mark asked for it an hour ago.
And just between us,
there are going to be some layoffs.
Who's Mark?
Mark? Ted's boss.
Hired Bill? Overhauled
the entire division with Ed?
Ed Fielding?
What other Ed would I be talking about?
How long have you worked here?
Fifteen years.
Wow, Rita.
Um, I am so sorry.
Just give me that list.
Big pimping!
It's like a Superpower.
Yo!
It's the clipboard.
Damn!
(ANNIE SIGHS)
(MUFFLED CHATTER)
Brian.
Hey, I was gonna call you back.
(SCOFFS) Yeah.
I'm so sure.
I just got really busy.
Mm. Is that why you bailed
in the middle of the night?
Had to get cracking
on that to-do list, huh?
Uh, who are they?
Don't you worry about it.
Let's talk later.
No! I need that receipt.
What?
The receipt that you wrote
"in-home hookup" on.
Ew, gross.
Seriously.
I don't have it.
Well, go get it.
I threw it away and took out the trash,
okay? It's gone.
Why? Why would you do that?
Daddy.
WOMAN: Who is it, babe?
ANNIE: Oh.
That's why.
I'm sorry.
Who are you?
Actually, uh...
No, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Wrong apartment.
But... Hang on.
Let's go.
Who was that?
Nobody.
(DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE)
(PLASTIC RUSTLING)
(ANNIE EXCLAIMS)
Is that it?
I don't know. Can't tell.
I need more light.
Here. Can you shine that?
Hmm. I need glasses.
I can't see anything.
Dear God, please end this suffering.
Just give...
Just give it to me!
All right. Chill.
Huh?
No, I think it's Starbucks.
No!
Are you sure?
Yeah, I can make out
the word "macchiato."
I'm sure there's coffee
grounds all over us.
(WHISPERS) That's not coffee grounds.
(ANNIE LAUGHS)
This isn't funny.
Come on, it's a little funny.
We're in a dumpster because of you.
(SCOFFS) Wait.
How is this on me?
How is this not on you?
(GASPS, WHISPERS) There's
a Band-Aid on my arm.
And it's not mine.
He stole my receipt.
I got played here.
No. You screwed a married guy.
How was I supposed to know
that he was married?
Maybe take one more minute
of conversation before
you drop your pants.
Are you slut-shaming me?
I'm just plain shaming you.
You are on the wrong side
of history. Trust me.
Because, once again,
you made the smart, responsible decision.
You know, Beth, I'm really sorry,
but it's not my problem
that you haven't had sex
since Emma was born,
and it's all dried-up-ass twigs in there.
(WHISPERS) Damn.
You're a child.
Right. Yeah, I'm a child,
and you're just...
You're all about that responsibility
lifestyle, right?
That's why you just let
that lying douchebag off the hook.
What are you talking about?
You could have busted his cheating ass.
But no, you didn't.
You let him get away with it.
I didn't let him get away with anything.
That's exactly what you did.
I just Saw you.
You think she doesn't know?
The state of that woman's marriage
was written all over her face.
We didn't have to tell her.
She already knows.
(GAGGING)
Dirty diaper.
They do have a baby.
(GASPS, WHISPERS) It's adult.
Found it.
Oh, God.
Just, um, underneath his kid's artwork.
Okay. Let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, let's go.
Take off your shoes, Mommy.
You'll bring in dirt.
Shh.
Morning, Mrs. Boland.
Hi.
I didn't mean to scare you.
No. I'm fine.
I just haven't had my morning coffee.
KENNY: Mom.
Yeah. Hold on. Just one sec.
Is your husband home?
No, he's already at work.
He's an early bird.
Why? Is there a big break
in the dog poop case?
(CHUCKLES) Yeah, right.
Because I'm sure he'd wear a wire
if you needed him to.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
Actually, it's you that I wanted to see.
Oh, why's that?
Mom, come on!
Yeah. Hold on. Hold on.
You know this guy?
Uh... No.
This is your house, right?
Yes.
But you've never seen this guy?
Because, see, from this angle here,
it seems like maybe he's coming right out
your front door.
No, no.
Hmm. Okay.
Well, I'll swing by later
and show it to your husband, too.
When's the big guy home from work?
Please don't do that.
Why not?
I can't talk about it right now.
Mom, we're gonna be late.
Not in front of my kids.
Then I think you should
come by my Office.
Okay. Uh, tomorrow's okay?
Today's better.
Okay.
Go Red Wings!
Yeah.
What are you looking at?
Hey! Wash your hands!
(DOOR THUDS)
Animal.
Hey, did it start yet?
My baby's performing...
What's going on?
Excuse me.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Stan?
Your daughter had a seizure.
RUBY: (SIGHS)
She was so much better.
I don't understand.
Her kidney's basically
non-functioning at this point.
(BOTH SIGH)
How... How does this even happen?
We're not Sure.
But let's start dialysis
and get her stabilized.
And then what?
We'll run some tests.
Try to get you all more answers.
Now, you said Sara was taking Eculizumab.
She was doing great on it.
You watch her take it?
Every night.
You see her swallow?
Ruby.
(PILLS RATTLE)
(SIGHS)
BETH: So, what do I say?
RIO: To who?
BETH: The FBI.
What do I tell them?
They ain't got nothing.
They've got a picture of you.
That ain't special.
I'm on Facebook, too.
Your cut.
(STAMMERS) Wait. Wait.
(SIGHS)
Listen. In my line of work,
if you don't have the FBI on your back,
you ain't making noise.
I don't want to make noise.
They're gonna want to know
what someone like me is
doing with someone like you.
What are you doing with someone like me?
Well, obviously, I can't tell them that.
Right, right.
All right, so tell them I was hitting it.
What?
Oh, I'm sorry, sweetheart.
Tell them we're making love.
I... (SCOFFS)
How do I even say that?
(CHUCKLES)
You'll think of something.
Make me sound good, though, yeah?
(DOOR CLOSES)
I was feeling better.
So, I was saving it
until I needed it again.
That's not how medicine works, baby.
Yeah. I thought you were supposed
to be honor roll here.
Now we're gonna have to take
that bumper sticker off.
(CHUCKLES)
I wanted to try and help you guys out.
Help us out with what?
Like money and stuff.
I Know we can't afford it.
Well, there's something you don't know.
Should we tell her?
I don't know.
You think she can handle it?
The truth is
we are stinking rich.
I'm talking stacks
on stacks on stacks, loaded.
We are rolling in it.
And the truth, my dear, is that you are,
wait for it,
royalty.
(SINGSONG) Mm-hmm.
We didn't want you to grow up spoiled.
That's why we kept it on the DL.
STAN: Mm-hmm.
This is like a bad movie.
It's why we bought
the tiniest, cheapest house
we could find.
(STAMMERS) Okay.
Hold...
It's not that bad.
Oh, and that explains the car.
Exactly.
What's wrong with my car?
And the food.
That makes sense.
Hey, watch yourself.
Baby, don't worry about us.
Just go to school
and play and be a kid.
That's it.
And swallow your damn pills
from now on. Okay?
Okay, Mommy.
All this stuff you think you're keeping
from them, you're not.
Don't go there.
(SIGHS)
I mean, I'm not gonna
say that I'm a bad mother.
She's going there.
But...
I could have paid more attention.
You do the best you can.
(SNIFFLING)
Those better be donuts.
Do not come at me with some wack-ass
cheese Danish.
Those aren't donuts.
It's everything.
It's our whole cut.
We knew you'd need it
for the hospital bill.
We don't want you
to even think about it, okay?
And messed up my damn face.
(SIGHS) It was already pretty messed up.
(SIGHS) Hate you guys.
We know.
So, have you already discussed the
comment about the twigs in the...
Ah, yes. Yes, we...
We had a discussion about it.
Damn, I missed it?
Mm-hmm.
I was the bigger man.
I apologized.
Yeah, sort of.
Well, I said it wasn't my finest moment.
You also said it could have
been way worse.
Yeah, because I wanted to Say raisin cave.
But I restrained myself.
What does that even mean?
Uh, I think I know.
And it is not an apology.
What you want from me, blood? Please.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Raisin cave.
I mean...
(SQUEALS) Oh, my God!
Hi.
Can I help you?
Yeah, I'd like to fill out one of those
customer complaint cards.
It's about my recent in-home hookup.
Oh, a comment card.
Well, all my comments are complaints.
But call it what you want to.
Absolutely no problem.
Overall, how happy
were you with your service?
Un. Very unhappy.
One through ten?
Mm, like a negative six.
Absolutely no problem.
And was your service
performed in a timely manner?
By timely, you mean,
like a little woodpecker, then, yeah.
Absolutely no problem. Um...
Was the job completed
to your satisfaction?
Uh, no. I was definitely not satisfied.
He didn't finish?
Oh, he finished.
(SIGHS) I am so sorry
about your experience.
We take our customer feedback
very seriously.
Now, how seriously is that?
Do you dock people's pay?
I...
Do you fire them?
Because I'd hate to see that happen.
If the situation were
extreme enough, certainly.
You didn't happen to catch
your technician's name?
You know, he just wasn't that memorable.
Kind of had, like, a...
Like a mini dad-bod.
Mm.
And he smelled like...
It's hard to describe.
Have you ever been to a zoo in the rain?
Oh.
There he is.
Wait. You're Nicole?
Mm-hmm.
He actually talked
to a lot of smack about you, too.
I'm just saying.
(DOOR OPENS, CLOSES)
Hey.
Wow. You cooked?
Yeah. I watched that Rachel Ray Show.
Something wrong with that woman.
She's, like, so happy.
I Know. It's really weird.
(CHUCKLES) Oh, yeah.
Hey, do you want me to heat up your plate?
Sara's in the hospital again.
I'm gonna shower,
and then head back there.
All right. Hey, Beth.
I'm really, really trying here.
I Know.
Think I can fix it?
I think it's gonna take more than
filling up the car and Rachel Ray.
Right.
If it never happened...
You know, Amber, the money.
Would you still be with me?
I don't even know how to answer that.
I think you just did.
Mrs. Boland, can I
get you anything? Coffee?
Oh. (CHUCKLES) You
drink coffee at this hour?
I don't sleep much anyway. You?
I had an affair.
You had an affair?
I'm not proud of it, and it's over now.
But that's why he was
at the house, and that's
why I couldn't say anything
in front of my husband and my children.
Oh.
Well...
Okay, then.
Okay.
Just out of curiosity,
where'd you meet him?
I'm just wondering where
a nice lady like you meets
an inner city gangbanger.
PTA? Or is it like a speed dating thing?
What's that website?
It's Just Lunch?
At a bar.
What was he wearing?
Jeans.
What about you?
Dress.
Where'd you meet him?
At a restaurant.
You just said bar.
A bar restaurant.
They had food.
What was the name?
Lucky's.
I bet they'd remember
a pair like you. Who drove?
You or him? Who drove?
Um, we both did.
What kind of car does he drive?
Black BMW.
It'd be registered.
I'll check it.
It might be a Cadillac.
Maybe.
Have a good nigNt, Mrs. Boland.
It was a one-night stand.
I had just found out that my husband
was cheating on me with a child.
More or less.
And I was lonely and angry.
And
normally, sleeping with
a complete stranger would repulse me.
But it didn't that day.
I dropped the kids off
at school and I went straight to the bar.
Where was your husband?
Screwing his secretary
and losing all our money.
Fair enough.
We drank a little,
and I invited him back to my house.
We drank a little more.
And then, I realized
what I was doing was insane.
And I told him to go.
And he kissed me.
I kissed him back.
He pulled my panties down
and we screwed right on the kitchen table,
on the breakfast dishes.
The kids had pancakes.
Blueberry, if you were wondering.
It only happened once.
And I've never seen that man again.
And I don't plan to.
Thank you for coming in.
Mrs. Boland.
Just be careful
who you bring into your home.
I'm tougher than I look.